Charm magic?
I'm afraid there's nothing
I can do about that.
It's a curse I've been afflicted
with since birth.
You should be more angry at yourselves
for being born women.
I hope you don't expect
that handsome face to dull my sword,
spear wielder.
If it did, I'd be bored to tears.
The Saber Class's anti-magic
is impressive.
Good.
There's no honor in killing a woman
when my face has robbed her of the will to fight.
because of my face.
I'm happy to see you have backbone.
Oh?
So you seek a fair fight?
Then I shall consider
myself fortunate, as well,
to be able to face such
a proud Heroic Spirit.
Excellent.
En garde.
They've begun.
Someone's erected a barrier...
Probably that Servant's Master.
One could see the entire battlefield easily from up there.
True, that would be the
best place to observe from.
It would be obvious to anyone,
upon seeing that platform.
Maiya, you approach from
the east-side wharf.
I'll come from the west.
We'll set up points from which
we can monitor
Saber's battle, as well as the derrick crane.
Understood.
Now, my little King of Knights,
let's see what you're capable of.
Saber's keeping a close watch
on both spears at the same time.
She doesn't know which one Lancer
will use for his strongest attack.
The long spear in his right hand,
or the short spear in his left...
Which one is his Noble Phantasm?
If I can figure that out,
I can come up with a suitable battle plan.
Or if we only knew his identity...
Obviously, he has mastery of the spear.
But I need more to go on...
Come on, Saber!
Show me what you can really do!
He's good.
That sword is dangerous.
Without knowing its length, it's impossible
to strike at the right distance!
And for her to deflect my spears...
This woman's sword skills are first-rate.
Maiya, northeast of Saber...
Lancer's Master is on the warehouse roof.
Do you see him?
No, he's in my blind spot.
Understood.  I'll take care of him.
Assassin?
We have activity by the warehouses
at the mouth of Mion River.
The first battle in the war has commenced.
You are mistaken.
Officially, it is the second battle,
Kirei.
It appears that the combatants are Saber and Lancer.
Can Assassin evaluate them
from his position?
But of course.
Saber is an especially gifted warrior.
Almost all of her stats are solidly rank A.
I see.
No wonder they call it the strongest class.
Saber is likely to be more
problematic than Lancer.
Can you see their Masters?
One other person is standing in the open,
behind the Servants.
She's out in the open, right behind Saber.
A woman with silver hair.
Then Lancer's Master has the sense
to stay out of sight.
Meaning he is no amateur.
He knows the proper strategy for
fighting in a Holy Grail War.
Wait, did you say a woman with silver hair?
Yes, she's a white woman.
Silver hair, red eyes.
She almost doesn't look human.
An Einzbern homunculus?
They've created another artificial Master.
I thought the only pawn that
Jubstacheit von Einzbern
had in play was Emiya Kiritsugu.
I cannot believe this escaped my notice.
Then, is that woman is the Einzbern Master?
Either way, she's key to shaping the
course of this Holy Grail War.
Don't take your eyes off her, Kirei.
Understood.
I'll keep someone on her at all times.
I see him, too, but...
Assassin should be dead,
so how can he be here?
There's more to this than
meets the eye.
Better to keep observing for now.
Watch Assassin for me.
I'll take Lancer.
I'll attack Assassin to draw his attention, which will give you the opportunity
to attack Lancer's Master.
Forget it, Maiya.
Assassin is the main problem now.
We aren't prepared to fight Servants.
As you say.
I suppose there's no honor at stake,
when we have not even said our names.
But know that you have my respect.
I've not even seen you break
a sweat since we began.
Woman or not, that's impressive.
You're too modest, Lancer.
Regardless of whether I know your name,
to receive such a compliment from a master
of the spear such as yourself...
The honor is all mine.
I accept it, with gratitude.
Enough playing around, Lancer.
Lancer's Master?
No more dragging things out.
Saber is a fearsome opponent.
Finish her quickly.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
As you wish, Master.
The long spear is his Noble Phantasm?
Well, you heard him.
From this moment on, I'll be fighting to kill.
Saber, you've been using wind magic
to conceal your sword, correct?
I see now.
You must have a reason
to keep your sword hidden.
The sight of it would reveal your identity.
Sorry to disappoint you, Lancer.
But this fight will be over before
you ever have the chance...
to see my blade.
I wonder.
I believe I can lift the veil from
this invisible sword, Saber.
There it is.
Your precious sword.
He dispersed the Invisible Air?
What happened?
That red spear is shaving away
the Invisible Air!
I have the full measure of your blade.
It no longer matters if I can see it or not!
But considering the strength of his spear...
There is a way to win.
If I can just endure...
a single misplaced attack.
Saber!
Thank you, Irisviel.
I'm all right.  Your spell is working!
I should have known you'd never
let me win so easily.
How?
My armor should have been
more than enough to defend
against that strike.
Why did the spear pierce me?
My armor appears untouched?
How can this be?
Lancer's spear could only have
passed through my magical armor.
I understand.
I've discovered your spear's ability, Lancer.
Oh?
That red spear severs magic, doesn't it?
So your armor is, in fact,
a magical barrier.
I hope you weren't relying on it
to see you through this battle, Saber.
Before my spear, you may as well
be completely naked.
Don't be so certain you have
the upper hand,
simply because you found a way
to bypass my armor.
If I cannot defend against your spear,
I'll simply cut you down
before you can strike.
En garde, Lancer.
That's quite a risk you're taking.
Do or die, is it?
Still, you've turned your armor's loss
into an advantage, by casting it aside.
What bold and graceful determination.
I admire it.
But on this particular stage,
that is a gamble you will not win, Saber.
I wonder.
I'd rather you waited until after our next
exchange before admonishing me.
You lose.
The long spear wasn't his
only Noble Phantasm!
A trap!
No, no...  This is no good.
W-What?
Lancer's using his finishing move.
He's trying to end the fight!
But that's a good thing―
Fool, do you realize
what you're saying?
I wished to wait here until more
Servants arrived,
but at this rate, Saber will fall
before that happens.
And then, it will be too late.
W-What do you mean, too late?
I thought the plan was to wait till it's over
and pick off the winner?
I had anticipated that more Servants
would rise to answer Lancer's challenge.
It is more logical
to defeat our enemies in
one fell swoop,
rather than hunting them
down individually, is it not?
In one fell swoop?
Yes!
How often do you get a chance
to cross swords
with heroes from across centuries?
It would be a shame if all six gathered together
and I missed a chance to fight them all at once.
Watching Saber and Lancer...
The longer their battle goes on,
the more I want to fight both of them.
It would be a shame for one to die.
What good will letting them live do us?
The Holy Grail War's a fight
to the death!
Victory without obliteration,
and subjugation without causing shame.
That is the essence of conquest!
No more watching from afar!
We shall join the battle, boy!
You stupid, crazed nutter!
You're doing this all wrong!
If you don't approve, you can stay
up here and keep watching.
I'll go...
Take me with you!
Good!  Now those are
my Master's words!
Damn, he cut the tendon.
I cannot move my thumb.
Still not done?
You just won't let me win, will you?
Excellent. I respect your courage!
Why must you insist on paying
these pointless compliments?
You should've finished her off, imbecile.
A thousand pardons, my Master.
Irisviel, heal me again.
I have...
I cast the spell. But it isn't...
Your wound should have
been mending!
Your body should be completely healed, Saber!
Fortunately for me, my Gáe Dearg
convinced you your armor was worthless.
Still, you cast it aside too hastily.
Had you kept it, it would have
protected you against Gáe Buidhe.
I see.
That spear inflicts cursed wounds
that cannot be healed.
I should have recognized you earlier.
A red spear that pierces magic,
a yellow spear that bears a curse,
and a teardrop mole, beneath your right eye,
that confuses the hearts of women.
First among the knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid of the Love Spot.
Never did I expect the honor
of such an opponent.
That's the thing about the
Holy Grail War...
Really, though, the pleasure is mine.
As one who has also transcended time
and space, to appear as a Servant,
there is no mistaking that golden sword.
I can hardly believe I've
landed a blow
against the one who is rightfully known
as the King of Knights.
Apparently, I'm not to
be underestimated.
Well, now that we know
each other's name,
I'd say we can finally have an
honorable fight, as fellow warriors.
Or do you feel aggrieved over your injured arm, Saber?
Surely, you jest.
I'm insulted you would even see fit
to mention such a scratch.
Prepare yourself, Saber.
I'll have your life this time.
Only if I don't take yours first, Lancer.
A chariot?
Sheathe your swords!
You are in the presence of royalty!
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors.
Brought forth to fight in this
Holy Grail War as Rider!
Episode 4
Spearhead
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I can't read any of their stats!
Irisviel, get back!
Maiya, his Noble Phantasm...
I command you, with a Command Spell.
Believe in your Master!
I am reborn anew!
I'll destroy every last bit of your corpse!
Next Time:
A Wicked Beast's Roar