I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
Our constantly opposing feelings
have vanished into the light...
I'm no longer sure if the path I'm stumbling
down is truly the right one or not...
I'm sure there are times when
people lose their way, but...
I'm sure the mistakes I made in the past are having an
effect on me now, and will affect me in the future.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Fate!
Nanoha!
Are you all right? Return, Bardiche.
Yes, sir.
Fate!
Fate! Stop! It's too dangerous!
Stop!
Stop, stop...!
Stop... stop.
Stop!
Fate!
The Raising Heart is a device that can
endure large amounts of energy, yet...
To damage it this badly in only one impact...
Could that girl's magical powers
have conflicted with Nanoha's?
No... even if they did, that still wouldn't
explain this amount of damage...
That really was... the Jewel Seed's...
Yuuno-kun... is the Raising Heart all right?
Yeah. The damage is pretty extensive,
but I'm sure it'll be fine.
Its automatic regeneration system is working,
so it should be fully recovered by tomorrow.
I see...
Are you all right, Nanoha?
Yeah... because the Raising Heart protected me.
I'm sorry... Raising Heart.
I'm sorry, Fate! We're almost done...
I'm fine.
Thank you, Arf...
I have to report back to Mother on my current status
tomorrow, so... I'll have to get better soon, right?
Because if I went home in this shape,
I'm sure I'd worry her.
Would she really... worry about you? That woman...
Mother is just a little awkward, that's all...
I can tell how she really feels towards me.
If you're only going to give your report,
I think it'd be okay if I went alone...
Mother... never really listened to
what you had to say, did she?
Even though you're such a kind, good girl...
W-Well...
I think tomorrow will go okay!
In the short amount of time we've been here...
...we've managed to collect four Lost
Logia... or rather, Jewel Seeds.
I'm sure she'll be full of praise for you,
since there's nothing to be angry about, right?
Yeah.
You're right.
Huh? Nanoha!
Ah, Onee-chan.
You sure are up early today. What's up?
Well... my eyes just felt like opening this early, I guess.
I see.
Huh? Where's Onii-chan?
Oh... he went long distance running
with Dad this morning.
Umm...
If it doesn't bother you... do you mind if I watch?
I don't think it'll be all that interesting, but...
It's fine with me! I don't mind.
Okay.
Thanks!
Nanoha?
Yuuno-kun?
What's wrong? You're up pretty early...
Ahh... I just woke up this early, that's all.
Oh, and Yuuno-kun...
I've been doing a lot of thinking...
I'm... really curious about that girl... Fate-chan...
Curious?
She's so strong...
And even though she seems so cold...
...she has such beautiful, kind eyes...
Yet... for some reason, she really
looks... incredibly sad.
I really believe she has a reason for doing all this.
Her reason for collecting the Jewel Seeds...
That's why... I want to talk with her.
So... in order to do that, I'm going to...
This should be fine for a souvenir.
Sweet candies, huh?
Will this really make that woman happy?
I don't know, but it's the thought that
counts for this kind of thing, so...
Dimensional Transfer. Dimensional Coordinates -
876C 4419 3312 D699 3583 A1460 779 F3125.
Open, O Door of Invitation to the Garden of Time.
To the household of the Testarossa family!
What's our status, people?
Are we still on the proper heading this time?
Yes. Presently, we're cruising at a constant
level three nautical velocity.
By my calculations, we're planned to arrive at
our target dimension in roughly 160 vecs.
There hasn't been any noticeable movement since that
small-scale dimensional disturbance they caused...
...but the danger of those two people
colliding again is extraordinarily high.
Is that so?
Excuse me. Here you are, Captain Lindy.
Thank you, Amy.
Indeed.
Even if it was on a small scale, outbreaks of
dimensional disturbances... can be quite problematic.
If it gets too dangerous, we'll just have to hurry directly
to the scene of the disturbance. Right, Chrono?
Everything's fine.
I'm quite aware of our situation, Captain.
That's why I'm here in the first place.
A mere four...?
This is terribly disappointing.
Yes...
I'm sorry...
...Mother.
Do you understand, Fate?
You are my daughter. The sole offspring
of the Great Mage Precia Testarossa.
Nothing is impossible for us.
No matter what it may be.
Yes. We must complete anything
we begin, in all respects.
Yes...
You've made me wait this long...
only for these meager results...
There's no way I could have welcomed
you home with a smile.
I trust that you understand, Fate.
Yes... I understand.
That's why... that's why I want you to remember.
Never disappoint me again like you've done today.
What the hell... what the hell is wrong with her?!
This is just too cruel! That woman...
That woman... that woman claims
to be Fate's mother...
This isn't the first time she's been cruel to Fate, but...
It's just too much this time!
What the hell is wrong with her?!
Are the Lost Logia... the Jewel Seeds worth all that?!
The Lost Logia are essential to
the fruition of my dreams.
Yes, Mother...
They're central to everything... the purity of the
Jewel Seeds goes far beyond any other substance.
You're a kind girl, so you might hesitate
when trying to collect them, but...
If something gets in your way, destroy it.
Through any means necessary.
And the power to do so lies within you.
Now go, bring them to me, my daughter.
My charming Fate.
Yes... I'll be going then, Mother...
I'm going to rest for a bit.
Next time, be sure to delight me with your offerings.
Yes...
Fate!
Fate, I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Why are you apologizing, Arf...?
I'm fine... perfectly fine...
But...! If I had known something
like this would happen...
Even after you got what she wanted, I never thought
she'd do something this cruel to you...!
If I had known, I would've stopped you, no matter what!
It wasn't cruel...
Mother... was thinking of me when she did this.
Yeah, right! This was cruel and unusual punishment!
No... after all, we're mother and daughter...
I'm sure the Jewel Seeds are
really important to Mother...
Mother's always been so full of sadness...
so I want to do something that might cheer her up...
But... even so...
Arf, please. I'm perfectly fine.
I'm sure that...
...once I return with every Jewel Seed,
even Mother will smile again...
She'll go back to being the kind mother
she used to be, so long ago...
And I'm sure she'll even be kind to you, Arf...
So, let's go...
This time, I'll definitely...
...make no mistakes.
Bardiche, how are you feeling?
Recovery complete.
I see. You really gave it your all. You're great.
I sense it... even I can tell that it's around here.
Yes. It'll soon be activated, and it's very close.
Raising Heart... you're all better, aren't you?
Thank goodness.
Condition green.
Will you give me your best again?
All right, my master.
Thank you.
Emergency Barrier! Expand!
Wow! They're pretty arrogant,
already putting up a barrier.
The creature this time is stronger than the others.
And that girl's here as well.
Yuuno-kun! Run!
Flier Fin.
Fly, Raising Heart! We have to go higher!
All right.
Arc Saber.
Let's go, Bardiche.
Shooting Mode.
Let's go, Raising Heart!
Crush it!
Divine...
...Buster.
Pierce it, thunder!
Thunder Smasher.
Sealing Mode, Set up.
Sealing Form, Set up.
Jewel Seed Serial VII!
Seal!
It looks like we can't put any more
stress on the Jewel Seed.
Yeah. If it turns out like the one last night...
I'd feel sorry for my Raising Heart and your Bardiche.
However, I won't yield this match to you.
Device Form.
I just want to talk with you...
Device Mode.
If I win... and you understand that I'm not just
some innocent girl mixed up in all of this...
...will you let me listen to your story?
Stop!
Commencing combat here is too dangerous!
I am a government official from the Time-Space
Administration Bureau, Chrono Hallaoun.
I'll need a detailed explanation about this from you.
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
After hearing some things from
the third mage, Chrono-kun...
...the true identity of the Jewel
Seeds has finally become clear...
...and things have
gotten really serious!
And I've personally learned
something extraordinary!
Yuuno-kun is... Yuuno-kun is...!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Eight:
There's a Really Big Crisis?
I, Lyrical Magical,
will do my best!