Cry of the Spirit?
The souls of people who are captured by a strong spell and lose their freedom may leave their bodies in search of help.
Poltergeists also are of their kind.
I believe that is a crystallized Cry of the Spirit.
Does that mean that someone captured by the Star Crystal became a Cry of the Spirit and brought forth that darkness..?
We’re not sure whether or not that’s the Star Crystal,
but if that’s a fragment of the Cry of the Spirit, then that person is under the control of some other person’s will.
To put it in simple terms, the person’s possessed.
Possessed... a person that isn't quite him or herself...
If that’s the case, then there is no way that this situation can be resolved without releasing the owner of that spirit.
Well, if it is the Star Crystal, we can’t possibly handle it.
Why? Because that's something even the Thousand Master couldn’t deal with.
Anyway, are they targeting the Academy? Or something else?
Continue your investigation.
Yes, sir.
I ain’t helping.
You may be granted amnesty if you do, Eva.
Thanks, but I’ll pass.
Evangeline!
Does the numerous, mysterious darknesses have anything to do with the stolen Star Crystal?
What’s more, what about the true identity of the crafty Black Rose Baron?
Could he really be a figment of Negi’s thoughts and feelings?
The mystery can only go deeper.
Ooh!
I went over by three minutes!
Would you like to try dying once, mya!?
by Ayaka
Eh? Negi did?
Yes, Negi-sensei was taking a stroll.
Probably dealing with the investigations of the strange darkness, de gozaru.
But does he have to do it alone? He has partners like us, you know.
That’s true.
I wanna help him out!
Desu!
You’re right. After this, let’s all give him a hand! Right, Asuna?
Hmm… it’s a pain in the butt to do it, but I guess we have no choice.
I mean, come on, he can’t do a single thing without us around!
Oh, Asuna, speaking in a roundabout way again…
Just a minute! Just a minute, I say!
You Chupa Team army corps who wear chupa T-shirts and have no sense whatsoever!
Iinchou!
What do you mean “No sense whatsoever”!?
Army corps...?
It simply is what it is! Isn’t that right, Makie-san?
Ah, yeah, I guess…
With a shirt like that, you’re the one to talk.
My, Setsuna-san! What is that supposed to mean!? In any case, it’s Negi-sensei!
Makie-dono, you seem to go pretty darn well with her!
Eheh, well, I manage to get by with it…
It’s because she shares the room with Iinchou!
Must be troublesome, desu!
Silence, both of you!
Well then, yes, aside from that, I have something to ask of you army corps.
Something to ask of us?
Army corps, are we..?
Just recently, I heard you guys were with Negi-sensei on a secret camping trip.
I’ve already finished the investigations.
Yup, we went.
Konoka!!
But, it was a Chupa Team camping trip!
Eh?
For the Chupa Team? Hmm, so that’s why I wasn’t invited.
Yeah, that’s it!
De gozaru!
But wait, Negi-sensei has no affiliation with the Chupa Team!
Well, that’s because… of that! Right, Asuna?
Ah, yeah, that, that!
Because of that!
I don’t understand you at all!
Can’t you just give me a straight and clear answer?
Uh, um…
Ah! Oh no! We went over by three minutes!
Eh? Really!?
Oh! The noodles will get soggy, de gozaru!
Oh no!
Desu!
Hurry, to the noodles!
Wait a second!
What do you mean “noodles”!?
We were in the middle of a conversation here! Hey, come back here right this instant!
This is suspicious. They’re hiding something, aren’t they!?
You’re just thinking too deeply about it, Iinchou!
That was the story they gave us, and that was what they did: They decided to go out on a whim!
What are you saying, Makie-san!?
What do you mean, “Just”!? What do you mean, “On a whim”!?
If this is your way of thinking, then you fail!
Eh? “Fail”? I fail!?
If you look at things halfheartedly like that, you won’t be able to see the reality of things!
Do I… really fail!?
Yes, you do! You fail at being Sasaki Makie!
You’re a Sasaki Makie failure!
I’m going to say the English word for “Juu”.
GUN!
No points.
There’s no meaning!
Eh!? That’s bananas! I don’t have any bananas, though.
Ah, but if it’s tissues you want, then I have some.
Grade: Incompetent
Meaning: Unknown
Incoherent!
Bizarre!
Yakiniku Meal Set!
Reward the good, punish the evil.
World Peace!
Eat up.
At any rate, I won't let this slide unless I know the whole story of that camping trip.
You will assist me, won’t you, Makie-san?
Sasaki Makie… fails at life…
This is a problem.
Doing troublesome tasks myself contradicts my own style, so…
Maybe it’s best if I just send a servant over to investigate…
I’d need an energetic one who is tame like a puppy,
and who can work without knowing fatigue like a carriage horse…
Wow, what a run, aru! I feel great, aru! But I can still run more aru!
Like you!
And, after school…
Aniki… were there any reactions...?
Yeah…
I think this is alright for today. Let’s just go out for more drinks!
Alright…
Well, let’s give it one more round.
We found Negi-kun!
Owwie!!!
Afternoon tea with a green wind. Hailing from the country of mist - Love and bravery’s ambassador of friendship.
They call me the Black Rose Baron!
Looks like we meet again, Negi Springfield-kun.
Black Rose Baron…
Wah! Rather… it’s stuck, Aniki!!
Have you found the darkness?
Baron! I have something to ask you.
Hello!? My tail, my tail!
You have a question? I have things that can and cannot be answered.
Proceed.
What exactly are you?
That, I cannot answer.
Proceed to the next question.
Ah, yes.
Then, do you recognize this?
Well, do you?
What a beautiful bracelet!
So you do recognize it!
That, I cannot answer.
Please answer me, Baron!
Well then, I’ll leave it as is for the day.
Wait! Are you not the Thousand Master, Nagi Springfield!?
Baron!
Father!
Poor Negi-kun… so this is how he thought of the Baron…
Did you forget Aniki..?
Even if the Baron is really your old man…
Possessed, captured by the magic, and may not remember his original memories…
I know.
I understand that, but…
Negi…
Aniki…
I found you, Negi!
You guys…
Negi, we had a bone to pick with you, so we went to look for ya.
Yeah! You’ve made so many partners,
and you’ve made contracts for whatever reason there is.
You guys…
Alright, we should start investigating that darkness thing!
What are you gonna do, Negi?
Uh, ah... um...
Okay, then.
Negi-sensei…
You’re a lifesaver, Haruna-san, Yue-san!
I had no idea what the Library Island had!
Not at all. I like going there, anyway.
And it wasn’t us that did the searching, it was Yamada-san.
But aside from that…
Hmm?
Are you sure you don’t want us to help with that?
Looks pretty darn painful to hold all that.
It’s no problem at all! Right, Natsumi?
Huh? Ah, um, yeah…
You can’t help it; she lost in a game of Rock Paper Scissors, you know.
And you promised, right?
I… I guess so, Chizu-nee.
Janken!
Pon!
I won!
That wasn’t fair…
Makie?
What’s wrong?
Shall we ignore…?
Hello, I am your father.
I’ve decided to accept the position you gave me as “daddy”.
Sasaki Makie… fails at life!
SHOCK!
Daddy… fails at life!
Brought down like lightning…
Is that so…? Iinchou-san did that?
Yeah. Looks like she thinks our camping trip was suspicious.
Looks like we have to be careful whenever we gather for magic training.
We should also be careful for Negi-sensei’s sake!
I’m sorry… I’m starting to have you be careful…
Idiot!
Come on, what’s with that tone?
You baby mage, you!
Asuna-san…
Well, well, well!
I was wondering who it was; it’s Negi-bouzu, aru!!
Kuu Fei-san…
Whatcha guys up to, aru?
Oh, crap!
What do we do…!?
It’s looking great, Kuu Fei-san!
You should ask them about their oh-so casual camping trip secret at that condition!
N-nothing! I was just feeling kinda warm and stuff, so I decided to take a stroll with Asuna-san and Nodoka-san…
Really, aru?
By the way, Negi-bouzu!
Yes? What is it?
This is just an oh-so casual question, but it seems that you secretly went with Asuna-san and the others on some camping trip, aru!
And it seems like there’s some secret which cannot be told to anyone, so Iinchou asked me to get info out of you…
Now you shall oh-so casually answer, aru!
Rice Scooper Smack!
How the heck was that “oh-so casual”!?
I-Iinchou-san…
Oh my, Negi-sensei! Good day to you!
For me to be searching for some kind of suspicious secret…
My, what ever was Kuu Fei-san talking about?
No, just forget about anything that just happened, okay Negi-sensei?
Can’t you think of any better excuses..?
Iinchou-san!
Yes?
I’m sorry for not inviting you to go with us on our camping trip!
Eh?
I’m really sorry!
Ah, no, no, that wasn’t really what I was…
Next time we go somewhere, I’ll make sure to invite you, Iinchou-san.
So please, forgive us on this one!
Negi-sensei…
Thank you so much! I’ll be looking forward to next time!
Please forgive my rudeness as well.
Well then, please excuse me.
Oh geez.
I… lied to her.
I’m sorry, Iinchou-san!
The wand!
Iinchou-san!
Chizu-nee!
I got the tea ready!
Ah! Thank you!
Natsumi?
It started up again?
Where are we?
The forest in Wales…
It’s so cold…
Negi-kun!
Sensei!
You guys, too?
There! A fairy!
Secchan! Get it!
Will do!
Who are you!?
What’s going on…?
That fairy’s controlling the girls!
Negi-sensei, the provisional contracts!
Ah, yes!
On this occasion, let’s go with everyone!
Eh!? Ane-san, what’s with your reckless talk!?
Gotcha.
Eh!? Are you serious, Aniki!?
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna; Konoe Konoka; Sakurazaki Setsuna; Miyazaki Nodoka;
Narutaki Fuuka; Narutaki Fumika; Nagase Kaede. Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
Hey, we transformed!
We’re Japanese-style and Western-style detectives!
I… don’t think I did much of a transformation, de gozaru.
The girls from the Walking Club got the Cosplay Card.
On the other hand…
The rest of you are Suka Cards!
We got caught!
Use your skills, won’t you!
What’s that? I don’t get it!
Nin!
She transformed!
Thanks, Kaede-nee!
It’s so cool that you can transform like that, desu!
No, no… When I thought it would be nice to transform, I was able to, de gozaru.
Kaede-san!
Now!
Aim for Negi!
Negi-bouzu!
Aniki!
Tel
ma
Amoris!
Light of the darkness,
disappear.
Go beyond the gate,
be sent far away!
Tel
ma
Amoris!
We did it!
Where are we?
What in the world did we…?
Their target is me…
Negi, I hope you didn’t catch a cold. I was talking on the phone with Anya yesterday.
The food where she's staying doesn't go well with her; she got pimples from it!
She says she’ll be eating out from now on. She was so angry!
Ah, also, the black roses bloomed beautifully this year!
Next time, I’ll send a picture.
Oneechan…
Multiple mysteries bewilder Negi’s heart…
The Star Crystal, the illusions, and especially the Black Rose Baron.
The answers derived from all…
Sit tight and wait till next time!
Being a genius is 99% effort, 1% insight.
Next Time: “Eh? So the Baron is a type of rose! I thought it was a potato!” by Haruna!
By the way, I’m 99% insight. This must make me a super genius!
Baka Rangers have finally infiltrated the lair of the evil organization Waruwarutan!
However!
That was a trap of the defeated general, Dr. Pooh!!
Hahaha! As your name says, you guys are stupid, Baka Rangers!
Prepare to make friends with Death!
Damn you Dr. Pooh!
This is a time bomb, de gozaru!
If that goes off, it’ll be over for us in one shot, aru!
This is truly the end of the line for us, drawn as a picture!
You guys…
Can’t we do anything about that bomb?
It’s so far from us that we can’t reach it, de gozaru!
Wait a second! I can reach it!
Baka Pink…
I can use my ribbon to reach the bomb!
But that’s impossible, de gozaru!
One wrong move and you’ll bypass the timer and it will explode!
It’s alright! Just trust me!
Baka Pink…
Go away! Die!
So long, Baka Rangers! We will never forget your bravery!