Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
How nice that it's selling...
Najimi?
Najimi!
Yeah.
You're being absent minded.
Ah, you were thinking
about perverted things again...
Yeah...
No, there's no way!
Look, it was something
that happened all of a sudden...
It's like, yeah...
It's going well, so it's okay I think.
Well, it is, but yeah...
Hey, you and Justice...
Haven't you had a chance to become
a professional and debut before?
I have.
What?
Yeah, a couple of times.
Then, why haven't you debuted?
Such a waste.
Well, I like working
at my own pace.
Yeah...
For me, what I'm
pouring my passion into...
...isn't accepted by many magazines.
For example, like this.
It's totally erotic!
Or like this.
Wow, there are morals, you know...
This kind of line is said...
That's seriously going way too far...
But I think you should
grab this chance that you have.
That's right. If it's you, it'll go well.
Najimi, as long as you're happy,
I'm happy for you too.
Well, you never know.
I don't want it to be a letdown
if I get my hopes up too much.
That's right. There's no way 100
copies will sell out in three days.
Watch!
We'll sell off 100 copies easily and
go straight down professional way!
Then live in, like, a designer apartment
and have a driver with a Rolls-Cabbage?
Rolls-Royce.
Ride on a Rolls-Royce and
say good-bye to trains like this!
12th Edition
I still want to do it, I want to do it more.
Wow, they really are selling it.
And somewhere where
it stands out that much.
But...
It's not selling...
Well, of course.
It's the first days,
so I don't have to worry so much.
Go buy one.
Myself?
Yourself.
Well, that's sort of, cheating...
If you miss this chance, your road
to success might be closed for life.
W-What are you saying?
You're going to ride
a Rolls-Royce, right?
Welcome. Is this all?
Y-Yes...
Why did you dress like that anyway?
You don't want your fellow employee
seeing you buying your own book.
No one is going to know
that it's the book you made.
Even if you say that,
it's an erotic book.
You were the one that made it.
Shut up!
Excuse me...
Yes?
You were off today, right, Najimi-san?
No, no, I heard from Hoshi-kun.
I hope it sells!
Yes...
They knew...
Thank you very much!
Hey, Najimi-san.
Please be happy.
Yesterday, two copies sold.
Really?
Well, to tell you the honest truth...
...I got worried yesterday
and bought a copy myself.
Eh? You did?
I was worried that not even
one copy was going to sell...
I guess I got worried for nothing.
Yeah.
Then, please keep up the good work.
Ah, yes!
Two copies with
just you and herself.
Speaking of, why didn't
you guys buy for me?
I'm not old enough to buy.
I was given a copy from you.
Just 'cause.
Cold-hearted beings!
What about you, Nido-san?
What, you're sticking out your
tongue in this 21st century era?
Are you still jealous about it?
Can't you just cheer me on?
No, it's not jealousy!
Then, what is it!
You don't really want to
debut as a professional!
What a novel theory.
You're right.
That's not true!
It is true!
There is no way you
would know how I feel!
I know!
No you don't!
Kaneru-chan...
Stupid!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
I get it, I get it!
Stupid!
Today is the fated day.
How about this?
It's a limited sale that ends today!
It's totally erotic!
It's my recommendation!
I know you have good intentions, but
you're making it harder for them to buy.
You're right...
Hey...
Can I get this?
Welcome.
That's...
Nido-san.
Wow, you have a great eye!
This artist is named
Beauty Love-sensei and...
...right now her stuff is only
being sold in select places, but...
Isn't that Justice-san?
It's Justice!
You're right.
He's buying that.
Then I'm also going to!
Thank you very much!
You sold out like a dream.
T-Thank you very much.
But I got the result by email,
so I didn't get the full effect of it...
It really did sell, Najimi-san.
But I heard that it was because
Justice was buying it, so everyone else did.
So it's kind of different...
Hey, hey, you're going to debut now...
That's right, what
am I looking back for?
Then, please let me
see your manuscript.
Right.
It was the first time
without eroticism, so...
...it felt really fresh.
I-I feel like my lifeline
is going to shrink with this...
Ah, it's good.
It's done very well.
You did it!
So please look through the
contract and stamp the seal here.
This is our company's rule.
Ah, yes.
What is it...
Well, it's written there...
Because you're becoming a pro...
...from now on, we can't
have you do any dojin work.
I'll make you feel better.
Najimi, as long as you're happy,
I'm happy for you too.
You're going far away!
Najimi-san, you're going
somewhere too far way!
What's wrong?
Najimi-san?
Um, I think dreams should be...
Bah-bam!
Is how you go for it.
Congratulations on your debut.
Good-bye.
Wait up!
Najimi!
Hey! Let me think about it more!
What is there to think about?
It's professional!
Isn't this what you wished for?
That might be true, but...
I still want to have
embarrassing experiences like...
Secretly buying erotic
games at the store...
Seeing my friend after that and
having a really awkward moment...
I still want to slowly draw
manga with my really bad skills!
Swaying in a crowded
train with not enough sleep...
Alternating between hope
and fear with little profit...
And handing my book to
each and every customer!
That's stupid!
Yeah, I know it's stupid.
But, I still want to do it.
Well said, Najimi.
Brother!
It's you. Perfect timing.
Please hold off the one
that's not understanding.
Okay.
See you.
No, idiot! Not me!
You were the one that
said let's use that girl!
I'm sorry. There was
something wrong with me.
The manuscripts...
Leave it up to me, kuma.
Nido-san.
I am Aioros, a brave fighter, kuma!
I don't like disputes, kuma!
Hoshi-kun!
Oh, no!
H-He's going to get me!
Construction?
Brother, take this!
Jump to the left?
You couldn't seal it on your own?
Even if your mouth was saying
what you said, your body is honest...
Hoshi-kun, I'm sorry about
giving up the chance you gave me.
What are you saying?
Najimi-san, you've
sold out twice already.
Isn't that amazing alone?
That's right...
When you put it that way, that's true.
Welcome home, Najimi-san.
Yeah, I'm together
with everyone again!
This is the application form
for the next Comic Fest.
The deadline is tomorrow.
Of course!
Najimi looks so happy.
What am I supposed to tell my boss...
I'm sorry. To be honest,
I like Takamura-kun...
Shiho?
So that's... Takamura!
Takamura-kun...
Nishitani, I like you...
Are you stupid? Too nice!
Shut up! Don't say that to me.
So far from quickly becoming rich...
...but I, Najimi Osana, for my friends
and rivals, and also for the fans...
No, no, for myself...
I came back to this place...
That's right...
Dreams aren't things that
should come true that easily.
Probably.
But, God, after a little time has gone by,
please give me another chance.
Until then, I'll work hard.
Because even if it's bad, it's a lot of fun.
And that's my...
...Dojin Work!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!