You're finished!
Homura...
You...
W-What the hell are you doing!
Oh, so you're the Irregular I've heard so much about.
That's a funny nickname.
Get out of my way!
Sayaka!
She's fine. She's just unconscious.
Who on earth are you? Whose side are you on?
I'm with people who are rational,
and against people who pick useless fights.
Which one are you, Kyoko Sakura?
Wha...
Have I met you somewhere before?
I don't know, have you?
You've got an incredible poker face.
I'll just be going for today.
That's smart of you.
Did you just save us?
How many times do I have to warn you?
You're such an idiot.
How many times have I told you not to get involved?
I...
If you do something stupid, I'm not holding back.
Homura... why?
Anyway, she's definitely planning something.
Be careful.
Homura Akemi, don't tell me you're...
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 6     This just isn't right
Miki
Now it'll last for a while longer.
Er, it's totally black.
That's dangerous. If it absorbs any more taint, the witch could be revived.
Don't worry. Give it to me.
It's safe now.
Did you eat it?
This is one of my jobs too.
But you'd better find another Grief Seed quickly so you can purify your Soul Gem again.
I didn't know it was this important to purify it.
You've seen it. Kyoko Sakura was powerful.
If you have a surplus in your Soul Gem, you can overuse magic and be fine.
That's her strong point.
Just because of that, she sacrifices people for Grief Seeds?
The more you use your magical power, the dirtier the Soul Gem gets.
Sayaka, as long as you don't have any Grief Seeds,
you should assume that you can't beat Kyoko.
Damn, that sucks...
Mami didn't have enough Grief Seeds, did she?
But she kept on fighting.
I guess that must be her talent then.
Well that's true.
That's cheating! It's not fair!
That's just how it is.
Kyoko is both talented and experienced.
There are Puella Magi with no experience who could be stronger than Kyoko just from their talent.
Who would that be?
Madoka Kaname.
Madoka? Seriously?
Yes.
If you really want someone to help you fight against Kyoko, you can just go ahead and ask Madoka.
She just needs to make a contract with me.
No way!
This is my own fight.
I can't get her involved.
To All Customers:
Please do not drink or eat while playing.
No flirting, soliciting or pandering.
To All Customers:
Please do not drink or eat while playing.
No flirting, soliciting or pandering.
Hey. What is it this time?
I'm handing the town over to you.
Didn't see that one coming.
You're the type to be a good Puella Magi.
Sayaka Miki can't handle it.
I was going to do this anyway.
So what about that Sayaka?
She's gonna butt in again if we don't do anything about her.
I want this done as quietly as possible.
Don't do anything.
I'll handle it myself.
I still haven't asked my biggest question.
Who are you?
What are you trying to do?
Two weeks from now, Walpurgis Night will come to this town.
Why do you know that?
I can't tell you.
Anyway, if I just defeat her, I will leave this town.
After that, you can do whatever you want.
Hmm.
So it's gonna be a Walpurgis Night, huh?
That'll be pretty tough alone.
Maybe we could win together.
You want some?
We've wasted too much time.
There's no way we can find that Familiar now.
Damn...
Sayaka...
If you keep on hunting for witches, it'll be yesterday all over again, won't it?
Of course it will.
Well then, if you meet that girl again, try talking to her.
Or else you're going to start arguing again!
Arguing?
Madoka, do you think we were just arguing last night?
That was a fight to the death.
It didn't start off that serious...
but then we started trying to kill each other.
Don't do that again!
So you want me to talk to her?
Don't be stupid.
She's the type to sacrifice people to get more Grief Seeds!
You think we can understand each other?
Sayaka, didn't you become a Puella Magi to hunt Witches?
She's not a witch. She's a Puella Magi like you.
I'm sure if you try, you two can get along!
You may have different methods, but you both want to hunt Witches!
Homura too...
If Mami could've gotten along with Homura...
You're wrong!
Madoka, you were there.
She didn't come to defeat the witch until she knew Mami had been killed.
She murdered Mami for a Grief Seed!
That's... not true...
That transfer student and that Kyoko are the same!
They only care for themselves!
I understand now.
Mami was different. All the other Puella Magis are like them.
No...
The familiar that had escaped last night was small, but it can still kill people!
Your mom and dad might be next.
Or maybe even Tetsuya.
Madoka, is that all right with you?
You'd forgive someone who let that happen?
I didn't just take up this power to fight Witches.
I want to protect the people who are important to me.
If there are people even worse than Witches, I'll fight them too.
Even if they're other Puella Magi.
Sayaka...
Kyubey, say something!
All I can say is that it's too reckless.
Sayaka can't possibly beat Homura Akemi or Kyoko Sakura yet.
But she won't listen to reason.
You must be exhausted.
There's potato salad in the fridge.
tomo
Can't sleep?
Can I ask you something?
My friend's in trouble.
She's not doing or saying anything wrong.
But whenever she tries to do the right thing, it just gets worse.
That's normal.
Unfortunately, it doesn't always end happily if you do the right thing.
Actually, the more everyone tries to do what they think is right,
the less happiness there is.
She's not doing anything wrong. Why can't she be happy?
What should I do?
It's not the kind of thing you can fix by talking.
You want to fix it, even if it's not perfect?
Yeah...
Then you need to make something wrong.
She's too right. She needs something wrong done for her.
Wrong...?
You might tell a lie, or run away from something.
Later, you'll realize it turned out okay.
If you're really stuck, try doing something wrong.
Will she know I'm doing it for her?
She might not. Definitely not soon.
I did say this wouldn't be perfect.
Either you give up or accept that she won't understand.
Madoka, you've grown into a wonderful girl.
You never lie and you don't do anything bad.
You always try to do the right thing.
You're the perfect child.
You need to learn to make mistakes before you grow up.
I need to...learn?
You heal quickly when you're still young.
If you learn how to get hurt gracefully now, it'll help you later.
When you've grown up.
It's hard when you make mistakes.
As you get more responsibilities, it's worse when you mess up.
Isn't that hard?
It's always hard being an adult.
That's what alcohol's for.
I can't wait until I can get drunk with you, mom.
Grow up faster, then!
It's really hard, but just as fun.
Oh!
Kamijo left the hospital yesterday.
His rehabilitation went pretty well, so we pushed his schedule ahead.
R-Really...
You're just gonna go home?
But you've been chasing him all day.
You...
This is the kid, right?
The reason you made a contract with Kyubey.
You seriously wasted your one miracle on this crap?
You'll never understand!
You're the one who doesn't understand!
The point of magic is making your wishes come true!
Nothing good happens if you use it for someone else!
Didn't Mami Tomoe even tell you that?
There's an easier way to own your man, anyway.
Just use that magic you worked so hard for.
What?
Just go in there and break his arms and legs so he'll never be able to use them again.
Make him totally helpless without you.
Then he'll be totally yours...
body and soul.
I'll do it for you if you don't have the guts.
As a favor from one Puella Magi to another.
It's easy.
I... I can't stand you anymore.
This time, I'll...
Let's go somewhere else, then.
Someone will see us here.
She's too right. She needs something wrong done for her.
But how do I...
Madoka.
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in danger!
Follow me!
No holding back up here.
Let's put on a good show!
Sayaka, wait!
Madoka!?
Get out of here! This doesn't concern you!
You can't do this! This just isn't right!
Annoying people always attract annoying friends!
Are you saying something about me?
We discussed this. You're not supposed to do anything.
Your plan's too slow!
Besides, we're all ready to fight!
Then I'll fight her. Stay put this time.
Fine. You've got until I'm done eating.
That's enough.
Are you making fun of me?
Sayaka, sorry!
Madoka! What have you done!
I had to!
Sayaka?
This is bad, Madoka!
You just threw your friend away! Do something!
What?
What do you mean?
Stop!
What the hell is this?
She's dead!
Sayaka?
Please, Sayaka!
Wake up, please!
What's happening? Hey!
I didn't mean to!
Sayaka!
What the hell is going on?
Hey!
Puella Magi can only control their bodies within 100 meters.
100 meters? What the hell does that mean?
Usually it's right there with you. This almost never happens.
What are you talking about, Kyubey? Help!
Don't let Sayaka die!!
Madoka, that's not Sayaka. It's just a shell.
You just threw Sayaka over the rail.
W-What are you talking about?
You can't fight Witches with a regular human body.
A Puella Magi's former body is just a big robot.
Your soul is in a form that more efficiently uses magic.
Since it's smaller, it's also much safer.
As the one that forms contracts with Puella Magi, my job is...
to take out their souls and turn them into Soul Gems.
You bastard! What did you do to us?
It's like you've turned us into zombies!
Isn't this better for you?
Even if you get stabbed in the heart or lose all your blood,
you can just repair your body with magic.
You're invincible as long as your Soul Gem is safe.
It's much better than fighting with a weak human body.
That's terrible! How could you?
You people are all the same.
Every time I tell someone, it's the same response.
I don't get it.
Why do humans care so much where their souls are?
What?
What happened?
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Kamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate God Himself
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Hajime Ueda
Before you took up the burden of this fight,
you had a wish you wanted to see fulfilled.
And I did make that wish come true, didn't I?
Episode 6     Can I face my true feelings?