February 28th. Sunny.
Today, I finally got something off my chest that had been bothering me for a while.
Kagami, Kagami...
What is it? As you can see, I am preoccupied.
Um, I... Well, I wanted to ask...
Will you be my friend?
Wake up!
I'm serious!
I'd rather not get involved. Being your friend sounds like trouble.
Just listen!
I transferred here at the most random time of the year!
Then I'm the younger sister of a homeroom teacher,
and that idiot scared everyone away by saying,
"She's a sad little girl who used to be a shut-in."
He made it sound like I have some tragic backstory!
So now everyone keeps their
distance and treats me like I'm fragile.
Even when I make the effort to talk to
people, they only want to talk about school.
None of them talk to me about normal stuff.
That's true.
I am sorry for not noticing.
You're actually the biggest offender.
Anyway, I want to experience normal school life.
Normal, mundane school life.
But I only have another month or so of high school left!
And what does becoming friends with me have to do with this?
Well, I'd have to start by befriending someone like you.
That way, I can make everyone think I'm a happy-go-lucky girl
and they'll be lining up to talk to me!
I am kind of curious as to what you mean by someone like me.
Please!
I've never had a friend before.
I don't even know where to start.
So, erm... I want to practice making friends with you!
You know about my situation. That makes it easier for me.
I thought you'd make a good practice friend.
Like a stand-in friend, got it?
Are you aware of how rude you, as a human, sound right now?
Please, Kagami.
Very well. I will.
Really?!
Your first act as my friend will be to show some consideration and allow me to sleep.
Okay, yeah! I mean, we're friends! Good night!
Be quiet. I can't sleep.
And that's how I made my very first friend.
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
With the mere tap of a finger, the gods set my seasons in motion
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai nemuri wo yusaburu uta
This song has come further than any star just to wake up me from my slumber
Sasami@Unmotivated
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to watashi ga kieta mitai datta
Walking through the crowd with my ears covered made me feel like I was invisible
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
I do want to express my true feelings, but I'm too immature to do so using pretty words
deatta kouya no hana
I see flowers blooming in the wild
kowakute yasashikute
They're fearful yet gentle
fureta shunkan ni jiorama datte hontou ni naru
And the moment I touch them, this virtual reality I'm in becomes my new reality
kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashi no miraichizu
The map of my future is drawn by the mere whims of the gods
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
The myriad of sounds it rings with destroys the future I've been chasing after
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching over us, we became closer than ever before
nukumori ga mieta yo
I found your warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our bond might have been formed out of bloodshed,
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of bond I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 5
I'm not even serious yet
Kagami! Kagami!
It's lunch time! Class is over! Wake up!
What do you want?
Let's eat lunch together!
Why?
"Why?" Because we're friends!
My body does not require nutrition,
so I would prefer to sleep during lunch when I am actually allowed to.
But you sleep even when you're not allowed to!
Friends should eat lunch together!
Then let's put our desks together.
You can eat your lunch while I get my sleep.
That'd just look sad!
Anyway, I didn't bring a lunch.
Let's go to the cafeteria.
Really? That's so stupid.
I mean, very well. Then let's go.
We're friends after all.
Main Cafeteria
Go, Tsukuyomi!
You're our only hope!
Don't lose!
Gimme another bowl!
Coming right up!
I won't lose! There's no way in hell I'll lose!
Is our midget teacher a monster?
What are they doing?
That's my sister...
Oh look, he's dead.
Boy, I'm stuffed!
What are you doing, Sis?
It's an eating contest, duh.
The loser has to buy me lunch for the rest of the year.
What did you wager?
A kiss on the cheeks.
Men are so helplessly and unbearably stupid.
Kagami?
Oh, sorry! I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
There's no need to apologize. It was an accident.
I'm sorry, Sasami.
I need to get changed. You'll need to eat lunch on your own.
Kagami...
Hey, Kagami!
What is it now?
Since we're friends, you should do
something with me instead of sleeping!
Very well.
You can do something with me while I sleep.
What do you expect me to do?
Oh, I know! Let's go to the bathroom together!
What? You can't go to the bathroom by yourself?
That's not it!
I've always dreamed of going to the bathroom while holding hands with a friend!
It's like a must for girlfriends.
A robot like myself has no need to go in such a place.
Oh come on, quit being a stick in the mud!
You can just wait outside!
I am not going inside the bathroom with you.
Kagami... I thought we were friends...
I am failing to comprehend any single part of this idea.
Don't worry!
This'll make everyone think that I have a friend.
Some "stand-in" friend I am.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I stepped on something.
No wonder I felt something poking at the bottom of my foot.
Doesn't it hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm not a human, so I don't feel that much—
Kagami!
—that much pain.
Looks like today isn't my day.
Please go to the restroom alone.
So, I became friends with Kagami.
Oh, get me that salmon.
Okay.
She's always asleep, but she excels in class.
Take off half the rice.
Okay.
She can memorize a textbook with a single glance.
And she can even do seven-digit multiplication in her head.
No wasabi.
Okay.
She's a high-spec robot for sure.
Maybe I should ask her to tutor me.
I'll kill you if you get soy sauce on the rice.
Okay.
Say "ahh."
Delicious.
Kagami used to be a robot with no free will.
Tea.
Okay.
An evil organization created her using a part of Tsurugi's body,
but Tsurugi took her back and she began to
harbor emotions as she spent time with Tsurugi.
Cool it off.
I wonder if she seems cold and indifferent
because her emotions aren't complete yet.
Or...
Sasami.
Yes?
Why do you talk about Kagami so much?
Why won't you even comment or tweet about me?
Sasami, please... Please... Please...
Please eat me!
I can love you the most!
Wh... Wh... Wha...
Don't put sushi on your nipples!
Don't embarrass me in public!
Sorry, I'll do it at home next time.
Don't do it at home!
And there won't be a next time.
Stupid brother.
What's wrong, Sasami?
Kagami!
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's you two.
Are you on your way home?
Quit acting like nothing's wrong!
We should get you to a hospital.
Don't worry about me.
Unlike you humans, I'm built to last.
My wounds will heal in no time.
What happened?
I was just sleeping.
Talk to me!
We're friends.
This has nothing to do with you.
Can we just be friends when we're at school?
I am only a stand-in friend until you make real friends.
I do not know what you had in mind,
but I dislike how clingy you are.
Kagami...
Kagami!
March
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
Um... Kagami...
Kagami?
How can I help you?
Well, I won movie tickets...
Would you like to see it with me?
I'm sorry, but I have something else to take care of.
March
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
When's a good time for you?
We should hang out.
It doesn't have to be a movie.
I'm sorry.
Could you not bother me for a while?
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
Am I annoying you?
No.
March
Your existence has no effect on my life or my everyday.
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
Anyway, see you tomorrow.
Fine...
I won't talk to you anymore!
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
6 Days Left Until
School Ends
March
Sasami
There's a staff meeting.
I'll be home late today.
Kamiomi
Really, Yagami?
I wanted to talk to you.
You can ask me anything.
We're friends.
That's great!
What are your hobbies?
I... hate this...
I could never live a normal or quiet life to begin with.
I shouldn't have ever left the house...
Come get us if you can hear our claps.
Gotcha!
This scent... Sacchin?
You're mine!
Hey, no fair!
Eat me too!
Hey, hands off!
But I'm the weakest of the demons.
Even if you defeat me, a stronger demon will appear!
Hm? I smell Mamarin.
Mamarin!
I'm playing blindfold tag!
I'm too much for these guys without a blindfold!
Huh?
You're Mamarin, right?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Or did I make a mistake?
Hm...
Let's see.
Yep, tastes like Mamarin!
Hm? Are you crying?
Let's play, Mamarin!
It's dangerous to let you be so sad.
The myriad gods will try to make you happy and mess up the world.
And when you're sad, it makes me sad too.
I'm stupid, so I don't know how to cheer you up, but I like it when you're happy.
Let's play.
'Kay.
Cya tomorrow!
I'm beat. I'm too old for this stuff.
That was fun, Mamarin!
Let's play again!
If I'm ever up for it again, sure.
Okay!
Hey, Tama...
How do I... make friends?
Why do you ask?
Because I don't have any friends.
But aren't you friends with Kagami?
She sounded pleased when she told me she made a new friend.
She talked about how you two practiced together during P.E,
and how you became partners in English.
She always has the same expression, but she sounded really happy.
As gods, we're always a little scared.
We can use our powers to alter things and make anyone be our friend.
And that's why it's so scary.
No matter how much we play together or how much they say they like us,
we could just be making them say that.
Tama...
But you two are both gods, so you know
you're really friends, and that's really cool.
Mamarin, please get along with Kagami.
It'll be over soon.
It'll only be until the school year ends!
She said it's something she has to take care of by herself.
Just give her some time! Pretty please?
Download charm-loaded machine gun.
Input spirit missiles.
Upgrade protection from the Fire God Kagu-tsuchi to level B.
Awaken, Yata-no-Kagami.
Uninstall vulnerable factors and malfunctioning mechanisms.
Set heart and soul to sleep mode.
So that's what was going on!
The myriad gods do whatever they can to make God Almighty like them.
And right now, my stupid self is God Almighty.
And I, God Almighty, wished for a friend.
Then I chose Kagami.
The myriad gods became jealous, and they all began to attack her!
I used to be a puppet with no free will.
An automatic machine that completed an
objective in the most efficient way possible.
But now I have a family.
And maybe a friend too.
By becoming friends with her, I made the whole world want to attack her.
I don't care what may come my way.
If it is my friend's wish, then I will shed
blood to protect her normal, mundane life.
She only wanted to be friends at school
because that was the limit of her power!
It's not that I want her to thank me.
I was so happy to have a friend.
Thus, I took it upon myself to clean this mess up before she noticed.
I shall send all standing in my way to the very depths of hell.
Because we'll be friends... until the very last school bell!
Kagami...
You don't want to see me mad.
Class 1-Right
Kagami...
What's wrong?
You're here awfully early for school.
What about you?
You're here awfully late after school!
I was sleeping and lost track of time.
I saw you walking with some classmates.
Are they... your friends?
I don't have any friends.
I had to purify those girls. They had evil gods hiding inside of them.
They were probably trying to get close to you using those girls.
You're a naive little girl, so I'm sure you would've rejoiced.
There would've been trouble if you were influenced by them and made bad alterations to the world.
You were looking after me.
Did you listen to a single word I said?
Are you stupid?
Thank you, Kagami.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry...
Don't worry about it. I've finished purifying the school.
Any friends you make from here on out will be real friends.
Not alterations.
Why don't you go have your happy-go-lucky school life?
Kagami!
I'm sorry Kagami!
I'm such an idiot!
What do you think you're doing?!
You'll get snot all over me!
I'll make sure the gods know that I mean business.
I won't make them hurt you anymore.
So... So...
Shut up, you whore!
I'm sorry! I love you!
That's disgusting, you bitch!
Kagami!
Please be my friend!
Please!
Not just a stand-in friend!
A real friend!
Sasami...
I... used to be a doll.
I had no heart.
I was cold and didn't have the ability to cry.
Still, I admired being normal.
I admired being a normal girl who could laugh and cry.
If I could have one wish, God, then I would wish to be human.
Humans are stupid and weak, but so warm.
I want to be human.
Kagami, you're already warm.
Can I be a human?
Can I be someone's friend?
Of course!
No, let's be friends together, Kagami.
Good night, Kagami.
Sasami@Unmotivated
I apologize for what the fake Sasami did last time.
The staff took full responsibility, captured the culprit, and then ate her.
They ate her?
In any case, if you took this job more seriously, we wouldn't have had that problem.
Stop being so lazy.
I can help out a little if you need it.
Then you should sing with me, Kagami!
I can't do it alone, but I bet we can do it together!
Get real.
Feel free to sing whatever you please. I shall cheer you on from the sidelines.
Don't say that! Come on!
You smile at me with a disappointed look
Hey, let's go home together
I can hear your voice
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony
Light shines down like love
Let's hold hands forever
I can feel our osmotic pressure,
and I don't want it to stop
Hey, that was actually kinda fun.
I'm tired.
Never doing that again.
Sasami@Unmotivated
It's time for the Unmotiviated@Quiz.
Unmotivated@Quiz
Question 1.
What kind of question will I ask?
Hint: It's the kind of super difficult question no one in the world can answer correctly.
Answer: Let's go with what you have.
Question 2.
What's the answer to the question you asked?
Next time, episode six.
Next Time
Episode Six
Only Parents       Give Us Problems
Only Parents Give Us Problems.