Your BFF, Ryugamine Mikado, is the leader of the Dollars.
Please take me to that meeting.
We'll take you up on your offer to fight.
If there's a faction that's friends with the black biker and is targeting the Yellow Scarves...
It'll simply turn into a real conflict if things keep going like this.
I'll remove that crap from reality!
We're the Yellow Scarves!
I didn't quit back then.
At the time, why didn't I...?
Did Masaomi...say anything?
Kida?
No, I haven't seen him yet.
It's not like I suspect him or anything.
You guys said you didn't tell anyone that I'm in the Dollars, right?
Oh...yeah.
This isn't something you should feel responsible for.
I've...decided to quit the Dollars.
It's stopped being colorless.
I see...
I've been thinking about it for a while, but maybe you're in the—
No!
Alright.
That day, he said:
"But once you step into that world, it'll only take about three days for that to seem normal, too."
"If you truly want to escape from everyday life, you've no other choice but to keep evolving."
"No matter whether you're aiming higher or lower."
I decided to keep evolving.
But...
Is this...the result?
Your call will be forwarded to an answering machine.
So, weren't you listening?
I said, "No more fighting."
But...
...Didn't I?
Sh-Shogun! Is it alright to keep going on like this?
It's a fact that the headless rider is part of the Dollars!
You just want us to grin and bear it while they make us look like idiots?!
Plus, the Dollars' leader might show himself if we keep this up.
I'll investigate the identity of the Dollars' leader a bit longer.
Don't do anything until I find out something more concrete.
Got it?!
Either way, you can't stop us.
It's nothing to worry about.
Even if that hadn't happened,
it probably would have turned out like this anyway.
I wonder...
There are lots of fights like that in this city...
And it's nobody's fault that someone who
goes to the same school as you got attacked.
So don't worry about it.
The Dollars...
Are you one of them?
Got it?
Alright, I'm leaving this private conversation.
Okay?
Huh?!
Hey, you!
You're not going to say anything even after you bumped into me?!
Wait...
Heiwajima...
Shizu—
Yeah.
Huh?!
It's such a nice night.
Hey, Shizuo!
Yo.
Sorry about that.
He's also in the Dollars, right?
Yeah, he was at that gathering six months ago.
Idiot! Heiwajima Shizuo and that black guy from Russia Sushi are exceptions!
Don't lay a hand on them unless you want to die.
Yo.
Uh, hello.
You're alone?
Kida isn't with you?
Did you want to talk to Masaomi?
Not really. It's just dangerous roaming around by yourself.
A Raira student got attacked, you know.
Did you know him?
I see...
Th-Thank you very much.
This town's been in an uproar ever since that thing with the Slasher.
I heard that the Yellow Scarves are gunning for the Dollars...
The Dollars haven't attacked anyone.
The boss hasn't issued any real orders, either.
It seems that some people are worried about that...
Well, it's just a rumor anyway.
Are you in the Dollars, Kadota?
No. Why?
I've been wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
Is the Dollars really necessary?
Who knows...
Even Mikado...
I see.
So, you were having a private conversation with Saika—Sonohara Anri.
Except she wouldn't respond to you no matter how much you typed.
Well, I figured she'd be depressed, seeing as how things are.
However...
What about her cell phone?
Can you reach her?
It seems like she turned it off.
Anyway, what's up with Kanra?
He's just writing stuff that'll make Anri worried...
By Anri, you mean the Sonoharas' daughter?
Yeah...
The daughter of that antique salesman who sold Saika...
The leader of the Dollars is her classmate,
and she has a friend in the Yellow Scarves as well.
Anri doesn't know that Mikado is the leader of the Dollars.
Anyway, the three of them are friends, and neither the Dollars kid nor the Yellow Scarves kid know about her.
Probably...
I haven't asked her much about it.
Sorry, but please don't ask.
I'm sorry.
A regular gathering of the triumvirate.
So, what're you going to do?
I can't say anything if Anri's going to stay quiet, can I?
All I can do is pray for their safety.
Heyoooo!
It's Kanra!
Oh my, there's not a soul around.
You didn't leave me behind to go do something fun, did you?
Hmph!
But, that's okay.
I'm basking in my praise!
The game's getting really interesting, so I'll log off, too!
Bye byes!
Kanra has left the chat room.
There is currently no one in the chat room.
A number of days passed.
I haven't been to the Dollars' website since.
The uproar that's gripped the city is apparently still going on.
However, my everyday life here hasn't changed.
Also, Takeguchi was released from the hospital.
If I stay like this, I can live in peace.
This is my everyday life.
But...
Huh? Kida's already gone home.
Thanks for visiting me.
Um...
This is it for me today.
I see...
Then...
See you tomorrow.
Hey, you're in the Dollars, aren't you?
N-No I'm not!
Of course you are.
Eh?
Huh?
Please run while you can.
What're you doing?!
A-Are you going to betray us?!
Mother has asked us...
Mother has asked us to put a stop to you.
If it looks like anyone from the Yellow Scarves is
about to attack someone in the Dollars, please stop them.
Yes. I understand, Mother.
Please, I'm counting on you.
Huh?
It's my fault.
It's my fault that Kida...
Is there anyone in the Yellow Scarves who can hear my voice?
I have to do something.
I have to...
Hello?
Queen to C-Ke-6.
Black to G-Ka-6.
Good, good.
This is getting interesting.
Hey! Spit it out! C'mon!
I-I really don't have any idea...
What? I can't hear you...
You don't remember, huh? Don't screw with us!
It's the truth!
That's enough.
But we need to make an example of them for—
Do you really not remember anything?
When we came to, everyone was angry at us...
It's true! It's true!
Could it be hypnosis?
Like, "You're getting very sleepy?"
It may actually have been hypnosis.
Huh?
I mean...Right?
Yeah...
If the Dollars have the headless rider,
hypnosis should be easy for them.
Umm...
What is it?
Sir, I saw them with a girl.
A girl?
Now that you mention it...
I did, too.
I feel like they started acting weird after meeting with that girl.
What's she look like?
Sir, she wore a Raira uniform...
had glasses...
a-and big breasts...
The girl on the headless rider's bike also wore glasses, didn't she?
No...
She had big tits, too.
It couldn't be...
You got a pretty good look despite the situation, huh?
Alright, let's capture this girl and—
No!
I told you already...
No more fighting!
If we bring her into this, then—
You all understand, don't you?
Don't start anything until I say it's okay.
Yes, sir!
It's not true.
It's not true, is it?
I mean...
She...
Anri...
If you show them to Mika...
Really? Then I'll show her my notes.
I don't even remember her!
You're useless.
Huh?
What is it?
Something's weird.
That's right, neither Masaomi nor Sonohara are here.
So this is how vast this city feels when you're alone.
I remember thinking I wanted to go home when I first got here.
But I met lots of people and experienced many
things while Masaomi was showing me around,
so I feel like this city has become my own now.
Yet...
There have to be members of the Dollars amongst them...
Ryugamine?
What timing!
I have something to ask you.
U-Um, Harima...
What did you need to ask me?
Oh, that's right.
What's gotten into Anri recently?
What do you mean, "What's gotten into her?"
Ryugamine, you haven't noticed at all?
Huh? Noticed what?
It seems like something's been bothering Anri recently.
That obviously made me worry, so I asked her
what was wrong, but she just kept saying, "I'm fine."
Anri's always been the type to bottle stuff up, so I'm worried.
I hadn't noticed at all.
So I figured that she might have told you something.
No, I haven't heard anything...
Hmm. I see.
I'll ask her later.
If you find out anything, tell me.
Okay.
That's all.
Let's go, Seiji!
Ryugamine.
You love Sonohara, don't you?
Well, er, um...Why?
Don't play dumb. Anyone can tell by looking at you.
If you truly love her, don't turn a blind eye to her.
No matter what you learn about your partner or see her do, don't turn a blind eye to it.
Don't let go of the arms that embrace you.
That's your responsibility as a lover.
See you.
Wow! I'll also fulfill my responsibility to love you!
Yagiri's a weird guy...
...but I thought he seemed kind of cool.
Damn! Unbelievable...
That little brat acting all tough...
Yeah, there's something weird going on.
Oh, Horada!
Huh?
Over there!
Hm?
Oh?
A Raira uniform...
Glasses...
No matter what you learn or see...
...don't turn a blind eye.
Take...
I had no idea...that Sonohara was worried about anything.
What about Masaomi?
Did he notice?
I might not have noticed anything
because I've only been thinking about myself.
Concerning Sonohara as well as the Dollars...
What...do I know about the Dollars?
Why didn't I...quit the Dollars back then?
I'm leaving the Dollars.
Don't keep writing that!
I'll kill the Yellow Scarves.
That's why our leader needs to do something!
Who's our leader, anyway?!
Do you think the Dollars should exist?
We don't need it anymore.
You're just saying you're quitting, aren't you?
I said, "Don't keep writing that!"
I don't want it to go away. That's why I
want our leader to do something about it.
Our leader should take some responsibility,
since he started the Dollars.
What responsibility? No one's above or below anyone else;
We're all free. Isn't that what the Dollars is all about?
Don't rely only on a boss in times like this.
Come to think of it, I remember
someone posted something like this before:
He said we should turn the Dollars
into a good group by our own power.
There may be bad people in this
group, but don't worry about them.
Maybe this doesn't have anything to do with a leader.
That's right! The Dollars isn't someone's group, it's all of ours!
Yuck.
We should just do what we can by ourselves.
Go die.
I agree! We should protect this city
from the Yellow Scarves by ourselves!
You mean like go on patrol?
They don't know who we are, since we're "clearly colorless," so we can all help each other!
That's right.
That's right!
Like before...
A Raira uniform...
Glasses...
Breasts...
It couldn't be!
Sonohara...!
Black has surrounded white's queen...
No way!
It couldn't be!
That can't...
Is this a dream?
No.
That's what he told me.
How come you never notice what's important until it's too late?
Next Time: Break-Up Announcement.