Wow, you like WIXOSS?
I'm pretty persistent!
Kiyoi, you're really funny,
the way you look so sulky.
Nice to meet you,
Kominato Ruuko-san.
Huh?
I suppose this isn't our first meeting, is it?
We've met before, as Selector and LRIG.
I need to talk to you.
What?
The Selector battles aren't over?
Indeed.
But that's impossible, because...
Because Mayu is gone, right?
Mayu, a girl whose short life ended
before she ever saw the outside world.
Her emotions came to dwell within the
cards, creating the first Selector battle.
And Mayu is...
Mayu is still there, inside that white room?
No, Mayu is gone.
You saved her.
Right?
But the battles haven't ended.
The emotions of all those
lost and tormented girls
have put the next set of gears in motion.
An endless cycle of darkness...
And I want to stop it.
Stop the cycle?
Help me.
You released all the LRIGs, so with your help...
I'm sorry!
I... I can't help you.
I have a friend I care about.
One who means everything to me.
If I get involved, I'm sure she'll...
I don't want her to fight any more battles!
I see.
A friend she cares about...
Kiyoi!
Amika?
Jeez! Why don't you answer your phone?
Where were you?
I'm not telling you.
Visiting another former Selector?
Jeez... I keep telling you to stop.
I know. That's why I turned off my phone.
Come on...
You don't need to worry.
Of course I'll worry.
My friend keeps trying to get
involved in a dangerous game.
Why do you have to do this?
Maybe you hurt those girls,
but it's not your fault alone.
Just stop.
Thank you.
But I can't.
Is this about Sakaguchi-san?
Yes.
But it's not just that.
If I do nothing, my meeting with
you will become a lie, as well.
You're an LRIG that brings misery, aren't you?
You bring misery to every Selector you meet.
Like that girl, Aoi Akira...
I don't want to hear that from someone
who's enjoying watching it happen.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I love you.
No one comes here as often as you do.
Each time you do,
another girl's wish is crushed.
And you're starting to feel
nothing when you crush them.
It's wonderful.
Who will you destroy next?
Like you did to that girl, Sakaguchi...
I can't wait to find out.
Um... "This LRIG will be your avatar"?
I don't get it.
Sakaguchi?
"Piruluk"...
Are you the one who'll grant my wish?
That is an acceptable assessment.
Win enough battles, and
your wish will come true.
Can the wish be for someone besides me?
As long as it is what you truly wish.
My mom is sick.
If I wish to save her,
will that wish come true?
If you win enough battles...
Her face reminded me of Sakaguchi.
That was all there was to her,
or so I thought at first.
But...
I was so scared when
I found out Mom was sick.
I was so worried, and
I couldn't talk to anyone.
That's why I was so happy when
I had you to talk to, Piruluk.
And you know, I liked you
the first time I saw you.
It's funny how your face looks so sulky.
Wait, no! I meant sulky in a cute way!
LRIGs have no special powers.
Get rid of me, and stop participating
in the Selector battles.
Huh? Is that you, Kiyoi-chan?
Remember!
Kiyoi?
It's been so long!
She's a Selector now?
What? What do you mean, Piruluk?
Oh, so your name's Piruluk now?
This body was originally hers.
Her name was Mizushima Kiyoi-chan.
I was Kiyoi-chan's LRIG.
Kiyoi-chan won enough battles
to become an Eternal Girl.
Then she switched places with me.
Switched places?
As the price for their wish coming
true, Selectors become LRIGs.
That's the rule.
That can't be...
Oh, but don't worry.
The LRIG that takes their
place will grant their wish.
I granted Kiyoi-chan's wish.
It was, "I want to save my hospitalized friend."
Right, Kiyoi-chan?
You have a wish, too, don't you?
So let's battle.
Huh, but...
We were lucky enough to meet each other...
Amika, no!
You've lost twice!
If you lose one more time...
Hello, Dad? What is it?
Mom is...
Okay. I'll get to the hospital right away!
Amika...
But first...
Let's do it.
Amika, get rid of me!
I want to save my mom!
Open!
Even if you trade places with an LRIG,
your wish won't come true.
And if you lose three times,
the opposite of your wish occurs.
Which means...
It'll be impossible to save her mother.
Liar...
You lied to me?
I believed in you!
Why?
I've sacrificed many Selectors
to get revenge on Remember.
You're just another one of them.
But when I met you, I wavered.
Because you were just like Sakaguchi.
I should've just left you sooner...
but I couldn't!
Because I felt like I never
wanted to leave you...
I'm sorry, Amika.
Piruluk...
I'm changing my wish.
I want to save my mother.
But if that's impossible,
I want to make you human again!
Because you're my friend.
Amika...
Oh, is that all you want for your wish?
Either way, I'm going to win, though!
Attack!
Piruluk, grow!
Level 5?
The battle ends with this turn, Amika.
Will you believe in me just one more time?
Okay, Kiyoi.
Peeping Analyze!
Turn end.
She's not attacking?
I don't know what she's after, but...
I'm going to take an easy win, then!
Kiyoi!
She just threw away her win?
The level-up turned Peeping Analyze into
the power to change someone's will.
I took over Amika's mind
and rewrote her wish.
Her new wish is "I want to lose my mother."
The Selector battle rules
are merciless and definite.
With her loss, the opposite
of her wish will come true.
She'll never lose her mother!
You threw away your only chance?
Are you stupid?
Well, I doubt we'll ever see
each other again, though.
So long!
I feel betrayed.
I simply managed to get what I
wanted while sticking to the rules.
I need to punish you.
How about I just erase you from existence?
I see.
You don't seem scared at all.
You'll disappear! You'll be annihilated!
I've hurt many young girls.
I need to be punished for that.
You're crazy!
Why aren't you screaming, "I don't want
to disappear! I don't want to die!"?
It doesn't matter anymore.
I granted Amika's wish.
You remind me, I think,
of what I was until a short time ago.
Always alone, unable to believe anyone.
Feeding off nothing but revenge.
But deep down in your heart,
you want to be saved.
I met Amika.
Someday, you, too...
I hate you.
I hate you, I hate you!
I hate you!
You're going to suffer for ruining my game!
Kiyoi?
Amika...
Your meeting with me would become a lie?
The girl named Sakaguchi Ayumi...
Since I lost my memories,
you told me about her many times.
Oh, that's a WIXOSS novel!
Wow, you like WIXOSS?
Let's have a battle sometime! Okay?
I think this'll work for a deck.
I sure wish I could battle someone.
Knock it off.
I decided I wouldn't give up
until I played WIXOSS with you.
I'm pretty persistent!
Why?
You have lots of friends.
You don't need me...
I want to play you, Kiyoi.
Kiyoi, you're really funny,
the way you look so sulky.
I always thought it would be fun to
talk to you about all kinds of things.
But if you really don't want to,
I can't force you.
I guess one game would be okay...
Mizushima-san's always ignored Ayumi,
but now that Ayumi's ready to give up,
she finally agrees to battle.
Why not just say she wants to be friends?
It's creepy.
Wait!
Hey, Kiyoi!
Did I do something wrong?
I was looking forward to our battle.
I thought you'd give up
if I said just one time.
You really are persistent.
Kiyoi?
I don't like WIXOSS, and
I don't like people like you!
Kiyoi!
Hello, Selector.
I'm Remember.
I'm here to grant your wish.
My wish?
My wish is... to save Sakaguchi!
I accept...
The laws of the Selector.
Remember, what are you doing?
Sakaguchi-san, rest in peace, okay?
She was released from suffering...
through death.
No...
Congratulations.
Your wish came true.
It was my fault Sakaguchi
was in that accident,
and my fault that Remember killed her,
but now I feel nothing about that.
Kiyoi?
I'm not the real me anymore.
If I remain fake forever,
I can never face you.
I want to truly be your friend.
I can't stop you, can I?
I want to get my memories back.
I want to atone for the past.
These are my personal reasons.
Everyone has to face this
for their own reasons.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Ruu-chan.
Ruu!
Welcome back, Ruu!
I'm home, Tama.
Oh, my.
I'm home, Grandma.
Dinner tonight is meat and
potato stew, your favorite.
Beef and potato!
That's great!
Why?
Who's there?
Who are you?
Who?
An LRIG.
An LRIG, right?
Who's there?
Me.
I am no one.
I am this room itself.
I am Eternal.
Eternal?
What is your wish? The wish
you want to come true?
Tell me your wish.
Wish?
Hmph. I just want this boring
world to be more exciting.
Everything is here.
Everything...
What?
A strong LRIG.
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting for you.
Do you want everything?
This room...
You're saying I can control
the Selector battles?
Open the door.
Open it.
You must...
gather the keys to open
the door of the heart,
the keys to open the door to despair.
Gather them.
You must.
We're waiting.
Sounds like fun...
Piruluk...
It's been a long time, Kiyoi.
I see. So it's begun.
Yes. It's begun.
The Selector battle.
For the next ninety days,
you'll battle for coins that
are linked to your memories.
You're that Piruluk?
That's right.
You and I were chosen
to be Selector and LRIG.
The old rules said that Selectors
were chosen randomly.
Is it different this time?
So it seems.
I have your memories within me.
The treasured memories you lost.
Let's get them back together.
Yes.
What's this?
A key card.
A new rule that was added for these battles.
To use it...
More and more Selectors are being born...
So you're Satomi?
That's the name of the
last owner of this body.
Call me Carnival.
Huh... I like it.
Then you can call me Layla.
So what do you want?
A battle that will make my blood boil.
Reason / Hesitation and Resolution
If you want, you can talk to me about it.
It didn't work out last time,
but I'm starting over.
I'm helping, too!
I told you, no!
Let us begin!
Initiation / Usual and Unusual
Initiation / Usual and Unusual.