You're in a good mood this morning.
You're a vulgar boy, aren't you?
You have bad taste, Haruka!
It's nothing.
Anyway, what is that?
Some sweets I bought for Moritani-san at the hotel yesterday.
I wonder if she'll like them.
There's been a new development in the investigation
regarding the series of attacks that have been occurring throughout this area.
Did something happen?
What? What's wrong?
Moritani-san's been...
arrested?
TLC:
Tobikage
Timer:
Floris257
Editor:
Chippo
K-time:
Floris257
Karaoke:
Naruto-kun
Logo : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter:
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC:
Robo731
Floris257
Hritham
Encoder:
Floris257
Interrogation Room #2
Won't you tell me what happened?
But You're Not Here
If you don't, that guy with the scary face,
his name's Yama-san, will be really mad.
Um...
Hey, are you hungry?
I bet you're hungry.
Okay, let's order something.
Moritani!
What's that?
Is Moritani really here?
Yeah. It's faint,
but I can hear her thoughts coming from this way.
Yeah? Then...
Can you hear me, Moritani?!
It's me, Manabe!
Kotoura's here, too!
If you can hear me, answer!
Manabe...
Kotoura-san...
Manabe! Kotoura-san!
I-I...
I didn't do anything!
You're wrong! I... I didn't...
Why are you two screaming?
Only authorized personnel are permitted to access this area.
I'm sorry! Please, give us just a second!
I heard her! It was clear this time.
Moritani-san! I know the truth!
I know you were just a bystander!
Moritani!
Moritani-san!
Can you hear me, Moritani?!
Your friends? Wow, they're really something...
You two are so reckless.
You'll wind up getting arrested as well.
Well, when I heard Moritani-san had been arrested,
my mind went blank, and I just...
And I couldn't defy Kotoura's glare.
I understand that you're worried,
but if you go too far, you'll end up like that.
Mori! Mori!
Set Hiyori free!
Unlawful arrest is unforgivable!
Mori! Mori!
Miss! We'll save you!
Want to join them?
Anyway, just so I'm clear,
Moritani-san was arrested on suspicion of being the one behind the random attacks, right?
Yes. That's what the police and reporters standing in front of the school were thinking.
But they're wrong!
I saw the real criminal that day.
I know.
Still, even though it won't affect us, telling the police would...
Now that you've done that...
Sorry.
What is it, Muroto-kun?
Who's that?
The detective from before?
Moritani-san!
You guys were arrested, too?
Yeah, when I thought about it,
I realized I hadn't eaten anything since last night...
Jeez... But I'm glad you're okay.
It's no big deal.
So she says, but when she heard you calling her, she cried like a baby.
S-Stop that!
It might be a little late to ask now, but was it okay to let us in here?
Uh... As long as no one finds out?
Besides, having her friends here might make it easier for her to talk.
Um... She seems to be serious.
So, Moritani-san, what did you do to get arrested, anyway?
Well...
Remember that rumor about Kotoura knowing who the attacker was?
It was my friend who started spreading it.
I tried to stop her from spreading it further,
but it didn't go well.
Then, I checked all the places she seemed likely to go.
So you ended up finding your injured friend after she'd been attacked,
and they arrested you.
Yes.
But is it normal to arrest someone just
because they're discovered at the crime scene?
There's been testimony regarding that.
Previously, the suspect had made threats, saying things like, "I'll kill you" to the victims.
What a jerk, saying things like that...
Just because she was trying to stop the rumors about me spreading, Moritani-san was...
Kotoura-san...
Moritani-san is not the criminal!
I know who the real criminal is!
Wh-What?
Sounds like you're having an interesting conversation here.
It seems you know something about the criminal.
Why don't you fill me in?
O-Okay.
Hey, are you sure, Kotoura?
Yeah. It's okay.
Th-The thing is, I...
Tsukino, send them home.
I'm not lying!
I really can read people's minds!
Sorry, but I don't have time for childish games.
Hold it, old man!
How do you think Kotoura feels, telling you all this?!
Manabe-kun...
That's true.
Then, let's test Kotoura-chan's psychic ability on the detective.
You're gonna read my mind?
Ooh, I'm so scared.
Go on. Don't hold back.
Okay.
Um... You're having a hard time getting by
because your pocket money was recently reduced.
Your hemorrhoids have gotten worse, making it painful to use the toilet.
Your wife won't wash your soiled underwear for you.
H-Hold it—
When you came home late one night,
in place of dinner, you found divorce papers that had been filled out...
Stop! Please stop!
I give up. Spare me already.
You'll release Moritani-san now, right?
Sorry, but that's a different story.
Wh-Why?
Because it's not recognized by society,
a psychic ability can't be used to gather evidence.
Is that it?
Exactly. Besides, we police have our honor.
We can't rely on things we know nothing about, like psychic abilities.
The honor of the police?
After you used my mother to your hearts' content, then let her die?!
President...
What are you talking ab—
I had a feeling I'd seen you somewhere before.
Could you be...
The daughter of Mifune Chizuru.
I see... The clairvoyant's daughter...
Let's go, you guys.
What? But...
Kotoura...
Yes. Let's be on our way.
The clairvoyant, Mifune Chizuru, is fairly
well-known among the police force.
She even assisted in police investigations.
Although that was off the book, of course.
Which is why we had to feign ignorance when she was declared a fraud.
Of course, I never believed in the existence of psychic abilities, anyway.
I wonder how those kids can stand to be around that girl.
That aside, you need a good talking to.
What?! But I got the testimony!
Give me a break!
I couldn't do anything.
It was my fault Moritani-san was arrested, and yet...
Don't be stupid. You did nothing wrong.
Well, it's obvious that she's innocent.
She'll be cleared of any wrongdoing soon enough.
Why don't we search for the criminal after all?
It doesn't look like we can rely on the police.
The idea of leaving Moritani-san in custody makes my heart hurt.
Yuriko, you...
This could be a chance
to make your psychic ability useful for Moritani-san's sake.
My power... useful?
I'll do it.
I'm a little scared,
but if I can use my power to help someone...
Don't worry, Kotoura-chan.
The ESP Society will do all we can to help you.
P-President...
I'm against this.
Manabe-kun?
I'll never approve of using a psychic ability to track down a criminal.
Where's Manabe-kun?
He hasn't spoken to you since then?
No. Not a word.
Like the idiot he is, once he's made up his mind,
he'll never be swayed, not even by Kotoura-kun.
Kotoura, there's no need for you to find the criminal.
But it's my fault Moritani-san...
Don't make me repeat myself!
It wasn't your fault. Moritani knows that.
Besides, what can someone who faints just from peering into the criminal's mind do?
That's not...
I thought my heart was going to stop.
I don't want to see you like that again.
Manabe-kun...
Still, I believe this is something I have to do.
You're doing it again!
Why do you have to shoulder the burden entirely by yourself?
You haven't made any progress since you ran off!
Is it wrong to want to do whatever I can?
Even more so if it will help my friends or senpai!
Trying to do something when you know it's dangerous is just stupid!
It's not stupid!
Forget it.
You won't understand no matter what I say, and I hate you for it!
What?!
Is that so?! Fine, do what you want!
I will do what I want.
And Manabe-kun can do what he wants.
So you were the one who struck the final blow.
Y-You really think so?
Nothing we can do about someone who's not here.
We'll track down the one committing the random attacks in this town.
Um, what are these dots?
The crime scenes, and the point where you walked by the criminal.
Looking at this,
it's clear the criminal is somewhere in this town.
The area downtown where Kotoura-kun passed by him... is the most crowded place in town.
I would guess that the criminal was there to pick out victims.
If he's downtown, there's no shortage of the high school girls he targets.
He'd have an abundance of choices.
He most likely follows them to a less crowded area, and then attacks them.
Hey, Kotoura-chan...
Y-Yes! I wasn't thinking about Manabe-kun or anything...
You can go for today.
No, that's okay.
To be honest, there's nothing for you to do yet.
You should rest up while you have the chance.
Okay...
I'll be going, then.
Sort of feels like old times again.
Yeah.
It was just you and me at first.
Then the real psychic, Kotoura-chan, showed up...
Manabe-kun and Moritani-san came along soon after.
It was fun.
I wish we could stay that way forever, but that can't happen.
No matter what I do, I'm...
Do you despise me now?
Didn't I tell you before?
I will neither agree nor disagree with you.
I'm here because I choose to be.
You don't have to worry.
He most likely follows them to a less crowded area, and then attacks them.
I've gotta get home, fast!
Whoa, relax! It's me, Tsukino!
Um, I'm sorry for screaming.
No, it was my fault for startling you.
I just happened to see you while I was out investigating.
So, how is Moritani-san doing?
She's doing really well. Actually...
Maybe a little too well.
Please tell Moritani-san that we're going to find the real criminal and prove her innocence.
What do you mean?
You saw my power, right?
I can hear the criminal's thoughts.
Wait, wait. This is no place for high school kids to stick their noses.
But I've made up my mind.
Why? You want to show off your psychic ability?
My power has always segregated me from people.
But...
the people I've met in this town gave me a chance to change.
Thanks to them, I'm no longer alone.
That's why...
I want to help them this time.
Sorry, I don't quite understand.
What?!
I don't really have any friends, you see.
She blurted out something so sad so easily.
But they must be good friends, huh?
Yes. They're more than I deserve.
They seem to have no problem sticking with you, after all.
Friendship sure is great.
She's not a bad person. She's just a little blunt.
Isn't she lonely, having no friends?
Anyway, just leave this to the police, okay?
Moritani-san!
Mori!
I was so worried!
I'm so glad you're all right, Miss!
Are you okay, Kotoura-chan?
Uh, I'm sorry I worried you all.
You were released because the same kind of crime occurred again, right?
That's what I heard.
Well, I'm not all that happy though, since another person was attacked...
It's okay to be glad that you're no longer under suspicion.
We didn't get a chance to do anything.
What do you mean?
We were trying to find the criminal ourselves in order to save you.
Th-That's pretty reckless.
Could we continue to search for the criminal?
Are you sure?
Thank you.
By the way, I've been wondering...
Where's Manabe?
Oh, uh, Manabe-kun is...
Um...
Sorry! Restroom!
Because of me, Kotoura-san and Manabe are...
Those two will be fine.
So don't get any ideas about this being your chance, Moritani-san.
What?! I know that!
Kotoura-san hasn't picked up anything since then, either?
The random attacks have suddenly stopped.
He may no longer be in this town.
Tsukino-san...
Hello, this is Kotoura.
Hi there. How's it been going?
Well, we haven't found a thing.
Huh? No, I meant with Moritani-san.
You're actually looking for the criminal?
What did I tell you?
You shouldn't do anything dangerous.
Do you even need to keep looking for the criminal now that Moritani-san has been released?
Yes, we do.
Anyway, just give up on searching for the criminal.
And definitely stay away from the 2nd Street alley.
We've received word that the suspect is still hiding out there.
Promise me, okay?
Wait, Tsukino-san!
What did the detective want?
She found out we're looking for the criminal.
And she said the 2nd Street alley is dangerous, so we should stay away.
This is our chance!
President?
No! It's too dangerous!
You can't use yourself as bait!
Now is my only chance to get back at the
people who looked down on psychic abilities... on my mother!
You'll all help me, right?
It's pretty crowded for so late at night.
Well, this is the heart of downtown.
Kotoura-san?
Kotoura-kun!
I think her name was Mifune...
So she really did show up.
Why?
Why does the criminal know the president's name?
What does she mean by "She really did show up"?
Calm down, Kotoura-kun.
Is that really true?
Muroto-senpai, the president is...
Why? How?
Kotoura-kun!
Muroto-senpai...
You know where the criminal is?
Yes.
I'm almost there, Mom.
Kotoura-chan, a real psychic just like you, is helping me.
With her help,
The psychic is a fake!!
we can finally show all those people who didn't believe in you!
Eight Weekly  Revealed at last! The phony clairvoyant
So just watch, Mom.
Mom...
Yuriko!
Kotoura... I'm done for.
What happened in the short time I didn't see you?!
Not...
Not?
Not enough dirty thoughts...
Manabe-kun is suffering from a "dirty thoughts" deficiency...
Oh, there's nothing dirty in the next episode, either.
Episode 11
Stand By Me