Th-This can't be happening!
Even Groribas, our best warrior, was defeated?!
What manner of creature is he?
And how'd he get aboard?
Damn it!
Melzargard was supposed to be guarding the ship!
Now he and I are the only elite fighters left!
I bet he's just mucking about…
I need him now!
Curse the bastard!
Geryuganshoop, what is the problem?
Lord Boros!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
I've allowed one of the natives to infiltrate the ship.
In the mere four minutes since coming aboard,
he has damaged 23% of the ship.
It seems he is alone,
but he has managed to instantly kill every warrior sent to intercept him.
Do not panic.
As long as the power sphere is safe,
the ship will not go down.
The damage so far is limited to the crew's living quarters.
But minnows won't be enough.
Geryuganshoop…
you, Groribas and Melzargard, my top lieutenants,
will go eliminate this intruder.
Groribas has fallen, sir…
What?
Let me get Melzargard back here!
He and I together will wipe out the intruder without fail!
THE DOMINATOR
OF THE UNIVERSE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
We have more information on the enormous flying object that suddenly appeared in the skies over City A.
I'm here at the scene.
As you can see, all the main roads leading to City A
have been closed, and officials are on high alert.
According to survivors, City A has
been almost entirely demolished.
Employment Application
Name
Hammerhead
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
This image of the giant flying object was captured with a telephoto lens.
What are your thoughts?
Most likely, this is the act of an alien or extraterrestrial being.
Or perhaps it's an unidentified life-form that has a highly advanced civilization unbeknownst to us.
Of course, other possibilities exist as well.
I see.
Also, there have been eyewitness accounts of very powerful life-forms descending to the ground from the spacecraft.
Several Class S heroes are presently at the location tackling the issue.
He pummeled that thing with nothing but his bare fists.
Guess that's what makes him an S-class hero.
But even so…
It's no good!
It possesses incredible regenerative powers.
And don't let it hit any part of you.
A single blow instantly tore my arm off.
Dodge its attacks at all costs!
If I may cut in…
Shall we use a bombardment to finish them off?
That is good.
Contact the ship.
I will go.
Get back here!
You scum!
Best mind your manners!
I hope ya like mincemeat, freak!
Melzargard! What are you doing?!
I'm in battle.
We have an intruder!
Ridiculous.
It's true.
Finish them off and get up here!
This one's locked too…
Hey, open up!
You've got a visitor!
Oops… I broke it.
I've decided.
I'm going to rip your limbs off, then keep you as the ship mascot.
That is good.
Put yourself together again, eh?
I'm gonna keep you for batting practice!
Comrades!
It may be that direct physical attacks have no effect on it!
Let's withdraw for now and think of
a way to destroy it, like heat or something!
Smashing is all I can do!
Forget it!
This is all I know, too.
Can't teach an old dog new tricks.
Me, too.
Sorry, sweet Iairon!
Iai, don't you have faith in me?
There's nothing I can't cut down.
It's pointless…
These guys aren't the type to listen.
Melzargard!
Look, I really need you on the ship.
Getting rid of the intruder takes priority.
I'd love to, but I'm busy.
These creatures are persistent.
What the hell?
The life-forms down there are proving tough to handle too?
Nothing tough about them.
What's with the ship?
Is it going down?
It's not going down,
but more than half the crew have been killed.
What?!
Listen.
Begin cleansing my location with a bombardment from the ship!
I've got my hands full right now.
Besides, artillery bombardment is the job of the lower ranks.
Well, I'm in a situation where I can't return to the ship.
All right.
I'll notify the artillery crews.
Don't get caught up in the barrage and die.
Hey, wait!
You should come down here and help me.
That'd be much faster.
Hey! Geryuganshoop!
Damn him.
How tough is this intruder?
How about another one?!
More futile attacks.
Although you are exhausting yourself... That is good.
The hell is this?
A marble?
Why've you got this?
G-Give it back!
Sure thing.
Damn!
That's nasty, ya nasty bastard!
You dead?
Hey, this guy's got marble-looking things inside him.
That's where ya hurt him!
Oh!
Nice work.
So I just have to keep slicing until I hit a vital marble!
Impossible!
I'd been growing that head for a hundred years!
It died in a dump like this?
But you scum are all dead when the shells hit.
They're on their way!
Attention, intruder!
Stop your destructive acts and leave this instant.
Leave immediately.
Otherwise, we will unleash all our forces against you!
That's weird.
I hear a voice right inside my head.
Take one more step…
and you're dead!
Even if I wanted to get out,
I can't. I've lost my way!
Really? You'll leave?
All right, I will guide you.
Take a right, then go up the stairs there.
A right?
Exactly, a right.
I guess I'll go left!
No, wait!
Not that way!
W-W-Wait…
Hang on! You can't…
All right, that was my fault!
I'll come to you. Please stay right there.
Ah! No!
Now this place looks like a control room or something.
You…
An octopus?
You dare go around busting up our ship?
Hey! The debris is all flying at me!
Now Geryuganshoop, the supreme telekinetic power in the universe,
will grind you into blood sausage.
Just about there.
Lord Geryuganshoop, preparations for the bombardment are nearly complete.
Shall I proceed?
Maybe he went to the bathroom…
Hey, Lord Geryuganshoop!
Telekinetic power… Like a psychic?
You leave me no choice.
Super Telekinetic Gravitational Wave!
Die, Earthling!
My unparalleled telekinetic powers allow me to manipulate even the forces of gravity!
Have you any idea what a black hole is, you ape?
Inside one, the gravitational effects are so strong even light itself cannot escape!
Wait…
Now what?
Take this!
Telekinetic Shower of Rubble!
I got him!
What a waste of psychic powers.
I mean, all you're doing is tossing pebbles around.
Anyone can do that.
How... could...
I… Geryuganshoop…
be...
Excuse me—
Can I ask…
where your boss is?
This looks bad.
Is that confirmed?
Yes, Child Emperor said that the energy level in the spaceship is rapidly rising.
Yes, but the civilians—
Recall the search and rescue teams for now.
Have everyone take cover.
You'll be taking fire soon!
Hop on!
There we go.
Geryuganshoop still hasn't gotten back to me…
but whatever.
Let's see…
I believe the order was to concentrate fire around the enemies on the surface near Melzargard.
Two heads to go!
I'll bust 'em wide open!
Is it time?
Ship, bombardment, coming…
There they are.
All right…
Click!
It's over.
Evasion impossible. Instant death.
Huh… What happened?
What on earth?
They stopped.
All of you would be dead without me.
Can't you even finish one small fry?
Maybe try starting over from Class C.
You can have…
your shells back.
Th-This is…
I wanna go home.
I didn’t expect you to be here.
Thank you, Unlicensed Rider.
Which areas are likely to have survivors?
There must be more out there.
But you…
I'll go rescue them right now.
We want to know, too.
Yeah, can't let him hog the limelight.
Stinger, Lightning Max…
Mind if we borrow this?
You guys…
Nice catch.
Found it…
Smush.
One left!
Silverfang!
A… direct hit.
Weak, weak!
You are all so very weak.
Dead after a single hit!
A change of tactics was all I needed.
If I forget defense and focus on attack,
this will all be over quickly.
And you're next!
I will spring past that sword and squeeze your skull 'til it pops.
Think so? Then be my guest.
So he's come.
This planet's finest warrior…
I can sense no limit to his energy.
You the boss of these invaders?
Wonderful!
Before we fight, let us exchange names.
I lead the pirate band known as Dark Matter,
and am Dominator of the Universe. I am Boros.
I'm a hero for fu—I mean,
a professional hero.
My name's Saitama.
Saitama…
Look, I don't know what the Denominator of the Universe wants with Earth…
but you sure trashed City A.
What I want with Earth?
There exists a prophecy.
Prophecy?
You mean…
Once, I traveled the universe, ravaging everything in sight.
But I was too strong.
Eventually, there were none left who could face me.
I came to know the torment of utter, all-encompassing boredom.
Then one day, a seer told me…
On a faraway planet,
a being exists who is my match,
one who could rekindle my passion for battle.
That was nearly twenty years ago.
Have you any idea the distance I have traveled to get here?
My men thought the prophecy was a ruse, made up to lure me away…
But now I am certain.
Come.
Give stimulation to my existence.
That is why I am here!
Are you stupid?
You can't just go around attacking other planets just to liven up your boring life.
Even telemarketers wouldn't think that.
This set of armor, used to seal in my immeasurable, irresistible power…
has been broken.
Okay.
It is time!
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
The
Strongest
Hero
The
Strongest
Hero
Next time, on the final episode of One-Punch Man,
"The Strongest Hero."
What does it mean to be "strongest," Saitama?
You must tell me too…