[narrator] September 1st.
They say many students become depressed
on the first day of a new semester.
Perhaps they're mourning
the end of summer.
Perhaps they have anxiety
about their environment.
Nobody really knows the truth,
- but this is how Tadano feels.
- Huh?
[grunts]
The students who attend this school
seem just... fine.
[Komi breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[Inaka] It's so depressing.
My name is Nokoko Inaka.
I get a heavy heart
when I think about the new semester,
that's gonna be startin' today.
None of them have even noticed.
- At least not yet that I'm...
- [laughter]
Fine! I admit it!
[sobbing]
I'm a country girl from the sticks!
[theme music playing]
MISSION 29
"IT'S JUST A COUNTRY KID"
[Inaka sighs]
The first semester was such a pain!
If they find out I'm a country kid,
they'll throw rocks at me!
So I just stay quiet
while they're all having fun
chattin' away!
And when everyone shorten their skirts,
I'm the only one who kept mine
below the knee!
It just wouldn't look good shorter!
But now, I'm a totally different person!
My skirt is now a bit shorter,
at three inches below my knees!
That's right! It's a complete
summer break transformation!
[Inaka sighs]
Hmpf!
It's so embarrassing.
Oh, how depressing.
Why do I have to be so...
[gasps]
Oh my!
There's our Class Goddess! Her Majesty!
[gasping]
She's beautiful today as always.
Now that there's a real city girl.
Oh, I wish I were like her,
a city girl strutting' downtown,
with a Espresso Standbakes in her hand.
- [Najimi] What?
- Huh?
[Najimi] We have actual class today?
- But I didn't even bring my lunch!
- Oh, come on.
So, Komi...
Go to Sabowey
and get me their turkey avocado sandwich
on honey oat, with cheese, lettuce,
pickles, extra olives, no onions,
balsamic dressing,
a side of basil fries and a diet cola.
And have the bread toasted.
[Tadano] Go get it yourself.
[laughing] C'mon Tadano,
don't be such a meanie.
The thing is, I just haven't finished
my homework yet.
[Inaka] Wait! Did I hear Sabowey?!
That's a trendy city chain store,
like Standbakes!
Oh, so cool!
I wanna eat a Sabowey sandwich and say,
"This item doesn't comply
with our standards."
[Inaka] How cool would that be?
Aw, we're friends Komi, right?
This is an emergency.
Come on, help me out here!
- [Komi gasps]
- [Tadano] What? You're going to go?!
- Yahoo!
- [narrator] City girl.
[Inaka] Her Majesty is going to Sabowey!
I-I can't miss out on this chance!
I'll follow her and see
how she orders her Sabowey sandwich,
so I can become a city girl, too!
[playful music playing]
[sighs]
[Inaka] I'm a watchin'.
[Tadano gasping]
Now there's someone else
following Komi, too!
Her Majesty!
Stands so majestically
in front of that trendy store.
I would've been flustered
and just gone inside.
She's as cool as a cucumber!
[narrator] Actually, she's terrified.
[Tadano]
I have a feeling she's got Komi all wrong.
[narrator] She heads inside.
[Inaka] Well, here goes nothing.
[twinkling]
[narrator] All these professional-looking
adults in such a trendy place.
It's intimidating.
[worker] Hello, welcome!
I can take your order here
when you're ready!
[Inaka]
You... You can't keep the worker waitin'!
- [Komi grunts]
- Oh!
[Inaka screams]
[narrator] Komi walks right out.
[Inaka] She... She walks out
right at that moment?!
What the heck's she thinking?!
Oh my...
Look how calm she looks!
She doesn't cater to the workers' needs!
She sets her own pace, her own style!
She's not going to waver!
That's what makes her so cool!
- Oh, I'm learning so much!
- [narrator] Attempt number two.
[worker] Hi again, welcome!
Are you ready for me to take your order?
[Komi moans softly]
[trembling]
A Sabowey turkey avocado sandwich,
coming right up!
Will this be to-go?
Which bread would you like?
What would you like put on it?
Would you like it toasted?
Would you like all the veggies
that come with it?
Which condiments would you care for?
Would you like to make it a combo?
[narrator] She's confused.
[Inaka] Oh! "Make it a combo?"
[Inaka whimpering]
[whimpering]
Her Majesty?
[both gasping]
[worker]
I-If you don't have any preferences,
I'll just make it as recommended.
[narrator] Information overload.
Made as recommended!
[worker] Thank you! Please come again!
[Tadano] Did everything go well?
[Tadano and Inaka gasping]
[Inaka] Uhh-mazing!
She placed that monstrous order
without saying even a word!
Her Majesty really is something else!
I swear I'll be your follower forever,
Your Majesty!
And one day, I'm going to become
a city girl just like you!
Right! I'm gonna order
a Sabowey sandwich myself!
-Just like she did!
- Hey, wait!
[sting]
[narrator] She successfully bought one.
Hey, um, Komi, this...
- isn't my order.
- [Komi whimpering]
[gasps]
MISSION 30
"IT'S JUST A VIDEO GAME"
[phone chimes]
[gasps softly|
FROM: OMOHARU NAKANAKA
[narrator]
When a person has extreme social anxiety,
also known as sociophobia,
they struggle to communicate with others.
But take this into consideration.
[GASPING]
[laughing]
[grunts]
[narrator]
They only struggle to communicate.
It doesn't mean that they don't want
to form long-lasting connections
or friendships.
[footsteps]
[narrator] Komi's extremely nervous.
But she's going to try.
THE NAKANAKA RESIDENCE
[trembling]
[yelps]
Second year junior high syndrome.
[Nakanaka] I've been waiting for you,
Princess Komilia.
[in low voice] Come in.
[gasps] She actually showed up!
[Nakanaka] Th-This is my room, here.
[door closes]
[playful music playing]
- [narrator] She's fascinated.
- [Komi gasps]
[chuckles]
[Nakanaka] Komi's actually here.
She's in my room!
Wait. Come to think of it,
this is a pretty big deal!
The fact that the Class Goddess
is here, in my room!
Does this mean that I'm a winner now?
Oh, what am I doing?
I have to keep her entertained!
So, Komi... Uh... Um...
Just... You may take a seat
wherever you like.
[narrator] She hasn't had a friend over
since grade school.
- [narrator] Tranquility.
- [Nakanaka] How peaceful.
Ooh! Oh yeah! I'm at the climax
of this really cool video game!
- Would you like to watch me play it? Cool.
- [Komi sighs softly]
[beeps]
[Nakanaka chuckles]
Just check out these graphics!
The latest games
have evolved to this level!
What do you think of the visuals?
They're more beautiful than reality!
Aren't you impressed?
Oh, let's not forget about the story!
Not only set in a profound world,
but so well written that the story never
loses focus from the central character.
I just know there will be no choice
but to cry in this final scene...
- [narrator] She doesn't understand.
- Huh?!
[Nakanaka] Oh, yeah.
You're a light user, an ordinary person!
You can't fully appreciate
the latest technology in this game!
This is bad.
I just know you're going to tell me.
You are so boring.
[Nakanaka] I can't let this happen!
She'll never come over again!
Wh-What should I do?!
Aah!
Wh-Why don't I invite Najimi?
The more the merrier, don't you think?
[narrator] This is completely
out of character.
I was summoned so here I am!
- Bump ba-daaa!
- Lame intro.
Oh, wow, it's been a while
since I've been here, Nakanaka!
Hey, Komi!
- Aah!
- And I brought Tadano with me, too!
Oh, but, um, boys are not...
[Tadano] Oh, yeah, I kinda thought so.
It's okay. You'll barely notice he's here.
[Tadano] What?
[Najimi] What do you wanna play?
Since we're all here, let's play
something with four players.
Hey! Why don't we play Swamp Bros?
Yeah, let's play that!
How come you get to decide?
[narrator] What is Swamp Bros?
It's the short name of the game,
Combat: Swamp Brothers.
Known for its unique concept of throwing
your opponents into the swamp to win
and the variety of characters
you can play.
It was so popular
back in elementary school, remember?
- We've played it before.
- [game character 1] Najio!
- Just who are you talking to?
- [game character 2] Chuny!
- I didn't play it that much.
- [game character 3] Tadashi!
- [grunts softly]
- [beeping]
[Tadano] Right. I figured as much.
[game character] Komyusho!
[Tadano] You press this button to defend,
and I think this one's for...
[Najimi] Whoo-hoo!
The great "Combat" fight
has already begun!
Komi! You're like a sitting duck here.
[thud]
[Najimi] Oh?!
[Nakanaka] I won't let you
lay a finger on my ally!
Finally, some competition!
Use that button right there to move.
- Hmm.
- [grunting in game]
- [Najimi grunting]
- [Komi gasps]
[Tadano] Yeah, there you go, you got it!
And now, uh, you can jump with this.
What are you doing Komi?
Hit the jump button repeatedly!
You gotta hit the jump button!
[Komi breathing heavily]
Now!
Since I invited Komi to my castle
as a guest,
I must make sure she leaves satisfied!
I won't let her be an easy target!
[Najimi scoffs] What a softie!
You haven't changed a bit
since elementary school!
[Najimi] I'll distract you with my combo!
- [grunts]
- Oh, shoot!
[Najimi chuckles]
Seems like I'm still one better than you.
- Now for the finishing blow.
- Huh?
[Nakanaka] Sure, I may have been like that
in elementary school.
But!
Now that I have someone to protect...
Defeat is not an option!
[Najimi]
Don't go underestimating this game
and kid yourself that you can win
with just with your feelings!
Oh, yeah. After the swamp,
you move slower because of the mud.
[Tadano] So, hit the R2 button.
Hit the R2--
[narrator] She didn't mean to do that.
[Tadano] Oh! Don't worry about it.
That's just how the game is.
This button right here.
- [grunts]
- Yeah! There you go!
[game music playing]
[Najimi] What? It's the mud cancel!
Who could be using
this advanced technique?!
[Nakanaka] I am right here!
[Najimi] Shoot!
[game announcer] K.O.!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
- I defeated Najimi!
- I lost...
[laughs] Would you look at that?
That's my first win!
[Nakanaka cackling]
No way! That was pure dumb luck!
Whoa, what?
I just got a little distracted
by Komi's mud cancel!
You despicable sore loser!
[Najimi]
Maybe I'll play for real next round!
[Nakanaka] Bring it on!
I just finished my warm-ups myself!
[both grunting]
MISSION 31
"IT'S JUST A PART-TIME JOB"
BEEP
HE
I'm so sorry to call on our day off!
The person that was supposed to show up
canceled at the last minute.
[Najimi] I asked around a bunch,
but everyone was super busy!
Let's get started!
- Our mission, pass out tissue packets!
- [narrator] She couldn't say no.
We have to pass out 5,000 of these
by today.
[Komi gasps]
[Najimi] Well, we just have to
pass out tissues,
so you'll be fine with that, right, Komi?
I'm gonna go pass them out over there.
- Thanks for your help!
- [Komi gasps]
Have a tissue!
Here you go, take one!
Here you go! Here's some tissues!
How about a free tissue packet?
[narrator] Motivation times two!
[passerby 1]
Wow, that girl's really pretty.
[passerby 2] You're right!
I wonder what she's doing.
- [passerby 1| Passing out tissue packets?
- [passerby 2] Let's get one from her!
[passerby 1] It doesn't look like
she's passing them out.
[passerby 2] Then what is she doing?
[passerby 1]
Maybe we shouldn't talk to her.
[narrator] Motivation times three!
[cheerful music playing]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[narrator] Komi's on the verge of tears.
[mumbling]
[whimpering]
[narrator] Motivation times four!
Hmm!
- [wailing]
- [narrator] 128 points of mental damage!
[trembling]
Wait, hold on.
Was she just passing out tissues?
I should have taken one.
[panting]
[Hoshiko] Oh, no, no, no! Right now, I...
I really want a tissue packet!
My nose feels itchy
like I'm about to sneeze!
My hands are sticky
because I spilled a soda earlier!
I'm all sweaty and I'm about to meet up
with someone soon!
I stepped on gum
and now there's gum stuck on my shoe,
and of course it's the one time
I forgot to bring my handkerchief!
That's why
I really want tissues right now!
[Hoshiko] Hey! I-Is that person
passing out free tissue packets?!
But I don't really feel comfortable
going up to her to ask for one.
[frustrated moan]
- Huh?
- [gasps]
Beautiful girl passing out tissues
is looking at me!
Will to give me one?
Will you hand me a tissue packet?!
Tissue... Give me a tissue...
Tissue... Tissue!
[Hoshiko] Thank you so much!
[narrator] She made it very obvious
she wanted a tissue.
- Oh, so you are passing out tissues!
- [Komi gasps]
In that case, may I please have one?
[gasps]
[upbeat music playing]
[man] I'll take one of those!
- [woman] Me too, please!
- [giggles softly]
- All right!
- [Tadano] Where did she come from?
If you would like a tissue packet,
please stay in line!
And remember, there is a limit
of five packets per person!
EMPTY
[Najimi] We passed them all out!
How amazing, Komi! Thanks so much!
Hmm!
[Najimi] I'll split the pay equally,
three ways!
Alright! See ya soon!
[narrator] Did they just rip her off?
Huh... It's hot in here!
- Good morning!
- What's up?
- Hi!
- Good morning, everyone!
Good morning, Komi.
- You're early today.
- Mm-hmm.
Huh? [gasps]
What? What are you looking at?
[trembling]
- You all right?
- [gasps]
[narrator] She can't decide
if she should point it out or not.
She decides to just observe
and figure out what it is.
Is it a piece of food? A zit? Or what?
- [heavy breathing]
- Huh?
[trembling]
What? What is it?
[Tadano reading] "Are you really Tadano?"
[Tadano] Yeah, it's me.
[narrator] She could let him know with
her notebook! But that's embarrassing.
So then, she shouldn't tell him?
But he'll be even more embarrassed
if everyone else sees it.
- What a dilemma.
- Uh...
- [Najimi] Hey, hey, Komi. Hey, Tadano!
- [gasps]
- Good morning!
- [shrieks]
What is it? What's going on with you?
[laughs] So Komi, what's going on?
Good morning, everyone!
It's a beautiful day again today,
isn't it?
Good morning, Komi.
Love your look today as always, Goddess!
I can't believe Komi beat me
to school again!
You are beaming
with forbidden power like always.
[heavy breathing]
[panting]
[gasps]
- [narrator] It was a dream.
- [trembling]
THE NEXT DAY
Good morning, Komi.
- You're early today.
- [gasps]
[Tadano] Najimi!
You didn't show up for our meeting again!
[laughing] What is it, Tadano?
So, you wanted to be with me that bad?
Najimi,
about the culture festival paperwork...
Najimi, that book I lent you...
Najimi, you know what?
- [Tadano] Najimi.
- [sighs]
Najimi.
Hmm?
Uh... what's the matter, Komi?
[Komi gasps softly]
Eh?
[gasps]
[Tadano reading]
"Please call me by my name too."
What? Your name?
Well, uh... What do you mean?
Huh?
[Tadano reading]
"You and Najimi are friends,
so that's why you call them 'Najimi,'
right?"
[Tadano] Oh, yeah.
- [moans softly]
- Mm?
"So then..." So what?
"Please call me Shoko."
Huh?
[Tadano] "Please call me Shoko?"
BWOOSH
No, no, no, no, no!
That wouldn't feel right!
Because it feels rude to address a girl
by her first name!
[Najimi] Hey, so tell me, Tadano.
If that's the case,
are you saying that I'm not a girl?
[Tadano] You be quiet.
[Tadano reading]
"It's okay if you don't want to."
Oh! I-It's not that I don't want
to call you by your...
Well, how can I explain? Uh...
- Well, I'll call you Shoko.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[narrator] It's a strange feeling.
Come on, it's your turn, Tadano.
- Say Shoko! Say Shoko!
- What's that?
Shoko! Say Shoko!
Do...
Do I really have to say it?
- [Tadano reading] "Don't force yourself."
- Of course you have to say it!
It's Komi's urgent wish!
[gulps]
[Tadano grunts]
[straining]
[gulps, exhales]
Sho...
Komi...
Boy, you're a wimp! You've got no balls!
All right! His first name!
- You say it, Komi.
- [gasps]
Hey, wait a minute, you're gonna make Komi
endure this torture?
Yeah, sure! Of course!
If she really wants to be called
by her first name,
then she should start doing it first!
[Tadano] Sounds fair.
All right, let's give it a shot!
Oh, yeah, Tadano's first name
is "Hitohito," by the way!
Just in case you forgot his name.
[Tadano] I sure hope she remembered it.
- No, writing it down doesn't count.
- [gasps]
[trembling]
[Tadano sighs]
[sighs] Hi...
[sighs]
[narrator] Komi couldn't say it either.
- What?!
- [Tadano sighs]
[sighs] Good grief, we're done here.
Well, I guess "Hitohito" is hard to say.
It's a corny name.
Oh, by the way, Tadano.
You've got a sesame seed
that's stuck to your face.
Sesame seed?
- [Tadano] Huh?
- That's right.
It's been there all morning.
[narrator] Najimi can say anything.
[closing theme music playing]