It's so hot...
Today's the start of September, so why's it so hot this morning?
We had to eat the leftover curry quick—
Good morning, Minorin!
Hey, hey, you two!
How you been doing?
Y-Yeah! Kushieda, how have—
Hey, everyone!
Have you done your summer homework?!
Did you brush your teeth?!
Did you take a bath?!
What's up with you, Haruta? You're way too merry.
Oh, could it be that something happened over summer break?
The summer break is already old!
The second semester is the new cool!
Onwards to the new stage, the culture festival!
Or maybe something new!
Must be nice...
having a summer break where something happened...
Y-Yuri-chan-sensei!
But that's how it is... of course something happened...
I mean, it's your seventeenth summer.
It's completely different for a single woman who just entered her thirties...
Ah, the world is such a cruel place...
It seems that Yuri-chan-sensei had nothing happen whatsoever.
pure! purepara-to! tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre-Preparation! Even though I'm not strong at all.
pure! purepare-do! itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru!
Pre-Pre-Parade! Someday I will catch you!
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa (warete  bari bari)
P re prepa P re prepa P re prepa (Coming apart,  shattered!)
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
P re prepa P re prepa P re prepa
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugoshite
If you let your guard down, there'll be a tickling attack. Prepare yourself.
chiisai kedo hasamuno mijinko mitai na anata
You're small, but fit in, you who are as small as a water flea.
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
What we wanted was a plus-tic heart.
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
(Plus! Plus! But then, minus!)
demo sore ja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono kachi
But that's too boring. Those who notice this will win!
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing.
tanjunmeikai fukuzatsukaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, complicated and mysterious.
dou demo ii koto bakkari ki ni shitari suruno
If you keep worrying about useless things,
donna kanji? sonna kanji
how will it feel? It'll feel like that.
onkoutokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You who are gentle and sincere, yet eccentric,
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
put up a fight by pretending like you're tough with your whole being.
sunao na dake da to shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
The impact from being too honest will send you dizzy spells.
kizutsuichauno
You hurt someone.
(kizutsukechauno)
(You've been hurt)
junjou purepara-to
A naïve preparation.
atama no naka wa
In your head
(itsumo hitori no)
(Always on your own)
junjou purepare-do
A naïve pre-parade.
Oohashi High School
Culture Festival (Part One)
The arbitrary decision is that this year's event will be limited to just one day...
Even with the power of the president...
It's not like this was a one-sided decision forced onto us.
This is a trade.
Victory is ours!
The negotiations with the teaching staff have just begun.
Exactly.
If we manage to pull this off the way we want,
even giving up the second day will have its merits.
No matter what the obstacles, I will make this year's culture festival extravagant!
After all, to me...
This will be my final major school event!
Takasu-kun, next we'll go find a UFO!
Whoa! Stupid chi'!
The hell you doing, you trash!?
Like I said...
My nails are long at the moment, so I can't touch the ball.
They'll break otherwise.
You stupid chi'!
Her cute smile...
Ami-chan is an angel after all...
I'm a Palmtop Tiger fan.
Well, I prefer Kashii.
Kihara's sure fine too!
Whoa, Ami-chan's riding the Tiger like a horse!
Man, I wanna be ridden like a horse too...
Ladies and zentlemen!
What now?
There are no ladies here!
And what the hell is "zentle"?
Don't you all want to see the girls you hold dear to your heart in their "Cute non-everyday form"?
Hey, are you okay?
You didn't get into anything strange during the summer break, did you?
Come on, hear me out!
Soon it'll be the culture festival.
During the long homeroom tomorrow,
our class, 2-C, has to enter talks to decide what we are going to do for this event.
And!
I'm on the culture festival committee!
So what?
That-is-why!
If we, for example, host a maid café during the culture festival, it means we'll get to see the girls in maid outfits!
If all the guys conspire together and force a decisive vote, we'll have an indisputable majority!
How's that sound?
That sounds rather good...
even if it is coming from Haruta...
Wait a moment.
If we're going to do that... instead of maids, I absolutely...
want them in Chinese dresses!
That works too.
Takasu agrees with me, right?
Y-Yeah... Sure...
I already get to see her in something like a maid outfit at her part-time job anyway...
An outfit like a Chinese dress that fits to the body's curves perfectly is more...
No, that won't do!
If it fits to the body's curves perfectly,
it'll mean that I'll end up having to make fake breast pads...
What're you saying?
N-No, nothing!
Rather than Chinese dresses, I'd... yeah, I know!
Lolita or something...
Takasu...
You're a frickin' genius!
What?
Then I'd like nurses!
I want stewardesses!
You fool! Call them "cabin attendants"!
I want shrine maidens!
Wait, wait, everyone! Don't go off ranting!
Oh man, what were we talking abou—
A cosplay café...
would satisfy everyone's needs, no?
Guy's dressing room
THAT'S IT!
Taiga, I'm going on ahead.
Okay.
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Look at this.
What now, all of the sudden?
Whoa, this is horrible!
It got torn by the stupid chi'.
Hey, you!
How about not smearing my good name?
You stepped on it, tripped, and ripped it all on your own!
It all happened because the stupid chi' dodged the ball in the first place!
Like I said, that was because my nails—
Stop it.
I'll stitch up the tear.
Again he spoils her.
Make sure you have it ready by next week.
Wait! Don't walk away after putting the blame on someone else!
Hey!
They're quite vigorous.
Kushieda.
Now, now, let's return to the classroom as well.
Y-Yeah.
Good idea.
B-By the way...
That talk about finding a UFO later...
My, aren't instant noodles ever the enemy of the dieting warriors!
What?
Oh, so scary.
Absit omen.
I'll have to put another piece of cloth under this.
I guess I'll sacrifice one of Yasuko's old thermal shirts.
It's ringing, Taiga.
Whatever, I don't care.
Jeez, that shitty old man...
Shitty old man?
What's that all about?
Well, whatever. But, it's bothering me, so take the cellphone-
Oh, shut up.
What is it now, all of a sudden?
I'm telling you to leave it be!
He's the guy who re-married, decided that I was inconvenient,
rented me an apartment and then threw me out of his house.
He abandoned me! He's that cold-hearted of a man.
Wh- Your old man?!
No, shitty old man!
No matter how he is, your father is your father.
Calling him "shitty old man" is a bit...
Your family's always somewhere in your heart, even when you're apart.
It's like...
I'm telling you he's a shitty old man!
Shi-tty.
Shitty!
Shitty, shitty old! Old!
You don't have to learn that!
Hemorrhoid. Hemorrhoid. Hemo-hemorr!
Again Inko-chan is...!
He-hemo-hemorr! Hemo! Hemo!
What? Are you talking about your papa?
Not my father!
He was a wonderful person!
In order to protect himself in case he got stabbed—
That story again?!
Doing that isn't wonderful at all!
Rather, don't go telling people about him that way!
Awww, but...
So...
We'd like to decide on our exhibition and our Miss Oohashi candidate!
Topic
Culture
Festival
Topic
Culture
Festival
Culture Festival Committee Member
Haruta Kouji
Ummm... for the Miss Oohashi candidate, we'll go with Ami-chan,
and I don't think anyone has any objections, so our problem is the—
Same
Kawashima Ami
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
Huh?
Although I'm happy for the thought, I've been selected as the master of ceremonies for the Miss Oohashi contest.
So, even if you did decide to pick me, I couldn't be in the contest.
So, I think...
that Aisaka-san would be great!
I mean, Aisaka-san's really tiny and cute.
And she's famous all over school too.
What are you saying, super stupid chi'?!
Why do I have to do something like that?!
But that might actually be rather good.
In truth, the Tiger is famous.
It might actually go well.
You bastards...
Now, now!
That's won't do, Taiga-chan!
You're a member of this class too. You've got to actively participate in this kind of event!
You bastard, stupid chi'!
If just saying it won't get it through your skull, I'll smash the whole festival—
There, there.
Calm down, calm down.
If it's Aisaka, we might even win this.
Right?
Yay! So, the decision falls in favor of the Tiger being our Miss Oohashi candidate!
Continuing where we left off, I'd like to ask what we should have as our exhibition—
Here! Here!
Yes, Noto-kun?!
How about a cosplay café!?
WHAT?
Isn't that like, super otaku?
That will most definitely overlap with other classes.
I absolutely do not want to do that.
Ummm...
You see...
This is kinda my opinion, and it's not like I want to do it, but...
I really hate these kind of things, but if everyone would have fun, it would be great, or so I thought...
And so... ummm...
Ha-Ha-Haun—
Oh, I'm getting a nosebleed.
Don't take this wrong, okay? It's not like I was going to say something weird...
I... ummm... want a ha-ha-ha-haunted house—
Kushieda. Leave it at that.
Your body can't keep up.
I won't let you...
I'm not letting you, okay?
Yu-Yuri-chan?
Coffee shop? No way!
Make a band and put on a concert? Man, that's the most lame in Japan these days!
That kind of one-day excitement is nothing but an illusion!
You're going to suck by Christmas anyway!
Either way, we won't get anywhere like this!
Now that it's come to this, we're going to have a final decisive vote!
The lot of you, get your hands writing what you want to do!
No matter what the girls write, they're merely a big mob.
They're no threat to the Male Alliance.
All right! Everyone's done writing, right?
Here I go then!
Shake and...
lottery!
Huh?
Wait, what?! A lottery?!
Announcing it now!
For this year's culture festival, our class exhibition will be a pro-wres...
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious)
Who was it that wrote "pro-wrestling show" and "serious" in parentheses?!
Hey, why didn't you make it a majority decision?
Huh?
Oh.
That stupid chi' bastard!
While she's going through the endless circle of transmigration, I'm going to drop her down to all kinds of Hells!
Give it up and just enjoy a class event for once.
You're too narrow-minded.
What now? You're being all happy on your own.
Happy? Me?
Ever since we came back from the trip, you've been—
Huh?
Why?
What's wrong?
Weird. I can't withdraw any money.
Balance
0 Yen
It's saying that the balance is zero.
Fine, I'll—
Impossible.
It's because I kept ignoring the phone calls...
He'll do these kinds of things...
I can't believe him.
Phone calls? The ones you've been getting recently?
He's been calling many times for some time now.
But it ticked me off, so I ignored them.
So now he's cleared out the account for my living expenses.
That shitty old man... I really want to kill him!
Saying that about your parents is bad, you know.
Incoming
Call
Shitty Old Man
This is him threatening me.
Just pick it up for starters.
Either way, nothing will happen unless you talk.
And besides, not having any money will be bothersome, no?
Well...
Her picking it up was great, but...
How did it end up with me meeting him alone?
I see...
I understand. Anyhow, it seems my daughter isn't coming here.
Yes. I'm sorry.
I absolutely wanted to see Taiga.
But, it seems I made her hate me more instead.
I'm sorry as well. Ummm, was it Takasu-kun?
Now that it's come to this, please order anything you'd like.
Ah, no, I'm fine.
I'm having dinner after this.
N...No, wait! Uh, I'll help myself then!
I'll have an egg bagel!
I see.
Excuse me. Could we place an order?
An egg bagel for him.
And, I think I'll have a salmon bagel.
Put a ton of cheese in it, as much as possible!
Oh, right. Before I forget it, take this.
The money.
I... really wanted to see her.
I had something important to talk with her about, you see...
Something important?
Ummm... then, are you like that with Taiga?
Are you going out?
N-No, that's wrong!
Rather, we're merely friends and it's not like we're going out or anything like that.
We just live close to one another...
And so... we just got along... somehow.
I see.
If that's the case,
you must have heard lots about me from Taiga.
My new wife was way too young.
With that, Taiga just couldn't get used to our new life.
And then all kinds of misunderstandings piled up, one after another.
My current wife's name is Yuu.
It got to the point where either Taiga or Yuu had to leave.
And then, Taiga...
I want to live with Taiga.
Together, like before.
I wanted to tell her that today.
I no longer have any doubts.
I want to start over with Taiga.
I am going to divorce Yuu soon.
And then I will live together with Taiga.
Because we're father and daughter.
Because I love her.
This is serious.
Your dad's saying he's coming for you!
What are you doing?!
Do it properly! Rinse them in water for more than five seconds!
Oh, shut up.
Don't butt in.
In exchange for your going to meet him, I promised that I'd do the dishes, didn't I?
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Then wash them properly!
Whatever, go away!
You know...
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Your old man's a weirdo.
He doesn't seem like a normal adult or—
Go away, I said!
Boil some water and prepare some tea or something!
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Your old man was really worried about you.
Because of that, he now wants to live with you agai—
Are you dumb?
I'm being serious here.
Your old man said he wants to live with you.
He asked me to—
It's none of your business!
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Don't butt into other people's families!
What?! You're the one who made me go!
Is it over now that you got the money from him?!
That's right.
That's why I'm standing here right now doing the dishes.
That's why this ends it.
I won't ever see that guy again.
Hey. Don't give me that crap!
Properly—
Shut up!
Don't touch me so overfamiliarly!
Your old man was depressed because he's being ignored by you!
I felt sorry for him!
I'm the one you should feel sorry for!
Tai...
ga...?
All right!
Has it been passed out to everyone?
I really felt responsible for this.
That's why I made this. A pro-wrestling show script.
Hey, maybe we should just drop it?
Drop the class exhibition, and focus on the Miss Oohashi contest.
Here you go.
Everyone!
Come on, have some interest!
We can't go back on this now!
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Yuri-chan already stamped and submitted the exhibition activity plan!
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Pro-wrestling
Show
(Serious!)
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
Culture Festival Class Exhibition
Year 2 Class C
Homeroom teacher:
Koigaku
APPROVED
This might actually be a lot of fun.
Everyone's got a role properly assigned to them.
You've outdone yourself, Haruta-kun.
Oh, I'm the lead!
That makes me kinda happy.
Ami-chan...
It's true.
It's done really properly.
Haruta-kun, let's do our best!
All right!
For now, let's start practicing!
YEAH!
In the near future,
the students of class 2-C were happily living in peace under the class leader, Ami-chan.
But! There were some who considered this peace unpleasant!
They were the personification of evil, the Palmtop Tiger, and her follower, Delinquent Takasu Ryuuji!
Wait a sec.
Why am I her follower, and on top of that, a delinquent?
Why am I the personification of evil?
Hey, come on, come on! Hear me out, okay?
The Palmtop Tiger attacks her classmates of 2-C!
The classmates one by one are brainwashed!
But! By the desperate persuasion of Ami-chan, the brainwashing gets removed!
In the end, everyone combines their powers,
and successfully drive away the Palmtop Tiger and Delinquent Takasu Ryuuji!
And with that, they lived happily ever after! Happy end!
How's this?!
You ask us to hear you out and then we get that?
But it's simple, yet dramatic.
This might just go well.
No way!
I'm absolutely not doing something like that!
Sheesh, Aisaka-san is ever so selfish.
Hey! First the Miss Oohashi contest, and now this!
Why are you only making me do weird things!
If hitting me will end it, hit me as much as you please!
As you wish!
But! Nothing good will come from doing so!
What?
Oh, the Palmtop Tiger's really into it.
Already practicing, huh? Such intensity!
All right!
Now, Taiga, the brainwashing line!
What?
The line, the line! Look, this one.
"Taiga keeps screaming something..."
A-min has changed lately.
Yeah, that's true.
Wait, what the hell is that?!
Dunno. Haruta-kun said he was giving me an especially nice role.
Everyone, hear me out!
A decision was just made by the school!
This year's culture festival will be a competition between all classes.
The class who places first will receive extravagant prizes!
And while I'm at it, these are the prizes!
One! For the rest of this year, a refrigerator will be set up for your class!
Don't you... wanna cool your juice?
One! Your class will be getting next year's new state-of-the-art humidifying air conditioner installed!
Don't you... want moisture?
The current restrictions on the use of electrical outlets in the bathrooms will be lifted!
Don't you wanna... curl your hair?
And finally! Discount coupons at Super Kanoya!
Don't you want... discount coupons?
Wait, what?
Hey boys, get your act together, okay?!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, what should we get for dinner?
Amberjack.
What should we do with the amberjack?
Teri.
Teriyaki, huh?
Sorry.
I waited for you here.
For a while now.
Ummm...
You stalker bastard!
Taiga!
Stop being so stubborn already!
Let go of me, stupid dog!
Are you on his side?!
How cruel! Here I thought that at least you would be on my side!
I'm saying this because I'm on your side!
I'm saying this for your sake!
Who is that? He's your father, right?!
Don't you see he's come for you?!
You should at least hear what he has to say!
Wrong!
That's a stalker! I don't want that!
Don't you go spewing bullshit!
Weren't you crying because you had been abandoned?!
Be honest!
Be honest already!
You actually want to return home, don't you?!
How can someone like you understand anything about me?
I don't need that guy anymore.
I wasn't abandoned. I abandoned him!
He was useless trash I had no use for, so I abandoned him!
You bastard...
Does that...
Does that person...
really look like trash to you?!
My old man won't come home no matter how much I want it!
I'm not doing this for Taiga's sake.
I'm...
Sorry. Taiga...
I...
Enough already.
If you say so, then...
So,
don't make that face anymore.
Tai—
It's a good thing, right?
I'll think of it like that.
I don't know if I can think of it like that or not, but...
But since you're saying so...
I'll think of it like that.
It's for the better.
It's for the better, it must be.
Right?
vanilla salt de burning love...
A salty vanilla... burning love...
amai dakenara salt kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet.
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
I expose myself more than anyone else
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
because I want you to understand me more and more.
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
modokashi sugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a bit different.
watashi ga motometeiru mono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for.
shiro to iwaretara kuro datte icchau
When you tell me white I reply with black.
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself.
suki to iwaretara daikirai datte
When you tell me that you love me, I shout I hate you!
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, yet what am I saying?
amai vanilla ni salt kakeru yo ni
I'm already putting salt on sweet vanilla.
Next Episode Preview
Oohashi High School Culture Festival (Part Two)
Koigakubo Yuri entered her thirties this summer.
Everyone, please give me presents.
Actually, please take me.