With the help of his students, Negi managed to free Evangeline from the Star Crystal’s command.
But, while everyone was calming down…
Negi was sucked in by the Star Crystal!
What’s going to happen next?
"Negi-sensei, looks like it’s the climax now!" by Akira.
"Let’s all go home together ok, Negi-kun!" by Misora.
Negi-sensei!
Negi-sensei…
Negi-sensei!!!
Negi!
Negi-sensei!
Asuna-san…
Nodoka-san…
Are you hurt anywhere?
Konoka-san, I’m…
You’re fine now, Negi-sensei.
Setsuna-san…
But… where is this place?
I don’t know why but… everything just kinda turned into this.
It looks like it was made with the enemy’s magic.
Magic…
Whoa! It’s huge!
Amoris!
Now!
Takahata-sensei, where’s Negi?
Where’s the Star Crystal that sucked up Negi-sensei?
This magical world was created by the Star Crystal.
So, if we really want to "get back," we have to get back the Star Crystal.
So, the Star Crystal is essentially… the magic world?
Moreover, it's probably easier to think of the Star Crystal as the sole reason why this world even exists.
Yeah. That’s right Hakase-kun.
I see. So that’s what it means.
Did ya get all that, Kuu-chan?
I totally don’t understand, aru!
Well that’s good! There’re a TON of people who don’t get it, either!
Birds of a feather, aru!
What bird?
Actually, Natsumi doesn’t understand either, I bet!
Eh? I-I do!
No way!
Eep!
I know. Natsumi, lying will cause you to become shorter, you know.
I already knew from the get-go!
Hey, Takahata sensei, do we even know how Negi-kun’s doing right now?
What are we going to do if he gets hurt?
Ehh!? No way!
Takamichi… isn’t there anything we can do about it?
To find out about his condition?
Well, I’ll see what I can do.
The forest is-!!
This is bad!
Nekane-kun!
Alright!
I guess we’re alright for now.
But since these two are holding up that force field, we can’t find out about Aniki’s condition.
Eeh!? No way!
What about Evangeline?
Ah! That’s right!
Eva can use Western Magic, too!
Hey Eva! Work your magic!
No.
WHAAAAT!?
Forgive me for speaking out-of-place, but you have made a contract with Negi-sensei, Master.
I’m not sure if that obligates you to provide some assistance, though…
Stop it with the contract talk!
Please! Eva-san!
No.
A-Alright… but only just this once…
As expected from Asuna Ane-san.
Lic
lac
la
lilac
Oh, closed doors…
The last flower petal,
Retrieve us just one ray of light, and focus it upon my wings.
La
lac
Spiritus!
We got it!
Negi-sensei!
What a relief… He’s alright!
Eh? We’re there…
You’re right… What’s going on?
Those are illusions!
Illusions… Fluids that cannot flow.
Negi-sensei doesn’t look like he realizes that yet.
Negi, you dunce!
The real things are right here!
He can’t hear us here.
Eva! Make it so he CAN hear us!
Don’t ask for the impossible!
Is something happening on the other side?
They’re probably out to deceive Negi-sensei.
It must be a trick. Negi-bouzu, please be careful!
Negi…
Wow… This place is high…
I can’t see down there…
I wonder what’s down there…
Isn’t it dangerous?
But, even if we continued to run around up here…
Boy, go have a look.
You have a staff, right? Try and see what’s there for a bit.
Negi-kun! Don’t do it!
It might be that down there is…
… the Underworld.
The magic world is a black hole!
Black hole!?
If Negi-sensei ever gets sucked into that…
Negi…
DON’T!!!!
Go down there, Negi.
You’re our homeroom teacher, aren’t you?
We’re lost, so go and lead us down the right path!
It’s back!
This time there’s tons of it!
Eva-san!
Go quickly!
Leave it to me!
I’m from Class A, too. I don’t want to see my classmates get hurt.
Negi! You heard that right!?
Eva would never say that even if she were on her DEATH BED!
What!?
And a soft smile… Not even plausible!
Remember the real Eva!
Remember the incredibly impolite, incredibly heartless thing!
Hey you!
Hey! The screen is disappearing!
What are you doing!?
Hurry, boy!
No…
You are not Evangeline-san!
And, all of you!
Negi…
What are you saying?
That’s right Negi-kun…
Don’t say depressing things like that…
You can’t trick me.
You guys are not my students!
You are illusions!
As expected
Negi.
Well
observed.
You
got us.
But
this place
is
the Star
Crystal
’s
world,
ya know?
You
and your
magic
al
powers
are
from
now on
no
longer
usable
by
you
now.
Too
bad,
though.
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Negi…
Oh, what is it, Chachamaru?
That.
Damn you…
She seems to have been hurt by what was said earlier.
Asuna, it’s cuz you said "even if she were on her DEATH BED," ya know!
“Incredibly impolite, incredibly heartless”…
I guess that was a bit too much…
What the hell, dammit!!
The Magic Academy…
Negi.
Anya.
No!
You’re not Anya.
You are an illusion created by the Star Crystal!
What are you saying?
I’m the real thing.
No! You are not the Anya I know!
You’re a crybaby, as usual.
You were like that back then, too.
Remember? When you got lost in the woods…
Stop it!
When it got dark, you cried.
Stop it.
You didn’t stop crying, so I had to give you some candy.
You are not Anya!
You are not Anya.
Give me back Anya!
Did… Anya use that?
It’s a planetarium.
It seems we’ve been forgotten.
It’s been happening for a while now, ~mya.
Take a look, Negi.
The magical item that even the Thousand Master can’t use…
If I can use this…
What if I fail?
But… At this rate, I’ll lose!
For me to lose…
Anything but that!
I will beat Negi!
Anya went to take the Star Crystal for herself.
Why?
You wouldn’t understand.
You’re surrounded by friends.
You’ve never gotten hurt… you’ve never been betrayed…
Anya was lonely.
Anya wished for you to be hurt, to be sad.
Negi!
Stop it!
Please, just stop it!
What did Negi-sensei do to deserve this!?
That’s right! He didn’t do anything wrong!
It’s all because you hate him… and all because you blame him, isn’t it!?
Being resented in return can be a good thing!
That’s so cruel! Stop it!
Everyone…
That’s more like it.
Give back Anya.
Anya would never wish for me to be hurt.
Nor for me to be sad!
Your words are just made up by the Star Crystal!
What are you saying… ?
She would never do that.
She would never think of something so despicable.
And that’s because…
Anya loves me!
That’s my Anya!
Negi…
Please…
Bring back Anya!
Stop believing in people already.
People betray each other.
People hurt each other.
For their own sakes, people do things.
I believe!
You’re so soft-hearted.
Bring back Anya!
Negi!
Negi-sensei!
The Pactio Cards…
What… what’s happening?
It’s their hearts…
Negi-sensei!
You guys…
Come, Negi-sensei.
Use our powers!
Let’s save the real Anya from the Star Crystal!
Alright!
Give back Anya!
Ras
Tel
Ma
Scir
Magister!
Spirits of light and time…
The brilliance of the morning dew…
The silence of the fog of night…
Rise souls of the heart!
Hear my orders.
Come in this place, and tear apart the darkness!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Anya!
Negi…
Anya…
It’s alright now…
Come, let’s go.
Come.
That’s…
The timeless void.
Anya!!
They are getting sucked in!
Negi! Anya!
That’s the Star Crystal’s magic.
Looks like Negi-kun is not yet a match for…
Come on Aniki!
It’s no use… I can’t…
Anya!!
Let go of me! Save yourself!
What are you talking about!?
It’s my fault!
It’s all my fault!
Negi!!
No!
No way! I’ll never let go!
Negi…
Man, it’s no use!
What’s that?
That was…
Don’t tell me it’s…
Well, well… Looks like he somehow made it on time.
Honestly, in a good way.
Master is always late, ~mya.
Wah! What’s that?
Looks like the magic world is closing.
What’s going to happen to us after it closes?
I dunno.
Don’t give me that crap!
Huh?
Father…
Huh? This place is…
Is it the magic world?
Nope. It’s the real world.
We’re back.
Anya…
Negi…
I…
Thank goodness…
Negi…
Really… thank goodness…
Thank you…
The Star Crystal is in here.
That person that saved us…
Ah. There must be a misunderstanding.
Looks like it, ~mya.
That person… Could it be…
Ahh! Look!
It’s beautiful!
That’s true…
It’s daybreak.
Somehow, all of that felt like a dream…
Konoka, why you… !
Asuna, if you wanna do it, then go ahead…
Why would I want to!?
Come on, don’t be shy.
Hey! What are you doing?
Saying “No! No!” is part of love.
That’s not right!!
Stop saying silly things already…
Oh, Asuna…
And so! The Case of the Star Crystal has been solved!
Who was that who saved them at the last moment?
Looks like it’s…
Well, I wonder about that…
Well, thank goodness for Negi! And see you next time!
The Baka Rangers are now undergoing modification surgery by Doctor Hakase to become modded humans!
Now with the instincts of the great animals, you will become an unbeatable fighting force!
Come, open your eyes, Baka Rangers!
Red Boar!
The reckless—Baka Red!
Black Owl!
One with the night—Baka Black!
Blue Kappa!
RUMBAPPA! Baka Blue!
Yellow Tiger!
Running in circles—Baka Yellow!
And… Pink Monkey!
Eh?
Mamma?
Ookie!