The experiments we've run so far
prove that the D-mails are being sent to the past.
But I couldn't change the outcome of my match with Feyris!
That's a problem with you, not with the D-mail.
There are problems with the system,
including the issue with Rukako,
but if we work on it, we can turn it into a real time machine...
Time machine?
You were listening to us?
Feyris just brought your order!
Do you want any maple syrup or milk?
I refuse!
Then you can have my everything!
There it is!
Secret Move: Stir While Gazing Into Their Eyes!
I'm so jealous I could explode, Okarin.
Kyouma, what do you mean by a time machine?
Do you think you can seduce me
into giving up classified information?
I won't ask Kyouma then.
Daru-meow!
You think Daru would betray me?
We built a machine that sends texts to the past,
and by "we," I mean mostly me!
That was entirely too fast!
Messages to the past?
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mono kodou no kazu sae
is a trivial matter with little glamor for you
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Even trapped in the past and lamenting the future
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
The dreams that stretch into "infinity" and the future we imagine
"mugen" ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
are vain privileges we allowed ourselves
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no kenri
"Finity", that's what the two hands of the clock show
"yuugen" sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
towards a cruel agreement and choice
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
and protect your smile
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
And once again, a solitary observer
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
is sucked into a time loop without sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Stupid Daru...
spreading our secrets to outsiders...
Why?
Why must you take it that way?
I just wanted to...
No, that's not what I meant!
I...
Wh-Wh-What?
I'm not crying!
It's not like I was crying, okay?
You were clearly crying...
Your eyes are still red.
No way!
Something's in my eye...
What is this, an old soap opera?
Anyway, I'm not crying,
so no questions.
Got it?
I didn't say anything.
Shut up!
Christin—
Shut up! Don't talk to me!
I'll just say this...
You're an important ally.
Any time you want to talk, I'll listen.
Okabe...
Just as planned, she fell for it!
Now I can use her for all the grunt work!
Hey.
Good work out there!
Feyris!
Are you heading to Kyouma's?
Yeah, he wanted me to bring lunch.
Hey, have you seen the time machine, Mayushii?
Time...
Oh, the Phone Microwave?
Phone Microwave?
There's this big sparky thing, and it's kind of scary...
Wow!
It's like a time machine out of the movies.
Yeah...
But Mayushii doesn't really want him doing that stuff.
Why?
It feels like Okarin is leaving me.
We will now begin our Round—
Okarin! Okarin!
What?
Isn't this strange?
Mayushii says she isn't cosplaying.
It isn't cosplay.
It's her school uniform.
I had school today.
It's a super-realistic portrayal of a school uniform.
That's sexual harassment, and she doesn't have to put up with it.
Here's yours, Okarin!
Thanks.
No, wait. I said we're having a Round Table!
You're the one who wanted me to bring lunch.
Don't mind him.
Obviously, it isn't anything important.
You can say that after you hear the discussion topic...
Physical time travel!
Mayuri, is there still barley tea in the fridge?
One second.
Realistic.
It's me!
The Organization has initiated an operation to tear apart the lab.
Hououin Kyouma's words, my words,
fail to reach them!
Do they ever?
Then why are you ignoring my awesome topic?
Because it's impossible.
We can send messages to the past.
It must be possible...
It's not.
We can send 36 bytes plus some extra.
Three messages, each with six characters.
No more.
If you want to experiment, why not be the guinea pig?
That's if you don't mind ending up as a gel-Okarin.
Gel-Okarin, huh?
That'd really hurt.
SERN's experiments demonstrate the difficulties
inherent to physical time travel.
Even using the LHC, the largest particle accelerator in the world,
they've had no success.
We can't possibly do it with this equipment.
Then how do the messages get to the past?
I don't know.
That's the problem.
As I said before,
SERN's trying to use the lifter-black hole combination
to achieve time travel.
The Phone Microwave probably works on the same principle.
But the microwave doesn't have anything
to function as a lifter.
So where is it?
I don't know.
We're limited in the times we can send D-mail too.
Currently, we can't be sure that this machine
really sends messages to the past.
Before we continue,
we should deal with more relevant issues first.
Boring!
99.9% of science is boring.
If you call yourself a scientist...
I'm not a scientist!
I'm a mad scientist!
Epic fail. I better do something soon.
Miss Makise...
Don't tell me you're...
Shut up!
Not another word!
Because that's impossible!
Get back on topic already.
Continuing on to the reports,
how's the translation of
SERN's server documents going, Christina?
Or should I say, 4channer?
I told you that's not true!
Then you sure know your memes.
I do not!
There's nothing to report.
I see.
Continue your investigations...
4channer!
Stop calling me that!
Daru's up next. How's the hacking coming?
No change.
Until I analyze the mysterious program
on the other server, there'll probably be no change.
How's the IBN 5100 analysis going?
It'd be great if I could do it.
What do you mean?
Huh?
You haven't started the analysis?
How would I do that?
Where's the IBN 5100?
How would I know?
That can't be...
Okarin, what's wrong?
Christina...
did I, by any chance, fail to find the IBN 5100?
You don't even know where it is.
I see.
So if I choose to believe what you say, you found the IBN 5100.
Yes.
I carried it back here with you.
But you're the only one with any memory of that.
The D-mails probably changed the past.
Changed the past...
But we've only sent minor stuff.
It's the butterfly effect.
Sending one message into the past
causes the world line to split,
from a world where we didn't buy a Lotto 6 ticket
to one where we did.
Little by little, this changes what was meant to happen.
One change causes another,
and they pile on top of one another.
It's one of the long-recognized risks of altering the past.
Then where is the IBN 5100?
Let me ask this instead:
where was it?
Yes, when I asked my dad, he said it used to be here, but...
It's gone now.
I see.
Well?
There was an IBN 5100 at Yanabayashi Shrine,
but it's gone now.
No one knows when it was taken or by whom.
A dead end, huh?
But it's strange to donate a PC to a shrine.
I wonder who would do that.
Feyris?
What's up?
Here's the list of ten questions I wrote
to ask the maids at the next event.
Let me see...
"If you could go back and redo one thing from your past, what would it be?"
What would you do, Feyris?
Let me think...
Feyris... doesn't look back on her past! Let's go.
It's the task of the cat-eared maid,
who brings everyone happiness, to forge ahead!
Oh, my phone!
Hi, this is Feyris.
Kyouma.
A PC?
An IBN 5100.
Did your family give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
I don't really remember...
but you're right. My daddy did have a lot of old PCs.
Kyouma...
is this related to the time machine
you were talking about?
Look, look!
It's an Upa!
A metal Upa!
Do you still want a metal Upa?
Still?
How long are you going to stand there staring at it? Let's go.
Wait!
Daru!
Here I am!
What did you buy now?
I found a limited-edition that sold out before I could buy it!
As you might say,
"This encounter was the choice of Steins Gate!"
Don't use it for stuff like this!
Anyway, why are you two following me?
You could've stayed back at the lab with the assistant.
Once I heard you were going to Feyris's place,
I had to come along!
I wanted to go and play too!
Why did Feyris tell me to come to her house?
It's Kirari!
Mayuri, wait...
Geez...
The IBN 5100.
Shining Finger!
Wait! Hey!
Shining...
Moeka!
Kiryuu Moeka!
Why?
FB said it was there!
Okabe...
Back there, you mentioned the IBN 5100...
Do you know where it is?
You don't know either?
I don't.
Okarin!
Moeka?
Yeah.
Okabe...
Moeka's so pretty and stylish.
I'm sure she'd make a great cosplayer.
Mayuri, you know Shining Finger?
I do!
How?
How do you know her?
You brought her to the lab!
After Moeka sent her D-mail,
she disappeared from everyone's memory.
And then, after Ruka sent his D-mail,
they knew her again.
Little by little, the world changes
each time a D-mail is sent to the past?
Is this really the place?
I'm sure of it.
Seems it's on the top floor.
The mistress will be here soon.
Just one moment.
Butler cafés aren't my thing.
A real butler!
I've never seen one before.
Look!
Everyone looks like ants!
I love it!
Okarin...
Figures he'd say that.
Sorry for the wait.
Feyris!
Now it's Feyris wearing her normal clothes!
What luck!
Feyris Meow Meow!
It seems I must question your true identity!
Feyris is...
...Feyris, meow!
Stop fooling around!
If you refuse to explain, then I'm leaving!
Oh, fine.
Feyris's family owns all the land around here!
Then Akiba is...
That's right.
What about Akiba now?
It's Feyris's real name.
Akiha Rumiho!
I didn't hear that!
Feyris's real name is Feyris!
What a sad attempt to escape reality.
By the way, Feyris was the one
who asked to bring the culture of cute to Akiba.
No way!
And she works as an angel at May Queen
to further spread the culture of cute!
How splendid!
And my eyes are also splendid for recognizing her before anyone else!
But, but... keep it a secret, okay?
I want you to treat me
with Feyris-love, just like you always have!
I will! Totally!
Thank you, meow-meow!
No meow-meows!
Anyway, what about the IBN 5100?
Oh, that?
But before that, I have a simple request...
You want to arrange a trade?
It's nothing difficult.
I only want you to let me use the D-mail, just once.
Of course!
Use it as much as you want!
Wait! The D-mail is absolutely off-limits to outsiders...
Then why not make Feyris a lab member too?
Wait! Wait!
Sending more messages to the past would be—
You're the one who sent the Lotto 6 number back to try and make money,
yet you won't send one for Feyris?
Just this once!
No, that's not it...
But if I stop now,
there's no guarantee that the IBN 5100 will return.
If this is any indication...
Very well.
But as Mayuri said,
you'll have to become a lab member.
You are now Lab Member 007, Akiha Ru—
I-I-I can't hear you!
It's done.
You're sure you want to send it back ten years, right?
I'm sure!
What does it say?
Well... it's a secret!
Tell me.
As leader of the lab, it's my job to know.
No. A maiden's private life is off-limits to guys.
I think it's wrong to look at someone's emails.
I agree! Totally!
Fine.
Then put your hand on the send button and wait.
Hello?
It's me!
What's the situation...
She hung up on me, dammit!
Yeah, I bet she did.
That Christina!
Doesn't she know she's my assistant?
Hello?
It's Hououin Kyouma. Don't just hang up on me without a word.
Hououin? Oh, Okabe.
I thought it was a prank call.
I'm sure you saw my number on the display.
Even so, those first words
were creepy enough to make me hang up.
In other words, you are terrified of the mighty Hououin Kyouma—
She hung up on me! She hung up on me again!
Okarin, aren't you ready yet?
Wait!
Curse you, cold-blooded pervert girl genius...
Hello?
Listen, the Zomb—
Hello, my name is Okabe Rintarou.
What is it?
I would be eternally grateful
if you'd set the Phone Microwave (name subject to change)
to the values I proferred in my earlier message.
You should have just said that from the start.
Also, that isn't what "proffer" means.
You're embarrassing yourself.
And stop calling it the Phone Microwave (name subject to change) already.
Shut up, Cel 7!
I'm trying to be polite, and you're...
Do they not like each other?
I think it's the opposite.
Agreed.
Will you send?
Maybe...
Maybe I don't need to do this.
Feyris!
The electricity's started.
Send it.
Um...
Who are you?
Daddy!
Daddy?
Were you talking to Kyouma?
Yeah.
I'll be on my way.
Enjoy yourselves.
Feyris's dad has this
kind of refined air about him, doesn't he?
Indeed! You can tell he's Feyris's dad.
Um...
Do you know anything about an IBN 5100?
I haven't heard that name in ages.
I'm looking for one.
Unfortunately, I parted with mine a long time ago.
Did you give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
Shrine?
No, I didn't.
Goodbye, then.
Before Feyris sent her D-mail,
I heard that the IBN 5100 disappeared after it had been given to Yanabayashi Shrine.
But now, the shrine never got it.
Each time we send a message, things change.
Something may be changing,
even without me being aware of it.
It's possible that we've already done something that can't be undone.
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
Okarin! Okarin!
Mayushii is going to Nakano to buy a Lovely Sword comic.
Lovely Sword?
We can't escape the twelve rules
Kouga Yui?
Nakano's far away.
Yeah.
I wish there was a Toranoana comic shop here.
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
What are you talking about?
Toranoana's right over there.
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
What are you talking about, Okarin?
Why would there be one in Akiba?
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten