When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Boyfriend?!
M-Mom, why are you suddenly
bringing this up?!
You scared me!
I mean, you're getting to that
age already, right, Hina?
I thought maybe you'd want to spend you
birthday with someone that's special to you.
That's got nothing to do with anything!
Or rather, I don't have anyone like that!
Oh, you don't?
Besides, it's always been the rule that
we spend birthdays with just the family.
I guess it's already been
10 years since then.
Hey, w-wait, what are you...?
You were so little and now you've
grown into a fine young lady...
Time certainly flies.
Q-Quit it! You're embarrassing me!
There's no way the boys would leave
a wonderful girl like you alone.
There's bound to be a wonderful
guy out there somewhere,
who'll come flying to you if
you'd just call out to him.
Someone who would come if I
would just call out to him...
Why does Hayate enter into the picture?!
Sure, I think he's a nice guy
and it's not like I hate him,
but that doesn't mean he's
special to me or anything!
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
It's not true!
It's totally not like that!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Hina Love
Good morning, Hinagiku.
M-M-Morning!
Hinagiku?
What's gotten into her?
Could it be that I did something
to make her hate me again?!
Hey, get a grip.
What's the point of getting
depressed even before the exams?
Oh, now that you mention it, today
is the day of our finals, isn't it?
Huh? Then what were you getting
depressed about just now?
N-No, it was nothing!
Sheesh. I got weirdly self-conscious
because of what Mom said yesterday.
Miss Hinagiku Katsura
Th-This is...!
No name on the back.
Who in the world could it be?
Someone's got quite a lot of
nerve to send me a love letter.
C-Could it be Hayate?
No, impossible!
But he did try to talk to me earlier...
I-I wonder what it says...
I will be waiting in front of
the kendo training hall after school.
Please come for sure.
"I will be waiting in front of the
kendo training hall after school.
"Please come for sure."
What are you doing, Hayate?
Eeeep
I-It's nothing! Nothing at all!
The kendo training hall...
Could that mean the sender is Hinagiku?
No, no, calm down, Hayate.
There's no way such a straight up YA event
would ever happen in real life!
Besides, have there even
been any events so far
that might have elevated my
relationship with Hinagiku?
Wait, maybe her strange behavior this
morning was the prelude to this.
H-Here you are, Miss!
Thanks.
No, no. If I fail like this, I'm
not going to get another chance.
I have to focus!
And thus, the hours of the final exams
were spent on agonizing distress
and wild dating game fantasies.
And after school let out...
What?! That's wrong, too?!
Honestly! And after I taught
it to you over and over, too.
Just what kind of a blockhead are you?
Oh, crap. What should I do?
Nagi, should we not check answers
for my dear Hayate as well?
No problem there! Hayate's a guy who
can do it when he puts his mind to it.
Right, Hayate?
Y-Yes, of course, Miss!
But I actually couldn't focus
much because of this thing.
I guess for starters, we'll
do an intensive study group
for the guy who can't do it even
when he puts his mind to it.
Who can't do it even when
he puts his mind to it?!
Like hell I'm coming over to your place!
Aww, and here, I was thinking
of doing it at Isumi's place.
What?!
A-At Isumi's place?
That would be fine with
me. Let us study together.
I-If you say so, Isumi. I won't
mind keeping you company.
So, sorry, but you go on
home without me, Hayate.
Right...
I have some free time now...
I guess I'll at least go check it out.
Kendo Training Hall
Having said that, surely it's not going to
turn out that Hinagiku's really waiting there...
Uh, was there a "Tree of Legend"-ish thing
in front of the kendo training hall?
Or why are there cherry blossom petals
in the air when it's only March?
Or like, that's not a cherry
blossom tree to begin with...
I'm going to ignore all those
jabs that don't matter and...
H-Hinagiku...
H-Hayate!
Hinagiku, what are you doing here?
Wh-What am I doing?
I'm just here for the kendo. Obviously!
What are you doing here, Hayate?
Uh, um, could it be...
Could it be...
...that this letter is from you, after all?
Huh?
I've been waiting for you, Ayasaki!
Oh, you're Mystery Kendo Team Member A!
Who are you calling Kendo Team Member A?!
Don't treat me like I'm a nameless character!
What are you doing here, Azumamiya?
Miss Katsura, today, I will surely defeat
my foe, Ayasaki, right before your very eyes
and show you what I am truly capable of!
Then could it be that you
wrote this letter, Azumamiya?
So that was the punch line...
What's wrong, Ayasaki?
Yielding already, now that you've
found out that I'm your opponent?
So what is up with this
adorable letter of challenge?!
I mean, a letter of challenge
with a heart mark?!
What kind of cannon fodder
character are you?!
Don't call me a cannon fodder
character! My name is...
I know.
You coolly declared me
your rival in Episode 15,
you were lamely defeated instantly
by Hinagiku in Episode 16,
and since then, you have been
granted almost no scenes
and in Akiba's popularity poll, you ranked
lower than the mother of Mr. Hata,
who handles the title lettering.
Kotaro Azumamiya, correct?
Th-That's right!
More like, don't explain
my character unnecessarily!
Hayate...
Could it be that you thought
I wrote that letter?
N-No, I would never!
Oh, please, as if I would think that.
After all, you would never do
something so girly like that.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
What do you mean that I would
never do anything girly?
No, there wasn't really any
deep meaning behind that...
Then what meaning was there?!
So I've angered you again?!
Looks like you've even
alienated Miss Katsura.
Serves you right.
Never mind me.
Why don't you go keep him company instead?
H-Hinagiku?!
Hear that, Ayasaki?!
Looks like Miss Katsura wants to see
me win a cool victory over you, too!
I would ask you to do so as well.
As one butler to another.
Please serve as the Young Master's opponent.
In these long 2.5 half-seasons,
the Young Master has endured
training from Hell!
And he has finally discovered
the secret to defeating you!
For Azumamiya to fight against me?
Precisely.
For the wimpy Little Master Azumamiya
to challenge someone to a fight
of his own will is rare indeed.
To turn your back on that would make
you less of a man, would it not?
Y-You have a point...
Besides, if you were to refuse to fight,
the bill for this shower of flower petals
to be sent to Little Master Azumamiya
would get sent to the
Sanzenin family instead...
Himuro, do I still need to keep going?
Please hang in there, Little Master
Taiga. It will be over soon.
Fine. I will be your opponent, Azumamiya.
Okay! I'll do my best for you, Himuro!
Most gallant of you, Ayasaki!
A secret technique he devised
just to defeat me...
What kind of technique could it be?
Here goes.
He discarded his bamboo sword?! Don't
tell me he's going to fight unarmed?!
The secret technique that I devised...
This is it!
Huh?
My turn!
A river!
Um, what is the meaning of this?
It's obvious, isn't it?! It's
a cat's cradle competition!
Huh?!
The secret that the Young Master discovered
over the course of the 2.5 half-seasons...
It was that in the final analysis,
he had no chance of winning at kendo!
Such being the case, he came
up with the ultimate strategy
of defeating you in something
that he most excels at!
That is the Little Master Azumamiya for you.
Truly a wimpy strategy in the extreme.
Just how lame of a Nobita are you?
What's wrong, Ayasaki?
Admitting defeat already?
You leave me no choice.
I did accept your challenge, after all...
The Murasame Liger from "Zoids Genesis"!
What the heck is that?!
Or rather, how can you
make something like that?
There is no such thing as
the impossible for a butler.
Wh-Why you...
I lost...
All my hard work, wearing through tens of
thousands of loops of yarn, has been for naught!
Just what kind of hard work was that?
Young Master!
Nonohara...
Allowing a single defeat to
break your spirit is pitiful!
I believe I taught you sternly
that if you are a man,
you will keep crawling back up with
dogged resolve until you are victorious!
You're right! I can't go to pieces
just because I've lost once!
So you understand?
And so...
I challenge you, Taiga Ohkouchi!
What?!
That is my Young Master!
Choosing and challenging an opponent
who seems to offer certain victory!
You have hit upon an excellent plan!
H-Himuro!
Interesting.
Please do not underestimate my Little
Master Taiga's abilities, Nonohara.
How does it end up like this?!
Um, would it be all right if I left already?
But they're not listening.
That reminds me. Where did Hinagiku go?
Oh, really! Really! Really! I swear!
Why did I get my hopes up that
this letter was from Hayate?!
Oh, it pisses me off!
It's like I got dumped,
and I don't even like him.
Man, being young is so great!
That is all.
NOT ON DVD!
Continuing on to the second half, leaving
the Azumamiya vs Ohkouchi fight unfinished.
I did my best, but it was no use!
(Ganbattan dakedo dame datta!)
Tarutaru monk recommended!
(Tarutaru monku suishou shimasu!)
It's no use!
How can it be that I can't
focus on my studies?!
When you're in a funk, it really is best to
go out into town for a change of scene...
Say, what do you want for your birthday?
As long as you're with me, Gintan,
I don't want anything else!
Yeah, you're right.
The best way to spend birthdays is to be
lovey-dovey and be with that special someone.
Yup, yup.
It would suck not to have that special
someone to share your birthday with!
Sheesh! Showoffs!
It's so stupid.
What does it matter if you have a
boyfriend or not on your birthday?
H-Hinagiku!
Hayate, what are you doing here?
I thought I might look
for a new study guide...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Wh-Why are you suddenly apologizing?
Uh, I don't really know, but...
I mean, it seems I made you
angry again yesterday, so...
Do you really feel bad about it?
What?
Then treat me to some tea.
Huh?
Thank you for waiting.
Please enjoy.
The cappuccinos are delicious here.
I see...
I wonder what's suddenly
gotten into Hinagiku.
It's rare to see you in
normal clothes, Hayate.
What? D-Do you think so?
Yes, they look very good on you.
Thank you very much.
Um, you look very cute yourself, Hinagiku.
What?
H-Hayate, what are you
saying all of a sudden?!
Uh, no, I mean, that's not it.
It's your outfit. Your outfit.
Your outfit.
What?
Oh...
Oh, my outfit.
What? Um, what's gotten into you, Hinagiku?
So, did you do all right on your exams?
No...
Come on, don't give me that sad look.
Never mind all that. Let's
forget about the bad stuff
and go for a refreshing change of scenery!
What?
The neverending blue sky
With a heart and mind fresh as can be
Can you get me?
It's so cute!
I love it! I want it!
Just watch! I'm going to get it for sure!
Uh-huh...
And that flower was of an innocent color
Aw! And I spent everything I had on me, too!
Making the petals sway with humming
You want that stuffed animal that badly?
I guess you have a girly side to you, too.
If you're all show, then goodbye
That's the second time!
What?
You said the same thing
at school yesterday, too!
That's not "love", right?
Something about how I'd never
do anything girly or something.
The thing that makes me who I am
Oh!
N-No, that was...
That one moment
And I still hadn't asked you
what you really thought.
Make it blossom
Huh?
Admit it. You thought that I'd
actually written that letter, right?
What?!
Power of Flower
You did, didn't you?
And someday, even that bud
No, I would never think such a thing!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!
Will bloom large right in
the middle of your heart
That I'm really not girly?!
Oh, there I go, opening my big mouth again!
I-It's not like I'm seriously mad.
Power of Flower
At first, I thought that
letter was from you, too...
Stupid! Stupid! Go get the
hell out of here, Hayate!
Okay, bye-bye!
It seems I've angered Hinagiku yet again.
Why am I always like this?
What am I doing?
We were having fun and I just had
to go and wreck it all on my own.
I'm willful and I hate to lose...
I've never shown my girly side...
Not in front of Hayate.
A kitten!
Wh-What should I do?
I can't go rescue it when
it's so high up there!
Wait, I feel like I was in a
similar situation once before...
Hey, why am I remembering that now?!
Oh, you can't go that way!
I'm coming to save you!
No looking down!
For now, just focus on my target overhead!
Come on, come over here.
There, there. Good kitty.
Nothing to be scared of now.
Thank goodness.
I'll get you back to your
mother right away...
Help! Someone!
I would come to your
rescue if you'd just ask.
H-Hayate...
I would come to your rescue...
Hayate!
Are you all right, Hinagiku?
What?
Hayate?
P-Pardon me.
I-It's fine, it's no big deal. I-I
should be the one thanking you.
Um...
Uh, here.
Huh?
You went to the trouble
of getting that for me?
I feel like you're always
helping me out somehow.
I told you, didn't I?
That I would come to your
rescue if you'd just ask.
Well, I'm going this way, so...
Yes.
Thanks for keeping me company today.
I had a lot of fun.
Oh, please! I feel the same way.
Say, if I call for you again,
would you come for me?
Yes. Please call for me whenever you like.
Since I'm an expert at crane games.
Then, see you again tomorrow.
Goodbye.
What's gotten into you, Hayate?
Poor me...
What are you brooding on self-pity for?
Are you that unsure of
how you did on the exams?
No, that is not it...
My wallet is completely empty
due to an unplanned expenditure.
Huh?
Nagi, what shall we get
for Hinagiku's birthday?
I'll leave it to you.
Um...
Is Hinagiku's birthday coming up?
Yes, it's March 3rd.
I-I had no idea.
Then, do you suppose I should
get her a present as well?
Why would you give Hinagiku a present?!
And anyway, didn't you
just say you were broke?!
Yes, right...
Besides, before you think about Hinagiku...
Thank you, Hayate.
Will Hinagiku call upon that special
someone on her special day?
But that is a different story.
Maybe it'll get told at some
other time in some other place.
So, next time, they'll be battling
against really ordinary stories.
Yay! I won again!
I-I have lost!
Goodness! You are so good at
this, Little Master Taiga!
No, no, Young Master Azumamiya's
wimpiness is truly without equal!
How long are you guys going to keep at this?
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
This is Hinagiku Katsura's Butler Report!
Hinagiku Katsura's
Lettering by Shizuka Itou
Butler Report
Hello, I am Hinagiku Katsura.
What did you all think of today's
"Hayate the Combat Butler" episode?
I think I might have had the
most lines ever in that one.
So, I got put in charge of the Butler
Report for this episode, too,
but I'm not sure what to talk about...
Wait, what's this image?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What is this?!
When did you get this?!
Hey, come on out, whoever's
responsible for this!
Oh, see you later!
Preview
Hello, there, everyone. How've you been?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
The next episode will feature us,
the Student Council Girl Trio.
Better hurry up and go buy a Blu-ray
player equipped with a DVR!
Hey, what in the world is the episode about?
You will have to wait and see.
All right! Stand by until
the next episode airs!
Next time, "Ordinary Stories"!
I'll be making a solid appearance
as well, so not to worry.
Ordinary Stories
Come Fusion! Grand Cross! with "Hayate
the Combat Butler" again next time!