She doesn't realize that Haruka is in love with Nayu, not Komachi.
I can't let him get away with it after all!
W-What's wrong?
Nothing, I just remembered what happened this morning.
Point One!
Ahh, I guess I just can't beat you, Yako.
Your strength isn't bad!
You're just too indecisive, Kota.
Hey, that's the men's locker room, Yako!
Yeah, I couldn't find the key to the girl's locker room this morning,
so I got changed in here.
Recently we're the only ones assigned to morning practice.
It doesn't really matter!
B-But!
By the way, how's your Kendo club doing?
You just started, right?
I heard you were in the top four at last year's kendo tournament.
Hey!
Why don't you at least respond when someone's talking to you?
Why are you facing that way?
W-What do you mean, why? Aren't you embarrassed, Yako?
Changing in front of a man.
No, not really.
What's this all of a sudden?
I don't know about the other boys, but it's you we're talking about, Kota!
I-It's not like I'm happy seeing you in your underwear anyways.
Hey, I can't let that one pass.
I just told the truth!
You don't have any boobs, but you're still wearing some bra like that!
What?!
You don't even need underwear like that, Yako!
Now you listen here.
This isn't just 'some bra'.
It's a respectable sports bra!
And that's how it went down.
He's hopeless, right?
Y-Yeah... that may be...
Unforgivable!
Sports bras are wonderful! He just doesn't get it!
That's what I mean!
You better not underestimate sports bras, Kota!
Yeah!
Recruiting translators for the upcoming shows. Visit #ryuumaru@irc.rizon.net or contact us at Ryuumaru.Fansubs@gmail.com
Why did he attack me like that anyways?
Maybe it felt awkward?
Awkward?
Yeah. Komachi-kun said a while ago...
As a boy, I'll see underwear as something erotic.
He said that boys can't help but see underwear as something erotic.
That crybaby Kota?
No way!
What's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
I think Nayu-chan is right.
Even if he is your childhood friend, he's still a middle-school boy.
You know he's like family.
I got it! Let's ask Komachi-kun.
Huh? Cat-eyes?
Yeah, I think he would be pretty easy to ask.
Thanks to him, I don't get as nervous anymore when talking to boys.
He even gives me good advice for the Underwear Appreciation Society.
Wow, he must be pretty smart.
Yeah! Yeah!
I wonder what this feeling is?
I felt something in my chest for a second...
For those who are practicing swimming, please stay on the right side of the pool!
Okay!
Is that Jinguji-san?
She's pretty good at sports.
And there's Hayama-san.
She said her goal was to swim 25 meters this summer.
This is another page in the book of youth!
Huh?
Shiraishi-san?
Sensei...
Why are you sitting all the way over here?
Um...
Are you not feeling well by any chance?
No, that's not it at all, but...
It's just that... Sometimes... My chest tightens up right here.
It tightens?
Is this because my boobs are getting bigger?
Geez... It's all their fault that I am behind on my studies from last semester.
I'll have to catch up this summer.
S-Sorry! Are you okay?
Hayama!
You again?!
When does it happen?
Well, you see...
Geez! How did you send a kickboard flying?!
Do it properly!
Sorry, I was playing around with it a bit, and it went flying!
What, are you a little kid?!
Here!
Thanks!
Wait!
What is it?
Today's the summer festival. You're coming, right?
Y-Yeah. We're going as the Underwear Appreciation Society, right?
Yeah. Are you going to wear a yukata too?
TL Note: A yukata is a casual summer kimono.
Keigo-san has one.
It might be a bit big, but I think you could wear it if we shorten the sash.
Right?
Umm... About that question you just asked...
The reason your chest hurts might be because your heart is growing.
My heart?
People's hearts develop along with their bodies as they grow up.
That may be the reason why your chest tightens up, Shiraishi-san.
Okay, okay! All I have to do is come to your house tonight, right?
Yeah!
See you!
Okay!
I still don't understand it very well.
You're right, it might be a difficult problem even for adults,
so it might be best to slowly find your way to the answer.
Okay.
Thank you very much, Sensei!
She's a middle-schooler. It's normal for her to be interested in boys.
I was the same way!
My chest used to tighten up just by seeing him!
He was always my shining prince!
You know... Mizuno-Sensei sometimes creeps me out.
Yeah.
Summer is bad for makeup.
Class Rep...
Did he just ignore me?! What the hell!
I can't do it!
I can't just dive into the pool!
And you call yourself a man?
I-I-I'm not a man!
Hayama-san?
Oh, so that's how it is!
Y-Yako-chan, you don't have to take those off!
B-But I thought you weren't supposed to wear panties with a yukata!
It used to be like that it the past...
but people wear underwear under their Susoyoke nowadays.
TL Note: Susoyoke is a thin half-slip-like piece of underwear worn by women under the Kimono.
It doesn't matter as long as the panty-line doesn't show through.
There you go!
In stead of wearing something as annoying as that, why don't you just wear a t-back thong?
I didn't think of that!
How bold!
Isn't it tight?
B-But, isn't it a bit too soon for a middle-schooler to be wearing that?
Even elementary-schoolers wear these.
And you're a middle-aged woman wearing a jersey.
Ah, here Sensei!
It's a bra worn with Japanese clothes.
Huh? My boobs look slimmer than usual.
Yes. A woman with tits like yours will look better in a yukata when wearing that.
The trick to wearing Japanese clothing is to have as little curvature as possible!
It's Underwear Appreciation Society 24/7!
That's Nayu-chan for you!
She can't put a yukata on properly, though.
Nayu-chan, I'm going to pull on the collar a little.
Okay.
That's amazing, Haruka-chan!
Huh?
I'm impressed!
That's...
I've just gotten used to doing this since I was a child.
I think you're much more amazing than me with your extensive knowledge of underwear, Nayu-chan!
R-Really?
I received a message.
Kota?
He must be trying to make up with you!
Well if that's what he says, then I guess it can't be helped-
Idiot! You don't even have any tits to put into a bra!
That asshole!
Who are you calling an idiot, idiot?!
I'll remember this! I'll beat your ass at the dojo tomorrow!
What's up with her? Did something happen?
Well...
Jinguji-san is at fault!
Hey, come in.
Okay, you can get changed in here.
Okay.
Why do I have to apologize?!
Isn't it obvious?!
Now, now, calm down you two.
Shut up, Sensei!
Alright!
They're rather loud, aren't they?
What are you doing?
You shouldn't have screamed like that in front of that Kota boy like you did just now.
Geez, I don't get you.
You just won't get how much it hurts to not be viewed as a member of the opposite sex...
...until you experience it first-hand.
Not being seen as a member of the opposite sex...
Yako-chan.
Maybe that's what hurt Kota-kun's feelings.
W-What do you think, Komachi-kun?
I think it goes both ways.
O-Oh, I see.
Nayu-chan, do you want to go check out the Goldfish Scoop over there?
Ah, Sure!
I'm going to go buy something. You guys go on ahead.
We'll lose you, Amahara-san!
I'm not a kid, I won't get lost!
These kids have a lot on their minds!
Speaking of which, he said that he got called in to his office...
I wonder if he'll make it in time for the fireworks.
Ah, watching fireworks with him!
How beautiful!
Yes, but you are so much more beautiful!
Ah, Um... My tits are gonna pop out!
Don't worry.
My hands will be your bra.
What would I do if that actually happened?
Huh?
E-Everyone?! Were did you go?
Ah, look at these goldfish!
They're beautiful!
Their tails sure are long!
Want to give it a go?
Kota...
You should talk to him!
Huh?
But...
Men are stubborn creatures,
we have a hard time apologizing.
Cat-eyes?!
What's going on?
Give him a chance too!
That's right!
This isn't like you, Yako-chan!
Nayu...
I think so too!
Haruka...
He's your childhood friend, right?
You should treasure him!
Alright. Dwelling on it like this really isn't like me.
Sorry! I'll be right back!
Alright!
I hope they can work things out.
Yeah.
By the way, why are you wearing a mask?
That's gonna be kept a secret from you, Hayama-san!
H-Hey, what are you doing?!
Just come with me!
Please stop going off on your own guys!
Got one!
Wow, you're good at this, Sensei!
Amazing!
Hayama-san didn't see your perverted face while you were looking at her, did she?
I'll charge you for it later.
H-How much?
100 yen.
What, are you an old man in a sales shop?!
Class Rep, summer is the season where girls open up!
Why don't you try asking Hayama out on a date?
Geez, you're completely red again!
You really are fun to tease!
They really get along well, don't they?
I wonder if it's because they're in the same class?
Yeah, you're probably right.
Ah! There's a lot of them right here too!
Which one do you like, Haruka-chan?
That doesn't bother you, Nayu-chan?
What?
Well...
How do you feel about Komachi-kun?
H-H-Haruka-chan!
It tickles!
This really sucks...
It's okay to do it over here.
Sorry, Haruka-chan!
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna fix your bra first, so I'm gonna stick my hands in, okay?
Alright.
Sorry! Did I hurt you?
Not at all.
What's up with this sound?
It's even louder than when we did the bra fitting.
Please... don't let Nayu-chan hear it!
Alright, it's OK!
Huh? Aren't your underwear a little mature today?
Yeah. I don't really know why, but I've started wanting to wear stuff like this lately.
Could it be that you're in love with someone, Haruka-chan?
Huh?!
W-Why do you ask?!
I just remembered that my grandma once told me that love and underwear are inseparable even if you tried.
So I was wondering if you had fallen in love with someone since you changed your underwear style.
Sorry if I was way off!
W-What's wrong?
Did the goldfish bite you somewhere?!
No! That's not it...
I... might be in love with someone.
Huh? What did you say?
Well... you know...
I Lo-
Maybe they're around here...
Hayama-san, Shiraishi-san!
We're over here!
There you are! Here, I brought you a towel!
I got a message from Keigo-san.
From Senpai?!
It seems he'll be here soon.
Umm...
You should go meet up with him.
Like I said-
But...
I'll be okay. And Sensei's here too!
Um, I can go if you li--
Okay, I'll be right back then!
Be careful...
Why did you bring me all the way out here?
S-S-Sorry about this morning...
F-For showing you such pathetic underwear...
N-No, that's not what I meant...
So, what do you think about these underwear?!
I didn't do anything!
What are you doing?
You idiot!
Who'd show their underwear off in front of a boy?
Even if you are my childhood friend!
Yako!
I'll be more careful from now on!
I apologize as well.
I said some pretty terrible things.
I was trying to make things right in the text as well,
but...
Cat-eyes was right!
Huh?
Now we're even!
I won't go easy on you starting tomorrow!
I wouldn't want it any other way!
Ow!
Gotcha!
Geez...
You should never let your guard down! That's the way of the warrior!
Your leg's showing!
Nayu-chan!
Nayu!
I worked things out with Kota!
Huh? What's wrong?
Hayama-san got lost!
Oh, Keigo-san?
They seem to have missed each other!
She's not answering her phone!
Hey, don't cry Haruka!
Anyways, let's look for her!
Yeah.
Geez, can't she do anything herself?
Sorry! I was supposed to be keeping an eye on her...
No, it's not your fault.
It's alright.
I'll stay with you until your mom finds you.
Here's a candied apple!
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
Bye-bye!
Sorry, everyone...
The fireworks are over...
They do fireworks every year, so we can come together again next year.
This year, and the year after next.
I want to go to festivals with Nayu-chan and everyone else like this, even when we become adults.
You guys!
Yeah, stop causing us so much trouble though.
Huh?
I dropped my cellphone!
Don't tell me you just noticed?!
Yeah...
That settles it! You're treating us all to chocolate bananas!
Ah, come on!
We went all the way to the lost and found for you.
You've made some wonderful friends, Nayu.
Breasts apparently come in all shapes and sizes.
Oh really?
There are bell-shaped, plate-shaped, rock-shaped, and squash-shaped breasts!
Like hanging squash?
I don't want those no matter how big they are!
Don't miss out on the next episode of Chu-bra!
Recruiting translators for the upcoming shows. Visit #ryuumaru@irc.rizon.net or contact us at Ryuumaru.Fansubs@gmail.com