I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I received was a courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
With our new encounter, our destinies
have been set in motion once again.
We're both traveling through a forest of bewilderment.
However, I'm sure the small light illuminating
our feelings lies within both our hearts.
I've decided to believe in that light and travel
that path, even if it ends in the darkest skies.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
It appears the battle is underway at their location.
The core of the Lost Logia is rated A+.
Their actions seem haphazard and insecure, and as you
can see, they're using their special attacks erratically.
This emergency affects us on a dimensional level.
We'll have to collect it as soon as possible.
Enforcer Chrono Hallaoun. Can you make it out there?
The transfer coordinates are already set.
Given the command, I can go at any time.
Well then, Chrono, I order you to go to the combat site,
cease all hostilities, and retrieve the Lost Logia.
Listen to their explanation of
the circumstances, as well.
Understood, Captain.
You be careful out there, okay?
Yes... I'll be going now...
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Stop!
Commencing combat here is too dangerous!
I am a government official from the Time-Space
Administration Bureau, Chrono Hallaoun.
I'll need a detailed explanation about this from you.
Time-Space Administration Bureau?
Firstly, withdraw your weapons!
If you continue to fight here...
Fate! We have to withdraw! Get away from there!
Fate!
Fate-chan!
Don't!
Stop! Don't fire!
We're going to run for it, Fate! Hold on tight!
Combat has ceased.
One of the two combatants has escaped.
Can we trace her?
She concealed her escape route by transferring
multiple times. It doesn't look like we can follow her.
Is that so?
Well, he ended their battle in time, and we
also managed to secure a Lost Logia.
I think everything ended well.
And besides, it seems like we'll
find out what really happened.
Chrono, good job.
I'm sorry, I let the other one get away.
Well... that's all right.
Oh, and I'd like to hear their story, so I was wondering
if you could bring those two to the Asura?
Understood, I will return momentarily.
Yuuno-kun... Yuuno-kun, what is this place...?
We seem to be inside the Time-Space Administration
Bureau's Dimensional Cruise Patrol Warship.
Umm... to put it simply, we're inside a ship that
moves through space between dimensions.
I... I don't think that's really simplifying it much...
Umm, let's see... along with the world you live in...
...there are hundreds of others similar
to it, including the world I come from.
This ship and the people of the Time-Space
Administration Bureau travel between them...
...and supervise the affairs of those worlds when
they interfere with dimensional space.
I see...
Ah, you must be uncomfortable in that outfit.
You can release your barrier jacket and device here.
Ah, that's right.
Y-You're right. Well then...
Also... shouldn't you return to your true form, too?
Ah, yes! Now that you mention it, I guess I will.
I've been in this form for so long
that I'd completely forgotten.
I guess it's been a while since you've
seen me in this form, huh, Nanoha?
N-Nanoha?
Yuuno-kun, you're... Y-Yuuno-kun, you're a...!
Ah, what the heck's going on?!
B-But w-weren't you just a... no way!!
Did your images of each other just change?
Umm... N-Nanoha.
When we first met, I was in this form, wasn't I...?
No, no! Y-You were a ferret to begin with!
A-Ah! T-That's right, isn't it!
Ah, sorry about that! Sorry!
I never did show you my true form.
Yeah! You never did! You really surprised me.
Umm... can I say something?
I don't know what's going on between you two, but...
...the captain is waiting, and we'd like to
hear your story as soon as possible.
A-Ah... yes.
Excuse us.
Well then, this way please.
Captain, I've arrived with them.
Good job.
Well, please come in. Make yourselves at home.
Go ahead.
Y-Yes.
I see. Is that so?
You're the one who excavated the
Lost Logia... the Jewel Seeds.
Yes... and I went there to retrieve them.
How noble.
But at the same time, it was also reckless!
Umm... just what are the Lost Logia?
Ah... if I told you they were relics of a lost world,
you probably wouldn't understand...
So let's see...
Within dimensional space, there exist countless worlds.
Countless worlds that are all
born and grow on their own.
Among them, there existed a world
that was just too evolved.
Because their technology and science was too
advanced, they ended up destroying their own world.
All that remained were the dangerous
technological relics of the lost world.
The general term given to one of
those relics is a "Lost Logia."
How they're supposed to be used is unknown,
but depending on the user...
...it can harness enough power to not only destroy
a single world, but all of dimensional space.
It's an incredibly dangerous technology.
We must handle those items properly, and they must
be stored in a proper place for safekeeping.
The Lost Logia you two are searching
for... the Jewel Seeds...
...are crystallized forms of energy
for dimensional interference.
If several Seeds were activated together, a dimensional
distortion would occur and, worst case scenario...
...a dimensional dislocation could be created
because they're so dangerous.
When you fought that black mage, that flash of light
was an explosion which had a huge impact on space.
That was a dimensional distortion.
Even using a couple thousandths of its power
can cause that large of a disaster.
The effect of gathering and activating several of them
to their fullest extent at once is unfathomable.
I've heard of that happening once before...
In the year 462 going by our old lunar calendar,
a dimensional dislocation occurred.
Yes. That was a terrible incident.
Many of its adjacent worlds were
completely annihilated.
It was a horrible tragedy that
will always stain our history.
We can't let that happen again.
So, I'd like to inform you that the
Time-Space Administration Bureau...
...will take over all authority regarding
the Lost Logia, the Jewel Seeds.
It'd be best if you two just forgot
about what happened...
...returned to your separate worlds,
and continued to live your lives.
But, that's...
This incident involves dimensional interference!
It's not a simple matter that we could
let civilians get involved with.
But...
Well, we brought this up so suddenly,
so you probably can't think clearly.
So why don't you two think it over this evening
and discuss it between yourselves?
We can discuss everything again in the morning.
I'll take you back. Where we
were before is okay, right?
Yes...
For the time being, should we go home...?
Yeah...
And umm... I guess you're about my age?
Ah... yeah... probably.
Umm... are you mad about this...?
I really didn't mean for things to turn out this way, but...
...it ended up looking like I was
keeping it a secret from you...
Oh... not at all. I was a little surprised, but that's all.
Umm... I'm sorry. And thank you.
F-For now...
It seems more convenient for
me to stay in this form, so...
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Let's go have dinner, and then do some thinking...
about what to do from this point on.
They're amazing! Both of them are AAA class mages!
Yeah...
This girl in white seems like she'd be
your type, Chrono. She's pretty cute.
Amy! I don't care about stuff like that...
Looking at the average of this girl's
magical power... it's 1.27 million!
And the girl in black's is... 1.43 million!
When they release their greatest
powers, those numbers triple!
They exceed you in magical power
statistics alone, huh, Chrono?
That's not all there is to magic!
There's also the ability to apply yourself
to the situation at hand...
...and sound judgement when faced
with a problem, you know!
Well, of course.
I trust you. After all, you must be the most talented
of us all here on the Asura, Chrono-kun.
Ah, Captain.
Ah. You're looking at their data.
Yes.
They're amazing, aren't they?
If that much magical power flowed into a Lost Logia...
...a dimensional distortion would undoubtedly occur.
Those kids... we now know the reason why Nanoha-san
and Yuuno-kun were gathering the Jewel Seeds, but...
...I wonder why this girl in black
was gathering them as well...?
She looked... pretty desperate.
I wonder if she has a strong reason
for what she's doing?
Reason, huh...
She's such a young girl...
She still looks young enough to be
relying on her mother's love...
...if she's being raised like a normal girl...
Don't move.
Now that the Time-Space Administration Bureau's
shown up, we won't be able to continue.
Let's run away... we'll go somewhere
where we can be alone...
I can't do that...
But even though we managed to
get away, he's a top class mage!
If he really tries to come after us, we might not be
able to stay here forever without being noticed!
And that demon woman... your mother keeps
saying all those things that make no sense!
And she's so cruel to you, too!
Don't speak badly of Mother...
I will speak badly of her!
Because I'm so worried about you!
Whenever you're sad, my heart hurts so much
it feels like it's being ripped to pieces.
Whenever you're crying, my eyes and nose get all
blurry and drippy, so much that I lose myself!
I don't want you to be in pain or to cry anymore, Fate!
I guess that's because you and me
are linked in mind and spirit.
I'm sorry... if you're ever hurting, I'll be sure to
stop myself from being sad, to stop crying.
I just want you to smile and be happy, Fate!
Why... why can't you understand?!
Thank you, Arf...
But you see... I want to grant my mother's wish.
And it's not just for my mother.
I'm sure... it's for myself, as well.
So... just a little more...
There's only a little more until we reach the end,
so will you give me your best until then?
Promise me...
...that you're not doing this because
that woman's telling you to...
...but you're doing your best because
it's for you, and you alone.
Then I'll definitely always protect you.
Yeah.
So... Nanoha and I would like to help you.
Help us, huh...
Even without me, I'm sure Nanoha's magical
power will increase your strength.
In collecting the Jewel Seeds, and
fighting against that girl...
...or whichever way you choose,
I'm pretty sure she'll really help you.
I see. You sure have thought things over.
In that case, I guess it'd be all right.
M-Mom- Captain!
Let's have them help us. I'd like to save our
trump card until the last minute, if possible.
Isn't that right, Enforcer Chrono?
Yes...
We have two conditions.
Both of you must put yourselves in the hands of the
Time-Space Administration Bureau for the time being...
And to always follow our instructions.
I trust that's all right?
I understand.
Nanoha, it's been decided.
Yeah... thanks, Yuuno-kun.
Well then, Momoko, Nanoha...
Kyouya and I are going out back now.
Yeah, will you be training again tonight?
Yeah.
Be careful!
Yep.
Now then, shall we go?
Yeah!
It's been a while, so I'm not going to hold back!
Ah! Wait, wait! Let me watch!
If you're gonna come, hurry up.
Yeah! Just wait a second!
Miyuki, I see you're still the same as ever!
Well then, that's that.
Yep.
So... what was that important thing
you wanted to talk to me about?
Yeah...
I told my mom about what happened from the
day I met Yuuno-kun all the way up to today.
I couldn't really say the stuff about magic and
Yuuno-kun's true form, but... I told her all that I could.
And then I told her that because of everything,
I had to leave the house...
It's possible that it might be dangerous, but...
I want to see what I've begun with
all my friends through to the end.
Yes...
It might be enough to make you worry...
Well... you know that I'll always worry about you.
Because I'm your mother.
Of course I'll be worried about you, Nanoha.
But you know...
If you were still thinking about which path to take...
...I think I'd probably tell you that you can't
do anything dangerous like that.
But you've already decided for yourself, haven't you?
You want to finish what you've
started with your friends.
And you still want to try talking things
over with that other girl you met.
Yeah...
Well... have a nice trip, and don't
regret anything you do.
I'll bring your father and brother around
to my way of thinking, too.
Okay... thank you, Mom!
I can no longer turn back...
This is the path I've chosen...
This is what I truly want to do!
Hurry... hurry, Fate...
The promised land... Alhazred is awaiting us...
My... our utopia!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
Yuuno-kun and I have ended up
staying with the TSAB on their warship, the Asura!
An incredible reaction of the Jewel
Seeds, beyond anything we've ever seen before...
And the reunion of
Nanoha and Fate!
Just what does
Fate-chan's mother want...?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Nine:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean!
Lyrical Magical won't lose!