I'm so stupid...
I just wanted to get rid of him at first,
but, now...
There she is!
Good. She's alone.
All right!
I've decided!
I'll go back to the way I was,
before I met Koutarou!
I was fine before!
He's not my friend!
That's what I have to tell myself...
Now!
Get her!
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Wait up!
Jeez, where'd Sanae go, anyway?
Precious Charms
It's almost lunchtime.
Not here, either.
You're alone today.
Hm?
Sakuraba-senpai.
Hello there.
You're not with the girls from yesterday?
Oh, I'm kind of doing my own thing today.
Did something happen?
Well...
Where did she go?
No, stay away!
What are you doing? Let me go!
You guys are ghosts, too, right?
What are you trying to do?
Resistance is futile.
We hired these guys.
They're wandering spirits.
You're the perverts from yesterday!
We're not perverts!
We're ghost hunters!
Ghost hunters?
Yes, we capture ghosts and sell them.
That's our job.
You're going to sell me?
Yes.
A ghost like you, with a stable and high-density form, is very valuable.
There's people out there who'd
pay a pretty penny for you.
Money...
No, I don't want to be sold!
Oh, no. I have to save her.
But...
There's a lot of weird things over there...
I don't know what to do, Satomi-san...
Someone... Someone...
I think it'd be bad for you give up.
Sakuraba-senpai...
That's right.
I'm the magical girl who
stands for what's right,
Rainbow Yurika!
Come to me, Angel—
Here it is!
A miracle given to us by the cosplay gods!
I see, you fought with your friend.
Yeah.
She got mad, took off, and
hasn't come back yet...
Do you have any idea why?
Yeah, I guess I do, but...
Yeah, we are enemies.
I just told it like it was,
and I guess that hurt her...
How it was...
We're always arguing about
the same thing, though.
So, I'm not sure why
she got so mad this time.
I think I understand how she may feel.
Huh?
Open up!
Let me out!
I said, let me out!
I'm not letting you sell me!
Just give it up already.
You...
Hey now, don't give me that look.
You might get a nice place
to live after you're sold.
Of course I won't!
You mean you have a place
to call home right now?
I do!
I have a nice place at Corona House, Apt 106!
You must be causing the people
there all sorts of problems.
Problems?
You seriously think they want you there?
Huh?
Try thinking about it for a second.
Who wants to live in a place with a ghost?
I...
That's not...
We're just a nuisance to the living.
A nuisance...
But, I...
Why do you think they sell charms?
It's because they're trying to get rid of us.
Some of them might accept that we're here,
but it's not because they want to.
Not in the slightest.
That's reality.
That's... reality...
Well, listen.
We're both club members, right?
Yeah.
But, I could also say that
we're strangers that happen
to be in the same club.
Huh? But...
But that's how it is, isn't it?
And I'd feel bad if you said
something similar to me.
What about you?
I wouldn't like it, either.
That's what you did to your friend, though.
Even if what you said was the truth,
you've both spent a lot of time together,
and things come across
differently when you're closer.
I mean, I want you to
think of me as a friend,
and I'm sure your friend does, as well.
She wants me to...
Am I wrong?
No, but...
I'll put it this way.
Did you come all the way out here
to look for a mere stranger?
Thank you, Sakuraba-senpai!
Sanae!
Hey!
Where are you?
Huh?
One, two, one, two...
Oh, Satomi-kun.
We meet again.
What's going on?
It was a chance meeting.
I told you I wouldn't let Yurika-chan go.
Wouldn't let her go?
Hm? Yurika?
Could you let me talk alone
with Yurika for a second?
Hm? Well, I guess it's okay.
Ghost hunters?
That's right.
There were a bunch of ghost-looking things.
They took Sanae-chan away before I could do anything.
Ghosts...
All right, got it!
Thanks for the info.
Satomi-san, I...
I want you to save me, too—
What?
Sanae was taken by those
perverts from yesterday?
Yeah.
You guys got attacked yesterday,
but they were really after Sanae.
How awful.
Also, it seems they have
ghosts as their underlings.
Sanae couldn't get away, supposedly.
I see.
So, we're up against ghosts?
We need to figure out where
Sanae-sama is before we do anything.
Oh, I have just the thing.
Hm?
A ghost locator!
I'm sure we can find Sanae-chan with this.
Great work, Shizuka!
Let's go.
All right, let's do this.
Why did it explode?
The etheric oscillations
caused a malfunction.
It was so old it couldn't
handle the oscillations.
In simpler language, please?
Sorry about that.
No, it's not Shizuka's fault.
Anyway, we need to come up with another plan.
But, our technology doesn't...
In that case, leave it to me.
Karama, Korama!
Right!
Eye beams!
Why?
Don't worry.
I'm just doing this so you owe me later.
It would be a stain on the Mastil family
for me to stand idly by.
I can't forgive anyone who does
something improper to a girl.
Leave it to us, Satomi-kun!
We'll get rid of those
ghost-hunting perverts for you!
You guys...
Scan complete!
We're ready!
All right!
Let's go get Sanae back!
I feel bad for you.
No matter how long you wait,
no one's going to come for you.
I-I'm not really waiting for anyone.
Yeah, right.
I can see it all over your face.
You still have hope.
I'm sure he told you that you
were the only one he could trust,
and you fell for it.
No, Koutarou isn't—
You think he wouldn't betray you?
I know how you feel.
Huh?
I went through the same thing.
So, this is it?
I waited for someone just
like you, a long time ago.
But, I was betrayed.
He was happy to be rid of me.
That's why you shouldn't get your hopes up.
A sad, homeless life,
no one waiting for you to return.
That's what we ghosts live.
No one to go home to,
no one waiting for us...
Living humans and ghosts
are enemies.
There's no way to convey how
we feel, nothing to be gained.
Huh?
Bro, look at this!
The trap we set upstairs...
What was that?
Too easy.
I think we might have overdone it just a bit.
Yeah...
Karama, Korama.
There's an area below us.
And stairs up ahead.
Let's go.
Right.
Yeah!
Spin! Spin!
There we go...
Ow...
I won't lose!
Sakuraba-senpai!
Fight, Yurika!
Fight!
They're coming!
Guess we'll have to use the ghosts.
Could it be Koutarou?
But, we're enemies...
No matter how close we've gotten...
He'll always hate me because I'm a nuisance.
I don't want that...
I don't want that at all!
Sanae!
Koutarou...
Are you okay, Sanae?!
Jerk!
Huh?
Why are you here?!
I didn't tell you to come!
You just think I'm a nuisance, don't you?!
Idiot!
Of course I—
Sorry to interrupt your tear-jerking reunion,
but this ghost is ours.
I think you kids should go
home before you get hurt.
That's right!
You've got to be kidding, you perverts!
I'm turning you over to the police!
Oh, that's strange.
What law have we broken, exactly?
What?! You kidnapped Sanae!
What law states we can't kidnap a ghost?
Well then, you chose the wrong
people to get involved with.
What was that?
You want to know?
We're invaders.
We don't care about the law.
That's right, I forgot.
We don't care about what this planet thinks.
Isn't that right, Ruth?
Yes.
A tenant and her landlady
are practically family.
Even if she's a ghost, that
doesn't change anything!
You're giving us Sanae back, bad guys!
Get them!
Anyone who takes them out gets a bonus!
Protect Sis!
We won't let you lay a finger on her!
Haniwa beam!
They might be weak, but there's a lot of them.
This is a nice change of pace.
I get to let loose.
You need to pay attention, Satomi-kun!
Sorry about that.
Leave this to me.
Hurry and go get Sanae-chan.
Right. Thanks.
Wait for me, Sanae!
You guys...
You shouldn't trust them.
They're your enemies.
Even if they save you today,
who knows how it'll be tomorrow?
They're going to discard you.
There's no reason to deal with that pretense.
But...
I...
I want to trust them all!
I see.
So, you're going to betray me, too.
I was so nice to you, too.
I won't forgive you...
I won't forgive you!
Come to me.
If we become one, you all will be able
to have some of this girl's power!
Want to eat...
What are you guys doing?!
Stop it!
Now, come!
Sanae!
Uh...
Sakuraba-senpai...
I'm sure she'd...
Satomi-kun!
Are you okay, Koutarou?!
Satomi-sama!
No!
Stop it!
Koutarou!
Save me, Koutar—
Sanae?!
I can feel it now...
I can feel her power!
Damn you...
How dare you do that to Sanae?!
She's mine now!
I'm not letting you take her!
There must... there must
be something I can do...
Grandma, help me...
Begone, spirits!
Let's go, Angel Halo!
Bind: Undead!
Modifier: Huge Area Effect!
End casting time!
Four times!
Did it work?
Are you sure about this?
If you use that, this girl will be gone, too.
Unfortunately for you, my Sanae
isn't that weak of a ghost.
I know.
This won't hurt Sanae.
So... I'm taking Sanae back!
Stop it!
Sanae!
Huh? I...
What? It doesn't hurt.
Safe
Family
That's right...
That's what we are.
We're enemies,
but we're more than that.
This is my...
Our charm.
Hey, why are you crying?
Are you hurt?
Neanderthal, why are you making her cry?
Huh?
You said something mean to
Sanae-chan again, didn't you?
No, I—
I'm disappointed in you, Satomi-sama.
Huh?
What?!
This is why you...
Koutarou...
You all...
Thank you...
I'm tired.
That was terrible!
What are they?
You want to know?
We got you in a etheric light net!
There's no escaping, now!
Now, time for some punishment.
No!
I see, so you made up.
Yes, it was all thanks to you.
Thank you!
That's right.
Yes!
Yeah!
Huh?
You came here to bug me, didn't you?
Maybe I did?
We're enemies, aren't we?
You know...
Time to bug you!
Hey, stop it!
Safe Family
Time to play beach volleyball!
I'm betting on Koutarou again!
Right!
Okay, let's go!
Hit!
Silly!
Dummy!
Next Episode: Cultural Festivals and Beetles