Summer Time Rendering
I actually thought I was dead, Shinpei.
Shide...
Haine...
No, Hiruko.
Yer worthless trash now.
You've shrunken so much.
There's no way you'll recover.
Yer eyes are broken now.
I'm just so disappointed in ya.
But look at yer right eye!
That is the observer's right eye.
Ya must be the egg.
You've just awakened!
But why?
When Haine looked, most of yer data was corrupt.
I didn't realize that'd become what ya developed into.
I guess only someone like ya were able to be restored.
So that's the power of love!
If I can take yer eye from ya, my dreams will still come true.
I failed to take it from Shinpei who had it in the fourth loop,
but I can take it from the egg who still has it.
If what he really wants is what I
saw in his mind at that moment...
I'm not letting him get it!
Shide... wait...
I can still do it...
If I eat enough humans, I'll get better.
So come home with me.
M-Maybe take Ushio's eye... and give it to m-me.
I don't need ya anymore.
What's that?
Ain't Haine yer mother?
So?
I don't care about the past.
Shide!
And ya call yerself human!
However, I need Hiruko to stay alive.
If she dies, my armor will disappear.
I'll take ya home, as ya wish!
N-No, I'm not going like this...
Come, Observer.
Let's settle the matter over there.
Ushio!
Gimme Nezu's weapon!
Shide!
Shinpei!
Thanks!
This is bad!
Shinpei, we're being drawn in!
I'm weak.
Too weak!
Mortals can't go past this point!
If ya do, ya can't leave nor die!
You'll end up lost!
But...
I'll go by myself!
No!
I'm never leaving ya again!
Dummy! Were ya listening to me? Yer so stubborn!
Ryuu, can ya hear me? Take Shinpei and go!
If I leave ya now, Sis will never forgive me.
Ryuu!
Sis made a promise with ya.
And I'm gonna keep it fer her.
I'll be Shinpei's support.
I won't let him get lost!
I'll follow yer presence.
Always!
I'll be by yer side.
I love ya, and I wanna be with ya.
Got a problem with that?
Dummy.
Shinpei!
Sou!
Take care of everyone!
Ushio!
This is Haine's home.
Where's Ushio?
Endless Night
The flow of time is cut off here.
It's just like how Dr. Hishigata said.
What?
Time doesn't flow here.
It's stagnant.
I don't think I can go back by looping.
If I die, that's probably it.
This isn't good.
Ushio!
I just had her in my hand!
I know she's here.
The shotgun that she printed hasn't disappeared.
So she's within 50 meters.
I can sense her faintly too.
She's on the move.
L-Let's go after her!
Shinpei! I'm sorry.
It's because I jumped.
No, I told you to go after Shide with everything you had.
This is nothing compared to what Ms. Nagumo went through.
Let me control your body.
I'll take on the pain.
But then you'll be hurting.
I'll be okay.
I'm a shadow.
I can tune down the sense of pain.
It's not just your leg injury.
Your entire body is starting to give out.
If I don't support ya internally, ya won't have a chance here.
How does it feel?
I'm going to move your body now.
It feels strange.
My body is numb, yet I'm conscious.
It's usually like that for me too,
but being conscious only is weird.
Yes, but it's kind of like when I take a bird's-eve view. I can get used to it.
Ushio!
Can ya hear me?
Ryuunosuke, is this Hitogashima?
It looks similar.
I can see the Wakayama mainland across the sea.
Right.
Hey, Shinpei?
I meant to tell ya this earlier.
What is it?
Ya don't have to speak so formally to me.
Yer older than I am.
No, you're the same age as Ms. Nagumo,
so you're much older!
No, I'm in junior high. When I died, that is.
Ushio immediately called me Ryuu.
Well, she's extremely friendly to anyone.
I'm not the type who's super casual just because you're younger.
Are ya always so formal with anyone?
Yes.
I'm more casual with people my age.
Really? So what about Mio?
Yer super casual with her.
That took getting used to.
I'm a bit jealous.
In that case, I'm gonna go casual with ya!
What?!
So be totally casual with me too! Ya got it?!
The way I speak is how I show respect.
It doesn't mean we're not close.
No, our lingo is super important!
So please... uh... just do it!
What's so funny?
It makes me want to get to know you more, Ryuunosuke.
Really?
Wait.
Look.
A ball?
I've seen it before.
It's Haine's ball.
Let's go after it.
Roger that.
Ryuunosuke, see that sign?
"Tekram"...
No, Kobayakawa Market?
Wha—
What are these things?
Are they shadows?
Dunno, but they don't seem like they'll attack us.
Ushio!
Ushio, are ya okay?!
Tell me what happened!
Shinpei...
My head...
Th-This presence...
It's Haine!
I promised Ushio.
Her body is a part of Haine's.
If Ushio loses herself and Haine appears, I'll kill her.
If I'm no longer around, Ryuunosuke...
You need to keep that promise.
Shinpei, I'm gonna shoot! I will!
Okay?!
Shinpei?
Hold it, Ryuunosuke.
She's saying something.
It's okay.
It's fine now, Ryuu.
She's different.
She's not the evil Haine who killed ya.
Her consciousness split at that moment into the human girl Haine and Hiruko.
So who's inside ya, Ushio?
A girl who loves sweets.
Ms. Nagumo's friend.
Her friend?
Right.
And she's also...
me.
Haine wants to talk to ya.
Will ya listen to her?
Yes.
Thanks.
Nice to meet ya.
Summer Time Rendering
So yer...
Ya don't gotta be shy.
They're Hizuru's friends.
Okay.
I had a long dream.
It was Ushio's memory.
Sorry, Shinpei, Ryuunosuke.
I got everyone involved...
You, Hizuru, and Ushio...
Everyone died because of me.
It's not yer place to apologize.
Hiruko was the one who ate me.
That's just what she does.
Shide is to blame, fer taking advantage of that.
Yer going to fight Shide?
We're in an endless night.
It's a world that exists above our real world.
In an endless night, time does not move.
Shinpei and Ushio, can ya see that?
Yeah.
Now look at Ryuunosuke with those eyes.
Ryuu ain't ahead of us!
Yer right.
I've been talking without lapse.
That's why Shide wanted to bring us here.
We can't loop nor see two seconds ahead.
He's trying to steal Ushio's eye here.
The one with the awakened eye sees beyond the current world to a higher dimension.
He will have control of all of life, time, and space.
It's like how a three-dimensional person can easily pick up a comic book, throw it on the ground, and burn it.
Wow!
Seriously? It doesn't feel like I can do that!
It just awakened, so it seems unstable.
Yer in an endless night too.
That eye is at its best in the real world.
The ending...
It's the thought that I saw when I scanned Shide.
He wants to destroy the world,
as if he's turning off a console.
There's nothing after that.
It's really the end.
I-I know this sound.
An update from the central military district.
B29s are headed north from Kii Channel.
There are 250 enemy bombers
headed north in five squadrons.
One has circled over Awaji Island and is headed southeast.
To all the citizens of Wakayama: we pray for your safety.
It's the air raid siren!
Ushio!
Stay down, Ryuu!
Ushio, don't make a shadow on the ground.
The fire is dangerous.
Keep yer true form as small as possible!
I'm okay!
Shadows can't die here.
This doesn't hurt one bit.
Shide!
Nothing can touch me, no matter what ya do.
Y'all look like slugs down there.
Ushio, first let me burn ya to a crisp, then I'll take yer eye.
So about what ya were saying...
Shide wants to use yer eye in the real world, right?
Which means there must be some way back to it!
Shinpei, yer right!
Kill Hiruko.
Even in an endless night,
ya have the power to do that, Ushio.
The endless night disappears with Hiruko.
We can go back to the real world.
Ya got it!
But how?
Shide is way up in the sky.
Leave that to me.
This air raid is Hiruko's memory.
Stop...
It's hot...
I'm burning...
Don't make me relive... something like this...
It's a memory?
The endless night is linked to Hiruko's memory,
although I doubt this is a past she wants to remember.
Calm down.
Even if it hurts, it won't kill ya.
Yer pain gives 'em pain.
It's Shide forcing Hiruko to relive this!
Ushio, jump at my signal.
What?
I have this memory too.
I can push it back fer a little while.
But beware of Shide's armor.
It works like an echo and sends an attack right back.
To defeat Shide, hack him, and erase the armor first.
Then we kill the inside.
It's a two-step process.
But after the first step, he'll get to Ushio.
No, I won't die.
Mio gave me something.
I'll finish him off in two steps, no matter what.
Before my hair burns away completely!
All right.
I can buy ya a few seconds.
Do ya trust me?
We do.
If my sister befriended ya, yer my friend too.
Ryuunosuke.
Right, Shinpei?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I'm ready.
Yes.
Now!
I see you've got Haine on yer side.
I'm counting on ya, Ushio.
Stop Shide.
Let Hiruko rest in peace!
Leave it to me!
At this height, I can't get to Ushio's true form.
They're fast and massive!
I can't avoid 'em with my hair.
I'll kill ya even in if I die too!
What?
What is he?
Even if ya die?
There's nothing inside!
That means I can't even try to trade blows.
So ya read my mind.
He hacked—
She revived herself?
Did she eat a part of the original Ushio?
Then take this!
What did she do?!
The air raid stopped.
Wh-What happened?
She touched me to erase the memory of the air raid.
Shinpei, can ya hear me?
Ushio!
I get it now.
Shide's body is in the real world.
In the real world?!
Shide is remotely controlling his armor using Hiruko.
If there's nothing inside, there's not much we can do.
What does Shide's armor look like now?
The left half I erased is still gone.
Then erase the rest and go fer the win.
Ushio?
Ushio!
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time