Year 850. Trost.
The sight of Eren Jaeger activating his mysterious Eotena powers
was one that terrified his fellow soldiers.
I'm... Human!
He's not an enemy of Mankind!
For Mankind's glory,
I will use what little time I have left
to vouch for his tactical worth to us!
The only thing Eren and company could do was vouch for themselves
until they were saved by Dot Pixis—
the commander-in-chief of Mankind's southern areas.
I get the feeling I should listen to what these kids have to say.
They are the prey and we are the hunters
We are the hunters
Without knowing the name of the trampled flower
The fallen bird awaits the wind
Prayer won't change anything
What you need right now is the resolve to fight
Swine who laugh in the shadows
At the will to move forward
Are no more than livestock
In a world of false prosperity
That stifles the freedom of the hunters
The humiliation of captivity
Serves as the signal for retaliation
As we move to slaughter our prey
That wait beyond those walls
Jaeger!
We let our bodies burn in the fire
Of our raging desires
We light a flame in the twilight
With a crimson bow and arrow!
We are the hunters
Icon
The Battle of Trost ( 7 )
I'll do it!
I don't know if I can block that hole,
but I'll give it a shot!
Well said.
Spoken like a real man.
Summon the planning officers! We need to come up with a strategy!
No way.
That plan I came up with is completely unreliable,
and he's just going to run with it?
I was just thinking the same thing.
But there's no sense in doubting his decision.
Commander Pixis must see potential in something the rest of us can't see.
Something we can't see?
Also, I think there's a bigger issue that must be addressed
before the plan can be put into motion.
And the Commander's fully aware of it.
What do you mean?
The Eotenas aren't our only enemies.
There's no time to waste.
I need you to do your best, young soldiers.
A plan to retake Trost?
You've gotta be kidding me!
We have no way to seal that hole.
What is the brass thinking?
We'd just be dying in vain if we went back in there!
As long as we can't seal that hole,
we should be focusing on protecting Wall Rose's gate instead!
Damn it all. How much of a glory hunter can you be?
Do I have to return to that Hell?
No! I don't want to die!
Let me see my family!
Hey, Daz! You're being too loud!
You there! I heard you!
Are you saying you want to abandon your mission?
That's right!
This is nothing but mass suicide! It's meaningless!
Have you no respect for Mankind or its laws?
It'd be well within my rights
to have you executed this very minute!
Go ahead.
It'd be a hundred times better than getting devoured by Eotenas!
Stop it, Daz!
No! Let me go!
I'm not going back in there!
You hear that?
Well, can ya blame him?
Hey...
I hope someone over here rebels, too.
I'd at least like to choose how I die.
Hey!
J-Just kidding!
Do it.
Go all out and rebel!
And get others to go along with you!
The Garrison has many dissenters too.
I'll take advantage of the commotion and leave!
Leave and go where, exactly?
I'll go see my daughter.
This wall's not gonna last, anyway.
They say that before Eotenas took over the world,
people fought among themselves
in endless wars over race and ideologies.
That's when someone said,
"If a powerful external threat were to appear,
Mankind would cease its wars and unite."
What do you make of that?
First I've heard of it.
Quite naïve, I must say.
Almost silly.
Your mind is as warped as mine is.
Well, that powerful threat
has pushed us to the brink of destruction,
and yet we're a far cry from "united".
Indeed. It's high time we did unite.
Otherwise, we won't even be able to put up a fight.
Eren?
He's safe, huh?
Focus on the mission?
How dare he address a superior officer that way?
By the looks of things, Mikasa and Armin must be safe too.
But what's Eren doing
with the Commander?
You want some?
Yes, please!
Kill me!
If you're going to execute me, just do it already!
You sure? I'll actually do it, you know!
Attention!
I shall now explain the plan to retake Trost.
This mission's objective
is to seal the hole where
the gate was destroyed.
Seal it?
How?
As for how we'll do it,
let me start off by introducing you to him.
This is Cadet Eren Jaeger.
E-Eren?!
He's the result of a top-secret project
to turn humans into Eotenas.
He can create and control an Eoten's body.
Hey...
I have no idea what the Commander's talking about.
Am I just too stupid to get it or something?
Would you shut up, idiot?
He'll transform into an Eoten,
pick up the giant boulder by the shattered gate,
carry it over to the hole and seal it.
Your job will be
to protect him from Eotenas while he moves the boulder!
We don't have to fight the Eotenas?
I-I apologize.
I didn't mean any disrespect by speaking up to a ranking officer.
I don't mind. Continue.
Y-Yes, sir.
Eotenas are typically drawn to pursue
the largest number of people.
If we can take advantage of that
to lure them along the walls,
we can draw most of them away from Eren
without engaging them in direct combat.
And by using the cannons against those
lured away, we'll minimize our own losses.
But since we can't leave Eren undefended,
a small elite force should protect him.
And we can't avoid engaging the Eotenas that come through the wall.
The skills of the elite force will be critical.
All right, understood.
We'll take that into account and revise our plans.
But this will only work if Eren can carry that boulder
and seal the hole.
We are proceeding with the operation
without certain proof that he can.
I can't help but feel worried.
Indeed, given the uncertainty of a crucial element,
I do not relish sending many men to their deaths.
But I do understand what
Commander Pixis is thinking.
Yes.
The first issue is that of time.
Even as we speak, Eotenas continue to enter the town.
The greater their numbers in Trost, the worse our odds of success in retaking it.
And the higher the chance of Wall Rose falling.
And one more thing.
There's a limit to how much one
can be motivated by terror.
Lift that giant rock?
Is that possible?
Has Mankind finally learned to control the Eotenas?
You're lying!
I won't put my life on the line for some incomprehensible plan!
What do you think we are?
We aren't...
We aren't pawns for you to sacrifice!
A human weapon?
He's lying!
He thinks we're fools!
He's telling us to die here today!
I'm outta here!
Me too.
Same here!
I'm outta here too!
Wait!
You'll get the death penalty for this!
I'll spend Mankind's last hours with my family!
This is bad.
Yes.
If we don't do something, there will be chaos.
Ready to die, traitors?!
I'll kill you right now!
Here is my decision!
I shall pardon anyone who deserts now.
Once you succumb to fear of the Eotena,
you can never fight them again.
Those who have felt that fear should leave.
And anyone wishing their parents, siblings,
and loved ones to experience it should also leave!
Daddy!
I can't do that...
My daughter's...
my last hope.
Let's talk about what happened four years ago.
About our attempt to retake Wall Maria.
As I'm sure you're all aware,
that operation was no more than the government's way
of dealing with its inability to feed all of the unemployed.
It was a culling.
The reason no one speaks of it is because
by sending them outside these cramped walls,
we were able to survive within them.
All of Mankind, including myself, bears the weight of that sin!
Since not many people lived in Wall Maria's territory,
there was never any open rebellion.
But what about now?
If Wall Rose falls,
we'll have to sacrifice more than twenty percent of our population!
The territory within Wall Sina
can't support even half the remaining population.
If Mankind falls,
it won't be because we were devoured by the Eotena.
It'll be because we killed each other.
We must not die even deeper within the walls.
I beg of you
to die right here!
I don't know if I can use the Eoten's power to lift that boulder,
but I understand what I must do.
I may be a fake,
but I must make this plan succeed.
I must become a symbol
of hope for everyone!
Information available for public disclosure
Multiaxial Maneuver Gear Weight-Shifting Device ( 1 )
To maneuver in multiple axis, it's necessary
to be able to shift one's weight precisely
using belts strung all over the body.
Multiaxial Maneuver Gear Weight-Shifting Device ( 1 )
To maneuver in multiple axis, it's necessary
to be able to shift one's weight precisely
using belts strung all over the body.
Information available for public disclosure
Multiaxial Maneuver Gear Weight-Shifting Device ( 2 )
To allow quick maneuvers in
multiple axis, the equipment has
been made as light as possible.
Multiaxial Maneuver Gear Weight-Shifting Device ( 2 )
To allow quick maneuvers in
multiple axis, the equipment has
been made as light as possible.
I see you're all here.
You have one mission.
To guard Eren Jaeger,
eliminating any risky elements that appear during the operation.
It will be the most dangerous and difficult task in the entire operation.
It's no exaggeration
to say that Mankind's fate rests on your shoulders.
Commander, may I say something?
What is it?
Does this human weapon really work?
Quiet, Riko!
You don't believe it either, do you?
Commander, this operation depends on Eren Jaeger,
and we know nothing about him.
If he doesn't do his job, many soldiers will die in vain.
Well, then...
Do you really enjoy losing to them that much?
I don't.
I hate losing more than anything.
But unfortunately, I've been losing for my entire life.
I want to win against them.
I want to beat those giant freaks
more than anything in the world.
S-So do we!
Then betting on him is our only option.
You're right. We know nothing about him.
But he's the only chance we have to defeat the Eotenas.
Commander, it's time for the decoy operation to begin.
Ian Dietrich,
Riko Brzenska,
and Mitabi Jarnach.
You are the Garrison's most elite troops.
I'm entrusting Mankind's fate to you.
Yes, sir!
Ian, you take command.
You have full authority out there.
Me, sir?
I have no objections.
Neither do I.
But I don't believe I'm good enough.
Don't worry.
You're a man who knows his drinks.
You're well-acquainted with drinks both bitter and sweet.
I'm counting on you!
Yes, sir!
Eren, I'm sorry.
I ended up making you responsible for everything.
Like I said before,
you have the ability to find the right answer.
I believe in that.
Eren, I'm going to—
Don't tell me you're going to come with me.
You've been assigned to the decoy team.
But I can't leave you alone.
If you're alone, you'll—
Enough!
I'm neither your little brother nor your kid!
I told you that!
Ackerman,
join the elite force protecting Jaeger.
We need your skill.
Let's go. It's time!
Later, Armin.
Don't die.
Yeah, you neither.
A top-secret human weapon, was it?
As long as you can seal that hole, it doesn't matter.
We'll protect you with all we've got.
We're counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Eren, are you feeling okay?
Yeah!
Eren...
I said I'm fine!
I feel much better than when we were surrounded.
We aren't playing house here, Jaeger.
I didn't mean...
I can't believe we have to
leave Mankind's fate up to a spoiled kid like you.
Cut it out, you guys!
We'll soon reach the shortest
route to the boulder.
I'm not seeing any Eotenas.
Everyone must have succeeded
in luring them away.
Listen!
You only need to get them to the edge of town!
Avoid unnecessary combat!
Listen, Jaeger.
A lot of soldiers will die during this operation.
They'll die for you.
They'll be our colleagues, ranked both above and below us.
As soldiers, they're prepared to die, of course.
But they are not pawns without a voice.
Wait.
Not yet.
A little more.
Go!
They have names and families.
And all the feelings that those entail.
Alyosha, Dominic, Phine, Isabel,
Ludwig, Martina, Guido, Hans.
They're all humans as alive as either of us.
I've known some of them since my days as a cadet.
And today, many will die for you.
You have a responsibility to ensure that their deaths mean something.
No matter what happens.
Never let yourself forget that.
And be prepared to die for that responsibility.
Right!
I'll do it...
I'll make this happen!
Since the Eotenas appeared,
Mankind has never won against them.
Their continuous advance has meant
Mankind's continuous retreat and loss of territory.
But when this mission succeeds,
Mankind will have retaken its territory from them
for the very first time!
Right here.
Let's go!
This will be Mankind's first victory against the Eotena!
Green smoke round, confirmed.
The elite force has begun the mission.
It may seem insignificant compared to all that we have lost,
but this one small step will be a titanic leap for Mankind!
Thinking about it from a human's point of view,
I doubt anyone could lift that boulder.
But I'm sure Eren has the strength to lead us forward.
Eren?
The dream where your heart seeks comfort
Is more fragile than your life
You can abandon it, yet always find it again
Now, sleep in peace
My pulsing rage
Defiles the wishes I harbor
Before I forget them
Only to remember once more
In this beautiful and cruel world
We keep on asking ourselves
Why it was we who survived
What will we protect
With our strength and with our weakness
If reason and logic no longer hold sway
The operation to retake Trost has begun.
As many soldiers die,
Eren, now an Eoten, loses control
and destroys his own head.
The operation seems to have failed, but...
Wound
The Battle of Trost ( 8 )