Why don't you introduce yourself?
Er...
I'm, uh, Homura Akemi...
Pleased to, um, meet you...
Akemi has been hospitalized with heart disease for quite some time.
She hasn't been to school in a while, so she's probably not feeling very comfortable.
I want you all to help her out!
Akemi, what school did you go to?
Were you in any clubs?
A sport? Or maybe an art?
Your hair's so long! Isn't it a pain to have to braid it every morning?
Umm...
I, uh...
Akemi!
You have to go to the nurse's office, right? Do you know where it is?
N-no...
I'll show you. I'm the class monitor.
Sorry, guys. Akemi needs to go take her medicine during break.
Oh, really?
Sorry to keep you...
See you later, Akemi.
Sorry.
They're not trying to bother you, they're just excited about having a new classmate.
That's not it... Just...
Thank you.
Don't be so nervous. We're classmates.
I'm Madoka Kaname.
Call me Madoka!
I...
Don't worry about it! And I can call you Homura, right?
I... Um...
People don't normally call me by my first name...
It's a weird name...
Aww, no it isn't.
It sounds really awesome!
I don't really live up to it...
C'mon, don't sell yourself short.
Live up to your wonderful name!
Why don't you try this problem?
Oh, right, you were absent for a long time.
You should borrow a friend's notes.
Wow, her anemia's acting up during warmups?
Well, she did spend half a year in bed...
Homura, you should live up to your cool name!
I can't... I can hardly do anything...
I just cause trouble for people and make mistakes...
Why?
I'm always going to be like this, aren't I?
You'd be better off dead, right?
I'd be better off dead...
Yeah. You should die.
Die...
Where am I?
What's going on!?
That was a close call.
You're safe now, Homura.
You're...
They're Magical Girls. Those who hunt witches.
Aww, you gave away the secret already.
Don't tell anyone else in class!
Kaname... Have you always fought those things?
Always? Well, Mami's the veteran.
I only contracted with Kyubey last week.
You were great today, Madoka. You're showing real improvement.
And you're okay with it? You're not...
Scared... Or anything?
Well, "fine" isn't really the word, and sometimes I'm afraid,
but hunting down witches lets me help a lot of people.
See, it's worth it.
Plus, we've got to get Kaname up to speed before Walpurgisnacht arrives.
I'm going.
No...
Even though Tomoe died?
That's why I'm going. I'm the only one left who can stop Walpurgisnacht.
No! You won't be able to beat it alone!
You'll die too, Kaname!
No matter what, I'm a Magical Girl.
I have to protect everyone.
Let's just run away!
It's all we can do!
No one would blame you!
Homura... I'm glad we were able to become friends.
I'm still proud that I was able to rescue you when you were attacked by a witch.
So I'm happy I became a Magical Girl.
That's how I feel.
Kaname...
Farewell, Homura.
Take care.
Don't go! Kaname!
Why!?
You knew you'd die!
Don't try to save someone like me! Live for yourself!
Are those words true?
Homura Akemi.
Will you stake your soul on that wish?
If you have a wish so strong you will accept a fate of battle, I will grant you power.
If I contract with you, you can make any wish come true, right?
Certainly. You possess the qualifications.
Tell me. With what wish will you spark light in a Soul Gem?
I...
I want to meet Kaname again.
Not as someone who is protected, but as someone who protects her!
The contract is concluded.
Your wish has surpassed entropy.
Set that power free!
I... Haven't been discharged yet?
It wasn't a dream...
Why don't you introduce yourself?
I'm Homura Akemi. Pleased to meet you.
Akemi has been hospitalized with heart disease—
Kaname! I'm a Magical Girl now too! Let's do our best!
Umm...
Here goes!
What do you think, Mami?
Stopping time, huh.
That's amazing, but isn't it a bit difficult to use?
Mami! Now!
Okay!
Go for it, Akemi!
Sure!
I did it?
I did it!
You did it!
Good work.
That was amazing, Homura!
What's wrong!? Hold on, Kaname!
What?
Why!?
Why this!?
I have to tell her.
Kyubey's tricked you all!
Jeez, what would Kyubey get out of lying to us?
Well...
You just want to give us these weird ideas and split us up, don't you?
You're really on that Kyoko chick's side, aren't you!
No!
Sayaka, you're doing a good job of it yourself...
Fine, whatever. But I don't want to team up with her.
I get the ranged weapons you and Mami have, but this "explosions out of thin air" stuff is too much for me.
It just feels like we're getting in too deep.
Akemi, don't you have any weapons other than bombs?
I'll think about it.
What are you!?
What did you do with Sayaka!?
Stop it, Sayaka! Please! Remember!
You wanted to avoid this!
Sorry... Miki...
Sayaka...
Dammit! Why did this have to happen!?
This is terrible... I can't take it...
Tomoe!
If Soul Gems give birth to witches...
We all have to die!
Even you! Even me!
Stop it!
No...
I can't take this anymore!
It's okay.
We'll do out best, together!
We'll beat Walpurgisnacht together!
This is the end for us...
The Grief Seeds are...
Yeah...
Together, we'll become monsters.
And wreck everything in this world.
Everything unpleasant... Everything sad...
Get rid of it all.
Destroy... Destroy... Destroy everything.
Doesn't that sound nice?
I lied.
I saved one.
Why are you giving it to me!?
I want you to do something I can't.
Homura... You can return to the past.
You said you could change history so this wouldn't happen.
You can save silly me from ever making a contract with Kyubey...
I promise! I'll save you, no matter what!
No matter how many times I have to try, I'll save you!
Thanks...
Can I ask... One more thing?
I don't want to become a witch...
No matter how much there is that's unpleasant or sad,
there are so many things I want to protect.
Madoka!
Homura... You called me by my first name...
I'm so happy...
No one believes their future.
No one can accept their future.
So I...
Who's there?
Madoka.
If someone appears before you promising miracles...
Don't believe him.
Homu...
I won't rely on anyone.
I don't need anyone to understand me.
I won't let Madoka fight ever again.
I'll burn all the witches myself.
And this time, I'll take on Walpurgisnacht...
With my own two hands.
That's terrible!
It's impossible. It's too much for her.
No! It can't end up like this!
Madoka! Don't let him tempt you!
If you give up, it's over.
But you can change destiny.
Unavoidable destruction, grief... You can reject them.
You hold that power.
Really?
Don't be fooled! That's exactly what he wants!
Can I really do something?
Can I change what's going to happen?
Of course!
So contract with me, and become a magical girl!
No!
Madoka's truly awesome when transformed.
I predicted she'd be the strongest Magical Girl, but...
I didn't think she'd take out Walpurgisnacht in one shot.
And what will happen? Now that she's exceeded your expectations?
Sooner or later, the result will be the same.
As the strongest Magical Girl, she defeated her fiercest foe.
After this, nothing remains but to become the wickedest witch.
It shouldn't take her much more than ten days to annihilate this planet.
Oh well, that's humanity's problem.
We've reached our energy recovery quota.
Aren't you going to fight her?
No.
This is not my battle.
Homura Akemi... You're...
Again.
No matter how many times, I will repeat it.
No matter how many times I live the same days,
I seek only one exit.
A path to save you from your fate of despair...
Madoka...
My only friend...
Homura...
You...
For your sake...
Even if I'm sealed in an eternal labyrinth,
I don't care.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 10 I'll never rely on anyone again
Illustration: Chloe Mura
Didn't you feel anything all the time you were protecting them?
Didn't any of them realize how badly you hurt?
Episode 11 The last guidepost that was left.
Episode 11 The last guidepost that was left..
The last guidepost that was left.