To Katsuragi Junichi-san
I empathize with you. You were right about the way things are, but we should stand up for ourselves. And so, I have decided to form a publishing company together with a few of our comrades joining forces. I would like you to see it as the same battle but in a new form, and hope you will join me in this endeavor. I want to talk to you about this face to face.
- Arita
Arita
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
A Christmas party?!
And we can go, too?
Of course. It's next Sunday.
We'll be there!
Since it's an Olympus party, will you play guitar for us?
Well, if you've got a request...
Hey, Ricchan, are you coming too?
A Christmas party!
You can go with Nishimi-san, right?
I'm not really part of that group, so I'll pass.
Sorry, there's a Christmas mass at the church on Sunday.
Then Kawabuchi-kun is going to that, too?
Yeah.
We should've checked before...
Maruo-kun.
If you don't mind, I think I'd like to go to the party after all.
Really?!
Of course, you're very welcome!
I never thought you'd agree to come, Nishimi-kun.
Like this, little by little, it's best to put some distance between us.
I'm sure of it...
Hey!
You're late, Bon-baby!
H-Hi...
Alright! Next we'll play the Spiders.
What about the Beatles?!
Let's go with "Bang Bang Bang"!
Nishimi-san, how about some cider?
Sure.
Feigning innocence, bang bang bang!
Bang bang, bababababababa-bang!
He's someone I can't beat!
Come on, Nishimi-san, let's sing together!
I don't really know the popular songs...
I wonder what he's doing right now...
Maybe he's talking to Ricchan at the church?
I go to a party and all I do is think about those two...
I feel like a fool...
Kaoru-san?
Ricchan...
Why are you here?
I thought you were going to church...
Yeah.
The church's Christmas mass is over.
He isn't here with you?
Does he have to be?
Um...
He went home with the little ones.
Oh, I see...
It's cold, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey, come on!
I got you, babe!
Come to think of it, it's almost his birthday, isn't it?
I hope you finish in time.
Why?
Why do you say things like that?
You're wrong!
This is for...
Never mind! Kaoru-san, you're an idiot!
What did I do this time?
I don't know.
It's hard to understand women.
Why did I lose my temper like that?
I'm the one who rejected Kaoru-san in the first place.
Even if I finished knitting this,
there's no way I'd be able to give it to him.
I'm relieved.
You're safe for now Yurika,
but let me tell you something...
I know.
You're going to tell me not to see him, right?
You don't have to keep repeating yourself.
Chet...
No!
Chet!
Sentaro...
What are you doing here?
What am I...?
I've been waitin' for you.
W-Why are you acting so formal?
Rikko...
I'm sorry.
I never realized how you felt 'til now.
I may have said dumb things an' hurt you...
I'm sorry.
But... um... how can I put it?
But about your feelings, I, uh...
Sentaro, why are you suddenly on your best behavior?
Stop it already.
This isn't a yakuza movie.
Did I get it wrong?
Yeah.
You got it wrong.
O-Oh, a misunderstanding.
Sorry for talkin' so weird...
R-Right! We're like family.
You made me nervous for a second there...
I-In that case, good.
We're like family,
so I couldn't stand the thought of causin' you pain.
I'm glad I heard this now, and not a while back.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm never going to tell a blockhead like you.
There's something I have to tell you.
I'm going back to Tokyo soon.
I probably won't see you again...
An upperclassman from my college
is starting up his own publishing company
and he wants me to help him.
I plan on leaving soon after New Year's.
It's taken me a long time to get to this point,
but I owe it to you for making me think I should give going back another try.
I'm grateful.
"Idiot. I don't want to hear those words.
Just don't leave me..."
But I couldn't bring myself to say it.
Not when he's finally trying to move forward.
Ritsuko-chan!
Yurika-san!
W-What are you doing?
Looking for something.
I carelessly threw something away that was important to me.
Hey, is that girl homeless?
Say, Ritsuko-chan...
Never mind me. Please, go on ahead.
A beautiful girl like you shouldn't be seen doing something like this, Yurika-san.
Ritsuko-chan...
I'll help you.
P-Please, don't!
It's something important, isn't it?
Yurika-san...
So... what am I looking for?
Here it is!
This is it, right?
Yes!
But, I'll have to start over with clean yarn...
Is this going to be a present for someone?
Um... maybe.
Why did you throw away something so important?
I was confused.
I suddenly felt stupid for knitting a gift that I'd never be able to give.
Why wouldn't you be able to?
B-Because a lot of things have happened between us...
...and I once hurt him terribly.
You turned him down, didn't you?
And I couldn't tell him I like him now, after all that,
so I decided to let it go.
But then I thought that wouldn't do.
See, there was another time when I said nothing and just gave up.
Do you regret it?
No. I'd given up on that long ago.
Besides, I've realized this person has been there
to support me all this time, whenever I've felt down.
I had no confidence in myself, but he did his best to encourage me.
This time, I want to be the one to tell him how I feel.
I finally decided to stop keeping my mouth shut and waiting for things to end.
I'm sorry for talking about this...
No, I'm glad you did.
I think you've opened my eyes as well.
So...
By the way, who is it?
Who's your prince, Ritsuko-chan?
Oh, that's...
Shall I try and guess?
W-W-What are you saying?!
Please, stop!
You're so cute!
Yes. I'm set to leave this weekend.
Working in Tokyo?
Yeah.
A lot happened at college and I ended up dropping out.
But you'll come back once in a while, won't you?
Like you've been doing?
No. I'm never coming back to this town.
Kaoru-kun, our sessions were fun.
I'll miss seeing you and Sen-bou,
but I don't want you guys to stop playing jazz.
Jun-nii-san!
Did you tell him you were going back to Tokyo?!
Hey, Sen!
What's the hubbub, Bon?
It's about Jun nii-san!
Yeah, he's about to go back to Tokyo, right?
I heard from Pops.
Well, ain't got nothin' to do with me.
Hey, wanna jam?
You're going to let that be the last you see of him?
There's nothin' to say.
You looked up to him as a big brother since you were a kid!
You may never get the chance to meet him again!
There'd be no point.
Once he's gone, it'll be too late!
Enough about Jun-nii already.
Let's get started here.
If you don't feel like practicin', I'm goin' home.
What's all the fuss about?
I guess college students from Tokyo and all over have come to demonstrate
against letting the nuclear aircraft carrier into port.
That's terrible...
In their eyes, I'm a traitor.
They may never forgive me.
But...
...all I can do is search in my own way from now on.
Using a different method than them...
Oh, you're here, Bon.
Here, eat.
I made it myself, so it might be a little salty...
But if you're not gonna eat it, I will.
Is this any time to be eating?!
Did you forget what I said last time?!
What are you talkin' about?
Don't play dumb!
Are you going to be stubborn until it's too late?!
Jun nii-san is leaving this town today or tomorrow!
It's today.
I'm taking the night train, Kaoru-kun.
Sen-bou, this was rather old-fashioned of you.
LETTER OF CHALLENGE
I thought it was some kind of joke.
It's no joke.
I wanted to try havin' a serious showdown with you, Jun-nii.
Wait... You're not really...
I made it in time?
Let me in on it, too.
Musical Note: "Four" by Miles Davis
This is no duet.
They're seriously duking it out.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble, Pops.
Tell me about it!
And when you reach Tokyo, first thing you do is get to a barber!
Sure, sure.
Well, I'm off.
Jun-nii!
I'll remember today's session
for the rest of my life!
Yeah.
Me too, Sen-bou.
What are you doing here?
I told you not to see me off.
I have four questions I want you to answer.
If you try to dodge me, I'll get on this train with you.
So answer me truthfully.
Question number one:
Why did you tell me not to see you off?
I hate sad goodbye scenes.
Question number two:
Didn't you think to take me with you?
The work I'm going to be doing is kind of a gamble.
Even if I took you, there's no
guarantee of making any kind of living.
Besides, you're still in high school.
Question number three...
Why didn't you do anything more than kiss me?!
Did you not touch me because you intended to leave from the start?
No.
I knew.
I knew how much you cared about me...
This is my last question...
Won't you take me with you?
I want you to take good care of your own life.
I figured you would say something like that.
Now it feels like I've been set free, too.
I'm going back to my own world.
Thank you, Junichi-san.
Goodbye.
Yurika, where are you?!
Come out, Yurika!
How dare you embarrass us by walking out
in the middle of an arranged marriage meeting like that?!
Calm down, dear!
We're going back there together, Yurika!
Yurika, where are you?!
I'm going back to my own world.
I dragged you on board...
Now what?
What is there to do?
The train's already left the station.
Yeah...
Well, when we get there, we'll go to my room first
and maybe I'll have you cut my hair.
It's freezing today.
Yeah. Think I'll light the heater.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.