What's wrong?
You're from Mistral? That place sucks.
But it has great food and a ton of hot chicks.
It's been almost six months since the armistice, huh?
Gotta thank my lucky stars that I'm still alive.
Look, I win.
You're kidding me.
Not again...
Ready to get up, missy?
I'll share my booty with you.
Caramel!
I can't accept something so expensive...
Um... Sergeant!
Don't worry.
As long as you don't give the trumpeters a hard time,
they'll make sure you hear the withdrawal signal loud and clear.
Don't see too many new recruits nowadays, what with the draft being over and all...
Are you a volunteer?
Yes! I want to learn music!
No, I mean...
Nah, honesty's the best policy.
Good luck, missy.
What's your name, private?
Kanata.
Sorami Kanata.
Sound of the Skies
Does the radiance from the sky
reach all the way to your heart?
The melody I heard in my dream reminds me of a calm night.
Even when your hands are still so far away
I hope you'll still recall that gentle voice.
It's the blissful chord someone sang for you.
May the sound of the sky ring far and wide,
up and over all the sorrows gelid.
Only the real world reflects in your eyes.
Not even tears can bind you in this place.
Within the overflowing light,
may you play out the morrow.
Resounding Note
The Street of Daybreak
There's going to be a festival in Seize today.
A festival!?
So I'll be taking my leave of you here.
Look over there.
That's where you've been assigned to. It's called the Time-Keeping Fortress.
Find a way there by yourself.
Yessir!
Appointment.
Private Sorami Kanata will be assigned to the 1221st Platoon in Seize, Trois.
Republic of Helvetia Army Headquarters.
1320, mission completed.
Thank you, sir!
Seize, the city of springs and glass...
Hang on!
I have to report in at 1500 hours.
I'll finally be able to play music with you!
Route check, complete!
Time check, complete!
Equipment check, complete!
Charge forth!
D flat... what a wonderful note.
Wow, a fish!
$12.25...
Wow... What a beautiful doll-
S-Sorry!
What's the matter, Rio?
A kitten got lost amid all the hustle and bustle.
That happens all the time.
I mean, kittens just love wandering around all over the place.
That's why they're so cute.
I would agree if it had been a wild cat...
Unfortunately, this one was a pet.
That really startled me...
I found something fabulous, though.
How may I help you?
Thank you!
Look, a soldier!
Is she from the fortress?
Awesome!
Now we'll have a good fortune for sure!
Thanks!
Darn it...
How dare you get me wet!?
Take this!
Thanks!
Hey!
Are you retarded?
You're frickin' soaked.
What the hell is wrong with you!?
Umm...
Hey, watch i-
Tha...
Christ... Come on, follow me.
How's the temperature?
Perfect!
Glad to hear it.
Looks like she's a pretty easy target...
Hey, did you not even try to dodge them?
It's fine.
This type of fabric is very easy to clean.
Don't worry.
That was a festival, right?
Yeah, it originated from a legend we have here in Seize.
A legend?
What's it about?
Maidens of flame protecting the city.
Sorry for the imposition.
It's on you.
The maintenence is complete, too.
And... this.
Felicia...
That busybody...
She's late...
She's late! She's late! She's late!
We came all the way here to welcome her!
Let's just calm down and wait patiently, okay?
Didn't your dad give this to you?
It's quite nice.
D flat.
Thanks for letting me use your bath!
I... kind of have a tendency to get lost.
But that's why I met awesome people like you!
You're welcome.
Try not to get lost, though.
Can you recognize notes easily?
The sound is very clear.
It's somehow comforting.
That's not what I-
Thief!
You idiot!
T-Thank you.
God damn... is that thing worth more than your life!?
But that bell...
Don't worry.
I'm sure this is okay...
They're late.
Happiness...
Umm...
I have to leave. I have something to attend to.
Don't get lost again.
That bell must've been really precious to her.
What should I do?
Oh no!
Over there?
Charge forth!
Maidens of flame?
Long, long ago...
Long before the world became like this,
a winged demon lived in the ravines of this city.
It showered fire down upon the land,
bringing great suffering to the people who lived here.
It kidnapped the maidens who lived here
and imprisoned them in an underground labyrinth.
However, the maidens did not despair.
They called upon one another using the golden horn bestowed upon them by the Lord,
and thus escaped the labyrinth.
They defeated the demon and took its head
by borrowing the power of a great spider.
Even so, the head would not cease spewing its flames.
If it had continued to do so, then the entire city would have been engulfed by fire.
So, in order to halt the flames,
the maidens took turns embracing the demon's head.
The people of the city poured water upon the maidens every day.
After a year, the fire was finally extinguished.
Ever since then,
we've held the water festival in order to appease the souls of the maidens who saved the town.
Looks like the recruit's not coming...
Who cares!
Captain, look at Rio!
How very fitting.
I think we made the right decision in letting her handle it.
Didn't we draw lots...?
I got lost again.
I pretty much suck, huh?
I have fun when I get lost...
but only because I meet people I don't know.
I hate being alone.
Are you lost?
I want my mommy...
Don't worry.
As long as you keep believing...
your feelings will reach her.
Really?
Yes, your sound will resound without fail.
It'll resound...
It shall resound without fail.
And reach her.
Maiden of flame, rest here in peace.
Embrace the demon and appease the curse...
so that it will never again awaken.
What the hell?
The golden horn!
Has the demon arisen!?
Kureha!
Please...
Please, let my sound reach someone!
It reached someone...
It will resound and...
Wake your ass up, Private Sorami Kanata!
Huh? Where am I?
Just how long were you planning to sleep?
This is the Time-Keeping Fortress, the garrison of the 1221st Platoon.
I'd like to apologize for what happened yesterday...
God dammit.
I'm so sorry!
It's just...
Nah, I'm just giving you a hard time.
Don't be so reckless in the future, though, okay?
Seriously, this is just an ordinary bell.
I'll teach you...
How to play trumpet!?
...why this fortress is known as the Time-Keeping Fortress.
It's the sound of the skies!
Kazumiya Rio.
That's my name.
I'm going to be your trumpet instructor.
I'm looking forward to working with you, Sergeant Rio!
Just call me Rio.
That's what Felicia- the captain wants us to do.
We don't address each other with military ranks here.
Umm...
How about Ms. Rio?
All right, let's go ahead and get started.
Let me hear a wake-up call!
Whoever's playing now is terrible...
Let's get friendship, love, and other feelings together,
and play out how important they are.
I cried from joy.
I laughed from pain.
But that's all a part of me,
and tells me that I'm alive.
Let's take this slowly.
Everybody singing
Can you tell me how you really feel?
You're just my friend
Even when friendship and love waver,
I know, you know, will be happy
I hope this melody will ring forever.
Can you count my precious flower
Overflowing words are hardly enough to describe it.
This is our harmony.
Can you hear our harmony?
First Campaign:
The Story of the Chair
Next episode: First Campaign: The Story of the Chair.