If I exist inside my self-refusal, surely...
shasu ni iraretara masakasa ma ni
I who have fallen, will be turned to hatred.
ochireta no jibun ugoku nikushi mi wa kawawari
And the map is engulfed in flames.
de chizu wa honoo to saki
Possession in disorder, everything is only for the sake of observing.
midare ni woguyuu wa no kanshi nodake subete ni harerawareta
Give me your hand.
te wo kakeyo
Hold onto my hand.
te ni wo motte
Peel off your image and open your fingers.
zou wo hakuri hiraku yubi
Things get heated up at night.
ban nieru moe ni
If you have...
moshi mo omae ga
...gone on an illusionary journey,
mousou sosarareba mayoi no tabi
should I hold onto this destroyed place as well?
uchikuta koko to mo dakeyou ka
It is just a play of words.
mousu souse yo
The fortunate lovers have turned into the sound of water.
tada nusuru tonki wa mizu otoni
Living in the times swept by blood, facing this lukewarm feeling.
chi wo haki toki ni mabiru nurukubi to mukawaru
Your violent owner can no longer be seen.
sobou nushi to mirunai
What's left now is an open heavenly door, so walk to tomorrow with a laugh.
ten no he oubi yahira ka dake yuku asu hewara e yo