This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's 12 and dreams of becoming a singer.
But unfortunately,
she only has one year left to live.
They chose a manager for her, and we all went to introduce her to Dr. Wakaouji.
But we had a really hard time
keeping her secret from being exposed!
But, thanks to my heroics...
...we overcame those problems,
with approximate success.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
Be sure to watch TV in a well-lit room
and a safe distance away.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Full Moon wo Sagashite
Original Subtitles by a.f.k.
Searching for a Full Moon
The road to love is far too long for me.
Toosugiru koi no michishirube
There's no way for me to love you any more. Nope! Nope!
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
where I can even tell you how I really feel.
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
I wear my favorite clothes every day
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
so that person will turn his gaze towards me.
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
"I like you!" If I could bring myself to say it out loud
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
I would even be able to talk about love with you.
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
I want to be tucked into your heart
Anata no haato ni tsutsumaretai no ni
and I will do anything to be there.
Doushitara tsutsunde kureru no
"I love you!" Those are the words I want to hear from you
I b YOU wo anata kara kikitai
and my breath will quicken when we kiss.
Kisu suru shunkan no chikai kokyuu wo
The me who is performing for you is the cutest of them all!
Anata wo mane suru atashi wa ichiban kawaiku naru hazu
Transcribed by Steve
Editing, TLC: Zalis (ReDone-Subs)
Retiming, Encoding: E_B (Soldado)
Typesetting, KFX: shani-san and E_B (Soldado)
QC: E_B, Yogicat
This unladylike behavior must stop at once.
How can you be so rude as to only worry about your skirt?
You should be more attentive while eating.
What is that sound?
I-It's nothing!
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful. Good night.
Ah, wait a minute.
I haven't finished talking-
Must I keep her on a leash?
That was close.
H-Hello?
Ah, Mitsuki-chan? This is Ooshige.
Ooshige-san!
It's short notice, but the sale date
has been set for your debut single.
Eh?
Eh!? My debut!?
THE FEELINGS IN YOUR SONG
Mitsuki-chan, this is your producer,
Takasu-sensei.
[ -sensei: used to address people
prominent in a given field ]
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki.
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
Your debut concept will be
"Cool Lolita - Dynamite Love."
Um... could you repeat that?
Yeah, about that... just follow
my orders, and you can't go wrong.
Keep in touch.
What? You've got nothing to worry about.
With the right costumes and choreography, you'll be sexy as hell.
"S-Sexy," you said?
Just send it my way, okay?
Here's your debut song. Hot off the presses,
straight from the lyricist.
A tempting kiss.
The two of us are already a Non-Stop
Love Hurricane.
Love... may... doe...?
"Love Me Do Forever".
Aren't you a high school student?
Don't you recognize English?
Oh, sorry!
"A tempting kiss..."
"The two of us are already..."
"...a Non-Stop Love Hurricane"?
Now, let's move on to the subject of your debut...
Um...
You want me to sing this?
What, it's not good enough for you?
"Not good enough" isn't the issue... This is...
P-Please excuse us for a minute!
You mustn't, Mitsuki-chan.
You have to act more pleased about it.
Takasu-san is the one who produced Matsushita Genki's and...
...Kobayashi Rika's debut.
He's an amazingly productive producer.
Okay...
But that song won't be able to reach Eichi-kun.
Eichi-kun?
Then why don't you try writing one yourself?
You're saying you want to put your own feelings
into your own song, right?
If so, you'll have to write it on your own.
My own feelings in my own song?
Give songwriting a try,
if you think you can hack it.
I'm leaving this to you, Mitsuki-chan.
Man, new artists are all so conceited these days.
I hope you'll understand
how impossible it is for you.
I'll try writing a song.
Eh?
It's just as you said, Takasu-san.
I'll try to put my feelings in it.
Thank you very much for the advice.
That wasn't supposed to be advice...
What? That's bad...
I got it. I'll be right there.
If nothing else, this should be interesting.
However, you've got a three-day time limit.
I can't wait to see what a headstrong amateur can come up with...
...in a mere three days.
I'm...
I'm very sorry!
Mitsuki-chan...
Yes?
As your manager, there's one thing
I want to confirm here.
Y-Yes?
Can you tell me who this "Eichi-kun" is?
I see... So you have someone you like.
Yes.
But he left for America,
and I haven't had any contact with him.
My desire to become a singer is because I thought that...
...if he heard me, he might notice me.
All right!
If that's the case, I'll be cheering for you.
Really?
Yep.
That song back there had no musical sense
or anything else going for it.
But... it'll be a big seller, right?
Good sales don't necessarily mean good songs.
I want you to debut with a good song, Mitsuki-chan.
Ooshige-san...
Write a great song and show
Takasu-san what you're made of!
Okay!
All right, time to get writing!
Come on, that song won't write itself, you know.
I kind of wish it would...
Just how do  you write a song, anyway?
Don't tell me you don't even know
how to write songs!?
Yeah...
Then why did you say you would?
That's because...
This is what you get for just blurting out,
"I'll write a song!" without thinking!
What should I do?
I only have three days to write it...
Just leave this to me.
Do you have any CDs or lyric cards?
Yep. Wait a second.
Do you always keep them way back there?
Yes. Because if they get found,
they'll get thrown out.
See.
It might work, but it's so beat-up...
This is about the only music-related thing I have.
I've read it over and over.
You're really so... valiant!
By the way, Meroko... What do you plan to do with that songbook?
Oh, you'll see...
Eh!?
Meroko, have you gone rabid or something!?
I can't understand what you're saying!
Man!
Anyways, let go of my ha-!
That was a hint just now.
So then, what was it?
What do you mean, "What was it?"
You just tried to rip my hand off with your teeth!
Exactly. "Ripping off" is the idea.
But... I wonder if I'll be able to get by that way.
You're not getting anywhere!
You'll get somewhere.
You're just doing this to see
the person you like, after all.
I guess so...
Do whatever you want!
W-What was that?
Now Takuto will be all lovey-dovey with me.
Sheesh, you said to leave all the songwriting to you.
What a joke.
She's...
...a real piece of work.
You're up early.
Ah, Takuto.
Good morning.
By the way, should you really be staying up so long?
Yeah, I seem to be fine.
I must've forgotten I was sick.
Forgotten?
It's the first time I've ever been
absorbed enough in something to forget...
...about my poor health.
It feels so good to do what I want,
as much as I want to.
And... it was you, right?
This.
That's why I'm fine.
Thank you!
A-Anyways, did you write some lyrics?
Yeah, I wrote what I could, but...
What is it?
Meroko.
Let's see.
H-How is it?
Well... How should I put it...
Huh?  If you don't understand it,
then I'll take a look.
"If you are smiling...
the weather in my heart clears up."
"If you are crying... it's like a great flood."
"As long as I am by your side,
it'll always be smiles and peace."
What is this supposed to be?
I knew they wouldn't be any good.
N-Nobody ever said they're no good...
Y-Yeah. There's a first time for everyone.
It's okay. Even I know they're awful.
I haven't experienced anything I'm writing about.
So I can't imagine what it's like.
Then why don't you go on a date?
Eh!?
Yeah! If you do, you'll be able to write something.
But how can I go on  a date
when I don't have  a date?
T-That's right...
And it was such a good idea, too...
Good morning, Mitsuki-chan!
How are you feeling this morning?
There he is!
Your date for the day!
A date with Dr. Wakaouji!?
Wow!
I always wanted to come to Harajuku!
I'm glad you're this happy about coming here.
I was really surprised when you asked me out on a date, though.
Well, as long as you're this cheerful, your body should be okay.
Okay!
All right! Let's start our date.
Wow! This is really good!
Isn't it?
I was sure that you would like it.
I can tell this guy's had experience escorting girls around.
Heh. He's just faking it.
So... how's the date?
This will be useful for your work, right?
Yep! And I've had lots of fun!
It's almost like being on a date with Eichi-kun.
No wonder you seemed so distracted. So your mind's on Eichi-kun?
"Eichi-kun, Eichi-kun"...
She's so cute!
Not really...
Well... it's about time.
Shall we go back?
Okay!
Mitsuki-chan!
Are you all right, Mitsuki-chan!?
Yes. I'm fine.
Mitsuki-chan! Mitsuki-chan, hold on!
Mitsuki-chan!
It looks like the medicine's taken effect.
Your fever's gone down, and you don't seem to be coughing anymore.
I'm sorry. It's because I was acting selfish.
No.
I was at fault for being careless.
That's not it. I stayed up really late last night.
You stayed up?
Don't tell me it was because of your job.
I did  say I'd cooperate with you.
But if you do such unreasonable things,
I can't allow you to continue being a model.
Please stop saying that, Doctor!
I want to debut, no matter what!
If I don't, I won't be able to
let Eichi-kun know that I'm here.
I... I...
I understand.
You don't need to say any more.
If I oppose you, your health might deteriorate.
Don't worry. I'll still back you up.
Really!?
Yes.
But try to keep things in moderation.
Okay!
Eichi again?
Eichi must be happy that she thinks about him this much.
And you know, Takuto,
I think about you just as much!
L-Let me go already!
I'll excuse myself, then.
What are you doing?
The medicine's working, so now's my chance...
Stop it. Go to bed.
I can't be sleeping now.
I only have one day left to write a song.
Hey, Takuto, can you make me 16 again?
That way, we won't have to
worry about my health, right?
That's true, but...
Why do you have to push yourself so hard!?
What does it matter?
That producer Takasu's songs...
...are sure to be hits, right!?
I don't want just any hit song.
I have to send my feelings to Eichi-kun properly.
That's it, I quit!
Huh?
Takuto?
I'm not helping you for all the tea in China!
What do you mean by that?
Just give up already.
Writing a song was impossible for you in the first place.
W-Wait... Hold up. Takuto!
Takuto! Takuto!
My voice won't come out.
If Takuto isn't here, I...
...will never be...
like that again...
What should I do?
Man... what's with her?
Everything she says is "Eichi, Eichi, Eichi."
Can't she knock it off!?
Takuto, wait up!
Wait up, I said! What possessed you
to say something like that?
Why'd you just stop dead in your tracks?
Meroko.
It kinda looks like they're arguing.
Let's check it out.
O-Okay.
What is the meaning of this?
What do you mean, "the song is already done"?
Just what I said.
Her debut song remains unchanged.
That can't be.
The other day, you promised to wait for Mitsuki to write her own song!
Do you understand...
...how much we'll lose if this project fails?
If we got burned by leaving this up to an amateur, could you  take the heat by yourself?
W-Well...
But, a promise is a promise!
You're naïve. You won't get far in this world with that mindset.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Serves you right.
That's what you get.
Someone like you could never
understand Mitsuki's feelings.
That's right. You don't know how important promises are to her.
I should've known that...
So why did I say what I said to her?
I'm going back.
What are you doing to my head?
Wait! Geez... what's his  problem?
Yeouch, it's so hot!
Ow! That hurts!
Ow!
Mitsuki...
Back there, I...
What are you doing? Hurry up and apologize.
Takuto?
Then, this is...
While I was writing my song,
Grandma kept coming in to check on me.
So I fooled her by propping up my blanket.
W-What...
Takuto, I'm sorry about earlier.
E-Er... that's supposed to be my line.
I've been depending on
you and Meroko for everything.
Wanting to debut, and wanting to see Eichi-kun...
...are both part of my dream.
It'd be wrong for me to not make the effort myself.
So you've been writing this whole time?
Yeah. I've gone through a lot of grid paper.
But it was fun to think this much about a song.
I really do love singing!
Earlier, when I thought
I'd never be able to sing again...
...I was really sad. It was painful.
Of course, I do want to see Eichi-kun.
But I want to sing just as much!
This feeling makes my heart skip!
I can't make it stop!
That's it.
Eh? That's what?
Try singing with the true words that came from your heart, just as they are.
And put those feelings into my song?
Yeah.
But I wonder if I can say it well.
You told me just fine.
Me, too.
Okay! I got it! I'll try it!
That's it. That's the spirit!
Work hard!
Okay!
This represents the fullest
possible expression of my feelings.
Please take a look at them.
I suppose I can give it a glance.
You've backed me into a corner.
Hey, Takasu here.
Tell the lyricist that I decided to go with
something else for Kouyama Mitsuki's song.
That means...
I lost. I never thought you'd write a song this good.
We'll have to totally revamp
the concept and the costuming.
Does that mean-?
You did it! It's been accepted!
Your song's been chosen!
Eh? Really?
Yes. But either way,
we're on a tight schedule.
You made this bed,
so you'd better be ready to lie in it.
We're going to be busy.
Yes! We'll do our best!
What stage name are you using, if any?
That's right...
How about it? Should we just
go with your real name?
N-No, that'll be bad...
Um...
Hey, Mitsuki.
We've got nothing to worry about...
...if we get separated.
Why not?
Even it we're on opposite sides of the world,
the moon will still be in the sky.
So, I'll look for the moon up in the sky.
That's why you have to shine even brighter...
...so that I can find you sooner.
I've decided.
I'll go with Full Moon.
There's just one thing that's never gonna change...
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
the dream that I have always been drawing.
Zutto egaiteta yume
How would I, as I am right now
ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
look to those small eyes I used to have?
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
Say, won't you look up? The night sky stretches so far.
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Yes... very soon... you will understand...
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up...
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
...and find the full moon.
Full Moon wo sagashite
Let's sing a song!
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now.
itsu demo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Day by day...
Day by day
I hold the fate dealt by the past and the hopes of tomorrow in my heart.
kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou wo kono mune ni kakae
Let's sing a song!
Together, forever! As long as I'm with you, I can overcome any pain.
itsu demo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
More and more...
More and more
More and more and more... to be closer to you,
I stand here now and give...
Motto motto motto chika zukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Many thanks for you!
PREVIEW FOR NEXT TIME
Yo-do-le-hi-hoo!
Where'd that come from!?
Can't you tell? Just look at this scenery!
Blue skies, green mountains, and fresh air...
We didn't come here to play!
This is her first job, after all.
We have to see things through.
I get it. But I wonder if that girl can pull it off.
When all's said and done,
she's still 12 years old on the inside...
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The First Job.
THE FIRST JOB
Look forward to it!