TOO BITTER!!
Bad Fumika!
In order to become a proper full-grown lady, you have to be able to drink coffee!
I know what you mean, but still, it’s so bitter!
Fumika! We’re already in the 9th grade; how much longer will you stand to be treated like a kid!?
I don’t like that at all!
That’s why we have to work hard and prove to them that we’re adults!
Okay!
Now, let’s drink this and become more adult-like!
Yeah!
Ah, Fuuka-dono, Fumika-dono!
Ah, Kaede-nee!
I figure it’s been a while since the Walking Club actually went on a walk, so I came to invite you to join me, de gozaru.
What do you think, de gozaru?
YAAAAY! Yeah, we’ll go!
You two are so child-like and have the cutest responses, de gozaru!
The drawings seen are from Koyama Kimiko (Fuuka), and Kanou Mari (Fumika). Which is why we saved them.
BillyG x Hinatanko = nekkid pics!
by Fuuka
Fumika
There’s Asuna-san, Nodoka-san; then there’s Setsuna-san and Konoka-san.
Way to go, Aniki!
Having four partners in such a short amount of time is a brilliant achievement!
Is this alright, Negi? You’re making provisional contracts like no tomorrow!
Negi-kun, you’re a man now; learn to take some responsibility!
“…take some responsibility”?
In Japan, the law is that if you kiss someone, you have to marry that person.
Otherwise, it’s the death penalty.
W-what am I gonna do?!
Thanks for telling me that; I don’t even think my heart’s ready for this…!
I can’t believe you believed that, Asuna…
Well, back then they used to say, “a partner improves a wizard,” right?
You should aim to make contracts with the whole class rather than just four people, Aniki.
That’s a bit overboard, Chamo-kun.
Well then, shall we go out now?
D-Don’t tell me that we’re all gonna make partners out of the whole class…!
You’re mistaken, Asuna-san.
Didn’t you hear anything..?
We're going to investigate that incident.
That fairy was the cause of the accident, right?
What in the world… is this?
So this does have something to do with the fact that the Star Crystal was stolen!
But who did it? And what for?
What’s wrong, Aniki?
I could’ve sworn someone was watching us…
Ah, what’s this? It smells nice…
A flower petal?
From a black… rose?
And so, the Narutaki Sisters childishly set off to learn the teachings of Adulthood 101.
If you can face a scary dog, then you’ll become…!
You’ll become…!
If you can sit through a scary movie, then you’ll become…!
If you can walk back home while staying only on the white line, you'll become...!
You’ll become…!
With what we’ve done, I bet you we’ve become more adult-like!
I agree!
Aiming to become an adult must be hard, de gozaru.
What’s this? It's the three girls from the Walking Club, mya!
Ooh, so the tallest one in the class is hanging out with the two smallest ones in the class!
It kinda looks like a scene with a mother and her two kids!
Mother?
Kids!?
With the three of you lined up like that, you two look all childlike and pretty!
Childlike…!?
English gentlemen seem to praise women like this…
Were you actually praising, mya?
Oh, I forgot to buy frozen pilaf.
From here on out, the Walking Club is over!
My, my. Why, de gozaru?
Kaede-nee, whenever we’re around you, we look like kids!
We won’t be able to appear adult-like!
Is that so, de gozaru?
But not everything is based on appearance, de gozaru.
If you can improve your inner self, you two will be ready to become adults, de gozaru.
Really!?
Really, de gozaru! So there’s no problem with the Walking Club, de gozaru!
But you know…
…how can we improve our inner selves?
Hmm, de gozaru…
I got it!
If we go there, we might know!
Library Island… Mahora’s largest library!
Precious books were collected from all over the world for many years.
After interior reconstruction… the result, after all, no one really knows 100%.
Amazing… it’s like a labyrinth of books!
Honya-chan, is this what it’s like down here!?
Yes, but this is only a minute portion of the library.
So this is an exploration, eh?
It’s dangerous here, so us middle schoolers are only allowed to go three stories deeper.
Wow, full of books, isn’t it..?
Ojou-sama, it’s dangerous here, so I ask that you refrain from touching any of the books here.
Could these be the masterpieces and art scrolls made for the Shinmeiryuu during the enlightened era...
for the Ougi Hyakusei technique!?
See, Ojou-sama? It’s dangerous here.
Look who’s talking, Secchan…
Ah! These are the masterpieces of the Second Generation Shinmeiryuu!
There are traps set up here for thieves, so please be careful!
Really?
I doubt that’s what you should be saying…
GHOST!
Ah! Hello, Ojiisan!
Down here again? You must love books. Yamada, over and out.
W-Who is that man?
A regular at the library. He knows anything and everything about the library here!
Ah, he fell.
Yeah, sure he knows anything and everything about it.
With these around, we can’t search in a relaxed manner.
Negi-sensei, what kind of book are you looking for?
I want to research and find out what this is.
It’d be great if I had access to an old magic encyclopedia, but if possible, I’d like one from before the 18th century.
What’s wrong, Honya-chan?
I’m sure if we delve deeper into the library, we can find it, but…
But…?
If we go deeper, it’s likely that there are more dangerous traps.
But it’s okay! If it’s for Negi-sensei, then…
I’ll do my best!
Hey, is it alright if I go home now?
I see; it’s Library Island, de gozaru. You’re going here to read up on adulthood and learn its culture. Right, de gozaru?
No, Kaede-nee! They say that deep down here, there’re all types of books.
We’re hoping that we can see if there’s anything written in there that would say anything on how to become an adult quicker.
A book that will help you turn into adults, de gozaru?
Is there even such a book, de gozaru?
There is!
Who are you!?
Yamada.
Please be careful where you step.
A...
Please watch your…
su...
Please watch…
na!
Are you okay, Asuna-san!?
She falls for traps, amusingly…
Asuna’s mishaps are normal…
No, not to that extent!
That’s not a compliment.
Motsu’s late, mya.
Hibernation?
Neither Makie nor Motsu would know that this would be the encounter of destiny which would influence their future, Amoré.
I think… this is the place!
By overcoming many, many predicaments, Negi and company have finally arrived.
Thank you, Chamo! We will never forget you and your accomplishments!
I'm still alive!!
Check it out! A tree made out of books!
Whoa, a pool of books!
Looks like it’d hurt if you swim in it.
Secchan, they have a restaurant!
Whoa, the menu looks like a dictionary!
"Natsume Souseki Menu:"
"I am a Cat Soup", "Sanshirou Sauté", "Son’s Red Shirt with Cream".
Is this even edible!?
Well, it’s a black goat menu, no?
Ah, all this is making my head spin!
Are you gonna be okay, Asuna-san?
Well, she hates studying, so being around a plethora of books has caused her mind to go blank!
This isn’t good… I have to find that book I was looking for and get out of here ASAP!
I don’t wanna go home!
I love this! I wanna live here!
Nodoka-san…
Well, at least someone lives here.
It’s that guy again.
My name is Yamada.
According to Yamada-san, it should be around here, de gozaru.
I’m so tired… I’m completely exhausted!
But we still have to hurry and find a way to become adults!
The Walking Club always tries their hardest, de gozaru!
All that’s left is for us to go beyond that door!
Looks like it’s the wrong door, de gozaru.
That door over there looks suspicious!
Let’s open it and see what’s inside!
I’m Yama-DAAAAH!
Looks like the wrong door again, de gozaru.
Let’s try that one, then.
Oh, are you here to collect the payment?
This isn’t it either. What’re we gonna do?
Maybe it’d be quicker if we asked someone for help!
Alright, then I’ll ask Yamada-san, de gozaru!
You two just wait right there, de gozaru!
Wait, Kaede-nee!
Kaede-nee!
She’s not here…
D-Daddy!
IT’S A PLOT TWIST!
You’re wrong.
This is a magic book and all, but…
The magic books you own are more detailed, I think…
Ane-san’s got such a serious look on her face; this is new.
I found it!
Really, Asuna-san!?
Look, look! It’s “Chupacabras Around the World!”
Ooh, it’s a photo collection!
So they do have such things.
Geez, Asuna-san…
Oh, I know, Aniki! Why don’t you use Nodoka-jouchan’s skill to find what you’re looking for?
Nodoka-san’s?
From what I can tell, her encyclopedias are like a databank of knowledge,
containing records and documents from all over the universe!
If that’s the case, would we be able to look into the future from here…?
Please help me confirm this, Nodoka-san!
Okay!
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
Argh, Suka Card again!
Geez, just do it properly, Negi!
Even if you say that…!
I’m so sorry…
I’m so hungry. I can’t move…
Quick to exhaustion, aren’t you?
Here is your meal.
This is the Natsume Souseki Menu.
So, Tanaka-san makes the food…
It’s Yamada.
I’m lost, de gozaru.
Thank you for the meal!
This time, I’ll do better!
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
It’s a Rare Card! Nice job, Aniki!
As long as I have these encyclopedias, there’s nothing to worry about! Just listen to me!
Well then, can you please tell us what the item is?
Of course!
What is the name of this item?
Like I said, I want to know what the item is called.
If you do not know the name of the item, please refer to the Table of Contents.
Oh wow! There’s so many items on here…!
W-What should we look for?
Um…”Magic Item”…I think…
No, it must be more specific, or…
Wait a second here!
Doesn’t this look like a rice cracker?
Jou-chan, that is definitely wrong…
Alright, then what if we look up “fairy”?
"Fairy"… there’s so many of them!
Can’t you just instantly pull up data like before!?
We were desperate back then…
Then be desperate!!
I’m hungry again…
I guess we’re out of time…
I guess the Souseki Menu was no good...
What’s wrong, Negi?
Black roses…
These were blooming earlier...
That shadow was…
No way… it can’t be…
Wait!
Negi! Don’t!
Wait! Wait up, Father!
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
Fuuka-san?... Fumika-san!?
Negi-sensei…
is flying…
Ah, he got caught again…
That’s why I told him not to do it…
So, Negi-sensei…
You’re a mage!
Oh, so Negi-sensei’s a school teacher as an assignment from magic school…
For everyone to become a partner, I’m so shocked!
Please don’t tell anyone about this, okay?
Okay!
So you’re aiming to be a great mage like your dad... eh?
How cool!
Don’t think of it that way!
I’m still just a child.
Not at all!
Negi-sensei, even if you’re younger than us…
you’re like an adult!
Yet, on the other hand, we’re…
I’m sure you’ll turn out to be awesome adults!
It’s alright.
Negi-sensei…
I think we should just give up…
on finding out how to be an adult…
Hey, Negi-sensei.
What is it?
Um… we would also like to exchange a provisional contract with you…
Are we allowed to?
We are, right? We’re even keeping this a secret.
Negi-sensei…
Okay.
Yay!
Aniki! Preparations are done!
Pactio!
Provisional Contract Complete~
Tastes like an adult!
Desu!
In the end, I wasn’t able to find that magic encyclopedia…
But, it’s great that we all made it out alive!
I know! I thought I was gonna die back there!
I’m lost.
Looks like you’ve gained two more partners, huh?
Then that means… here ya go!
From here on out, you’re now members of the Chupa Team!
I see. That might actually be a good idea!
So, you’re making all of Negi-kun’s partners Chupa Team members as well for a secret identity!
So then, for us to be gathering like this wouldn’t be suspicious…
What are you talking about!? Of course you become a Chupa Team Member if you become partnered with Negi!
It was an ordinary club joining, then…
I see. So are all these people your partners?
You’re…
They call me… the Black Rose Baron.
Black Rose… Baron?
Wait!
While Negi has made two more partners, Fuuka and Fumika, a new presence has arrived: The Black Rose Baron!
Is he a friend, or is he a foe? To find out, however, sit tight and wait until next time, Amigo!
In order for a ninja to practice running without making any noise, they must run on wet tissues without tearing them, de gozaru.
Next Time: “By concealing 'heart' with 'blade' we read: 'Enduring'…
It is a bit different from writing 'seriousness', and reading it as 'really'"… by Kaede
Did they even have tissues in the Edo Era, de gozaru?
I did it! It’s complete!
You’re finally done!
This is the ultimate equip item: an exoskeleton-powered suit made to fit even the smallest hand...
and boosts your power and raises your fighting strength!
AKA: Super Power Hand!
Ooh, I can feel the power!
Battle with me, Kuu Laozi!
Fight!
Meat bun?
With a shark fin filling!
I am defeated!
And the battle continues!