The Girl of White had a truly beautiful, good heart.
In contrast, the Girl of Black had a very unsightly, evil heart.
The Girl of Black envied and despised the
Girl of White, always cheerful and smiling,
and yearned to erase her very existence.
You...
were listening, right?
But there's more to it.
These two Girls...
were once one and the same girl.
Now, go and enjoy their world.
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
All done, nice work!
Both of you did really well!
Come to the dressing room later.
Ulith—
No. There are people here.
I-I'm sorry...
Save it for when we're alone.
I'll be waiting.
Iona...
I hope you're ready for this.
Iona-san is the Girl of Black?
Is that true, Iona-san?
What's... happening to me?
W-Well, what happened to Futase-san after that?
That's all I heard from her.
I see...
It doesn't really add up, though...
I mean, even if Iona really is that "Girl of Black,"
what does that have to do with Selector battles anyway?
And then there's the Girl of White, too...
White...
Ruuko?
Ah, yeah.
My conversation with Mayu-kun lasted but a short interlude.
Chiyori-chan?
Don't hold it in if you need to go.
Uwaaaah!
Wh-What?
The excitement is killing me!
Ah, she has these spasms from time to time.
Just don't mind her, and please continue your discussion!
So what you're saying is that the WIXOSS novelization was born from
the intimate friendship between Futase-sensei and Fumio-san?
Friendship?
It started off as a web novel, right?
Yes.
Writing as a
Profession
As I was researching ways to become a novelist,
I discovered that this approach had become viable.
Futase Fumio discussion thread.
1. Anonymous Writer : 20XX/XX/XX(X) XX:XX:XX
This crazy good newbie writer named Futase Fumio just appeared!
Discuss!
2. Anonymous Writer : 20XX/XX/XX(X) XX:XX:XX
It looks like this Futase submitted to Doors.
Was this really Futase's first work?
Give me some recs
Have you heard of
Futase Fumio?
Hell yeah I have
Pretty good, right?
Author
Futase Fumio
Everyone's Ranking
Web Novel Ranking
Comprehensive Ranking 1-50
By Genre
Monthly
Weekly
Daily
Wish ~That card leads beyond eternity
I didn't expect it to turn out this well, though.
To: Futase Fumio
Sub: Your "Wish ~That card leads beyond eternity~"
Dear Futase Fumio:
Pleased to meet you, I am
Tachibana from Full Moon Books.
In regards to "Wish ~That card leads beyond eternity~",
I would like to discuss a proper novel release...
You're amazing, Sensei!
Every fiber of Chiyori is wailing
from that happy end!
What kind of moron are you?!
And what part of that is happy?!
What happened to Fumio-san after she became a LRIG?
Not even Futase knows where she is.
Futase-san returned from being a LRIG,
only to become a Selector looking for battles.
But that's...
Wait.
The wish was granted the moment she got published, right?
Then isn't it strange to become a Selector for the same reason?
From my perspective, you're the one saying strange things.
How so?
You being a LRIG now must mean that you've been a Selector before.
You must have had your own unyielding wish ,
so you believed in your LRIG's saccharine words and won enough to become an Eternal Girl.
Hanayo-san wasn't out to deceive me.
She always looked out for me.
I'm sure she's worrying now, too...
Is your wish of the kind you can truly call granted if it lasts but for an instant?
Well...
Or is it of the kind that's only realized when it lasts beyond the moment—when it lasts forever?
It's... something I wanted to last forever.
How about you?
Fumio, too...
Her wish is the same.
Becoming a novelist means living as a novelist.
Having written two volumes doesn't give me the right call myself a novelist yet.
I'm merely a hollow existence that will fade like mist were I to stop writing.
The true fulfillment of a wish only begins once you believe it has been granted.
There is no meaning if you are satisfied by your accomplishments before you die.
That means... there's no end to it.
Unlike Fumio, I haven't read all that many books.
The only reason I somehow
managed to write the novels
was because I had first-hand knowledge of both a LRIG and a Selector.
But it wasn't long before her well of knowledge dried up.
I see. That explains her writer's block.
B-But you swore a passionate oath, and I'm sure the power of your friendship will save Futase-sensei—
Reality and stories are different!
Friendships, oaths—none of that will help you!
B-But Sensei can...
I can't write, as much as I want to.
And yet I must keep writing!
What is it that binds me—
a duty or my promise to her?
As I've continued living as Futase Fumio, I've lost sight of even that distinction.
Who am I?
By the looks of it, it's less of an Eternal Girl's wish...
...and more of a curse, isn't it?
A curse that crushes you under the weight of someone else's wish,
making you live a stranger's life and lose sight of who you once were.
I will go to the room with the white windows again.
Mayu... I have to meet her so I can keep writing the story.
So, are you my next opponent?
Or is it you?!
Which one of you will battle me?
Neither Chiyori-chan nor I will battle you!
Oh, so you won't...
Wait...
I can write a new chapter thanks to you.
I need to write... I need to write...
Do you see now?
You may be acting the part of a novel heroine, adamant as you are about being right.
That's not what I—
However,
some have to rely on Selector battles.
Like Futase.
I need to go...
White room...
Large windows...
To Mayu-kun...
I need to go...
White room...
Don't let it bother you, okay?
Sure...
Chiyori-chan?!
She must be in shock, considering how crazy she was about the novels.
How about you, Yuzuki?
To be honest, it was a bit much for me, too.
I realized just how much Hanayo-san
must be suffering because of my wish.
It's just too painful, even if they get to be human again.
That's why we have to put a stop to Selector battles!
I thought that if we made all the battling stop, no one would have to suffer anymore.
Ruuko...
But some girls need to battle even though they know the truth.
Her situation is different!
When I met Akira-san, she said that battling me would let her find the strength to live again.
And we only met because we were all Selectors, right?
You're at it now, too?!
That's why I...
I still want to free all the girls who became LRIGs!
And I don't want anyone to suffer after they've become Eternal Girls!
Ruu—
Ruuko...
And if there's a way to help Futase-san become her former self again,
then I want to make that possible, too.
What Iona-san said earlier...
If you really want to save everyone, don't let
minor issues sway you, and show your true self!
...made me understand what's truly important.
Iona-san, thank you for what you told me during that battle.
Iona-san?! What's the matter?!
You're a good girl.
It's because you asked me to...
Oh?
Aki-lovely's group
I think I've noticed a few girls
who changed all of a sudden!
What happens if you have one?
Something good?
Oh, so that's what's
got all the girls excited
Oh, it's me!
I think I have one of those!
Was she serious about that
whole "special LRIG" thing?
If you have that special card
then what happens?
I'm so happy.
I actually have another favor to ask you.
What is it? I'll do anything!
Anything!
It's something I can only ask from you, Akira.
I see. I'll do it.
But she's probably going to say she doesn't want to battle.
Do you know what it is that's most precious to her?
Start thinking from there.
I'm looking forward to an entertaining show.
You won't let me down, will you?
I'm home, Grandma!
Welcome home!
P-Pardon the intrusion!
Welcome to you, too!
Girl of Black...
Girl of Darkness...
I'm...
You're the Girl of Black.
The Girl of Black?
Envious of everyone, you bring them all sorrow.
Hated by everyone, you hate them all.
You're such a bad girl.
And such a lonely girl.
No...
That's not me...
Ah, you hate, hate, hate,
hate them all.
The Girl of Black brings misery to everyone.
No... no, no!
Battling for all eternity,
bringing misery to everyone...
That is the fate of the Girl of Black.
No!
No...
What should we do? Do you think she caught a cold?
Maybe some medicine?
Let me go get it!
Hold it! How do you plan on giving it to her?
O-Oh, right...
I haven't caught a cold or anything since I became a LRIG...
Iona-san...
Are you cold? Do you feel feverish, Iona-san?
Does your stomach hurt?
Why... is she...
If there's anything I can do, please tell me!
... so concerned about me?
I'll stay by your side!
But...
that's why...
I just feel... a little cold.
Isn't it painful?
Doesn't it hurt?
You're the Black one, so you're bound to hate all that's white.
Longing for what's white, wishing to be by the White one's side...
will just...
make the pain even worse.
Looks like she's calmed down a bit.
Yup.
You know...
Does all that stuff about Iona being the Girl of Black mean that...?
Yeah...
Iona-san must know something after all.
We need to grill her again when she's back to health.
Wouldn't she open up to us more if we became friends?
Ruuko?
She must have a reason why she's keeping secrets from us.
I had things I couldn't tell Tama, either.
I only thought of my own feelings,
and I didn't consider how Tama felt at all.
That's how I hurt her...
This time, I want to do things right!
I want to start over again...
You're such a softie, Ruuko!
Wh-What?
Now I totally look like the bad guy here,
saying how we should grill her.
Let's all start over again, together.
This time in a way that nobody has to sacrifice themself.
Yeah.
Yup.
Ruu-chan?
Don't you think Hitoe-chan's family will be worried soon?
It's this late already!
I have to leave now!
Hitoe.
Do you... mind if I stay?
Sure, be by her side.
I wish I could stay too, but my mom would get worried.
Both of you, thanks.
I'm good from here.
You have Iona-san to care for.
Take care, okay?
I'll call you when I get home!
I guess I should hurry...
You're late!
I was getting tired of all the waiting.
A-Akira-san...
Hittoe, let's battle!
We haven't battled once since we got new LRIGs, right?
I don't want to!
You scared of losing again?
C'mon, don't worry!
I'll...
hurt you even more than last time.
I won't battle!
Aww...
If Hittoe doesn't want to battle me,
I guess I'll just go pay Ruu-Ruu a visit!
Don't get involved with Ruuko anymore!
Huh?
The hell asked for your opinion?
I won't let anyone trying to hurt Ruuko get away!
You're pissing me off...
You're fucking pissing me off!
Don't push your luck, you worthless extra!
I decided... to start over with everyone!
Battle me, then...
Show me how you're gonna stop me!
Looks like she doesn't have her LRIG with her!
Huh?!
There's not even a whiff of one!
Are you shitting me?
What the hell?!
Looks like you can only play a regular game of WIXOSS!
Shut up!
Damn it... damn it!
What am I supposed to tell Ulith...
I'm letting her down...
No... no way...
Ulith will start to hate me!
I don't want that!
Wh-What?
Trash me...
She's going to trash me...
I don't want that... I don't want that!
What should I do?
Sorry... I'm so sorry...
Start thinking from there.
I'm looking forward to an entertaining show.
Akira-san...
Ah...
As long as I've got you here,
I'm still good.
Rain?
The rain's getting stronger.
I hope Hitoe isn't getting drenched.
Warm...
Iona!
Do you remember? You suddenly collapsed!
I'll stay by your side!
It... wasn't a dream?
Are you feeling better now?
Yes...
Thank goodness...
Ah, this is...
You said you were cold, so I thought...
Doing this is of no use to a LRIG like me.
Maybe it's Hitoe!
Grandma, I'll get it!
Hitoe, did you make it home before the rain?
Hittoe wouldn't cooperate, so she got all wet!
Akira-san?
New
Urisu
I caught her
Correct!
Great job, Ruu-Ruu! It's Aki-lovely!
Where's Hitoe?
Get your ass to where I tell you.
Yup, yup... okay!
Ruuko, don't!
Hitoe?!
Shut up, shitface!
I got it! I'll come, so please stop hurting Hitoe!
Don't forget to bring Iona with you!
Selectors and LRIGs have to be
buddy-buddy all the time, you know!
Right now, Iona isn't—
You're coming, now!
How's Hitoe?
Ruuko?
Akira-san got Hitoe...
She said to bring Iona with me...
Fine. Take me with you.
But...
You can't abandon her, right?
I'm fine now.
Iona, I'm sorry.
Thanks!
Ruuko!
Hitoe!
That's horrible...
Tell me about it!
I mean, just look at this bruise she left.
What am I supposed to do about my next shoot?
You're the one who started it!
It's your fault for not being with her even though you're her damn LRIG!
So where's Iona?
You're as brutish as always.
I wish you could've seen Hitoe
getting all desperate and stuff.
Like, how she was going on about protecting Ruu-Ruu...
Getting up in my face, weren't you, huh?!
Hitoe!
Once a nobody, always a nobody.
If you want a battle with me that much, then you've got it...
Ruuko!
But in return, I want you to never do anything like this again!
Oops! Looks like you're totally off the track here!
She's here!
She came!
Are you trying to leave me out of the fun?
Ulith...
That
Existence
Is
Pitch-Black
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
How unsightly.
How pathetic.
It's not like I'm interested.
What a letdown.
It's not my taste.
It's not my taste, but...
That
Lie
is a
Scar
That lie is a scar.