When was it again?
Sitting under a sky aglow with dusk,
our little boat lingered onward dreamily.
Children three nestled near with eager eye and willing ear.
Long has paled that sunny sky.
The echoes of their laughter and the memories of our joy
have all been slain by autumn frosts.
Where has she gone,
having rivaled the sun itself?
In a wonderland they lie, dreaming as the days go by.
Dreaming as the summers die.
Ever we drift down the stream, floating through its golden gleam.
Mirror Capital
Life, what is it but a dream?
CapitaL CraZe
Thus spake Koto,
our protagonist
Whatever life may hold, I'll regret nothing.
That's what I decided. That's what I believed.
That pride walks by my side as an old friend.
So it has, and so it will.
CHILDHOOD
I have to get going.
Okay.
Sure is a gloomy face there!
What a moody little brat!
Shut it.
CENTRAL
AXIS
UNION
CENTRAL
AXIS
UNION
SHRINE
It won't be long.
Okay.
Thanks.
Take care of the cottage.
Okay.
If anything is wrong, just tell the priests.
Also...
Count your tears, crybaby!
Inari won't be around to save the day, coward!
That's enough, you two.
The familiars don't mean it like that.
Don't mind them.
You have to stand your ground now that you're part of the shrine people.
Planetary Union
Shrine
Don't let it get to you, whatever they say.
Okay, Master.
I can't believe that kid the fox took in is one of us now.
He's sort of a free spirit, you know?
She's hopeless.
What's the fox thinking?
Is she human or spirit to begin with?
Just look at her red eyes.
Don't skip practice.
Be strong and pay the boys back.
I'm sure your mother wants that too, Koto.
Do your best, kiddo!
Next time we meet we'll play with you.
Take care!
He didn't really tell me anything,
but it sounded like my mom's alive somewhere.
I was surrounded by many adults who hated me and only a few who liked me,
but that thought was enough keep me going.
You're not gonna stop Koto?
Koto!
If you're going to beat him up, pay attention to your stance!
Okay!
Those two are abnormal!
The bearer of the fox mask should know how to behave!
I demand that the chief priest hear about this!
Inari, Koto!
You heard the man.
I think it's his fault because he was messing around during practice!
I also think he should have apologized!
And he shouldn't be so weak!
You should take a few days off.
I can take care of your students in the meantime.
No! No! I don't want that, Master!
But he feels he is at an impasse with his educational ideas.
No, no, no, no!
Someone should help him with his job.
That wasn't the point!
In a wonderland they lie, dreaming as the days go by.
Good morning!
You're mumbling to yourself again.
Mumbling?
You were thinking about the Mirror Capital again, weren't you?
I wonder.
You're always lying!
I know it!
Ouch!
You put your whole weight into that kick, didn't you?
I guess I should praise you for taking practice so seriously.
Of course!
I'll be the strongest one the shrine has!
And you used to cry so much...
There's no greater joy for a teacher than seeing your students develop.
I might be stronger than you one day.
That'd make you the new master.
I wanna go and look for my mom.
I want to meet her and talk to her.
It'd be nice if she was pretty.
She'd be surprised, right?
I wanna ask about Dad too.
But you know the truth, don't you, Master?
Yeah.
Koto,
I'm sure you'll make it there one day.
Where summer dies and is born anew.
Paradise lost.
The place beyond the mirror, where the gravestones of memories stand in neat rows.
I'm sure.
How are you doing, Master?
I'm doing great!
There! Stop them!
Do it!
Gosh, the city is lively again.
I'm happy to see everyone's having fun.
Do enjoy the food, now.
There are two kinds of people in the world.
Those who cause me trouble and those who don't.
You with me?
Ouch!
You little...
I'm having a fair amount of fun here,
but I still want to meet you all again, Master.
I don't know when I can go back,
but I know one day we will all...
To be continued!