Why, Rin? Why did you become a dark ninja?
If you want to know...
Come and find out!
A map of Serpentine Academy?
I'll be expecting you, Mr. Kiriya.
Rin!
You can come out now.
You knew we were here?
Well, that's Mr. Kiriya for you, eh?
I thought I ordered you to wait in the room.
We're terribly sorry, but you were acting out of sorts, Mr. Kiriya, so we...
couldn't resist.
Mr. Kiriya...
You know Serpentine Academy's whereabouts now, don't you?
Probably.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
Yin and Yang
That's where they're based at?
It's pretty deep into the mountains, huh?
It's an area that is off-limits,
because nominally, it's a heritage site.
Probably the work of some company with dark ninja connections.
Please let us go to Serpentine Academy, Mr. Kiriya!
Yeah! We have to help Hibari!
I can't do that.
Why not?
Mr. Kiriya!
Things are not that simple.
If we charge right into a dark ninja facility...
Ikaruga is right.
We would risk igniting all-out war between us.
Ninjas exists as shadows in society.
If these shadows waged war with each other, it could rock the very foundations of society.
Then why are we the only ones who have to keep ourselves in check?
They attacked us first, didn't they?
Indeed. I doubt the dark ninjas would violate our tacit agreement.
Assuming this was an arbitrary act by them...
Rin, what is your objective?
We can't just leave Hibari with them like this!
Yin and Yang.
Such is the way of the world.
Grandpa!
Master Hanzo!
Without Yang, there would be no Yin. The opposite likewise.
Are you saying that fighting the dark ninjas is pointless?
No, their conduct has been lawless and evil.
The presence of virtuous ninjas as a shield to resist their evil is a vital necessity.
None of this complicated stuff makes any difference!
We have to—
We know the location. I'm going.
Yagyu!
Go ahead.
This is, ultimately, a conflict between fellow students.
Fellow students?
Then, we will not be participating?
Of course not.
Adults should not become involved in playground spats.
But, in that case...
I, Hanzo, will bear full repsonsibility.
I won't let anyone come down on you.
Master Hanzo...
Grandpa!
All right! We've got the go-ahead from the legendary ninja, Master Hanzo!
How can you be so happy-go-lucky?
How can you call yourselves ninjas if you can't save a friend?
Right, Yagyu?
Yes.
If those are your orders, Master Hanzo... I understand.
Mr. Kiriya!
That's more like it!
Well, with that... here are some goodies from me.
Putting all that aside...
Aww...
I know we left the room without permission, but he doesn't have to keep us this long.
This is all part of our training.
Here we go again...
What?
Nothing!
Katsuragi...
Hmm?
Once we set foot in enemy territory, anything could happen.
I'm going to be counting on you, okay?
Wow... Those words, coming from you, Ikaruga...
We have our responsibilities as upperclassmen, okay?
I've been counting on you, right from the start.
Huh?
Let's get ourselves fired up and go, class rep.
Right.
Hey, Yagyu.
We'll rescue Hibari, no matter what, okay?
We're sure to save her. Hibari has not just me, but all of these friends here to turn to as well.
Yeah, you're right!
With all of us together, it'll be fine for sure!
Yeah.
As I guessed.
Security's lax inside the castle.
I'm sensing a powerful presence on the top floor.
If the top-secret ninja art scroll is anywhere, it must be...
You mean to betray me?
I do not understand what you mean.
You revealed our location to Hanzo Academy.
If that isn't betrayal, what is it?
Simply obtaining the top-secret ninja art scroll is meaningless.
As I've repeatedly said, the scroll requires its chosen bearer to be present.
All I did was facilitate the process.
You intentionally called the students of Hanzo here, in order to fight my own students, is that it?
Affirmative.
The ninja students are still unaccomplished,
and as a result, owing to their strength being unknown as well,
it's possible that one of them could inherit the secrets of the scroll.
As long as we have both the Yin and Yang scrolls,
it's inevitable that the Yang scroll's successors,
which is to say, the virtuous ninja students would be summoned.
Are you insane?!
If the higher-ups hear that the virtuous ninjas have learned of this place—
You were the one so eager for success that you acted of your own accord.
What?
Bury your head in the sand or take flight. Whatever suits you.
I won't stop you.
Why, you little... You've got some nerve!
Seize the traitor Suzune!
Everyone is coming here?
Hanzo Academy Training Camp
We're not breaking them?
Talk about a letdown.
Well, it's plastic.
Cleaning up afterward would be a hassle.
Ikaruga!
Yes.
Katsuragi!
Yessir!
Asuka!
Yes.
Yagyu!
Your mission is to infiltrate
Serpentine Academy, save Hibari,
and recover the top-secret ninja art scroll!
Understood!
The priority, though,
is to return with Hibari, safe and sound.
Yes!
Ultimately, this is a squabble among children, after all.
It's morphin' time!
Right! Ninja morph!
Move out!
Forward!
Launching!
Here goes! Yahoo!
Right into enemy territory, huh?
Even though we've never beaten them before.
Asuka.
Grandpa!
Do not forget what constitutes true strength.
True strength...
You mean this?
When I heard that you had won that, I was so pleased.
I've been keeping it as a good luck charm.
Listen, Grandpa...
Hold onto it. When I come back, I'll need to put the scroll we retrieve in here, after all.
Very well. Off you go then.
Right!
Asuka... taking off now!
I'm not afraid! After all...
I'm Grandpa's granddaughter!
And also...
I'm a Hanzo Academy ninja!
Come back safely now.
If only...
this could be so simple.
Daidoji?
You're talking about Rin, right?
Mm.
Rin was probably acting on her own when she gave us their location.
Once that comes out, punishment is inevitable.
Which is why you're planning to follow the girls, isn't it?
Was it that obvious?
With the two of you plus Rin tangled up in this, it seemed unavoidable.
It's not something you can leave alone.
You are most perceptive.
I have uncovered another disturbing fact.
How disturbing?
Each of the dark ninja students seems to specialize in a forbidden art.
A forbidden art?
Senran Kagura
I'll show you the training grounds today.
Everyone is coming here.
I can't tell Haruka about it though.
What do I do?
What's wrong, Hibari?
It's such a large area, but nobody's here.
Oh, they're here, all right.
Then, this is for earth camouflage techniques?
Yes. This place is for drills to merge with the ground's surface.
It's been just about... 30 hours since they started, I'd say.
Th-They do it that long?
"That long"? They're not even halfway done.
And over here, water camouflage techniques?
Hibari!
Hibari, it's your turn.
I'm not sure I can do this.
It's all right. I know you can.
Yagyu...
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
There! You're exposed!
They don't have to go that far.
I-I'm sorry! Thank you for your guidance!
Students who fail must learn the hard way.
Ultimately, it benefits the student.
What's wrong?
She got so hurt, but her friends...
Nobody even attempted to look after her.
What are you talking about?
Her friends are there to make sure the mission is carried out, right?
Those who become an obstacle are no help at all, are they?
But...
This is why coddled little princesses are no good to us.
I see you too!
Thank you for your guidance!
The training here is harsh.
That's the whole reason why we
...desperately strive to aim higher...
so that we can become first-rate ninjas.
We have a lecture this afternoon.
I see. Their way of thinking is completely different. They are completely focused on their goals.
Hibari?
Y-Yes?
My, you're such a clumsy little girl.
I-I'm sorry.
That's part of what makes you so adorable.
Off you go.
Everyone ready?
Yes.
So that's Serpentine Academy, huh?
Hibari's there.
Let's wait here for the sun to go down.
A nice bath after training is the best!
I have to get the scroll back before everyone gets here.
What's with the gloomy face?
Oh, it's nothing.
U-Um, can I ask you all something?
If it's to do with sprouts, ask whatever you like!
I-It's not about sprouts.
Well, what's it about then?
I was wondering... What's Ms. Suzune like?
Well, she's a good teacher.
She's very strict, but she places faith in our strengths.
It sometimes hurts me that she isn't interested in sprouts,
but she's the one who brought me up to be as fine as I am.
Seize the traitor Suzune!
What's the matter?
Are you starting to miss your Hanzo Academy teacher?
You are free to go back to them.
I-It's not that!
Everyone, stop picking on my Hibari.
She's still a newbie here, after all. Right?
U-Um...
Oh, my... Whatever is the matter?
Looks like you're the one picking on her, Haruka.
Oh? That's not true at all.
H-Haruka, you're being a bit indecent.
Why are you turning red, Mirai?
I-I am not turning red! Yomi, you dummy!
Idiots.
I think, deep down, Haruka isn't a bad person.
Neither are the others.
They didn't have any other option but to become dark ninjas.
The scroll's in that room, all right.
I have to get it back somehow.
I, Homura, am here with the others, as per your summons.
Camouflage drape: crafted specially to refract light,
it allows one to visually blend in with one's surroundings.
I'll stay here until everyone leaves.
Ms. Suzune betrayed us?
What do you mean by that?
Suzune leaked the location of this place to Hanzo Academy.
Why would she do such a thing?
Dear me, did she take a leaf out of my book?
She blindsided me.
I had not forgotten that Suzune came from Hanzo Academy, but still...
I knew it.
So the rumors are true.
Ms. Suzune...
was a virtuous ninja?
Now that those Hanzo folks know about this place, they'll probably attempt to sneak in here.
It will be up to you to intercept them and wipe out every last one of them!
Affirmative!
Consider this a battle not just for our academy, but for the fate of all dark ninjas!
Defeat will not be tolerated!
Of course!
That desire. Such should be the spirit of a ninja.
Know though that if you lose, I shall extinguish your Entity Crests.
Entity Crests: a forbidden art
that grants the caster absolute control over the life of the subject.
My ninjas, representatives of the proud Serpentine Academy,
I trust you are all content with that.
In other words, our backs are to the wall.
Hmph, surely you jest.
It's not possible for us to lose.
That's right.
On the contrary, it makes it more thrilling this way.
Naturally, since there is no escape from our Entity Crests.
I have to tell the others!
Oh, my. What are you doing here?
Um, I was going back to my room, but got lost along the way.
Really?
And you wandered all the way to the top floor?
Hibari, is your sense of direction really that poor?
Y-Yes, it is.
I see. Well then...
That means you heard everything.
Wh-What are you doing, Haruka?!
I'm sorry, but your interference will mess things up for us.
I knew it'd be you.
You were sent here to spy on us, weren't you?
Uh oh, does this call for torture?
Remember what I said in the beginning? You're responsible for your actions.
Let's go!
What happened?!
Over there! Hurry!
Getting here's one thing... but we can't find the entrance to the castle!
Splitting into two teams was the right call.
Intruders!
This way appears to swing around to the rear of the castle.
You're right.
Now, you behave yourself in there, okay?
Haruka, are you all going to die if you lose?
Yes, that's right.
That's messed up! It's wrong!
Everyone has an Entity Crest cast upon entry into the Academy.
Everyone?
Originally, it was used only on students who dropped out
or ran away to prevent them from
.revealing the location of this place.
But he is able to freely alter its conditions.
Aren't you afraid to bear such a terrible curse?
"One who fears death, fears failure less."
Isn't that right, Ms. Suzune?
Ms. Suzune?!
We've got intruders! They could be students from Hanzo Academy!
Hmph, they've come, all right.
The amount of time and money invested into this academy is astronomical.
But if my superiors find out about this fiasco,
I'll lose more than just my position. I'll be a dead man.
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to unravel the mystery of Yin and Yang myself,
and with its power claim the organization for myself.
The entrance's nowhere to be found, huh?
Well, I wonder how Asuka and Yagyu are doing.
Ikaruga! Katsu!
Oh, it's you two!
We didn't find the entrance either.
There must be a hidden passageway somewhere.
They know we're here. We have to hurry!
You don't have to tell us. We all know!
Hibari...
What is it, Yagyu?
What are you doing?
It's Hibari. I'm picking up Hibari's scent.
You what?
Could that be?
A hidden door, as expected.
Nicely done, Yagyu!
It was only because of Hibari.
Welcome.
It's you!
We are here to offer you a warm reception...
ladies of Hanzo Academy.
I wonder if you might make this a bit entertaining for me.
Next Episode Preview
Asuka, would you put this away for me?
Sure, Grandpa.
And this, too.
Huh?
This, too.
O-Okay, but I can't fit all of these down my front.
It's like a refreshing exercise for the heart!
Next time, "Castle Showdown."
Castle Showdown
Come get it like your life depended on it.