If you don't water these morning glories for your school project, they're going to wilt, you know?
One more round!
Are you listening to me?
Sheesh.
Have you done your summer homework?
Have you finished cleaning the bathroom?
I'll do it later!
You kids.
If you sit around playing games all day instead of doing your chores,
you'll get turned into Desertrians!
How I have waited for this moment!
This burning heat together with the end of summer vacation!
The children of this world shall surely find the Flowers of their Hearts weakened!
Ah, the brilliance of this plan amazes even myself!
'Tis a curse to bear such genius.
Now!
The greatest and most brilliant of plans is underway!
And with it, nothing shall stop this world from becoming a desert!
That stupid book report.
All that studying!
My summer homework.
I don't wanna do it!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Good mornin'.
It's already afternoon, you know?
Did you only just get up?
Yeah.
Jeez.
It's 'cause you stay up all night
watching DVDs, reading comic books,
and going to bed so late that you
can never get up in the mornings!
It's not a big deal. It's summer vacation, after all.
It won't do you any good!
If you spend all day being such a lazy lazy lazy lazy lazy lazy...
Yeah, I get it.
Gimme a sec to get ready, okay?
Sabark's Greatest Plan Yet!
We Haven't Finished Our Summer Homework!
Time to dig in!
Are you really having that ice cream for breakfast?
Yeah!
It's so hot that I just don't feel
like having an actual breakfast.
If you don't have a proper breakfast, the heat will get to you, you know?
I'll be fine, really!
So, what're we gonna do today?!
You won't be fine at this rate!
Don't come running to me if you end up collapsing!
Oh, Momoka! Good afternoon!
Sorry to intrude like this.
Nice to see you both.
Cut that out already! Jeez.
Wait, are you off to work?
I got the day off.
I've been so busy, I haven't had a
chance to do my summer homework.
Yuri's going to help me with it.
You don't need to worry about homework yet!
'Cause summer vacation's so long!
Yeah, but there's less than half of it left now.
Huh?!
1, 2, 3...
Huh? That's strange.
Have you two been keeping up with your homework?
I just have my book report left.
I've finished all of mine already.
All of it?!
Y-Yeah...
You see?
Oh, I know. Why don't we
spend today doing homework?
Huh?
She's right! Let's get it done!
Hold it right there!
Enjoy what's left of summer vacation!
No!
You can do your homework later!
It's more fun to play!
And a lot less boring!
Nah, that's fine!
It's summer vacation, so let's have some fun!
But...
Don't worry about it!
I'll get all my homework done on the last day of summer vacation!
And yet every year you end up crying and rushing to get it done in time.
Shut it!
We oughta have fun since we're all here together!
Let's enjoy our summer vacation!
Here it comes!
Why are we going to the library, anyway?
I want to borrow a book for my book report.
And there's one I'd rather like to read too.
Bo-ring.
Your clothing really doesn't match today, Erika.
Well, it's summer vacation! No point getting dressed up when it's so hot.
Your hair's sticking up too. Right here.
Well, it's summer vacation! No point going through all that trouble if I'm just with my friends.
I know she's forgetful, but she's
normally really fashion-conscious.
This summer vacation is making her lazy in both body and spirit.
And shpirit!
Kibougahana City Library
Playground
8th Grade Math
Summer Vacation
Problems
Oh, I've been meaning to read this fantasy novel!
Huh?! You want to read such a huge book?!
Shh!
It's a very good read.
Once I started, I couldn't put it down.
I stayed up all night reading it.
All night?!
Shhh!
Homework
Summer
vacation
We recommend these titles for your book report!
Homework
Summer
vacation
We recommend these titles for your book report!
Homework
Summer
vacation
We recommend these titles for your book report!
Homework
Summer
vacation
We recommend these titles for your book report!
Homework
I guess those two being pretty much done
with their homework must be getting to you.
N-Not really.
Erika, shouldn't you get your homework done already?
I told you I don't need to worry about it yet, all right?!
Shhhhhhh!
Erika, you didn't check any books out?
I don't really feel like reading in this heat.
It's much cooler in the mornings, though.
Enough to get some work done on your report.
That's no good, seeing as Erika
doesn't ever get up in the morning.
That's why she never gets any of her homework done!
Oh, just be quiet already!
Isn't the reason we have vacation in the summer because it's too hot to get any studying done?!
So why do they give us all this homework?!
Well, that's because...
Summer should be a break from studying,
so we should play as much as we like!
Look, all the elementary schoolers are having so much fun playing.
No one's playing at all?!
It is rather quiet.
It's too quiet.
Something's wrong.
Wh-What the?!
Homework! Drillillill!
A Desertrian?!
Let's go!
Right!
Sheeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Huh? Is it over already?
I didn't even get to do anything.
I wonder if the heat affects Desertrians too.
It's weird.
There's something wrong here.
Homework! Drillillill!
Huh?!
There's Desertrians.
Huh?! There's this many?!
Why do we have to do homework during summer vacation?!
Huh? Homework?
I hate homework!
We hate it!
Down with homework!
Down with it!
Could these be all the kids who haven't done their summer homework?!
Exactement.
Kobraja!
These children ignore their duties and waste their days away.
Their hearts are so simple for us to manipulate!
Huh?!
Now go, my dear Desertrians!
Destroy those meddling Precure!
Marine!
I'll get you!
Huh?
Whoa!
It's tiny!
Hey, what?! No!
I hate homework!
I don't wanna do it!
I know how you feel, but...
Marine Dynamite!
Are you all right?
I just don't feel as powerful as normal.
It's because you didn't have a proper breakfast!
The summer heat is getting to you!
That'sh right!
There's still more of them?!
They keep on coming.
Hark, my Desertrians!
If you don't like homework,
then why not just get rid of your school?
Huh?!
That's right.
We should just destroy the school!
He's right!
Let's all go and destroy the school!
Okay!
Um, would you mind doing the
middle school while you're at it?
Marine!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
We'd better head to the elementary school!
Right!
I hate homework!
We hate it!
Let's knock down the school! Knock it down!
Knock it down! Knock it down! Knock it down!
That's right! If you hate doing your
homework, then just destroy your school!
Right!
Look, you!
Don't start talking like you understand!
You don't know how it feels to worry about your homework!
You're quite right. I don't.
If you don't want to do it, then don't. Simple as that.
Huh?! I can do that?!
No, you can't!
Yeah, I figured.
This shall be the first step to making this world a desert.
By encouraging the lethargy in children's
hearts, we can make it grow even stronger.
Then we destroy their school and deprive them of their curiosity.
Until finally, their willpower and their
hopes for the future fade into nothing.
And once they do, the Flowers of their Hearts
shall wilt, and the Great Heart Tree shall perish!
And this world shall become a desert!
Ah, je suis impeccable.
I won't let you!
The reason we have summer homework is so we don't forget all the things we've learned!
So we don't forget all that time we spent studying!
It's true that it can be a chore at times, but that's not what it's really about!
Please try to remember! Remember just how fun learning can be!
Is it, though?
Marine! Just whose side are you on?!
Well, Tsubomi can say stuff like that cause she likes studying.
Do you really think that, Marine?!
Running away from anything you find difficult, and making excuses so you don't have to work your hardest.
Are you really okay with that?
Look out!
Huh?
Destroy the school!
Blossom! Sunshine!
I've got to try harder than this!
Use a Heart Seed to get fired up!
All right!
The Blessed Perfume of Magenta Light!
A spray makes me ready for action!
I'm fired up now!
Here I come!
Precure Forehead Punch!
I know how you all feel, but you can't just destroy your school like this!
Hmph! Humans are innately foolish creatures.
Just going to school isn't going to change that.
You're wrong!
Studying can be tough, but that's why we have school!
If you're trying to destroy that, then...
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Homewoooooooork!
Because the Desertrian's so big, her power alone isn't enough!
Leave it to me!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Hoooooome... work!
Sunshine!
Right!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Tch!
However, as long as summer homework remains undone, I have more chances!
Hey, all you kids who haven't done your summer homework yet!
I'll be coming for you next!
Huh?
Why are we at school?
I think you must've all zoned out because of the summer heat!
Yeah, that must be it.
I see.
What's the matter?
I was just thinking, summer
vacation's gonna be over soon.
Everyone sheems sho down.
Because they haven't finished their homework, they feel burdened!
Hey, you kids.
What are you doing here?
Sir!
Why are you here at school?
It's summer vacation.
Even during the vacation, there's always a teacher here.
You can always ask for our help if you need to.
Oh, I know!
I think they're all struggling
with parts of their homework.
Huh?
If you get your homework finished, you'll be able to enjoy the rest of the holiday without worrying about it!
Sir, can you help me with my homework?
Mine too!
Oh, mine too!
Okay! Let's head to a classroom, then!
Yes, sir!
Erika, you should finish yours too.
Fine.
I'm glad they were able to help all those kids!
Wait! This means we're going to get a ton of Heart Seeds!
Potpourri, ready the Heart Pot!
Okay, shir!
With this, the Great Heart Tree
has recovered a whole lot more!
Here's a hint: formulas.
Oh, I see!
I-I did it!
I finally solved it. Wow.
It's kinda fun when you finally work it out.
That's right! When you finally understand what
you're studying, that's when it becomes interesting!
"A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step."
If you work on things one step at a time, I'm
sure even you'll begin to enjoy studying, Erika!
Right!
Now then, let's keep this pace up and get them all finished!
Easy to Understand
Math
Problems
Easy to Understand
Math
Problems
Summer Vacation
Diary
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Hayashi travels tough and steep roads on his bicycle.
No matter how many people tell him he can't
do it, he believes in himself and never gives up.
Because when he reaches his goal, it'll be the memory of a lifetime.
That's why I've made my decision!
I'll find that new side of myself and make a beautiful dress!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Final Stretch of Summer!
I've Finally Finished My Dress!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!