Year 850:
The Colossus Titan reappeared
and destroyed the wall,
which allowed the Titans to invade.
Soldiers fell before the Titans, one after another.
And then...
Eren, hur—
Eren, too, was devoured.
Really, Mikasa's amazing.
Just how does she move that fast?
No, she isn't calm like usual.
I'll win no matter what!
I'll live no matter what!
A mysterious Titan-killing Titan then
appeared before the cornered Mikasa.
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
I Can Hear the Beating of His Heart
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
④
All right, the operating device still works.
You can have all my blades too.
But just... leave me this one, if possible.
I want to at least avoid being devoured alive.
Wh-Why...
Armin.
I won't leave you here.
B-But moving through a crowd of
Titans while carrying someone is—
Come on!
You can't. Please stop.
At this rate, I'll get my friends killed again.
Wait!
Hear me out. I have an idea.
An idea?
Only you two are needed for it,
so the final decision is yours.
I know it's crazy, but maybe we
could make use of that Titan?
That Titan?
It attacks other Titans
and shows no interest in us.
So I was thinking we might be able
to guide it to the supply station.
If it takes out the other Titans
for us, everyone could be saved.
Guide?! How the hell do you plan on doing that?
I'm assuming it fights solely on instinct.
Your job would be to take
down all the Titans near it.
Once you do, it'll probably
move in search of more Titans.
It should eventually head toward HQ.
D-Do you think we'd risk our
lives over an assumption?!
But if it's true, we could take all the Titans
attacking HQ down in one fell swoop!
It's worth a try.
What? Are you serious?!
It's better to bet on an assumption,
rather than simply wait for death.
I agree with Armin.
So you plan to fight Titans with a Titan?
Yes, exactly.
Fail, and we'll be made a mockery of.
But succeed, and everyone will be saved.
Let's prepare ourselves.
Fine, I'll do it!
Do I have the right?
The right to be in a position of responsibility?
No, wait a minute.
It's now or never.
It's our chance now that
some of them are distracted.
Now!
Rush over to HQ now!
This is our only chance.
We'll be finished if our gas runs out anyway.
Everyone, charge!
Jean!
Thanks.
We got away, thanks to you.
You pulled through for us.
I told you, didn't I?
You're suited to be a leader.
Well, I don't know about that!
Damn!
How many made it?
How many died on my order, taking
advantage of our comrades' deaths?
You guys... are the supply squad, right?
Yeah.
Stop, Jean!
These guys left us out there to die!
People died in vain because of you lot!
Titans broke into the supply station!
There was nothing we could do!
Did you forget it's your job
to do something about that?!
Get down!
Shoot!
We got too many people here!
Hurry!
Get inside!
Stop! We can't all get in at once!
Where did Mikasa go?!
She ran out of gas and got devoured!
It was obvious.
I guess this is how reality is.
Was I... trying to immerse myself
in some dream or illusion?
I should have noticed... our reality.
It's obvious if you think about it.
There's no way we can beat
something this gigantic.
What?!
What's... that?
Mikasa!
Whew, it just ran out.
We did it. Just barely!
Y-You're alive!
We did it, Armin!
Ow.
That hurts.
Your plan was a success!
Everyone, that Titan's an Abnormal
that attacks other Titans!
Not to mention, it doesn't care about us!
If we can make good use of it,
we'll be able to get out of here!
Make good use of... a Titan?
You think we'll be saved by a Titan?
Something that delusional—
It's far from delusional.
It doesn't matter what it is.
All we need is for that Titan
to continue its rampage.
Realistically, that's our best plan for survival.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Three-dimensional Maneuver Device Mechanics Part ③
<Fan Section>
Gas is directly blown into the fan to make it rotate.
The pressure of the gas is regulated to manipulate the output.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Diagram of the Titans'
Size Comparison
It's fine.
That Titan's stronger than your average one.
The building won't be attacked
as long as it's rampaging outside.
How much do you guys
know about that Titan?
We can worry about that
after we get out of this.
True.
First things first.
We found them!
They're the Military Police Brigade's stock.
There's a bit of dust on them though.
Are three bullets really enough?
Besides, are guns going to be
of any use against Titans?
I think it'll be a lot better than not having them.
If only seven 3- and 4-meter-class Titans are there,
it's possible to blind them all
simultaneously with this much firepower.
First, we'll lower a crowd of people from
the center part of the roof using the lift.
Then, we'll all fire at the faces of the Titans
at the same time to rob them of their sight.
Everything will be decided in the next moment.
The seven people hiding atop the rafters
will match the timing of gunfire
and slash at the Titans' vitals.
In other words, this plan bets everything
—all of our lives—on a single attack.
It's a strategy that'll allow seven people to
take down a Titan each, all at the same time.
I'd like the seven most physically
capable people to take up this task,
though I apologize for burdening
you guys with that responsibility.
No worries.
Regardless of who does it,
if they fail, we'll all die.
The risk is the same.
But is my plan really the best way to do this?
Let's just go with that.
There's no time anyway.
It's all we've got.
Now we just have to give it our best!
Don't worry.
Be confident in yourself.
You have the ability to seek out the right answers.
Eren and I have been saved
by that ability in the past.
What?
When?
Lift is ready!
So are the guns!
They're all loaded!
You just don't realize it.
Let's talk later.
Okay.
But are we gonna be able to take down the Titans
without three-dimensional maneuver devices?
Of course.
They're only 3- and 4-meter-class Titans.
Their vitals will be easy to target.
Yeah, we just need to slash the nape from
top to bottom, regardless of their size.
One meter long, ten centimeters wide!
Or I could stick this up their asses.
That's their only other weakness.
I had no idea.
That's an option too?!
I didn't know until now either.
Reiner, those could be your last words, you know.
It's good.
There are still only seven here.
We'll stick to the plan.
Calm down!
Let them get closer!
Wait.
We can't afford to lose our advantage.
Not if we want everyone to survive.
We'll decide it with a single blow.
Wait.
Ready...
Fire!
I got it.
And the others?
U-Um, I apologize for sneaking
up behind you so suddenly...
Oh no.
Sasha and Connie need help!
Hurry, cover for them!
I'm...
so sorry!
Mikasa!
You saved me!
Are you hurt?
No, thanks to you!
Then stand up already.
Thanks a lot.
No problem.
Hey now, that was dangerous, Annie.
I'm relieved you didn't get hurt.
We got all of them!
Start filling up your gas tanks.
Great!
Yeah, we're saved now!
No more Titans are coming inside!
It's thanks to that Abnormal's rampage!
I surrendered to a Titan.
I'm too ashamed to look anyone in the eyes!
We'll all scorn you for it later!
Right now, we need to leave!
I can't agree that I'm suited to lead.
So stop saying I am.
You might get mad, but listen.
You're not a strong person,
so you can sympathize with
the feelings of the weak.
Nevertheless, you excel at
looking at things objectively,
so you have a clear idea
of what needs to be done.
Your orders were right.
That's why I was able to move
and why I'm still alive.
You all ready?
Let's move out!
We'll leave together!
Climb over the wall!
We'll meet up with the main forces!
Mikasa?
Mikasa!
We need to leave now!
That Titan...
Cannibalism?
It can't regenerate?
I thought that if we could solve the
mystery of that Titan somehow,
it'd become a chance to pull ourselves
out of this hopeless reality.
I agree.
If it gets devoured, we'll be as clueless as ever.
Let's take out the Titans clinging
to it and keep it alive for now.
Are you serious, Reiner?!
We can finally get out of this hellhole, you know!
But there's a chance that
Titan could become our ally.
Don't you think it'd be a greater
weapon than any cannon?
An ally?
Do you hear what you're saying?
That's...
the Abnormal that ate Thomas.
Hey...
You want to save that?
Looks like it finally ran out of gas.
We're done here, right?
Time to go.
There's no way that monster could be an ally.
A Titan is a Titan.
What now?
Mikasa?!
It's Eren.
His severed arm and leg are still there.
Back then, Eren was devoured by a Titan.
Back then...
What... in the world...?
Does that mean Eren did all this?
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba
"I'll exterminate the Titans."
That powerful sentiment
transformed Eren into a Titan.
But the Garrison considers
him to be a threat to humanity
and turns their blades on him.
The Whereabouts of His Left Arm
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑤