That's where school uniforms come in!
Leave the curry to me!
Let's go visit Hanako!
It's funny how they get pulled in.
Oh, yes.
I am going to be a zombie.
I will give her educational guidance!
How about a café?
And we can cosplay.
We could do a haunted house.
Or do fortune telling.
Oh, I like that.
All boring ideas.
Then, what do you think?
Huh?
You have some really amazing ideas, don't you?!
Hm...
A cat café...
...or something?
A cat café?
Well, a dog café is fine, too!
No, but I want it to be related to cats.
Cultural
Festival
Panel
Presentation
Okay.
Present your ideas with decorations,
material acquisition and production,
an ordering system if serving food, costume
preparation, work shifts, and tear-down process.
All right, who has an idea to share?
Curry Tastes Better on the Second Day
Cultural
Festival
Panel
Presentation
So... we have a panel presentation
composed of cell phone pictures.
Any others?
We have to think of the whole layout, though...
Right?
Yeah...
That's too hard.
Here!
Here, here!
Odagiri?
A curry shop!
What?!
That sounds like a lot of work...
It's a cultural festival after all,
so I want to do something!
Curry's easy to make.
Cultural
Festival
Panel
Presentation
Curry
shop
Curry shop.
Will we have costumes?
It'd be a lot of work to make them.
That's where school uniforms come in!
Ordinary curry made by high school
girls in uniforms with aprons?
That's worth something.
Recently, there are many cheap-looking,
mediocre costumes.
They are common.
Ordinary uniforms!
That's the easiest and best way!
Oh, she's from the cake shop!
What?!
No way...
I'm just mistaken! Mistaken!
Oh, yeah!
Right?
It's hard to make costumes.
If we're just wearing our uniforms...
I have an apron already.
Wait... is she in our class?
Huh?
Where did she go?
She's small and doesn't have curves,
so she didn't look out of place.
This is a nightmare.
This is a daymare!
So, our class decided to do a curry shop.
Sonobe...
A lot of people like curry, and we
can entice them with the smell.
It's a good idea.
Can't resist the smell!
It must be stressful since
you are class representative.
Not really.
Nishiyama was eager to help out with
decorations after I told her she's good at it.
Oh my!
She's so easy to flatter, I feel sorry for her.
She likes to be in the limelight.
What is your class doing, Miss Youko?
We are going to do a haunted house.
A haunted house?!
This is my first time.
I wonder it is like.
I-I'm not very good with those.
Futaba?
Oh, are you scared of ghosts and such?
Because it's hot fair if you
can't see or touch them!
And you can't punch them if you need to!
Oh, yes.
I am going to be a zombie.
A zombie?!
Aren't you glad?
You can punch those.
I don't want to!
If we use our desks as tables, we should use
paper placemats so they don't get dirty.
Tablecloths are hard to clean,
so disposable placemats are easier.
I see!
You're so smart, Nishiyama!
I'm thankful there's somebody who will
step up to take the lead during these events.
I didn't expect people to be
so reluctant to work.
I'll call you Leader Nishikawa from now on.
No, stop!
In exchange, leave the curry to me!
Stuffed Hut
Extra large
Challenge Menu
Pot of Curry
Free if you finish
Time limit
30 min.
The extra large challenge
just happens to be curry.
Here you go.
Curry is just a drink!
I won't lose!
Ready, go!
Okay, time's up!
I-I lost...
It's spicy!
Way too spicy!
It's impossible!
Hm, really?
Somebody already finished it yesterday,
so I thought it was too easy.
What?!
Thanks,
Mr. Stuffed
Her nerves are probably dead.
You can't eat the curry,
because it's too spicy?
What a kid!
What?
I can handle spicy foods.
And that's because I'm an adult.
I'm older than you!
Damn...!
You're the same.
What is this, it's way too spicy!
What?
Hmm, then I'll have to rethink this one.
You couldn't finish, but since you're
both regulars, I'll give you half off.
Really?!
Then...
...this would be a waste,
so I'll take it to go!
Me, too!
So, I did lots of research yesterday.
You even took the pot?
If I add a few things, I might be
able to tone down the spiciness.
But, that curry's from yesterday.
Curry tastes better on the second day!
The cultural festival is still days away.
Well, I'll use Mr. Stuffed's flavor as reference
and make it from spices like real curry.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
We don't have a budget for it,
and spices are expensive.
Let's go with store-bought roux.
Well, it's a cultural festival, so I guess
we'll go with the ordinary stuff.
People might think it's weird if
we serve something authentic.
Curry
Everybody will bring the cut
ingredients they're in charge of,
and we'll use disposable utensils. Then...
I can make curry, but I'm a little nervous,
since I haven't made large amounts at once.
Oh, go ask Odagiri for tips.
Hayama!
Do these decorations look okay?
Ask Nishiyama about decorations.
Nishiyama!
Preparing for the cultural
festival usually seems tough...
...but those two have been unexpectedly
helpful, so things are okay.
Um...
You don't know how to prepare to be a monster?
Yes.
My classmates seem to know...
...but I am the only one...
Why don't you ask Tsuji?
Tsuji is...
...very popular among my classmates.
She does remind me of a small animal.
What's wrong, Miss Youko?
Did something happen?
Actually...
Then, let's go to the bathroom.
What? Why?!
Let's go visit Hanako!
Why are you referring to her like a friend?!
I'm not going! She's not there!
Hanako probably very busy!
Ehhh?
If you're doing something after school,
you have got to see seven wonders.
Where did you get that rule?!
Don't wanna!
I don't like scary things!
Because you can't eat them?
Even if I do like eating, that's not why!
Who is this Hanako?
What?
Nishikawa, you don't know?
You see, she haunts the bathroo—
Not listening!
I'm not listening!
Are... they done?
She looks super interested!
Let us go!
Let us try to see if we
can meet this Hanako!
I can't! No way! It's dangerous!
What if she drags you into the toilet?
I will give her educational guidance!
All right, let's go.
Yes, let us!
No!
Okay, I'm going back to the classroom.
Hey, w-wait.
E-Everybody's gone.
Wh-What should I do?
Haunted House
Maybe I should go back to the classroom, too.
Odagiri.
It's a high school girl ghost who's been
in second place for a thousand years
and has unfinished business in this world!
Wh-What? How rude!
You're in charge of the curry, right?
Come on and do your job!
Kondou is gone, too.
Where in the world did she go?
Kondou went with Miss Youko
to visit Hanako in the bathroom.
What?!
The Hanako from the bathroom?
What's the point of looking at that?
To give educational guidance?
They're up to something!
We have returned.
H-How was it?
Hmph, it's impossible to look
in every toilet in the school.
Yeah, it's too much work.
O-Oh yeah?
I'm glad.
Miss Youko, you'll be a zombie?
I am supposed to wear makeup and scare
the visitors, but I still do not know what to do.
Then, I realized that there is
a professional monster here.
How can I move stealthily like you?
I'm a human and move as I think a human would.
No!
You are not a zombie, Miss Youko!
And you'll be scaring people?
You're not that kind of character!
Your classmates don't
understand you at all!
Does your homeroom teacher
know about this?!
We are the monster's parents, huh?
We're not your parents, though.
But, I am looking forward
to the cultural festival.
I will be going, too.
As am I!
Thank you both.
Wait, you both come anyway!
Indeed.
Oh my, how scary.
By the way, Sonobe, I heard you snuck into Class 3...
Get on your knees!
Cultural Festival
We will now commence Central High School's
thirty-second cultural festival!
The theme is "Beautiful Metamorphosis."
Let's all do our best and make this
a wonderful day full of memories.
All right.
The curry is ready.
Okay, let's do our best, everybody!
Okay!
Well, eating curry probably isn't
the first thing people do—
Two bowls, please!
What?!
Hm...
Ah.
Actually, make that three!
Already?!
I won't have energy unless I eat.
And it'll be good advertisement.
Welcome.
Would you like to have your fortune told?
Please!
What should we do?
Curry
year
Class
This is yummy!
Plain delicious!
What a simple and gentle flavor!
It tastes like high school girls made it.
So ordinary!
Welcome!
Curry
We have curry made
by high school girls!
This curry is made by high school girls?
I see.
It's plain delicious!
Thank you very much!
Hey, hey.
So many people are here!
We can do better than this.
I'll go out to advertise.
Maybe Futaba can do that.
Leave it to me!
Yeah, I wouldn't want her to eat all the food.
A lot of people come to our
cultural festival, huh?
Yup.
Curry
All right!
Let's attract some customers!
Curry
Curry!
I think there's a place that's selling it!
Let's go see!
First year, Class 3's
homemade curry is that way.
It's plain delicious!
It's funny how they get pulled in.
They just keep getting pulled...
What?!
Wh-What's going on?
H-Huh?
Wh-What? What is it?
It already has a mosaic?!
I see.
Miss Youko, you were trying
to draw in customers, too.
It's a zombie...
It's rotting...
You put way too much into
this for just a cultural festival.
Sonobe helped me with the makeup.
I tried out pastry shop techniques.
You tried out pastry shop techniques?
How long have you been there?
I do not know why, but whenever I go out
to advertise, people outright avoid me.
Commoners must shrink back in fear when
someone of Miss Youko's rank speaks to them.
Oh, Yamaji!
I'm used to him popping up unexpectedly.
Therefore, do not fret about their reactions.
You think so?
No, I think it's because of the zombie makeup.
I see!
They tremble with fear
because of your realistic acting!
Yup, I get it.
You should get your ears checked.
So, how is the haunted house going?
It is surprisingly lively.
I have not been that involved, though.
I refuse to go through the haunted house.
It's made by high schoolers,
so it's probably fine.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe even I can do this...
Let's go in!
Mua-ha-ha, you have entered, Odagiri Futaba.
I'll scare you and avenge my brother!
Hey, it's darker than I expected.
I can't see.
Hey...
She's here!
Boo! Feel my vengeance!
I said, I can't see.
Oh, here's a flashlight.
Right here...Right here...
Where? Wh-Where?
Hey, did you hear that scream?
It's here.
It looks fun!
Okay, no pushing, no pushing.
Please line up so you don't get hurt.
I ended up attracting customers here, too.
You're a huge help.
Fried Octopus
Dumplings
Popcorn
High school cultural festivals are great.
This cute cultural feel is the best!
Ms. Sonobe!
Welcome!
So forceful.
Ah, er, I'm full.
It's fine.
It's just juice!
Well, I guess if it's juice...
Grape                            Fruit                        Orange                 Apple
Oolong Tea
Let's see...
I'll have...
I recommend the vegetable juice for you!
Cider
Vegetable
Juice
You just look like someone who'd like it.
I give off that image?
Here!
Free extra large for you.
I-It's spilling, spilling...
Oh, Ms. Sonobe are you going to see Teru?
Oh.
Take this to her, will you?
Is this some sort of trial?
But, even if I've gone bad, I must do this as former maid...!
And this is for Youko and Futaba.
I....will...not...fail!
Curry
Hey, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Haunted houses and stuff... are just not good.
Not good.
The quality of Miss Youko's
costume was just way too high.
I apologize, Futaba.
No!
Don't come near me with that face!
Pfft, Odagiri Futaba, pfft, pfft!
I can't believe you're scared of a haunted house!
Pfft!
H-Hey!
Boo! I'm a ghost.
Feel my vengeance!
Ah, yes.
You're trying very hard.
No!
You're supposed to be scared!
Watch out!
Right there...
Right there...!
...are the remnants of what
used to be a student!
Please, run away!
Ah!
Wai—
This is just vegetable juice...
Hey...!
Karaoke Battle
Sakura!
That's the name of an angel!
Please make sure to separate trash
and dispose of it in the marked areas.
Students who are done cleaning
will be dismissed first.
The cultural festival is over.
Both the curry shop and
haunted house were a success.
I'm glad.
Quite right.
They will make great memories.
I was very anxious.
I thought I would be the only one
who could not be of help.
However, everybody did have fun.
I had a lot of fun, too!
Miss Youko...
That's great.
Yes!
By the way, Miss Youko?
Yes?
When will you take that makeup off?
I have it on already, so I
will wait until I get home.
No, no, no!
Take it of, take it off!
You'll get arrested.
They will be after your head!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Personal opinion. They may or may not represent the actual effects of product. Not available on this site.
Yes,
I have it
every-
day.
I used to
be worried
about my
dry hair...
Yes, I have it everyday.
I used to be worried
about my dry hair...
Everything changed after I drank it!
Everything
changed
after I
drank it!
The
world
became
brighter.
The world became brighter.
It cleansed my ugly heart.
It
cleansed
my ugly
heart.
These are
some of
the great
things
people are
saying
about it.
These are some of the great things
people are saying about it.
That Juice
Indescribable flavor
Cheese-like flavor
Rhinoceros beetle flavor
AAAAAAA
Made by Ms. Kou
Next time: A Day to Gorge on Chicken and Cake