World Domination Diary.
Edogawa Jou.
I've finally completed my perfect, foolproof plan.
To realize it,
I have begun the ritual to summon the Nine-Headed Dragon.
It started...
It started when the night turned to day,
and I switched places with her.
My name is Lord Awashima.
On a night when Edogawa Jou's divine spirit slumbered,
another consciousness was given control over her body.
It was one of the gods that she had once consumed.
My body sometimes grows a penis!
Curses!
I need to give an honest—
Body?
She believed it?
Right, my body!
It grows one every now and then, but it goes away in a flash!
So, you really are a girl?
Yes.
I beg you, keep it a secret.
S-Sure.
It's a secret between us.
Y-Yeah.
Thank you.
But...
that thing isn't contagious, right?
Huh?
I won't grow one too, right?
You're fine!
It seems that I fooled her somehow.
first year arahabaki
tamamo-no-mae
I feel that you've struck out.
first year arahabaki
tamamo-no-mae
You saw that, Tamamo-no-mae?
Given your tone, you seem to be the male Madam.
I'm about to switch over, though.
This ritual is special for Jou.
It sure is.
The sun is about to rise, Lord Awashima!
Really, what have you done?
You let Sasami discover our secret!
Unforeseen circumstances.
We'll begin the ritual.
Wing General Garuda!
Garuda is on standby in case of danger.
Tamamo-no-mae, erect a barrier to keep humans away.
Understood.
From here on, we shall display the combined power of the corrupt occult society Arahabaki...
and begin our plan for world domination.
Everything is for my happiness.
Everything is for my own gain.
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Final Episode
I Won't Do Anything Tomorrow
She says to ask if I can call you Joey.
At that moment,
a small bit of hope budded inside me.
Sis...
I'll invite you into my organization.
You'd be my employee,
and you'd use your powers for me!
Sis!
What are you doing?
Well, my sister...
Sis!
You will explain at once!
Are you not my servant?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa!
But I have to go!
I'll call you later!
Wait!
Stop right there, Sasami!
Fine, do as you wish!
I don't need you!
Of course.
Hopes are bound to be betrayed.
Especially when dealing with humans.
I was looking forward to spending the festival with you, just a little.
Why won't she do what I want?
This is why I hate humans!
I hate how confusing they all are!
Being involved with them is pointless!
They make no sense!
Madam, everything is prepared for our plan.
Fine.
This is my fate.
I'll accept it, cackle, and push on.
Alone, if I have to.
Corrupt occult society Arahabaki...
Attack!
Ow!
We must run!
The guy went fally!
What do I win?
Meatie is enough for me!
I cannot raise more pets!
Would you raise Mamarin?
Tama, wait here.
I shall return soon.
What's wrong?
I am certain it is a needless concern...
but I must leave for a moment!
Are you getting that guy?
Somehow, I doubt it.
What?
What's happening?
Mamarin, save meflqwafj—
Tama? Tama!
Tama is... being fed some kind of drug...
and it's... reaching me...
This got struck too?
The shrine arches, shrine grove, the guardian deity statues of Jizo...
and even large trees or crags with spiritual energy were completely wiped out.
I'm worried about those guys from the chat room.
This is lookin' like some serious trouble.
What is it, Ms. Tsurugi?
A barrier.
We're stuck on this island!
Uh...
what're you doing?
It seems that high tide has arrived.
Hey, I'm not a kid!
Well, I guess I don't want my clothes getting wet...
I was actually planning to ask you who you really were once we were alone...
but oh well.
This is fine for now,
Bro.
You haven't kept in touch, Flame Emperor Kagutsuchi.
Oh, but it's Yagami Kagami now, isn't it?
I was told that my sister had encountered you,
yet you are somehow still alive.
Wing General Garuda is doing fine as well.
Aren't you glad to see your former comrades?
So you all still linger,
corrupt occult society...
Arahabaki!
My right hand wields Iwasaku's sword,
And my left wields Nesaku's sword.
These blades that once rent you asunder are now deified!
The wild swordsmanship of India,
the strategic swordsmanship of China,
or the ritualistic swordsmanship of Japan...
which would you prefer?
You'll be filleted by a world-class beauty either way!
Good morning, Tama.
Edogawa...
Wh-Wh-Whoah! Where's Mamarin?
Mamarin!
Mamarin's not answering!
This island is completely sealed by a barrier.
Sasami has no way of reaching you from Ame-no-nuboko Town.
What...
are they doing?
A secret festival.
You will go along with it.
The ritual reenacts the Nine-Headed Dragon's extermination.
You are to play the hero who slays the wicked dragon.
Huh?
A newer god defeating an ancient one.
I feel it's a fitting role for you,
new generation Yagami Tama.
I am an ancient, forgotten god myself.
The oppressed, yet never subdued Arahabaki.
I feel the dragon is a fitting role for me.
Now,
use that sword to kill me.
No!
Do it.
Kill me.
No!
Can't do it?
Well, I...
it'd be...
really bad...
You are kind.
Your foolishness saved me.
The ritual reenacts the past.
As such, the roles we play now will occur in the past!
With Tamamo-no-mae's power, we can deceive the world!
Our rewritten script will have the dragon defeat the Imperial Court!
We will Transform history!
Oh? Does it hurt?
You gods can feel pain?
Why're you doing this?
Mamarin was your friend!
Arahabaki is the one true god.
It alone is perfection.
It alone is all-knowing.
It needs no friends, family, subordinates, or anything else.
The ritual is complete!
History has Transformed,
and the dragon is victorious!
And with that history molding our present,
the dragon shall once again regain its true form!
Slander the history of the Yaoyorozu!
Erase the mythology of the Yaoyorozu!
Everything is for my happiness.
Rather,
everything is for my own gain!
Tama! Tama!
Mamarin...
you're back.
What happened, Tama?!
The island got destroyed...
And hey, you know,
I got eaten...
And this really scary god destroyed everything...
Don't cry, Tama.
Look, you've gotta do something.
I can't!
I got gobbled up!
Don't give up, Tama!
Please, there has to be something—
And indeed there is.
You all can still be of some utility to us.
It's you...
the playfully chaotic Tamamo-no-mae!
You're quite late, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
And here I opened a window in the barrier waiting for your call.
What the hell did you do?
What does it look like?
We revived the ancient Nine-Headed Dragon and destroyed the island.
We will use the Nine-Headed Dragon's endless power as a weapon
and declare war on the world!
Why you...
You should be proud, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
My master holds you in high regard, and named you the New World Priestess,
New World Priestess
effectively making you the ruler of all mankind!
Ruler of Mankind
Huh?
A conqueror cannot allow her subjects to be destroyed.
Humans are a precious resource.
Precious Reso
To use them properly, we need a priestess to mediate between human and god.
Priestess
Don't listen...
She's one of the bad guys...
She's gonna trick you...
I am compromising with you.
If the Nine-Headed Dragon's energy is released,
your town of Ame-no-nuboko can be vaporized in an instant!
Can I trust you?
Of course you can.
We've lost.
We didn't stop you, and a lot of innocent people were dragged into this.
There's no point in fighting until we're all dead.
So if it's me you want...
Mamarin!
Then swear allegiance to God!
"I, Tsukuyomi Sasami,
shall be the priestess to Arahabaki" will suffice!
To God?
A vow to God absolutely cannot be broken!
If you can make one, then we shall place our trust in you!
Mamarin, don't!
It's all right, Tama.
It's over.
But you...
I'm done...
stalling for time!
You what?!
You turned your back on your greatest foe, Tamamo-no-mae.
Unthinkable!
I put an end to you myself!
True, those swords are my natural enemies.
I judged the fight unwinnable and simply played dead.
You feigned sleep?
You were more clever than I, a fox?!
I am but a divine spirit housed by a spiritual robot.
Were you to defeat me, I could simply abandon my body and find a new one.
And you chose my Killing Stone golem?!
Sorry, everyone.
I didn't tell anyone the whole truth.
Mamarin...
I wanted to join the trip as soon as I got over my cold.
That's why I moved my entire house to the inside of Tama's body and came with her.
I've been controlling Tama from the pilot's seat of my house!
So you've been inside this barrier the whole time?!
Because of the medicine, I stopped sharing senses for a bit.
I went outside once
and entered the bath with Edogawa.
Your mistake was in believing you had defeated the Yagami sisters,
and in opening a hole in your barrier to communicate with me!
Right now, Tsurugi should be outside your barrier and working out a plan.
She's still alive?
This is terrible!
I must inform Madam—
Did you believe that I would let you escape?
Burn to cinders!
Flame Emperor Kagutsuchi!
And with that, I am the new owner of this body.
Are you all right, Tama?
Sis...
Sis!
Wait, Tama...
OWW!
This is no time for pleasantries.
We must first take care of this alternate world.
I will use the Eight-Span Mirror.
Tama, you must protect yourself.
World of Humans,
return to your original form!
Ow...
This island's empty...
So all the destruction was just an illusion?
For one reason or another,
the Nine-Headed Dragon's resurrection did not seem to succeed.
If it was all an illusion, everyone might be safe.
Even Edogawa...
Is that...
Sister?
Gimme a break.
I only came to check things out 'cause shit looked weird,
so why do I gotta do all the borin' crap?
It's 'cause of you not keepin' a damn lid on the underworld that the dragon got resurrected!
Hey,
there are islands in Japan that are like gods, right?
Yes.
If a god can become an island,
an island can become a god.
Then that means...
this island is...
It is the Nine-Headed Dragon.
Haven't cut somethin' this huge since the Eight-Forked Serpent!
Divine Judgment!
Heavenly Slasher of Wings!
You retard!
Tone it down, dumbfuck!
Sasami's on that island!
I'm sorry.
For not going to the festival with you.
Don't worry about that.
Sorry.
I got scared back then.
Scared?
If I obtained everything and became the greatest being on the planet,
I'd never go on a trip like this, have people call for me, laugh together, or eat together ever again.
I'd be all alone.
It was obvious, and it should have been what I wanted...
I know.
It's scary to be alone.
What do you know about me?
Since I was a child,
I tried my hardest to meet everyone's expectations as the head of the organization.
I tried, tried, and tried some more.
But still...
You're right.
I might not know a thing.
But...
you'll be happy if you run away.
But one day...
I'll kill you.
Then we'll be friends until that day comes.
You're strange.
And you're persistent, Joey.
I'll rest until help comes.
I'm a bit exhausted.
Yeah, me too.
I can smell Sasami over there!
For real?
My spiritual energy reserves are depleted,
so Teacher's nose is all we can rely on.
Paparin, full speed ahead!
Sasami, we're coming for you!
No matter how desperate the situation may seem,
I've grown quite tired of their cries of wolf.
Ruza's depravity, however, is nigh intolerable.
I have not one excuse.
You avert your eyes from your true duty and indulge in your avaricious lifestyle...
how foolish.
I must correct you myself.
I echo your thoughts.
But...
you're cute when you get all jealous!
From now on,
we won't do anything!
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Even though we say our goodbyes,
I start to miss you right away (In the stream of love)
Until I board the train,
I want to listen to your voice (Just feeling your heart)
I'm stunned when you smile and ask
to walk home together
I can hear your voice
everywhere like a resounding symphony
The light shines the color of love
Let's hold hands forever
I want to feel the osmosis grow