The word "narezushi" isn't used on Hitogashima, is it?
Huh?
I've never eaten it before.
Have you?
Huh? What?
She's from the ferry!
Wh-Where's the Shadow?
It's gone!
Wow.
Do ya have eyes in the back of yer head?
How?
N-No way.
Did she just defeat the Shadow?
We haven't met before, have we?
I was only here as a child, so I've never had narezushi.
I'm curious to see what it tastes like.
Wh-Who are you?
Oh, forgive the late introduction.
I'm Nagumo Ryuunosuke.
Nagu...
Ryuunosuke?
I came to save you, but
it looks like I was a bit too late. Sorry.
Ajiro Shinpei.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Maelstrom
Na-Nagumo?
This way.
Wh-What—
It's a Shadow.
Ushio!
I told her to stay put, dammit!
Wait, it's dangerous up there.
That's where the Shadows are gathering.
Y-You can tell Shadows and humans apart?
What stands above the shadow is nothing but a lump of flesh in human shape.
Pay attention to their feet.
Their true form is the flat shadow cast upon the ground.
Thus, they hate it when their shadow is stepped on.
If you try to, only the shadow will move to avoid your feet.
This is just my sister's hypothesis, but
Shadows scan humans with light and absorb their information.
Why? Because it's an action related to how they feed.
Shadows survive by eating human data.
However, the data of taste requires them to consume the subject directly.
Look.
Those stains are the remnants of humans eaten by Shadows.
Due to certain circumstances,
we're currently being targeted by them.
Well, so are you, I suppose.
The Shadows' numbers have grown in the past three days.
No matter how many I kill, they just keep coming back.
I sense some sort of will controlling them.
It's as if they're all working toward one singular goal.
Goal...
They said their mother will awaken soon.
That light!
You can kill the Shadows with that gun of yours, right?
Miss Nagumo!
Or... can't you, novelist?
Oh, well... yes.
I knew it!
Please, you have to help me!
I have a million questions, but
for now...
Mio's up there! My family and friends are all there!
Ajiro Shinpei.
Can you really save everyone?
Sis...
Toki!
Shinpei?
Thank goodness.
Where is everyone? Where's Mio?
Toki?
I'm sorry.
This...
This isn't why I dirtied my hands!
Toki?
Don't. Stay back.
The hour of nine approaches.
The festival is over.
Now I shall draw the curtain on the final day.
The shrine grounds were filled with a mixture of the hot night air
and the gag-inducing stench of blood.
There was a literal mountain of corpses.
I won't let you interfere.
One... Three...
Five, seven, nine,
eleven.
I was subconsciously counting them.
Even my frozen brain was capable of that.
And then...
Sou!
Mio...
Run away...
Hoo, boy! That's mighty impressive!
Using my own body as a shield?
I really do love ya, huh, Mio?
N... No!
And yet for you, it's always been
Shin this, Shin that.
Sou...
Mio!
What?!
That was dangerous.
The fact that you've intruded upon this sacred ritual means
you must have defeated Mio.
You're... the parent, aren't you?
Who...
Who the hell are ya?!
That right eye of yours...
I knew it! It's the eye Mother lost long ago.
Is it the original?
But why do you have it?
With that, it should be possible to control time.
Let me go!
Hey, settle down.
What's yer deal? Quit strugglin'.
Yer one of us, ain't ya?
No! I'm human!
I'm Kofune Ushio!
Idiot.
Humans can't immediately recover from a broken arm.
No matter how many times the hero dies,
they can always restart from a save point.
So the only way for the Demon King to win is to cut the game console's power. Don't you agree?
Then what would happen if the 2D Demon King became aware of the 3D concept of "electrical power"?
I would ask of you this favor, Shinpei.
Observe the moment I cut the power.
No! Let me go!
I'm not like y'all!
Shinpei!
Please! Mio!
Protect her!
M-Mio...
Mi...
Shin...
Just wait...
I'm...
Sh-Shin!
...coming!
No! Mio!
Mio!
No!
No! No!
Damn you!
Damn you for taking Mio!
Your final meal is ready.
Please, enjoy it to your heart's content.
What is that giant Shadow?
All it did was touch them... and they were swallowed, huh?
I was the good-for-nothing, Ryuunosuke...
It looks like I was too late.
And grant me the last of your strength...
Mother!
Summer Time Rendering
What lies ahead is nothingness.
Whazzat?
Hishigata Clinic
Seems by devouring a thousand humans, she has recovered.
Now she rises.
Behold.
The island is being swallowed in shadow.
Haine...
That was good.
This is my ending.
I... I'm sorry...
Mio...
Everyone!
Forgive me, Shinpei.
If only I'd believed that message earlier.
But it's too late now.
It's all over.
It's not over!
"I should've done things differently back then."
"Why didn't I say what I should've?"
I'm always, always regretting things.
But I haven't reached the stage of regret yet!
It's not too late,
Miss Nagumo!
Please shoot me!
I'm begging you, please kill me!
No matter how many times I die, I always start over!
Shoot! Aim for my head!
You really say the oddest things.
I can go back to the 22nd!
It's pointless.
This is my last shot, you know.
Please trust me, Miss Nagumo!
You will be swallowed by the shadows, as well.
Why, you...
big dummy!
If you can really go back,
then find me and say your name.
I swear I'll save you.
It's dark.
There's nobody here. No one.
They're gone.
What is this scene?
Am I in objective mode again?
Stop...
Stop it.
Stop it, please!
The island!
What's that red light?
A girl?
Our eyes just met.
Shinpei.
Ushio? Are ya there, Ushio?
Be careful. There's a limit to that power.
At the summer festival, everyone dies.
I-I can hear ya clearly now!
Ushio! Where are ya?!
Shinpei, yer the only one who can stop it.
Protect Mio,
okay?
How was Tokyo?
Did ya go to Shibuya? Did ya?
July 22nd
Shin?
I'm... back...
Sh-Shin?!
I did it!
Are ya freezing from fallin' in the water?
Mio! She's alive!
Did ya hit yer head?
Sh-Shin?
Thank God!
I-I'm fine. Just a little sick from the ferry.
My clothes are wet.
I see!
I fell in the water when I tried to stop Mio's bike.
And she ended up saving me instead.
Ya don't look so good.
Let's go home so ya can change and rest.
I'm glad our phones are fine,
but we can't show up to the funeral all wet and sticky like this.
I need a shower, too.
"There's a limit to this power."
That was Ushio's message.
Bistro Kofune
Take a step back. Look at everything that's happened objectively.
The first time, I was on the ferry.
I just got off on the second.
And I've just met Mio on the third.
The start point for my "loops" is slowly moving forward.
Whatever happens before I open my eyes is set in stone.
Toki comes over to do
Mio's yukata.
Sou and Mio come to my room.
Mio, Sou, and Toki and I go
to the summer festival.
Leave from Otomo Beach.
Trek to shrine. View procession.
Explore shops until fireworks.
Get Mio's favorite, candied apple.
Run into Mio's shadow on the
shrine stairs. My shadow.
Nagumo defeats Mio's
shadow with a shotgun.
Go into the shrine with Nagumo
Loop for 3rd time
In other words, there's no longer any way for me to avoid falling into the water.
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
The next time I loop, I'll most likely awaken at a time further than this.
I can't keep failing over and over.
If my point starts and ends up after Mio and the others are killed,
then I'll never be able to save them, no matter how many times I loop back!
Three days.
The summer festival is in three days.
Is this something I can solve in just three days?
No! What am I thinking?
Shinpei, yer the only one who can stop it.
I will do this!
July 22nd
Huh?
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Orbital Resonance