"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Hey, Kagami, do you like wafer chocolates?
I like them, but why?
I see. Then you can have this.
Oh, thank you.
I'll have some!
I've got more!
I've still got tons more,
so go ahead and splurge!
Wait a minute, why do you have so much?
Well, they come with toys.
But I couldn't get the one I
wanted, so I bought a whole case.
There are those people
that see only the toys,
and are very inconsiderate to the snacks.
"To Each Her Own"
A fox... let's see... a squirrel... a dog?
What are you talking about, all of a sudden?
Well, I was just wondering what would happen
if I were to associate everyone with animals.
Since I love pranks, I'd be a fox.
Tsukasa's image is that of a dog.
Yu-chan is like a cute rodent,
so she'd be a squirrel.
I see.
I'm sure you want to say that I'm
like a tiger or a wolf, right?
No, since you get lonely often, Kagami,
you might be a rabbit, you know?
Those twin ponytails look like ears too.
That's a little embarrassing in
its own way, so knock it off.
That's amusing. I wonder what
the others would be like?
I'm a rabbit?
Sis Yui has the image of someone that
cheerfully runs around, so a leopard?
Iwasaki-san is so cool and
awesome, so maybe a hawk?
Yuki-chan has a very fluffy feeling,
and somewhat soft, so maybe a sheep?
Fumoffu!
No, however you look at it, Miyuki-san is...
...a cow. Especially here.
You're thinking like a dirty old man.
I read through literary magazines
from elementary school and stuff
at Konata's house yesterday.
Oh, is that so?
You know, Konata, you look very slovenly,
but surprisingly enough, you
keep stuff like that properly.
Dad tells me, "Make sure
to keep stuff like that!"
But your dreams about your future
were even more surprising.
You used to have normal ideals,
like vets and lawyers!
Is that so?
Well, it's just like you, to have
a different dream every year.
When I look at stuff like that,
I can tell what game or manga
I was really into at the time.
Oh, I see, so that's it...
It comes down to that after all.
Though there are people
who write down "a bride"
for the occupation they want to be, too.
I mean, that's not an occupation!
Hey, that's cute.
No, well... I'm talking about you, Tsukasa.
Oh? Is that so?
This is why airheads...
A lot of airheads tend not
to realize they are, as such.
I'm not an airhead!
You may be right about that.
I'll come out and say it...
Miyuki-san, you're like that too.
Oh? Is something the matter?
Miyuki-san, without glasses,
what's your eyesight like?
Worse than 20/200.
I see...
I heard somewhere that eating
blueberries is good for your eyes.
That's true. There's also
brightly-colored vegetables
like carrots and spinach
that are full of vitamin A,
and pork, sesame seeds, and liver,
that are full of B vitamins.
Furthermore, food with protein
is said to be good for the eyes.
Also, LASIK treatments have become
rather popular nowadays...
I see.
Honestly, I don't have the courage
to go through such an ordeal.
I have also seen vision
training on TV and such.
I see... You sure know a lot.
Well, only a little, from
everything that is out there.
But if you know all that, Miyuki-san,
why isn't your vision any better?
Oh?
I have the knowledge, but I
don't actually do those things.
Why don't you do them?
I wonder why that is?
Why don't you try some of them
out? Like the vision training.
Right now?
Let's see... First, you close
your eyes, then blink them open.
Then, you keep your face still,
and move just your line of sight left
and right, up and down, like this.
Miyuki-san! Your face!
Your face is moving too!
Oh? Oh? That's strange...
That's enough, really...
I feel like my eyes are
more tired afterwards.
You don't think your vision
will get any worse, do you?
Hey, Kona-chan, what does "moe" mean?
When I'm actually asked
to define it... hmm...
It's definitely an expression of
emotion that you like something.
But I really don't know the
details about it myself.
What, you use it and you don't
even know what it means?
My honest opinion is that
if you can naturally
accept the term as it is, you're an otaku.
Not that I care, but I think
I understand what you mean.
We're focusing on doggies
around the world today!
Daffundah!
Puppies are so cute!
Dad, we should raise a dog too!
Now, now, Tsukasa. You say
it like it's no big deal.
But can you take proper care of it,
train it, walk it, feed it, and so on?
And a puppy's not the same
thing as a grown dog, you know?
You know that it's a life,
and not just a thing, right?
That's true... I should
think it over properly.
But you've really thought about it, Sis.
Well, it's just that I'm simple-minded too.
That's why I looked up all sorts of things...
Come on, Konata.
You like this artist, right?
Try reading it.
Geez, I get it. You're so annoying.
You're in my space!
Stare...
Um... yes?
I was just wondering how far you've read.
Did someone named Osano show up yet?
No, I'm not at that level yet.
Now, now, hurry up and read.
There are lots of elections this
year... It's really annoying.
Is that so?
Hey, what's with the
gloomy look on your face?
Kids facing college entrance exams
should go home and promptly study...
Ma'am, we were just talking about
how all the elections are annoying.
What's with that, out of the blue?
You know how regular broadcasting
gets changed around
with all the election specials, right?
I mean, the other day, the first
episode was delayed by four hours.
And on top of that, they show election
updates in the regular broadcast too!
That L-shaped frame makes
the picture so tiny!
But, you know,
election programming lets you
study about current events.
You don't have time for all the
"anime this, anime that" anyway.
Besides, election programs aren't the
only thing to change broadcast times.
Even stuff like K-1 boots out regular
shows to get airtime, right?
Izumi, I thought you liked martial arts?
I've had experience,
but it's not something
that I particularly like!
And anime shows sometimes
have specials too, right?
My honey!
But they don't cause trouble
to the programs after,
because they never run long!
Dammit, kids facing college entrance exams
shouldn't worry about stuff
like that! They need to study!
In the end, it comes down
to brute force after all...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Kona-chan said she didn't bring an umbrella.
At least watch the forecasts!
Maybe I should just go home as is,
not caring whether or not I
get wet, like all the guys do.
But why don't boys care
whether or not they get wet?
Because they don't have to worry
about their bra showing through?
I see...
I'm sure you have a point,
but don't say it out loud so frankly.
Have a bit of modesty!
So, one of you, lend me an umbrella.
Well, we're going home to the same place,
and one umbrella will barely cover us both...
Thank you!
But don't you leave an umbrella here?
You leave your textbooks behind, after all.
Well, I had one until the other day.
But after using it once, I totally
forgot to bring another one.
It's not like I make a habit
to bring one, you know.
When you don't keep up with things,
you don't learn good habits.
Hold on, Suzume, wait!
Come to think of it,
when you're wearing a
raincoat and rubber boots,
you have this image that
it doesn't look cool.
You're right... It feels a bit childish.
But when you see it in a
picture, why is it so moe?
Like I'd know.
Lucky Star!
S'up, Konata!
Morning... Wait, what's wrong, Tsukasa?
I got scolded because the cell phone
bill was really high this month!
I rarely use my cell phone, so I
always pay only the basic rate.
I see...
Isn't it economical?
You say it's economical, but
if you hardly ever use it,
wouldn't the basic rate you pay
each month be a waste of money?
Let's not worry about the
petty details, Kagamin.
Oh, it's a text message.
Please buy eggs on your way home...
I understand.
I will go to the store with
Sis on my way home. There.
Is that really how you talk with your folks?
When you text to each other, don't
you end up speaking more politely?
Well, I kinda see where you're coming from.
But when you get used to it,
your intonation changes.
How long have you been using that thing?
About a year.
Normally, how often do you change phones?
Isn't two years about the right time?
Isn't it around there that
your battery life gives out?
I'll make sure mine lasts twice...
No, three times as long!
I'm adamant about it!
I don't get why you're so adamant.
I take good care of what I have, so
things last a long time around me.
You just leave it alone.
There are people like this out there...
They pay no attention to how much
they spend on their hobbies,
yet are really stingy
about everything else...
I'm sorry, Sis, can I borrow
your world history textbook?
Again? Geez, you're so helpless...
Here. You should be more
careful next time, okay?
Yeah. I'll come return it later.
Hiiragi's sister is rather clumsy, too.
That's right. That's all the more
reason why I have to be reliable.
But isn't it more like, you know,
when you have someone that you can rely on,
you end up letting your guard down?
In other words, Hiiragi, you're
enabling her to be that way.
That really is a convincing argument...
Hiiragi, what time is it now?
There's an alarm clock right in front of you.
Oh, you're right.
"Shock!"
The legend of a violent Hiiragi
when she first wakes up...
Look, it just chipped
because I dropped it, okay?
"Lagoon Engine by Yukiru Sugisaki"
Tsukasa, manga is nice,
but read a newspaper or
something once in a while,
to learn about the world, okay?
Okay...
Let's see...
N-Newspapers are so difficult to read...
When there's a line break, where
do you go for the next line?
I thought your reason
was something like that.
Oh, hey you, right there!
What?
Can you call Miss Kobayakawa
out from this class?
Tell her Izumi, a senior, is here to see her.
Sure...
Kobayakawa! Izumi-sempai, a
senior, is here to see you!
What is it, Sis?
Man, it's so amusing how they
suddenly start speaking politely
when they find out that I'm older...
They're so cute!
Iwasaki-san, I'm so jealous
that you're so tall.
I wonder why there's so much of a difference?
I don't know... But it might be
because I drink a lot of milk.
I see! I guess it's a fruit
of your everyday labor.
No... It doesn't really
go that easily for humans.
I wish it wasn't my height, but
somewhere else, that grew...
Phys Ed today is going to be
dodge-ball in the gymnasium,
because it's raining today.
Iwasaki-san, your image says you'd
be on the court until the very end.
Because you look so tough.
I'm also the type to last until the
very end, if I'm playing infield...
Maybe it's hard to aim at
me because I'm so small?
They both remain, but I'm sure
the reasons are different...
I'm not really good at anything
that moves my body around a lot.
I mean, I'd feel bad if I hit Kobayakawa-san.
I wonder if that's so... I wouldn't know.
It's unfortunate that we
ended up on different teams.
We're on the same team, though.
Yeah.
Iwasaki-san seems to be
good at athletic stuff,
and she looks like she'll show
no mercy... So she's scary!
"Head - out of the question"
"Upper body - big trouble if hit
hard and her condition gets worse"
"Lower body - big trouble
if she trips and gets hurt"
"But still, what would happen if
I left it up to someone else?"
I asked to play outfield, so it's all right.
I'm glad...
Iwasaki-san really is a
good person after all.
Then, Kobayakawa-san, you're on offense?
Yup.
And you, Iwasaki-san? You're infield?
Yeah.
Then, you're the catch...
No, I mean... defense...
The health rep attacked me!
Are you all right?
In any case, you're amazing, Iwasaki-san.
You precisely hit one person after another.
You think so?
You have good vision for moving
objects and good athletic reflexes.
Not really...
Oh, no, is she mad because I'm making a fuss?
No, she's just blushing.
Really? Then I guess it's okay...
I really can't tell with her.
I see...
So this is what people who often
get misunderstood are like...
When you don't know that person,
the impression you get changes.
Have you gone anywhere on vacation
since you came over here?
Yes. I paid homage to all the sanctuaries.
Sanctuaries?
Yes. I paid homage to the three
great sanctuaries of Japan.
You mean, like Kamakura, Kyoto, and Nara?
No. Akiba in Tokyo, Nipponbashi
in Osaka, and Osu in Nagoya.
I'm also going around all the notable
places in this area as well.
You mean, like Tokyo Tower and Asakusa?
That's not it. Like, Nakano and Kichijoji.
Well...
What's wrong?
I think I got some dust in my eye.
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Tell me if you can't take it anymore.
Yeah, I'm okay.
This is a good situation!
No! Don't stare at your friends
with such a rotten view!
Hello!
Yeah, come on in!
I'll bring the drinks right now.
Oh, so many books!
Though I only have stuff like this.
Hiyorin, you had times like this as well...
Please kill me now. Just
kill me off in one blow.
And this is now.
Oh, no!
Wow, what growth!
You're right. She's really good.
Yeah...
Somehow, this picture looks
a lot like Iwasaki-san.
Oh, yeah...
It's Takarazuka!
Oh? Is this me?
Is this a fable or something?
Yeah...
I see.
When it's done, let me read it!
I can't...
I can't go drawing my friends
from such a rotten point of view!
Tamura-san, would you
like to go to Otome Road?
Yeah, I plan to.
Otome Road? What kind of a place is that?
You don't know?!
Nope.
Neither do I...
Oh, brother.
Otome Road, huh...
Otome Road, or "Maiden
Road," is a road located
to the west of Sunshine
60 in Ikebukuro, Tokyo.
"Otome Road"
There are lots of shops that
specialize in manga and anime,
as well as shops that are
full of character goods.
It's said that maniac fans gather
there as much as in Akiba.
However, unlike Akiba, there
are a lot of female patrons...
That's why the street was
nicknamed Otome Road.
In other words, it's a street
where the fujoshi go.
"Women and children"?
No, no, you write "rotten girl,"
and read it as "fujoshi."
They're rotten?
Well, when you put it that way, they are...
Oh, come on, the three-second
rule! The three-second rule!
If it's within five seconds, the
germs don't attach themselves!
What, I didn't say anything!
The meatballs... my favorite!
What about the three-second rule?
Well... If you can let it slide,
depending on the situation...
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Yes, I'd like to bring it to
you with spirit again today!
Despite everything, we're already on
the 18th episode of Lucky Channel!
And yes, your navigator is a
familiar face by now, Akira Kogami!
And...
Yes, I will do my best as Akira-sama's
assistant again today.
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Now, today's theme...
We'd like to introduce to you all of
the new additions to the cast... with a bang!
Bang!
Too many!
First off, we have Miss Yutaka Kobayakawa,
Miss Konata's cousin who is
staying with the Izumi family.
Her classmates, Miss Minami
Iwasaki, Miss Hiyori Tamura,
and Miss Patricia Martin.
Furthermore, furthermore, we
have Miss Kagami's classmates,
Miss Misao Kusakabe, and
Miss Ayano Minegishi.
This truly is getting to be a rowdy bunch!
I'm sure you have noticed this already,
They're in the way, aren't they? Eh?
but all the new members are showing
up in the opening sequence...
This is in my way!
It went flying!
Just how many do they have to bring
out before they're satisfied?
It's already episode 18!
What's the status of my appearance?!
Oh, that reminds me, you had
an appearance, Akira-sama!
In that ultra-cute outfit, the
raincoat and rubber boots!
No, no, you know what...
I had a chance to chat with
last week's guest, Mr. Anizawa,
and I was told that what an
actor needed most was flair,
a sense of presence!
Just how you entered the
scene today, Akira-sama!
It was only a fleeting
moment, but in my eyes,
"Akira Kogami is here!"
was written all over it.
Hey.
Yes?
Hey!
Oh, no, no, that's not it, okay?
Oh, too bad! It's already
time to say goodbye!
And so, we continue to ask for your
impressions, praise, and opinions. Keep them coming!
Hey!
Hold on...
We're still accepting them on
the homepage, and on the radio!
Then, bye-nee!
Turn that off!
A text message?
Then, thanks for the hard
work! Oh, no, it wasn't.
Was that a text message?
No, no, it wasn't! Of course
it wasn't anything like that!
Who were you texting?
Oh, well, it was from my parents...
For what purpose?
Well, um, they want me to
come visit back home soon.
What are you writing up?
Well, um, that's...
Spill it.
Wait, hold on...
♪ I had been looking for all this time ♪
♪ For what you call the person
you were destined for ♪
♪ I'm sure that it is you ♪
♪ Though I have no
basis for saying that ♪
♪ When I see your smile ♪
♪ Even ordinary everyday life ♪
♪ Starts to glimmer, so
it's rather wondrous ♪
♪ It's like a magic spell was cast ♪
♪ Feelings of affection, and
feelings of loneliness ♪
♪ You taught me both of them ♪
♪ No matter how long the road ahead is ♪
♪ I'm not afraid if I'm
together with you ♪
♪ Such a special day as today ♪
♪ I'm glad I'm spending
it together with you ♪
♪ With everything that I have ♪
♪ I will protect everything
about you forever ♪
♪ I promise you ♪
There.
I screwed up a bit on the falsetto.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was touched!
I was touched! I was touched!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
That's such an old quote! So old!
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Hiyori here.
Patricia here!
Patty, have you gotten used to your job yet?
Yes! It's perfect!
When you're dealing with them, Patty,
I'm sure the first-time customers
can relax and enjoy their stay...
No, I don't deal with the
first-time customers.
Oh? Is that so?
I only serve big spenders
who come to our place often.
That's the store rules that we have.
That's unexpectedly harsh.
Next episode: There's Substance in 2-D.
Please look forward to it!