Though my true power has been unleashed,
you are still able to keep up.
Yeah.
You're pretty strong, too.
Putting City A back together might be impossible.
Well, right now I should be focusing on the battle.
She may be rank 2 or whatever, but I can't leave it to one little girl.
I got my own ways of fighting enemies in the air.
Like this!
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
This area's got some nice rubble.
Hurry up and get out of my way.
This is her psychic power?!
I give up!
We're under attack again!
R-Return fire!
The guns are jacked!
Seriously?! We're dead meat!
This planet's too tough!
Lord Boros!
I wanna go home…
Such incredible power.
Tornado may actually bring it down on her own.
I have errands to run.
I will head out now.
Things appear under control.
Sure, go ahead.
Some heroes have already left.
Before I go, Genos, have you got a second?
There's something I wish to tell you.
Drive Knight, Class S, rank 9.
This is a first…
Listen.
Metal Knight is your "enemy."
Be careful.
What do you mean?
You will know soon enough.
But for now, stay away from him.
Bastard.
You sure make things interesting.
I'm beginning to taste victory.
The stiffness in my shoulders is gone.
But I suppose I'm a little rusty.
You're alive—
Hey.
Forget something?
ATOMIC
SLASH
Atomic Slash!
Insolence...
Such complete insolence!
You move your heart-thing around your body to hide its location.
But your regeneration always begins with your head
and in the center lies…
your heart.
After seeing it so much, even a monkey'd figure it out.
See? Checkmate.
No!
Silverfang!
All I needed was one more swing.
Keep your hands to yourself, Silverfang.
Goodness, I really do need to do more full-body workouts.
We got all the heads.
That means victory is ours!
Yeah, but there's still that big-ass ship up there.
All right, this is the last of the reported survivors.
Let's move!
Right.
Licenseless!
Quit your staring and come on!
Yeah, okay.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
I'm here! Go on! Let's fight fair and square!
What's going on?
I don't feel anything
There's no one to oppose me
Justice! Action! Take no prisoners!
I win! Evil loses!
Rest in peace, bitch!
Power, get power
The adrenaline's pumping
I'll blast you away with the skills I've mastered
Hero
Even the strongest started out as wimps
Nice moves.
As I thought, you are strong.
Hero
Of all the myriad beings I have fought, only you…
But they overcome themselves and become strong
survived this long!
Nobody knows who he is
God is here, so raise your fist
I only go straight forward, no exceptions
Now to release the destructive
energy held within me!
Hero
A hero fights until he's broken and no longer can
Any normal creature hit by it
would find even their bones vaporized!
A solitary hero
Behind you!
I wanna be a superhero
You were a worthy opponent,
but the outcome of this battle is clear.
In the struggle to survive amidst the harsh environment of our home world, my species came out on top.
We possess the ultimate in regenerative abilities.
I, in particular, have self-healing power, physical prowess,
and latent energy beyond your comprehension.
A deep wound that would be fatal for you
heals itself on me in mere moments.
By focusing all my energy on my destroyed arm, I can explosively speed up the healing process.
Good as new.
You, on the other hand, will only get injured more,
all while your stamina gradually decreases—
Shut up.
Blah, blah, blah.
Are you done?
With this?
Not yet!
Meteoric Burst!
The energy shunted from my body transforms into a propelling force,
elevating speed and power to a level beyond the limitations…
of living flesh!
Doing this places enormous stress on my body, similar to anaerobic exercise.
As a result, it shortens my life.
Therefore, it should only be used as a trump card for settling fights quickly.
It's listing!
You're doing it!
Awesome, Tornado!
Oh.
I made it.
This man…
makes me want to go all out!
That's the way, Saitama.
You are indeed worth defeating!
Consecutive Normal Punches.
I will defeat you!
All my energy will be released,
blasting you and this planet to Hell!
Collapsing Star, Roaring Cannon!
In that case, I'm using my final move too.
Killer Move: Serious Series…
Serious Punch.
Did I lose?
You're still conscious?
You really are strong.
The prophecy held true.
The battle was hard-fought.
Yeah. It sure was.
You lie.
You had strength to spare.
I never stood a chance.
It wasn't even a battle.
So much for prophecies.
You were too strong…
Saitama…
THE STRONGEST HERO
It's crashing?
Is this Master's doing?
We're done!
The power sphere's been broken!
We're going down!
Lord Boros went wild!
Get out, get out!
Run!
Stop shoving, stupid!
I wanna go home, Mommy!
It's coming down.
Huh?
Hey, we better get outta here!
This is bad. Run for the Association HQ.
Iai! Hold on to me!
I'm okay, Master!
Damn. How'd Silverfang get so fast?
Now's not the time to be competitive.
Angel Dash!
Hey pansy, don't you run in front of me! You're too slow!
Don't just say it! Move!
We're gonna crash!
It's down.
All right, let's go.
How did City A end up like this?
CLASS A, RANK 1
MASKED STUD HANDSOME MASK
All of Class S was meeting today…
Care to explain, Metal Bat?
Huh?
Explain it so I can understand.
Masked Stud Handsome Mask...
Where the hell'd you pop up from?
I was filming a TV drama in the next town.
There was a roar and tremors,
so I came and found City A wiped out.
Monsters on a huge-ass ship attacked us.
They fired artillery at us and did all this.
But we took care of it.
"Took care of it," you say?
You call this victory?
Such incompetence.
I'm completely appalled at all of you!
Hey.
You didn't even get here in time, so don't go acting all big.
It's true I didn't make it in time,
but you all were right here.
You didn't save a single brick!
We were having a meeting inside the headquarters building.
We went outside as soon as the enemy attacked,
but the city was already in ruins.
So what?
You think if you tell them that,
the media will just let all this go?
You…
Whose side are you on?
We did our best.
I'm on the side of justice.
Having S-class heroes this pathetic…
is an embarrassment.
Anybody this useless should voluntarily retire.
Hey!
Don't start talking crap with us!
Who's gonna care about a pop idol
with a face busted all to Hell?!
Do you have any idea why
I don't move up to Class S?
I remain Class A, Rank 1 so I can prevent
weak, good-for-nothing pissants like you from moving up to Class S.
Metal Knight, you skip the meeting and only show up now?
This is…
magnificent!
Metal Knight!
What are you doing here?
The battle is already done.
Metal Knight is your "enemy."
Genos, right?
Do not tell me you have come to recover the spaceship.
Are you here so you can create more powerful weapons with the alien technology?
Precisely.
Powerful weapons are a necessity…
for the sake of peace.
Even with powerful weapons, in the hands of heroes like this, they'd be wasted.
You're mine later, pretty boy. Watch your ass.
Hey!
I found some alien survivors!
I thought Lord Boros never lost.
Are we going to be killed?
Maybe we can talk our way out of this.
Argh, I'm so hungry!
Idiot! Now's not the time for—
Shh! Someone's coming.
Handsome Mask! What the—
They did not deserve to live.
They were evil.
I swiftly implemented justice, that's all.
I'm sure you understand,
Genos…
You've been busy since the exam.
But from what I saw of the Deep Sea King incident and today,
you've mostly been a disappointment.
Best leave it.
Do not worry.
I am fine.
He reminds me of how I was before I met Master.
A man on edge…
too eager to eliminate evil.
Just like me,
he must have gone through something terrible in his past.
Wait!
Where is Master Saitama?
Oh, I'm out!
Hey!
Why would a B-class hero like you be inside the ship?
Master!
You are safe!
Hey, Genos!
We're done here. Let's go.
Did you defeat their leader?
Yeah, he was really strong.
Maybe the strongest I've faced.
I see.
So without you, Master, the prophecy about the Earth's destruction would have come true.
They're ignoring me?
Nah.
Turns out you can't trust prophecies to begin with.
Hold it right there!
I don't know how you did it, but you went in the ship on your own?
You're just a B-class hero. How dare you butt in like that?
I didn't need you. I could have handled it on my own.
Baldy! Octopus! Boiled egg! Light bulb! Avocado!
Lame face! Goblin! Bug! Baldy!
G-Genos.
Ping-pong ball! Rice grain! Beanhead!
Say something.
Kettle! Baldy! Kneecap!
Yes, sir.
Listen, spoiled brat.
Shut up and get lost, or get beat down.
That's it! Yeah!
Unforgiveable. Me, a brat?
I'm older than you!
Genos?!
You're next, B-class!
Cut it out, Tornado.
You're part of the Association, a hero, right?
Whatever.
Why are there so many troublemakers amongst the elite heroes?
Genos… Your joints are all bent the wrong way.
Here, I'll fix you up.
Oh sorry, your arm came off!
My back is killing me.
City A was wiped off the map that day.
The arrival of aliens and City A’s annihilation were history-making events, the top stories for days.
But eventually the coverage died down and no one mentioned the city that had disappeared.
Metal Knight salvaged the spaceship.
Soon thereafter, the Hero Association headquarters was reconstructed all the stronger,
and became an impenetrable fortress of steel.
The infrastructure was rebuilt with new roads leading out of HQ.
Heroes were able to deploy quickly to every city.
And heroes ranked Class A and above were given the option to live at headquarters.
With sadness in my embrace, I ride the wind to tomorrow
Don't worry, just rest
Then you can start walking again
The world keeps spinning,
and with time we all experience pain we'll never forget
But close your eyes
Your memories will become your smile
Hope is the key
The sun sets of its own accord, bringing sleep with it
Memories, become my smile
Just keep those first happy memories
Then wave goodbye
You can see it clearly!
The entire building has been ripped out down to the foundations.
The monster appeared in City Z, but now City Y is in—
PLUTON
KING OF THE UNDERWORLD
THREAT LEVEL: DRAGON
You humans waste your existence in gluttony, littering the earth with worthless objects.
Now shall you boil and rot in the depths of the underworld that spreads below my mighty snout!
Who do we have here?
A great man who is a hero for fun…
and profit.
A great man?
And his disciple.
Back to one punch again…
God damn it!