How's your daughter doing, Niekawa-san?
Do you know Niekawa?
Yeah, just the name.
Niekawa Haruna-san...
Who is she?
No way. Shizuo's way stronger than I am.
The one who's been trolling Ikebukuro
BBS and chat rooms, right?
Run!
I love you so, so, so much.
Kadota, I'm borrowing your door.
Who do I have pay for it?
When I got back, I told Shinra
what had happened.
I told him it was all over.
But it wasn't.
No. It was just beginning.
It was a long, long night.
I left the collapsed man to Kadota and the others,
and I took the girl back home.
She's the girl who's always with Mikado.
She said she wanted to see
if I really was headless.
So you showed her.
Like Mikado, she wasn't surprised.
I wonder if, these days,
all young kids are like that.
No. I don't think youth has
anything to do with it.
Celty-san?
Um... Who are you?
Hello, Sonohara-san.
I am Niekawa Haruna.
Mutual
Love
So, yeah. Thanks for looking into Saika.
But it's over.
Yeah, well... Just seems
a bit anticlimactic.
Now, what do we do with this guy?
Ambulance, maybe?
You know...
Somehow, this just doesn't feel right.
I wonder why.
I'm off to Shinjuku to murder Izaya.
Hey, hey! Shizu-chan's definitely
in love with Izaya.
Two guys... Like BL!
No!
No. You know it might-
Shut up!
Just thinking about it makes me sick.
Anyway, here it is.
Don't touch it.
It might possess you.
This is Saika?
It's a butcher knife!
It surprised me, too. But the guy with it had
glowing red eyes and talked like a girl,
and he was rambling on
about love or something.
Love...
I've seen him somewhere before...
What's the relationship between
love and slashing, anyway?
Is Saika a sadist?
No, it's not really sadism.
Saika wants to love people.
It loves humans... Loves them so much that, eventually,
it stops loving any one individual and
starts loving a thing called "humanity."
All of humanity.
I don't understand. If it loves them,
why slash them?
You know why I've come to see you.
Right, Sonohara-san?
About Nasujima-sensei?
That has nothing to do with me.
It's just weird rumors.
I'm sure that's true.
But I love Takashi.
When people are in love,
they try expressing it through
different actions, right?
Actions?
Talking, holding hands, embracing...
Um, were you dating him?
It was more than that.
We were in love.
Just knowing it was enough for us.
Yes.
Forever and ever and ever...
But one day, I was rejected.
All I tried to do was give shape to my love!
Give shape... What do you mean?
She wanted to express her love
through action, too.
But Saika is a cursed blade.
She has no body.
That's why it uses its owner's body...
And keeps slashing people.
Again and again and again...
To realize her love.
To give shape to her love...
I was rejected
by Takashi.
No, I don't hate him.
Because I love him.
No, well...
Even if Takashi doesn't accept me,
even if he loves someone else,
I can forgive him.
But you know...
I can't forgive your being liked by him.
Ever...
Around five years ago,
Saika temporarily vanished.
But from what we see in the chat room,
she's still filled with love.
Wait, Shinra.
I remember!
I do remember meeting the
man with this knife!
He was a reporter.
His name was...
But I guess you can't use other people.
It's just proof that if you want love,
you have to do things yourself.
I thought my father would fare
better than the others...
But it didn't work.
So I'm going to finish things myself.
With you, my rival in love...
Was that man your father?
He said he was attacked,
right in front of his house.
His name was Niekawa Shuuji.
What was that about?
Are you OK?
Um, well, do you feel like anything's
trying to possess you?
No, it's fine.
This isn't Saika.
Look.
Why would a blade, whose records date
back decades, be made in 2009?
What's going on?
I know I... Believe me!
I believe you.
How could I doubt you?
Maybe this Niekawa guy knew the
Saika legend, and he imitated it.
But if this isn't Saika...
Saika is somewhere else.
Even as we speak, it's using someone to slash another.
What about the chat room?
What's happening to it?
But I...
I don't care about Nasujima-sensei at all.
Sonohara-san, it doesn't matter
what you think about him.
I'm just doing what's right for my love.
I don't love you, but she...
Saika will love you well.
I failed. The timing was bad.
How dare they hurt my sister...
A mother's orders are absolute.
This means there was no point in hiding it.
I can take stronger measures.
I guess they met Shizuo,
but I lost contact.
There are so many Saikas...
I can't feel them anymore.
How dare they hurt my sister...
If I had to analyze this,
I can guess one thing.
The timing was bad.
Celty, imagine this.
If you love someone so much,
what would you seek next?
But this time, I won't fail.
I'll give Heiwajima Shizuo my love.
I don't know.
Isn't that enough?
If I can love Shizuo, I can love this whole town.
Maybe not for humans.
I can love the town of Ikebukuro,
built by the deeds of many men.
After they've loved one another,
I'm waiting at South Ikebukuro Park.
they want something the two
of them can love together.
Heiwajima Shizuo
Appear...
You can't mean...
That's right.
Saika is giving birth.
It puts its children into the souls of those it cuts.
Wait a second.
You should take this chat log.
You're going to see Shizuo-kun, right?
Izaya-kun...
Let's pl-
Why are you here?
I came to punch you, of course.
Why do you want to punch me?
Because I'm pissed off.
Aren't you a bit old, to be acting as the Doraemon bully,
Shizu-chan?
Shut up!
How deep in this are you?
What are you talking about?
The Slasher that's causing trouble in my town.
That's a horrible accusation.
Violent, screwed-up crap that doesn't make
any sense is 99% likely to involve you!
Think you could believe in the last 1%?
You couldn't, could you?
I looked into you.
You're so sad.
Since middle school, you've hung onto
some girl named Harima Mika.
Trying to seduce every guy you see...
Oh, yeah... Five years ago,
a robber broke into your house...
What can I do to escape...
And killed your parents, right?
You were in the same room,
but supposedly didn't see them.
It's simple.
Just say it has nothing to
do with me, like I always do.
Why? You had to have seen them.
Oh, I know.
You seduced the thief, didn't you?
Even though you were in elementary school.
Maybe he was a pedo.
That's right.
You're a parasite. It's an easy way to live.
You live parasitically off others.
It's not easy.
What?
It's not an easy way to live at all.
Depending on someone else...
I think "parasite" is a good way to put it.
But do you know how much a parasite sacrifices,
so they're not chased off?
Understand?
So you sacrificed yourself, so that
Takashi would like you, huh?
No.
Nasujima-sensei isn't worth it.
I see.
Then die...
A friend?
Fine.
I'll stab your friend, right in front of you,
and then I'll kill you.
Seriously?
Oh, my...
Celty?
Why?
The hell?
This part of your plan?
If I could have planned for Celty
randomly appearing here,
I'd have dropped a meteor on
your house ages ago.
Geez, how's an idiot like him that smart?
This is why I hate him.
Niekawa!
Takashi!
I don't have time to deal with you anymore.
I'll have everyone kill you.
Everyone...
Honestly, everyone else is too
busy to deal with you.
There's still something else important left.
I love you... Shizuo...
Hey, Shinra. How many Saikas will come
to South Ikebukuro Park?
I don't know.
But Celty, one of them is the original Saika.
You should find it.
I understand.
That's the mother, right?
I wanted to see you so much,
Heiwajima Shizuo-san.
You really are wonderful,
just like mother says.
Each of us knows you defeated my sister.
The internet's nice that way.
The mother's not here?
Why?
At first, it was hard for our minds
to learn how to use words,
but right now, we have a determined mind,
just like our mother's.
Now, Shizuo-san...
Show us your strength, in front of everyone!
And let's all love each other!
No one will stop us - not that
monster there or the cops!
They're real busy right now!
Just a little bit away, my sisters
are making more sisters!
Can I ask something?
What is it?
Why do you like me so much?
You're strong!
That insane strength of yours... We want it.
So we can love all humanity.
The same way humans want good genes.
And no one else will love
someone like you, right?
But we can love you!
Snap out of it, Shizuo!
If things get bad, I'll make sure you get away!
No, Celty. Honestly...
I'm happy.
I hated this power so much. Hated it!
I thought that no one would accept me.
But you see...
So many... How many we got here?
Well, it's a lot.
So, then it's OK.
I can accept myself.
I can like myself.
This power I hated so much,
that I wished to be rid of so much...
I can use it all.
By the way,
ya'll ain't my type. Not a bit,
not a drop, not at all!
I guess I hate you almost as
much as I hate Izaya.
Shinra, there's something else that bothers me.
You said Saika vanished five years ago, right?
Why?
What happened then?
I doubt it was taking a vacation.
It's possible that someone very strong held it in.
A strong person...
I've thought about you for so long.
You loved me just as much.
You showed it in the way you
tried to use me for money,
and you showed it when you tried to
abandon me, once you were bored.
I accepted it all, forgave you,
and loved you!
But it wasn't enough.
That wasn't enough.
Then Saika started speaking to me.
Like this...
When, little by little, I gave her my blood.
Will you accept my love today?
Wait!
Niekawa-sempai!
Stop it...
Stop hurting people with that blade.
How did you escape?
Please stop.
Whatever.
Someone saved you again, I guess.
But Sonohara-san, I don't want to
hear this from you.
From a weak person whose only choice
is to parasite off others...
It wasn't my only choice.
It was the life I chose.
That is all.
A meaningless distinction.
I don't want you to decide whether people
are strong or weak, just by how they live!
Hey, Sonohara-san, have you
ever loved someone?
You couldn't have.
And so you couldn't understand me.
I took over Saika with the power of love.
The first time Saika told me to cut Takashi,
I resisted with everything I had.
But as I listened to her voice, I understood.
So Saika and I will be mothers.
We're making many children and spreading love!
Spreading the power of love!
We will love all humanity
and control them all!
You're right. I cannot love.
Ever since that day five years ago,
I've been too scared.
So I live by depending on something else.
Impossible!
Just like you made children by cutting others,
your Saika is a child, as well.
The original is right here.
I cannot love.
That's why I depend on Saika,
who can love others in my place.
No...
I am her parasite.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Everything
Changes
It's a lie.
It's the truth.
When a sorrowful past collides with the present,
she gains an incomparable power.
An incomparable everyday...
Next time:
Everything Changes.