When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Hayate.
His name will be Hayate.
We shall call him Hayate.
My, that's a great name.
Why did you choose that name, though?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because I want him to become a strong boy who will be able to run away from debt collectors like a gust of wind.
I see! That's a wonderful name!
Isn't it? It's because I'm a genius.
Now we won't have to worry when the day comes when we have to cast away our child and run.
You're amazing, Dear.
This is how the boy named Hayate became fated to obtain ultimate strength from the moment he was born.
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
The entire US population cried!
We'll make you laugh three times in five minutes!
Nothing but despair in getting Academy Awards!
What is this picture?
Isn't it a great portrait?
It is a gift brought to us.
Can you guess how much it is worth?
Open the price!
One... Ten... Hundred... Thousand... Ten thousand... Hundred thousand... Million... Ten million...
Two hundred million yen!
It's petty cash.
Here's the milk tea.
Good work.
I'm sure in ten years from now, an autographed illustration of mine will cost a hundred times more than this.
Good grief. I guess Milady doesn't understand quality yet.
The quality of the best things!
What did you say?!
What's wrong, Hayate?
This is a fake.
Eh?
Wh-What do you think you're saying?!
Do you understand that this costs more than the debt you have to spend the rest of your life paying?!
Excuse us.
How is it, Sensei?
It is a fake.
We received a call saying that
this might be a fake a little while ago.
Then, excuse us.
SFX: Gahhhhhhhhhhhn
Hey, where are you going?
Yikes!
I was thinking of becoming an artistic statue in the art vault.
B-But, Hayate-kun, you have a great eye for authentication.
How did you know that picture was a fake?
Well, that's because...
You see...
Back when I was little, I used to sell art as my father's assistant.
Oh, your father was an art dealer?
No, not exactly.
You certainly have a great eye!
He first showed a genuine picture.
Then, when the customer bought the picture, he gave the picture to me in front of the customer, so they didn't suspect him.
He will be packaging it.
Please hold on just a moment please.
The art would be expensive,
so the customer would be cautious, too,
but they always let their guard down against children.
So we sold the fake hidden behind the genuine while I pretended to be packaging it.
That's absolutely a crime!
I was little, so I didn't know that it was a crime.
And I was drilled by my father to be able to authenticate any kind of picture instantaneously.
How much useless information do you have in your head?
Ayasaki Hayate.
This show's main character.
Heroine on some occasions.
Man with an invincible body even though he never defeated the And****** Force.
The author loves World Masterpiece Theater,
so he's developed into a very unfortunate boy.
Excuse me...
Nagi, what have you been reading there?
May I have a moment?
Something's been bothering me,
so I'm reading the original work from volume one.
Something bothering you?
Please don't take away my narrating job.
You do think Hayate has great abilities, don't you?
Yes, of course.
He's too amazing.
Dexterous but powerful.
Does anything perfectly and quickly.
Over to the next room.
And he even has strange special abilities.
It's a waste to keep him as the main character for a love comedy show that doesn't go anywhere.
But there are times when the situation forces itself to battle.
So here's the question.
Does he have any weaknesses?
Huh?
Weaknesses!
Like mice for Dor***on.
Dogs for Oba*.
Tails for Go**.
Manga or anime main characters usually come with a weakness as a default setting.
Do they?
How do I say... Hayate indeed is amazing,
but has this I-want-to-make-him-cry aura.
Please stop.
I won't deny that.
Right?!
Since you have the same weakness as Robo***, you agree, don't you?
What kind of relation is there to this?
In fact, don't remind me of such a terrible thing!
Therefore, I think Hayate needs a weakness!
Come on! Hinomaru Box!
I prepared things that might be Hayate's weakness in these Hinomaru Boxes.
Then, may I see inside the Ma box?
Okay.
Open the box!
Um, Nagi?
Don't bring such a creepy thing near me!
Then don't prepare it.
It was our mistake to rely on Psychic **na!
"We"? I didn't.
We must find the weakness through observation.
Good, this is correct, too.
I've finally overcome my weakness in math.
Damn. Look, one of Hayate's rare weaknesses has been overcome.
I don't think that's a problem.
Let's observe more to see if there are any other weaknesses.
Oh, take a look.
Milady never eats sardines like this.
I'll mince it up and use ginger to get the smell off.
She's not good with carrots and green peppers, either.
She can't eat anything spicy.
Oh right, she's not good with chicken skin, either, is she?
He's making clear observations of things you're not good with.
It's because she has so many likes and dislikes that she doesn't gr-
Damn you!
Damn you, Hayate!
Looks like we have to try out common weaknesses.
Huh?
Tada!
How's this? He'd be surprised by this, wouldn't he?
Yes... It's surprising on multiple levels.
There's no one in this world who wouldn't be surprised to see a ghost.
This is a perfect plan.
To be exact, isn't that your weakness?
All I have to do now is wait for the night, and while Hayate is asleep...
I don't think you have to wait until dark.
See, all you have to do is make the room dark.
No, Maria...
I-Isn't it still early for this?
You think so?
But if you don't push it,
no one will be afraid.
You don't have to be that afraid.
You've got a long way to go!
That voice is...
Nattou, akadashi, and monjyayaki!
Note: Stereotypical foods people from the Kansai region of Japan don't like.
If it's weaknesses, I've got some, too!
Sakuya-san.
Where did you come from?!
The debt-ridden butler's weaknesses, eh?
All right, leave it to me.
Guys like him usually have unexpected weaknesses.
Something unexpected?
The fearful invaders that almost made humans extinct...
However their ambition gets trampled by microbes!
Isn't that an alien's weakness?
I can't leave this in Saku's hands.
What's a good idea...
I have a good idea.
Isumi!
What's your idea?
That's...
...to ask the person himself.
Right, that's a thought.
Eh?
So, what do you fear?
Let's see...
A cup of tea. Oh, so fearful.
Those who don't get it, please listen to a comedy titled "Scared of Manju".
Don't try to use something as old as the Edo Period!
Dom Pérignon is scary! Dom Pérignon is scary!
Did something just pass by?
It was your imagination.
Hey, what's your weakness, Isumi-san?
Eh?
I was wondering if the almighty ghost sweeper has something she's afraid of.
Something I'm scared of?
Yes, there is something.
Oh, what is that?
I'm scared of caterpillars.
Caterpillars?
So you're afraid of something very standard.
180 m long and weighs 20,000 tons,
it's the deity of Infant Island and makes a large cocoon on Tokyo Tower.
It withstands electro-heat wave attacks.
Once it hatches, it causes devastating damage to the world.
No wait! That's not exactly a caterpillar!
Laughed enough?
Nekasanaiyo.
Nekasanaiyo. = I won't let you sleep.
Yorokonde.
Yorokonde. = With pleasure.
I'm so full!
Thanks for the meal.
Sorry we had you prepare lunch for us, too.
Not a problem.
You sure picked them out well.
You thought you nailed my weaknesses, but not quite.
You'd better watch out, Hayate;
I will soon reveal your weakness.
You still haven't given up?
Maria-san.
When I finish cleaning up, may I take a break?
Yes, that's fine.
What are you planning to do, Hayate?
Just for a bit.
I wanted to continue studying.
The final exam is coming up, too.
Final exam?
I need to do well, so I can advance along with you.
With... me...
Y-Yeah, I guess...
You two. Don't disturb Hayate's studying, you hear?
You better not try and go find out what his weakness is.
You...
We'll be careful, Nagi.
Oh right, I have last year's math exam.
Would you like to look at it as a reference?
Yes, I'd love to!
Um, this is math, but the problems are not in Japanese.
Yeah, it's in German.
What? German?!
Germany would be that country famous for sausages!
Yeah, and also beer.
This is beyond the level of calling it hard!
H-Hi, Wataru-kun. Welcome.
We've sure received a lot of guests today.
Why did you come running in and shouting?
What is this exam about?!
Well, Hakuou is a prestigious school after all.
So obviously it's hard.
There is a limit to how hard you can make it!
He's right. There's no way we can read this.
You two can't read it?
Wataru, you even skipped grades, and you can't read German?
Just English is a handful for me.
You can choose to take the exam in English.
Um, I'm very iffy with English, too.
By the way, for reference,
what happens if you get a failing grade?
Please don't go quiet there.
What should I do?
It's really hard to be enrolled in a prestigious school.
I'm glad I went to a normal school.
Saku...
Looks like it's the end of the fun.
You guys, good luck with your studies.
Let's go, Isumi-san.
What? Me, too?
Yeah. If you're here, Wataru can't concentrate.
Why can't he?
Saku! You bastard!
Ah, well...
See ya, Nagi.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Let's go, Isumi-san.
Yes...
Oh, fine.
Meanwhile, at a normal high school...
Heh? What's with this quiz score?
Maybe it's a little bad?
Many say it's love, relationships, and whatnot and spend highschool living merrily, but high school life is quite rough.
I must study!
That'll do.
What are you doing, Milady?
There is a limit to how much studying you can do alone,
so I was thinking of taking care of my poor little brother.
I see...
I guess there are limits to studying alone.
Then I'll-
Unlike you, Hayate, he's not someone who can accomplish anything just by putting effort in.
Um, Milady?
I'll go teach Wataru.
I won't forgive you if a Sanzenin butler gets a failing grade.
Yes.
So what are you going to do, Hayate-kun?
Well...
Please teach me, Maria-san!
I knew you were going to do that.
Thank you very much.
Gosh, you'd better thank me.
I do.
If you were to drop a grade, I'd feel bad for Saku.
So you'd better work hard.
Y-Yeah.
But I didn't know both Wataru-kun
and Isumi-san were skipping grades.
Right, we didn't tell you that, did we?
Since we were sure Nagi wouldn't go to school without
her friends around, we asked them to skip grades with her.
They had good grades, too.
But originally, Isumi-san and Sakuya-san were supposed to advance.
To be honest, Wataru-kun's advancement was rather forceful.
There was a reason why Wataru-kun wanted to go to Hakuou badly,
but there were only three seats available for students who can skip grades.
Nagi was the one who taught him then, too.
I see...
They get along well, don't they?
Yes.
So, when the small beauty on the Infant Island gets lost,
I'm sure the entire world will fall into a panic.
Enough with that story.
By the way, how's school been recently?
Is it fun?
Yes.
But Nagi won't come to school that often.
Then is Wataru like the only person you hang out with?
Not necessarily.
I only say hi to Wataru-kun every so often.
Oh great. I was wondering if there was any progress, and it's this.
Eh? What are you talking about?
Nothing.
So, what happened to King ***ra?
Ah, so King ***ra goes-
But I'm a little worried.
What?
About Milady and Wataru-kun.
Although they are still children,
a young boy and girl are alone in a room.
Oh, come on, Hayate-kun.
It might be wise to bring coffee for them, aiming for the right timing.
You're thinking too much.
Besides, if you say a young boy and girl are together, just the two of them, so are we.
The obviously expected love-comedy mode.
Shall we bring coffee to them, after all?
Aiming for the right timing.
I-I agree.
Sorry for making you teach me all the time.
What's with the creepy honesty?
Y-You idiot!
I'm always honest!
You'd be cute if you were that honest all the time.
Stop it!
Milady!
We've brought some coffee.
Nice timing!
W-Why are you two holding hands while studying?
It's not what you think, Hayate!
Th-This is from how things turned out!
How things turned out?
What were you going to do?
Nothing!
Yes, Hayate! You got it wrong!
Yeah! I would never think of doing anything to Nagi!
What did you say?
After all, I like Isumi!
Eh?
U-Um...
I got lost while looking for Sakuya, and...
No, Isumi!
This is... um...
Hehe, just a joke.
Oh, it was a joke?
Don't you want to make progress, you wuss?!
There's absolutely no meaning in going to the same school if it's like this.
But you see it now, right?
You don't have to worry about us.
I-It seems so.
Now I can study with Maria-san
without worrying about anything.
You can rest at ease and-
Hold on just a moment.
Do what, did you say?
I said, study with Maria-san.
Study alone with Maria?
How dare you go do that, sneaking around behind my back?
I won't forgive you!
Milady?
Milady, what are you angry about?!
I don't want to hear it!
Looks like Hayate-kun's greatest weakness is not being able to understand the minds of girls.
And so next week, even the Hollywood movies will be surprised.
We'll fight against large luxury cruisers, terrorists, and sharks.
You've got to Isumize your joke.
No, you mean minimize your joke.
Just kidding!
You really like to make jokes.
Although they're not very funny.
But he's funny as a creature.
Looks like I have to train him.
Katsura Sister's,
Butler Network!
Bang! It's Katsura Yukiji.
B-Bang! It's Katsura Hinagiku.
We are the famous pair of beauties, the Katsura Sisters.
Tada!
Was that really right, Onee-chan?
I'm working with you since you say it's your chance to be on stage, but it's very embarrassing for me.
Hina, you need to enjoy it more.
We rehearsed so many times yesterday.
When this song sells, we can say goodbye to poverty.
I can drink all the Dom Pérignon I want!
See you next week!
I get it. I see.
The reason why Hayate doesn't look at me...
In starting a relationship, you need a cold attitude.
Isn't there any situation where Hayate would rely on me?
Nagi, Sakuya-san is inviting you on a cruise on her boat.
That's it!
Next time, Poseidon Advance Generator Gavas.
But wow, this ship is well-made.
You think? That's nice.
Even if you act cold, I won't fall for you!
Next time, just in on Hayate no Gotoku!