There will be strong north winds tomorrow,
and scattered rain showers can be expected near the Pacific coast.
I should bring the laundry in and let it dry inside.
Overall temperatures will be lower than in previous years.
Grandma, I'm back!
Welcome home!
I'll be borrowing Nii-chan's computer, okay?
Oh, my.
Come on! Hurry it up!
I've never been good with computers...
Let's see...
Kominato Ruuko
Folder
Inbox
Drafts
Sent Mail
Date and Time
This...
No way.
Is she trying to gather all the Selectors so they can battle?
It's really close by...
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
It's here somewhere, right?
Yup.
Ruuko?
Here?
When the construction work is over, it'll be just
like they planted a big pillar in that alley, right?
Ruu?
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Ruu...
Um, Ruuko?
If there's something bothering you,
or if you have something on your mind,
just say it.
Yuzuki...
So you think I'm... scary, too?
No one can tell what I'm thinking after all...
Huh?
Wait, that's not what I meant! That's not it!
It's just that you always try to
keep all your burdens to yourself.
Well, not like I was any different...
In any case, sorry!
And well, see this?
We're friends, you know?
Yuzuki...
Why are you so kind?
Huh?
Wh-What are you saying? You're weirding me out.
Why are you so strong?
Ruu...
If only...
I was like that.
Yuzuki.
Tama.
I...
I'll battle Iona-san.
What are you saying?!
You said you weren't going to battle!
Yes...
But...
But, you know...
I have a wish now!
I...
I want to save Yuzuki,
and Tama,
and everyone else who became a LRIG.
I want you all to be returned to your own worlds!
That's my wish!
No matter what I have to sacrifice,
that's my one and only wish!
Ruu...
I appreciate the sentiment,
but it's impossible.
Why?
As I said before,
Eternal Girls were originally LRIGs.
And LRIGs were originally ordinary girls, just like me.
A wish that can't be made true
by a normal girl can't come true.
There are some wishes that can never come true, right?
For example, wanting to time travel.
It's as you say.
However, it is not up to me to decide that.
What?
Thinking of the wishes the girls put on the line in Selector battles,
most of them are not
particularly difficult to grant.
Common sense, self-preservation...
It's aspects like these that
prevent wishes from coming true.
Still,
a LRIG must not be bound by such things.
If one continues to reject their Selector's wish,
she will never be able to leave her card.
LRIGs who wish to return to the outside world
grasp onto any wish with even the slightest chance of coming true.
For that wish to come true,
any underhanded deed may be taken.
That's...
And that is the very reason for the ritual of acknowledgment.
It is required as the final trigger.
Now, let's say it together.
I accept...
I... accept!
the Laws of the Selector.
The Laws of the Selector.
And now!
A new Eternal Girl will be born!
Once an Eternal Girl,
she is obligated to make a wish come true.
If, after the wish is accepted and the contract completed
the wish can not be granted,
the Eternal Girl disappears.
Remember what Hanayo-san said before?
How Hitoe's memory can't be restored?
That's because Hanayo-san judged it couldn't happen.
What about my wish, then?
I have no idea how to release all the LRIGs from their cards.
That girl might know how, though.
But I don't know how to find her again.
I might be able to do it.
I'm not sure, but...
I feel like I know how to make the LRIGs return to normal.
What do you mean?
I don't know!
But I feel like I can do it somehow...
I thought... I could...
Tama...
Maybe...
That's stupid!
It was all for nothing!
There was no need for us to go through all these battles!
A wish anyone can grant
just by putting some effort in...
But we become cards, disappear, and lose everything...
There are exceptions.
Not all Eternal Girls are normal girls.
Among them
may be special girls who hold mysterious powers.
What are these "mysterious powers," now?!
That's just ridiculous!
Despite being turned into a LRIG,
do you still attempt to deny the mysterious?
It's about time.
Your dawn as a LRIG card and the
meeting with your Selector has come.
W-Wait! Who are—
I will always be here.
Here, in the rift between the world of the cards and the world of reality.
Now then,
good morning.
Tama is somehow different from other LRIGs.
Maybe she's one of those "special girls" that girl was talking about.
Then my wish can...
You can't.
Did you forget?
If your wish comes true, you'll become a LRIG!
But...
if my wish is to release all the LRIGs from their cards,
I may not become a card at all!
But can you know that?
For all we know, you could end up sealed away as a sacrifice—
or something even worse!
But... But!
Let's give it some more thought, Ruuko.
We may meet again,
and we may talk like this again, too...
But...
you may not meet those who aren't Selectors, like your grandma, ever again.
Hitoe?
That's my LRIG, isn't it?
Hitoe, I...
Please give me back my LRIG.
Hitoe?!
Hitoe! Listen to me!
U-Uhm, Hitoe? I...
I have nothing to discuss with you.
Hitoe!
Wait!
Hitoe?
I will participate in Urazoe Iona's fan gathering.
If you want to talk,
we can do it on the battlefield.
If my wish comes true...
Grandma will...
I'm ba—
My, it's you.
She's doing fine.
She made friends, too.
Yes, right.
Stop with that, please.
A long time has passed since then.
There's no point in blaming yourself.
But...
please stop acting as if you're a mother.
It just wasn't in you to become a parent.
Miyako Cell
Message Memory
Notices
You weren't meant to be one.
Moreover...
Ruuko is neither the adult
nor the child you take her for.
Ah, right... I'll call you back.
Well then.
Ruu-chan, dinner is ready.
Mom?
You know, I have a wish now.
A wish?
You know, when I was a little kid...
Mom and Dad used to fight all the time.
It was really sad.
I knew that Dad and Mom really
wanted to feel close to each other.
But watching them fight still made me sad.
I figured that wanting to be close to someone makes things painful.
So I thought that I didn't need anyone else but you and my brother.
But...
Ruu-chan, you told me you wanted to do something for your friends, right?
Is your wish about that?
Is it something bad?
It's not!
Is it something good, then?
I think it's something good... I'm sure it is.
You know, Ruu-chan, you're my treasure.
If you think something is good,
then I think that something is wonderful.
Do what you need to do.
Your wish will come true.
Especially since you're such a kind girl.
Grandma...
My, what a huge baby I have here.
Ruu?
Are you really going to battle?
Yup.
We can battle Iona-san again, Tama.
I bet you can't wait!
I don't want to battle!
Grandma said all that because she doesn't know!
If she knew, she'd say no!
I want to be Ruu's LRIG!
I want to be with Ruu forever!
Grandma and I, we don't want to ever be away from you!
Tama, I'm sure it'll be okay.
But Yuzuki said you can't know that!
You know, when my wish comes true,
and I don't become a card but stay as myself,
then...
let's stay together forever.
Tama, you can live with me, too.
We'll have breakfast together...
We'll go to school together...
We'll be friends with Yuzuki and Hitoe...
It's closed now, but during summer, the candy store at the corner sells really good soft-serve ice cream.
We'll buy some together on the way home.
So, please...
I...
don't like it.
I don't.
And yet...
Tama,
I... have to go.
Take care, Ruu-chan.
Okay.
Will you be back by dinner?
Dinner...
I want to eat potato gratin!
With plenty of bacon, right?
Yup!
I'm going now!
I made a decision, so I need to go.
Everyone here knows
that we're all Selectors.
Welcome to the fan gathering, everybody—
No,
welcome to our Selector-only WIXOSS Party.
This building is owned by my father.
Construction work has been halted for the day.
No one will get in our way.
We are battling for our respective wishes.
But we don't know how many wins we need.
Our conditions are unclear.
I believe everyone present is frustrated by this.
However, with this many Selectors gathered in one place,
some here are bound to meet their conditions.
Today, several Eternal Girls will be born.
Several Eternal Girls?
But for every victress, there must also be a loser.
I do not intend to have anyone lose her rights to become an Eternal Girl through random battles.
The battles will be undertaken in the form of a tournament.
I will ask you to leave the battles if you lose.
This is to prevent unnecessary sacrifices.
Whichever Selector makes it to the end
will enter a battle against me.
Twelfth floor, number four?
Are you all ready? Now then...
Let the battles begin.
Open!
Tama. Grow!
Gothic Boundary!
I'm sorry!
I'll win this all and save you and everyone else!
I summon Mitsurugi!
This is the final blow, Tama!
Tama?
Tama...
Tama needs to agree with me,
or else my wish won't come true.
I'm sorry, Tama!
Akane
Naruse
Kominato
Konaka
I still...
need to keep battling.
It looks like we meet again.
You're willing to talk now, aren't you?
We'll talk on the battlefield.
Open!
There's no indication of any
Eternal Girls being born.
Yes...
But it looks like some Selectors have lost their third battles.
I'm going to go there.
I will reach that white room.
The place where she's waiting.
I bounce Suberia! Attack!
Yuzuki. Grow!
Banish Mikagami.
Hitoe...
She's a lot better now!
Severing Steamroll.
Tama, I'm sorry!
Yuzuki, attack. Banish Square!
Hitoe...
This...
is different.
What is different?
It's different from... when you and Yuzuki and I battled!
Ruuko...
We had so much fun playing WIXOSS together!
But back then, I thought that wasn't enough.
I wanted to battle more seriously.
Ruuko...
But now
when I think we'll never battle like that again...
Never again...
I knew it.
Hitoe...
still has memories of us.
Yuzuki?
Hitoe, listen to me! We three used to be friends!
Yuzuki!
It hurts, doesn't it? Forgive me.
But I want you to remember!
Y-Yuzuki, Hitoe is suffering—
Ruuko! Do you want her to stay like this?!
Being controlled by Selector battles...
And just when we finally became friends...
I want to have battles with Hitoe and Yuzuki like the ones we used to have!
I want us to battle as friends!
Stop... Stop!
Hitoe! Please remember!
Your wish already came true!
You don't need the cards for that! It's already true!
No... no... no!
Hitoe, don't give up!
Then, we'll once again—
Just shut up!
Hitoe!
I don't want to hear any more of this!
I... I want to make my wish come true!
I'm telling you that your wish already came true!
Just listen to—
No!
Please... Please!
Let me have my wish come true!
Hitoe...?
Hitoe?
That scrunchie!
Now then... isn't it about time?
This will be
my final battle as Urazoe Iona.
Yes...
I enjoyed battling by your side, Iona.
You were lovely to be with, you scum.
I will accompany you to the very end,
That
Summer
is
Longing
Selector.
That
Selection
.is...
That selection is...