I want seconds!
Coming up!
Wait a second, that's not right!
Why has it become normal for you to eat breakfast at my house?!
And why are you just accepting it like it's normal?
It's not a big deal.
Taiga-chan takes-up a small amount of space since she's so small.
Plus, it tastes so much better when we all eat together.
Just serve it already.
I just cooked three cups of rice!
How much are you gonna eat?!
S—Sorry...
Are you trying to make your pet go bald from stress?
Don't make it any more hideous than it already is.
Don't call him hideous!
It's so true. You know, they say that pets resemble their owners.
You...
You’re so ungrateful!
You're saying that to me when I; not only made your breakfast and dinner, I also packed your lunch.
Oh shut up, you mutt.
There you go again!
Give me that lunch back! Along with my kind feelings!
Shut up... and rot.
Ever since that midnight raid, Aisaka Taiga has started visiting our family meals.
Wait Aisaka!
I told you to wait!
And…
More importantly... behave properly when we get to school.
You better mediate things between me and Kitamura-san...
You promised me that you'd work for me like a dog!
This is the situation I'm in now...
If it looks like things aren't going well...
Minorin!
TL Note: Taiga is mispronouncing Minori's name as "Minorin"
You’re late Taiga!
Alright! You're energetic today too!
Good morning, Minorin!
Huh? It can’t be! What the heck!?
I-I'm sorry, I had no idea!
So Taiga and Takasu-kun were in the kind of relationship to go school together. Two-shot style.
That's wrong!
Yeah, no one says "two-shot" now-a-days.
That's not what I meant!
Oh I see! So it's "that" thing... Now-a-days it would be...
I'm so confused that I can't think of a correct way to say it!
I got it! It’s abeck!
TL Note: abekku(アベック) is not a Japanese word. It means couple.
I told you, that's not what's wrong!
Aisaka and I just happened to meet over there.
Right, Aisa--?
Oh, so it was just a coincidence.
It seems that we live near each other.
Well then, see you again Takasu-kun!
So yesterday on TV--
So that's how it is…
If I want things to go well with Kushieda, I have to get Aisaka and Kitamura together first.
Fine by me!
Alright! The 10th step is over!
Next, we'll have everyone form groups of two and pass ba--
Hey! Aisaka!
Let's form a group!
Sure, sure! Let's group up, Takasu-kun!
Right!
--lls for practice.
What is it Takasu and Aisaka? You two sure are full of spirit.
Taiga?
What? What? Is that what're they up to?
The plan is simple.
I'll lightly hit the ball against Kitamura's partner
And then...
You'll make an excessive racket about it and take him to the nurse's office.
If that happens; Aisaka and Kitamura, the only two that are left will have to be partners.
Maruo! Come pair with me!
If you want to pair with Haruta-kun
Yeah, I don't mind.
Come to this finger.
If you want to pair with Haruta-kun.
So, stop calling me that.
But you look just like him!
Come to this finger.
What?
H-Hey! Kitamura-kun's with a weird chick!
What the heck is going on?!
Y-You hit me in the gut...
You want to try pairing with me?
Alright, I will.
Kushieda too?!
Oh well... Time to carry out the plan.
Huh? But you...
Don't discriminate between genders.
And the bump that the brachium shows is--
Hey, Haruta. What’s wrong?
Without using your thumbs... you throw it!
It won't reach like that Kushieda.
The path to understanding the ball is quite a grim one.
It’s alright. Not everyone can keep up with me.
Man! That Noto…
Hey, pass it!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Pass! Pass! Pass! Pass!
Here I go, Maruo!
Alright!
Your pass is good.
What are you talking about Maruo?
No, that was quite a--
Hey, pass it!
Pass it? But...
I can't do it to a girl.
Here I go!
Pass!
I'm sorry Kihara... I'll make amends for my sins!
Ugh! You bug!
I’m sorry Maruo!
What happened?!
Takasu-kun brought palm-top tiger down!
Cra-crap...
The palm-top tiger that bites anyone without distinction.
Though, the more she screws up, the more obvious it is that she's trying her best.
It kind of makes me want to root for her.
Alright. It's important that you hand it to him as carefully as possible.
Don't suddenly act like there's something going on.
I got it.
With light feelings right?
Yeah... carefully... easily... loosely...
Here we go.
Hm?
Huh?
Where's Kitamura?
Oh, if it's Kitamura, he left saying that had some business at the B Area...
Ta-Takasu-kun!
He just left so he should still be around there!
There he is!
We're going after him!
Right.
What the?!
Get out of my way!
It's Takasu!
She's fast!
Well, she should be able to catch up then.
Ryuuji?
What about the cookies?
Ouch, it turned into a bump, just as I thought.
Hey, did you find it?
Was it alright?
Is that so?
Hey.
Could it be that I'm a klutz?
You weren't self-aware about it?
When I write a love letter I get the wrong bag.
When I storm in I fall over from starvation.
When I play basketball I get a ball straight into my face.
If I try to hand over cookies I fall over and drop them.
Also...
Hey, hey, there's still more.
Like forgetting the contents of the love letter.
That's right...
That...
Give me one of those.
Wait... those are all bits and pieces.
Plus they're...
They're delicious!
Looks like you were able to make them fine.
It's unfortunate... Let's try our best on another time.
I saw it for sure.
They were buying onions and white-radishes at a supermarket together.
They’re practically a married couple.
Those two came out of the same apartment in the morning and
I think it really smells really suspicious.
Plus, they were eating hand-baked cookies together!
They were like, "Here, say ah!"
Oh! Is that so? Is that so? No way!
Hey Minori, so what's up with your best friend?
What the heck?
Hey, get inside already.
Kya~
Kya~?
Can I talk to you for a moment?
The sun has dried up...
What's gotten into Kushieda-san?
I have no idea.
Takasu-kun.
Yes?!
Wait, me?
Please take care of Taiga!
Huh?
Taiga is a precious friend to me!
Please, please, guide her to happiness!
Wait a second Kushieda. Are you implying that--
Happiness?
So that’s how it is.
Don't you guys think it's a joyous thing?
Kitamura?! What in the world are doing up there?
I was wondering about the fact that you guys were together a lot, but
Now that I think about it, you two are perfect together!
Aisaka! Hang in there!
You there! Stop laughing!
Takasu-kun. If you make Taiga cry... I will never forgive you.
Kushi-eda.
Sorry about that.
Because I barged into your house, Minori has the wrong idea now.
No, that's--
It felt...
Hmm?
Really comfortable
at your place.
I've been on bad terms with my parents.
I told them, "I want to leave this kind of place!"
and they just provided me with that apartment.
Even though I already knew that they were that kind of parents.
Those cookies were salty weren't they?
Huh?
It felt vexing when I saw them in pieces so I ate a little.
What’s up with that? It was the worst.
But you just ate all of it and you even lied.
A mutt like you'll go bald if you care too much about others.
That's not your business.
Hey, do you think about Minori and get worried sometimes?
Yeah, I do.
Of course you do...
Aisaka?
I wonder why no one will understand.
Even though we're worried so much.
Why doesn't anyone know?
Really... everyone... everyone... everyone... everyone...
They
really piss me off!
Piss me off!
What's this palm-top tiger crap?!
I'm not alright at all!
Stupid Minori!
Stupid Kitamura-kun!
Why won't you listen to what I have to say?!
Papa and mama too!
No one... tries to understand me...!
I'll back you up.
What's wrong with being small?!
Don't call me a delinquent behind my back!
What's wrong with having a weird name?!
Sorry for having such "evil" eyes!
Hey, you alright?
Ryuuji... Is this thing tilted?
Huh? There's no way that could--
It's tilted?!
Right?!
We did it!
We won! We won!
Alright, I've decided.
I'll tell Kitamura-kun tomorrow.
And I'll put it to an end with that.
End?
The dog’s servicing is going to be over.
Starting tomorrow, we’ll just be neighbors in the same grade.
That’s all.
Bye bye, Takasu-kun.
Ryu-chan, isn’t today’s meal early?
I do like canned mackerel but...
I wonder if Taiga-chan is still sleeping.
Who knows?
Did you two fight, Ryu-chan?
We didn’t.
It's kind of boring.
Right?
Huh?
Uh-yeah.
Hey.
This is…
T-Takasu... Um, Sorry. Starting a weird rumor like that.
Aisaka-san got mad at us.
What?
"There's nothing between Ryuuji and me."
“Ryuuji isn't a delinquent!", she went on a rampage.
The palm-top tiger is certainly terrifying.
But didn’t I tell you guys that Takasu isn’t scary?
What? When did you say that?
More importantly, won’t we get in trouble if we don’t clean this up?
Kushieda?
Takasu-kun, I’m sorry.
About what?
Taiga, said to me...
Huh?
"I would never go out with Takasu-kun,
so it's a misunderstanding." Is what she said.
She said she wanted me to understand at the very least.
She had this serious, desperate look on her face.
But isn't that? Isn't that?
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Takasu-kun?
She--
What is she doing?
You’re going to tell Kitamura today right?
It isn’t time to be worrying about others.
Starting tomorrow, we'll just be neighbors in the same grade.
That's all.
That's all, huh?
Kitamura-kun!
I...
Kitamura-kun...
Kitamura-kun I...
That is...
Hey now... You're doing it just as you get to school?
If he rejects you, the rest of the day will be awkward between him.
Hold on a second.
It's still a little ambiguous, but I think I know what you're going to say.
Though, before that, I want to verify one thing with you.
Aren't you going out with Takasu?
That was Minori's misunderstanding.
There was nothing between Takasu-kun and I.
Don't you like Takasu?
That's not it.
We just happen to be neighbors.
It's not that I like him or anything like that.
Then, do you dislike him?
I don't dislike him...
But it's different.
It's not something like that.
Takasu-kun is
Uh..
Right! Fried-rice!
Ryuuji made me some delicious fried rice.
He cheered me up.
He even lied to make me feel better.
He stayed with me.
Because Ryuuji was there... because Ryuuji stayed with me...
That's why, I have the courage, even now.
Kitamura-kun, I like you!
Aisaka. You’re amazing.
Is that so. Don’t worry. I think your true feelings did reach me.
Kitamura-kun.
Do you remember Aisaka?
About one year ago.
You’ve started making a more interesting expression compared to back then.
An interesting expression?
Yeah. When you’re with Takasu, you have a truly interesting expression.
Takasu is a very great person.
And I believe the fact that you can think of Takasu in the way you just mentioned
makes you a truly wonderful girl.
The way I just mentioned?
Wha—
What did I say?
Anyway. I'm glad that it's true that you two get along well.
W-W-W-W-Wait a second!
Ryuuji has nothing to do with this.
Is my expression that interesting?
N-N-No that's not it!
W-What is it that I want?
Wait, what am I saying!
Was I able to say that I like--?
It’s alright Aisaka. It’s alright.
W-W-W-W-Wha-What's alright?
I don't even know what I said myself!
It's alright. I'm sure that we'll become very good friends from now on.
I told you, not friends! I was telling you that I---
Friends?
Right, we’ll be friends.
Oops. I’m going to be late for my homeroom.
You be sure to hurry too Aisaka.
I thought you were going to start crying.
Y-You! W-Why are you!
Were you watching?!
It wasn't on purpose.
Not on purpose? But you--
More importantly,
what do you want to do?
I'm going home.
Is that so?
In that case, I'll cook something up for you.
I bet you haven't had your breakfast yet right?
Did you even eat properly last night?
I bet you just went to a convenience store.
Cut it out!
Why?
If you do something like that, people will misunderstand again.
I told you that you don’t have to do that sort of thing anymore!
I don't know either... but I just can't leave you like this!
I told you that it's fine!
You're not my dog anymore!
Is that so?
Right, I’m not a dog. I’m Ryu.
That's why, I'm able to stay by your side.
Ai--
Taiga!
Taiga? But you--
Since the past, it's been a rule that a dragon should stand by a tiger's side.
I will become a dragon.
Then, I'll forever be by the tiger's side as a dragon.
There's a limit to being impudent!
Know your place!
You know!
Uh-hey!
Hurry up! I'm hungry.
Plus, we're going to form our next plan.
Something like that isn't enough for me to give up on Kitamura-kun.
Does that mean?
I don't care if you're a dog or a dragon.
You told me you'll be by my side so you better work diligently for me!
Ryuuji.
Guess I was too rash with that one.
Come on, hurry!
Alright, alright.
He said "Taiga".
After school-club girl, Kushieda.
Working girl, Kushieda.
Oh, you are Kushieda.
Wherever and whenever you dazzlingly shine.
Give one shot to 'em!