Geez...
You're so stubborn.
600 yen for a carton.
It's not getting any cheaper.
You can buy from someone else if you don't like it.
Okay, okay!
I'll take it.
Thanks for your business!
I guess that's enough for today.
Hey, young one.
Do you sell those cigarettes separately?
I'd like to buy just one cigarette.
I can't do that.
Twenty in a pack.
Ten packs per carton.
And one carton is 600 yen.
That's how I run the business.
I see.
Sorry about that, old man.
What a pity.
I wanted to try just one.
Here!
You'll sell it to me?
I told you.
I only sell for 600 yen per carton.
This is mine.
You can take one if you like.
It's good.
It tastes really good.
See ya, old man.
Make sure to buy a carton next time.
Say, where do you live?
I'll come get another one before I die.
So can you tell me where you live?
So, did you tell him your address?
Yeah.
I thought I'd just spin him some bullshit,
but it felt like that old man would see through any lies I told.
Really?
That's quite an old man, if you couldn't lie to him.
What are you saying?!
Oh, yeah.
I don't think you've ever told me either.
I mean, where you live.
Well, don't worry about it.
I'll show you my mansion sometime in the future.
With a place this small, I can't even bring a girl home.
I'm running low.
All right, I'll go to Lily's place tomorrow and get—
Not again.
America?
Yeah.
He has orders to return.
And he's invited me to live with him.
Really? That's awesome!
I'm so happy for you, Lily!
Really happy!
Well...
Still, if I leave, how will you get your cigarettes?
Don't worry.
A lone man can survive in any business.
Besides, I can't be in the black market forever.
So when are you leaving for America?
Next month.
He's going first to prepare for me to immigrate.
So you'll live here by yourself until then?
Something like that.
Then I'll come over to play from time to time.
I'll even bring the guys over.
If you like, we can live here as bodyguards.
Mario or Soldier, maybe,
but you?
You've never seen how strong I am.
It's not like I'd ever want to know.
Say that again?!
I'm gonna miss you.
If you want to see me, you should come too.
To America.
To America?
You know what he said?
He said you'd be able to do business wherever you were.
I'm leaving Lily in your hands.
Sure.
America, where drums pound,
and the sounds of trumpets and saxophones fill the air.
America, where a giant fridge bursts with meat and ice cream,
and aerodynamic cars rule the roads.
He's never forgotten his hatred from the bombing,
but for Turtle, the country overseas was a world of dreams.
I'll have to make as much money as I can, while I can.
Matsu'ura goes for a tackle!
He's got Aoki in a corner!
What will Matsu'ura do next?
There it is!
It looks like they're at it.
Matsu'ura's made his...
What's going on?
What's happening to my body?
Daddy!
Mommy!
Tae!
Where...
Where did you all go?
I don't want to be alone!
Isn't anyone here?!
Well...
Time to get to work—
Is that why I'm like this?
Give me a break.
It can't be.
I'm just tired.
A flash of light, a giant blast of sound,
and his daddy, mommy, sister, house, and school all disappeared.
Whenever he feels sick,
he's always reminded of the nightmare from thirteen years ago.
Can I help you?
Are you Maeda Noboru?
Yeah, so?
Mr. Sugi wants to see you.
Mr. Sugi?
Who's that?
My, what a surprise.
You don't know Mr. Sugi of One Percent Loan?
One Percent Loan?
Well, whatever.
It's your choice whether or not to come.
He simply asked me to relay the message.
However, I've never seen anyone stupid enough to turn him down.
Well, excuse me now.
What are they in line for?
That old man!
Mr. Sugi, I'm sorry.
I only came here to pay the interest.
Sure, no problem.
Just come show your face every day.
Um, I'd like to borrow 1000 yen.
Okay, very well.
Well, well...
I came to check this place out,
but you're just a small-time moneylender.
Hey, can you get me and this old man some coffee?
Coffee? Okay.
A cup of coffee is 50 yen.
Paying 50 yen for someone is the same as loaning him 5000 yen.
Are you really that rich?
I'd like to show you something.
Come with me.
I started my business right after the war,
and I built this house just two years ago.
You're kidding, old man.
You built that house in ten years from your small-time moneylending business?
I'll pay you 3000 yen per month.
Well, would you like to help me with my business?
For just 3000 yen?
To be frank, you should be paying me for the lessons.
But I guess that general has some good in him.
Yeah.
Hey, we're short on beer!
I know, I'm coming.
Sorry for the wait.
Hey, Noboru.
Have you decided what you're gonna do now?
Yeah, I have.
I'm gonna be a moneylender.
A moneylender?
Yeah.
It's a job that helps the people in need.
Does it have something to do with that old man you met?
Yeah, you could say that.
That old man does this "One Percent Loan" business.
It's not like a normal loan business.
He loans no more than 3000 yen per customer.
Interest is one percent a day.
One percent...
So if you borrow 1000 yen, it's ten yen a day?
Yeah, and it makes the customers more likely to borrow and repay.
It's an easy way to get through the rough spots.
Further, he doesn't write up an IOU.
Are you serious?
However, he does make the customer promise one thing.
Are you sure I don't need to sign an IOU?
Yes, I don't care about your business.
However, do promise me one thing.
Come pay me back every day with at least a day's worth of interest.
I want to see your face every day.
That's it.
What an interesting old man.
So you're going to help him with his business?
That's right.
I'm not exactly the type to work under someone,
but I feel like I can under him.
A moneylender, huh?
I think it suits you.
It sure does.
You're cheap.
Hey, who's cheap?!
"Don't take a one percent profit so lightly."
"If that old man can build a mansion in ten years,
I'll build a hotel in twenty."
Turtle, who was the smallest of all,
spoke more proudly than any of them.
We should start cleaning up.
Meg, can you wake them?
Okay.
Who are you folks?
That's what I want to ask.
This house is supposed to be vacant.
What are you saying?
This is the general's house.
That contract expired last week.
From now on, this man here will be living here.
So get out.
Please wait.
It has to be a mistake.
You still don't understand?
That general deceived you.
Don't give me that, you bastard!
The general...
...probably told her he'd take her to America, and she really believed him.
It happens all the time around the base.
They don't have to pay alimony, and once they return home, it's sayonara.
Shut up.
Stop laughing, you fucker!
But it's hilarious!
A prostitute thinking she could be an American soldier's wife?
Who does she think she is?!
Hey, knock it off.
There are some things you just shouldn't say.
If you say any more, I might kill you.
I figured something was up.
He sure pulled a good one.
He got me to say uncle.
That old man's pretty good.
Lily...
Well, sorry about that, sir.
I didn't mean to be a bother.
I'm sorry, but I have guests over today.
We'll all be gone by tomorrow,
so here's for the trouble we've caused.
Tomorrow? Give me a break!
Get out now!
You're Japanese.
That American deceived me.
Can't you give a poor woman a break?
If you're still here tomorrow,
I'm reporting you to the police.
Sorry about that, guys.
Can you help me clean up?
Hey, why the gloomy faces?
Well, what are you going to do now?
I'm not a complete idiot.
I figured this would happen,
so I scammed some money from him,
enough to start a business.
You have secret savings?
Are you serious?
I never trusted that old man from the beginning.
What's wrong, Lily?
That asshole...
He took the money I worked so hard to save.
Dammit!
Don't give me that, you shit-head!
You can use my room.
I'm leaving tomorrow for a wrestling tour.
Yeah.
I'll do something.
I'll do something so that Lily can make a living.
Turtle...
See ya.
I'll come over to your place tomorrow.
Take care of her.
"Even if she's a prostitute or whatever, Lily is family."
"There's no way in hell I'll let her solicit on some cold street corner in town," Turtle swore.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Family.
They all worry about each other and risk their lives.