We 11 Valkyries have answered your call,
and by your wishes have assembled here.
What is it you need from us?
[Göll] Oh, our sisters.
Brünnhilde, may I ask
what it is you're planning?
I don't understand.
How can the other Valkyries help?
Greetings, Randgriz. Step forth.
Right. Very well.
RANDGRIZ
FOURTH OF THE 13 VALKYRIE
It's nice to see a familiar face.
Let's not dawdle, then.
I trust you have knowledge
of Thor's Divine Treasures.
Why, but of course.
First, there are the iron gauntlets,
which can block off any attack,
the Járngreipr.
Then, there's Mjölnir,
the hammer that became legend
when it defeated the Jötunn army.
That's right.
The two powerful weapons
wielded by the god of thunder.
They're the pride of heaven,
but they're damn cheap if you ask me.
Uh, that language...
For us to stand a chance against Thor,
we'll need to outclass
those armaments of his.
If you would be so kind, then go ahead
and offer yourself, Randgriz.
As you wish, sister.
With the utmost pleasure.
Uh, hold on.
Offer yourself how?
[heavy metal music playing]
KILLER MOVE
- [crowd cheering]
- [intense operatic music playing]
[Heimdall] Whoa, what's going on?
There's light from Lü Bu's halberd!
Is it starting to glow?
Curious. I sensed this.
Something strange.
Wait, could this be...
Huh?
- Isn't that thing...?
- That's impossible!
[Brünnhilde] Feast your eyes.
Behold the vast power
that lies deep within each Valkyrie.
It's our trick for leveling
the playing field against the gods.
Cheat for cheat.
Witness transcendence!
[narrator] When a Valkyrie
transforms her body
into the form of an earthly weapon,
the one who holds it wields a godly arm.
In other words, a Divine Treasure.
And that power has a name.
[Randgriz] Divine Treasure Forge!
Völundr!
[shimmering]
[metallic ringing]
Now that is an unyielding blade,
for an unyielding foe!
If this is the afterlife...
consider me impressed.
[narrator] When Völundr
is cast on a weapon,
it inherits the attributes
of the Valkyrie who performed it.
The fourth eldest Valkyrie is Randgriz.
Her name translates to...
"Shield Destroyer"!
Then there's Mjölnir,
one of the mightiest instruments
of the Divine Treasures.
With enough force to shatter the earth,
power flows from it like lava
capable of incinerating
the very life that wields it.
According to the Edda,
Thor must wear Járngreipr
to protect his hands from his hammer,
as one cannot brandish it without it.
Járngreipr, a formidable counter
to the most formidable weapon,
and therefore the most sturdy
armor of the heavens.
[shattering]
Till now, this sight
should have been impossible to see.
[grunts excitedly]
That's our Griz for you!
[Heimdall] What? He pulverized it.
A Divine Treasure!
He's managed to do the unthinkable!
Lü Bu has crushed Járngreipr
like a potato chip!
- Excellent!
- Yeah! Nice!
- [crowd cheering]
- Eat your hearts out, you pathetic gods.
Lü Bu's the strongest man in
the Three Kingdoms, so pay your respects!
I bet you're pissing yourselves, huh?
[growling angrily]
[laughing happily]
Huh?
Enough, Zhang Fei, it is not
in our place to cackle so boastfully.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Well, that would be proper etiquette.
- Hm.
But as one who shared an era with him,
who witnessed his courage,
I cannot deny it.
A pride that burns from my soul.
[soldiers chanting]
All hail Lü Bu!
[soldiers] All hail!
That strike was incredible!
Your strategy is beyond compare!
My liege!
Tha... That was flawlessly executed.
Look how you're enjoying yourself.
To fall on my sword,
and to rise once again in your name,
is truly an honor!
[humans in crowd shouting encouragement]
[man 1] The skills of that man...
He's tougher than steel!
[man 2] That guy's stronger than an ox.
[narrator] In that moment,
the people trembled in anticipation.
For this was more than history.
Since the dawn of the human race,
nobody had ever managed to surpass a god.
This was unprecedented.
How curious.
So that's the truth
of this entire charade.
Ah, you're catching on?
As you know, a Valkyrie's sworn to duty.
She's the bearer of souls.
Descending upon the Earth,
they look for the finest warriors
and summon them to Valhalla,
forming a divine army to prepare
for some impending heavenly crisis.
But, conversely, I've also heard some
unsavory rumors floating about.
They say that these preparations aren't
merely for an assault against the gods.
Now, according to the legends,
the Valkyries form a bond
with the heroes they have chosen,
transforming themselves into the most
perfect weapon suitable for that warrior.
In this way,
the sisters grant them their powers,
which rival those of the gods.
And the name of that special skill...
is Völundr!
It's a magical process of metamorphosis.
[whooshing]
With their newfound ability
to face off against the gods,
the vanguard will attack.
In essence, a Ragnarok.
[splashing]
[grunting]
Of course, I understand now.
This isn't a challenge.
In truth, it's actually
a bold-faced rebellion!
[coughing and groaning]
[grumbling] Those girls.
I never imagined they would
take up arms against us.
Why, since the Big Bang,
this is the most insufferable,
unspeakable...
[shouting] extraordinary thrill
I've ever felt!
Ah ha!
My heart is on fire!
[inhaling deeply]
Huh?
Br... Br... Br...
- Brünnhilde!
- [Göll whimpering]
Brünnhilde! Where are you, my sweet?
[Brünnhilde] You might wanna
stop leering at us, you pervy old lech.
- [crowd murmuring]
- [gasping]
[sizzling]
[man 3] Goodness, what is that?
[man 4] What's happening?
Huh?
What's going on here, sis?
Uh, I'm confused.
[gasping]
[Zhang Fei] Careful down there, Lü Bu.
[man 5] It's red hot.
[crowd chattering]
That hammer's beginning to smoke.
I wouldn't wanna touch that.
Could this be...?
Look, his weapon is starting to melt.
It's turning into
a big puddle of hot lava.
[Heimdall] Well, what a spectacular sight!
It's as broiling hot as the legends say.
Talk about unexpected.
But whatever the reason,
Thor may be in trouble.
Because now that the god of thunder
has lost one of the Járngreipr,
he's going to have a tough time
wielding Mjölnir with both arms.
Surely this is a joke, right?
Does this mean he can't use it anymore?
No way. [whimpering]
- [thumping]
- Huh?
[thumping]
Hey, do you hear
that weird thumping sound?
[thumping]
Hmm. Hm?
[Heimdall] Is that some kind of drum?
[thumping]
Wait a minute.
This is astonishing!
It's not a drum.
It's Mjölnir's heart beat!
[thumping continues]
Finally, you've awoken.
[beating continues]
[screaming] No!
Is that hammer actually pulsing?
The hell?
Don't tell me that it's a living creature.
I'm gonna be sick.
Ah!
[Zeus laughing]
About time that hunk of junk
decided to wake up!
"Decided"? Like it's alive.
That's frightening.
[chucking]
There's a fallacy
about the legend of the Divine Treasures.
- However, it's a fairly common one.
- [cracking]
Really? What's that?
Why those gloves do exist.
In reality, the reason that they're worn
isn't to protect Thor from his hammer.
I'm afraid I don't follow.
I'm saying those gloves are there
to keep his power safely contained.
Thor uses them
so he doesn't accidentally crush Mjölnir
with his grip before it activates.
[crashing]
Uh?
[gasping]
[Zhang Fei grumbling]
Hm!
[thumping continues]
Ah, rise and shine, sleepyhead.
[crowd exclaiming]
[chuckling]
One-handed grip.
How mighty.
[gasping]
[Heimdall] Wait, what's he doing?
Human...
No. Your name was Lü Bu.
I have one lone request for you.
Huh?
[crackling]
Don't you die.
Huh? [laughing]
[Heimdall] The stakes have been raised.
At last, the mortal hero has inspired
the Norse Force to start getting serious!
It seems like anything could happen next.
Not even the gods can predict
how this one will turn out.
We're in uncharted territory, folks!
[crowd cheering]
- [ringing]
- Uh?
Huh?
Hey! It's against the rules
to check your phone, Brünnhilde!
Hurry up and put it away
before we get into trouble.
[whooshing]
[breathing deeply]
Uh, sis, are you okay?
- Ah!
- Well, now we know.
Huh?
The challengers
who will be participating was unknown.
Until now, that is.
The official list was released.
Ah! Wow.
That's a stacked list.
ZEUS, BUDDHA, LOKI, APOLLO,
POSEIDON, SUSANOO NO MIKOTO
HERCULES, VAIŚRAVAA, ANUBIS
ODIN, BEELZEBUB, SHIVA
QIN SHI HUANG, KING LEONIDAS
NIKOLA TESLA, KOJIRO SASAKI
JACK THE RIPPER, ADAM,
TAMEEMON RAIDEN, SOJI OKITA, RASPUTIN
NOSTRADAME, SIMO HÄYHÄ, SAKATA NO KINTOKI
That's two teams of 13 champions,
whose actions decide everything.
[shivering]
With the fate of the whole
human race at stake.
It's a countdown.
Those 13 people aren't just fighters.
They're the 13 last hopes for mankind.
[scoffs] That sounds desperate.
[giggling] Don't despair.
I have a more suitable name.
A proper title that all beings
shall know and revere.
They shall be the 13 god killers!
The Einherjar!
The great saviors of humanity.
The legendary Einherjar!
Lord Zeus,
the participants who will be representing
the human race have been determined.
Oh, let me take a gander.
Oh, that's an intriguing lineup.
[laughing]
This could be
more interesting than I thought!
I can't wait to see how this will go.
[laughing]
[thumping continues]
[Heimdall] All right,
look alive, everybody.
The tension is unbearable.
But the first round of the ultimate
showdown between man and maker continues.
The destiny of the entire human race
hangs by a thread.
And with Thor now at full throttle,
the standoff between the god of thunder
and the champion of China
reaches the apex!
[all murmuring]
[groaning]
Lü Bu...
Thor's not kidding around, huh?
I've never seen him
fight like this before.
I don't suppose that I have either.
[narrator] The strike
of a pulsing Mjölnir,
Though the gods may be omniscient,
it is the first time that any of them
has ever observed such a phenomenon.
[crackling]
Don't forget now.
[exhaling slowly]
[straining]
[narrator] A story from the younger Edda,
written by the renowned Icelandic poet,
Snorri Sturluson.
As the tale goes,
Thor defeated the Jötnar, smashing his
opponents' skulls with his mighty hammer.
Because of Mjölnir's magical properties,
when Thor throws his hammer,
he never misses.
[exhaling rapidly]
[steaming]
[grunting]
[Heimdall] He's too fast
for the naked eye.
He dodged the hammer
by the skin of his teeth!
Thor is unarmed
and Lü Bu is in for the kill.
[growling]
Wait! Mjölnir somehow returned!
It'll hit Lü Bu from behind!
[metallic scraping]
[Heimdall] He parried it by twisting
with the movement of the spin.
Thor's weapon flies back to him!
[grunting]
[narrator] There is more to the legend
than what was recorded.
He doesn't merely fling his hammer
to sail it through the air.
That is only one element of his strategy.
The true intent behind this technique,
is to build speed and momentum.
Allowing him to unleash
his ultimate attack.
[gasping]
No, watch out!
[giggling joyfully]
I know that maneuver.
Ah!
He won't survive this.
It's the same move Thor used
to finish off Jörmungandr years ago.
That was the only time he resorted
to it, right? Now he's using it again!
Ha!
[chuckling]
[growling]
[Thor] Geirröd Thor's Hammer!
[narrator] This was the most emotion
Thor had shown during the onslaught.
And with a sneer, Lü Bu smiled
back with his evilest grin.
[horse screaming]
[Japanese pop ballad playing]