WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the seiyuu for 志筑仁美(Shizuki Hitomi):
新谷良子(Shintani Ryouko) - affectionately called りょーこ(Ryooko).
Hello everyone! Um, with the role of Madoka, it's Yuuki Aoi! Um, this time...
it's Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika volume four, episode seven Can You Face Your True Feelings? audio commentary!
Me, and—
Yup! With the role of Homura, Saitou Chiwa, and—
Yup, arranged with the role of Shizuki, Shintani Ryouko!
Yaaaay *clapclap* Ryouko-chan!
Yaaay *clapclap*
That's right, she's Shizuki-san, huh?
That's right, Shizuki Hitomi...
That is Hitomi-san.
Right, right, right.
The kanji is hard.
That's right, it was hard to read at first.
And now it's completely serious! From ep6.
Ne~?
It sort of crawls up on you, though...
Ne?
No more brightness.
You don't have time to finish recovering.
Ufuu~!  (ﾟεﾟ )
That's right, like you'll get deceived by this cute little thing.
Really, he's scary~
Yes.
Ne?
Cute QB.
Really, now, the story moves forward a great amount...
with this thing's bad parts.
Ne?
This completely white thing...
Rapidly.
has a lot of darkness associated with it!
Well, Ryouko-chan has finally come.
Yes!
That's right!
That's right, huh?
Right here is when he becomes like that. Right? (lol)
Mm!
That's right.
It isn't normal, you know.
That's there, that's there.
That's right, he begins to get a bit evil.
Now, I wonder what we should ask, Ao-chan?
Right? Ah, um... What do you think of Hitomi?
Eh? (lol)
How about for auditions?
Then, auditions!
Mm.
Ahh, the topic of auditions is okay? It's a bit of a sorrowful topic though.
Ah, mm, I think it's fine.
I didn't originally ask for Hitomi's role. After the other roles were probably no good, I went to Hitomi.
Ah, I see, I see. So you didn't intend to get Hitomi.
Ah, so you didn't.
Ehh
Mm.
At first it had changed around, though.
Ahh, right, right, right.
Also, QB.
But that seems to be about true for everyone.
Right? Seems so, right?
Then, there was Kyousuke, too.
Ah, right, there was Kyousuke too.
Kyousuke, you know.
As for me I took QB, and one more... so it was Kyousuke, you know.
Ahohoho, right, right, right!
Unexpected!
I took QB and Kyousuke, and um... I was told by Urobuchi-san to try out Homura, so I took Homura, though...
Is that so?
Right, that's why, it seems like everyone tried a lot of characters.
I was told "What do you want to do yourself?"
Ne?
That was probably, Sayaka and Homura.
Ahh, is that so?
Then,
I asked to please try them out. Right, right.
That was a bit of a special part.
Right, but Hitomi was a bit of a surprise!
Hitomi, you know.
Because Sayaka and Homura are pretty different, right? Obviously. So when I took Hitomi...
"What kind of tone should I take," I thought. Mm.
How did you interpret the role of Hitomi?
Somehow, when I first took Sayaka and Homura, there was a slight overview of the scenario, right?
When I saw that, I knew that she'd be a character who'd change Sayaka quite a bit.
Somehow or another, she had that image.
Then, I found out that I thought she was a pretty wicked girl.
That's right, it was always covered up.
She might just be the most bad.
Right, right.
After I was told, I thought "Ah, what should I do?"
When I had first seen the script, I thought she was like a tidy ojou-sama, so...
Mm, that's right. Right, right, right.
At this point, I thought that if she was going to move out of righteousness to grant her love, then I sort of had a guess...
Well, my image of her was that of a sincere ojou-sama.
That's right, she really seems like a delicate person, doesn't she?
Sincere and pure.
Ahh.
I'd say she somehow or another had that image, though...
Ahh, I see.
She had that feeling, huh?
That feeling!
(lol)
But then, starting here? Is this where it starts?
At this time, I'd say "Oh, Hitomi's dirty."
Ah, that's right, huh?
In a word, yes. (lol)
But with her "black" expression, you wouldn't know.
What is different will differ, huh?
Somehow, you know...
She's upfront, but also too much of a thief, right?
Mm, mm.
That's right. Right, right. But, that's...
Um, that's true for their age range though.
Mm.
They're middle schoolers, so they'll end up hurting each other's feelings and such. You understand when seeing that sort of thing.
Right?
When you think about the fact they're middle schoolers, you can really say that they're amazing, I think.
That's right, isn't it?
For Sayaka, you know.
They're strong, aren't they? Super strong girls, aren't they?
Mm.
strong.
That is, somehow, she's a "properly righteous and strong" person...
Well, it's just that she probably doesn't know much about Sayaka's circumstances.
That's right, ne.
But there's no helping that, is there?
Well, it has begun now, so...
That's right.
From the eyes of Madoka herself, her view of the world has completely changed now, hasn't it?
I believe she is seeing absolutely different things now.
Somehow, there was that conversation before, wasn't there?
Right, right, right.
That's why around here, Madoka goes into a constant decline, right?
Right.
Madoka and Sayaka are constantly depressed.
That's right, you don't really see smiles anymore.
That's right...
That's true, huh?
Sayaka has been feeling dull...
Riiiight.
Sayakaaa
That is, you know...
She begins to converse with Homura a lot more.
Mm, mm, mm.
That's right. Mm.
Around here, what is it, when Homura-chan comes, she gives Madoka a slight bit of relief.
Like at this time, by talking to each other, they give each other stability and a bit of relief.
It's as if though, at least for now, they won't break.
That's right, isn't it?
But around here Homura's sense of herself is extremely shaken up, though...
Right, right.
Really, just like this, Madoka's direct interactions build up, and she endures it but she can never respond to it,
I think that a lot of people who aren't sure about her circumstances are watching this, since you don't know until the end, but...
When you know it, and listen to her lines once again, there's a sort of pitiable feeling the entire time.
Right?
Right.
Riiight.
From episode one, it's pretty painful to watch from Homura's side.
Right–right–right–right–right
That's why, each and every episode, Homura-chan is unexpectedly shaken up, isn't she?
That's right, isn't it?
Although, that's... perhaps not in this episode yet, but they add moments where she's extremely shaken up...
Mm, mm mm.
That's right.
But I can't that say until later. Even though it's commentary.
That's right, isn't it?
(lol)
It's done on purpose!
Ahh, is that right?
On purpose~
(lol)
That's right, isn't it?
Right, right, right.
That's true for Madoka as well, isn't it?
Right!
There are a lot of things you can't say. Right, right.
Thesre area lot! of things you can't say. Right, right.
Mm, mm.
You can't say anything about Madoka until the very, very end.
Right, right.
It's a "can't talk about it" mountain.
Mm, there are a lot.
But, well... at this point, everyone did it on purpose, right?
Mm, mm.
Ne!
Did it on purpose~
Even for Hitomi, after this...
Right, right.
Ne? Ne.
It was on purpose, after all.
On purpose, you know. (lol)
On purpoyou know~
But you know, I think Homura is amazing.
mmm
mm, mm.
Somehow, you know, she's extremely strong, isn't she?
That is true~
But perhaps, really, when I was acting as her, I could see her strength, but...
I thought she was also very weak.
Delicate!
That's right, isn't it?
It feels like she has no choice but to become strong.
In the end, I guess that's really how it is if you have something to protect, huh?
There is strength... but you may be weak as well.
But you know, lately I've been having thoughts that, in the end...
the exhausted people who say "Help me!" are the really strong ones, you know.
Ah, but you know, that just might be right!
Mmmm.
Right.
The people who don't say that are the ones who are actually weak–This is true for Sayaka.
That's right, huh?
That's right.
She doesn't say anything, does she?
I really think this, but when you get cocky about yourself, or think of yourself as strong, or place too much on yourself...
That entraps you, and it's actually weak.
That's right, isn't it?
In that sense, Hitomi is actually the opposite, she's really "resolute,"
That's right, ne.
but she acts very fluffy and girlish, when in reality she's extremely strong.
I consider her strong!
She is strong.
Somehow, she seemed a bit strong in those scenes that imply she's studying to become empress, too.
Somehow... that's true, isn't it?
She properly has confidence within herself too, you know.
Right, right.
She does, she does, she does.
Hauum~
I sort of want to be like that.
want to be like that.
Mm, right, right!
As a girl, it's strong.
Right.
Since I'm a person who would cry when given the chance...
Ne?
Right.
Ahhhh.
Mmm.
That's one part I think is amazing about Hitomi.
Right, right.
I think she's amazingly strong.
This has been mentioned before, but it feels like Hitomi will be the most happy in the end.
(lol)
Right? I think that's right.
Probably, girls like that will properly grab hold of happiness.
I think so. (lol)
Mm.
I feel as if though I aspire to be like her. It's an ideal image for me.
Right, right.
Mmm.
Then... the one Ao-chan loves.
The one I love. It's Kyouko-tan.
Kyouko~
Cute, isn't she?
Kyouko-tan is the absolute best!
Nice, isn't she~?
I love Kyouko.
Riight.
Dangerous...
And then you know, Aipon's play of her is extremely nice, isn't it?
Really.
Ne?
Neee?
It's a bit playful.
Mm!
Mm.
This, what is it... it's like she isn't trying to be cool, but she's still REALLY cool.
Right, right, right, right.
That's amazingly nice~
Then, since she always has her heated temperature turned on...
Right, right, right, right.
It's really nice, isn't it?
That's right, isn't it?
This part—During the recording for this part of the show, it was always like "Sayaka Magika!"
That's right, I thought "Sayaka Magika."
(lol) Sayaka Magika, yeah!
It was always said.
Right?
Mm.
That's right.
Ne?
Right.
But right here, the slight discrepancy in these two's sense of what's "correct" gives off a very human sense of contrast between them...
And this art here is wonderful, isn't it? Amazing.
Really, I'm taken aback by this kind of atmosphere each and every time...
Amazing, isn't it?
Mmm.
Mm.
It's like "HWAAA!"
Amazing.
I'd say it's... cute, but scary, and a little bit enchanting.
Mmm.
Amazing, huh?
This is true for Kyouko's topic of discussion right now, but...
There really is justice born from anguish, but it gets thrown off a bit and breaks...
That's right.
Nee?
Right?
Mmm.
But, when she takes a departure from justice, she begins to go into denial.
That's right, right, right.
Right...
That's right.
Mm.
That's why in this story, you can really feel everyone's sadness...
Right, it hurts...
Right, right. But you know, somehow at the very end, this is relatively true for all of the characters. They all, umm, probably...
Between being ruined or becoming refreshed, they end up being ruined, don't they?
Right, right, right, right.
They're shaken up to such an extent, everyone cries...
At this point I'd say that everyone is falling into ruin...
Mmm, mm, mm.
Right.
That's right.
That's right, isn't it!?
That is another part of this story...
Ah—Yeah. I can't say it (lol)
Everyone is definitely carrying some regrets...
From there, a path of regeneration isn't really chosen...
That's why, throughout the entire story it feels like everyone resonates with you, right?
That's right.
There are a lot of things like that. A lot of cases where people choose to fall into ruin from a regret.
Later, it's like receiving help would have been all right, when you think about it afterward...
Surely, you will grow from that experience, when thinking about it afterward...
Right, like you won't repeat the same thing again.
That's right.
Right, right.
But you know, from the despair becoming a witch—
Ah–eh, uhh mm, tte–
(lol)
So, when they become one, it's extremely "Ahhh..." feeling.
That's right, isn't it?
Really.
That's why even when things that have a forward-looking attitude are said,
like Kyouko-tan's conversation right here, they're still always holding sorrow.
That's right, huh?
Right.
Somehow, Kyouko-tan is giving it her all, but she can't properly obtain what she's aiming for... that hurts too much.
That's right, isn't it?
Right.
That is painful.
That's right. Actually, um...
Madoka's family is properly depicted,
Sayaka and Hitomi are people who also have a family...
In comparison, all the of the mahou shoujo are pretty much alone, aren't they?
That's right.
That's right, isn't it?
Then, I believe there is a contrast between those people, but...
Unexpectedly, the people who have others giving them protection are weak.
Then, Kyouko, Homura, and Mami-san, the people who are alone, are brighter spirited and look forward.
That's right, ne.
Umm, well, Homura isn't bright spirited, but she's the one looking ahead the most.
That contrast left a huge impression on me...
That's why, for the people who are protected by family or such, probably, they are somehow...
They depend on other people and show weakness.
Then there are the ones who don't depend on anyone.
Ne?
Mmm.
They aren't hung up on their past,
but that past hurts so, so much.
Since they all stood up by themselves, you know?
Mmm.
Ne?
Moreover, there is their age, too...
That's right.
Right.
That's why they seek friends, like this.
That is true for Homura, who is constantly seeking friends. Same with Mami-san.
That's right, isn't it?
It's actually true for Kyouko, too.
Right.
That's right, isn't it?
Mmm.
Kyouko~~ ♡
Cute, Kyouko~
What's this, now?
You love her, don't you, Ao-chan?
I love her, you know~
I understand it. Kyouko is nice.
She's nice, isn't she?
What is it... You could say she has an antiheroic style, yet she's aiming for "justice" more than anyone else...
Right, right, right.
Very human-like, isn't it?
Right.
Even though she aims for an overall justice that she believes in, she has to fight to overcome aspects of her own unjust self...
Right, right, right.
Somehow... I think that hurts a lot.
Really, I find this difference between Kyouko and Sayaka's reasons for fighting amazing.
Riiight.
Ne?
I think, "That's amazing!"
Somehow, Kyouko is fairly sour, but she's actually the one acting in others' interest the most.
Right, right, right.
Sayaka is constantly like "Kamijou-kun, Kamijou-kun" but then in the end might've been doing it for herself.
That contrast between the two is really...
Right.
Mm, mm.
Really, you know...
It successfully felt like a woman's viewpoint, didn't it?
Mmmm.
That's right.
Mm.
Ryouko-chan, you acted as Hitomi, but other than Hitomi, were there any completely unrelated roles you liked?
Riiight,
well, looking at it objectively, then Kyouko.
Mmmm. That's right.
Mm, I think it's amazing.
Mmmm!
Kyouko is cute.
Well, looking at it objectively, Madoka is the one I understand the least.
Ah, I see!
Ahhhh!
That's right, huh?
You still don't really know, right?
That's right.
Then in the end, as the person inside Hitomi, after this, it's a bit... She isn't shown much.
So I haven't seen how the other characters develop in the after recording stages.
I see, I see, I see.
I'd say Madoka is the number one character who is still very mysterious to me.
I see, I see!
I'm already... "Madoka Love."
(lol)
Right, I thought that might happen!
So I haven't actually seen what happens at the very end yet...
I want to know about Madoka so badly it hurts. (lol)
Well, Madoka is really the most normal girl, but...
That's right, huh?
She's the one who blunders about the most, but...
in response to that, umm...
At the end, you know!
It's huge.
It feels like it completely transcended the rest.
In the world, there are people who properly voice themselves, and then there are people who are apprehensive about it.
When the indecisiveness and silence of those who are apprehensive disappear, it's scary.
(lol)
Ahh, I see.
That is certainly true, ne?
True for Mado-chan.
People who have bad circumstances end up being good people.
That's right, they're good people.
Ahhh.
The ones floating about are like little kittens.
The little floating kittens are cute!
(lol) Right. It's like that.
Like that.
Ah, she's come, finally.
This everyday life is kind of... relieving, isn't it?
A bit relieving, isn't it?
Mmm.
A bit, you know.
On the contrary, I find it scary.
(lol)
By now you'd call it scary.
Looking at it now, right?
How did the people around you perceive Hitomi?
How did that go, um... Director Shinbou said "You can do this," but...
Somehow, you know... this really... Looking at it afterward, especially to the fans...
You know? I don't really stand out that much (lol)
Really?
Hitomi herself might not stand out that much. (lol)
I think that being her seiyuu is amazing, truly wonderful, but...
Really, what is it... eople properly watching this series...
They know the views of the multiple characters it commands, especially those of Madoka and Sayaka...
But as for Hitomi, she's standing in a position where she doesn't know much about Madoka or Sayaka's circumstances.
Right, right, right, right.
She's a girl going for her own justice.
I think that doesn't go so well.
That's right, ne~
But you know, the viewpoints on Hitomi differ between girls and guys, don't they?
They may differ.
They're probably different, ne?
Looking from a girl's viewpoint, it's pretty "Uwah!" but... you understand.
you understand.
That sort of feeling.
Right.
From a guy's viewpoint, it might just seem pretty terrible.
That's right, huh?
It might feel like she's snatching him away.
But, everyone is really like "that," right? It's sort of like... what fairness.
Ne?
Like she is raising her public image a bit.
No—
Somehow, Sayaka hasn't been boiling over very much, but this is kind of like a fire starter.
Mm, how's that.
There is something like that too, isn't there?
That's right.
Right, right.
But you know (lol) really, she just decides on the timing herself.
Right! That's right.
One day, huh?
Hitomi has decided, just one day.
B—But they're still only fourteen years old!
Well, that's true.
It's honorable, isn't it?
Right, right.
It's fair and square and it's honorable.
But you know, this girl's ability to look forward makes you think "Ah wow, she's so confident in herself!" It's enviable isn't it?
She has strength, huh?
Mm.
Right.
Strong.
She's a strong girl.
Right, right.
Somehow, you know.
Then, Sayaka is the type of girl who's bright and energetic, but has no self-confidence...
Somehow, I really understand that.
Mmm.
In this work, the contrast between any two characters is really interesting, isn't it?
Right, right.
Relating to that, this work is one with a lot of conversations that hurt, isn't it?
That is right.
Th–This girl is just scary now~
If I was told this, I'd definitely be more like Sayaka - "Ah what3jaefja3jafd."
If I had to pick one, I'm actually closer to Sayaka.
Somehow, this... She isn't really wrong, so...
The spot it hurts is surely painful.
That's why Sayaka is all mixed up inside of herself, you know...
But everything happening at this timing is incredibly bad for her.
That's why, even if she's saying something that is fair and square, it's still like "Ehhh?"
Sayaka would be like "Ehh?"
It's like if this happened a bit earlier, it might've been a lot better.
But you know, that's... they're children, after all.
That means they won't give too much previous notice.
Right, right, right.
But somehow, thinking about what happens after this, I believe that Hitomi is also a really big victim...
Guess so~
Right.
But we haven't watched that far yet, so it's off-limits, you know?
(lol)
R–Right.
Somehow, weak people will be taken under someone's wing, but...
even for strong people, until they truly become strong, they also rely on support...
I think that as a rule, you can't say it's awful.
This story hopes that you dislike Hitomi more and more here. That's the feelings it adds.
There is such a meaning, yeah.
I get really into my own role, though.
I think so.
That is very amazing...
It's nice, it's nice.
Ne.
Mm.
Sheesh, this part... (´；ω；`)ｳｩｩ
I really understand it...
Yaa, I can feel it.
It's got a more heavy resonance to it.
And then you know, Eri's play, you know...
Right!
It hurts, huh?
It hurts!
This is dangerous.
It hurts.
But during after recording, at this point, every time I saw her like this, I thought "Sorry~"
(lol)
I was always thinking that (lol)
Mm.
Mou, this is cute...
That's right, isn't it?
At this time, Madoka is really kind, isn't she?
I think she's a girl that does it well! Amazing!
She isn't just acting here. The fact she actually feels and accepts it is amazing. That's what I think (lol).
She is able to do this, but she just quietly accepts it.
Right.
She's there when she wants her, isn't she?
That's right, you know that's important for being friends.
Mm.
Somehow, in her class, she doesn't really stand out, but she can really read the air.
That point of Madoka really does stand out to me.
Mm, mm, mm.
Mm.
I'd say that is there.
That's right, huh...
Right here, Sayaka has her own circumstances going on. She's sorting things out for herself,
That's right, isn't it?
and Madoka understands that, so she's staying quiet, you know.
That's right.
Right.
Even still, she holds feelings of wanting to help her, but for right now she'll stay quiet.
Amazing. I think that a 14-year-old knowing so much about relationships with others is amazing.
Amazing.
Right, right, right, right.
Before this conversation, when talking about the relationship of "those three," it's really like Madoka wants to protect Sayaka.
That's what I think.
Really, three girls are difficult together, huh?
(lol)
Difficult, huh.
In that regard, having a childhood friend who's a boy would be a blessing.
Neee~? Ne!
It really is a blessing, then. (lol)
A boy, huh? Ah, difficult...
(lol)
And, here we go.
Ah, it's come.
Mm, it has come—
This part DEEPLY MOVES ME!
This gives me goose bumps!
It's too cool.
This is coo—
I thought "So this kind of thing has come," this kind of presentation.
It surprised me.
It's like it's in shadows.
This! How it's a bit brighter, so you can properly see the art.
This is quite cool.
Right, right, right, they properly drew all the art, didn't they?
This is super cool!
Cool...
This is cool, isn't it?
Then, what is this, this part has Sayaka's true feeling—
Riiight!
The colors become a bit more dull...
Ahhh...
Mmmm.
That's right.
Right,
Then if that's the case, you could say that Sayaka is actually stronger...
That condition, you know.
Mmm.
Mm...
Somehow it's like "Being a hero hurts, huh?"
That's right, huh?
and then there's the fact she uses a sword.
Ah, she has received help.
Ahhh!
あんこ(Anko) - Anko is Kyouko's nickname in the online JP community.
It was given to her because they read her name wrong in early magazine scans.
Usually when people post things saying 「あんこ」, you'll see a reply like 「あんこじゃねえ！きょうこだ！」(It isn't Anko! It's Kyouko!)
Anko~
It's Kyouko-tan!
(lol)
Everyone is pretty quiet right now, though!
But it's commentary though, you know!
It's too amazing, though...
When I read the script, it said she had a "crouching start," which made me laugh,
But then when I saw it on air, it was a little bit too cool...
I felt a bit embarrassed at myself for initially laughing. (lol)
It was actually cool, like this.
Right, right. Like "Ah, so it's like this."
Ah, this part of the show is really like S–Sayaka time.
Super Sayaka Time ☆
It hurrrts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
(lol)
I'm sorry~
No, no, no, no, no, you were just doing your job.
(lol)
Mmm.
Somehow, for having a hand in creating this work.... Ryouko-chan, what do you admire?
Mmm, right, somehow, really... Mm, somehow...
This might be getting a bit too detailed, but in order to make such an extremely brilliant world, the process of it turning darker;
the transformation of that sort of presentation.
For example, it had what you'd call the "mahou shoujo image," especially the whole "kira bright sparkly" part of it,
but then it strayed THAT far away from it...
When doing a seiyuu's job, you really felt the difference in how you had to speak.
Oh, ohh—
Amazing, to go that far.
In that sort of way, your heart flows out...
I'd say there's growth, but properly, there are also things that do not change.
That sort of... molding of each person... I think of it as it deep.
I watch it every week.
Amazing, huh?
Man, seriously. "What's going to happen after this?" REALLY piques your interest.
Ne?
Ne~
Commentary is almost over.
Yes!
Yup. Next time who'll be on?
...
Ao-chan, you okay? You look like you're about to cry.
(lol)
Next time is—
Next time Taniguchi-san will be coming.
Ah,
Is that so? (lol)
(lol)
It was there just earlier, you know.
Ahh ::garbled mess::
Next time Taniguchi-san will come.
Yees
Yes
I think he will be someone you'll want to hear talk from here on out!
Right, then, Ryouko-chan, thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Yup,
We will continue commentary next time.
Wed willcontinue! commentary next time.
I look forward to working with you!
Yeees~