You deceived us, didn't you?
I believe I precisely requested that you become a magical girl, didn't I?
I omitted an explanation about what kind of thing the "reality of their figure" is, though.
Why didn't you inform me of that!?
Because you didn't ask.
If you didn't find out, it wouldn't have brought you any inconvenience to just go on without ever knowing, either.
In fact, that Mami girl never realized even at the very end.
First off, you humans aren't aware of something like your soul's existence to begin with, are you?
Over there is nothing but a collection of neurons,
and over there is just the center of a circulatory system.
Nonetheless, when that can't maintain life, even a human's mind and soul will be annihilated.
To prevent that from happening, I gave you girls your souls in a materialized form. One that you can hold and precisely protect.
I'm hoping to make it a little bit safer for you to fight witches, you know.
Thanks for the big help! Such an unnecessary thing!
You're thinking about those things called "battles" far too lightly.
For example, how much do you think it would stimulate your body's sense of pain if a spear was stuck into your stomach?
This is the original amount of pain you would receive.
It's just a single strike, but you can't move, right?
At the end of your battle with Kyouko, you were able to stand up because this saved you from anything too intensely painful.
It was only possible because your consciousness isn't directly linked with your body.
Due to this, your life extended past that battle.
If you grew accustomed to it, you could also completely cut off all pain.
Although, if you did that, your movements would become dull, so I don't really recommend it.
What for...?
Why do we have to go through such an experience...?
You had a desire that you wanted fulfilled, even if it meant accepting a fate of battle, right?
And that unmistakably became reality, didn't it?
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it again here?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away however many times necessary as I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 7
Can You Face Your True Feelings?
Stand.
Bow.
Homura-chan, were you aware?
Why didn't you inform anyone?
Because even though I have discussed it in the past, not a single person has believed me so far.
Why does Kyubey do such an awful thing?
That thing doesn't even think it's awful.
It's not an animal that can be held to human values, after all.
No matter what, he will only repeatedly state that it is justifiable compensation for a miracle.
That doesn't counterbalance anything at all!
He gave her a body like that...
But Sayaka-chan simply wanted to heal the injuries of the person she loved!
There's no mistaking that it was a miracle.
He made the impossible possible, after all.
Even if Miki Sayaka devoted her whole life to nursing him...
There never would have come a day when that boy could put on musical performances again.
A miracle, you know... In truth, it isn't something that can be bought, even with a person's life.
That thing walks around selling them for that price.
Sayaka-chan can't go back to her original way of life?
I've already said it before, right? "Give up on Miki Sayaka."
Sayaka-chan gave me aid!
If Sayaka-chan wasn't a magical girl, Hitomi-chan and I would have died at that time!
You mustn't confuse gratitude and responsibility.
There are absolutely no means by which you can rescue her.
Since you don't want to feel inferior, you want to do something like repay your debt...
Throw away those obtrusive thoughts.
Homura-chan, why are you always cold-hearted?
That's right...
Perhaps it is most likely because I'm no longer human.
With a body like this... what kind of face should I meet Kyousuke with?
(Don't sit there dejected forever, dummy.)
(Lemme see your mug for a bit. I have something to say.)
As I thought, you're having regrets, aren't you?
About getting this kind of body.
Y'know, I just thought, "I guess it's fine."
Whatever happens, I can do as I please since I've obtained this power.
You shouldn't go as far as regretting it, y'know.
You're just suffering the consequences of your own actions, right?
That's right, suffering the consequences of your own actions is good, y'know...
If you only live for yourself, anything and everything is your own fault.
You won't resent anyone, and there's no way you'd have something like a regret.
If you think of it that way, you can carry almost any burden, y'know.
Bringing me all the out to a place like this, what do you want?
It'll become a bit of a long story.
Want a bite?
Don't disrespect things you can eat, all right?
I'll kill you.
This place, y'know... was my old man's church.
A person who was too honest and excessively kind.
Every morning, he had an expression of sympathy each time he read the newspaper...
He was the kinda person who took worries seriously, y'know.
"To save a new era, a new creed is necessary."
That was my old man's saying.
That's why on one occasion, he went as far as preaching things that weren't in the doctrine to worshippers.
Of course, the worshippers' feet came to a sudden halt.
He was also excommunicated from the main branch.
No one listened to what my old man had to say.
That's natural, isn't it?
Viewing it from the outside, it'd be a suspicious-looking new religion, y'know.
No matter what kind of moral or obvious things he said,
to society, he was merely someone who'd take hold of your nose.
Our whole family was left in a state where we didn't even have stuff to eat.
I couldn't comprehend it.
My old man never said anything that was a mistake.
They were merely things that were different from what other people said, that's all.
Five minutes would be fine.
If they'd just properly bend an ear, anyone would have understood that he was saying things that were moral.
Yet... no one would give him companionship.
It was frustrating.
It was unforgivable.
The fact that no one understood what that person was saying...
I couldn't endure it.
That's why I relied on Kyubey.
"Make everyone listen to my old man's speeches seriously."
The next morning, my old man's church was full of commotion from a huge crowd of intrusive people.
Every day, worshippers multiplied at an absolutely frightening rate.
As for me, I openly joined the ranks of the magical girls, y'know.
However good my old man's sermons may have been, it didn't mean they exterminated witches.
So for that part, I plunged into it wholeheartedly like an idiot, thinking, "That's where I come in!"
I thought my old man and I would save this world, both on the surface and behind the scenes.
But, y'know... one day, the trick was exposed to my old man.
When he learned that the crowd of worshippers weren't there simply out of faith, but were gathered by the power of magic...
my old man became enraged.
He spoke ill of his daughter, me, saying, "She's a witch that bewilders people's hearts."
That makes you laugh, huh?
Even though I was continuing to fight real witches every night.
And then my old man broke.
The end was pitiful.
He nearly drowned in sake, his mind went crazy...
It ended with a forced group suicide, taking his family against their will, y'know.
I was left by myself.
My prayer had demolished my family.
Because I had just decided on my own to wish for another person's circumstances,
in the end, everyone fell into misfortune.
At that time, I made a vow in my heart.
I'd never use magic for another person's sake again.
I'd use up all of this power for nothing but my own sake.
Those things called miracles aren't free of charge.
When you pray for hope, an equal amount of despair will spread in proportion to it.
It reaches equilibrium and becomes zero, which is how the world holds its balance.
Why did you want to talk to me about such a thing?
You should get serious and do as you please... Living while suffering the consequences of your own actions, y'know?
Isn't that strange?
You should be living while only thinking of your own benefit, and so...
what's your reason for worrying about me?
You and I began with the same mistake.
You shouldn't continue a way of life that you'll regret anymore.
You've already paid too high of a price in compensation.
That's why, y'know... From now on, you ought to think about how to get a bit of change back.
Like you?
Yeah, right.
I understand that, while right now you continue to make mistakes.
I can't watch that kinda thing.
I had various misunderstandings about you.
For that, I'm sorry. I apologize.
But you know, I don't regret praying for the benefit of other people.
So that those feelings won't be lies, I've simply decided to have no regrets.
From here on out, too.
Why do you...
You know, I don't think I've paid anything like too high of a price.
Depending on how I use this power, I can do as many wonderful things as I'd like with it, after all.
And hey, you...
Those apples... how did you obtain them?
What about the money you paid to the shop?
You can't say it, then.
In that case, I won't eat those apples.
I'm not even happy to receive one.
You freakin' idiot!
We're magical girls, aren't we!?
There isn't anyone else like us, is there!?
I will continue to fight in my own style.
If that becomes a hindrance to you, then it's fine to try and kill me like before.
I won't lose...
I won't bear a grudge anymore, either.
Sayaka-chan, morning!
Good morning, Sayaka-san.
Ah... yeah!
Morning!
What was the matter yesterday?
Ah... I just felt a little sick or something, you know.
Sayaka-chan...
(It's all right. I'm fine now.)
(So you don't have to worry.)
Well then, let's have high spirits again today—
My, Kamijou-kun was discharged from the hospital?
Kamijou, are your injuries fine now?
Yeah. If I seclude myself in my house, I won't rehabilitate, you know.
My goal is to walk without crutches by next week or so.
Isn't that great, Kamijou-kun?
Yeah...
Sayaka-chan, go to him as well.
You haven't spoken to him yet, right?
I'm... fine.
So... what'd you want to say?
This is a conference regarding love.
You know, I have been keeping something a secret from Sayaka-san and Madoka-san since a while ago.
Eh?
O–Okay...
Since long ago, I...
have loved Kamijou Kyousuke-kun dearly.
I–Is that right?
Who'd have thought that Hitomi...
Ah, wow, that Kyousuke guy is pretty smart and knowledgeable!
Sayaka-san, you are a childhood friend of Kamijou-kun, aren't you?
Ah, well, that is... You could call it an undesirable yet inseparable relationship, or... what could you call it...
Is that truly all there is to it?
I have decided. "I won't lie to myself anymore."
What about you?
Sayaka-san, can you face your own true feelings?
W–What are you talking about?
You are my dear good friend.
That's why... I don't want to do anything like advance ahead of you or snatch from you.
Concerning how much time we've had our eyes on Kamijou-kun...
I'm surpassed by you, Sayaka-san.
That's why you have the right to move forward before I do.
Hitomi...
I will confess my love to Kamijou-kun after school tomorrow.
I will only wait a single full day.
Sayaka-san, please decide upon a path that you will not regret.
Whether or not you must convey feelings to Kamijou-kun.
I–I'm...
Madoka...
Is it okay if I come along with you?
I don't want you to be all by yourself, Sayaka-chan. That's why...
You... why?
Why do you show such kindness?
Even when I'm not worth anything like that...
That's...
You know, I... had a regret today.
"At that time, what if I didn't save Hitomi?"
For just an instant, I thought about that.
I'm disqualified as an ally of justice...
I wouldn't be able to face Mami-san.
Hitomi is going to take Kyousuke!
But I can't do anything!
Because... I'm already dead!
I'm a zombie!
I couldn't tell him to do something like hug me with this kind of body.
I couldn't tell him to do something like kiss me...
Thank you. I'm sorry...
Sayaka-chan...
I'm all right now.
That was refreshing.
Come on, let's go.
We have to beat witches tonight, too.
Yeah.
The fact that you're just quietly watching... is unexpected.
Today's enemy isn't a familiar. She's fighting against a witch.
It'll properly drop a Grief Seed, right?
It isn't a useless hunt.
You'd let her have the game for that kind of reason, would you?
Tch, that idiot.
She doesn't know how to handle it.
Sayaka-chan!
Seriously. I couldn't watch that.
It's fine, so pull back now.
'Cause I'll show you how it's done, all right?
Oi!
Don't get in my way.
I'll do it by myself.
Sayaka-chan!
You... No way...
It's true!
If you feel like it, then anything like pain...
can be completely cut off!
Stop... Stop already...
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
I'm going to be a different type of magical girl than all of you.
That's what I decided.
I don't need a reimbursement or anything.
I'm the only one who'll absolutely never use magic for her own benefit.
Episode 8
I'm... Really an Idiot
I'm... really an idiot.