Street Number 7
Lover's escape
If love were a western dish...
Love would be a Napolitan.
It's full of ordinary things,
but each ingredient brings something special.
Love is like a omurice.
One is occupied by the beautiful surface of the egg,
but the chicken rice within must also be appreciated.
Love is like curry.
With time, the flavor develops and deepens.
What a disgusting picture.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
七色の黄昏おりてきて
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
風はなんだか涼しげ
The wind is kinda refreshing
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Saturday night is lively
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
Minna ukiuki
みんなウキウキ
Everyone can't wait
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait.
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
http://FurukawaPan.net
#FurukawaPan@irc.rizon.net
Encoder: Xarda
Edit + QC:
lalala
Xarda
Liasion
Tetsu-nii
Translation: crazybob
Timing: SiegN
Xarda
Typesetting:
[Lover's escape] From Volume 1 Story 5
Blood type fortune: First up today is Type A!
Traveling far may draw you closer to your crush.
Where am I suppose to go on a weekday?
See ya later.
I saw you talking to the TV all morning.
You're going crazy.
Who asked you, baldie.
How can you call your parent "baldie"?!
Also, crab for breakfast? Gimme a break.
Shouldn't you be thrilled to have crab in the morning?
How am I suppose to be happy having crab as a side dish to my bread?
This is real crab bread.
Note: Crab bread = Kanipan, which is apparently a crab shaped cracker.
Hotori?! Why do you look so terrible?
Morning.
You're usually just barely on time. Why are you so early today?
I missed homeroom by a hair yesterday.
Wah! The damn bus stopped at every red light!
I.. I'm gonna be late!
Obviously!
Maybe I should give up.
Arashiyama, don't give up! Run!
Wajima?
Misawa?
Here.
Mori?
Yamato?
Heere.
Wajima?
Here!
Sit down.
Safe.
You're late, Arashiyama.
Go stand in the hallway until homeroom's over.
So unfair!
Wajima made it since her name's at the end.
Your attendance list order is the difference between heaven and hell!
If I were "Warashiyama" I would've been called last and made it.
Wah Wah.
Wah.. wahbit?
Teehee.
You'll be marked absent if you really keep standing there.
So that's why you're early today. Good thinking.
Not really.
I stayed up all night reading this.
Another mystery novel?
Take it.
Hmm. So who's the perp?
The girl named Misuzu.
You can have it back.
It doesn't matter who the perp is - just read it!
It's interesting!
She's like a bad drunk.
Thank you God!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Next stop: Oya Highschool
So cruel!
There's no God or Buddha in this world!
Such a delirious joy...
Having to end this delirious happiness with my own hands
is just too cruel.
Blood type fortune: First up today is Type A!
Type A... Type A...
Traveling far may draw you closer to your crush.
I'm no man if I get off now!
We'll just have a rendezvous with destiny!
Where am I?
The last stop.
Gained two kilos in a day, poko~
No way... First period's started already.
Sorry. I mean,
I.. also fell asleep.
Doesn't the bus keep going around in a loop?
That's what I thought too.
Seems like it doesn't.
The world is full of mysteries.
The return bus comes in about 20 minutes.
Then we can't make it any sooner than the middle of second period.
Nice weather, huh?
Wonder if there's any gym today?
Would be a waste to spend all day in class.
At this rate, we should just skip school.
Just kidding.
Really?
Having ramen after yakiniku sits heavy on the stomach, poko~
Wow! I've never been in this town.
She recovers fast.
I mean... people living in places you normally never see...
It's a strange sort of relieving,
yet somewhat vexing feeling.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
Okay! Sanada, let's go explore!
You look happy.
Huh?
Ah, sorry. I have younger siblings so
I've got a habit of holding hands. Don't want to?
That's not it at all!
I don't mind it even a tiny bit,
but...
not caring whose hand you hold...
isn't so good for a high school girl, I think.
No, it's fine cuz I picked you.
I, Sanada Hiroyuki, have been selected!
I'm truly thankful for all your warm support!
After 5 minutes
After 20 minutes
After 35 minutes
I'm losing my mind!
I must be completely spending the rest of my life's happiness!
Oh! A river!
The Tamagawa!
I wonder if we can get home walking along the river?
If we walk far enough that our legs turn into sticks.
Shoot... we skipped school.
Who cares now.
Can't hurt every now and then.
Yeah. There are important things besides studying, right?
Ahh, but what am I gonna do if I get called down to the office tomorrow?
We're both guilty. If you get called down,
I'll be going down with you.
Yeah.
Wonder how many years it's been since we've played together.
We played a lot when we were little.
I wonder why did we stopped hanging out...
Huh?! You don't remember?!
You...
Why would I play with a girl? Moron!
Let's go.
... is what you said!
I might've said it.
I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
I thought you were going to say that some day.
I'm home.
I better not forget how I felt today.
Let's start a journal.
Umm, today... today...
Today I skipped school with Arashiyama and hung out.
Huh? Was that all?
Guess I should read this novel to improve my writing skills.
Even though I know the perp already.
Book title: "1/4th Murderous Intent"
If love were a drink...
Love would be a delicious coffee.
The bitter flavor gives a the sleepless night
in exchange for dependence and peace of mind.
Arashiyama - cold one.
Huh?
But if there's a mistake, it becomes a misunderstanding.
What the heck? Who's a cold one?
Did you forget the name of your childhood friend?!
Huh?
Calm down! Arashiyama, "cold one" is...
What?! Who's a cold one?
Sanada, you use pretty old words don't you.
Wha?
Get out!!
I also used to be a bit bad, poko~
[Night Walker] From Volume 2 Story 16
I can't sleep.
It must be because of that.
A little early, but let's pee and go to sleep.
It's out!
Not screaming when you're scared so you don't disturb others...
Very impressive.
Oh it's Takeru.
What are you doing at this hour?
You're a kid - go to sleep at 9 and wake up at 6.
But I can't sleep.
If I could fall asleep I would not have come to a room like yours.
What do you mean like mine?!
It's sorta your fault.
4 hours ago
Hey, have a bottle about this big?
I'm building something.
Here!
An energy drink for when you're tired! Napotamin C!
But I need an empty bottle...
It had a really strong taste, but I didn't want to waste it so I drank it all.
And now I can't sleep at all.
Half a bottle keeps me up, but you drunk it all.
But thanks to that, my castle is complete!
Guess I gotta do something.
Want to burn off that extra energy and go for a 30 minute walk?
Is it okay?! It's not, isn't it? It's not!
You're ridiculously happy looking.
Well, it's late night to a kid,
but the evening's just started for me.
I'll lend you a hand, poko~
Why are we leaving through the back door?
The front door makes a racket. Mom would find out.
What's with the bag?
Travel preparations.
The enemies at night are strong.
What are you talking about? A game?
We're in a ordinary peaceful town.
Huh? Seaside is still lit. Is it still open?
Hold up, don't get too close at night.
Look.
It's becomes a hangout for delinquent middle aged men.
Try not to be like that when you grow up.
But... it looks fun.
I'm going to be a defense attorney when I grow up and defend you.
Mom said...
That's enough!
Carbonation comes from carbon dioxide, poko~
Whoa. The shopping district is completely closed!
Alright, where should we go?
Huh, he's still awake.
Guess I'll call him down to be my bodyguard.
Crap. Forgot my cell phone.
Sis.
What?
Oh! You got something useful?
It's full of junk.
SS.
"S. S."?
Here.
What do you want me to do with this?
That's not it?
There's nothing else that counts as SS...
Augh. I'll get it out myself.
SS is an abbreviation for slingshot!
Like I'd know! Just call it a slingshot, you idiot.
But I only have two DD left for this season.
"DD"? Acorn Bullets?
Note: DD -> Donguri Dan -> Acorn Bullet
I figured it out this time.
Elementary school kids are retards.
It missed!
My precious acorn...
You mean "DD"?
Huh?
You'll break it if you pull that hard!
Who's been talking outside...
Who are you, you bastard?!
I'll fucking kill you!
Crap. My ally is now my enemy.
I think he'll forgive you if you apologize.
I really doubt he'd listen to me.
I mean, Sanada probably likes...
Eh, whatever.
What?
Nah, it's nothing.
I'll apologize to him in a year.
Takeru, are you hungry?
Hmm. Now that you mention it, I might be.
In front of the train station... er, that might be a little too bad to show him.
There's a ramen stand in front of the station.
Really? We can do that at night?
It's that happy look again.
I'm sleepy and my eyes are rolling, poko~
Now that I'm here, I wonder if I'll get fat...
Should be fine if I just have half.
Oh, it's Hotori.
What are you doing at this hour?
Are you talking nonsense?!
Are you, man?
Shhh!
I didn't say anything! Nothing!
I said I'm going to boil some bamboo tips at this hour.
Here.
"I'm boiling some bamboo tips"
"What are you doing, Hotori?"
Isn't that pushing it?!
Just my imagination, huh. Good. Thought I had to discipline some kids there.
Why is the cop eating ramen here?
I'm gonna pull a Naruto move on him and chase him away!
You won't be caught until the day I arrest you!
Any reactions?
Am I suppose to be Lupin?
Sis looks mortified.
I don't hear anything. Looks like she's not here.
I feel like I really have to catch you one day.
Head poko~, poko~!
Takeru, guess you'll have to be my attorney after all.
Guess we'll have to turn to
the always open, machine-like convenience store.
It's a favorite hangout for kids.
It's completely dark outside the store!
Surprised by another ordinary thing.
Though it's true you've never been out after eating dinner.
Yamamura will be announcing midnight.
Takeru.
It's now just past 0 AM, May 1st.
Night Head Radio.
Your DJ is now handing it off to your amigo Kirihara.
"0 o'clock".. Zero o'clock?
Yup, that's right.
0 o'clock? 0 o'clock?!
Zero is nothing, yet there's a zero o'clock.
I'm scared.
It was April 30th just a moment ago, but
now it's May 1st.
You've crossed the border between yesterday and today.
Whaa?
Tomorrow's turned into today?
And today's turned into yesterday?
Yup.
You've just witnessed the world at work.
I wonder when I first saw this happen.
Wish I remembered.
They'll find out if you don't put your shoes back at the entrance.
Oh, right.
It was colder outside than I thought.
Let's take a bath to warm up before bed.
Cover it with a towel...
Feeling sleepy?
Probably.
Sis.
Yea?
You go out at night sometimes, don't you?
Eh? Why?
You're too good at not getting caught.
Today wasn't the first time, right?
You're probably better off as a prosecutor than a defense attorney.
Uh, I know who did it, poko~
But... poko~
If love were a snack...
Ha! I've just thought of a trick for a perfect crime.
Love is like a banana.
It provides a source of nourishment and a sense of closeness everyday.
If you kill the victim with a frozen banana...
And then eat the banana after...
Yes. The only thing left would be the banana skin. The murder weapon can't be found.
You simply saw the victim slip on the banana.
It becomes your camouflage! Not even the police will know.
I wouldn't want to eat a banana that was used to murder.
Ah! I wouldn't want to either!
Wah!
Hi,
1,
ひ、
Fu,
2,
ふ、
Hi, fu, mi, yo
1, 2, 3, 4
ひ、ふ、み、よ
Taikutsu ya
Living alone is boring,
退屈や
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
My pufferfish cheeks
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
Pulls the town into chaos.
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
I didn't confess to him today.
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
I play the drums to train
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
My body for ping pong.
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
But this band isn't a fake!
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
The members aren't playing rock!
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
We're not trying to lead the song!
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
We're not looking for Nirvana!
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
We're maids! Yea!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
メイド姿で参上！参上！
acho-!
アチョー！
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
They're maids! Yea!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
acha~
アチャ～
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
kanchoooO!
enemaaA!
かんちょぉぉお！
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
The time is the 21th century.
Suddenly,
convenient machines like washers and dryers were invented.
Even forgetting to dry your clothing after washing,
they don't end up smelling like washcloths.
It's like something from the world of dreams.
But! However!
There is no machine to fold the laundry and put it into the drawers!
We're still far from calling this
true automation.
Next time, Street number 8, "Automatic Band."
Street Number 8 [Automatic Band]
We'll be nihilistic all over, poko~