I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a twist of fate changed everything.
I was handed a red gem,
and with it I was given magical powers.
My unexpected encounter has set two things in motion.
My intertwined feelings,
and the beginning of this story.
This was when magic would first
begin to change my ordinary life.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha will now begin!
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
hiza wo kakaete heya no katasumi
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
itsumo fuan de furuete ita
I trembled with anxiety
hontou wo shiru koto ga kowakute
Afraid of knowing the truth,
tobira wo tojita
I shut the door to it
yasashii uso ni ibasho wo mitsukete
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
yume no naka ni nigekonda
and found shelter in my dreams
daremo shiranai kodoku no umi wo
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
fukai ao ni someteku
that was dyed a deep blue
sabishisa kakusu
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
ichizu na omoi kimi no kokoro wo kizutsukete iru
I ended up hurting your heart
hitomi no oku no himitsu suikomaresou na
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
egao no ura no shinjitsu ni
and the truth behind my smile,
yawarakana ai boku ga todoke ni yuku yo
I will deliver my gentle love to you
furetara kowaresou na nukumori ga ima
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
kako wo hanare afuredasu
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
zutto soba ni iru kara
Let us always walk together,
kanashii kage ni madowanaide
free from the shadows of loneliness
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
No way!
Wh-What's with all this!?
Episode 2
My Magical Incantation Is "Lyrical"?
Wh-What is this?
It's coming!
Protection.
Our magical devices are programmed
to help our magic take form.
And in order to make that system work,
its user needs to provide mana.
And that thing was born from an abominable power taking form to protect itself.
To stop it, you need to seal it with your
staff and return it to its original form.
I don't really get it.
What should I do?
Basic maneuvers, such as attacking and defending,
will happen just by wishing for them, like you did earlier.
But in order to use enough power to
fully stop it, you need an incantation.
Incantation?
Listen to your heart.
Your own incantation should come to mind within your heart.
Protection.
Lyrical Magical.
If you seal it correctly,
it should revert to a Jewel Seed!
Jewel Seed, seal!
Sealing Mode, Set up.
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical Magical. Jewel Seed Serial XXI!
Seal!
Sealing.
That's a Jewel Seed.
Touch Raising Heart to it.
Receipt No. XXI.
Huh? It's over?
Yes, all thanks to you.
Thank you...
Hold on! Are you all right? Hey!
I-I might get in trouble if I'm seen here...
F-For now, I-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Ah, did I wake you up?
Sorry for being so rough.
How are your injuries?
I'm fine now. I've pretty much recovered.
You're right. Most of your wounds
have vanished. That's amazing.
Thanks to you,
I was able to use the rest of my magic to heal myself.
I don't really get it, but... I see.
Hey, let's introduce
ourselves properly now.
Ah, sure.
I'm Takamachi Nanoha.
I'm a third-grader.
My close friends and
family call me Nanoha.
I'm Yuuno Scrya.
Scrya is the name of my clan,
and I'm called Yuuno.
Yuuno-kun, huh?
What a cute name.
I'm sorry... um...
You can call me Nanoha.
Nanoha-san, I'm sorry
I got you involved in this...
Ah, um...
Um... I think I'm okay with this.
Ah, I forgot. Yuuno-kun, you're still a little
hurt, so you shouldn't rest here.
For now, let's go back to my house.
We can sort out everything
else afterwards, okay?
Welcome home.
O-Onii-chan...
And just where have you been at this time of night?
Um... that is... uh... uh...
Oh, how cute!
O-Onee-chan?
Oh, he looks pretty tired.
Let me guess, you were worried
and went to check on him, right?
Um... uh, that is...
I understand how you feel...
but I still can't believe you snuck out of the house like that.
Come on, it's all right.
She came home safe.
And Nanoha's a good girl,
so she won't do it again. Right?
Yeah...
Um, Onii-chan... I'm sorry for
sneaking out and making you worry.
Okay, that settles everything!
But man, he sure is cute, huh?
I bet Mom will faint from cuteness
overload when she sees him.
I won't deny that possibility.
Good morning, Yuuno-kun!
Ah... um, good morning.
Well, for now, I'm glad you made
it out of last night in one piece.
L-Likewise.
Last night, when I showed Yuuno-kun to Mom and Dad...
Ah! He's so cute!
He really is adorable, isn't it?
Mom! Please take it easy...
He's so cuuuute!
Looks pretty smart for a weasel.
He's a ferret, Dad.
I wonder if he can do any tricks?
Here, shake.
He sure is a smart little thing, huh?
And so, the family was in a frenzy.
After that, we talked about what
to do for feeding Yuuno-kun,
and the whole fuss
over him started again.
In the end, the two of us didn't really get to talk much last night.
Are you used to calling me by my first name yet?
Yeah, Nanoha.
We only managed to get used to
calling each other by our first names,
and to start speaking casually.
Okay, I need to go to school now,
so let's talk when I get home.
Oh, that's not a problem.
Even if we're apart,
we can still talk to each other.
Nanoha, you're a mage now.
Oh, this is like when you first called out to me...
That's right. We can talk as long as
you have Raising Heart with you,
so try talking to me from your heart.
Um...
Like this?
That's right. Isn't it easy?
Y-You're right!
I'll explain more to you later.
Like about me, magic, and the Jewel Seeds.
Okay.
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha
Lyrical Nanoha!
Good morning!
Nanoha! Did you hear about
what happened last night?
Huh? Last night?
At the vet we went to yesterday,
apparently there was a car accident or something,
and they said the wall was destroyed.
We've been worried about the ferret...
Yeah...
Um, you see...
About that, you see...
I see!
So he's safe at your house, Nanoha!
But that's an incredible
coincidence, isn't it?
To run into him on the street when
he was escaping from the accident...
Really!
It's not a lie! It's not a lie!
I just fudged the truth a little!
And it looks like my family doesn't
mind having a pet ferret,
so we're going to be taking care
of him at my house for now.
I see!
Now we just have to come up with a name for him.
Have you decided on one yet?
Yeah. His name is Yuuno-kun.
Yuuno-kun?
Yep. Yuuno-kun.
As I told you before, kanji are formed
by using "hen" and "tsukuri" radicals.
By combining these radicals,
each kanji can hold many different meanings, even though it's only one character.
This is because each "hen" radical has its own meaning,
and each of the "tsukuri" radicals have their own meaning.
For example, to write the word "person,"
you only have to use the "ninben" radical.
To write the word "water,"
you use the "sanzui" radical.
And when writing "wood,"
you use the "kihen" radical.
Now then, let's have a short quiz on this.
Using these three "hen" radicals,
what other words can you think of by combining them with a "tsukuri" radical?
The Jewel Seeds are ancient
artifacts from my world.
Originally, they were magical stones
capable of granting their user's wishes.
But sometimes their power is unstable,
like what happened last night.
They'll turn on the user and devour everything in the area.
In some cases, a seed
will sense and manifest
the subconscious desires of people
or animals, and go out of control.
So why was something so
dangerous in my neighborhood?
It's my fault...
On my home world, I'm an archaeologist.
And one day, I discovered something
in an old rock formation.
I sent a team of investigators to excavate
it and put it into safekeeping.
But the transport ship had
some sort of accident, or worse...
Twenty-one Jewel Seeds were scattered
across this world because of that.
And I've only managed to find two so far.
So there are nineteen left, huh?
Stand.
By the way, don't you think the balsam has grown a bit?
I wonder how many centimeters tall it is now.
Maybe... two?
No way! It's definitely three!
Huh? But wait a second...
From what you've told me so far,
it's not really your fault the Jewel Seeds got scattered here, right?
But I was the one who first found them...
So I have to find them all,
and return them to where they belong.
Somehow... somehow,
I know how you feel.
You sure are a diligent person, aren't you, Yuuno-kun?
Oh, that reminds me.
Did everyone put up a sign saying
your plant is under observation?
It would be quite the problem if someone thought they were weeds
and got rid of them.
And please don't forget to write down your name, date, and how much it's grown.
Um...
I'm sorry for getting you involved last
night and making you help me like that.
I'd like to stay in your
care for a while longer,
so I can rest and
recover my mana.
Just a week...
no, just five days,
until my mana returns,
if that's okay...
When your power returns,
what will you do?
I'll leave to search for the rest of
the Jewel Seeds alone again.
I won't allow that.
Y-You won't allow that?
I won't be able to help
you during school hours,
but I can help you out any other time.
But it'll be dangerous, like last night.
Well, we already know each other,
and I've heard your story.
I can't just leave you alone now.
And if things are going to keep happening in the neighborhood like last night,
it'll be a problem for everyone, right?
Yuuno-kun, you don't have anyone to help you out if you're alone, right?
It's sad to be all alone.
Let me help you out.
"If someone's in need, and you
have the power to help them,
you should never hesitate to help them."
At least, that's what my dad taught me.
You seem pretty troubled,
and I can help you, right?
With my magical power...
Yeah...
Though I don't know if I can become a proper mage...
Bye bye!
You're already a mage, Nanoha.
I'm sure you have an incredible amount of talent, more than I do.
R-Really? I don't really understand...
but for now, can you teach me what you know?
Bye bye.
And I'll do my best, so...
Yeah. Thank you.
Now then, I'll be back
home any minute now.
How about we eat
some snacks together?
Ah, sure.
Thank you.
I wonder what kind of snacks we should have today?
Sorry!
Yuuno-kun, what was that just now?
Another Jewel Seed has been activated.
It's close!
What should we do?!
Let's do it together.
Help me!
Yeah!
Nanoha, use Raising Heart!
Ah, okay!
It's possessed an animal
that was in the area.
Wh-What should I do?
It's a lot stronger when it has a stable form like this!
It'll be fine... probably!
Nanoha!
Activate Raising Heart!
Ah! How do I activate it again?
Start from "I, who have accepted this mission..."
That's the activation password!
I can't remember something so long!
I'll tell it to you again,
so just repeat after me!
O-Okay!
Raising... Heart...
Stand by, ready.
Set up.
She activated Raising Heart
without even saying the password!
Nanoha! Your protective clothes!
Barrier jacket.
Nanoha!
Protect Condition: All green.
She didn't take any damage from the impact...
I knew it, this girl has an
incredible amount of talent.
Ow... but it didn't really hurt as much as I thought it would.
Um... all I have to do now is seal it, right?
Raising Heart, please!
All right.
Sealing Mode.
Set up.
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical Magical. Jewel Seed Serial XVI!
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt No. XVI.
Did that do it?
Yeah.
There's not much else to do now.
Huh?
Did I trip and hit my head?
Good job... I guess?
Yeah. I'd say so.
My first day as a mage had finally ended.
I made a new friend, Yuuno-kun.
I don't know much about him, magic,
or the dangers that will be coming.
Anyway, a whole lot has happened...
Well, I'm hungry after all of that.
I guess for now, I just have to keep doing my best!
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
koron dari mayottari suru keredo
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
anata ga ite kureru kara
as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
ah serofan no umi wo koe
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
mori wo koe
weaving through the forests,
gin no kaze wo nukete
and passing through the silver wind,
tarinai mono sagashiteta
I was looking for something neither of us had
ah jiorama no machi de tada
Ah, within a diorama of the city
naiteta no
I was just crying alone
ano hi sashidasareta
until the day your warm hand
atatakai te ni au made
reached out to me
yureru tsukihi no naka de
I felt your strong gaze
manazashi wo kanjiteta wa
during those swaying days,
nee himitsu no kagi wo
and then, at long last
yatto yatto mitsuketa no
I finally found the secret key
make a little wish
Make a little wish!
remon iro no tsuki no shizuku atsumete
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
anata no yuku sonomichi wo
and shine their light
yasashiku terashiteitai
down upon on your path
make a little wish chiisaku temo
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
dekiru koto ga nai kara
If you say you can't do anything,
anata ga ite kureru kara
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
watashi wa egao de imasu genki desu
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
Somehow, I've
become a mage.
I've had to do this and
that as a magical girl...
but I'm really excited about it!
I'm still Takamachi Nanoha, but...
there are a mountain of problems!
Next up is an incident so big it involves the entire city!
This is looking really bad!
Next time on
Mahou Shoujo Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 3
The City's in a Lot of Danger?
Episode Three:
Lyrical Magical, doing my best!