Are you prepared, my dear girls?
Prepare to advance!
Forward!
Advancing!
Where is our allies?
Left, forty degrees!
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Distance: 400.
Load the H.E.A.T. round!
Roger.
Origa!
Leave it to me.
After being canned in this thing for three days, I'm not dying until I have a shower!
Target locked!
Fire!
Direct hit!
Anna, signal the troops trailing us.
One vehicle destroyed. Continue advancing.
Roger!
Filicia, cover Anna please.
R-Roger.
It's flashing out there, but it's not thunder. Just relax.
I know!
Th-Three o'clock!
No way...
Second Lieutenant Anna!
Paper!
Bamboo strips!
Come on, Noel!
It won't be clean if you don't wash it properly!
It's so hot!
While it gets cold in the winter, it's great that this building stays cool in the summer.
Oh? Isn't it the Rio-senpais' turn to do the laundry today?
They're busy and asked us to swap.
Whose is that?
Filicia-san's.
She said she lost her appetite and told us to eat it.
I'll have it then.
What's that?
Preparations for dinner?
Or...
What are you doing?
It's a sin to play with food!
I-I'm not playing!
Well, it's almost time for Obon, right?
Huh? What's Obon?
Fiesta des Lumières.
Fi?
Fiesta des Lumières is an event unique to the southern part of Helvetia.
According to folk belief, the souls of the dead would return to the world of the living during the summer.
Paper lanterns are floated down the river as a symbol to send the spirits back.
In some provinces, the festival is called Obon.
Right. Thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
Oh? It's the same thing then!
Souls returning?
Wait, wait! What does that mean? Does that mean ghosts come back?!
In a sense, yes.
Paper lanterns?
That sounds lovely, in a way.
We build bonfires back in my village, but-
No way! People who have died go to heaven, and stay there forever.
Only the evil spirits remain loitering on earth!
What? That's not true!
But in Church...
We're back!
Hey! Come and help out!
When did you two go shopping?
Oh, those are...
They looked good, so we bought them.
And these too.
Is this fine?
No, Pastor.
Like this!
I'm done!
Your dad and mom?
I see... it looks good.
What? Even the Church acknowledges it?
That Fi-whatever?
Yeah.
If it was the Central Protestant Church, they would kick up a fuss,
but we're in a rural area here.
What a random answer...
In my village, we would make horses and cows out of cucumbers and eggplants
as vehicles for our ancestors to ride on.
And to amuse our ancestors who had returned, we would all dance.
Are you both making them too, senpai?
Yeah.
We only watched last year but...
It's part of our job to attempt harmonious relations with the local residents after all.
If you don't get too fixated on it, it's just another lovely festival.
Right, Filicia?
Filicia-san!
Are you all right?
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I just made a blunder.
But it's rare for Commander to be so clumsy.
Unlike Kanata.
Well, these last few days have been really hot, right...
「Water Melon」
I haven't been able to sleep well.
I'll take a short break.
Filicia-san...
The Commander seems a bit strange.
She skipped her lunch, and then goes off to buy watermelons, ignoring our food budget?
There must be reasons... even for her.
Still, I think I'll talk to her...
Stop that!
Everyone has things that they would rather not share.
Just leave her alone.
Noel?
Do you know about it, Rio?
I've seen the records.
I had a first hand account of the incident.
So...
Filicia...
Hold it steady. That's it.
There, there, it's fine.
And then... a ghost that looked like the Commander appeared...
There were many creatures things in this ocean long ago...
That's unbelievable, huh?
Have you ever heard that...
They say the world is gradually ending...
and eventually, all humanity will perish completely.
Those are just... rumors.
But if it's true, then what are we fighting for?
Am I...
Still alive?
Ideographs?
I'm sorry.
I really wish I could read your final words.
This equipment...
Could you be from the old era?
Commander...
Second Lieutenant Origa...
Martina...
Anna-san...
Why...
...am I the only one?
...are you crying?
I see.
There are still survivors in this world.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because...
...we lost...
...to them.
We couldn't protect you.
I'm truly sorry.
The world has ended.
No way...
You are the remnants...
The final remaining bubbles on the salvation of humanity.
Mankind...
For this world to regain it's former glory... is impossible.
Don't decide that on your own!
But that is the truth.
So, it's fine to let it end.
To live miserably in the dregs of the world, in despair... is simply too desolate.
No. I don't want this.
Why?
Is there meaning to surviving in a world like this?
That is...
Save me...
I am here! I am alive!
Please! Please save me!
You are...
I'm sorry.
If my unit had only arrived half a day sooner,
this would never have happened.
Your Highness, Imperial Princess Iria.
But I was a little surprised.
About what?
Well, you ignored the Fiesta des Lumières last year, Rio.
What caused this change?
That's...
That's a nice color, isn't it?
It's made in Treize. I bought them when the market was here.
Amazing! It's fantastic. Just fabulous!
Aren't they?
Yes!
Certainly...
She meant everything to me.
I thought of protecting the country, the people, like she did.
But at times, I think...
What meaning is there in that?
So if she really does come back...
I want her to tell me.
That aside, what about you...
They're all worried about you.
That's true. Admittedly, I may have worried them a little.
I fail as a Commander, huh.
It's not just them!
Even I... um...
Um?
Anyway, don't bear the burden on your own!
Even I can at least listen to you!
Thank you, Rio.
Then I'll accept your offer and speak.
What is it?
Actually...
I'm troubled that I've gained weight this summer!
What?
At this rate, I won't fit into my winter wear.
I heard that if you eat only watermelon, you can lose weight,
so I thought of trying that.
What's the matter, Rio?
Are you still feigning ignorance?
Huh?
That's because on the front lines at the battle at Area 21, you were-
Ahh!
Could you possibly be thinking that I was reminiscing about that?
Y-You're saying, you weren't?
It's so pretty.
Should we go too?
You made one too, right, Kureha?
I-It's not like I believe in souls or anything...
It's a mission. A mission.
Um...
Who are you sending off, Filicia-san?
My previous colleagues,
and a soldier whose name I don't know.
My saviors who helped me realize what is truly important.
Could those the people possibly be...
Filicia-san...
If you have any sorrows, I...
...I might not be able to help at all...
But!
It seems like I made you worry.
I'm sorry.
But, I'm fine.
That is too sad...
Even I want to worry about you!
Filicia-san, you always worry about me...
I always made you worry.
I want to worry about you, too!
Because I love you, Filicia-san!
I adore you too, Kana-chan.
Just remain the way you are.
Please.
Filicia-san...
You're always reminding me...
...not to fear putting feelings into words.
I think that is a wonderful thing.
Commander...
Filicia...
Even I...
Oh, you guys...
How adorable...
Do come again next year, ancestors.
Dad... Mom...
Mother... Elder Sister...
That person is...
Say, Rio, you were just asking if there was any meaning in this world, right?
Yeah.
Ever since I was the lone survivor, I had pondered on that a lot.
Why only I survived?
Listen up. You can't just space out like that.
And if there was a meaning to it.
And then I realized it.
It's likely that there isn't any meaning to this world.
But isn't that lovely as well?
Because, if there isn't any, then we can find them on our own accord.
And now, I've found mine.
The meaning for me being here...
And then even the Pastor too...
Even the Pastor?
He just did it his way? And Yumina-neechan.
Well, he was really bad at it, so Sister Yumina...
I definitely do not want them to suffer those emotions as I did.
That's true...
Next time: Phone Duty. Announcement of an Emergency Situation.