Hishigata Clinic
Welcome to the sandy beach of the sacred lily.
From the depths of the ocean,
the one reflected in the eyes of the lost whale
is none other than Hiruko.
I'm sorry, Hizuru.
I said I wanted to meet yer friends.
And yet, when they came, I...
There's no need to do anything ya don't wanna do.
I realize now I'm fine with just ya, Hizuru.
Yer different from other people.
Me? Different?
Everyone who sees me runs away in fear.
But ya didn't. Ya ran after me.
It's the clinic's second story.
So you could get up there normally 14 years ago.
People are talking about the ghost of the old clinic.
And because of that, I was forbidden from meeting ya like this.
By whom?
By Shide!
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Who is Shide?
It's supposed to be a secret, but I'll tell ya a little, Hizuru.
Shide is greed incarnate.
That's why they've got four arms!
Four arms?
Shide
Shide.
Four arms
As in "four arms."
Paper streamer
Or "paper streamer."
That must be the four-armed Shadow!
Oh, right. I brought ya something.
Here.
Yes, yes!
Thanks, Hizuru.
I've always wondered what these tasted like.
Okay, I'll play the mommy.
Then I'll play the eldest daughter.
We jumped to another day, huh?
Shinpei, is she really the Haine we know?
I dunno, but let's see this through until the memory ends.
What's wrong, Hizuru?
My finger got cut a little.
Are ya okay? Show me.
Hey...
Haine?
That tickles.
I hate being hungry.
I hate it.
Ya been looking pale lately.
Maybe ya should eat something other than my snacks?
Haine?
Many starved to death.
The adults didn't come back with no fish...
Come summer, Mother, Father,
my brothers—
They all died.
Hizuru.
My shadow.
Touch my shadow too.
Please.
Yer hand's so warm.
Ya can feel it through yer shadow?
Yeah.
I'll bring more food next time.
Thanks, Hizuru.
Please stay my friend forever.
It must be summer now.
Hey.
Are ya the Minakata girl?
What are ya doing out here in the wilderness?
Walking.
I can see that.
Beware of snakes!
I'm saying it's dangerous.
There's snakes in these parts.
Then why is it fine for you to be here?
It ain't.
It's still dangerous, but that's what I get paid for.
Yer interferin' with my work!
Pick a proper path for your little walk.
What? Snacks?
Yup. She came by earlier to buy lots of 'em.
Yer having a party today, right?
Yes, but she said she was going to Koba Mart and never came back.
Huh? She told me she was gonna eat with a friend.
Was she not talking about y'all, Asako?
Huh?
Is that true, Koba?
Mt. Takanosu!
Sis!
I wonder if she remembered to bring drinks.
I hope she's not collapsed somewhere.
She'd even forget to breathe if something were fascinating enough.
What the... Is someone there?
A red kimono?
Who's she?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Could this be the day?
Wait, is this the friend she was talking about?
Hey.
No... Ryuunosuke...
Don't do it.
Ya okay?
Are ya feeling sick?
Miss Nagumo!
Is someone there?
Huh? Did she hear me?
Just the wind, maybe?
"Miss Nagumo"?
Crap, she can't hear me anymore.
What was that light?
Ryuunosuke...
Why, Haine?
Did ya do this?
Hizuru?
No...
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me...
It wasn't me!
An eye?!
Haine's right eye!
Do ya think that was...
It hurts... It hurts...
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts!
Ryuunosuke!
Why?!
Why, damn it?!
Haine!
Strays!
Hooat? Hooat?
Enehme...
Go gewwum.
The hunter.
What the hell is this?
It's dangerous! Stay away!
M-Me?
It can't be...
Sis...
No way!
Who the hell are ya?
Impossible.
Are they immortal?
So this is where ya were.
I looked all over.
Hey!
I brought drinks for ya.
It's our birthday today, Sis.
He's inside of Hizuru!
She has the physical abilities of a Shadow!
Ryuunosuke's data bounced off of Haine and entered Hizuru!
So Ryuunosuke is controlling her right now?
What was that?
I'm sorry, Sis.
I think I dislocated yer shoulder.
H-Hey!
Ya okay?!
Stay with me!
Hey.
Hey!
Hizuru
Asako
We were friends, so I'll let it go this one time.
The next time we meet,
I'll kill ya.
Ow!
You just came back, didn't you?
This is just before we reached Koba Mart!
D-Don't do it, Miss Nagumo.
Don't go after them.
My house?
Ushio decapitated Shinpei and activated the loop.
What time is it, Papa?
It's just about 6 PM.
Last time was before the funeral,
and things picked up before collecting the bones.
The starting point is getting later?
Perhaps the reason for the shifting starting point is that Shinpei's power is waning.
Yes.
The range of time he can observe shrinks each time he dies.
This is a great discovery.
In that case, let's give him what he wants and make him loop over and over.
Until his limit's broken.
Are you saying that by killing Shinpei and making him loop over and over and over,
he'll eventually experience true death?
That's right.
We'll shave off his life little by little.
It'll be easier than trying to capture him alive.
Don't ya think, Shide?
Indeed.
Asako.
Seconds, please.
Summer Time Rendering
One hour later
Are ya hungry?
Ya can have this.
You are a strange boy, cooking at a time like this.
That day, Ryuunosuke's mind entered yer body, didn't it?
I was overcome with shock, but eventually I acclimated.
Ryuunosuke is strong like Ushio.
I couldn't count how many times I've been saved thanks to y'all.
I'd rather be the one doing the fighting, if possible.
I'd honestly rather not call Ryuunosuke here.
Ya must love yer brother a whole lot.
How do you come to that conclusion?
I love my little sister too, so I can sorta tell.
Ya don't want him to fight the fearsome Shadow that killed him.
You've stepped a bit too far back in your analysis, boy.
Have I?
I'm merely thinking of myself.
If he went all out, my body would be ripped apart.
That first time, I came away with a dislocated shoulder, a sprained ankle,
and was bedridden from the muscle pains for about four to five days.
That's not something one can bear constantly.
Oh, do ya not like spicy food?
No, I love it.
This reminds me of a dish I had at Kofune long ago.
In past loops, Mio's Shadow came to Kofune on the evening of the 22nd.
It'll most likely come this time as well.
It basically ignores Mio.
She moves on orders from above that supersedes a Shadow's instinct to kill its original.
In other words, Haine's orders.
And we're going to use that against them.
Indeed.
But do ya think Haine will know where I am with this brand?
We'll find out soon.
If our enemy is looping as well,
we cannot afford to let the first strike slip away.
If Ushio can impart her memories onto others,
everyone else can pseudo-experience the loops as well.
And with them, we could deliver the first strike with maximum firepower.
I'm sorry I called ya a monster.
Ya were fightin' so hard, and yet I...
Oh, y'mean that thing at the summer festival?
Forget about it!
I'm basically a monster, anyway.
Don't let it bother ya—
I thought I'd never see ya again!
Mio, ya don't hafta cry so much...
I'll fight too, Sis.
I don't wanna just sit here and let you and Shin keep protecting me.
Mio, we brought ya here to keep ya safe, not—
Shin.
I hate not bein' able to fight back.
Alan's not picking up.
He's normally already home by this time.
Shinpei?
Ya okay?
Y-Yeah...
Just a little nervous.
Are we really doing this?
This plan requires a leader.
Everyone's waiting for you to speak.
I don't think I can be the leader.
You should take charge.
Yer the only one who can do this, Shinpei!
Without yer power, we couldn't have gathered everyone here.
Th-Then, um, er...
For a long time, I've had this habit of stepping back from reality.
It was like another me would float high above,
watching me and considering my situation.
It allowed me to see a lot.
My surroundings, my own position.
I'd never fail.
Or even if I did, it didn't register.
But when Ushio died, I was filled with regrets.
Thinking, "Why didn't I call her at least once?"
"I should've come back for New Year's."
The last time we met, she asked for curry.
I should've made it for her.
I thought I was being objective, but I wasn't.
My whole life's been one mistake after another.
It hurts regretting things it's too late to do anything about.
I know swearing I'll do my best to live without regrets is probably impossible.
But I don't want to feel like that ever again.
So if I ever get the slightest sense that I'm about to regret something, I'll avoid it.
I've decided I'll run away at top speed.
Yer runnin' away?!
But that means I don't really get the option of doing nothing.
Even if it's something I don't want to do, or it's something I'll regret not doing,
maybe I should just do it.
That's... Yeah, that's the gist of it.
Basically, uh...
Like even if I screw up at the end and end up dying,
I want to feel like I used every last second of my life to the fullest.
I'm sure y'all saw this, but before she passed,
Ushio fought the Shadows in secret.
She tried to save Shiori and lost her life.
This is Ushio we're talking about,
so she probably felt bitter.
A whole lot, I'm betting.
I'm going to inherit her will.
I won't let the end of that summer festival come to pass again.
"With all of us here, I believe we stand a chance."
I cannot say that for sure.
Ya can't?!
There's no guarantee we'll all survive.
I can't even tell if we can win.
But I also can't tell ya to run if yer feeling scared.
This is all so I won't have any regrets.
It's my selfishness.
I don't want to think later, "I should've forced everyone to come along."
So I'm strong-arming ya now.
Take up arms and fight with me, please.
So where and how will ya appear?
Huh, just a snake.
A-Are ya crazy?!
Ya want us to die for ya?!
I ain't yer damn pawn!
Shinpei loves this island.
He loves all of y'all.
Sure his wording's horrible.
But Shinpei's on yer side.
And what's wrong with siding with the people ya love?
Count me in!
M-Mio?!
Me too, Shinpei.
I'm on yer side for life.
That fact will never change.
Do any of y'all know exactly how many Shadows there are on the island presently?
Right now, we have no chance of winning.
Especially if Haine is looping as well.
What yer attempting is group suicide, Shinpei.
Tokiko!
Yeah, yeah! Tell 'em!
But...
Since I've apparently already died,
I'll entrust my life with ya, Shinpei.
Wha—
Our only option is to exterminate them.
D-Damn it! It can't...
Damn it!
Fine!
Let's do this thing!
A man's gotta do what a man's gotta do!
Damn it all!
Thanks, guys.
Huh?
I'm home?
I went back...
Did I loop?
I... died?!
When?
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Lights, Camera, Action