Are you sure we're actually popular?
And I thought our merch was pretty cute...
Maybe it's because of your weird naming sense.
You think?
Toge-Toge rubber bands!
Who wants to buy some Toge-Toge towels?
I think we're doing better than in our Shin-Kawasaki days at least...
You sure about that?
It's fine, we have some merch that's selling like hotcakes right over there.
Here we go.
Hug!
I'm never getting into a bath again in my life!
You really should. Preferably head first!
I see...
I'll pass on those.
Excuse me.
I thought we might be of interest to you.
SHIOMI MIURA
"Golden Archer"?
- Indeed.
- I think I've heard that name somewhere...
It's a talent agency!
Indeed!
WANDERVOGEL
So basically, you're scouting us?
Yes, that is my intent.
I see.
Of course, you are welcome to look us up online in case you have any doubts.
- Do you know them?
- Yeah, they're pretty well-known.
A few people from my school said they'd love to work with them specifically.
They even have several bands under them.
But talent agencies are...
To be honest,
I'm a big fan of Diamond Dust!
But not the way they are now.
They lost that spark that made them special.
In other words, I'm a big fan of yours in particular!
I want you to be able to make the kind of music you always did!
And I think this band can do it!
I know, right!
Sit down, will you?
Got it.
The first time Diamond Dust was contacted by an agency,
we were immediately told that we'll have to change our style,
since it doesn't fit the times.
I see.
And frankly, I don't think they were wrong.
It's a fact that most of the fans accepted them as they are now.
But despite that, these four still want to give it a shot.
They're fully intent on going all the way, with my songs.
And I don't plan on letting them down.
Right?
Momoka-san.
Understood.
Huh?
You'll be playing at the festival, correct?
Make a splash at the festival, huh...
SHIOMI MIURA
GOLDEN ARCHER
If we manage to stand out,
it'll be easier for the agency to find us a label that can produce us.
And if we already have a big enough fanbase, the label won't see a need for us to change our style.
So this festival's gonna be like an audition for us, huh.
Nina.
What is it?
Could you think up some lyrics for our new song?
Wait, me?
I want to see how it'll turn out. A song written by my songs.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't get it.
Me neither.
It's fine.
What's important is that they do.
How's it going so far?
Not great.
Didn't you say you had an idea before?
I did, but...
Then just go with that.
You wouldn't understand...
Lyrics exist outside of us, you get what I mean?
The moment we write them down,
it's like something that was inside us takes on a life of its own.
And who exactly died and made you the resident philosopher?
How many songs do you think I've written?
Owowowowow...
I get what you're saying, but...
Come on, break's over.
Already?
What is it?
It's nothing.
Welco-
May I help you?
No way...how?
What are y-
Welcome.
Excuse me,
I believe a certain Iseri should be working part-time here...
I don't think she has a shift today...
I see.
Did you want to see her?
You must be Rupa-san, right?
Sis!
What?
Mom's here!
I'm not surprised
Ugh, you could've warned me...
Dad?!
Nina?
And that's why you're came crashing in here again?
I gotta say, it's really nice in here...
You don't even know why they're here.
Shouldn't you at least try talking to them?
Are you listening to me?
Nina?
Talking to them doesn't really work.
It's the same with your grandma, isn't it?
We don't see things the same way.
All they do is spout nonsense all the time.
Maybe, but still.
Besides, I have to focus on the lyrics.
We don't have much time until the festival.
Our future's at stake here, I can't bother myself with this right now...
Sounds to me like you're just running away.
By the way, you planning to stay the night?
THE NEXT DAY
Hello?
Stop calling me.
You ran away, didn't you?
It's not like that.
They're even bombarding me with calls at this point.
Asking where you are.
Recipient: Muneo Iseri Sender: Nina Iseri
What did you tell them?
What did you expect after sending them a letter like that?
Of course they'll show up.
But why?
Did you really think they'd just accept it?
If you have something to say, say it to their faces without running away all the time.
Nina?
She hung up.
Huh?
Did they change the lock?
It's my apartment, you know!
Give me the new keys!
Ugh, why is everyone so damn annoying!
Shut up!
But!
Here, for you.
We told the manager you'll be on vacation for a bit.
Think of it as a present from both of us.
TOKYO -> KUMAMOTO
But why?
I believe Tomo-chan already mentioned it to you before.
On the day of the accident, I was supposed to call my family.
But I had to stay at work for a bit longer than usual.
So I thought I'd call them the next day, thinking I had all the time in the world for that.
But I didn't.
We have a lot less time and opportunities than we think.
Sorry for rambling about myself.
Do you really think they're that worried now?
They never really cared.
I wasn't asking for sound effects.
I see now.
So that's your weakness, huh.
It's not a weakness.
Then go and talk to them properly.
Not you too.
I think you're misunderstanding yourself.
Huh?!
Deep down, what's really bothering you the most
isn't the exams, or the bullying.
It's the fact that your father didn't side with you at the time.
No it's not.
Then there's no reason to avoid them, is there?
I won't.
Then go and settle this. And you're banned from my place until you do.
I'm off.
Well, I'm here...
The train towards Suizenji and Hikarinomori will now...
TATSUTAGUCHI STATION
Let's do this.
Three, two, one…
Ouch!
Ugh...
Nina!
We looked everywhere for you.
Girls Band Cry.
Family Principles
A band?
And you want to make a living from it?
Apparently she does.
They even got scouted by an agency.
They're basically one step away from being pros at this point.
Don't know how much of that is true though.
All of it is true.
But...
You left, saying that you're going to study for college exams,
and now you started this whole thing without even telling us?
She did tell me, partially at least.
Did you even stop to think about your poor mother?
Here you go pulling that card again.
As if it's about her.
Dad, when I left, I remember you telling me to do what I want.
And I told you that's exactly what I intend to do.
No.
I said I don't mind it as long as you get into a college.
Do you realize just how much we let you get away with?
You said you wanted to quit school, we agreed and handled all the paperwork.
You said you wanted to go to Tokyo, we arranged it.
Don't just spin the story to your liking.
I did all of that my own!
I quit school by myself, and I'm living in Tokyo by myself!
You only got your apartment because your mother vouched for you.
Remind me again, who exactly is written as your guarantor in the documents?
You’re still a minor. Do you understand what that means?
There are adults who are responsible for you.
So I just have to do as you say?
Pretend I was never bullied?
Nina…
I knew it was pointless.
I came all this way
hoping that maybe we could understand each other.
And this is what I get, right off the bat.
I’ve had enough.
I want you to come with me somewhere tomorrow.
Hey.
Where are we going?
You’ll find out soon enough.
I'm not coming.
We're going to my school, aren't we? I'm out.
I already told them we'll be coming.
Just like you had things to say to me, I have things I want to say to you.
Thank you for coming when it's so hot outside.
LETTER OF APOLOGY
It’s no issue.
What is this supposed to be?
It must've been hard on you too.
- Could we begin?
- Yes, of course.
We conducted our investigation, and the student in question told us the truth.
I want to apologize on behalf of the school for not becoming aware of this sooner.
That’s it? Are you saying the school will not take responsibility?
That’s not what I’m saying.
But according to school rules, considering this to be bullying would be a bit...
I realize I'm not in a position to talk as if I've been there,
but surely the school wasn't completely in the dark about-
Enough.
But…
I said stop it.
But why? You are the victim here.
Momoka-san, about Nina...
Just in case she doesn't come back...what do we do?
Whatever will be, will be.
Tomo-chan!
Are you hurt?
It's okay.
Let's trust her.
You're back.
Yeah.
Are you staying for dinner?
- Going back already?
- Yeah.
And you're serious about the band?
Yeah.
Do you like it that much?
That song
gave me the courage I lacked.
People kept telling me to grit my teeth, that it was the smart thing to do.
Letter of introspection
So naturally, I always thought that's the only way.
Until I heard that song.
If I proved that I wasn't in the wrong, I wouldn't have to suffer through it anymore.
I wouldn't have to constantly be afraid, and could just take the leap.
But there was no way of knowing
whether I would fall into the depths of hell or fly towards the vast blue skies.
And that song is what let me fly in the end.
I no longer have solid ground to return to, and I don't need any.
You know,
back then, I really wanted to kill myself.
I might not actually have wings,
and I might just be daydreaming about flying,
but I love myself as I am now.
I can say it with my head held high now. Here I am, the real me.
Got it.
But please, at least eat dinner before you leave.
Here you go, lotus root curry.
Did you miss it?
- Are we eating here?
- Why not?
You know, the family principles.
Don't worry about that.
Things have been a bit weird since you left.
Dad started drinking alcohol he can't even handle.
He was completely wasted.
"What do you think I should do?"
He was saying that.
He was just that worried about you.
He might be a famous educator,
but he still went around asking for advice.
Also, your mom gave this train ticket
to your friends in secret, and told them to give it to you.
You didn't notice, did you?
We love you, you know.
I know our parents are clumsy, but they still do.
Make sure you keep that in mind.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for being alive.
And I love you too, Nina.
It's spicy.
Was Mom's curry always this spicy?
Family Principles
Nina, 10 years old
Everything is so white Everything is so slow
All the answers are empty of substance
You like this song, right?
I do.
I see.
You don't like it?
Of course you don't.
It's a good song.
I like it.
Dad.
Sorry for always being so selfish and never listening to you.
Try to cut back on smoking a bit, okay?
I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
I'm leaving.
Nina!
Wait.
What is it?
Do you still have something to say?
Have a safe trip.
Thanks.
Nina!
Don't forget your keys.
My keys?
Why?
Thank your dad.
Dad!
I'm going to sing a song I wrote soon.
Come listen to it if you have time.
Okay.
Great.
Nina.
I'm off!
And thanks for the branch!
Take care!
They're awkward, meddlesome, and irritating.
but I still love them.
Goodbye. See you soon.
Thank you for choosing to ride with us.
EMPTINESS AND CATHARSIS
Miss? Miss!
Y-yes!
Oh, it's you again.
Did you sleep well?
Yes!
I'm back.
Nina.
Where's my souvenir?
You're kidding.
Why?
Well, Momoka-san wasn't sure you'd be coming back.
One more day,
and she would've had me drive everyone to Kumamoto.
She was saying she'd drive there herself if she had to.
A bit more and Rupa-san would've had to pull out all the stops.
Hey, you were all on board with this!
Wait, she's crying.
Those are definitely tears, right?
Nah, she can't be.
Rupa-san, what do you think?
Hmmmm, can't say for sure.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
So, did you finish the lyrics or what?
Yep, they turned out great!
Next up: "The Center of the World".