[AIDE] So you think
that General Armstrong
had something to do
with General Raven's
disappearance?
[GARTNER]
It seems so...
However, she's too smart to
leave any evidence behind.
Yes, that's true.
Well, anyway...
The only thing we
have to worry about
is holding down this fort...
As for the general...
Well, I'm sure the
tigers in Central
will make sure
she's taken care of.
General Armstrong...
How nice to see you.
They posted you in
Central, Mustang?
You're well connected.
No, it's solely
based on merit.
That's rich coming from you.
[ROY] What brings you
here today, General?
Fuhrer Bradley summoned me
for an extended
stay, I imagine.
Is that so...?
Well, sometime, we
should grab some dinner.
Your treat...?
I hope you know I could
eat you into bankruptcy.
Maybe we should
skip dinner, then.
I see...
you're short on both
money and nerve, huh?
Maybe I could offer
some flowers, instead...
There are many fine
florists here in Central.
[OLIVIER]
Are there?
[knocking]
[BRADLEY]
You may enter.
[OLIVIER]
Sir!
[BRADLEY] Now then...
General Armstrong...
We need to talk about
General Raven's
recent disappearance.
Just what have you done?
[OLIVIER]
I won't be able to hide it all.
Pardon me, Your Excellency,
but I simply don't understand
how you could employ
someone as careless
and incompetent
as General Raven.
Is that the reason you
saw fit to dispose of him?
Surely you don't need him...
It can't be good
to have someone
so talkative on
you senior staff.
You have me intrigued, General.
What did Raven say?
Immortality...
the history of this country...
Your Excellency's identity...
He told me all sorts of things
without any prompting.
[BRADLEY] Hmmm... And
after learning all of this,
you still responded
to my summons?
Yes, sir...
I assume you'll
be needing someone
to fill that fool's vacant seat?
[BRADLEY]
Interesting...
I like the way you play.
Very well...
You can have General
Raven's seat...
but, as I expect
you'll understand,
my men will take over
Ft. Briggs... Agreed?
Of course... as you wish.
My soldiers are extremely
strong and well-trained, sir...
I guarantee they will serve
you well, Your Excellency.
I'm sure they will...
I appreciate the
sacrifice, General...
[HENSCHEL]
To steal a tiger's cubs,
you have to enter her den.
And it seems like the
General's landed herself
right in the middle of it...
Yeah. And now this
place is theirs, too.
But still...
there's one thing
they don't know...
Although our leader
might be gone...
we still stand as one...
We act with one will.
That's the Fort Briggs way.
From here on...
the bears will fight the tigers.
[ROY]
Is this spot taken?
[HAWKEYE]
No.
So how is work treating you?
[ROY]
See for yourself.
I have to work
through every meal,
or I can't keep up...
And how bout you?
I've been staying busy too,
especially with everything
I've had to learn...
Fuhrer Bradley works
very efficiently though,
so that helps...
He isn't a slacker,
that's for sure.
Sounds like this is gonna
be a dull conversation.
Well, apparently...
[tap tap]
[HAWKEYE]
Scar is up in the north...
The Elric brothers
are up there, as well.
I see.
[tap tap]
My former classmates,
Lucy and Ian are
stationed up there.
They like to
keep me informed.
Hmm...
aren't the north
and east conducting
joint exercises
this spring?
Yes, I think you're
right about that.
I hope Major Miles
and Buccaneer
don't show us up
like they have
in the past
[ROY]
Miles... Buccaneer... okay...
and York, Ida, and Sugar
all spoke to her too...
Havoc... Oscar...
Mike... Uni... Nora...
Charlie... Then Uni
and Lucy again...
Uni once more...
and then Sterling!
"Selim Bradley is a Homunculus!"
I'd say impossible...
But then, there
is no such thing...
What in the world is about
to happen here in Central?!
[HOMUNCULUS]
Young man... Hey... you there!
Oh, no!
[HOMUNCULUS]
It's all right.
Look. Over here.
Um, yeah?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Hey, now...
Can't you at least
bring yourself to act
a little surprised or something?
[HOHENHEIM] What do I
get for acting surprised?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Hmm... You show no fear...
I like that.
What's your name?
I'm Number 23.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Not your number...
I want you to tell
me your real name.
I'm a slave...
I don't have one...
[HOMUNCULUS]
A slave...?
You mean a person without
any rights or freedoms,
someone trafficked and
deeded as a possession?
Deeded? What's that?
[HOMUNCULUS] It's when
a piece of property
is transferred
to another person.
Seems you're not all
that bright, are you?
Hey, get outta here!
[HOMUNCULUS] How could
I possibly have been born
from someone as
stupid as you...?
You are the one who
gave me blood, right?
I guess so.
He said he was going to
use it for an experiment.
[HOMUNCULUS]
I exist today...
Because you gave
me your blood.
Thank you... Let's see...
"Number 23" isn't
going to cut it...
I think I'll give you
a name of your own.
Give me an name...?!
Who are you?
[HOMUNCULUS] You'll want a
noble sounding one, right...?
Let's see... Theo...!
Theophrastus Bombastus.
That's too long!
[HOMUNCULUS]
Huh...?
Oh yeah, you're
not that smart...
Maybe we shouldn't put
too many syllables in it.
Hey you, I'm
plenty smart!
[HOMUNCULUS]
Well, how about Van...
Van Hohenheim,
how does that sound?
So Van Hohenheim, huh?
I think I can remember that.
[HOMUNCULUS]
It's spelled...
Oh... you don't know how
to read and write, do you?
I don't need to read
and write to do my work.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Your slave work.
Don't you even want freedom?
Are you going to live out the
rest of your life as a slave,
without the rights
of a real man?
In that case,
you're no different from me,
trapped inside
this stuffy flask.
Let me teach you...
Van Hohenheim.
[HOHENHEIM]
Hey...
What are you...?
Who are you...?
What do I call you?
[HOMUNCULUS] I'll tell
you what, Van Hohenheim,
you can call me the Dwarf
in the Flask, Homunculus.
[MASTER]
All things are made from one...
and in the end, all
things return to one.
[HOHENHEIM]
In other words, one is all...
[MASTER] Indeed, and
all is one as well.
All is ultimately
of the one...
So if all is not
included in the one...
then all is nothing.
You have passed...
You are now an
alchemist, Hohenheim...
Well done, child.
I'm still only fit
to be an assistant...
My skill is nothing
near yours, Master.
[HOHENHEIM]
I'm grateful to you.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Oh? For what?
[HOHENHEIM]
I live as well as I do now
because of the
knowledge you gave me.
And I have also earned
the master's respect...
Thanks to you, maybe someday...
I'll even be able to get
married and have a family.
[HOMUNCULUS]
A family, huh?
How inconvenient
for you humans.
Unless you form
communities and breed,
your species can't
continue to exist.
Don't call it breeding...
And whether or
not it's a concept
that you're able
to understand...
That's where humans...
find happiness.
We live for the
bonds that we form
with friends and
family members...
That's who we humans are.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Sure, whatever you say.
Okay then, what is it
that makes you happy?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Well...
I'd hate to be guilty
of asking too much,
but I think I'd be happy if
I could just leave this flask...
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Immortality...
Why would someone who
already has so much power
and prosperity
need such a thing?
[MASTER]
Watch your tongue.
You're in the royal presence.
If you continue
with this insolence,
I will smash your flask!
[HOMUNCULUS] You wouldn't
dare to destroy such
an important
source of knowledge.
[KING OF XERXES]
That's enough chatter.
Immortality... tell me,
is it possible, or isn't it?
[HOMUNCULUS] Growing
impatient in your old age?
How lamentable, King of Xerxes.
Okay...
I'll tell you how you
can achieve immortality.
[VILLAGER 1]
What are you digging here for?
[MAN]
Irrigation canals...
The king's ordered them
to be dug all
throughout the country.
[VILLAGER 1]
That's the King for you.
He even cares about the
well being of us commoners.
Yes, he does.
Remember, there
must be no survivors.
[KING OF XERXES]
Hurry...! Quickly!
Carve out the crests of blood
while there's still time.
[CITY MAN 1]
The north village was attacked?
[CITY WOMAN]
I heard they all died!
[CITY MAN 2]
Before, it was the west village.
[CITY MAN 1]
Who could be doing this?
What an awful tragedy.
[HOMUNCULUS]
Yeah... real tragic.
Majesty... at long last,
your transmutation
circle is complete.
Hmmmm...
Took long enough...
Finally, it's done...
This is it? Everything's ready?
[HOMUNCULUS] Yes.
You may now become immortal.
Incredible...
The king will
achieve immortality.
[HOMUNCULUS] Yes, this is
an amazing moment, indeed.
This is immortality?
No, no, you must be wrong!
I don't understand it!
[KING OF XERXES]
You said if we were in
the center of the circle,
we wouldn't be harmed!
What the--?!
Wha-What's going on here...?!
Hey...! Homunculus!
The true center of the
transmutation circle
is right here where
you're standing.
It is?
[HOMUNCULUS]
Surely you remember
that your blood is within me...
I used it to open the doorway.
Blood brother of mine
Van Hohenheim...
Right now, you and I are
at the center of everything!
[voices wailing]
[HOHENHEIM]
Oh! Ah! Aaaaauuughhh!!!
Aaaauughhh!!
Majesty!
Master are you...
No, he's dead.
Is anyone out there?!
Willard... Mechthild...!
Reinmeir...! Toni! Mayo!
Somebody...
There must be someone left!
[FATHER]
It's no use.
All of their souls have
been taken from them.
[HOHENHEIM]
Majesty! Are you all right?
[FATHER]
Tell me...
Your body...
how is it feeling?
It's me...! Impossible...
[FATHER]
Using your blood,
I created a
receptacle for myself...
Nice... Finally...
I can walk on
my own two legs.
Are you... the
Homunculus in the flask?
What's going on here?
What is this?
What have you done?
To thank you for your blood...
I've given you a name...
And I've given you knowledge...
And now...
I've given you a body
that will live forever.
I'm immortal?!
[FATHER] Focus your attention
within yourself, Hohenheim.
You hear them, don't you...?
The voices of all the
people in this country
who were offered in exchange
for your immortality?
Well, half of their lives
were for me, actually.
I appreciate your
cooperation, Hohenheim.
[IZUMI]
Van Hohenheim?
I knew it!
[IZUMI]
Finally...
I get the chance to
meet Ed and Al's father.
[HOHENHEIM] And I finally get to
meet the one who taught my sons.
I'm sure they must
have been a handful.
Oh, no... They were fine boys.
What is it?
Izumi...! Are you all right?
Let me get your medicine.
[HOHENHEIM]
May I have a look at her...?
I know a bit about
the medical field.
Sure...
[IZUMI] I'm all right...
This happens.
No, you are not all right...
Mr. Sig, find us a car, quickly!
Hurry!
Right...! I'm on it.
Ms. Izumi...
You have... seen the truth?
What did you sacrifice?
Please be honest with me.
[IZUMI]
My insides... were taken.
I was trying to bring
my child back to life.
I see.
Yes...
I'm sorry.
Izumi! Hang on! Izumi!
[IZUMI] Calm down, dear...
Please... I'm all right.
He shoved his hand into you!
But my breathing...
It's easier.
How can that be?
[IZUMI]
There's... no wound.
[SIG]
That's impossible.
[HOHENHEIM]
Your organs were taken away
as a testament to your sin;
they cannot be brought back...
but I did rearrange
your entrails somewhat
to improve the flow of blood.
Ms. Izumi...
You cannot give into
your fate just yet.
You're the boys'
father... But who...
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am a Philosopher's Stone...
in the form of a man.
That's what I am.
[ED] The Sorcerer's Stone...
The Celestial Stone...
The Grand Elixir...
The Philosopher's Stone
is known by many names...
it's not necessarily a stone.
The one Dr. Marcoh had
was a semi-liquid form.
The one that Kimblee has
is similar to a crystal...
And it's about this big.
You say it has
incredible power...
I would have expected it to
be a little bigger than that.
It's not. I've never seen one
that's much bigger
than a small pebble.
Besides... to create a
Philosopher's Stone that big...
you'd have to kill
thousands of people.
Maybe it's possible...
but I wouldn't
ever want to see it.
[NARRATOR] If one
wishes to obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given...
That is the law of
Equivalent Exchange...
the law of alchemy...
the law that governs the world.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 41, "The Abyss."
A young man is called upon...
He must make his payment...
with his own pain.