This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
She's become the singer Full Moon...
...and has had her first taste of work, but...
...she keeps worrying about whether or not she seems enough like an adult.
In the end, she was even scolded!
But, after talking with the local female high school students...
...she realized that it was fine to accept the futility in trying to become an adult, so...
...she managed to complete her job safely.
Well then...
I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Hmm?
I wanna go too!
You can't.
You have to turn into Mitsuki and watch the house.
If you don't do that, her grandmother will realize that she went out.
But...
...I haven't had to do this before, right?
There's no way we can use visiting
Wakaouji-sensei as an excuse today...
...which means that someone has to take her place.
We can't do anything if I'm not there to change her into a sixteen year old.
That leaves you.
There's no one else who can do it.
But...
Meroko, I'm begging you.
Today's a very important recording session for my debut.
So... okay?
I understand.
Really?!
But you know...
Every once in a while, you have to watch the house, Mitsuki.
I want to go out too you know...
Come on. Let's go.
Okay!
Hey!
Selfish pigs!
The Long Day in the Studio
Is that the studio?
Wow!
There's a whole bunch of fans!
Just...
...who is it that's coming, I wonder...?
It doesn't matter who it is, right?
More importantly...
Eh! Who is it?!
Ah! Wait up!
Who is it?!
Wow!
No way.
It's the Guitar Boys!
They're going to record now?!
Amazing!
Hey, hey.
Didn't you come here to record, too?
Eh?
But... But...
Man... Let's go.
Well then, I'll get on here.
Hey! Mitsuki!
Ah. Ooshige-san!
Ah...
What's wrong?
Over here!
Here!
Hurry up and come here!
Ah. Okay!
I don't like this... everyone's looking at me.
You're a singer... that's how it's going to be.
Nothing you can really do about it.
Yeah...
A talking stuffed animal?
Well?
Did you get enough sleep last night?
Yeah. For now...
Then we're okay.
Let's work hard today!
Okay!
Come on, go in.
Wow!
I feel... somewhat overwhelmed.
Um... excuse me.
We have a job to do.
She'll be recording here starting today...
Full Moon-san.
Ah. I'm Full Moon.
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
We're counting on you.
Be strong. Mitsuki.
Okay!
It hurts...
Are you nervous?
Ah. Sorry, Takuto.
Don't worry.
I'm watching over you.
Okay.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Is she going to be okay?
Full Moon-san.
Please come over here.
Ah. Okay.
Then... promise me.
You'll definitely stay here and watch me.
Sure, sure.
Ah?
Hey?
I'm caught.
What? It's just you guys.
You came again?
If they find you, we don't know you.
Putting that aside...
Did you see a girl carrying a stuffed animal cat?
A cat?
Yeah.
The one who just went in that studio.
Full Moon-sama
Full Moon...
Who's that?
A new artist.
Hmm...
Full Moon, huh?
It's somewhat... peaceful in here.
So that unnecessary noise won't be picked up...
...we went all out in building this room.
Is that so?
Regarding the position of the mic...
...is this place okay?
Ah.
I-It's fine.
...I think.
Then... please wait a bit.
Ah. Ah. Ahem. Ahem. Ahem.
Ah. Ah. Ah.
I'm going to sing in here...
Takuto...
Huh?
Excuse us...
We need to run a mic check, so...
...can you say something?
Ah.
Um...
Uwa...
Um, can you hear me?
Ah. We can hear you.
It's okay.
Ah. Producer Takasu.
Yo.
You feeling up to this?
Yes. Somehow...
For now... here's Myself...
Try singing it.
Okay.
Then... music please.
Eh.
Um... start by putting your headphones on.
Headphones?
You put on your headphones so that you can hear the music.
Ah. Is that what it is?
Technology has sure come a long way.
Huh?
She's a fun girl, isn't she?
I'm sorry.
As an amateur, this is her first time in all of this.
Well...
Since she's new at this...
...we'll take it slowly.
Thank you very much.
This is going to take up so much time.
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima ma-
I never...
Ah, wait a second.
You're bringing out the loneliness at this part, but...
...it would be better if you showed the feeling of serenity with which you wrote them.
Serenity?
That's right.
You don't have to sing well... just put your feelings.
Ah, okay.
So then... let's try it.
Ah.
Kitty-chan!
Ah. Takuto.
A date, right now?
Wah! I'll go! I'll go!
Where are you going to take me?
Eh?! Really?!
Geez, Takuto.
You really like me that much, huh.
I...
I also like you, of course.
Why can't that ever happen every once in a while?
Huh?
I should...
Now I can't go outside and play.
Huh?
Takuto?
You still look a little nervous.
Ah. I'm sorry.
We've been looking at it for a while here, too.
How about a break?
Okay!
Mitsuki. Is your throat dry?
Do you want some coffee?
Ooshige-san.
Do you know what happened to the stuffed animal cat that was here?
Stuffed animal?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Ah.
The members of Guitar Boys!
Um... actually...
Are you a new girl?
You're Full Moon, aren't you?
How old are you?
I'm... I'm...
...looking for a stuffed animal cat...
Do you know anything about one?
A stuffed animal cat?
Dunno...
Ah, now that you mention it... just a moment ago...
...I saw Nanami-chan carrying something like that.
Really?
Where did that girl go?
Where...?
She went home already, didn't she?
Eh?!
Do you know where she lives at?
I have no clue... about something like that...
I see...
Takuto...
Hmm?
Where is this?
Ah! Kitty-chan.
You're awake?
Wha..?
Won't you talk with me?
Come on...
Come on!!!
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Stupid! That hurts!
He talked!
Man... spare me already.
See ya.
Eh?
Kitty-chan?
Where are you? Where'd you go?
Ah...
Kitty-chan disappeared.
Don't do this to me...
Yay!
Kitty-chan!
I can't go back to her at this rate.
Whee!
Geez... Takuto, where are you?
What should I do?
Ah.
When I'm not with you...
...use this whistle to call me.
I'll fly to you.
Huh?
There isn't any sound coming out...?
Hmm? She's calling for me.
Don't just talk to yourself.
Talk to me!
Hmph.
Hmm?
Say something!
Owwwww!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
What are you doing?!
Ah! You talked!
You're that  happy when I talk?!
I'm happy!
I'm not happy, so...
...I'm leaving, okay?
Sorry, but I'm busy.
I can't let you do that.
Why not?!
Kitty-chan is...
...my friend!
Don't decide that I'm your friend on your own!
Ah.
If you're going to say that...
...then I'll do this!
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I get it! I get it, so stop!
Let's play together, then.
Man...
You're even worse than Meroko.
When in the kitchen, dealing with oil is always a problem.
Ah! I'm bored.
Ah...
That's right!
Those two haven't come back yet.
Until now...
For heaven's sake...
Who left the television on?
It wasn't me.
Hold it...
You won't even let me watch television?
By the way, Tanaka-san.
Do you know what Mitsuki is doing?
Yes. I'll go get her right away.
I'm not joking!
That girl...
...she's had to put up with this kind of life?
At this rate...
If I don't find Takuto...
What's gonna happen?
This whistle is definitely broken!
I can hear it.
Takuto!
Yo.
Takuto.
Just... what?!
Come on, Kitty-chan.
Don't wander off on your own!
Hey.
Will you give me back that stuffed animal?
Nope!
Because it's mine!
But...
...it's really mine.
No it's not!
It's mine!
Takuto...
I don't understand it either.
Kitty-chan.
Your name is Takuto?
Ah.
Hey, Takuto.
You're my friend, right?
You took me away while I was
sleeping without even asking...
...friends don't do things like that.
While you were asleep?
You're mean, Takuto!
You said that you'd listen to me, didn't you?
A-A-At that time, you were still practicing.
I was totally awake while you were recording.
Oh, that's right!
What about your recording?!
Just now...
...they called to say they weren't ready yet, so it's fine.
Wait a second.
Don't talk to my Takuto so familiarly.
You know... Nanami-chan.
Takuto belongs to me.
Show me proof then.
I don't have any proof, but...
...but he's mine.
You're the singer Full Moon, right?
Eh?
Yes, but...
You should hurry up and go back to the studio, shouldn't you?
That's why...
If you don't give me back Takuto, I can't sing!
That's such a childish thing to say.
That's because...
Where are you going?
Back home.
That's it!
This place is my home.
Eh?
Come on.
Let's go in, Takuto.
Takuto, what do you want to play?
Nanami-chan.
Will it be okay if you don't go home?
It's fine.
Your father and your mother will be worried.
They won't be.
Why?
Because I don't have any.
Eh?
Nanami-chan.
You don't have a father or mother?
Yep.
You're... all alone?
Nanami-chan...
Takuto, here we go!
Yay!
This is fun!
Let's go again!
That's right...
Eichi-kun lost his...
Me, too...
Here we go!
Yay!
Are you having fun, Nanami-chan?
Yep. I'm having fun.
I see.
Nanami-chan, you're lonely, aren't you?
I'm not lonely at all.
That's a lie.
Because you're lonely...
...you took Takuto, didn't you?
Then... if I say I'm lonely...
...is it okay if I don't give Takuto back?
Eh?
Is...
Is it okay for me to be with Takuto forever?
Ah... That's...
As if.
Everything I said was a lie.
Eh?!
My father and mother are over there.
What did you just say?!
Hold it!
Nanami-chan!
See.
There's my father and mother.
That's a lie too, isn't it?
It is?
Ah.
Nanami-chan.
Your total comes to 933 yen.
Hmm?
Yes.
A thousand yen, is it?
I wonder what should I get.
If you have a mother...
...then why won't she make dinner for you?
That's because she's busy.
Are they really your father and mother?
Ah.
I'll get this.
It's true.
But...
When you entered the store...
...they didn't say anything to you at all, did they?
That's how it always is.
Always...?
Every day.
Eh?
You mean that you eat dinner by yourself every day?
That's right.
Every day?
This is too strange.
If they're your real father and mother...
...why don't they say anything?
Why?
If they were your real family...
When you go home...
...you'd say "I'm home", and they'd say "welcome back", right?
Because I...
If I had a father and mother...
I would say "I'm home", and I would want them to say "welcome back" to me!
And you say that you have parents...
Why?!
She...
Nanami-chan...
Because I also want...
...to talk to my father and mother, and...
...there are lots of things I want to talk about.
But...
They're always busy, so...
I...
Nanami.
Mama!
Mama! Mama!
I'm sorry, Nanami.
We couldn't...
...take proper care of you.
We're so sorry.
Please forgive us.
Nanami...
Papa!
Isn't this great, Nanami-chan?
Onee-chan, here.
I'm very sorry for taking Takuto without asking.
My, my.
I was wondering about what would happen.
Hey. Nanami-chan.
Do you want to go to the recording with me?
Eh?
This time...
You won't have to do it secretly.
Okay!
She's good, isn't she?
She's giving off an aura of serenity.
Yeah.
By the way, who is she?
Full Moon's Number One Fan.
Eh?
Come on, it's okay, isn't it?
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
Ta
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
Zu
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
I
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
A
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
So
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
Se
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
Full
and find the full moon
Moon
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
I
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
Kyo
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
I
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Mo
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
Preview
Costume, check!
Makeup, check!
Ah, Takuto!
What do we do?! What do we do?!
Will she sing well, I wonder...
What are you so worked up about, Meroko?
It's not like you're the one who's singing.
That's true, but...
Today's her debut, and...
...I'm worried.
Well...
She'll do what she can.
We can deal with the pain and joy later.
Wait...
She's gotten into some kind of trouble again!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Full Moon, Debut!
Look forward to it!