They all said we were fools...
That it was just a pipe dream.
But we will not be discouraged.
At times, we'll laugh together.
At times, we'll clash.
At times, we'll support each other.
Fight!
Explosion!
Yeah!
We'll continue running...
toward the paradise that all men dream of!
The mixed bath is currently closed
for remodeling. -Kotoura Hot Springs
Kotoura Hot Springs
Withdraw!
TLC
Tobikage
Timer
Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo AFX : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC
Robo731   Floris257
Encoder
Floris257
In This World, I...
I wanted to have a mixed bath...
The last chance I'll ever have to share
a bath with high school girls...
Well, well!
That looks delicious!
I think I made too much.
Kotoura-kun's cooking, huh?
Look, Senpai. I made some, too.
It's my revenge for the other day.
I'm sure Manabe-kun will have some.
Naturally, Manabe-kun will eat every last bite.
W-Well, at any rate, help yourselves.
The hot springs turned out to be a wasted trip, anyway.
True...
You must be disappointed, too, since you couldn't get in the bath with me.
Not really.
Manabe-kun has his issues,
but being ignored really hurts a girl...
Keep fighting, President!
Don't worry about me.
Shouldn't you be doing something about him?
For the sake of a mixed bath!
Heave-ho!
For naked fellowship!
With my granddaughter!
With Kotoura!
What are those two doing?
With my granddaughter!
With Kotoura!
Eek! Manabe-kun, you pervert!
With my granddaughter!
Eek! Grandfather, you pervert!
Even if you did uncover a hot spring in the yard, I'd never get in with you!
Hi-yah!
Damn it!
Why did we strike oil instead of a hot spring?!
Even if it substantially increases my wealth,
it's useless if I can't share a hot spring with my granddaughter...
M-Manabe, I think this one turned out better than the last one...
Damn! Damn!
H-How is it?
P-Please stop, Moritani-san!
It's not like we're still little kids...
Oh, no!
Hey! What are you two doing?!
Yahoo! It's Kotoura-san!
Oh, here... Put your clothes back on, Manabe-kun!
Eek! Kotoura, you pervert!
What are you saying, Manabe-kun?!
Kotoura-san is ignoring me... If you like nudity that much...
Fine! I'll strip, too!
I'll strip, too!
There!
Hey! Don't do that around boys!
Gotcha! Je t'aime, Kotoura-san!
No!
Come on! Come on!
H-Help me, Manabe-kun!
One won't hurt you!
We're perfect for each other!
Kotoura, your skin is so smooth...
No! That's not me!
We will never forget this tragedy
brought about by Moritani-san's cooking.
You know, since she can make food like that
from normal, everyday ingredients,
I'd say she's the biggest supernatural phenomenon here.
Hey, Head Priest.
Here, let me start you off... Huh?
Is something wrong?
Head Priest, this is what you wanted to show me?
I'm sorry to drag you—
That girl looks like she's having a lot of fun.
So, she's made friends, eh?
Yes, that's right. They're all good kids.
Has she forgotten...
the way she tore apart her own family with her nonsensical outbursts?
If you continue to associate with her, she'll ruin you too.
You'll lose everything, just like I did.
Kumiko-san, can't you at least meet with her?
And do what?
We'll only end up hurting each other again.
I see. So she was here...
I apologize for acting on my own.
I wanted Kumiko-san to see how Haruka-chan is doing now...
Sounds like she hasn't changed at all since then.
Her, on the other hand...
Come on, you two! Cut it out!
Wh-What the hell...
...is going on here?!
How could you forget?!
I loved you with all my heart last night!
What's done is done.
As long as you take responsibility...
Moritani Dojo
Enrollment Application
I'm the biggest jerk ever!
So you're awake.
You sure had a good time last night...
with Manabe-kun.
Wh-What do you mean, "a good time"?!
Wait... With Manabe?!
Good morning, Moritani-san.
Good morning...
Um, this isn't what it looks like.
It was an accident... an unfortunate accident.
Huh?
What a rough night. You two were really going at it.
Going at it? Rough? What was?
You don't mean... all three of us...
My eyes! My eyes!
What are you thinking about so early in the morning?
Honestly...
You both behaved inappropriately.
Sensei is very upset with you.
S-Sensei... Um, I don't remember anything...
I prevented you from doing anything that would have a lasting impact.
And you, Moritani-san, need to learn to show some restraint.
Especially when cooking.
Yes, ma'am.
And you're no better, Manabe-kun.
You need to keep that sort of behavior in modera— Hey!
Cut out the rude fantasies!
Sensei wasn't a part of it!
Stop!
Thank you for everything!
You could have stayed longer.
We'd love to, but one of us still has to finish their summer homework.
A
About
One
A
About
One
A
About
One
Hey, where's Kotoura?
Now that you mention it, the head priest isn't around either.
Let's go look for them.
Manabe, just a minute.
Yes?
She couldn't be...
Head Priest...
Haruka-chan, this room is...
Since I left that last time, I haven't been able to come in here.
But I was able to just walk right in this time.
So, my mother was here?
I can't hide anything from you.
I called her on my own initiative...
It's all right.
Head Priest... How can I make my parents
and friends stay with me?
How can I make them smile at me?
Haruka-chan, I promise I'll bring your mother back.
Head Priest, do you think...
I should have never been born?
I never realized this room was so small.
Haruka-chan...
Back then, this room alone was my world.
I planned to isolate myself in here forever.
But...
Head Priest, I'm going home now.
Kumiko-san, she wears such a lovely smile now.
So... my mother was watching me...
There she is! Kotoura-chan!
Kotoura, we're heading home.
Okay! I'm coming!
I-I'm just inviting him to hang out because it's summer vacation.
Manabe Yoshihisa
It's not like it's a date...
Oh, darn it! There!
H-Hello, Manabe-kun?
The person you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Uh... Um... I'll call you later.
August
The Next Day
The person you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a—
Today again?
Two Days Later
The person you have dialed is unavailable—
Man...
Again?
August
So, in other words, you're lonely because Manabe-kun won't talk to you?
He's probably just busy with something else.
But the other day...
So hot...
I wonder what we'll do with the ESP Society over summer vacation.
2x2=4. 3x4=12. 3x8=24. 5x3=15. 5x7=35. 8x2=16.
All he ever thinks about when I'm with him now is multiplication tables.
Doesn't that seem suspicious?
Thanks for the idea.
Our activity for today will be to observe Manabe-kun!
What?!
He's obviously plotting something mischievous.
For example, cheating on you with Moritani-san, who is also not here!
No.
Moritani-kun should be at home finishing her summer homework.
Mori! Mori! Mori!
What kind of bizarre setting is this?!
If we don't do this, you'll try to run away.
Miss, I graduated from Tokyo U!
I'll put my life on the line to help you!
Tokyo U?!
No, I'll help you! I graduated from Harvard!
Harvard?!
Mori! Mori!
Good pronunciation!
Whatever it is, we know that Manabe-kun is up to something.
Let's go, Kotoura-chan.
Uh, right...
And what will you do, Muroto-kun?
Pointless. I'll pass.
You're no fun.
Let's go!
Right!
Oh...
If you're after Manabe-kun, he's somewhere near the station.
You saw him?
No.
He really is in front of the station.
This is kind of exciting!
Um, isn't this an invasion of privacy?
Shh! Look!
Is he out on a date with her?
H-He couldn't be...
Here you go.
Thanks.
Just tissues...
No. Look closer.
Thanks!
He's only taking them from girls!
We're going after him.
Right!
Huh?
Lost him already...
Well, I guess there's nothing we can do.
Gah!
"Gah"?
What is it?
Do you like Mr. Bear?
Boobs... Boobs...
So many boobs!
President, this bear is dangerous! Get away from him!
That was too close.
She almost figured out it was me.
You're working?
Gulp!
Why are you keeping it a secret?
It's not something you should have to hide.
W-Well, see...
Boobs... Boobs are... round... pi... 3.1415926535897932...
You're not making sense!
In that case...
I-Is that... Kotoura's... boobs?
Why do you sound uncertain when I do it?
Manabe-kun, you jerk! Big pervert!
It's not like that!
The sensation of the president's boobs hadn't left me and...
So in the end, you ran away.
He's never kept anything from me before.
I understand that even Manabe-kun has his secrets, but...
Are you doubting him a little bit?
I see.
President?
Hey, there's the daughter of the phony!
It was on TV again yesterday,
that she killed herself because they found out she was a fake.
You're wrong! My mom...
My mom...
The TV isn't always right.
You have to believe what you see with your own eyes.
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
This is... my mom's book...
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
I've read it tons of times.
And I still believe...
Your mom was the real thing.
Uh, sorry!
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
Even when you love someone dearly,
sometimes you get tired of believing and begin to doubt them instead.
Wait...
Why are you crying?
Because... you... you...
Well, anyway, of course you want someone to tell you
that you're wrong in those times, right?
Yes...
Manabe-kun is an idiot, but...
No, it's because he's an idiot that it'll be okay.
Don't you think so?
Is it your boobs?!
Does that confidence come from your boobs?!
What are you talking about?
August
Summer vacation is over...
and I haven't seen Manabe-kun again since then.
Manabe-kun, wait!
Manabe-kun!
Everyone will leave you.
You should never have been born into this world, after all.
Moritani-san...
Kotoura-san, help me!
What happened to you two?!
I'm sorry, ma'am. She got away.
But now I'm certain that this dojo's future is in good hands!
Hiyori!
I did it! It's so easy to understand when you explain it to me.
Man, I should've come to you for help sooner.
So, how's it going with you and Manabe?
What?! I didn't do something wrong again, did I?
It sounds like you've had a tough time while I've been under house arrest.
Come on, cheer up!
But if Kotoura-san and Manabe have really...
Wait, what am I thinking?
Kotoura-san is an important friend to me!
Besides, Manabe would never betray her!
I'm such an idiot!
Hey! What are you doing, Moritani-san?!
Stop it!
Don't stop me!
I can't forgive myself for being so sinful!
What am I gonna do with you?
Moritani-san still likes Manabe-kun...
But it's no lie that she cares about me,
or that she trusts Manabe-kun.
Pointless. I'll pass.
Manabe-kun is an idiot, but...
No, it's because he's an idiot that it'll be okay.
Don't you think so?
Same goes for my senpais.
Then, I'll also...
After the Second Term Opening Ceremony
Manabe-kun, I...
Finally over! Let's go, Kotoura!
Wait... Manabe-kun?
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
Bir
thday
Haruka
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Hap
py
Bir
thday
Haruka
Happy birthday, Kotoura!
Your grandfather told me that September 1st is your birthday.
Geez, you really got us.
Hey! Why did you keep it from us too?
The president and vice-president aside,
if I had told you, you would've leaked it to her in no time.
Besides, you know...
I guess I like to show off a little now and then.
That's just like you. Stupid, but like you.
Here's your present.
It was kind of sudden, so I wasn't able to work for very long...
Sorry it's not much.
You should never have been born into this world, after all.
What's wrong, Kotoura?
Sorry... I... I...
Go ahead, Kotoura!
Okay.
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Kotoura!
Thank you, everyone...
Mother... In this world, I...
"The TV isn't always right," huh?
That's Muroto-senpai for you!
Exactly!
In other words, profusely thick steam in bath scenes
and nonsensical beams of light are wrong!
You've gotta be able to see everything!
Episode 8
It's Not a Date
You need to be reined in, pervert.