Alright, now look into the camera please.
We look so pretty...
Yeah, thanks to the touch-ups.
Wait, seriously?!
Huh, you're right.
Your nose kinda looks...more straight than the real thing.
No one asked for your analysis!
Let's leave choosing the photos for the contract signing day.
Got it!
AND THE SKIES TURN DARK ONCE MORE
They're still working part-time?
You should've told me.
Seems like today's their final shift.
They said they're indebted to the place, so they didn't want to quit too suddenly.
I see, that's understandable then.
Sorry about that.
Our president likes these kinds of things.
Like ordering water bottles with the company's name on them.
Togenashi Togeari water...
My throat's all spiky just from thinking about it.
Well, all the papers seem to be in order.
Which means that going forward, you'll officially be working with our agency.
And I, Miura, will be your agent. I'll be in your care.
Thank you very much.
We'll be in your care.
And that's how we found an agency.
200 thousand yen?!
Yep. I think she said the 25th's our payday.
And I can spend it?
Well, obviously.
It's your salary.
Reeeeaaaalllllyyyyy?
You didn't read the whole contract, did you?
Since you're getting that much money, there's obviously a catch.
Maybe one day they'll be like...
Surprise, you're an adult film actress now!
It was in the contract!
Pipe down.
But she said I'll be a-
Not that kind of catch.
The agency's just going to take a certain percentage
of everything we earn.
Like from merch, CDs, concert tickets, that stuff.
They're responsible for making us known, and if they succeed, it's a win-win situation.
Price Negotiable
Electric guitar
We recommend buying them as a set!
Amp set for beginners
Well, you get the idea.
I can't wait.
You sound kind of hesitant.
Are you still hung up about the festival?
You're always on social media trying to see if anyone's talking about us.
Of course I am! We rocked out there!
But all anyone talks about is DiaDust!
We were way better than them!
I said pipe down.
We weren't even on the same stage.
And they're supposedly idols,
who suddenly put on a show even diehard concert fanatics loved.
No surprise in them being the main buzz.
We were great too, why just them?
Hell if I know.
Still, we got plenty of positive feedback.
And we got our contract.
But...
Anyway, stop with the egosurfing.
Alright.
No point getting worked up over this. The fight's just getting started.
Got it.
Please, as if you weren't all worked up about it.
Ow!
GYUDON
Here you go.
Your contracts.
And, congratulations on your last day!
Huh?
Just take it.
What would you like to order?
I'll go with a medium.
Huh? Aren't we supposed to have hotpot later?
Same here, plus beer.
Wait, you're going to drink now?
Have no fear, I'll be drinking tonight too.
Alright, a medium set for me too then.
Okay, coming right up.
We really got a history with this place, huh?
It's where I fed you when we first met.
What's that about?
It took you 4 hours to get here from Tokyo Station,
and you were all crying about having no keys or something.
Nice sense of direction you got there.
Thank you. Beni-Shoga forever!
Tomo-chan.
Good work.
You too. The hard part's just starting though.
And now, let us open the Togenashi Togeari contract signing party!
Wait, what?
They said they'll be here soon, they already finished work.
Ah, got it.
I guess they had some things to finish up there.
Ouch...
I didn't know squash was so hard to cut.
It's been a while since one of your rich-girl phrases.
It's not like that.
I told you already...
You okay?
I just thought, maybe I really was a rich girl.
I mean, you had to teach me a lot when I first came here.
It was a huge shock for me.
Realizing that I couldn't really do anything by myself,
that I didn't know much about anything.
Did you get the hang of things by now?
I did.
Well, except for playing the guitar.
No regrets?
I'll make sure I don't have any. With the others.
Alright then.
Here we are!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Woah, it's cold.
It's colder than outside here.
Oooh! Beer, beer!
Sheesh...
By the way, I finished working on our logo.
Cheers!
Hey, don't start chugging without us!
We didn't even make a toast!
They can't hear you anymore.
Oh come on...
Let's get started too I guess.
Fine.
I told you I like my cabbage soft!
- Same here.
- See!
Stop being such a pain!
I'm picky about my food!
- Same here.
- Shut it!
It's obviously way better like this.
Here they go again.
What's so good about it, it just falls apart.
I'll have you on Team Soft Cabbage in no time.
C'mon, try it.
- C'mon, eat it.
- Wait, it's too hot!
- Let's eat tasty soft cabbage together...
- I'm telling you it's hot!
What's up?
I got an idea for a song.
And already thought of the title.
A FEW DAYS LATER
This looks amazing...
Good morning.
This is Nakata-san, the sound engineer.
Nice to meet you. I'm Nakata.
Nice to meet you!
And this is his assistant, Nakano-san.
Nice meeting you all.
This is Tanaka, a journalist.
I'm Tanaka, nice to meet you.
And this is Tano-san, from the marketing division.
I'm Tano!
Huh?!
How am I supposed to remember those...
Well, that's also part of the job.
You already remember them?
'Course I do. That much is a given for a functional member of society.
Alright then, what's the sound engineer's name?
Tanaka-san.
It's Nakata.
I'm so sorry.
Don't laugh.
We're playing the song you showed me the other day, right?
Yep. I tried scribbling down some lyrics.
Here you go.
You gonna stop laughing anytime soon?
Sorry.
Wait, this title…
Yeah.
It's about us, basically.
I was mulling over what our first song should be about.
And in the end, I think it should be about us.
Momoka-san...
Alright, shall we start then?
Nina.
If you're really serious about beating DiaDust, you better put your heart into it.
You got it.
And so, our first songwriting session together began.
Target!! Budoukan!!
BUDOUKAN
Do you think that part was too much?
You think so? I like it this way.
I even thought that maybe we could move this part to the beginning.
Well, that's an option, but...
Maybe you're right. Let's try it from the top.
My apologies, but we can't stay for too long.
Got it.
HEIWAJIMA STATION
Just barely made it, huh.
See you later.
I'll message you later.
It was really fun, wasn't it?
What was?
Making our own song all together.
Just imagine that it could actually reach someone so soon...
It's not as easy as you make it sound.
Sometimes songs don't reach as far as you'd like them to.
It'll be fine.
I mean, we're pouring our hearts into it.
We'll be alright.
I don't know, I'm still not sure about this part...
Want me to listen to it on my side?
Yes.
By the way, where's Miura-san?
She went outside to take a call.
We should probably ask for her input. Can you go get her?
Got it.
- Miura…-san...
- DiaDust what?
Really?
Understood. I will get back to you later.
Momoka-san wants you to listen to our...song.
Did you overhear us?
No.
I see.
What about Diamond Dust?
VALENTINE'S DAY BATTLE!
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Diamond Dust
I received this from their agency.
Two concerts at Club Citta.
Diamond Dust on day one.
Togenashi Togeari on day two.
Seriously? In that huge venue?
They’re planning it for February, almost as if they know when our new song will be out.
For Valentine's Day.
Fine by me!
Let's give them what they want.
Please read the next page.
The group that sells the most tickets and attracts the biggest crowd
will be chosen to perform the theme song for a drama series.
I see.
So that's how it is.
What do you mean?
CAFÉ MARUFUKU
We can't win?
Why are you acting as if we already lost?
- We won't know if we don't-
- Calm down.
DiaDust's have almost double the followers they had before.
It's rigged from the start.
The only reason they challenged us is because they're sure they'll win.
So they can prove they're better than us once and for all.
But still…
we’ll be facing each other on the same stage.
We just need to rock like we did at the festival!
Think about it for a sec.
About what?
We might be on the same stage, but we won't be in front of the same audience.
They call it a battle, but it's just two separate concerts.
And the deciding factor ends up being the crowd size, not how good we are.
The more popular band takes it all.
What the...
Getting angry won’t change anything.
How do you think the DiaDust members feel about this?
No idea.
They couldn't care less.
At least the Hina I know definitely doesn't.
She's the type to do anything as long as it benefits her.
We better talk about this properly before we end up fighting.
Is fighting a bad thing?
It always happens in dramas.
People throw drinks in each other's faces and such.
Been there, done that...
Eh, really?
- Well then…
- Guess it's up to democracy.
Who thinks we should go for it?
Who thinks we should sit this one out?
I see.
We discussed it together, and we think that it's a bit too early for us.
We're not ready yet.
Understood.
I’ll inform them of your decision.
Sorry for the trouble.
Miura-san, what do you think?
Nina.
Honestly, I wasn't sure.
At first, I thought that while winning would be difficult,
challenging DiaDust would become great publicity for you.
Then why-
But I realized that if they win by a significant margin,
TogeToge could get stuck with the stigma of being an unpopular band.
Which is exactly what they're aiming for?
Whether their intent was to boost us both, or pull the rug under us...
I can see both being true.
I honestly don't know which it really is.
I'm exhausted…
Guess there will always be ulterior motives, huh.
We're in the adults' world now.
What is it?
Do you still think it was worth a shot?
I was just wondering if being a pro means it'll always be like this.
You're the one who chose this path.
We're back.
This part's still bothering me...
Let's try going back to how it was before then.
No, that one was kinda off too...
At this point it'll be faster to just start from scratch.
I guess that works too.
Eh, are you sure?
Are you stuck on this part again?
Yep. I don't know, it just sounds a bit old-fashioned.
You think? I guess it would be trendy to put in some key changes there...
Like this?
Yeah, just like that.
Momoka-san.
What?
You're overthinking it.
I feel like you're straying further and further from the original idea.
I mean, it's supposed to be a song about us, right?
Maybe it's already great as it is.
The important thing is whether it really feels like "our" song.
I think that feeling would be more than enough.
I'll see you tomorrow then. Good work.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me!
Yes?
I want to accept DiaDust's challenge after all.
I know there's a lot that should go into that decision.
But it's also a chance to have our very own concert.
- To play our songs.
- I guess you can put it that way, but-
Then we should just go for it!
Whatever the reason,
I don't think we should run away from an opportunity to sing.
If we run away...
It'll be the same as losing?
Yeah.
Are you still against it, Momoka-san?
You should be the one to decide.
You have the strongest connection to Diamond Dust, after all.
I assume you all agree?
What will it be?
It's cold...
Really? Feels pretty warm to me.
Yeah, feels like a normal autumn day if anything.
What? That's a northerner for you...
My legs are naked here!
You wanted to be a high school girl.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sheesh.
This is Nina's neighborhood, right?
And why are we at a shrine?
I just thought it's a good time to visit.
In other words, you just want to ask the gods for something.
Yep, that tracks.
Momoka-san, did you ever do a New Year's shrine visit with DiaDust?
Nah, never.
We never really had the time, and it wasn't really my thing.
I see.
But right now we need all the help we can get, from gods or otherwise.
If they even exist.
What's wrong, Momoka-san?
You're always on edge lately.
Oh, that?
I just can't finish the song prop-
Liar.
I want you to be honest with us.
I'm scared, okay?
The more I get serious about songwriting,
the more my past anxiety starts affecting me.
I'm afraid of losing everything again.
I knew it.
I knew you were suffering.
We were all alone in this world, weren't we?
But we had music.
And even now, your passion still lives in me.
It's what led me to all of you.
I believe in this feeling, in this song!
So you should believe in yourself too.
I want to write the story of Togenashi Togeari.
To chase the same dream together, with all five of us.
I believe in the god of rock.
Would be nice if he existed.
If he did exist, what would you ask him for?
To sell a million CDs, what else?
Let's go all-out then, ten million!
We can do better, a hundred million!
I'll wish for...winning against Diamond Dust.
Momoka-san.
What is it?
And that's the final version.
What do you think? Any suggestions?
Seems good to me.
Yeah. It's probably the easiest to understand too.
I like it as well.
I try not to throw around my own opinion too much.
I see.
But if I'm completely honest, I really like this version.
It feels like it has everything you wanted in it.
After watching you for these few weeks,
I feel like this song truly represents you.
Really?
It was a pleasure working on it.
Working with bands like yours
really makes me feel happy with my job.
I mean it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much, Tanaka-san!
I'm Nakata.
Well then, I will contact you once we have decided on the mixing date.
When will it be released online?
If all goes well, it's scheduled for early next month.
I'll be off then.
I like it too.
I really believe it's going to be a hit.
Miura-san!
What is it?
Thank you for everything!
Thank you for everything.
Save your thanks for later. We're just getting started.
See you.
S-so cold...
Alright then.
God of rock,
A billion views please...no, even just ten thousand is fine.
Please.
Come on, please, please...
103 VIEWS
But how...
Next up : "Rock'N'Roll Never Dies"