With end-of-year cleaning finished,
all that's left is to welcome in the new year.
Cleaning a house that size was quite the challenge.
Sorry about that.
You were a huge help.
It was my pleasure. Don't worry.
All the stores around here will be closed to start next year,
so we'd better do our shopping now.
You can leave the carrying to me.
Gracious me, your nose is so keen—
you're not even through the door and you've already noticed
(I'm home!)
Now here you come, scampering down the hallway, out of breath
Tonight we're having your favorite
You've been craving this—that I know
(Yeah, this is it!)
Now just add you and it'll be perfect
We've been waiting for you with this feast
I am an Apron Boy!
Apron Boy!
Show off your skills, man of virtue!
I am an Apron Boy!
Apron Boy!
Your smile's my greatest dish
Our home sweet home is filled with laughter!
The living room's a wonderland!
You're already drooling so take your washed hands and...
Are you ready?
(Are you ready?)
Thank you for this food!
It caught my eye, and...
Well, dinner's a long way off.
It's probably fine.
Indeed. It's quite good, Shirou.
Shirou, it seems busier than usual here.
Yeah.
We all have the same things to do, after all.
So they're all preparing for New Year's Eve?
What's up, Saber?
What exactly does one do on New Year's Eve?
Well, we follow traditions for celebrating the new year.
Come on in!
We put New Year's bamboo decorations like the one I made at the front gate
Red and White Mirror Mochi
(Set of 5)
and set up offerings of Mirror Mochi.
Red and White Mirror Mochi
(Set of 5)
Oh yeah, we eat Osechi too.
Osechi!
I know of Osechi.
Saber-chan, you've got to eat Osechi!
Taiga told me about it the other day.
It's the dish where various types of food are put into a box, right?
That's right.
The beans, herring roe, fishcakes, and other stuff you put in each hold a specific meaning.
For instance, the beans are
a prayer for good health so you can work diligently.
mame
I see! A very fitting dish for New Year's Eve.
I would love to have some.
Yep, that will come tomorrow.
But before that, tonight's dinner will be...
Shinshuu Soba
This!
We're home!
Oh hey, it's Shirou. Welcome home!
So, this kotatsu...
I brought it!
How long have you been loafing away in there?
This is why I didn't set one up.
Shirou, once you get in this thing you can't leave.
It's as if there's magecraft being cast on me.
Even Illya?
Fuji-nee, I did the shopping.
Come help me with this.
Regrettably, as Onee-chan will be very busy paying respects to important people tomorrow,
she is in charging mode today.
Let me tell you right now:
I'm amazing on New Year's Day!
How's that?
New Year's Day is the only time Fuji-nee shines.
What do you mean by "only"?
Taiga in a kimono?
That would be something to see.
Oh yeah, will you wear one too, Saber-chan?
How about you, Illya?
Remember that kimono you wore?
Oh, those clothes.
I liked them.
Saber, could you help me—
Even Saber's stuck in there now.
There's only one thing we could possibly eat tonight.
The kaeshi is already done.
The base for the Soba stock is called Kaeshi.
Put mirin in the pot, bring it to a boil and reduce the alcohol.
Lower the heat, put in granulated sugar and wait for it to dissolve.
Add soy sauce.
Increase heat slowly so as to prevent burning.
When the sauce foams up on the edges
and white froth appears on the surface, turn off the heat and skim it out.
Leave it to cool, and you're done.
Now for this kombu I started soaking yesterday.
For use in stock, put kombu kelp that you've marinated in water into the pot,
and then take it out right before it boils.
Lower the heat, then put in the katsuobushi.
Leave it for 30-40 minutes.
Put it through a cloth strainer afterwards and the stock is done.
Cut the negi into thin slices.
Steam the komatsuna and cut it into bite sized pieces.
Cut the fishcakes into slices around 8mm wide.
Now for the tempura.
Remove the shrimp's shell and digestive tract.
Cut the tip of the tail in order to let out moisture.
Roll them in salt, starch, and a bit of sake.
Next is the batter for the coating.
Scramble the eggs in some cold water,
then add flour and stir.
Coat the shrimp, and fry it in 170°C to 180°C oil.
Get over here!
Combine the stock and kaeshi and add seasoning.
Cook the soba noodles a bit on the firm side,
then run it under cold water and shake it off.
Warm the soba with hot water and pour the broth.
Tempura shrimp,
komatsuna, fishcakes, negi,
some yuzu zest on the top...
Right.
Year-End Soba is served!
This is definitely the thing to have on New Years.
Year-End Soba?
Is it different from normal soba?
Yeah.
Does this perhaps hold some meaning, as Osechi does?
Soba is easier to cut than other types of noodles,
so it signifies cutting away the misfortunes of the year.
Its length and slenderness are symbolic of long life and health as well.
I see.
Then may eating this grant us all good health.
Thank you for this food!
Two shrimp? How luxurious!
I love this soup.
I'm going to Ryuudou Temple, anyone else?
Then I will accompany you, Shirou.
What about you two?
Don't want to leave the kotatsu.
I'll stay here.
I'll be going there tomorrow when I'm doing my work.
Just go without us.
Have a good trip.
I hope Issei will be okay.
They get jammed packed on New Year's.
Ryuudou Temple does?
Yeah, loads of people will come to pray.
To pray...
Is there a specific way to pray?
Hm, I suppose there is.
But don't worry, it's not that complicated.
Then if you would teach me the method, I will be sure to follow it perfectly.
Saber.
Year End Soba has a bunch of different meanings, but...
Well, one of them is this.
Yes?
"May you long be at my side."
...or so they say.
Well, it just popped into my head.
Um, well, anyway...
I look forward to our next year, Saber.
I do as well, Shirou.
When I smell a scent that fits right in with the scorched-red dusk,
I wonder "What will we be having today?" and gain a spring in my step
I still have so much to learn, and I've been so busy learning it,
But at least at times like this I want to take it easy
From where I smell a delicious aroma, I hear the sound of laughing voices
That I have a place among them makes me happier than anything else could
Every time I blink, a new frame of this scene is before me
My desire to remember each one and a feeling of bliss fill me to the brim
Every time I recall them, they'll slip down my throat and seep into my drained heart
These warm memories,
Forever and ever