When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
It was a Christmas present!
Hayate Ayasaki, a totally
unremarkable high school student,
found that his parents had very
considerately made arrangements
to have him taken in by some
"very generous people" folk!
However, he has a fateful
encounter in the park!
I don't really get it, but you saved me.
You scoundrels! Give that
girl back without a fuss!
I will make him Nagi Sanzenin's new butler!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
I will make him Nagi Sanzenin's new butler!
Why did you just repeat yourself?
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
A New Beginning with Nagi Sanzenin's Estate
Huh? Where am I?
Are you done already?
Are you done with your life already?
P-Please, Mr. Santa, you're
talking as if I'm dead...
You did die.
What?
You were a bright red spectacle,
which couldn't be shown on TV.
I see.
But if that's the case,
I guess I'm done then.
I don't have family who would mourn me anyway
and there's no home for
me to go back to, either.
Oh-ho...
Pretending like you're a tragic hero,
when you're a despicable kidnapper?
And while it may have
been in your imagination,
you hit me in the last episode, too.
Don't you forget.
It may have been a failed attempt,
but what you did was more than
enough to charge you as a criminal.
I-I apologize! I apologize! I
feel bad about it! I'm sorry!
I'm... sorry...
Huh? Where am I?
All this luxury... Gotta be
impossible in this world, right?
Which means, this has
to be Heaven, after all.
Or possibly, because I was poor...
Yes, it must be a vision,
a near-death experience,
created by my subconscious!
Thank you, Mr. Santa!
I'm going to enjoy this to the fullest!
Our protagonist's a dumb guy. Sorry.
Well, he certainly did
hit his head pretty hard,
but his life is not in any danger.
Likely, he works out on a regular basis.
Well, if anything else comes
up, please let me know.
Maria, I'm thinking of making that boy...
Making Hayate the replacement for Himegami.
What? Um, I'm not sure I follow...
Well, partially, because that's
what my savior requested, but...
How do I put this? That is..
He confessed having feelings
for me in the park.
Very passionately...
He said something about
wanting to take me away...
I-I see...
At any rate, call me right
away when Hayate wakes up.
I'm counting on you!
What could be going on here?
This will require verification
on a number of counts...
But before I do that...
Great Bath
Well, well! That's my dream for you!
This is luxury, the likes of which
I never even saw in my lifetime!
But if this is Heaven, dying isn't so bad.
Though, being all by myself
is a little lonely.
Th-The water's fine, isn't it?
R-Relaxing, isn't it?
What's relaxing got to do with anything?
Is this really a dream?
Wh-What's that scarf girl doing here?
Um...
Y-Yes?
You really must be physically tough...
Huh?
I mean, your life may not be in
danger, but to be taking a bath...
Normally, your wounds would reopen.
The bath was dyed!
It was dyed by the bright red bath elixir
that burst forth from Hayate's body!
Please get a hold of yourself!
Are you all right?!
Oh, a shooting star!
Wait, no, no!
We're not even done with
half of the first part!
Here's a fan service scene as an apology!
Are you awake, Hayate Ayasaki?
You were in the bath earlier...
The whole time!
You've been asleep the whole time
since you were brought here,
but are you all right?
I was asleep the whole time?
Of course! You were asleep the whole time!
I see.
Then I guess that really was a dream.
Oh, but... How did you know my name already?
Or rather, where am I?
Well...
This is the Sanzenin estate belonging
to Miss Nagi, whom you saved.
I... saved?
Th-That girl?!
And I am someone who looks after her.
My name is Maria.
And, I felt bad about it,
but I looked at this.
You seem to be in quite a terrible situation.
N-No, it's not that big a deal...
By the way, I'd like to
ask you about something.
That is... About the incident
concerning the Miss at the park...
Sh-She knows?!
You apparently said something
about taking her away?
Um, that is... I-I apologize!
I'll never think of kidnapping anyone again!
What?
Huh?
I see.
I understand the general
gist of your situation.
So um... I don't know how I
should make up for that...
Oh, but well, people do lie out
of necessity sometimes, so...
Ah! What's this? Awake already?
How are you feeling?
Y-Yes, I'm fine now.
Thank you very much for being so good to me.
But I'm sorry.
I asked for such a crazy
favor of you in the park.
Out of a desire for 156,804,000
yen of ransom money.
Well, it surprised me, but...
That is... I didn't find it unpleasant.
It was her very first romantic
confession, after all.
Even though it's a misunderstanding.
It's only that, we don't
know each other very well,
so I don't think it's good
to rush into things...
S-So I gave it some thought after that!
You were looking for live-in work, right?
What?
Then why don't you work as
my butler at this house?
Wow...
A butler?
Uh, um, Miss? Perhaps you
should make such offers...
...only after you have a good
grasp of his circumstances...
But we do need a replacement for Himegami.
Besides, Hayate is certifiably tough.
See, even after a car went
"wham!" and ran into him,
he was still alive and kicking!
I-I tried to kidnap her, but
not only is she forgiving me,
she's even offering me live-in work?
What a... What a kindhearted little kid.
Thank you, Mr. Santa.
So this is the very first present
you've given me, isn't it?
Uh, i-it's not really like that...
B-But Hayate doesn't even
know what a butler does...
I'll do it!
What?
Please leave it to me, Miss!
No matter what happens,
I, Hayate Ayasaki, will put my life
on the line and protect you, Miss!
Y-You fool! Do not say such embarrassing
things in front of Maria!
Wh-What am I going to do with these
two clueless people? Honestly!
What did you say? A new butler?
Certainly, as the head butler, I would
like a replacement for Himegami, but...
What kind of person is this
boy named Hayate Ayasaki?
Well, let me think...
He's the kind of boy who can ride a bicycle
and catch up to a car
careening along at 120 km/h
and then be perfectly fine when
he gets run over like trash.
Maria, what Gundam is this?
That's the kind of toughness
you see in giant robots.
No, Mr. Klaus, he's still technically human.
Besides, Gundams aren't giant
robots, they're mobi...
I-I see, so Gundams aren't giant robots.
I have been studying anime night and day
to be on the same wavelength
as the Miss, but...
It was but a youthful mistake.
You seem to have quite a good
grasp of the subject, though...
So, what about the matter concerning Hayate?
At any rate, such a person cannot
serve as a butler in this household.
Send him home.
But you see...
Please take care of it.
Wow!
How is the size?
Yes, it's perfect.
I'm glad to hear that.
It was worth my time to make the
alterations last night then.
What? You did this?
Then, shall we get to work?
Y-Yes!
Um, so... What will I be doing?
Hmm, let me think.
It's the end of the year,
so I suppose the first priority
is thorough cleaning.
Mr. Klaus told me to send him away,
but that would be somewhat
heartless, wouldn't it...?
Cleaning, huh?
Even I can do that much.
If I get fired from this job,
I won't be able to pay
back the 156,804,000 yen.
Nor will I have a place to live.
That's right. My new life is
going to begin, here, today!
Yes, as a butler of the Sanzenin household.
Don't steal other people's lines.
Commercial break.
I love you.
(Suki)
I hate you.
(Kirai)
That's right. My new life is
going to begin, here, today!
As a butler of the Sanzenin household!
I got to say it myself this time!
Oh, Nagi, good morning.
Ah, you two. Morning.
Please take a look, Miss!
Maria made alterations to this outfit for me!
Well, see that you work hard.
I-I feel like she suddenly
became cold towards me...
Oh, I don't know. If anything,
I feel like she's too fired up.
Well, whatever the case,
I will regain the Miss's trust with my work!
What? Uh, um...
Look at that enthusiasm.
I was told to send him away, but...
And how should I clear up the
misunderstanding with Nagi?
My attitude earlier wasn't good.
That was just too petty of me.
If only I could do needlework like Maria!
What do you think, Hayate?
It's incredible, Miss!
Hayate...
Miss...
Miss.
Miss!
Ah, Maria. Where's Hayate?
He's helping out with the cleaning.
He is brimming with enthusiasm.
I-I see.
He is apparently going to
work hard to gain your trust.
If you have something on your mind,
perhaps you should speak with him in person.
Y-You're right!
It's important to start by talking
to each other a lot, right?!
Yes.
I'm going to go see Hayate for a bit!
Go and gently clear up
the misunderstanding now!
Maria, I'd like you to check my work.
Oh... Is something the matter?
No, just thinking that you two
are thoroughly out of synch.
Somehow...
...everything looks really clean.
Does it? Thank you very much.
Very meticulous, even down
to the small details...
What's this?
Oh, that knob was made of silver, so
I polished it with a silver duster.
For this bronze bust, I got the
grime off with a brass brush,
then washed it with a mild neutral detergent.
After getting rid of the moisture,
I applied a finishing coat of wax.
The carpeting was woolen kilim,
so instead of hot water, I added
some shampoo to cold water and...
Wait, um, did I do something wrong?
No, I'm honestly surprised.
Or rather, I'm impressed.
Well, I've been lying about
my age since I was 8,
working part-time cleaning jobs
to pay for my parents' booze bill.
So cleaning is actually a specialty of mine!
Mr. Klaus, I'm sorry.
There is no reason we
should send Hayate away.
In a way, it seems Nagi's judgment
of his character was right.
But this estate sure is huge!
I wonder how many rooms there are to clean.
Study
The study?
Oh? This room feels pretty lived in.
Notebook
Nagi
What's this?
The Miss's school notebook, maybe?
Wha?!
Th-This is...!
A picture diary?
It's a manga.
N-No, no, I mustn't look
at anything so private.
Hey!
What are you looking at in
my room without permission?!
M-Miss! No, th-this is... well...
Th-That is my...
P-Please don't worry! I hardly read
any of it! Hardly any of your...
...picture diary!
Pi... Pi... Picture diary?!
You idiot!
What? Miss?
Shut up! See if I care about you ever again!
You don't even know what I'm feeling!
Hayate, you idiot! Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Miss...
Just get out!
Rear
Farewell, my tranquil life.
It was short-lived, but thank you.
Rear
Sanzenin
So we finally meet again...
...sonny boy.
Oh, hello there...
Take that! And that!
Are you sure about this?
Huh? About what?
Hayate has really left...
In a black pumpkin carriage...
Huh?
Wh-What?!
The End
H-Hey! The second half
isn't over yet, either!
Indeed.
Are you all right with leaving it like this?
I-I only told him to get out of my room.
I never thought he would leave the estate...
It's because you don't put
away your precious possessions
that things like this happen.
It cannot be helped.
Let us just forget about Hayate.
If you are through with him, Miss,
there's no longer any
reason to keep him here.
That's... well...
If you've grown to hate Hayate, maybe
this is actually for the better.
No, I mean, it's not like I hate him...
It's not?
Well, regardless, Hayate saved my life.
Forsaking one's savior...
...is something I can never do as
a member of the Sanzenin family.
Um, Mr. Very Generous People,
sirs, just where are we?
The emigration desk.
Wharf Warehouse
Huh?
Oh, I'm so happy! I've got unpaid
volunteer work to look forward to!
I'm never coming back to Japan again!
Rather, we won't be able to come back.
Wh-What should I do?! At this
rate, my fate will be...
Man
First, off on a cruise with
everyone else on a luxury liner!
But during our voyage, we'll
be attacked by pirates,
and for some reason, I'll
be recruited to join them!
After becoming a wanted man,
I'll ultimately be cornered by sea monkeys,
my dreams of becoming the
Pirate King will end in vain,
and I'll end up dying in
the grand cross-shaped sea!
Um, I just remembered something I have to do.
Eh?
L-Let go!
Don't you worry.
We've got a luxury liner all lined up, too.
S-Someone, help!
Bro!
Can't show you!
That hurts!
Bro, a-anything but blood!
Want me to save you?
Please hang in there!
That voice... Could it be...?
We can't put this on TV!
Miss...
WRONG!
My name is Na...
Can't show you!
Uh, no, wrong. Um... Masked... Mask...
Right! Mask the Money!
I came here at the request
of some girl named Nagi.
R-Right...
So I have a message for you from her.
Well, she said, "S-Sorry for
yelling at you earlier."
And that was, um...
Hayate, she wanted you to know that!
A-Also, the contents of
the notebook you saw...
...is something she considers a masterpiece,
a manga called "End of the Century
Legend – Magical Destroy" and...
I-It is by no means a picture diary!
Y-Yes, I understand.
Um, Mask the Money.
Good! If you understand,
then please continue
working as a butler there.
That will make her happy, too... I think.
I will.
There's no way that's gonna happen.
This guy's got a 156,804,000 yen
debt that his parents left him!
He's got to pay it all back.
Are you referring to this?
What of this scrap of paper?
I told you to shut up! Didn't
you hear me, you baldy?!
You damn brat...
D-Don't you lay a single finger on her!
You sound so high and mighty.
Then let's see you repay the
156,804,000 yen in full this minute!
I'll do that.
Repaid in full.
No way!
Is that all real...?
Of course, you fool!
We don't have a problem anymore, do we?
Bro.
All right, we're out of here.
Now, you just have to
get him to pay you back.
Mask the Money.
When you see the Miss, please let her know.
That I will work to repay her, without fail.
And also, that I look forward
to continue being her butler.
But she meant that money
as a free gift to you.
I-I couldn't possibly! I'd feel bad
if I don't work to pay her back!
Especially when she came to my
rescue in a silly mask like that.
Needless to say, the girl
thought it looked cool!
So, that money...
You will work to pay it back!
Debts really should be kept clear
or it won't be good for justice!
So you work like a pack horse
and repay every last yen to
your lender, Nagi Sanzenin!
Uh, yes, of course.
I am never... NEVER letting you
off the hook for a single yen!
Humph!
Your mask's fallen off, Mask the Money!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
They appear to have begun fighting.
D-D-D-Do not look at me!
Oh, r-right.
I think that's all right, though.
Don't look yet!
I understand.
They're like brother and sister.
Do you really understand?!
You really haven't looked, right?!
Don't look!
I apologize!
It's snowing.
And thus, their Christmas came to an end.
However, spring is still far away.
One crisis after another.
In the next episode,
he'll be fighting the show's animal mascot,
as well as a 21st century
household appliance.
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
Preview
Such a poor-looking boy,
who seems unlikely to ever
have any luck with money!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
I am absolutely against
hiring him as a butler!
What did you say?!
If you have a problem with Hayate's
strength or qualifications,
why not give him an evaluation test?
An evaluation test?
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Beast, the Robot, and the Butler that
Shouted or Maybe Didn't Shout Love..."
"...at the Heart of the World".
The Beast, the Robot, and the Butler that Shouted
or Maybe Didn't Shout Love at the Heart of the World
It'll be fine! Knowing you,
Hayate, you'll manage somehow!
The Red Lion's gonna roar!
Please watch "Hayate the Combat
Butler" again next time.