Yuki-senpai's handmade graduation album
Graduation Album
included the day I met all of them,
my days holed up in the department store,
my time with Kei... and our farewell.
Senpai and her friends came and saved me,
and took me back to their school.
All this happened before I joined the club.
So I'm really hoping she'll
decide to join the club.
Yeah, exactly!
A voice...
Her uniform's the same as ours,
so she must be a student here, right?
Then we'd have another new friend!
It'll be fine. Just leave it all to me!
Right? You agree with me,
don't you, Taroumaru?
That's...
Good morning.
School Living Club
Graduation Album
#6
Welcome
Still not feeling well?
Go and get her some water for now.
Oh! Good idea.
Want some water?
Y-Yes, please...
Okay!
This is... the school?
Here.
Drink up.
Thank you.
So, um, you're also a student
at Megurigaoka, then?
Oh, that's right. We haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
Correct!
I'm Takeya Yuki of Megurigaoka
High School's Class 3-C!
And I'm Sakura Megumi,
a teacher here at Megurigaoka...
No way... You're in your third year?
Yup! I sure am!
I'm being ignored already?
What about you?
I'm Naoki Miki, from Class 2-B.
That makes me your senpai!
She's really older than me?
U-Um... Where exactly are we?
The School Living Club's club room.
You know, that doesn't explain anything.
You need to tell her we're actually at school.
Oh, sorry, Megu-nee.
"Megu-nee" again? You know better.
Yes, Sakura-sensei!
I'll give you this as an apology.
Thank you. Hey, this bottle's half empty!
This is our school, Megurigaoka High!
The school...
It's really...
the school.
Anyway...
Oh, you're here, too.
Taroumaru!
That's right! He's the one that led us to you.
Taroumaru... I see.
Um... I...
I don't think he likes me.
Um... I know, Yuki-chan.
Since it's been such a long time,
why not show her around the school?
Yeah! Great idea, Megu-nee.
C'mon.
Let's go, Mii-kun!
Mii-kun?
You left the door open...
It's okay. Megu-nee's still in there.
Music Room
We'll start here. This is the music room.
I know that.
I used to be a student here, you know.
I wonder if the band is in here.
Band practice?!
Did nothing happen at the school?
Oh, it's empty.
It's all clear, Mii-kun. Come on in!
Or was it all...
just a dream?
See?
Isn't it great?
We've got all kinds of instruments.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Yeah, it really is great.
It wasn't a dream.
Go on. If you don't explain properly,
she won't understand.
You're right, Megu-nee.
If you join the School Living Club,
we can come here after school
and sing all we want!
School Living Club?
So? What do you think?
I think it's a waste of electricity.
No way!
How can you say that with Beethoven,
Bach, and Mozart all watching you?
I really don't care.
Wh-What do I do, Megu-nee?
Anyway, this is heavy. You hold it.
I can't! It really is heavy!
Can we just go now, Yuki-senpai?
Yuki-senpai
Yuki-senpai.
Senpai.
Senpai
C-Can you... say that again?
Can we just go now, Yuki-senpai?
Moved
You're creeping me out.
I was just thinking "Senpai" has a nice ring to it.
You've always wanted people to call
you that, haven't you, Yuki-chan?
Then act more like a proper upperclassman.
You're so strict, Mii-kun.
Why do you keep calling me Mii-kun?
Your name's Miki, so you're Mii-kun!
You don't like it?
I prefer Miki.
Oh?
Don't you think Mii-kun's cuter?
I don't need to be cute.
But you are, Mii-kun.
You agree, right, Megu-nee?
Don't push the issue, Yuki-chan.
Megu-nee, you don't think she's cute?
Of course I do, but that's not the issue.
Um... I don't really understand
anything you've been saying.
Huh?
Can I ask a question?
Who is
"Megu-nee"?
Huh?
Yuki left the door open again.
Hey, Yuki, you left the door open!
Wait... Huh?
Yuki and that girl are gone...
Music Room
Um, Mii-kun, what are you saying?
Oh, no, of course not, Megu-nee.
No one said you might as well be nonexistent.
Don't get so sad, Megu-nee!
That was mean, Mii-kun.
I know Megu-nee doesn't
have much of a presence,
but it's not like she's totally invisible.
Sorry! I meant it in a good way!
You lack presence in a good way!
U-Um... Well...
Tell her, Mii-kun.
Say, "You don't lack presence at all, Megu-nee."
Um...
Tell Megu-nee you know she's here!
Yuki!
School Living Club
So anyway, just surviving was starting
to make us horribly depressed,
so we decided to act like an
extracurricular club that's lodging here.
And that's your School Living Club?
Megu-nee and Rii-san came up
with it after things calmed down.
About this Megu-nee person...
She was our teacher.
She was always positive,
always concerned for her students...
She was a wonderful teacher.
Where is she now?
She's gone.
Megu-nee always protected us.
Even on that day.
Let me go!
Yuki-chan, stop it!
Megu-nee's still outside! We have to hurry!
It's too late!
Megu-nee, Megu-nee!
Wait!
Megu-nee! Open the door, Megu-nee!
Megu-nee! Megu-nee!
So that's what happened.
But Yuki-senpai was talking to her
as if she were right there next to her.
What's going on?
Yuki can still see her.
Like a ghost?
No, not like that.
In her mind, the incident never happened.
So even now, she still attends classes.
And in her mind, Megu-nee's still alive.
I see.
I hope she gets better soon.
Miki-san, I have a favor to ask.
May I?
What is it?
As long as you're here, will you
please play along with her?
But if we do that, she'll never recover.
It isn't about whether or not she recovers.
This is different.
I'm sure you don't understand just yet.
How is it different?
H-Hang on!
Calm down, you two. Okay?
All right.
I'll play along until I understand
Yuki-senpai better.
That'll be enough, right?
Welcome back!
Thanks.
I've been waiting for you guys!
Hurry up and take your seats!
What? What's going on?
So, what is it?
Everyone!
Let's have a sports meet!
Oh.
A sports meet?
Playing sports together will
make things more fun!
And Mii-kun will join us, too! Right?
Games?
It's not a game! It's a club function!
Club function?
Now, Yuki-chan.
Miki-san doesn't know.
Oh, right.
School Living Club regulation number five!
Club members must participate
in all school events!
That is why...
We'll have a sports meet!
Pose!
I don't understand.
Get it?
Aren't there other things we should be doing?
Better to do what you want
than what you must!
You're talking like a slacker!
I think it's a good opportunity.
It's your chance to get to know Yuki better.
I understand.
That's true.
Yay!
Red
Red Team
Opening Ceremony
Are
you
okay?
Great Mini-Basketball Tournament
Red Team
Mii-kun!
(Cries)
Don't
call
me
that.
Winners
Loser
Here.
Thank you.
Working up a sweat like this
feels pretty good, doesn't it?
Yes... I had fun.
I don't know how she does it, but Yuki
always comes up with this stuff
right when we need it the most.
Same with the trip to the mall.
She just declared that we
should go on a club outing.
I thought it was crazy, too.
It really came out of nowhere.
But I'm glad we went.
Thinking things out is important,
but if you do nothing but think,
you'll never move forward.
Do nothing but think...
Of course, there are times when just
getting some exercise wouldn't help.
And when it seems like both thinking
and acting get us nowhere,
Yuki gives us the answer.
Maybe you're right.
Food always tastes the best
after a good workout.
Agreed!
We've got enough for seconds.
Delicious...
Isn't it yummy, Megu-nee?
Oh, it's fine.
I wonder why...
I thought Yuki-senpai and
Megu-nee were so weird at first.
Just eating this much isn't
gonna change anything now.
I meant it in a good way!
But right now, I'm glad they're here.
You want to be holed up in that
room forever, just staying alive?
Yeah... All we did back then was not die.
Hey, so how was today?
Did you have fun?
I don't know about fun. It made me dizzy.
R-Really?
There's never a dull moment living with Yuki!
It's always lively here.
She's better at getting into
trouble than Taroumaru, though.
What was that?
I'm glad I came.
Nothing.
Mii-kun
Want seconds?
Yes, please.
Wh-What is it?
Nothing...
You're a more amazing senpai than I realized.
Huh?
You're amazing. Really amazing.
You think I'm amazing?
Actually, nah.
What?!
Hm?
Um...
Do you have a moment?
There's something I really need to say.
May I please join the School Living Club?
Even if it's just on a trial basis.
I want to get to know Yuki-senpai better.
We'd be glad to have you.
Welcome to the School Living Club.
Opening Ceremony
There.
Wow, it's looking nice!
Miki-san wasn't a club member at that point.
Yes, you were there, too.
Done!
Let's make lots of memories together!
Next time!!
We did it, Megu-nee! A new member!
"Senpai," huh... I love how that sounds!
Yeah! Makes me sound awesome, right?
Next time on Episode 7 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "A Letter."
#7
A Letter
Right, Megu-nee?