Who'll win in the end, do you think?
The Desert Apostles, or those Precure?
I care not.
My, my.
All I seek is to heighten my own strength.
Defeating the Precure is but a part of that.
It's that simple.
I see.
And all I seek is the pursuit of greater beauty.
Then do as you wish.
Of course. Such is my intent.
Dark Precure.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
What are you doing?
You're acting shuper weird!
We're imitating Yuri!
Imitating me?
What on earth for?
You're just so cool and mature!
Even just watering the flowers, you move with such delicacy and grace.
Exactly!
I wish I was that graceful.
You really think so?
It's not something I do consciously, I assure you.
Thank you all for your help.
It looks lovely!
Time to eat!
Someone's outside.
They ran off.
Who could it have been?
What's this?
A love letter?!
Whoa! An actual love letter!
Yuri's Lost at Sea!
We Saw His Love Letter...
I've never seen an honest-to-god love letter before!
It doesn't say who it's from or who it's for.
Should we open it?
I think that would be incredibly impolite.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
Well, we can keep it here at the gardens for the time being.
Huh?
"I've alwaysh loved you ever..."
No, Potpourri!
Why not?
I wanna shee what it saysh!
Okay, let's shee.
"I've alwaysh loved you ever shince we firsht met..."
A-Always l-l-loved them?!
They're very direct, at least.
Yeah...
Wh-What if it's for me?! Oh gosh, I can't deal with this!
It can't be for you.
Huh?
It says "always loved you."
You only moved here in the spring.
It must be for Ichuki!
Because everyone loves Ichuki!
All the girls do, yeah.
It seems Cupid is finally taking a shine to me.
What if it's for Yuri?!
Yeah, don't mind me.
I have to prepare dinner tonight,
so if you'll excuse me.
Where is it?
I know I dropped it around here.
Are you looking for this?
G-Give that back!
Um...
I'm really sorry.
We kind of read your letter.
So, who is it you have a crush on?
Could it be...
me?
Huh?!
I'm not interested in brats like you.
Brats?!
Then...
is it for me?
Wha—?!
Oh, she's a girl, really!
O-Oh, okay.
I thought you were Yuri's boyfriend or something.
Yuri's?
Wait, was that love letter for...
Yuri?!
Hayato, we're really sorry we read your love letter.
It was sort of an accident.
Don't worry! We won't tell Yuri!
So now we've got that out the way, tell us all about it!
What is it you like about Yuri?
Erika...
I'm not telling you!
Why the heck not?
You've always loved her, right?
Jeez!
Can it, Erika!
What'd I do?!
I think I know how you must feel, Hayato.
We all admire Yuri a lot too, in our own way.
So you've known Yuri a long time then, Hayato?
Yeah.
We lived in the same apartments, so we used to play together a lot.
Oh, so that's why.
Hey.
Do you know why Yuri's been so much happier lately?
Well, um...
A lot of different things have happened.
Anyway, it's good that she's happy again, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hayato?
Ever since her dad vanished, Yuri's always been so upset.
I couldn't do anything to cheer her up, either.
I'm just a kid, after all.
Hayato...
But I wanna make sure Yuri never has to feel sad again!
You're a real man, Hayato!
So that's why you wanted to give Yuri that love letter!
Yeah.
In that case, let us help!
Wha—?
We'll set everything up so you can give Yuri your love letter!
It's the least we can do to apologize for reading it.
What do you think?
Okay?
Uh...
Well, uh... sure!
A strategy meeting?
Well, it is true that we need to prepare for the Desert Apostles' next attack.
All right, I'll meet you after school.
Okay!
Y-Yuri...
Hayato!
Testing, testing, do you read me, over?
Loud and clear, over!
It's been a while.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
They're being really awkward, over.
S-So Yuri, what have you been doing lately?
You've seemed really busy.
Lately? Well, I...
It's been hectic.
Why?
Can't you tell me?
I'm sorry. It's... tricky.
What, is it because I'm a kid?
Yuri, I want you to—
Hey, do you remember?
We used to play here all the time.
Playing tag or hide-and-seek...
You always used to fall asleep while you were waiting for me to find you.
That was ages ago!
Really? I remember it like it was just yesterday.
They're talking about when Hayato was younger!
Yuri sheems to be enjoying it,
but Hayato looksh bored, over!
Make them quit the reminiscing, over!
Can you get them to change the subject, over?
You're fairies, right?
Use some miracle magic superpower or something, over!
Don't ask the impossible, over!
I'm so glad you were there for me, Hayato.
I don't have any siblings, so I always thought of you as the younger brother I never had.
I... I don't...
I don't want to be your little brother!
Hayato?!
His heart was stolen by an older girl.
The Flower of his Heart wilts before my very eyes.
Just what I'm looking for.
I shall take the Flower of your Heart!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Love letter!
A Desertrian?!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Why couldn't I have been born a few years earlier?!
I just want to be an adult!
Love me!
Sunflower Aegis!
Letter?
You came!
They turned Hayato into the Desertrian!
Here you are, Precure.
Get them, Desertrian!
Love letter!
Love, love! Letter, letter!
I don't want her to treat me like a little kid!
I don't wanna be Yuri's little brother!
Why, Hayato? Why don't you?
Jeez, you're dense!
Yuri, it's because Hayato is actually—
It's not your place to say it, Marine!
It's up to Hayato to tell Yuri in his own words!
Oh, but that will never happen, I assure you.
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
It's time we finished this once and for all, Precure!
Exquisite!
Kobraja! What is it you're fighting for?!
What am I fighting for?
All I care about is beauty!
But what is beautiful about the human heart?
It falters, it feels pain, and it
gives in to hatred and jealousy!
It possesses not a shred of beauty!
The human heart has no place in the world of wilted hearts,
a world of true beauty that the Desert Apostles shall create!
That is beauty beyond compare.
Not that I would expect you to understand.
Kobraja,
you're totally wrong!
What makes us able to truly appreciate beauty is the very thing you say we don't need!
Our hearts!
The heart is useless!
You disgust me, Precure!
Come on!
Right!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
I can't let them purify me!
Now's our chance!
No way... Dark Precure's back?!
And she's way stronger than before!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry, Hayato.
I just thought of you like a little brother
without realizing how much it upset you.
N-No...
That wasn't what I wanted to say!
I want you to have this!
Th-Thank you.
But I...
It's okay.
I just wanted you to know how I felt.
I'm gonna eat all my veggies, get lots of sleep, and become a big strong adult!
I'll become the kind of man who can make sure you never feel sad again!
Okay.
He's a man! He's a real man, that Hayato!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
In the language of flowers, a cherry means "young love."
Exactly the feelings Hayato has for Yuri.
Well, everyone loves Yuri!
She really is incredible.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Whenever I've felt sad wanted to cry,
my family's smiles have always helped cheer me up.
They mean the world to me.
And now, that family is about to grow a little bigger.
And it's my job to be the best big sister I can for the new baby!
HeartCatch Precure:
Our Family's Growing!
I'm Going to be a Big Sister!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!