It sounds silly,
but I saw it with my own eyes.
A Shadow copying a human!
We gotta tell Shiori!
It's not just a superstition that a Shadow comes to kill the original!
She's in danger!
So Kobayakawa Shiori saw her Shadow, too?
That's bad news.
Let's go to her house now!
But that's all the more reason I can't let Mio walk straight into danger!
Yeah, but I'm going alone.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Drifting Ashore
Koba Mart
So the store's closed after all.
This is bad. Nothing's changed.
Oh my stars!
If it isn't Shinpei!
Shiomi!
I know ya've had a rough couple days.
N-Not at all. G-Good morning.
Ain't no convenience stores on this island.
Must be hell after livin' in Tokyo, huh?
Nah, I like the items they sell here.
They've got green soft serve, too.
The taste of home, eh?
It looks like they're taking the day off.
Now that's odd.
I didn't hear anything about them being closed for the day.
Class 3-1 Kobayakawa Shiori
Anybody home, Koba?
Nothin'. Are they out?
Why, it's open!
Ya in there, Koba?
Are ya sure we can just walk in?
Ain't no bother!
Koba?
What's this? They've gone and left the TV on.
Oh, Koba!
Hey, Koba!
That's strange.
Koba!
Shadows...
This was the work of Shadows.
Totsumura's Shadow did the same thing to the real Totsumura!
Ya imagined the worst, right?
There must've been more ya could do.
The must've been something ya could've done to save 'em.
Idiot! I'm up against monsters here!
I'm fed up with being killed!
All I can do is warn the others and carefully observe the results.
So? What have ya learned from observing this?
The table's full of cold, untouched food.
They must've been attacked last night during dinner.
There are marks, like something hit the floor with immense power.
Lots of them...
What in the world happened here?
Shiomi, I'm gonna go look upstairs!
Sure, thanks!
There were two black stains left behind.
They were big. Adult-sized.
Probably Shiori's parents.
Then where is Shiori?
Hey.
Oh, I get it.
Have you seen a little girl that looks just like you?
Why did you say that yesterday?
The first thing I did during this loop was...
You're staring at me.
Is there something on my face?
Or is there something odd about my body?
That settles it.
Shiori?
The Shadow that was hiding at the funeral was Kobayakawa Shiori all along.
Y-You're talking.
Are you better now?
That was probably the stupidest question that I could've asked at this point.
Ah.
Papa and Mama said to stay quiet.
But my question—
Actually, whatever.
Whether ya answer or not,
I can find out the answer later.
I've been afflicted with the Shadow Sickness.
No...
I've been afflicted all along!
Shinpei!
Whassa matter? Is someone upstairs?
What is it? Yer stomach hurtin'?
No...
Thanks to Shiomi, I managed to survive, I guess.
After Shiomi called the police,
I left the Kobayakawas' residence.
If I let the day go by and do nothing...
There's the lady I was sitting across from on the ferry.
She knows something.
Maybe I can end up saving her now.
This time, I haven't met her yet.
I came to on the dock.
Her giant suitcase makes it seem like she's not just a weekend tourist.
I decided to check the inns on the island.
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Anmin-ya Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Tomarora
Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
Seaside Inn
Uozumi
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
A suit?
Yes. She was wearing a suit and had long, black hair.
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
And she wore glasses.
Remember anyone like that?
Can't say. So many guests comin' in and out every day, y'know?
And...
She had huge... y'know—
Oh, I know the gal!
Yeah, yeah! I remember she visited!
Ya told me when we met this mornin'!
'Member? Y'said she was wearin' glasses and had huge honkers!
Huh?
Nakamura's
Food and Inn
But she's not a guest.
Last night, was it?
She came to our cafe.
You gonna pay a visit to our cafe, too?
In the end, I learned she wasn't staying anywhere.
I couldn't find a trace of her.
Is this the limit of what I can do on my own?
Bistro Kofune
Lunch Specials
Pork Cutlet
Fried Fish
Spaghetti Napolitan
Welcome... in.
Shin, how'd it go?
How was Shiori?
R-Right...
Man!
Welcome!
Totsumura!
It is scorchin'!
Ah!
Hey, Shinpei! What was with that crank call last night?
I ain't seen no fight—
The usual B Lunch Set with an order of fried shrimp and medium-sized rice, right?
Y-Ya know me too well!
What?
Vanished?
All of the Kobayakawas have vanished?
Yeah.
Is that true, Shin?
It is.
I heard ya went inside with Shiomi.
Oh, yeah.
I'll take yer statement later!
I can't believe it.
I just talked to them yesterday.
I know, right?
Well, I can't share any details yet.
But a detective from the mainland will be coming over on the first flight this evening.
Totsumura's reaction is different.
Thank goodness.
It must be because he managed to avoid being killed by a Shadow.
He's the real one!
Oh, yeah!
I got somethin' fer ya.
Here!
Is that Sis's?
What?!
Y'see, Ushio came to me the day before she passed.
She entrusted me with that.
Said if anything were to happen to her, that I should give it to you.
Ushio wanted me to have this?
It's as if she knew...
what was gonna happen to her.
Everything's so intricately intertwined.
Yo, Shinpei!
Sorry, am I early?
Nah, I've been waiting for you.
I can count on him.
I should tell Sou everything.
Summer Time Rendering
So you see, Sou, I...
Ushio was killed by Shiori's Shadow.
That's what yer thinkin'?
Yeah.
The marks on Ushio's neck—
Strangulation.
It could've been possible there.
Is Mio really the next target?
Yeah.
Is there any way to tell the difference between a Shadow and the original?
No...
At least not that I know of.
Oh.
I see. That's a pain.
So basically,
ya could be a Shadow yerself!
Yeah, so could you.
What is this?
What are Shadows?
Calm down, Mio. It'll be all right.
Since they show up on camera, they definitely exist.
They ain't monsters or ghosts!
If they're alive, then they can be dealt with.
Right, Shinpei?
Yeah, true!
Hey, Shin! Why don't we go to Hiruko right now?
Karikiri knows a lot about this island's history.
He might know something about the Shadows!
That's right.
The first thing we also thought of back then was to go to Hiruko.
But we can't!
That thing is lurking near the shrine.
It's too dangerous to get close!
H-How about tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow's the summer festival, dude.
R-Right, the festival...
I knew ya'd forgotten.
Tomorrow's the busiest day of the year for the shrine.
The chief priest's gonna have no time for the likes of us.
No...
The busier it is, the safer it should be.
I convinced them that visiting the shrine during the festival was best.
All right, tomorrow we'll meet up at Kofune at 5 AM.
We should come up with a code.
That way we can tell if we run into one of our Shadows.
Right.
If I say mountains...
I say river?
Idiot! Anyone would say that!
The Tigris–Euphrates...
Let's move away from rivers, Shinpei.
Mesopotamian culture!
That's it, Mio!
Is this really gonna work?
Thanks, Sou.
For believing me.
It's nothin'.
Why wouldn't I, man?
Ya trusted me enough to tell me in the first place.
I still don't fully trust him.
Not as long as we have no way of telling a Shadow from the original.
Man, I'm such a buzzkill!
Yeah.
Also, there's something I want to look into.
If I learn anything, I'll give you a call.
Sheesh! I'm gettin' soaked!
The forecast didn't say anything about rain!
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
7/24/2018
Hey, Shin.
Huh?
Shin, how long are ya gonna stay on the island?
Oh, right.
With the funeral over, I was thinkin' of leavin' soon, but now...
It'd be nice if ya could stay forever.
Forever?
Not literally.
I just felt like sayin' it.
Forget it! Forget it!
Here! Hold out yer hand!
This is fer ya.
Sis was wearin' it till the end.
It'd probably make her happy to know ya had it.
Thanks.
Her birthday...
Input password
Password incorrect
July 24th
Not it, huh?
Mountains!
Huh?
Yer supposed ta say Mesopotamian culture!
Oh, is it that time already?
Wh-What a buzzkill.
That's definitely the real Shinpei!
Shinpei! Please put on yer pants!
Whoa! S-Sorry, Toki!
Hurry and get changed.
Everyone's waitin' for ya!
Right, Mio?
Wh-Whaddya think?
I ain't never wore a Yukata before...
I...
I think ya look super great!
Whatcha think?
I asked Tokiko to dress her up!
It was somethin' I came up with to tell her and the fake apart!
G-Good thinking.
I haven't told Tokiko anything yet.
Yeah, that's probably a good idea.
By the way, what was it ya wanted to look into yesterday?
Did ya learn anything?
Oh, that...
It was nothin' special!
Forget about it!
C'mon, enough lip-flappin'. Let's go!
Ushio's probably bored stiff.
Huh?
Yeah.
She was really looking forward to the festival.
It wouldn't be strange for her to be hanging around.
Then let's get a move on! For her sake.
Sou...
Yer lookin' to become a doctor, ain't ya?
What're ya doin, spoutin' this unscientific crap?
Hito Shrine
Welcome! We're Gyokurin-en!
Green Soft Serve     1 Cone    180 yen
Green Tea            1 Cup     100 yen
Hey, Sou.
Hm?
It's been two years since I left the island.
I thought I'd become a little more of a grown-up.
But I'm powerless.
I wasn't there for her when it really mattered.
Even though I promised to protect her.
Idiot!
It's not yer fault Ushio's gone!
Get yer head outta yer ass, Shinpei!
The one ya gotta protect now is Mio!
Yer her brother, ain't ya?!
I-I don't need ya to tell me that!
If ya can't cut it, then I'll take care of Mio fer ya.
Welcome! We're Gyokurin-en!
Sou,
do ya still have feelings for...
What? Ya got a problem with that?
Whatcha talkin' about?
Uh... um! Er—
We were discussin' which we like better, butts or boobs!
Hey!
Wow, I'll stay out of this...
Ya got it all wrong!
Shinpei, yer ice cream's melting.
Huh?!
I'm tellin' ya, he's lyin'!
Still, that's a curious conversation you're havin'.
Huh?
After all, didn't ya walk in on Mio in the bath two days ago?
Wha—
Wh-What the hell, Shinpei?!
Wait! I can explain!
I mean, sure I did end up getting a peek, but...
Shinpei, what are your feelings for Mio?
Wait. What're ya sayin', Tokiko?
W-Well, I...
Obviously, I care for her.
As family.
As family, huh?
Hey! That's enough, Tokiko!
Keep yer weird questions ta yerself!
Shinpei! I just got a text from my Dad.
Once the fireworks are over and they finish the send off, Karikiri will be free.
Okay! Until then...
What is it, Shinpei?
O-Over there!
Why don't we move inside the shrine?
It's easier to see the fireworks from there, too.
Sorry. Go on without me!
H-Hey, Shinpei?!
61st Annual Hito Summer Festival
Tuesday, July 24th
Join the island
in lighting up
the Hitogashima
summer!
Join the island
in lighting up
the Hitogashima
summer!
Procession
Fireworks
Send-off
Look after Mio!
Wh-What's gotten into him?
He gotta poop?
Excuse me! Coming through!
Sorry!
Ushio's probably bored stiff.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
She was really looking forward to the festival.
Take a breath, take a breath
It wouldn't be strange for her to be hanging around.
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
Hey, Shinpei.
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
Don't forget to find me.
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Ushio?
Next time
Jamais Vu