Yuu-chan.
Haruka?
Does your forehead still hurt?
A little bit.
You really scared me back there.
Yuu-chan!
What were you up doing last night anyway?
I've never seen you miss a ball before.
I was studying with Onee-chan until really late.
I thought I'd surprise you by getting a perfect score on our midterms.
Don't push yourself like that!
This is your punishment for worrying me so much.
Th-There's someone sleeping in the next bed over.
Don't worry. I'll be nice and quiet.
Quiet...?
I need more.
I-I'm injured, you know! Be more considerate!
Did I just hear Yuu's voice?
Sho
ck
If you're feeling better, stop bustling about by yourself and go back to class.
You're the reason I didn't get enough sleep last night.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Mom!
Our relative Megumi-san's wedding is next week, right?
What do you think I should wear?
Anything's fine as long as it's not white.
Why not go in your school uniform?
I guess that's fine.
Speaking of, your father will be away on a business trip that day.
Feel free to invite a friend in his place.
Can I really?
Yuu-chan it is!
And Shizuku-chan and Kotone-chan and Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan...
Let's keep it to a single person, shall we?
Then I think I'll invite Yuu-chan.
Marriage... it might not be long until it's Haruka's turn.
I won't give Haruka over to some random guy off the streets!
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Bang
n
g
Dear, you're starting to sound like a soap opera character.
He doesn't mind if it's a girl!
"Sakura-colored Wedding"
Hello? Yuu-chan, did I wake you?
I was already up...
Next week, do you want to... wedding together?
Isn't there a whole bunch of paperwork? And are your parents fine with this?
Yep, they said we could.
As long as you're okay with it...
Then I am too.
Really? Thanks, Yuu-chan—I'll call you back soon.
Haruka and I are getting married for some reason.
Is she really okay rushing it like this?
But we're both girls... what would the wedding even be like?
Onee-cha—
What is it, Yuu?
Little Sister
Nothing!
All right.
I can't talk to her about this!
But no matter what I do, she'll find out eventually...
This is too sudden, Haruka.
O-Okay!
Onee-chan...
You ready to talk yet?
Well, if two girls...
Ah, a call.
I knew I shouldn't've asked her!
What is it, Haruka?
Haruka-san?!
Yuu-chan, so about what we were just discussing...
Want to do it in our uniforms?
Our other option is to wear rentals.
I didn't know you could get married in school uniforms.
But this is a once-in-a-lifetime event,
so I think we should go with the rentals.
Okay!
Mom!
Yuu-chan wants to get rentals too!
Just go in your uniforms! Rentals will cost you at least 5000 yen each.
It'll come out of your allowance.
My allowance or a party dress...
If I had to pick one...
It'd obviously be the dress!
You want it that badly?
Sakura Trick
One Week Later
I haven't even done the pre-wedding greetings yet. Is this really okay?
Yuu-chan, are you nervous?
Just relax, Yuu-chan. There's nothing to be afraid of.
I ask that you accept me, inexperienced as I may be.
Of course, same here.
Clothing Rental
Flower
We're here.
Clothing Rental
Flower
It's not a wedding hall.
So Haruka really was joking.
Clothing Rental
Flower
What're we doing here?
We're renting dresses for the wedding.
Haruka.
I'm going to go greet everyone.
Sure.
We really are getting married!
Yuu-chan, you're too tense!
You look so cute, Yuu-chan!
O-Oh, I'm wearing dark blue?
I wanted pure white.
Was there one you liked better?
I think this looks great on you though.
That's what we need!
Yuu-chan, have you used makeup before?
Never.
Then let's give it a whirl!
Hey, I can do this myself!
Smooch
Now both our lips are ready.
Haruka, what is the meaning of this?
Huh, the meaning of what?
Why did you waste our wedding kiss like that?!
Waaah
It was supposed to be more meaningful!
Now, now
Were you under the impression that you'd be kissing the bride today?
We're attending the wedding as the bride and groom's guests.
What made you think otherwise?
The way you told me about it confused me!
Bang!!
Don't you want to marry me?!
Just now...
Huh?
That was our wedding kiss.
And this.
This one too.
They're all wedding kisses.
Are you girls ready?
W-We are!
L-Let's get going, Yuu-chan.
S-Sure.
I'm so embarrassed...
...I can't look her in the eye!
The bride and groom will be entering promptly.
Please welcome them with a round of applause.
Megumi!
Your father will probably act the same for you.
He sure cries easily.
They will now cut the wedding cake.
Look how big it is!
A matcha cake would've been even better.
Matcha!
Wh-What happened, Yuu-chan?
I just felt sad because all you can think about is food during such an emotional event.
I'm worried about your future.
She's caught up in it!
Now, the tossing of the bouquet.
We ask for as many people as possible to participate.
Can we go too?
Let's grab it together, Yuu-chan!
Yeah!
Without further ado!
Yuu-chan, it's coming our way!
It's here!
Haruka, I nabbed it!
Mom?!
I wonder what the future has in store for me.
Sakura Trick
Screentime...
"
Megumi-san, congratulations on getting married!
Thank you so much, Haruka-chan.
It might be your turn next, Haruka-chan.
squeeze
I don't think it'll be much longer either.
Haruka?!
My!
Please take some flower petals.
So we're doing a flower shower.
I've never done this before.
Congratulations!
Find your happiness together!
The bride was gorgeous.
Yeah, and the chicken was really yummy.
The cake, too!
Not to mention the salad.
Geez! Yuu-chan, I saw you moved to tears back there!
Geez!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Right, that reminds me.
My dad said that as long as I don't marry some random guy off the street,
he'd approve of my marriage.
No he didn't
What's with you all of a sudden?
"Sakura-colored Wedding"
The end
Who is it now? I was just starting
to make some progress.
Yes?
Good evening, President Mitsuki.
badump
H-Haruka-san?!
Would you like to go view the Luminarie tonight?
Wh-What? Haruka-san wants to be alone with me?
My heart's not prepared...
Big Sister
S-Sure, why not.
That's great!
Please invite Yuu-chan for me too.
Right...
Why did I have to misinterpret things again?
It's not like I've even hung out with Haruka-san alone ever!
But I guess that was the first time she's ever called me.
Up until now, it's always been Yuu inviting me.
Onee-chan, wanna go to the pool with me and my friends?
Haru—
The fact that she invited me directly is a clear sign of our progress!
Progress towards what?!
But wait...
Why did she call me instead of Yuu this time?
"Sakura-colored Christmas"
Yuu?
Yeah?
I got a call just now.
From who?
Haruka-san. She invited us to go see the Luminarie with everyone.
I got it. I'll get ready soon.
I bet she tried to call you first.
Did you ignore her call?
This girl is acting stranger than usual.
But if Yuu ignored a call from Haruka-san intentionally, then could that mean...
They're fighting?!
I'm getting changed.
Winter break is a terrible time to be fighting.
As the days go by, it just gets harder and harder to apologize.
But since Yuu seems like she wants to go,
I'm sure she intends to make up.
As Yuu's sister, I have to help them mend their friendship!
La-dee-da...
Yuu, listen to me for a minute.
You have a habit of being stubborn and not being honest with yourself.
Well? Right?
nudge
That's not true.
You can't simply sit quiet.
Being the first to compromise is the best way to deepen your friendship.
I'm sorry.
You understand?
Understand what?! What are you even talking about?!
Understand it already!
There you are, Sonoda sisters.
Yoo-hoo!
Did we keep you waiting?
Don't worry about it.
It really does seem as though Haruka-san is keeping her distance.
I'll get you two back together before you know it!
Anyway, check out how pretty everything is!
Wow!
This is no time to get swept up in the atmosphere!
Now's your chance to approach Haruka-san. Go, Yuu!
Are you okay, Yuu-chan?
Ah
You need to be more careful.
R-Right.
Oh man, that just made things worse!
This is bad—they're as far apart as possible.
They both must feel too awkward to make a move.
I thought she had a soft spot for Yuu, but Haruka-san can be unexpectedly stubborn as well.
Well, at least I got to learn something new about her.
This is no time to be giggling to myself!
Big Sister
Time for plan B!
What do you want with me, President Mitsuki?
Don't you think Haruka-san and Yuu are acting a bit distant?
Why, do you?
It's plain as day! Do you have any idea why?
No, not a clue.
Isn't this what you wanted? Last time, you were worried that they were too intimate.
This and that are completely different!
She's such a hassle.
Could we check out this store?
You bet!
Welcome!
So cool!
Oh, Yuu would probably like this pendant.
Haruka-san.
Isn't this cute?
Ah, I bet Yuu-chan would love that! I'll go get her!
That'd look great on you, President Mitsuki.
I'm glad, but that's beside the point!
That didn't work. What else can I try?
President Mitsuki, do you like that one?
Huh? Oh, yes, I think it's quite charming.
Then just go ahead and buy it.
I'm all out of cash after buying my little brother and sister their presents.
Are you really?
Then you'd better get that letter to Santa!
You're kidding, right?
Only seven minutes until they light it all up!
The people are piling in.
I don't think we belong here!
Don't worry. Plenty of other people are here with their friends and families.
There are all different kinds of love.
I'm going to check out that store one more time!
I'm gonna look at the shop next to that one!
They just keep drifting further away!
It's pretty much the same place, so I don't see why they're not going together.
Keep your mouth shut...
Wait a minute, isn't this the perfect opportunity?
Great!
Look, the other side has fewer people so we can probably see better.
Let's go around.
Then I'll just grab Haruka and Yuu—
I can get them! You girls go on ahead.
It's a long-standing duty of the council president to take care of her students!
Ehem
Every other word out of her mouth is just...
Let's-a-go!
They finally left.
President Mitsuki.
Do you know where everyone went?
They said they went to look for a better spot on the other side...
Ah, I just remembered that I
wanted to pick some flowers.
Do you mind waiting here for Yuu?
Sure...
Why flower picking, of all things?!
Bear with it, Mitsuki. What's done is done.
Huh? Shizuku-chan, Kotone-chan?
Oh no, I got separated from everyone.
Ah, Haruka!
Yuu-chan.
I-I wonder where everyone went.
I heard they went to look for a better spot over on the other side.
Th-That wasn't nice of them.
Right? They could've waited for us.
I was just about to call them,
so I'm glad I ran into you.
That was good timing.
This feels so weird.
Whenever I see Haruka, I can't help but remember what we did the other day and get excited.
I want her to look me in the eyes like usual
and talk to me like she always does.
Haruka...
SHINE
It is now 7 pm. The light show is beginning.
Amazing! The images keep on changing...
Let's take a picture, Yuu-chan!
Yeah!
Why? For a moment, we
were talking like normal. Haruka...
You have a habit of being stubborn and not being honest with yourself.
You can't simply sit quiet.
Being the first to compromise is the best way to deepen your friendship.
Haruka!
I think we can see better from over there. Let's go!
I-I didn't mean that!
I keep remembering all these things whenever I see your face,
and I get so overcome with passion it hurts...
I was so worried about getting overexcited again
that I couldn't get myself to call you directly today.
I...
I had the same thing on my mind, Haruka.
We're the same. Who cares if it hurts?
Let's indulge in our passion like we always do.
I feel like you're a bit different today.
That right now, your passion is
overshadowing even mine.
I-It is not!
I guess I just have to become even more passionate.
Otherwise we won't be the same.
Where'd you all go?!
"Sakura-colored Christmas"
The end
kagayaku illumination
Seeing the streets awash in illumination
mune ga tokimeku no
makes my heart beat fast
tobikkiri kawaiku kigaete
Let's put on our cutest clothes
dekakeyou christmas
and go out this Christmas
machijuu kirameku tonari ni minna no egao
The city is alight with everyone's smiles
afureru shiawase shiroi toiki ni naru
Our happiness spills out in the form of our white breath
furihajimeta
It's started to snow
sakurairo no yuki
cherry blossom-colored snow
kimochi tsutaetai konya dake wa ne
Tonight's the night to tell her how you feel
kamisama toki wo tomete
God, please stop time
kirakira kagayaku tokubetsu na shunkan
I want this special moment to keep shining
anata to tsunagaru nukumori
as we nestle warmly against one another
nee zutto gyutto
Let's stay this way forever
sakura christmas
Sakura Christmas
Next Episode
Kotone, I'm the only one you just call by name, right?
Do you want a nickname?
That's not what I meant...
Yuzu-chan.
That's gross.
Yuzucchi!
That's not good either!
Use-you!
That's not even a name!
You're so high maintenance.
Then how about... Mikan-san!
Anything but that!
Next time, Trick 9:
"Year-end Debut S.B.J.K."
"A Sour Plan!? Take Two"
and "A Sour Plan?! Take Two".
Look forward to it!
Harupoppo will make a debut!