Oh no! Oh no! An unexpected person
has come from the spirit world!
His name is Izumi Lio,
and he came because
the Division Chief of Death Spirits told him
to make sure we were doing our jobs.
What'll we do if they find out that we've
been transforming Mitsuki into Full Moon?!
We were able to
fool them this time,
but I get a bad feeling
we'll be caught sometime soon!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Well, our song of the day is
the one that rose
to the top of the charts for
the first time this week,
Full Moon's "Eternal Snow"!
This song is a cover song
of a masterpiece
created by an 80's band
called "Route L,"
and it is garnering quite
a lot of attention!
This song targets
a wide range of ages.
Let's see how well it does!
Check it out!
"Hi Full Moon.
How are you doing?"
"I went to buy your new single
the day it came out,"
"but once I got home, I found out
that my mom had bought it too."
"My mom and I are both
cheering for you!" this one says!
Umm... This one says...
Wow, this is from Nanami!
Full Moon, long time no see!
I bought "Eternal Snow."
This song is also fantastic!
There is no doubt about that because
I think so and I'm your number one fan!
Thanks!
But I can barely read all these,
let alone reply to them.
Here! I'll help you with that!
Stupid!
You can't write them back!
There, there. Anyway, this looks like
a pretty good start.
Maybe this brought you closer
to finding Eichi.
What?!
Y-You think so?
Oh, yeah! Maybe he'll come back
from America all of a sudden!
What?! Oh my!
Yeah! And you two will embrace each other
for the miraculous reunion!
Mitsuki! Eichi!
No, Meroko, stop it now!
Really!
That was Full Moon's
"Eternal Snow."
Excuse me, Ma'am.
You have a visitor.
Who is it?
Well...
Oh, Grandmother!
I have not seen you in so long.
Oh, please, don't be so formal!
I'm so glad to see you again!
Yes.
Excuse me, Miss.
Would you please take your shoes off?
What?! To see me?
Yes... She says she came all
the way from America.
From America?
Who could it be?
From America, eh? Maybe it's Eichi!
That's impossible!
It's a souvenir for you.
Here, please don't be so reserved!
I think it suits you well, actually!
Excuse me.
Hi, Mitsuki!
Oh, it was you, Ms. Kazumi!
I was wondering who would
be visiting me from America.
I am now married and living in America.
Really?
Oh, it's been two years!
How have you been?
Hey, Mitsuki!
Who's she?
She's Ms. Kazumi, my teacher from
when I was in the orphanage.
How disappointing.
Ms. Kazumi, you're being dramatic.
But I sure am glad you came
all the way to see me.
I had to run some errands in Japan,
and when I was at the airport,
I heard a song that
brought back memories.
A song?
Yes. The one that your father wrote,
"Eternal Snow."
You remember it, right?
Umm... Yeah...
Hey! If you don't mind, why don't you
show me your room, Mitsuki!
Is that all right?
Well, sure.
Okay. Then, let's go!
Huh? Oh, yes!
Yes, yes, this melody.
This is such a wonderful music box.
This is a memento from my parents.
Oh really?
Ms. Kazumi, I'm sorry.
My grandmother doesn't
really like music.
No problem. I kind of sensed
that something was up.
But weren't you dreaming
of becoming a singer?
Yes! I haven't given up on that!
Of course. Because...
- "No one can get in the way of my dream!"
You always said this to me back
when I was in the orphanage.
You remembered?
That's right!
No one can get in
the way of dreams!
I'll definitely make Takuto
care about me!
Hey, what are you
thinking about right now?
Are you curious about
what I am thinking?
No.
Oh, wasn't this calendar Eichi's?
Oh, yes. I'm looking after it for him.
Looking after it?
What?
Eichi, is that true?
Yes, I'm going to America with
my new dad and mom next week.
America?
I'm sorry for keeping it from you,
but I wanted to tell it to you in person,
before I told everyone else.
No way...
I was an emotional mess when Eichi
suddenly told me he was leaving.
And the night before
Eichi left...
Tonight is the last time we sleep
under the same roof, Mitsuki.
No...
I want to be with you tomorrow night,
and the one after that.
Mitsuki...
It's not like we're going to
be separated forever.
Until we make our dreams come true,
our time together is just going to stop.
The next time we see each other,
our time will start to move again.
Until then, I'll leave this
with you, Mitsuki.
It's been up there ever since that night.
The time between Eichi and I
has stopped there.
Is that so?
That's why she keeps
that old calendar.
Do you still talk with him?
I don't know where
he moved to in America.
Ms. Kazumi, do you know anything
about where he went?
I'm sorry.
I quit working at the orphanage
after getting married.
I see.
I know! I'll find him even if
I have to search all over America!
Really?
Oh, yes.
You and Eichi will always be
my dear students.
I'll do anything to help you!
Thank you so much, Ms. Kazumi!
Just leave it to me!
Now we have someone who can help us!
Right, Takuto?
So, what do you want to do
when you find Eichi?
Huh?
Since it's been two years,
you must have tons of things
you want to tell him, right?
Umm...
I don't know.
Well, then, think about it before
I go back to America.
It's been a while, but it's
a homework assignment I'm giving you!
Okay!
Maybe I'll find Eichi!
And...
Mitsuki, I like you.
Then, I can finally tell him "I like you,"
which I couldn't back then.
Oh, yes! I have to hurry and think
about Ms. Kazumi's assignment.
Did I serve a bad dish?
I'm doing fine.
Well, then...
Mitsuki, why are you spacing out?
Oh, yes!
Thank you so much for dinner!
W-Wait, Mitsuki, you're finished?
You barely touched anything!
I'm sorry.
I have homework to do.
Shall I write a letter?
A letter?
That's a great idea!
Letters are the most romantic!
Yes! What should I write?
What?
Do you think I have to write in English?
Of course Japanese is fine!
Right. Good.
I wonder how Eichi is doing.
Let's see...
What if Eichi has become way more
handsome than in this picture?
I don't know what I'd do!
I wonder if he'd think that
I've become prettier.
Yes! He will! Of course he will!
It's not like you're guaranteed
to find him, right?!
I'll be able to see him for sure!
Ms. Kazumi will find him.
In any case, it's not like
he'll be found today or tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Let's not even bother with guys that
don't understand girls' feelings!
More importantly, the letter, the letter!
Right!
Do as you please!
I'm fed up with this!
What's so great
about this Eichi?
Well, this guy Eichi isn't just
a fantasy or an illusion.
I'll find him even if I have to
search all over America.
Surely, you'll find him someday.
Well, so what?!
Stupid me.
I see. You've decided
to write a letter?
I thought of doing that and tried to do it
all night long, but couldn't really...
What are you mad about?
Nothing.
I see. So that's why you came
to me seeking help.
Yes!
But I'm not sure if
I can be of any help.
But you have such
a wonderful husband.
You think so?
How did you tell him your feelings?
In my case,
I didn't use a letter, but that...
Huh?
A...video?
That's right, I sent him a video-letter.
More than writing a letter,
I thought that sending the message directly
with words would convey more.
I see!
That's a great idea!
That way, you can show Eichi
how you sing when you're Full Moon!
Well, my story is just one example.
No, that was so helpful.
Thank you so much!
Ready... Start!
Eichi, I've finally become a singer.
I'm always singing to you across the sea.
H-Hey! Stop !
What are you doing, Takuto?
Hey! Why are you interrupting this?!
I don't like this at all!
What are you talking about?
Why are you in a bad mood?
Are you hungry?
Stupid, it's not that.
Well, then why?
Nothing, really.
What I really want to say is—
H-Hey! Let go of me!
Alrighty, don't bother us now.
Yes, yes, nothing gets done
when you mope around.
That's your favorite phrase, right?
How stupid.
Huh?!
Takuto!
Hey, I can't film like this.
I'm not going to help you anymore.
But...
Don't you think this is fake?
Using that huge camera and all.
If you really wanted to
deliver your message,
shouldn't you show your true self?
My...true self?
Right! You're right!
- If you got it, then...
- Thanks, Takuto!
What?! Hey, wait!
Jeez... Did she really get it?
Oh, is this what you wanted?
Yes. This one is better than
the ones at the TV station.
Relax, Mitsuki.
So she really didn't get it!
Hey you, if all you're gonna do is complain,
can you please go away?
All right.
Okay, let's get started.
Ready... Start!
Eichi... Umm... How are you?
No, you're too stiff!
Relax like you were before.
When I'm not Full Moon,
I feel kind of shy.
Just relax, relax.
Okay, here we go again!
Eichi, how have you been?
I couldn't tell you two years ago,
but I've liked you for so long!
Hey! Are you taking this seriously?!
You really like him, right?
Then you've got to put
more feelings into it!
But you told me to relax.
That's way too relaxed!
Just be your normal self.
You want to show how
you truly are, right, Mitsuki?
Yes! Once more, please!
I'm ready when you are!
Eichi, I like you.
Eichi, as we promised,
I am working hard to achieve my dreams.
I was determined to become a singer,
and I went to an audition as Full Moon.
Then, out of many applicants,
I was chosen.
These days,
I have put out two albums,
and I am participating in events
and performing at live shows.
I'm very busy every day with TV
and radio shows too.
I have fans that like my songs!
Full Moon is pretty popular
at school too.
So that's how it's been,
working towards my dreams!
Where are you,
and what are you doing now, Eichi?
I want to see you soon!
I'm waiting for our time together
to start moving again.
I'd say that's pretty good.
Yes!
Of course it is!
Because I directed it!
Ms. Oshige, I want to give this video
to Ms. Kazumi.
Her flight to America takes off
at 1 p.m., right?
If you leave now,
we can make it without a problem.
Hey!
Are you serious about delivering it?
Huh?
Hey, why are you still talking like that?
For one thing, this video has the real Mitsuki
and Full Moon all mixed up, right?
How can Eichi believe that
Mitsuki is Full Moon?
I have to film the transformation too.
Is that okay with you, Mitsuki?
Yes... Eichi is so important to me.
I want to tell him the truth,
like I told you and Dr. Wakaoji.
You're right.
So, let's hurry and film that too.
Takuto, please.
I refuse.
No way!
We came this far...
Takuto! Just stop your nonsense now!
Let me tell you this, you guys are
the ones that aren't making any sense!
What do you mean?
Mitsuki... Something's wrong with you.
Didn't you decide to let Eichi find
you through your singing?
I sympathized with that feeling and
helped you turn into Full Moon.
You wanted him to notice you
through your singing,
so shouldn't you keep your word
and go on working on that?
Think about it.
Hey, where are you going?
Takuto!
Yes...that's right.
Takuto is right.
Mitsuki...
What am I doing?
Eichi wouldn't be happy
even if I sent this video to him.
Don't you need to go to the airport?
Isn't it better to give him
the video than to do nothing?
Everything will stay the same if you don't.
But...
Let's go Mitsuki!
There's no time to be indecisive!
How is it? Can we make it?
Traffic is kind of bad.
We might just barely make it.
Your father conveyed his feelings
through this one song, right?
Why don't you try to follow
this example, shorty?
We made it.
Come on, Mitsuki, hurry!
What's wrong, Mitsuki?
Ms. Oshige. Meroko...
I am not going to hand over
this video after all.
What are you talking about?!
We came all the way here!
I'm sorry. But Takuto is right.
I've decided to have Eichi notice me
through my songs.
So I want to keep singing,
believing that he will one day notice me!
Ms. Kazumi!
Mitsuki!
I'm glad I made it in time.
Ms. Kazumi, if you find Eichi in America,
I want you to hand these to him.
Huh? These?
I think Eichi will understand once
he listens to those CDs.
This is the answer to the homework
you gave me.
I see. Okay.
I'll hand these to him for sure,
so just hang on till I contact you.
Okay!
Good! Very well done.
Eichi... I'll sing...
Believing that the day will come
when you'll notice me.
What?! Takuto!
You're all over Mitsuki again!
I can't help it! She has a gig
at the university festival,
and I have to protect her
as her bodyguard.
Shut up! You're the worst!
You're so mean, Takuto!
Meroko, calm down!
Whatever. I'll do my own thing!
You'll realize how great I am and apologize,
but it'll be too late!
Next time on Full Moon:
"It's Autumn School Festival!"
- Look forward to it!