[gunshots]
[Mustang] Elizabeth! Hey!
What's going on?!
[Ling] So this piece of info is
supposed to be confidential...
But whatever.. Barry told me
the Colonel's got a plan
to smoke out some military
guys he's been after...
the ones from the fifth
something or other.
The Fifth Laboratory.
Al?
I've gotta find them...
this could lead us
straight to the person who
killed Lieutenant Hughes.
Huh? Hey, not so fast!
Tell me your secret, first!
I'll tell you when
I get back, okay?
Oh, c'mon,
that's so unfair!
I'll be back soon.
Okay.. Just be careful.
I will.. I promise.
Are you all done now?
Then it's time to eat you.
[dog barks]
Stop it! That tickles!
Catch!
Bullets gone? Goodie, goodie!
I get to have
dinner and desert!
[Gluttony screams]
I barely made it.
Colonel...
Why the hell did you
leave your post?!
No matter what
happened to us,
you could still have kept
your involvement a secret!
That was the whole
idea, right?!
But you just come waltzing
in here, plain as day!
Are you a complete idiot?!
Yeah, fine, fine, that's
it... I'm an idiot. Happy?
Who the heck
was that fat guy?
[Fuery] Colonel! The
target's on the move, sir!
Strike the camp, Sergeant!
Don't leave a single trace!
And you stay right by the
Sergeant's side, Hayate!
Sir! [ruff!]
[Hawkeye] Colonel?
What is it?
Thanks for saving
us back there.
Tell me later...
Let's just stay focused
on the mission for now.
Sir.
Quick, get in!
Yes, sir.
Are you trying to go after
Mr. Hughes' murderer?
You in?
Yeah.
Don't let him get away.
He ain't goin' nowhere.
[66 laughs] My soul
won't be able to rest...
Not until I eviscerate
that meat bag!
So do you think we can
expect another appearance
from that blubber
beast back there?
I doubt it.. I scorched
him off the ledge.
Yeah, and I shot
him in the head.
But he didn't really
seem to mind.
[Al gasps] He didn't have
an Uroboros tattoo, did he?
A tattoo? Well...
Actually, yeah...
on his tongue.
In that case.. you were probably
dealing with a Homunculus.
[66 screams]
Watch it, Mustang!
Hold on a damn second!
What are you saying, Al...?
That's just not possible.
Yeah, that's what I thought,
until I got kidnapped
by a Homunculus...
He called himself Greed...
One thing he told me is
that nothing is impossible.
I know for a fact that they
have amazing healing powers.
I watched Greed get the top
half of his head knocked off...
but he was perfectly
fine a minute later.
They're real alright...
but I understand if
you don't believe me.
After what I just saw...
I have to believe you.
Hold on.. I
rendered fat boy
down to a bubbling
puddle back there...
Are you telling me
he's still alive?
[Al] Probably.
[Mustang] Wonderful...
It's just a never ending
parade of freaks lately, huh?
[tires screech]
[66] My body ran in there. Seems
to think it can hide from me.
[Mustang] The Third
Laboratory, huh?
So this ties them
directly to the military.
That's all we need for now...
We're pulling back.
Well, you have
fun with that!
Get back here!
That psycho stormed
the building.
Yep.. It's our lucky day.
Huh?
[66 laughs]
[screams]
Outta my way!
I don't want any of your
boring old skin and bones!
I got me a special
reunion to get to!
All personnel must
evacuate immediately!
Um, Colonel?
Stay back.. The man who broke
in is a deranged murderer.
My men will handle
his capture.
Order your guards
to seal off the exits!
Yes, sir!
[Havoc] How the hell are
we supposed to find him?
We're gonna
have to split up.
Yes, sir.
It doesn't look like anybody's
used this lab in a while.
I guess not...
What is this stuff?
I have no idea.. But
whatever they did here,
it was painful for someone.
Well now.. I am just shocked.
It's bad enough that you
stood me up on our date.
And now you
point a gun at me?
You've got some
nerve.. Don't you?
Solaris...? What's going on?
Hey, Havoc.
Your girl's got
the tattoo.
Yeah. First
I've seen it, sir.
Quit staring...
It's not very polite.
Well, I can see how she
tricked you so easily...
You've always been
a sucker for big boobs.
I can't help it!
I love 'em!
Did you tell this
woman anything?
No, I never said a single
thing about work, sir!
Tell me.. Do you know
who Maes Hughes is?
Oh.. yes, he was quite
the intelligent man,
wouldn't you agree?
I only wish I'd had the
opportunity to pick his brain.
[gunshot]
On your knees.. I
wanna know everything.
Sorry to say...
But it's gonna take more
than you're capable of
to make me get on my kn--
[Lust laughs]
How merciless...
Did you pick that up
in Ishval? Huh?
You're a Homunculus!
Indeed.. How very
astute of you, Jean...
But I doubt you've
seen this one.
Take a good look, boys.
It's a Philosopher's Stone.
I was created with this
stone at my core...
It's not just a legend...
It's my heart.
You're a monster.
That was uncalled for...
I do have feelings...
Apart from a few things, I was
made nearly identical to you.
I am human.
I've got a funny feeling
the only reason you're
telling us this.. is 'cuz you
don't plan on letting us live.
Yep.. it's such a shame.
Too slow!
Oh, no, did I get your ignition
glove all wet? Silly me.
[both yell]
What are we gonna do?!
She'll shred us with
her freaky fingers!
No, she made
a big mistake...
She flooded the
room with water.
A simple transmutation,
and we've got hydrogen gas.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Aw, crap...
This was a gift from one
of my ex-girlfriends...
Man.. Hey, Colonel? Ya mind
giving me a light, here?
Oh, right,
you're all wet.
Yeah?! Well, those things'll
kill you, you know that?!
She's dust.. I
definitely cremated her.
How do you know
for sure, sir?
The stench.
I'm pretty familiar
with that stink by now.
Ya mean from that time
you spent in Ishval?
For all we know, she
could still regenerate...
So stay alert.
Yes, sir.
Havoc!
Havoc! Hang in there!
Don't kid yourself.
He's a dead man.
No, he's not!
Give up! There's nothing
you can do that'll kill me!
Then you won't mind...
If I borrow this!
I need it to save Havoc.
I don't know that much
about medicinal alchemy...
But this should
amplify my abilities.
It seems like you should
buy a girl dinner first...
before you stick your
hand in her chest.
Uh-- Uh... Your Excellency!
What's the current status?
[Guard] The criminal responsible
for the prison break
has stormed the premises,
but Colonel Mustang and
his men are in pursuit.
Well then.. I'll give
him some backup.
Very good! We're right
behind you, sir!
No.
I'd prefer to
handle it on my own.
I told you...
The Philosopher's
Stone is my core.
I really hate to do this...
you were a prime candidate
for sacrifice and all. But
you've forced me to kill you.
Damn you.
Save your breath...
I want you to watch
poor Jean bleed to death...
then you can die.
Jean.. hey. Answer me!
Havoc! You can't die...
Not yet. Not before I do.
Havoc...
Sorry. But ya
got here too late.
Look at this mess.. My body
is damn near entirely decayed.
[66] I guess a body
just can't hold up
with someone else's soul
being shoved inside of it.
[Al gasps]
If a soul is incompatible
with another person's body...
wouldn't it be the same for a
soul bonded to a suit of armor?
If that's right...
there's no guarantee
I'll be able to stay in
this form long enough
to get our old bodies back...
Brother...
[66 chuckles]
I was wondering when you
were gonna show up, Lusty.
Number Sixty Six...
Care to explain why you're
helping the Colonel?
I thought it'd be fun to
switch things up.. Besides...
I've wanted to chop
you up since I met you.
You're such a
handful, Sixty Six...
And I'm sad to see
you here, armor boy...
You just had
to tag along.
Talk about a setback...
It's bad enough to lose one...
But now you're forcing me
to kill a second candidate.
Candidate?
A second one?
Yeah.. You and Mr. Gallantry.
That's enough of the
casual chit chat, Lust!
All I wanna hear
from you is screaming!
I do hate over-confident men.
Now then.. Where were we?
I think I was about
to send the Lieutenant
to join her superior.
Wait a minute...
So when you said you'd
already had to kill someone...
It can't be...
You didn't!
You biiittch!!
[Hawkeye screams]
Are you done?
[Hawkeye sobs]
Such a sad and weak creature...
Another typical human.
Stand up, Lieutenant...
You need to get out of here.
Do you want me
to kill you first?
Oh, my.. It appears
you've opened the portal.
Such a shame.. You are
a perfect candidate.
Listen, Alphonse...
Leave me and save yourself.
No!
Run!
I won't!
Go!
I won't leave you!
I'm sick of
watching people die!
And I can't just sit back
and take it anymore!
I won't let anyone
else get killed!
Not when I can protect them!
Well spoken...
I couldn't agree more.
Looks like I can get you
on your knees after all.
[Lust] He's using the
flint for ignition..
and he carved a transmutation
circle into his hand!
You should have
bled to death by now!
I seared the wound closed...
I came close to passing
out from the pain.
[Lust screams]
You told me I
couldn't kill you...
but I'd like to try
and prove you wrong.
So let's see.. How many
times is it gonna take?!
[Lust screams]
Colonel!
[Lust] You killed me.
I hate losing.. but there
are worse ways to die
than at the hands
of a man like you.
I love how cold and
focused your eyes are.
I look forward...
to the day when those eyes
will be wide with agony...
It's coming...
Colonel!
Are you alright?
Forget about me, we need
to get you some help!
Thanks, Alphonse...
Thank you for looking
after my subordinate.
Yeah, sure, we need
to call you a doctor.
[Mustang] Oh,
yeah.. hurry...
Call a doctor for
Havoc... Please.
He's alright.. He's alright.
Uh, hey.. I'm home now.
Moron! Welcome back!
Uh, okay.. Thanks?
I- I... W-Well...
[both laughing]
[clank, thud]
[Winry screams]
That shouldn't happen!
[Al] It won't stay!
I- I can't put it back on!
Holey moley.. That was
way too damn close.
I hope someone can fix me...
I'd rather not live
my life as sheet metal.
Ah! What the...?! How the
hell are you still alive?!
Hey... Oh, no! Put
me down right now!
I- I've got a second chance
to terrorize the city!
You're gonna ruin everything!
No... Don't do it, wait!
No, stop! Please!
[ding]
It can't be.
Is it?
Hohenheim...!
[Narrator] The truth stands
between two opposing mirrors,
each casting reflections
of outrage and joy.
When unexpectedly confronted
by his forsaken past,
the young man is forced to
resolve issues that have lay
hidden within the
shadows of his anger.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 20: "Father
Before the Grave."
It's not necessary
to shed tears..
A person can still
cry without them.