Please take me off of this mission, Ms McCunnen.
I have something important to do.
What if I said...
...there was something more important than that?
What is it?
It can't be...
Yes. This is your passport.
The real you... your past is written in it.
Ein.
Be careful.
I didn't know...
There's no way I could've known...
...about the twist of the fate that was waiting for us.
...about the future.
Go ahead and take a look.
Are you afraid of regaining your past?
I've been following the organization's orders to kill people.
Yes. You've had great achievements.
But I was able to kill them because I had no past and memories.
You've been following orders like a robot without feeling any guilt.
If you regain your original self,
you might be tormented by your sins.
You're afraid of that, aren't you?
But that's precisely why I want you to return to your former self.
With your own will.
With my own will...
The distance is 249 yards.
An intermittent strong wind is blowing from the south.
Return to your true self, and accept yourself as Zwei.
You're so selfish...
Your organization was the one that took away my memories.
And it was also the organization
that stained my hands with blood.
And now...
It's a change.
The organization will be reborn soon.
When that happens...
I want you to be there, Zwei.
But no matter how skilled you are,
I don't want a doll who only follows its orders.
I want a companion.
A dependable subordinate.
Someone who will follow me of his own will.
If I learn about my past...
I'm not confident that I can keep going as I am.
When that time comes...
My mission is to back up the raid.
The people in sight are my targets.
Which organization are they from?!
The lading...
A sniper?
We did it!
It's too early to say that, bro.
Just get the hell out of here!
All right!
Just to nail us down here...
You've got some guts.
Try reading your name.
Azuma...
Reiji.
Seems like you remembered it.
Right... I...
...was on a trip.
And then...
I've killed so many people with these hands...
Just because I wanted to live on.
I was better off not knowing it...
I told you, didn't I?
I don't need a puppet.
Wake up from your dream.
You'll return to being you.
Accept your past and your sins and face them with your own will,
Azuma Reiji.
Phantom?!
Damn you, Scythe!
What do you want me to do?
Follow me, Reiji.
With your own will.
There's someone who needs your help.
This is your home.
If you're willing to stain your hands with blood again,
and share your guilt with me,
I promise to show you a wonderful life.
However, I'm not forcing you.
You can make the other choice, too.
The other choice?
The other choice is...
Go back to Japan?
If that's what you want,
I'll make an exception.
You might doubt me,
but I'm serious.
I'll really allow you to go back to your hometown.
What I want is a subordinate with a solid will.
You idiot!
Why are you shooting your allies?!
This might be Scythe's order but stop acting like a puppet!
You can't escape!
Think about this.
That snaky bastard is just using you as a disposable pawn!
Go back...
...to Japan...
This is an important decision for you.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
Hello? This is the Azuma residence.
Hello?
There's no way I could go back there.
Look for her!
That Scythe bastard betrayed us.
Did you hear how many people she killed?
We shall repay him suitably.
Of course, Phantom as well.
Ein? What are you doing here?
Did you come here to kill me?
What are you talking about?
You don't know anything?
Then hurry up and return to the organization.
You can still make it...
Ein!
Ein...
It's me.
There's been a sudden change of plans.
Scythe betrayed the organization.
He made Phantom attack Inferno's lading.
Of course he immersed immediately.
Phantom has escaped, too.
But luckily Lizzie shot her.
The organization is looking for those two with all their might.
They haven't found either of them though.
They suspect that you've deserted the organization, too.
But I can give you an alibi.
I guess you don't have any time to consider my deal.
Make a decision quickly.
Come to my side...
Or...
I'll tell you one thing.
Scythe and Phantom are our enemies.
If you're with them, the organization will...
The bleeding won't stop.
The bullet didn't pass through all the way.
I've got to take her to a doctor.
I can't...
The organization probably has connections to hospitals.
I have to do it.
Don't die on me, Ein.
We sealed off all possible escape routes.
They're literally birds in a cage.
No one can run away from the organization.
Not even Phantom.
Now, who will hunt the prey?
Don't die, Ein.
You still can't find them with so many people?!
Highway?
Seal it off.
God damn it! If I had just killed her there...
Clau, what about him?
Zwei?
He's Scythe's pet dog, too.
It's quite possible that he'd be on their side.
When that happens, Lizzie...
You...
...shall kill him.
Ein.
You know, Ein.
Ms McCunnen gave me my passport tonight.
My passport...
After that, I remembered everything.
About my hometown, my family...
I had a place to return to.
I even remembered my name.
My name is Reiji.
Azuma Reiji.
It's much better than a boring name like Zwei, right?
But for some reason...
I'm not really happy...
I'm no longer my old self.
I shouldn't go back there.
Can I only return to the organization?
Ein... we should both go back...
Scythe and Phantom are our enemies.
If you're with them, the organization will... kill you.
I can't!
If I go back, Ein will...
In that case...
I'll leave Ein here...
...and go back alone?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Don't worry.
The wind.
Blue, white, and green.
That's all there is to it.
There's nothing else here.
But it's so bright there...
And the wind is blowing.
A very strong wind.
Ein.
Be careful.
You too.
Without having a name, we were just given numbers.
We were just used like pawns and abandoned.
This has to be a joke.
This has to be a joke!
This meaningless way of life has to be a joke!
Ein.
Ein,
I'm the only one who can protect you.
I won't forsake you.
I definitely won't hand you over to the organization.
Let's escape...
From this city...
From Inferno.
Reiji.
Let's escape together, Ein.
I'll give you a new name.
Not Phantom nor a number.
Your own name...