[LOUD FOOTSTEPS]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
So what's the story
with these guys?
They showed up under the pretext
of escorting Ms. Rockbell,
but I'm not buying that.
They only answer to Kimblee.
[MILES THINKING]
He's got some kind of
plan for us here... but what?
[WINRY]
You should've told me you
were heading to the North.
I didn't have a chance...
We were in a hurry, okay?
Yeah, and when are you
guys ever not in a hurry...
Anyway... What did
you do to get locked up?
[KIMBLEE]
It's only a misunderstanding.
Just a lack of communication...
I'll have them released
within no time at all.
Thanks a lot,
Mr. Kimblee.
These two are lucky to
have you watching out for them.
It's nothing.
Listen... I wouldn't
trust Kimblee if I were you.
What? Why not?
He seems nice.
[CAR ACCELERATING]
[KIMBLEE]
Miss Rockbell,
Is it true that your
parents lost their lives
while giving medical
attention during the war?
[WINRY GASPS]
That's right.
Thought so.
I was part of the squadron...
that recovered their bodies.
What?
We had been
dispatched to help them,
but it was too late by the
time we got there. I'm sorry.
Thank you for trying.
They stayed true
to their duty...
And they helped the needy
right up to the end...
I respect their bravery.
I wish that I could have
had the chance to meet them.
They were holding a photo
of a precious little girl
when we found them,
and I knew right away
that it was
their daughter.
The thought of you
kept them strong
during the worst
of the war.
Your parents
were true heroes...
...and it's an
honor to meet you.
Do you have any idea what
that psychopath did in Ishval--
[ED THINKING]
But what do I know...?
I've only got Lieutenant
Hawkeye's experiences to go by.
And she thinks...
She thinks I...
Speaking of Winry...
You're in love with her...
Aren't you?
[ED SCREAMS]
[KIMBLEE SIPPING]
[ED THINKING]
Don't freak out...! Just
think about something else...!
Try to think
about something else!
Hydrogen... helium...
lithium... beryllium... carbon...
[WINRY]
Uh... Ed?
Aluminum, silicon,
phosphorus, chromium,
manganese,
iron, cobalt...
[WINRY SIGHS]
Why did I haveta' fall
in love with such a weirdo?
Huh? Did you
say something?
No, Ed,
I didn't say anything.
[ED SCREAMS]
What the hell, Winry?
I told you to warn me before you
connect the nerves! Alright?!
Yeah, yeah...
Now let's do your leg.
[METAL CLANKING]
It's so light...
It's not gonna be any weaker
than my last arm will it?
Not really...
It's slightly weaker,
but I doubt you'll notice...
It is pretty
heavily reinforced.
[BUCCANEER GRUNTS]
Alright... What are you
doin' outta your cell?
I don't know...
Maybe some people respect the
fact that I'm a State Alchemist.
[BUCCANEER SCOFFS]
Finally upgrading
for the cold, huh?
Are you upgrading too?
[WINRY GASPS]
There's nothin' left
for me to upgrade to!
[EXCITEDLY]
Ahhh!
It's the M-Nineteen Mad Bear
lightweight combat model!
Whoa...!
What kind of reinforcement
is that on the claws?
They're not diamond
tipped, are they?
Yeah... She's fully modified.
It's a specially crafted model.
[EXCITEDLY]
Ahhh!
Edward! Do you want me to
upgrade you to one of these?
Not my style.
Who's the girl? She's too
cute to be hangin' around you.
She's my mechanic.
[BUCCANEER ANGRILY GRUNTING]
[CAPTION]
"KILL!!!"
What'd ya do that for?!
[BUCCANEER]
Because life isn't fair.
That was messed up.
Real life Northern automail...!
That's the first I've seen!
[NEIL]
Oh, yeah?
You wanna come check
out my work shed then?
[WINRY]
Please, please! I'd love to!
Hey.
What's wrong?
Uh... Nothing...
Try to keep on your toes...
And don't go off exploring.
Not on your own.
It's not safe here.
So be careful, alright?
Okay, I will be.
[WINRY]
Alright, let's see
what you've got.
[NEIL]
Well, this model
is kind of rare.
[WINRY]
Are you serious?
You've got a Crocodile?!
I see she's got
her parent's enthusiasm.
Well I've done a little
bodywork on this one to enhance
the model's
durability in the cold.
Well then...
Your little upgrade's all taken
care of and out of the way.
So why don't we find
a place to sit down?
I'm eager to
discuss our business.
[AL]
Excuse me?
Can you tell me why you're
keeping me in this cell?
Because that's where
Mr. Kimblee wants you.
We were given specific
instructions and orders
to only release
the Fullmetal Alchemist.
You just sit tight...
[AL THINKING]
Good strategy, Kimblee...
He's playing it safe by
keeping us separated...
And by dragging
Winry up here...
He just wants to remind us
they've got some collateral.
I never realized just
how nervous we make them.
I've gotta be patient...
Just wait for my chance.
The advance team took
three days' provisions.
It's been an entire week
since we last heard from them.
[OLIVIER]
That's cutting it close...
I'm also concerned
about the team's sanity.
An entire week
in total darkness...
Briggs men don't
get scared of the dark.
General... There's no telling
what could happen to us
while we're down here.
If we're not back
within twenty four hours,
seal up this
hole with concrete.
Very well then...
I'll do so.
[DOORS SLAMS SHUT]
[BOX SLAMS ON DOOR]
I want all of you to
listen very closely.
I am the only one
responsible for the incident
involving General Raven.
[OLIVIER]
You weren't there...
You didn't see anything...
You didn't hear anything.
If Raven's fate
is discovered...
I order you to solely
place the blame on me.
- Yes, General.
[ROCK WALL SLIDING]
Let's go.
[ROY]
Is that so...?
Sounds like things are
getting out of hand up north.
[FLORIST]
Indeed... They could use
an offensive lead about now.
The Fort Briggs
strong-suit is defense.
But you need
more than defense
if you plan on being the one
to make the first strike.
With the offensive expertise
of your eastern forces,
Madam Olivier believes
they have a chance.
I'm honored that
she would choose me
as her partner in arms.
Oh no...
[FLORIST]
Madam Olivier needs the
strength of your army, not you.
She said you might
as well just get lost.
Uh-huh.
I have to ask...
It's kind of
risky telling me this.
What's stopping me from
warning Fuhrer Bradley?
Well, you are. She assured me
you weren't that kind of man.
Well then...
That'll be thirty-five
thousand cens, please.
I appreciate it.
[ROY]
Hey, wait... Who are you?
[FLORIST]
Oh, just someone who
served the Armstrong family...
...for generations.
[ROY LAUGHS]
[ROY]
Well, Hughes...
It's safe to say
that our closest allies
they invariably turn out to be
the same people that we fought
side by side with
out on the battlefield.
But...
What do I do...
[WOMAN 1]
- Look at him.
- What do I do...
[WOMAN 2]
- What a freak.
- ...with these flowers?
[WOMAN 1]
- Oh, no! He's looking at us!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 4]
It's a massacre.
It's exactly the same
as Smith's arm...
Even this metal was
sliced clean through.
Keep on the lookout.
It might be close.
[BUCCANEER GASPS]
[ADVANCE PARTY GROANING]
[HENSCHEL]
They're still alive!
Are you alright?
Speak to me... Look here.
Lieutenant Henschel?
Thank goodness you're okay.
Is there anyone else?
What happened?
The others were...
They were all...
ripped apart!
Listen!
We have to get out
of here! It's coming back!
[HENSCHEL]
What is?
[LANTERN CLANKING]
Please! You've gotta get rid
of the lights! The shadow!
Hey, you're alright now.
It's coming!
C'mon, pull
yourself together!
The shadow... it's coming!
[ADVANCE PARTY 1 SOBBING]
Can you walk?
[BUCCANEER]
Let's go.
Try to help them walk
as much as you can.
[HAWKEYE]
I'm sorry to
bother you so late.
But I have some
urgent documents
the Fuhrer needs
to read right away.
Oh, my dear...
I'm sorry, but...
My husband isn't
home right now.
It'd be wonderful if he could
look these over by tomorrow.
That is urgent.
But don't you worry.
I'll make sure he does.
Well, thank you.
I apprecia--
Selim...
Shouldn't you be in bed?
[SELIM]
I was, but then
I heard the door.
I thought that it might
be Father coming home.
This is your Father's
assistant, Lieutenant Hawkeye.
It's very nice to
meet you, Lieutenant Hawkeye.
It's nice to meet you.
You must be working
hard to be up so late.
Not really...
I just had to bring your
father some documents.
But I should be
going now. Sorry I woke you.
Goodnight, Selim.
Yes... Come, Selim.
You need
your proper rest...
Otherwise you
might oversleep.
I know.
He seems like
a really sharp kid.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE LAUGHS]
He certainly is.
He's the pride
of my life.
I know it's impolite
to brag about my son,
but that shouldn't apply
since he's adopted.
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
I really shouldn't act
so surprised though...
He is related to my husband, so
he must have some of his genes.
He... He's not
related to you?
Oh, no.
[HAWKEYE THINKING]
This just doesn't add up.
The Colonel told me that
King Bradley was
raised as a test subject.
He doesn't have any family.
He didn't even
know his parents.
And I got that strange feeling
from Selim... Could he be...?
[SELIM]
So you've put
it all together?
All thanks to
my Step Mother...
She just doesn't
know how to shut up.
But you... Your baleful
presence also gave you away.
I recognized it somehow.
But I'm just now realizing why.
It's the same
bloodlust I felt
when Gluttony tried to
attack me from behind.
So, Selim Bradley...
What exactly is
your true identity?
You've got some nerve to
ask me a question like that...
...considering
the circumstance.
Such bravery.
You've also shown good judgment
by keeping your gun holstered.
Such a move would
only get you killed.
I'm guessing you're
a Homunculus, like Gluttony?
No... You've got some kind of
pressure coming from you
that he didn't have.
I'm offended that
you would even put
Gluttony and me
in the same league.
You ask my name...?
It's Pride...
...and I was
the first Homunculus.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
You said you were
the first Homunculus, correct?
What do you mean by that?
Just what I told you.
Are you actually trying to
get information out of me?
You're a courageous
one, aren't you?
Have you considered
switching sides and joining us?
Why would I...?
I'd just be a pawn to you.
So that's a no?
That's too bad. Oh, well.
Are you trying to humor me
with your empty threats?
It's just wasteful
to kill your hostage.
How perceptive you are.
Just remember, Lieutenant.
No matter where you are,
I will be
watching you...
...from the shadows.
[HAWKEYE SHUDDERING]
[ED]
You've got
a job for me?
[KIMBLEE]
That's correct. You are
a State Alchemist after all.
And it's a few jobs actually...
three... All from the Fuhrer.
First off, he wants
you to hunt down Scar.
You just find him,
I'll take care of the rest.
Secondly, he wants
you to locate Dr. Marcoh,
who has very
likely fled with Scar.
Why's Dr. Marcoh with Scar?
The only thing you need to
worry about is finding them.
And last
but not least,
he wants you to carve
a crest of blood here.
A crest of blood...?
Just like what I did
in Ishval. It's very simple.
We kill everyone and
soak the land with their blood.
I would never take part--
[ED SEETHING]
Did you really
join the military
without being
prepared to kill someone?
I was determined
not to kill.
Well how original of you.
I suppose you could take
just as much from that decision.
Listen, Kimblee, do you have
any idea what they're doing?
What you're helping them
to achieve? They're gonna--
I'm curious to see how
the world will change.
What?
Both sides clashing...
Will against will...
Life versus life...
Humans or the Homunculi...?
Which one will triumph...?
Which side does
the world prefer?
The Homunculi like to see
themselves as the next step
in the evolution of humanity...
But that's for
history to decide...
I just plan on helping
it make up its mind.
Have you forgotten
that you're a human?
How can you
take sides with them?
Because they've given
me complete freedom
to use my
alchemy however I want.
You're insane, Kimblee.
My standards do tend
to differ from society's.
However, if
I survive this battle
then the world will have
chosen my sanity over yours.
I stake my being,
the very core of
my own existence,
this is what I'm willing to bet
on the outcome of this battle.
Kimblee, you don't
make any sense.
That's surprising.
I had always kind of assumed
that self-centeredness was
a universal trait
of all alchemists.
Well then...
Let's see if
I can find something
that you do selfishly crave.
Something you and your brother
want more than anything.
And if you do what we ask...
I'll give it to you.
[ED THINKING]
A Philosopher's Stone!
I need to consult...
with Al and Winry.
Why tell Winry?
She has no
idea she's involved.
Despite what
you're asking of me,
I refuse to hide
the truth from her.
Alright then... But you're not
telling her without me there.
I don't want you
telling her too much.
[JAIL DOOR CREEKS AND SLAMS]
Winry, you were only brought
to Briggs as a hostage.
A what...?
What does he mean,
Al? Are you joking?
Listen... I've been
ordered by the Fuhrer
to fulfill my duties
as a human weapon.
In other words,
they're ordering me to help
them commit mass murder.
[WINRY]
Why don't
you just refuse?
I see...
that's why.
No... I'm sorry... they're
using me to hold you down.
I won't cry! I won't.
I'm just upset at
myself for being so naÃ ̄ve.
I'm sorry.
All you were
trying to do
is get your original
bodies back again.
About that...
They actually offered me a
Philosopher's Stone as payment.
A stone...? But...
That's right.
Kimblee has one.
We can't,
Brother!
The ingredients
for a stone are--
I know, Al!
Go ahead and
do what you want.
I will.
[KEYS RUSTLING]
[ED]
It's settled.
I'm in... Alright?
But finding Scar is
the first thing that I wanna do.
Oh, yeah...?
Why's that?
Scar is the one who
murdered Winry's parents.
They deserve vengeance.
[JAIL DOOR CLOSING]
[KIMBLEE]
I see.
Fine with me.
[ED]
Also, I need Al with me.
He doesn't have a body,
so he's immune to
Scar's bodily destruction.
Well, that is helpful.
[WINRY]
You're okay with this, Al?
[AL]
The Philosopher's Stone...?
They can only be made by
sacrificing human lives.
[WINRY GASPS]
Don't worry. Brother would
never actually use one...
And we don't need it...
We think we might be able
to use Xingese alkahestry
to get our bodies back.
There's a girl that's
been working with Scar...
We think that she
can teach it to us.
So then...
Is he going after
Scar to find this girl?
I think so.
I see.
Then I guess
I had better hurry up
and come up with
a believable excuse.
Huh?
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 7 SURPRISED]
This is the general vicinity
in which Scar was last spotted.
Then that's our first stop.
[WINRY]
Hey! Make room for one more!
[ED SCREAMS]
[ED GRUNTS]
Come on, Al,
scoot over some!
What are you doing, Winry?
[KIMBLEE]
I'm sorry, Winry, but you
need to wait here at the fort.
We're not going
for a picnic.
And neither am I!
I just performed a complicated
upgrade on his automail
that I've never done before.
What if there's a malfunction?
[WINRY]
It would tarnish the Rockbell
name if I'm not there to fix it.
Eh...
Do you even realize how
obsessed with your job you are?
You're a workaholic.
And proud of it too!
This has been my family's
business for four generations!
- Very well, then...
- This has been my family's
business for four generations!
- You can join us.
- Oh Yeah! Totally!
- I guess I
can allow you to.
- Four generations of gearheads.
There's nothing
wrong with that!
[ED AND WINRY ANGRILY GRUNTING]
[CAR ACCELERATING]
This could turn out
really badly for us.
Yeah...
[WINRY THINKING]
But still... I can't just
sit around waiting anymore.
[NARRATOR]
Set against the harsh backdrop
of a frigid and
windswept mining town,
an epic battle between humans
and Chimeras rages forth...
The only option in this fight is
to give everything you've got,
but even that's not enough
to guarantee that
you'll live through it.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Thirty Eight...
Conflict at Baschool.
At the moment of victory,
you'll find that
you're most vulnerable.