Thank you for traveling with us
To take the Chuo, Yamanote,
Keihin-Tohoku, Tokaido, Joban,
Sobu and Keio lines
or the Shinkansen
Tohoku, Hokuriku, and Joetsu lines,
please get off at this station.
The departure of this train, Hikari 519,
is scheduled for 5:54 PM.
Excuse me, miss.
Miss, miss!
Are you awake? We are already in Tokyo.
...Thank you.
I was told to get off at Shinagawa
and take the blue train.
But I slept till Tokyo station...
Umm, blue line, blue line...
The sea blue or the sky blue...?
Take the train from Kamata to Kannai...
Kamata to Kannai, Kamata to Kannai...
Kabayaki bento,
katsu sandwhiches, katsu curry!
Kabayaki to katsu...
Kabayaki to katsu curry...
Woow!
Umm...
Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama.
March. Age 17. I moved to Tokyo.
Because I refuse to give in.
To admit I'm wrong.
It's snowing!
1: TOKYO-HO!
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
I'm Iseri, I came for the key.
Of course, I am too late...
No good, huh?
So...
This should be it.
Excuse me, do you know where...?
- Shut up!
- I'm sorry!
Should be here.
Of course...
Usually in these places there's always a spare...
...Or not.
Umm...
Ouch!
I live here.
You need something?
Ehh...
I'm Iseri, I'm gonna be moving next door.
Is that... so? Nice to meet you.
Right.
Just, I don't have a key.
I should have gotten it from the agency earlier today...
- but I was late...
- Did you give them a call?
- My phone ran out of battery...
- Want to use mine?
I had their number in my phone...
I see...
Then want to come in to charge it?
Come on in, don't worry about it.
Umm, no thanks, I'll manage somehow.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, please just look after my suitcase!
Ah, finally!
MOM: 9 MISSED CALLS
Of course.
CALL FROM: SUZUNE
Hello.
Ah, you finally answered!
Mom!
Nina answered the phone!
Sorry, my phone ran out of battery.
What are you doing?
The agency called us.
They said you never arrived.
I know.
I'll go tomorrow.
Shut up. Just leave her be.
I gotta go.
Listen now, do you really think
moving was a good idea?
Sorry, my battery's dying.
I'm performing tonight here!
That's right here! At 10pm?
#KawasakiStation
No way!
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés.
Even if my fingers tremble...
There's no right answers, there's no giving in,
My whole life, I've just been me.
She really is here...
That's all there is to it.
No matter how much I fight from here on,
tomorrow isn't set in stone.
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
You are Kawaragi Momoka-san ...right?
Yes?
I'm a big fan!
Of Diamond Dust, and... of yours...
Thanks.
Umm, I... really love your songs.
I... just arrived to Tokyo from the countryside,
And your songs helped me take the leap.
That so?
It's true!! I mean it.
I've probably... listened to them
thousands of times on my own.
I saw on your socials that
you were performing here today.
It felt like destiny.
Then won't you buy my CD?
Ah, right, of course!
1000 yen...
Here.
Thank you.
That's not 1000 yen...
You sure are uptight.
Eh?
Did I say something dumb?
Nah.
Having fans like you...
it makes me happy.
Hey.
How many times do we have to
tell you this is our turf to perform?
Ah?
Then write your name on it.
Didn't you say you were gonna leave?
Let's go.
Ah, right.
Hey!
You bitch!
Run!
- Eh?
- You're dead if I get you!
Why me too?
Actually, good point.
If you tell'em we're just strangers,
maybe they'll let you go...
Come here!
...Or maybe not.
This way!
Idiots.
What does that sign mean?
It means "thank you".
Then why were they so mad about it?
What's your name?
Nina.
Iseri Nina.
Kawasaki and Shin-Kawasaki stations?
Wouldn't anyone think Kawasaki is next to Shin-Kawasaki?
How was I supposed to know?
Should've looked it up.
My phone ran out of battery.
That why you got locked out?
The agency said Kawasaki
was the best area to live in Tokyo.
They lied to me!
Tokyo?
What about it?
Kawasaki is not part of Tokyo.
It is actually part of Kanagawa,
buddying with Yokohama.
No way,
I was told it was the corner of Tokyo...
The real state agency fooled you completely.
Probably got given a leftover room.
That's why the rent was so low...
Well, I do like it here in Kawasaki.
True, and I got to meet you!
Actually, there's this Diamond
Dust ticket I always carry with me.
If you don't mind, could you sign it?
Thanks for waiting.
A medium gyudon.
Holy COW, it's gyudon!
What? Never had one?
Where did you come from?
From Kumamoto.
Is there no gyudon there?
There is!
But my family had a rule
that we always had to eat at home.
Family precepts
Meals must be always eaten at home
The use of smartphones in the living room is prohibited
A family meeting will take place every Sunday night
Wait... are you from a rich family?
Not quite, but...
Woah!! What is this?!
This is delicious!
Is it that good?
Yes!
Thanks for the food.
Last train's already leaving...
What's your plan?
I'll figure it out.
Like what?
Let's go.
Thanks for the food!
I paid for the both of us.
Thanks for your patronage!
Think of it as taking care of my fans.
It was delicious.
Thank you very much!
You trynna pick a fight?!
Why did you tell me it meant "thank you"?
That's just plain wrong!
Sorry, sorry.
Is this... it?
I'm warning you, it's cold inside.
The heating's not working.
What about your family?
Not here.
These take some time to take off,
go ahead.
The room at the end.
Excuse me.
Light switch should be on the left.
You okay with cats?
Take a seat, I'll make some coffee.
Thank you very much.
So cool...
Hm? Can you play?
Not at all, but as a fan this means a lot.
Wanna try it?
Is it okay?
Go on.
Woah!
It is heavier than I thought.
It doesn't suit you at all.
Of course.
I'm joking!
Anyone can look good holding a guitar.
You're still a high schooler, right?
Yes... I am 17.
I would have been a third year this year.
Want me to add sugar?
Ah, please!
I also left school just after turning 17
and came here with my friends.
That was 3 years ago already.
Eh? So you are only 20?
...I don't like the way you said that.
Well, it may really have been fate.
Yeah! It must be fate!
- Umm...
- You just got here today, right?
Yeah. Umm, if you could...
I'm going back home tomorrow. To Asahikawa.
GIRLS BAND CRY
You are ...going home?
I'm moving out from this place.
Going back home and quitting music.
...but, why? I mean, your songs are incredible...
Thank you.
It'll get cold.
Momoka-san!
Can't help it.
We didn't sell at all.
It's a difficult life to make money
from concerts and music alone.
Had to take job after job after job...
But you made this song, didn't you?
And it's gotten this many views...
I sold it.
I don't own the rights to it anymore.
Explain.
I'm listening.
None of your business.
I'm listening!
I mean, you made that song, right?!
There is no way you could let someone else have it!
There is.
There isn't.
- There is.
- There isn't.
You sure are stubborn.
Fucking Southerners...
Damn right.
Stop that.
Hands off.
Sheesh...
You were so shy just a bit ago,
what's got into you? Weirdo.
It's just, that song...
Hi.
...Hi.
The neighbors will get angry again
if you make too much noise.
Oh? You going out tonight?
Was that...
That was...
Y-y-your boyfriend? H-he is!
Y-you are living togeth-
Chill. Out. Already.
It's Tokyo. Normal to have roommates.
There's no way I could
pay for this place by myself.
But he is a guy, isn't he?
Yeah, but he's into guys.
He's heading to his boyfriend's place next.
Boyfriend...?
Too much!
Tokyo is too much!
We're in Kawasaki...
We keep to our rooms
and have different schedules.
- We rarely see each other.
- Actually...
You should also be thinking
about getting a roommate.
If you tried living by yourself you'd eventually
need to drown yourself in work.
How much is your rent?
50k yen.
Got a job yet?
I have... not chosen one yet.
Are you gonna be okay like that?
I have some savings,
And I was given some
money when I left home.
Ah, so you got it easy.
In that case, do as you want.
As long as you have the money--
What do you think you know about me?
Saying I got it easy...
please don't act like you know me!
Thanks for the coffee. I'm leaving.
Wait!
You sure are fast.
I'm sorry, it was my bad.
You quit school and came all the way here.
There's no way you got it easy.
What's your dream?
I don't really have anything in particular.
Nothing...?
I didn't come here to follow a dream.
I just didn't belong anywhere.
I did nothing wrong, and yet
it was like everything was my fault.
I just didn't want to give in to that.
I see... again, let me apologize.
Did something happen?
Momoka-san...
Why are you going back to Asahikawa?
There's no big reason.
We just kept getting into arguments.
...With Diamond Dust?
Yeah, and when we were disbanding
we were wondering who should keep that song.
The other members wanted
to continue making music so...
You let them have it?
I thought if I wanted to, I could just
make another big hit. Heh.
What?
Aren't you just too nice?
But I think that makes you really cool.
Ouch, ouch!
- You are blushing.
- Shut up!
Sheesh, leave my hair alone!
Wanna go to karaoke?
Right now?
That's a pretty old song.
My grandma liked this one.
From that to Diamond Dust?
Yes... you know,
I found your song when I was at my lowest.
And it really spoke to my feelings.
"I don't want to give up."
It became my song.
You know... that was my
last time singing that song.
My last time singing a Diamond Dust song.
I...
Come on, let's keep it going.
Ouch...
Kitty cat...
Good morning. By the time you read this, I'll have left.
Moving probably started already.
I'm grabbing some stuff from work
and then I'll go straight to the station.
I want you to take my guitar.
Alright then, enjoy your new life in Tokyo.
Sorry! I'll open the door for you.
Yes, this is my luggage. Thank you.
Go for it!
FLIP THEM OFF!
I'll be back in a moment!
Momoka-san?
Momoka-san...
Momoka-san? Momoka-san!
I'm sorry.
W-wait, you're...?!
Momoka-san! Momoka-san!
Are you okay with this?
Once it's over, it's really over!
If you give up and accept it,
there's no more going back!
...You okay?
I know I'm being selfish and
saying whatever I want!
But I came here because I refused to give up!
And I don't want you to give up either!
Please... Let's do it together...
Let's flip them off!!
You can sing, right?
Of course!
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés.
Even if my fingers tremble...
I'm lost at a crossroads that is marked on no map.
What can I even rely on, is there anything like that?
People always tell me to just do it by the book
But its words are so complex I dunno where to look.
My today hasn't changed in all these years.
Is it even possible to fill this void? Maybe someday.
If it were up to you, would you keep going?
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés.
Even if my fingers tremble...
There's no right answers, there's no giving in.
My whole life, I've just been me.
That's all there is to it.
No matter how much I fight from here on,
tomorrow isn't set in stone.
No matter how much I hold on,
NEXT: "THREE NOCTURNAL CREATURES".