Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
along with my food!
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
but sorry for finding out!
gomennasai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
Getting lost in silly conversations
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Chatting about love and relationships
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Say, why can't you make friends?
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
You came right out and asked?!
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You two never quit!
iitai houdai ne
The three leaves are on a rampage,
mitsuba ga daibousou
and there's nobody who can stop them!
dare ni mo tomerarenai
Fall is special.
I eat five times as much.
Ordering the extra large again?
Odagiri Futaba!
Odagiri Futaba, you meanie!
What is this all about?
Oh, poor me!
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
issei no mae mitekou
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
mae mae miteru
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
Three heads are better than one!
sannin yoreba monju no chie
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
Everything's going my way,
hora going my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
susumesou my way
Let's go full steam ahead
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
I'm living the best days of my life,
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
I'm sure that this is a
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
It feels like autumn is here.
It's a little chilly
at this time of day, huh?
Grape picking.
Chestnut hunting,
mushroom picking!
Maple leaf hunting!
Maple leaf hunting...
I wonder if
maple leaves are tasty!
Well, they are all natural,
so perhaps they taste good.
It's the autumn of eating.
You eat like crazy,
no matter the season.
Fall is special.
I eat five times as much.
How about you two?
What kind of autumn is it?
Hmm... The autumn of reading?
The autumn of thriftiness!
Same as usual, then.
Yeah, I guess.
Odagiri Futaba!
Huh?
Wh-Who was that?
Ten Yen Short
What was that all about?
Stuffed Hut
You don't know him?
Nope, never seen him.
How unbelievably rude!
He addressed you so disrespectfully.
As your friend,
I cannot abide such unruly behavior!
He must pay for his impropriety.
It's fine, Youko-sama.
He's just a kid.
He was wearing
East High's uniform, though.
No way, he's a high schooler?
I figured he was
a middle school first-year.
He knew my full name, though.
How did he know that?
All right, here you go!
Special Bucket o' Almond Jello!
Yay!
Here I go!
Youko-sama, you look like
you're disgusted by something.
You'll never finish this one!
Done! I ate it all!
Beaten again...
More like you drank it all.
That was amazing, Futaba-san!
But honestly, it was so amazing
that it unnerved me.
50 Jumbo Dumplings
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
piece
Fried Chicken
Finished!
1000 pieces
When did you do
so many challenges?
You could put this place
out of business.
It's okay.
I do food challenges
at other shops too!
Oh...
You get a commemorative photo for completing
the Bucket o' Almond Jello challenge.
Okay!
Like this? Or maybe like this?
No matter how cutely she poses,
she still just ate a whole bucket of almond jello.
Futaba Odagiri
finished 300 bowls
And those photos have her name on them.
Huh?
Futaba Odagiri
finished 300 bowls
My name?
Futaba Odagiri
finished 300 bowls
I've been thinking about it, and I'm pretty sure
he must've seen my name on the shop photos.
But why was he acting like that?
Right?
I'd understand if he looked up to me.
Normal people
would think you're weird.
Odagiri Futaba!
Is this déjà vu?
But that was a girl...
Unforgivable!
Not once, but twice!
No, they were two different people.
Hang on. They were
two different people, right?
I told you, the second one was a girl.
They did look exactly alike, though.
Why would he dress up as a girl?!
What is this all about?
Maybe I should have
Yamaji look into this.
The guilty must pay the price!
Hey, wanna do karaoke after school?
Oh, I do apologize.
Yeah, sounds good!
S-Sorry. I wasn't paying attention.
She must be the girl Futaba-san
and Hayama-san were talking about.
What? Sh-She's staring at me!
C-Can you meet me after school?
What?!
I wonder what Nishikawa-san
wants to talk about...
Nishikawa-san is pretty,
athletic, and has a great figure.
She's so cool!
I've never been able to approach her,
but now she wants to talk to me!
Ah, there she is.
Wow, you two really do
look exactly the same.
Yeah, they look like twins.
Looks like we made her mad.
Tsuji Sasame-san from Class 2.
Does that sound right?
I don't know the names
of everyone in my class yet.
I haven't exactly talked to them yet.
Why is Odagiri Futaba here with you?!
'Cause we're friends.
What?!
Today was the first time
Nishikawa-san talked to me, though!
Perfect timing. Odagiri Futaba, I have something to say to you!
Huh?
Don't get in my brother's way anymore!
Your brother?!
They must be twins!
He's a year older than I am!
Really?
You look like twins, though.
But how am I in his way?
I haven't done anything.
You have!
I'm talking about his eating challenges!
Eating challenges?
Ahh, so he's the same type as Futaba.
He's failed the challenges
at Stuffed Hut so many times.
I see.
He's stubborn and hates to lose,
so he'll keep overdoing it.
Not to worry.
I'll beat him so bad that he'll lose
all hope of succeeding ever again.
Odagiri Futaba, you meanie!
I just... want to eat.
Oh, poor me!
Yeah, right.
No more
eating
challenges.
-Meat House
No more
eating
challenges.
-Meat House
We reserve
the right
to refuse
Odagiri Futaba.
CHALLENGE
RESTAURANT
Banned!!
Maybe I overdid it...
But nothing on the
normal menu fills me up.
And I'm flat broke.
Welcome!
Stuffed Hut
Futaba-chan, welcome!
Ordering the extra large again?
Mr. Stuffed!
I'll just have
something normal today.
I don't wanna get banned
from here too!
What, something normal?!
Yup!
I'll have a large helping of curry topped with
egg, corn, cheese, croquette, cutlet, and sausage.
That's not normal!
Oh, huh?
So, you're the other Tsuji?
Mister!
I'll have the same thing
as Odagiri Futaba!
I won't lose, Odagiri Futaba!
You're my rival!
All right, here ya go.
Thanks!
Thank you!
XL Rice Bowl
XL Parfait
XL Noodles
XL Meat
XL Challenge
Delicious!
I won't lose, Odagiri Futaba!
I won.
I won!
I beat her!
I finished before you,
Odagiri Futaba!
Now you're no longer the—
Hey, Mr. Stuffed.
Did you change your ingredients?
I knew you'd be able to tell.
I used some new seasonal veggies.
I finished first!
There's no point in racing
if it's not a competition.
I want to savor it.
Wh—?
Dammit!
I'll remember this, Odagiri Futaba!
I won't forgive you, Odagiri Futaba!
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Oh, there she is!
Those are delicious!
Teru-chan!
Onee-chan.
Come on, let's go home together.
Odagiri Futaba.
If she's going to do a challenge somewhere,
I have to stop her!
But if I do, then Nishikawa-san
might not like me anymore...
Oh, what should I do?
I see. So that boy
is Futaba-chan's rival.
It's a one-sided rivalry.
Now that I think about it,
Onee-chan eats a lot too.
Is that so?
Well, you know
how she's a little spacey.
She eats while she's spaced out.
So it takes a while for her
to realize that she's full.
That's pretty spacey...
Something...
There's something...
Right there!
Huh?
Apologies.
Did you detect my presence?
Oh my, Yamaji.
What? It was just Yamaji?
You snuck up on us this time,
so it scared me.
Maybe I was just imagining it.
I thought there was somebody else.
I'm quite confident
in my stealth skills.
All right, let's go.
Hm?
Huh?
What's that?
One, two, pull!
Oh.
Tsuji-san?
Are you the sister
of Futaba-chan's rival?
Oh no!
How did you know?
Well...
There aren't many people
who'd fall for a trap like that these days.
This is how I catch my brother!
Hey, don't put me on his level.
I was trying to stop Odagiri Futaba
from doing more eating challenges!
But I didn't want Nishikawa-san to get mad at me,
so I tried to stay undercover.
She can hear you loud and clear.
I can't believe you'd set up a foul trap
in the middle of the road!
How atrocious!
This is all your fault,
Odagiri Futaba!
And there she goes,
just like her brother.
She set a trap!
Futaba-san, she's after your life.
Be careful!
My life?
Was it okay to talk to her like that?
What do you mean?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you've had a real conversation with?
That's right!
Before her, you hadn't talked
to anyone in your class.
Youko-sama, you're usually
a friendless loner in all your classes.
She's a valuable—
Yamaji!
Well, Tsuji-san's brother
is determined too.
It seems like we'll be seeing him
a lot from now on.
Don't worry. I'll beat him so bad
that he'll never recover.
That's really not necessary.
Maybe you can be nicer to him.
You both do like to eat a lot.
Hmm... I don't know.
Can you keep it down?
I'm trying to read here.
Oh, sorry.
What are you reading, Nishiyama-san?
Hey!
Murder Mystery!!
Oh.
N-No!
So you like these types of books?
I wouldn't have guessed.
I-I borrowed this.
Oh, that's the book I lent her.
See?
I buy most of them, but we've both
been huge fans since elementary school.
Especially Nishiyama.
Y-You didn't need to say that!
I-It's all right.
We all have our own tastes.
Why are you smirking like that?
It's fine.
It's not weird or anything.
It's kind of cute and easy to read.
It's still a book.
I-I won't forget this!
This seems to be happening a lot lately.
Which is why you should
be nicer to Tsuji-san's brother.
You're telling me to be nice?
Isn't she the first person in your class
you've had a real conversation with?
That is true.
But she was so rude to Futaba-san!
E-Excuse me.
Er, um... I-I'm s—
I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, my money.
Oh my!
Let's see...
Oh, there's one here too!
Nishikawa-san...
I'm ten yen short.
What?!
I wanted to buy strawberry milk...
I wonder where it went.
We must find it!
Oh, i-it's okay. It's just ten yen.
Just ten yen?!
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, Youko-sama.
What are you doing?
Odagiri Futaba's friend.
You're...
I'm Hayama from Class 3.
Tsuji-san dropped some coins, you see.
Oh, did you drop them around here?
Ah! I just realized.
It was my fault.
I'm surrounded
by Odagiri Futaba's friends!
Oh no.
What should I do?!
What?! Was it a lot of money?
Yes, her precious ten yen.
Ten yen...?
Here.
You can have it.
But if you'd rather,
you can also just borrow it.
See you.
I'm very sorry!
Oh, um...
Now what?
I'm in debt to one of
Odagiri Futaba's friends.
But...
I got to talk to Nishikawa-san a little.
And Hayama-san was nice.
I'm just going to return this.
Really? That sounds
just like Youko-sama.
She had that determined look that said "every yen counts!"
But that's what's so great about her.
She's been working
for a while now too.
Nishikawa-san works part-time?!
Huh?
The younger one?
Is Nishikawa-san working part-time?
I can't believe it.
Yup, at a cake shop at the outskirts
of the Central Shopping Plaza.
They handed out flyers
at our school before.
Oh.
This is it, huh?
Oh, wow!
There's a maid!
And someone who looks like a butler!
Nishikawa-san totally would work at such an amazing shop!
Tsuji-san?
Oh, you came already.
Oh, er...
What are you waiting for? Let's go in!
Wh... um...
Oh, this is good.
What a lovely fragrance.
Hey, where's the new cake?
Wh-What?!
How is this happening?!
What's wrong?
Drink it while it's still hot.
Smells nice.
It's good!
You like it?
This is one of my favorites.
Yup.
Here they are.
I've been waiting!
Huh?
We came to try the new cake.
I-Is it okay for me to try too?
What, you don't like cake?
Well, if you insist...
Ah! I'll eat it, I'll eat it!
You don't have to force it...
I'm not!
Oh really?
Yes! I like cake.
Good for you, Youko-sama.
Hmm?
Then I'll feed you.
You've made another friend.
Here, open wide.
Friend?
I can feed myself!
I guess when you put it that way...
It was a miracle just to have
Hayama-sama and Odagiri-sama.
In the end, having another high school girl
here will make things more fun for me.
You can make friends
even without money!
It's a good thing
that you became poor.
When you were rich and aloof...
Q-Quiet, you mongrels!
I can't believe that Tsuji-san
actually came to the shop.
Is she my friend?
I wonder... I'm not sure.
All right, pair up!
I need to find a partner...?
N-Nishikawa-san!
She called out to me!
Until now, I was always stuck
with the last person or the teacher.
She wants to pair up with me?
U-Um...
Hmm?
Are you all right?
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if it's turned black inside
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if I can't be extravagant
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
ryou ga ookutemo
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
sannin dakara tabechaou
I'm not wasting electricity at night
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Things that make me smile?
egao ni nareru mono
Food! Money! And things I can't say
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
Let's have fun and make silly memories
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
Will continue forever in just the same way
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
If you want to know the answer to one times three
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
Then come on over here
nee koko ni oide
Next  week
Now, next week's
Three Leaves, Three Colors will be...
Next  week
I'm Sasame.
Um... er... that's...
Oh, next time we'll have:
"The Cursed Sword,"
"Place of Death," and "Red Spider Lily."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Next
Time:
You've Got Them Hooked
Next
Time:
You've Got Them Hooked
Next
Time:
You've Got Them Hooked