Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Yutaka!
It's almost time to go!
Oof.
Okay, little sister of mine.
Today's the beginning of your new life!
Let's go with a bang!
Under One Roof
I'm here to report that Yutaka's passed and say hi!
Welcome.
Come on, Yutaka!
I-I'll probably be causing lots of trouble...
...but I hope we can get along well!
Just think of this as your own home.
Yes.
Let me start by congratulating you on passing.
Thank you!
It's a good thing she passed.
Now you can meet that handkerchief girl.
I win at life.
Going back in time
The day of Yutaka's Exams
Um...
Are you all right?
Do you want me to take you to the nurse's office?
So she talked to me...
Right after the exams
...and even lent me her handkerchief!
I'm so happy that I might be able to make a good friend.
But Yutaka...
She might've failed.
That won't happen!
People like her definitely pass!
I know how you feel...
She's definitely smart!
Thank you for the baseless rebuttal.
But you know,
Yu-chan.
What if you fail?
That's actually possible...
Well, you should be fine.
That's right.
I should be able to meet her on the day they announce results regardless.
I see.
I have to return the handkerchief.
You will be notified by mail of your results.
And then
The day of orientation and uniform fitting
E-Excuse me!
Here.
I'm glad I ran into you.
I've been wanting to return this.
You came to deliver this?
Yes.
I guess I ended up troubling you.
I didn't expect to ever see you again.
I never intended to have this returned.
I was worried I might fail.
Oh.
I see.
If you're here now...
...you're in the same year.
I'm sorry.
You probably thought I was someone's little sister.
I came by car today.
O-Okay.
Then we'll be parting here.
Um...
I hope we can have a great three years!
What a relief.
I already became friends with such a nice person in high school.
I didn't ask what her name was.
Turning back the clock
Make sure you ask for her name next time.
Present
Are you feeling sick, Yu-chan?
I think I got a little carsick.
I took some medicine, though...
Sorry to worry you.
Yutaka's got such a weak body.
Wait.
That's part of it...
I'll rub your back-
...but you need to realize what your driving's like, Yui-neesan.
Thanks-
Even I get a little blargh...
But I'm the only one from my old school who's going to Ryouou...
And I'll probably get sick again like today...
I'm worried about if I can get along with my classmates.
You're a good girl so it'll be fine.
You're treating me like a child!
Sickly
Little Sister
Pure
Brain...
Little Sister
Cute
Pure
Little Sister
...converting...
Walking
Pillar of Moe
Little Sister
Pure
If Yu-chan got together with our Miyuki-san, it'd be pretty crazy.
That's right.
I'm in Konata-oneechan's house now.
Onee-chan.
Good morning!
You're up awfully early when we don't have school.
Morning.
Actually, I'm about to hit the sack.
I was gaming all nigh-
This really is a different environment!
We have to take exams next year, huh?
We've been getting a bunch of phone calls from cram schools.
It's a pain.
If you use caller ID...
...you should be able to pick out those kinds of calls immediately,
since they use unlisted numbers.
I'm home!
Caller ID, huh?
I've come home!
My...
Is that so?
That must have been difficult.
Not at all...
It's the same for our family.
Well, my daughter's returned...
Yes.
Until we talk again.
Sorry to have taken up your time.
Who was on the phone?
It sounded like you were having a lively conversation.
It was from a telemarketer.
Um...
Didn't you say that you could pick out those calls immediately?
But you know...
I was bored and felt like having a conversation.
We talked over an hour.
This should be your total.
Whistherealdreadyanewitem!?
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
Tsukasa!
This world is always a battlefield!
You can never show mercy!
The other day, there was a little item I wanted...
Should I exchange my points...
I spent half a day thinking about it...
...Nah... but
there's other stuff I want...
Okay!
...and ended up deciding to exchange my points...
I'll go on the offensive!
But now there's already a new item I really want!
Look! Over there!
I don't have enough points left!
What to do!?
You sure enjoy your life.
Uh...
You haven't paid...
Would you prefer smoking or non-smoking?
Well...
We're minors,
so a non-smoking table please.
Then please follow me.
I'm going to the restroom first.
Hey, Tsukasa!
Over here!
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Hey...
I've been wondering...
Why are the restrooms in these places...
...usually located near the smoking section?
That's true.
Especially when we're in the non-smoking section.
But really...
I wonder why...
So there's a nearby water source if a fire starts.
They have buckets and hoses, too.
They even have hoses.
They do!
They sure do!
Typical of a person who's never worked out in the real world.
What a pain.
Good grief.
You're annoying!
Or maybe to cover up the stink.
And like...
Don't talk about this stuff while we're eating.
Stuff like the stink or restrooms...
Currently, in the city...
...a number of elementary school girls...
...have been approached from behind while on their way to school...
There are a lot more cases of kids being targeted.
You should be careful, Yu-chan.
That's right.
You have to!
Well, I can understand the perpetrator's way of thinking...
Really...
He's been all over the news for consecutive days now...
...yet he's still going up to little kids!?
What does he want!?
I really want to tell him something!
Man, I'm jealous.
I have no idea what you're thinking,
but don't do anything that'll get you arrested by Yui-neesan.
Excuse me!
Coming!
Hey!
I'm here!
Welcome!
Oh, where's Kagami today?
She went out with some friends from her class.
I see.
I'm kinda annoyed and then it feels like something's missing...
I guess you're lonely.
It's gotten really warm lately.
Sure has.
We don't have any homework for spring break...
...so it's really tranquil.
Sure is.
Pretty sure that...
...only people who normally work hard have the right to say that.
Don't hit any weird places!
No more!
Say...
Do you even recognize the characters in these robot games?
Some of them.
I see...
Since your manga and anime preferences...
...were influenced by your dad.
Yep.
In that case...
Didn't you have a hard time understanding what your female friends were talking about when you were little?
Why?
I actually saw more of that kind of stuff, so there wasn't any problem.
Really...
Huh?
Is that your final answer?
Final answer!
Why can't they just tell us?
I couldn't even breathe.
And his face is scary!
And huge.
Looking at the clock, she must have gotten the question wrong.
The show's already over.
Wait, Tsukasa!
Could you stop guessing if they got the question right based on the amount of time left when they cut to commercial!?
But I can't take the waiting...
And they really drag it out...
Isn't that the point of the show!?
But it's what Tsukasa would do.
Yo.
Yahoo!
Let me introduce you.
This is my cousin, Yu-chan.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
These are my friends Tsukasa and Kagami.
Then you're the ones Onee-chan's always talking about...
What does she say about us?
Hey.
What did you tell her?
Though, I can guess from her reaction...
See?
Just like I told you.
Did you already have your graduation ceremony, Yutaka-chan?
Yes.
A few days ago.
Graduation, huh?
Brings back memories.
I don't even remember our graduation.
Did you get a second button from anyone, Yutaka-chan?
No, I didn't.
Our middle school uniform was a blazer.
Oh, yeah...
I guess a lot more schools are like that now.
Actually...
...does the practice of getting something from the person you like still exist?
Really?
That's kinda sad.
Not that I ever did it.
If you read blogs...
...it looks like quite a few people are still doing it.
But you know...
You take it from someone you like, right?
Well, in most cases.
Then...
...wouldn't going to get a button be the same as confessing how you feel?
Wouldn't it be better to just confess and get the guy instead of a button?
Get you!
Ideally, sure.
That's right.
Did you like anyone at your old school?
No.
I was often absent from school...
When I did go, I would soon get sick.
I just made everyone feel bad.
And I'm all small...
...and I look like a child...
...so everyone always teased me.
I never had time to like anybody...
Don't worry!
You'll have no problems if you aren't picky!
Wh-What!?
Pocky!
Yu-chan.
Show me your graduation yearbook.
I wanna see it!
This is kinda embarrassing.
I don't show up very often.
Yu-chan, what class were you in?
You checked the absentee section first, didn't you!?
You could tell?
The differences between middle school and high school?
The fact that joining a club is no longer mandatory.
Doesn't that depend on the school?
Our school's geared towards getting into college...
...so there will probably be more material at a faster pace.
And the commute takes a while...
...so you'll need some stamina.
The decisive difference is that...
...class time naps have grown longer from grade school to middle school to high school.
Especially during classes you're bad at!
That's actually true!
The teacher sounds like he's talking in a foreign language...
...and my mind just starts slipping away!
Make sure you don't end up like them.
You brought your middle school uniform.
Our uniform is pretty plain,
so I thought I could wear it normally.
Since I'm no longer close to school.
I see.
What did you guys do with your uniforms?
We gave ours to some younger neighbors.
What about you?
Mine?
Well...
You wouldn't be able to give yours to anyone.
Be quiet.
How rude.
I saved mine for cosplay use like Yu-chan.
C-Cos...?
When you put it that way...
...it really gets on my nerves.
But it's cosplay.
Anyway...
Our old school, huh?
Now that you've brought it up...
...I kind of want to go visit my grade school and middle school.
But there have been a bunch of incidents involving trespassing...
...so people might give you funny looks.
Well, you don't have to worry.
You'll fit in just fine.
Pretty sure that wasn't a compliment.
But vacations sure pass by quickly.
That's true.
Before you know it, it's back to school.
Spring is a pain with physical exams and measurements.
But you've got really athletic nerves. Lucky you.
Hey, Tsukasa.
Which nerves are the athletic nerves?
Hello, everyone!
I'm a little late...
...but congratulations on graduating, Yutaka!
Nee-san.
Welcome.
To celebrate...
...let's all go get smashed!
Invite your dad, too.
My treat!
Onee-chan!
We can't do that!
She means juice-
Officer, we're still minors.
W-We can't!
Onee-chan.
I don't think we can go in those places yet.
If you just stroll on in...
...they'll never catch you!
I did it all the time when I was a student!
They never caught me once!
So you did-
No.
We can't!
Your two relatives will get us caught.
We can't, Onee-chan!
I see...
Don't mind.
Since Yu-chan's here...
...we could go to Disneyland or something.
Since it's spring break.
Um...
I really appreciate it...
...but I'm already imposing...
...so you don't have to go so far.
And I already went there on a school field trip a while back.
Yeah, I had a field trip like that, too.
But were you all right?
I didn't get sick.
It was fun!
And I was with my friends.
No...
I was talking about the minimum height for rides.
It was okay!
I'm in high school now!
So I was watching this school drama...
...when I realized there are a lot of differences between middle school and high school.
Guess so.
They stop feeding you in high school.
That's right.
You make your own lunch or eat in the cafeteria.
Or buy a lunch to bring.
Do you make a box lunch every day!?
P-Pretty much.
That's amazing!
This could get ugly...
You're really good at games!
Skilled at many forms of communication!
You can even cook and do other housework!
I've recently learned how much pressure an older sister feels.
You have to work hard with those eyes on you, right...
...Kagami?
Yui-neesan, wild at the wheel.
Hey!
Doing good?
Yui-neesan, comes home drunk.
Homework?
Just put down something random.
Yui-neesan, never serious about anything.
But I guess it depends on the person.
Make it so I can understand you.
Final answer!
Man, I seriously can't take this.
I finally get to record a line for the actual show...
Doing it again today.
...but I wasn't even on screen!
What are they thinking when they make this show?
Again.
Why am I stuck with this lame crap anybody could come up with...
Akira-sama!
The title call.
Title call!
U-Uh...
The title call...
Tiny eyes!
Good lucky...
This isn't the time for that.
Unbelievable. Incredible.
Only my voice. My voice.
My appearance was pointless.
U-Uh...
I wasn't on screen either.
Nobody gives a damn about you!
Windy, huh?
Hey...
Did I ask about you?
Hey.
Did I ever mention you?
N-No...
You didn't say a word about me.
So why did you bring yourself up?
Don't be so self-centered.
Are you an idiot?
You're always like, "Me, me, me."
That's called being overly self-conscious.
Make yourself scarce, Shiraishi.
Sheesh, I'm gonna end up with a dirty mouth.
Listen up.
The issue here is the fact that Kogami Akira wasn't shown in the actual show.
Sure is.
Let me ask you. What am I?
An idol, right?
An idol depends on her looks, right?
Isn't it a given that I should be on screen?
What do you think?
Y-Yes!
You're absolutely right, sah!
I can't hear you.
T-The staff for this episode...
...acted in a logic-defying manner, sah!
What are you writing?
Revenge of Kogami Akira
This special
broadcast
has ended!!!
Okay?
Here's a request from Akira!
The world is waiting for Akira!
Project Full Appearance in Actual Show!
Please show your support on the home page and other places.
Akira needs everybody's support to appear in the actual show.
So send in loads of encouragement!
Loads...
Any method works!
Just give them a push!
Say that you're dying to see me appear in the actual show!
Dying...
Just between you and me.
The other members of the cast...
...can't hold a candle...
...to a performance that features Akira's amazing talent and charm!
She's desperate...
She's really desperate today...
You can't wait to see such a pretty and gorgeous performance!
This is your chance!
Don't let it slip away!
Your feedback...
...can make this a reality!
What is it?
So the second this show ends, start getting to work...
Stop her?
Understood.
Um, Akira-sama...
Shut up!
Stop butting in!
I was on a roll!
How many times do I have to tell you not to get in my way!?
What? Already?
I wanted to tell you more about how wonderful Akira is.
You can see a lot more of my true charm during next week's actual show.
Just kidding.
Uh...
Look forward to next time!
Bye-bee!
It's over.
I'm in pain.
Hey, you.
Go get the producer!
Me!?
First of all...
Yes.
This week's modified manuscript was wrong.
What's the name of this program!?
Uh, Lucky Channel?
It said Lucky Paradise.
Well... Also...
What is it?
You've got guts to treat me like this!
Just because your last show was a hit!
Hey, producers!
Wait, you really shouldn't be saying that!
Don't mess with me!
Hey!
Miyagi-san!
Hello, I'm Shiraishi Minoru!
Okay! Please listen to me!
wakuwaku shitai to negainagara sugoshitetara
I've lived my life wishing for excitement.
kanaete kureta no wa dare na no
Who made my dream come true?
iroiro yosou ga dekisou de dekinai mirai
Some futures you can guess. Some you can't.
sore demo hitotsu dake wakaru yo
But there's still one thing I know for sure.
jikan no hate made
Even to the end of time!
boooon
Boooon!!
WAAPU de RUUPU na kono omoi wa
These looping feelings...
nanimou kamou makikonda sozou de asobou!
...warp everyone in to play with imagination!
aru hareta hi no koto
One clear, sunshiny day...
mahou ijou no yukai ga
...happiness greater than magic...
kagirinaku furisosogu
...pours down with no end in sight.
fukanou janai wa
It could happen!
ashita mata au toki
When we meet again tomorrow...
warai nagara hamingu
...we'll be smiling and humming!
ureshisa wo atsumeyou
Let's bring together happiness!
kantan nanda yo konna no
It's an easy thing to do!
oikakete ne
Keep on chasing!
tsukamaete mite
Try to catch it!
ookina yume & yume SUKI deshou?
We love big dreams, right?
The End
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Iwasaki Minami.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
Iwasaki-san.
The two of us are supposed to introduce the next episode.
Do you know what it's about?
I don't.
Sorry.
Really?
That's not good.
I don't know either.
Then we'll stop here.
「 Can't Change
So Quickly 」
Next time:
"Can't Change So Quickly."
Is it okay that we didn't say anything?
Look forward to next time.