Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
She's really desperate today.
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Yutaka, it's almost time to go!
Now, my little sister, your new life starts today!
Let's go with a bang!
Under One Roof
I'm here to report that Yutaka passed, and to say hi!
Hey, welcome.
Come on, Yutaka...
I-I will probably be a burden on you guys...
But I hope we can get along well!
Feel free to make yourself at home here.
Y-Yes.
First of all, congratulations on passing.
Thanks!
It's a good thing you passed.
Now you can meet that handkerchief girl.
I so win at life.
Going back in time
The day of Yutaka's Exams
Um...
Are you all right?
Do you want me to take you to the nurse's office?
And after saying that,
Right after the exams
she even loaned me her handkerchief!
I'm so happy that I might have made a good friend.
But Yutaka,
that person might have failed.
That won't happen!
People like her will definitely pass!
I understand how you feel but...
She has to be really smart!
Thank you for that baseless rebuttal.
But Yu-chan...
What's going to happen if you fail?
That's certainly not impossible...
Though I'm sure Yu-chan will be fine.
Oh yeah!
I should be able to see her on the day they announce the results, regardless of passing.
I see...
I have to return the handkerchief to her.
You will be notified by mail of your results.
And then
The day of orientation and uniform fitting
E-Excuse me...
Here.
I'm so glad I met you.
I've wanted to return it to you all this time.
You came to deliver this?
Yes.
I feel bad now.
I didn't think I'd ever meet you again,
so I wasn't expecting to get this back.
Like, you expected me to fail?
Not exactly...
I see.
If you're here right now, that means were in the same grade.
I'm sorry.
You probably thought I was someone's little sister.
I'm getting picked up today...
O-Okay.
Then we'll part ways here.
Um...
I hope we can have a great three years together!
I'm so glad.
I've made such a nice friend in high school already.
I forgot to ask her name.
Turning back the clock
Make sure you ask for her name next time.
Present
I took some medicine, though...
Sorry for making you worry.
Yutaka has such a weak little body, doesn't she?
Well...
That's true,
I'll rub your back-
but have you ever considered what your driving is like, Yui-neesan?
Thanks-
Even I feel it sometimes.
But I'm the only one from my old school who's going to Ryouou,
and I'll probably feel unwell like today again...
I wonder if I'll be able to get along with my classmates...
Yutaka, you're a god girl, so you'll be fine.
You're treating me like a kid!
Sickly
Little Sister
Pure
Brain...
Little Sister
Cute
Pure
Little Sister
Converting...
Walking
Pillar of Moe
Little Sister
Pure
If Yu-chan teamed up with our Miyuki-san, it'd be something amazing!
That's right...
I'm at Konata-oneechan's house now.
Onee-chan, good morning!
You're up awfully early even though it's a holiday.
Oh, good morning.
Actually, I was just about to go to sleep.
I was gaming all night-
I'm really in a different environment now!
We're finally taking exams next year, huh.
I've been getting a lot of calls from cram school and such.
It's a pain.
If you use caller ID...
...you should be able to recognize numbers like those immediately.
Since the numbers they use are unlisted.
I'm home!
Hm?
Caller ID, huh...
I've returned home!
Oh, is that so?
Why, that must be really difficult.
Not at all, it's the same with our family.
Well, my daughter just came home...
Yes.
Until we talk again.
Take good care of yourself as well.
Who was on the phone?
It sounded like you were really enjoying the conversation.
It was a telemarketer.
Um...
Didn't you say you could recognize those calls right away?
Yes, well...
I was a little bored, so I wanted to have a conversation.
We talked for over an hour.
And your total for these two items comes to...
zomgthereisanewitemwtf!?
What's the matter, Kona-chan!?
Tsukasa...
This world is always at war!
There is no mercy!
The other day there was a prize that I kind of wanted,
Should I exchange my points...
...Nah... but
so after debating for over half a day, I decided to trade in my points.
there's other stuff I want...
Okay!
I'll go on the offensive!
But now there is already a new prize that I want even more!
See, right there!
I don't have enough points!
What should I do!?
You sure are enjoying your life to the fullest.
Umm, your total...
Would you prefer the smoking or non-smoking section?
Well...
We're under-age, so the non-smoking section please.
Then right this way please.
I'm going to use the restroom first.
Okay.
Hey, Tsukasa!
We're over here!
Welcome back.
I'm back.
You know,
I've always wondered...
Why are the restrooms usually on the smoking side in these places?
That's true.
Especially after the trouble of being seated at a non-smoking table.
But really... Why is it?
So that if something were to catch on fire, there would be a nearby water source.
They have buckets and hoses as well.
They even have hoses?
Of course!
They sure do!
So typical of a person who's never worked in society.
How troubling.
Good grief!
Shut up!
Or to put the lid on the stench.
Rather, let's not talk about this stuff while we're having lunch.
Stuff like the stench or restrooms...
"Today an elementary school girl...
was approached from behind while on her way home from school..."
There are a lot of cases of kids being targeted, nowadays.
"Similar cases have increased in number."
You should be careful, too, Yu-chan.
That's right...
Unacceptable!
Well, I can kind of understand how the perpetrator feels...
You do?
Even after it's turned into such a big case in the media,
he still goes up to little girls like that!?
What does he want!?
I just want to go up and tell him,
"Aren't you jealous?"
I have no idea what you're thinking,
but just don't do anything that will make Yui-neesan arrest you.
Excuse me!
Coming!
Hey, I'm here!
Welcome!
Speaking of which, where's Kagami today?
She went out with some friends for her class.
I see.
How do I put it...
It feels depressing and lacking at the same time.
You're lonely, aren't you?
It's become a lot warmer lately.
Yeah, it has.
There's no homework over spring break,
so it's so peaceful.
Yeah, it is.
I believe that line...
...belongs to those who normally work diligently on their homework.
"Don't hit any place weird!"
"I'm done!"
Say,
do you even know the characters in robot games like these?
Yeah, for the most part.
I see...
You said your interest in anime and manga was a result of your dad's influence...
Yep, yep.
In that case,
did you have a hard time keeping up with the girl-talk when you were little?
Why?
I actually saw a lot of that kind of stuff, so I understood it better than the other girls.
Eh?
Oh... really...
Huh?
"Is that your final answer?"
"Yes, final answer!"
Why can't they tell us yet?
I thought I was going to suffocate.
His face is big and...
...scary.
Based on the time, she probably got this question wrong.
The show is almost over.
Hey, Tsukasa!
Could you stop trying to predict whether they get the question right or wrong...
...based on the time they cut to the last CM!?
But I can't take the suspense.
And they really drag it out...
Isn't that the point of the show?
Though that does sound very Tsukasa-like.
Yo.
Yahoo!
Let me introduce you.
This is my cousin, Yu-chan.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
These are my friends Tsukasa and Kagami.
Oh, then you're the ones Onee-chan is always talking about.
Hmm?
What does she say?
What did you tell her about us?
Though I can guess from her reaction...
See?
Just like I told you.
Yutaka-chan, did you finish your graduation ceremony already?
Oh, yes.
Just the other day...
Graduation, huh?
That brings back memories.
I don't remember my graduation.
Yutaka-chan, did you get a second button from anyone?
Oh no... not at all.
Our middle school used blazers.
Speaking of which, I've seen a lot of schools like that lately.
Or actually...
Maybe people don't give stuff to people they like as much as they used to.
I wonder...
That's kind of sad.
Not that I ever did it myself.
Well, according to the blogs and stuff online,
it seems quite a few people still do it.
I see...
And you're supposed to take one from the person you like, right?
Yeah, usually.
In that case, going to get one is like confessing your love,
so wouldn't it be better to just confess and get the actual guy instead of the button?
Get you!
Well, I guess that would be ideal.
Oh yeah, Yutaka-chan,
did you have someone you liked at your old school?
Not at all.
I was often absent from school,
and when I did go, I would quickly fall ill.
Hardly someone to get worked up over.
And I'm also not that tall...
And my figure is like a child's,
so everyone always made fun of me.
I never had a chance to like someone or be liked...
Don't worry!
As long as you don't mind what the guy looks like, there is a demand for your type!
D-Demand?
*pocky*
Yu-chan, lemme see your graduation album.
Oh, I want to see it, too!
This is kind of embarrassing.
I'm not in it that much.
Yu-chan, what class were you in?
You asked that after you checked the absentee list first, didn't you?
Ah, you could tell?
Hm?
The differences between middle school and high school?
Like how it's not mandatory to join a club?
Doesn't that depend on the school?
We're a college preparatory high school,
so there will probably be a lot more material to study at a faster pace than in middle school.
And the commute takes a while, so it's tiring.
One difference you can count on...
...is the increase in the amount of time spent sleeping in class as you advance through school.
Especially in classes you're bad at!
That's so true!
When the teacher starts sounding like he's speaking in a foreign language...
Just don't end up like them, okay?
...I just can't stay conscious!
O-Okay...
Yu-chan, you brought your middle school uniform.
Our uniform is pretty plain,
so I thought I could use it as casual clothes.
Since it's not from around here either.
I see.
What did you guys do with your uniforms?
We gave them to some younger kids in our neighborhood.
And you?
Mine?
Well,
I doubt anyone would need one in your size.
Be quiet.
How rude.
I saved mine just like Yu-chan...
...for cosplay use.
C-Cos...?
When you put it that way,
it sounds really bad.
But cosplay is cosplay.
Anyway,
that reminds me of old times... my alma mater.
Now that you've brought that up,
it makes me want to check out my elementary school and middle school.
But lately there have been a lot of cases involving stalkers and intruders,
so you might not want them to get the wrong idea.
Well, at least you don't have to worry about that.
You'll fit in just fine.
I take it that wasn't a compliment.
But breaks sure pass by quickly.
That's true.
Before you realize it, school's in session again.
Spring is a drag because we have physical examinations and measurements.
But you have athletic nerves, so I'm jealous.
Hey, Tsukasa.
Which nerves are the athletic ones?
Hello everyone!
I'm a little late,
but congrats on your graduation, Yutaka!
Oh, Nee-san, welcome.
In order to celebrate it,
how about we all go out for some drinks!
Invite your dad, too!
My treat!
Onee-chan, that's not legal!
She means juice-
Ms. Policewoman, we're still underage.
We can't, we can't!
Onee-chan,
I don't think we can enter places like those yet.
Oh, if you just keep your cool,
they'll never find out!
I did it all the time when I was a student,
So you did-
We can't, Onee-chan!
and I never got caught!
No, no...
We'll get caught because of two of your relatives.
We can't!
I see.
Don't mind.
Since Yu-chan is here,
how about we all go to Disneyland or something?
It's spring break after all.
Um, I really appreciate it,
but I'm already imposing so much on you,
so I don't want to cause anymore trouble.
I actually went there on a school field trip a while back...
Oh, I think I had a field trip like that, too.
But Yu-chan, were you okay?
Yeah, I didn't get sick.
It was fun!
I was with my friends, too.
No,
I was talking about the height limits for rides and such.
Of course, I cleared that!
I'm in high school now!
So I was watching this school drama...
...when I realized there are a lot of differences between middle school and high school.
I guess so.
They don't serve you lunch anymore in high school, do they?
That's true.
You have to make your own bento or eat at the cafeteria.
Or you can buy a lunch to bring.
Do you make a boxed lunch every day!?
P-Pretty much...
That's amazing!
It's going to be tough from now on...
She's really good at games!
Skilled with various forms of communication!
She can even cook and do other housework, too!
Lately, I've started to learn how much pressure an older sister feels.
When they look at you with those eyes, it really makes you try harder,
doesn't it, Kagami?
Huh?
Yui-neesan, who goes crazy behind the wheel.
Yahoo!
How you doin'?
Yui-neesan, who comes home drunk.
Homework...?
Just put down whatever, and you'll be fine!
Yui-neesan, never serious about anything.
But I guess it depends on the person.
Can you speak in terms I understand?
Final answer!
Man, I seriously can't take this.
I thought I finally made it after recording a line for the actual show,
Here we go again...
but when I played it back, guess who wasn't even on screen?
Is she going to do it?
What the hell are they thinking when they make this show?
She's going to do it...
Why am I stuck with this nonsense...
A-Akira-sama, the title call...
that anyone could have come up with-
The title call!
Huh?
Uh, well...
The title call...
Whoa, tiny eyes!
Oha-lucky...
I really don't have time for that.
This is unbelievable.
How can they do this?
It was my voice...
Just my voice!
My appearance was pointless.
U-Um...
I wasn't in it either.
No one gives a damn about you!
Windy, isn't it?
Hey...
Did I ask you?
Hey!
Did I even say a word about you?
A-Ah, n-no...
You didn't mention me at all.
Then why did you butt in?
Don't be so self-centered.
Are you an idiot?
You're always going, "Well, I..." or "Well, in my case..."
That's called not knowing your place.
Take a seat, Shiraishi.
Jeez, my mouth is becoming foul.
Listen up.
The problem here is the fact that I, Kogami Akira, wasn't shown in the actual show.
But let me ask you, what am I?
Sure is.
An idol.
An idol depends on her looks, right?
What's the point if no one can see it?
What do you think?
Y-Yes, you are absolutely correct!
I can't hear you.
T-The staff for this episode has indeed...
acted in an irrational manner!
W-What are you writing?
Revenge of Kogami Akira
This special
broadcast
has ended!!!
So, here is a plea from Akira!
The world is waiting for Akira!
Project Full Appearance in Actual Show!
In order for Akira to appear in the actual show,
I am going to need all of your help.
So please give me loads of support!
It doesn't matter how, just give them a push!
Loads...
Tell them that you're dying to see Akira's splendid acting in the main series!
Dying...
Just between you and me,
but the difference between me and the main cast for the show is like...
...the difference between the main star in a Hollywood movie and some random extra!
She's desperate.
You can't wait to see such a wonderful and gorgeous performance, right?
Don't miss this chance!
All it takes is a single postcard or little note online...
...and Akira will be in the main series!
What's the matter?
So the second this show is over,
E-Eh? Stop her?
Understood...
U-Um, Akira-sama...
please get out your postcards and-
Shut the hell up!
Why are you talking to me?
I was on a roll!
How many times do I have to tell you to stop interrupting me!?
Oh, is it time already?
I wanted to tell you more about Akira's greatness...
If you want to get a good look at my natural charm, be sure to watch next week's show!
Just kidding!
Um... please look forward to next week!
Bye-bii!
Ugh... it's over.
That was painful.
Hey you, get the producer!
Eh? Me?
First of all,
Yes.
this week's modified manuscript was wrong.
What's the name of this program!?
What?
U-Uh, Lucky Channel?
It said Lucky Paradise.
Well...
Also...
What is it?
Do you think you can treat me like this?
Just because your last show was a hit.
Hey, producers!
Wait, maybe you shouldn't say that...
What do you think you're doing?
Miyagi-san!
Hello, Shiraishi Minoru here!
Now, please listen to me!
wakuwaku shitai to negainagara sugoshitetara
I've lived my life wishing for excitement.
kanaete kureta no wa dare na no
Who made my dream come true?
iroiro yosou ga dekisou de dekinai mirai
Some futures you can guess. Some you can't.
sore demo hitotsu dake wakaru yo
But there's still one thing I know for sure.
jikan no hate made
Even to the end of time!
boooon
Boooon!!
WAAPU de RUUPU na kono omoi wa
These looping feelings...
nanimou kamou makikonda sozou de asobou!
...warp everyone in to play with imagination!
aru hareta hi no koto
One clear, sunshiny day...
mahou ijou no yukai ga
...happiness greater than magic...
kagirinaku furisosogu
...pours down with no end in sight.
fukanou janai wa
It could happen!
ashita mata au toki
When we meet again tomorrow...
warai nagara hamingu
...we'll be smiling and humming!
ureshisa wo atsumeyou
Let's bring together happiness!
kantan nanda yo konna no
It's an easy thing to do!
oikakete ne
Keep on chasing!
tsukamaete mite
Try to catch it!
ookina yume & yume SUKI deshou?
We love big dreams, right?
The End
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Iwasaki Minami here.
Kobayakawa Yutaka here.
Iwasaki-san, it's up to the two of us to introduce the next episode.
Do you know what it's about?
I don't.
I'm sorry.
Is that so?
That's not good...
I don't know either.
Well then... we'll just end it here.
「 Can't Change
So Quickly 」
Next Week: "Can't Change So Quickly."
I wonder if it's okay that we didn't say anything?
Look forward to it.