♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
HUH?
AAH!
[LAUGHS]
[YAWNING]
[RUMBLING]
HMM?
WELCOME BACK.
SO, HOW'D IT GO.
[ALL TALKING]
SO WHAT?
YOU DID IT.
YOU CAUGHT EVERY CRIMINAL
ON THE WHOLE LIST,
BUT YOU DIDN'T PICK UP
ANY LEADS OR CLUES?
COME ON.
[ALL GASP]
STILL USING PAPER TO
SEND IN THEIR COMPLAINTS.
THAT'S JUST HARASSMENT,
A WASTE OF RESOURCES.
AND OUR SERVER'S GONE DOWN
FROM ALL THE ECOMPLAINTS.
YOU KNOW THERE'S
A MOVEMENT OUT THERE
TO SUE THE COMPANY FOR DAMAGES.
WHERE ARE THE DAMN BOUNTY
HUNTERS WHEN YOU NEED THEM?
WE PUT OUT A HUGE
BOUNTY ON THE GUY.
TRUE.
BUT MAYBE IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
HI, AMIGOS.
ALL YOU BAD BOUNTY HUNTERS.
HOW Y'ALL DOING?
ONCE AGAIN,
IT'S TIME FOR BIG SHOT.
HERE'S TODAY'S HOT NEWS.
THEY CAUGHT
THE LOWDOWN OUTLAWS
WHO CARRIED OUT THOSE
WRETCHED GATE ATTACKS.
REALLY?
THE BOUNTY ON THAT GUY
WAS 12 MILLION WOOLONGS!
I SAID OUTLAWS.
THEY CAUGHT 20 OF THEM.
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, PUNCH?
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
WERE CAUGHT IN THE ACT,
BUT NONE OF THEM
WAS THE MASTERMIND.
OH, WELL,
YOU DON'T GET THE REWARD
UNLESS YOU FIND
THE MASTERMIND, RIGHT?
SHUCKS. HOWDY!
THAT'S RIGHT!
THEN THE GUYS WHO CAUGHT
THEM DON'T GET A PENNY.
SORRY, YOU GUYS.
WHY WOULD THE KIND
OF TWO-BIT HOODS
WHO USUALLY ROB
CONVENIENCE STORES
SUDDENLY ATTACK
AN ASTRAL GATE?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S A NEW
FAD FOR CRIMINALS.
RIGHT.
"HEY, KIDS, IF YOU'RE
A FASHIONCONSCIOUS YOUNG HOOD,
"REMEMBER, THAT CUTE GIRL
WON'T EVEN LOOK YOUR WAY
"UNLESS YOU KNOCK
OVER AN ASTRAL GATE.
DO IT TODAY."
YOU MEAN LIKE THAT?
[SIZZLING]
SO, LISTEN, GUYS.
WHY DON'T WE ALL PONY UP
THE INFORMATION
WE HAVE ON THIS CASE
AND AGREE TO SPLIT
THE BOUNTY 3 WAYS?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAID
TO WORK SEPARATELY,
EACH ONE GATHERING THE FACTS
AND EXAMINING THEM.
"OCCASIONAL RIVALRY BETWEEN
COMRADES IS HEALTHY."
I BELIEVE THAT'S
THE WAY YOU PUT IT.
DID THE SIZE OF THE REWARD
SCRAMBLE YOUR BRAIN?
WHAT?
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
KEEN ON THE IDEA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
AFTER ALL, WE EACH
WANTED THE BOUNTY
TO PUT IN OUR OWN
POCKETS, RIGHT?
[JET GRUNTS]
IN THAT CASE, ALL 20 HITS
WERE DONE THE SAME WAY.
EVERY ONE OF THEM
INFILTRATED THE TOLLBOOTH.
THEY ATTACHED THE HACKING
UNIT VERY PRECISELY.
SO, WHEN A SHIP WAS
COMING THROUGH,
AT THE EXACT MOMENT
IT PAID THE TOLL,
THEY COULD STEAL THE ENTIRE
BALANCE FROM THE CREDIT CHECK.
THE UNIT IMMEDIATELY
SENT THE CASH CREDITS
OVER A SECURED LINK
TO A BANK ON EUROPA.
THERE THE MONEY WAS
ELECTRONICALLY LAUNDERED
THROUGH A SERIES
OF BLIND TRANSACTIONS
THAT CAN'T BE TRACED
IN ANY WAY.
ALL THE CULPRITS WERE
CAUGHT IN THE ACT.
NONE OF THEM HAVE
ANYTHING IN COMMON
AGE, GENDER, NATIONALITY,
RELIGION, CRIMINAL
RECORD... NOTHING.
ON TOP OF THAT,
NOT ONE OF THEM
HAD A SINGLE STOLEN
WOOLONG ON THEM.
WELL, THAT'S ALL
THE INFORMATION I COULD GET.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
THE GUY I NABBED
WAS SO CLUELESS.
HE SAID HE WAS FOLLOWING
THE INSTRUCTIONS FROM A MANUAL
HE GOT MAIL ORDER
FROM SOME WEB SITE.
MAYBE THE OTHER THIEVES
WERE ALL WANNABES
WHO READ THE SAME
MANUAL, YOU KNOW?
MANUAL?
OH.
HERE.
HMM?
"ALL NEW CRIMINAL
SUPPORT SOFTWARE.
ACT NOW FOR THIS SPECIAL OFFER.
FOR THE LOW INTRODUCTORY
PRICE OF 30,000 WOOLONGS,
YOU CAN BE A BILLIONAIRE."
WHAT THE HELL?
IT'S COMPLICATED TO
BE AN OUTLAW NOWADAYS,
SO SOME PEOPLE USE MANUALS
TO HELP THEM OUT.
WHERE IS THIS
MAIL ORDER COMPANY?
IN CYBERSPACE.
IT'S VIRTUAL.
THERE'S NO ACTUAL LOCATION.
NOW THE WEB SITE'S
GONE WITHOUT A TRACE.
SPIKE, HOW ABOUT YOU?
THOSE HACKING UNITS WERE
DESIGNED BY SOME PIKER.
HE WAS AN INSIDER
WHO KNOWS PRECISELY
HOW THE GATE SYSTEM WORKS.
WHOEVER'S BEHIND IT
IS PROBABLY CONNECTED
TO THE GATE CORPORATION.
THAT WAS MY TAKE ON IT.
I TRIED TO LOOK
INTO IT, BUT, UH
YOU MEAN A CROOKED PROGRAMMER?
RIGHT. YEAH.
BUT THE GUYS FROM
THE GATE CORPORATION
SUDDENLY BECAME
VERY UNCOOPERATIVE.
IT WAS AS IF THEY
KNEW IT WAS GOING ON,
BUT THEY DIDN'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
[SCREAMING]
HMM. YOU DEAD?
HEY...HEY.
[HUMMING]
UH, WHERE WERE WE?
HUH?
HERE. WAIT A MINUTE.
YEAH. THESE PIECES ARE IT.
THEY'RE STILL OUR BEST CLUES.
GIVE IT TO ED.
HMM?
GIVE IT.
THERE IT IS.
THIS IS A MEMORY CARTRIDGE
FOR PLAYING ECHESS.
THE MEMORY CHIP STORES
DATA WITHIN THE PIECE.
YEAH. YOU CAN
ACTIVATE ONE GAME.
IT CONNECTS TO THE NET.
SEE?
AND SO THIS HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE INCIDENTS AT THE GATE?
NOT A BIT.
MAYBE THIS WHOLE THING
WITH THE ASTRAL GATE IS
REALLY JUST A BIG GAME.
GO AHEAD AND PLAY AGAINST
YOUR CYBER OPPONENT, ED.
RIGHT.
I'LL TRY DEALING WITH
THE GATE CORPORATION AGAIN.
OK.
1, 2, 3, 4.
ED'S GONNA SCORE MORE.
[LAUGHS]
PLAY BALL!
[SQUAWKING]
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
ANOTHER BOUNTY HUNTER?
I DON'T CARE WHAT HE WANTS.
SEND HIM AWAY.
HE SAYS HE'S LOOKING
FOR A PROGRAMMER
WHO LIKES TO PLAY CHESS.
WHAT?
HUH? IT'S YOU.
HMM?
[CHUCKLES]
YOU, TOO, EH, JON?
YOU WENT THROUGH
ALL THAT TROUBLE
FOR NOTHING,
LIKE AN AMATEUR.
HUH!
THIS ONE IS MUCH
TOUGHER THAN IT LOOKS, JET.
YOU READ OUR BOUNTY BULLETIN.
ALL THE INFORMATION IS THERE.
IT'S VERY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU NEED TO KNOW?
I'M AFRAID THERE'S
NO SMOKING ALLOWED IN HERE.
HUH?
OH, I'M SORRY.
MY BAD.
ACTUALLY, I DON'T
HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
IT'S JUST THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT YOU TO SEE.
WHAT'S THAT?
THIS IS A GAME,
ALL PLANNED OUT IN ADVANCE.
YOU GATE GUYS KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU PUT A BOUNTY OUT
ON SOME MASTERMIND
WHO MAY NOT EVEN EXIST,
WHICH MEANS YOU DON'T WANT
THE POLICE TO KNOW
WHO'S REALLY BEHIND THIS.
YOU SUITS ARE USING US
BOUNTY HUNTERS LIKE PAWNS,
AND I DON'T APPRECIATE IT.
BOUNTY HUNTERS
SHOULD LOOK FOR BOUNTIES.
I SUGGEST YOU DO THAT.
MAYBE YOU USED TO WORK
FOR THE ISSP, MAYBE NOT.
EITHER WAY, YOU'D BE WISE
TO DROP THIS LINE OF INQUIRY.
OUR GUEST IS LEAVING NOW.
MAKE SURE HE'S ESCORTED
OUT OF THE BUILDING.
[GRUNTS]
DAMN.
COME ON.
[STATIC]
WE SHOULD HAVE NEVER
TAKEN SUCH A RISK.
IF THIS THING EVER GETS OUT,
YOU KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
I'M FULLY AWARE OF THE DANGER,
AND IF WE DON'T CATCH HIM FAST,
THE SITUATION CAN
ONLY GET WORSE.
WHY WOULD A GHOST FROM 50 YEARS
AGO SUDDENLY COME BACK NOW?
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
AND HE GIVES EVERYONE
A CHESS PIECE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
CHESS MASTER HEX.
YEAH.
THE WHOLE THING REALLY
IS A GAME FOR YOU.
CHESS MASTER HEX, HUH?
HMM.
[LAUGHS]
[HUMMING]
OH!
NO GOOD.
THERE'S NOTHING
IN HERE BUT CHESS DATA.
I WONDER WHAT THEY WERE
PLANNING TO DO
WITH THESE THINGS?
WELL, THE DATA
DOESN'T HAVE ANY MEANING,
BUT WHAT IF THE CHESS
PIECES THEMSELVES
ARE SOME KIND OF MESSAGE?
[LAUGHING]
HEY, SPIKE, I'VE GOT AN I.D.
SEE WHAT YOU CAN FIND ON IT.
HE COULD BE THE SO-CALLED
MASTERMIND BEHIND THIS THING.
HUH. ED?
EDWARD IS VERY BUSY RIGHT NOW.
HMM.
[LAUGHING]
CHECK-CHECK-CHECK-CHECKMATE!
HUH?!
AH, SO I THOUGHT.
WELL, AT LEAST MY KNIGHT
TAKES YOUR ROOK.
HUH?!
[LAUGHS]
[BIRD SQUAWKING]
WELL, I'LL BE!
THIS IS EITHER
AN IDIOT OR A GENIUS!
I LIKE THIS FELLOW!
[LAUGHS]
CHESS MASTER HEX.
ESTIMATED TO BE 98 YEARS OLD.
A PROGRAMMER THAT HAD BEEN
DUBBED A GENIUS FROM HIS TEENS.
IN THE COSMO NET
CHESS TOURNAMENTS,
HE HELD THE CHAMPION
SEAT FOR DECADES.
HE APPLIED HIS INTELLECT TO
THE HYPERSPACE GATE PROJECT,
JOINING THE PROGRAM
AT 30 YEARS OF AGE.
HE EVENTUALLY DEVELOPED
THE CENTRAL CONTROL SYSTEM
THAT ALL GATES USE TO THIS DAY.
BUT AFTER THAT,
HE STARTED TO HAVE DOUBTS.
HE SAID THE DESIGN
HAD DEFECTS
AND THE GATES
SHOULDN'T BE BUILT YET.
HE WANTED TO RUN MORE TESTS.
SO THEY FIRED HIM AND
BUILT THE GATES ANYWAY.
HE'S BEEN MISSING
FOR THE LAST 50 YEARS.
SO HE'S THE MASTERMIND
WHO TAUGHT THOSE BEGINNERS.
BUT WHY?
IS HE TRYING TO GET REVENGE
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS OR WHAT?
MAYBE IF WE TRACK HIM DOWN,
WE CAN GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
HEY, ED?
EDWARD IS VERY BUSY.
TRY LATER.
FORGET LATER.
WE NEED SOME HELP NOW.
GIVE ME THAT
[HISSES]
ED, WE'RE TRYING
TO FIND A GUY NAMED HEX.
HE'S IN CYBERSPACE.
HEX.
HEX THE CHESS MASTER.
EDWARD IS PLAYING CHESS
AGAINST HIM RIGHT NOW.
HUH?
I TRACKED HIM
THROUGH EDWARD'S GAME,
AND WE'RE COMING UP ON HIM.
ARE YOU GUYS STANDING BY?
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
HE MADE IT MUCH
TOO EASY TO TRACE HIM.
THIS GUY'S TOO SMART FOR THAT.
MAYBE IT'S A FALSE TRAIL.
I MEAN, LOOK WHERE
WE'RE HEADING.
WOULD HE BE IN A DUMP LIKE THAT?
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
LISTEN TO ME.
I HEARD ABOUT THIS PLACE
A LONG TIME AGO
A KIND OF FLOATING SCRAP YARD
WHERE THEY LEAVE
WRECKED GATE PARTS,
ABANDONED SPACESHIPS,
AND SCRAP METAL.
PEOPLE MOVED IN
AND STARTED LIVING THERE
SQUATTERS AND DRIFTERS.
WHY THE HELL WOULD THEY WANT
TO LIVE THERE OF ALL PLACES?
THERE'S NO GOVERNMENT,
NO NATIONALITY,
NO TAXES, AND NO COPS.
THEY SEE IT AS TOTAL FREEDOM.
YEAH, RIGHT.
IT WOULD ALSO MAKE IT
A PERFECT PLACE TO HIDE OUT.
REMEMBER, THIS COULD BE A TRAP,
A CONTINUATION OF THE GAME.
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S AIR IN HERE.
THEN THERE'S SOMEONE THERE.
[BEEPING]
HMM?
HOW'S IT GOING, JET?
JONATHAN, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING OUT HERE?
TRACKING YOU, OF COURSE.
THANKS FOR LEADING THE WAY.
YOU MEAN YOU'VE
BEEN FOLLOWING US?
WHAT FOR?
IT'S LIKE THIS.
I'VE GOT A SCORE TO SETTLE
WITH THE GUY YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
[SCREAMING]
BYE-BYE.
[LAUGHING]
OOH!
[CAT MEOWING]
WHAT THE?
[LAUGHING]
[GASPS]
WHAT'S THAT?
UH, I
[DOGS BARKING]
WHAT THE HELL?
HUH?
[SNORING]
WHAT'S THIS?
[LAUGHING]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HI.
PEACE TO THE WHOLE GALAXY
AND TO MY BANK ACCOUNT.
LOVE, LOVE.
DO YOU WANT ONE?
AHH!
WOW! WHOA!
[LAUGHING]
CHESS MASTER HEX,
I TAKE IT.
DON'T TRY ANYTHING.
UNDERSTAND?
YOU BOTH, UH
WELL, COULD YOU BE JUST
A LITTLE QUIETER, PLEASE?
HUH?
OLD MAN... HAND IT OVER!
HEY, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
PRETENDING TO BE SENILE
WON'T GET YOU OUT OF THIS.
WHO ARE YOU?
EITHER YOU GIVE ME
THE MONEY YOU TOOK,
OR I PUT A HOLE RIGHT
THROUGH YOUR BRAIN.
HEH HEH HEH!
THAT'S QUITE
A LARGE PIPE THERE.
HEY, WHAT YOU DOING, HEX?
OH, YOU GOT TO SEE THIS!
MY FIRST FORMIDABLE
OPPONENT IN AGES!
HE MUST BE SOME PLAYER
TO PIN YOU DOWN.
WHAT'S YOUR NEXT MOVE?
I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S HAVE LUNCH FIRST.
YOU ATE LUNCH A FEW
MINUTES AGO, BLAST IT.
REALLY? DID I LIKE IT?
WHO ARE THESE GUYS?
DON'T KNOW,
BUT THIS ONE'S LOSING IT.
YOU LEAVE YOUR
BRAIN SOMEWHERE?
YEAH, LIKE YOU CAN TALK,
YOU NUMBSKULL.
ALL MY SAVINGS GONE.
I'LL NEVER GET IT BACK NOW.
DAMN IT. GODDAMN IT!
ANYONE, EVERYONE, YOU KNOW.
IT'S ALL A MISTAKE!
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO WITH HIM?
THE OLD DUFFER'S OUT OF TOUCH.
HE CAN'T RECALL YESTERDAY,
LET ALONE 50 YEARS AGO.
LUCKY FOR HIM,
HEX IS NO LONGER HERE.
THERE'S NO ONE LEFT BUT AN OLD
MAN WHO LOVES TO PLAY GAMES.
HEX WAS FURIOUS.
HE WANTED REVENGE,
AND THIS IS HOW HE GOT IT.
HE SET UP THE STING
TO KICK IN 50 YEARS LATER
WHEN THE GATE WAS PRE-SCHEDULED
FOR ITS FIRST
AUTOMATIC TECH UPGRADE.
IT WAS ALL PLANNED OUT.
HE EVEN ARRANGED FOR HIS
OPERATIVES TO CARRY CHESS PIECES
TO LET YOU KNOW THAT HE HAD
FINALLY GOTTEN BACK AT YOU.
BUT 50 YEARS IS A LONG TIME.
HEX GOT OLD.
THEN HE GOT SENILE.
HE COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT
THE TRAPS THAT
HE HIMSELF HAD SET.
WELL, IT'S BETTER
FOR YOU THIS WAY.
YOU KNOW HE WON'T
EXPOSE YOU NOW.
YOUR DIRTY LITTLE SECRET
WILL REMAIN A SECRET.
HE CAN'T TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THE DEFECTS
YOU BUILT INTO THE GATES.
SO THAT'S IT, THEN.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT US.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MONEY? IS THAT IT?
COME ON. SAY IT.
WHAT'S YOUR PRICE TO KEEP FROM
LEAKING THIS THING TO THE PRESS?
JUST LEAVE THE OLD GUY ALONE.
CALL OFF THE BOUNTY HUNTERS.
THAT'S ALL WE ASK.
YOU SEE, ED WOULD BE UNHAPPY
IF SHE LOST
HER FAVORITE CHESS PARTNER,
AND WE WOULDN'T WANT THAT
TO HAPPEN, NOW, WOULD WE?
ARE YOU PLAYING AGAIN?
NOT AGAIN.
ED'S STILL PLAYING.
YOU MEAN YOU'VE PLAYED
THE SAME GAME FOR A WEEK?
MMHMM.
I SEE.
WELL, GOOD LUCK, ED.
YO, NEWBY, YOU'RE
IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY.
HOWDY THERE, GUYS.
HE'S AN EASYGOING
DUDE, AIN'T HE?
SURE IS, ANTONIO.
NICE FELLA.
CHECKMATE.
AAH!
HE GOT ME!
[CHIRPING]
[SQUAWKING]
LOVE IS TO BELIEVE
IN EVERYTHING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
LOVE IS THE HEART
THAT GIVES TO ALL.
COME ON! THAT'S WHAT
THE STORY'S ABOUT!
LOVE IS THE HEART
THAT ACCEPTS EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW I'M NOT BUYING THIS.
WHITNEY,
YOU LOVE ME THAT MUCH.
YOU REALLY CAN'T TRUST
THE PREVIEWS ON THIS SHOW.
A ROMANTIC LOVE STORY
FOR ALL YOU LOVERS.
NEXT EPISODE
MY FUNNY VALENTINE.
IT'S GOTTA BE A LIE.
YEAH.
SHE'S MAKING IT UP.