So, Aki, how many people are coming on this trip?
Yoshii Akihisa is in a predicament.
You said there were nine of us altogether but... that's probably a bit much.
It'll be fine if we rent a minivan... But who are the other seven?
For example... Well, hey, you know them too right?
Yuuji...
and Hideyoshi...
and Voyeur...
Who else?
And...
Crap. Sis has forbidden me from making friends with girls.
Kirishima will probably be able to pass off as Yuuji's fiancée.
But if I tell her I called Himeji...
and Minami...
and Kudou?!
What'll she do to me?!
So? Who else?
Eh? Umm... Hi-Hi...
Hideyoshi? You already said his name.
I-It's a Se~c~ret?
Aki, clench your teeth.
I'm sorry! I was joking!
Aki, if you're honest about it, I'll give you a kiss!
The remaining four people are actually aliens.
Aki, close your eyes.
Hey wait! I was obviously lying.
Even humans can be considered aliens in a broad sense.
Wait! I apologize!
Stop! Stop!!
Goodness! I can't believe you'd go so far to stop me!
Sorry. But we're siblings, so...
That turns me on.
Pervert! This woman is an incorrigible pervert!
Don't be so serious. Thirty percent of that was a joke.
Crap, she was more than half serious.
In the first place, you shouldn't deceive your sister with lies.
Why did you do it?
Promise you won't get mad.
Of course! I won't get mad as long as no girls are coming with us.
I won't even make you cross-dress.
Where do you think you're going, Aki?
Please don't get mad and hit me and crush me and make me wear girls' clothes!
I see. You really did invite girls too.
No I didn't! It's... umm...
I'm indebted to Himeji and the girls for helping me in my studies,
and we're good friends so it'd be rude not to invite them.
I don't really expect them to want to stay over, so I thought it was fine.
Seriously. You're such a...
Very well.
Th-Then...
Just this one time, okay?
However, if you try to pull anything on the girls,
I'll lay waste to your entire family!
That means you'd die too.
A single or a couple without love, which one is...
FABULOUS?
Love!
How far do we take our chat
of my colourfully rotating future?
Ignoring the disadvantages!
How far do we take our chat of my colorfully rotating future?
My feelings for this giant world are evergrowing
I'm loving today, too
I'm really looooo-ving it!
looooo-ving it!
My idiot who came from amongst the stars is still an idiot
Honestly still cannot accept that
I had a dream of walking with you
Still I'm sorry
Because I did not know about love, you know.
Answer: You and the riddling me are infinite jump!
And so it's the day of the beach holiday.
I'm glad the weather's great. Right, Yuuji?
Yeah. And we managed to get everyone to come too.
I was so excited about this, I couldn't sleep.
You're not in elementary school any more, Mizuki.
I even bought a new swimsuit for today.
Didn't you buy one just recently?
Oh! That one... doesn't...
Let me guess... you got fatter?
Increase in size
Just a little! It's really just a little! Just a little too much.
Too little or too much?
That's not it. I gained weight because I grew my hair longer.
Really now, it's only because you weren't prepared.
I slimmed down because of the summer heat.
Eh?! That's so unfair, Minami! You're a horrible traitor!
Yeah I slimmed down.
My chest, that is.
Himeji, Shimada, art not thou worrying about it too much?
I don't think you've really changed much from before.
Well excuse me!
In any case, my breasts are growing slower than yours, Kinoshita.
I doth not possess breasts and they won't grow!
You don't really have to be worry.
In any case, you're going to leave me behind and become all bouncy-bouncy.
Glamorous Kinoshita won't understand why we're annoyed.
I'm a guy! Calm down you two!
What's with you today?
It's just that...
I'm jealous of that chest.
I'm jealous of her slim waist.
Certainly, Akira is a threat.
I will need to keep close watch over Yuuji.
They go "boing-boing", aren't they awesome?
I'd expect her to have a swimsuit made of strings, like you see in porn mags.
Oh, Kouta, are you all right?
Just a little car sick.
I've never heard of getting nosebleeds from being car sick.
Aki, can you take out the car sickness medicine from the bag?
Okay!
Eh? The zipper's stuck.
One, two,...
There, it's open!
This is the old type of school swimsuit. Wow.
Sis, you mustn't!
What the hell, Akihisa?
What do I do, Yuuji?
There's an incorrigible person in my family!
I'd say the one clutching the school swimsuit is the incorrigible one.
No, this swimsuit belongs to Sis—
I see. You're interested in your sister's school swimsuit.
You really are far gone.
You're misunderstanding! I won't approve of this!
School Swimsuit
Sexy + Cuteness
Moe points + alpha
Aki, you told me you didn't want to be embarrassed,
so I should show as little skin as possible.
I'm sorry, but I'd prefer if you showed bit more skin
instead of walking next to your little brother in a school swimsuit.
Get a new one! A new swimsuit!
I'm your brother! I can't have you doing things like this!
So that swimsuit isn't skimpy enough?
Exposure
Ah fine... let's just go with that.
Akihisa, restrain your libido in these situations.
Ah! Even the emperor of eroticism, Voyeur, told me off!
Don't cry, Akihisa. You too call people idiots, don't you?
So am I the emperor of idiots now?
Well, all right . I'll get another swimsuit.
Actually, that one is too tight and my chest looks like it's overflowing.
Censored
This is a great view!
There's a wonderful breeze too!
It's a perfect location.
Okay! Let's get changed quickly and go swimming!
Right!
Today I shalt maketh them realize that I'm a man once and for all.
I made sure to buy men's trunks this time.
No one should have any complaints.
I changed inside the car!
These tan lines sure are different from the ones off the swimsuit I use for the swimming club.
This one is sexy too, isn't it, Voyeur?
If you want to, you can take as many pictures as you want.
I don't mind.
Don't be so conceited, Kudou Aiko.
Your swimsuit is of secondary interest to—
I'm getting heat stroke.
Good effort, Voyeur. 28 seconds.
Awesome, Voyeur. You beat your nosebleed endurance record.
Are you all right, Voyeur?
Ah, don't come close, Kudou, or else he'll—
Gah! The sun... it burns!
Voyeur!
May I be born as a bird in my next life.
No! Don't say such a dramatic thing in real life!
And may I be able to fly in the sky,
and peek into the girls' locker rooms to my heart's content.
He didn't learn a single lesson from his life.
Whoosh, whoosh.
Lemon juice tastes really nice with sugar too, doesn't it?
Sorry! Thanks for waiting!
Thanks.
Is Tsuchiya all right?
He's stable for now.
Aiko, don't bully Tsuchiya too much.
Well, I didn't really do anything!
Tsuchiya got too excited from Kudou's cute swimsuit.
I haven't... confirmed that really happened.
Excited?
Yes! Tsuchiya is a boy, after all.
I see.
Scissors.
Wha yoo do tha faw?!
I must make you get excited from my swimsuit.
You don't have to do that. You two look really stylish and pretty.
Oh no! Pretty? I'm so embarrassed.
Thanks, Yoshii.
Of course I'm not stylish at all. Bleh!
That's not true! You're slender, you have curves—
Right, right. My chest is slender and I have a big stomach, don't I?
I didn't say that!
Greetings, everyone! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey you! What the heck are you doing?!
Is something wrong?
Why aren't you wearing a top?
That would be because this is a men's swimsuit.
A girl shouldn't wear men's swimsuits!
Nay, I'm not a girl—
Shut up and come with me!
Stop! Listen to— Wait! Where art thou taking me?
Oh, Minami! Did my brother do something rude?
What's wrong, Minami?
Nothing! There's no way I can win anyway!
Akira, please excuse me.
Amazing!
I'm sorry! Please excuse me too!
The beach is so cruel, isn't it?!
No, God himself is brutal.
I beg your pardon, good sirs. I'm late.
What happened, Hideyoshi? You look sad.
Just leaveth me alone.
The summer beach is cruel indeed, in many, many ways.
Question 1:
Fill in the blanks with the correct answer:
"The force which holds solids and liquids composed of molecules together is known as the _______ Force.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
van der Waals interaction
Teacher's comment:
Correct. It is also called
"the van der Waals force".
Be careful not to confuse
the van der Waals force
with the Coulomb force
which occurs between ions.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
Wandervogel force
Teacher's comment:
Well, that certainly sounds
right. Unfortunately, that's
the force that attracts mountain
climbers, not molecules.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
Eff force
Teacher's comment:
I'm cool with this answer.
Baka Test!
A little to the right!
No no, it's actually a little to the left!
Yoshii, it's right in front of you!
Who's telling the truth?
Aki, 32 degrees counterclockwise, 4.7 meters forward.
She's telling it backwards.
All of their directions are different. What do I do?
What about Yuuji?
Yuuji, how do you like this swimsuit?
It's all right. I've seen it before too, you know.
I'm sure you didn't see it carefully back then.
Here, look at it up close.
Hey stay away! You'll bump those into me.
There you are!!
You will die!!
That was close!
Tch, I missed.
My bad Yuuji. I thought you were the watermelon.
It didst look like you were aiming for him, though.
Whatever are you saying, Hideyoshi? That is so not true!
That's right, Hideyoshi. Akihisa had to find the watermelon after all.
Well then, it's my turn.
What's wrong? Let go of the bat, Akihisa.
Weren't you scared of it just now, Yuuji?
The first round was yours. It's my turn in the second round now.
It's only fair to go in reverse order in the second round.
Um, it'll be a waste to splatter the watermelon, so let's stop this.
It's all right! We won't hit the watermelon.
Just what dost thou two intend to hit then?
Ah, I'm pooped.
We haven't even swam yet. Why are we so tired?
Thou reapeth what thou soweth.
We're back!
We bought lunch.
Sorry for taking so long.
Was the shop crowded?
Oh no, actually...
Actually, we got hit on.
I really hate those types.
Me too.
Heh, that must've been tough.
Why didn't you just brush them off?
That's right.
Now now. That's a bad attitude, you two.
Wow, you don't understand the feelings of a maiden, do you?
Yes, you should be more worried, Yuuji.
Huh? Why should I—
I'm sorry!!
If only he was more concerned about us...
I know! Shall we make him fret a bit?
Let's!
Those type of guys are a bother no matter where they are.
Indeed, they're always, always so annoying.
Oh? Do you two get hit on a lot?
Yes! All day!
Yes! Everywhere!
Yet you still don't seem used to it.
That's not true! It just happens so much that we've had enough of it!
Right! You wouldn't understand.
You're blunt and have no experience in romance.
Nonsense. I too flirt a lot—
A lot?
In the first place, I doubt you even can flirt!
That's right! You don't look like the type that flirts.
I doubt it'd go well even if you tried.
Don't boast like that.
You don't understand a maiden's feelings, Yuuji.
That's why nobody likes you.
I don't want to hear that from—
Everyone has things that suit them and things that don't.
Romance doesn't suit you, Aki.
Damn! I just don't get it!
I feel like I got scolded for no reason at all.
What the hell does she mean nobody likes us?
I know, right? If we were serious, we could easily get a hundred girls—
What happened, Akihisa?
Un...believable...
Vo...ur...
Huh?
Voyeur... is getting hit on...
Nonsense. Don't sleep talk in the middle of the day—
Hey, you must be a genius at taking pictures.
This is... pretty average.
Oh gosh, you're so shy, you cutie you.
Impossible! How could Voyeur be so...
Yuuji.
What?
This is just something I thought of right now.
Could it really be that nobody likes us?
Don't be ridiculous! I won't stand for that!
You're right, it can't be!
At first glance, Voyeur looks clammed up and withdrawn.
We just have a different personality from him, don't we?
They were too hasty in claiming nobody likes us.
Exactly! What do they mean we don't look like the type that flirts?
We'll show them!
That's how it's done, Akihisa.
Let's show them just what we can do!
Now that I think back,
I'm sure there was something wrong with us back then.
But how exactly do we flirt?
It's too soon for us to think we're good at it.
We'll just copy Voyeur.
Do you want to target girls who want their picture taken?
Yeah. One of us asks to take a picture of them.
Then she's in our grasp.
The other one can then talk about something else. It'll be easy.
What topics will the second guy talk about?
Well, just wing it.
So even if it fails, it's not the first guy's fault, is it?
Akihisa, you bastard! Where do you think you're rushing off to?
You too, Yuuji. What's with the madman sprint?
You can come later at a slow and easy pace.
Don't worry, I'll set up the conversation for you.
I'm your true friend, I can't let you do that.
Leave this to me.
I'm not gonna let you.
I'm ready! Say cheese.
Miss... you sure are pretty.
Would you like to have a picture taken in your swimsuit?
We... never thought they'd call the cops, did we?
It's probably tougher to approach girls by asking them to have a picture taken.
Looks like it.
We aren't good with a camera like Voyeur.
All right. Let's change our approach.
What are you gonna do?
How about we compliment them on their appearance, throw them off guard, and use that get close to them?
Yeah, no one would mind being complimented.
But how exactly should we compliment them?
We compare them to, say, a TV star,
or a sports figure.
Whatever they seem to be,
we'll roll out a conversation from there.
It's a plan!
Thanks.
You're really pretty, Miss.
Eh? You think so?
Yep, you've got a really nice body!
I agree! It's really great!
My, you have a way with words!
We really mean it!
That's right, we really think so.
Yeah you're really stylish,
just like...
Just like,
Just like a nude model in a porn mag.
That arm had a world class right hook.
She'll win a championship in the future.
Deep down, I know it.
Oh? Where have you two been?
You face is beat in.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened! Right Yuuji?
Yeah! We just tripped, right, Akihisa?
Yuuji, let's continue our swimming battle.
Lead the way! I won't lose this time!
We were this close to success and you blew it with that stupid line.
It's because you were talking nonsense.
You were the one who told me to! What the heck?
Bastard, you wanna go?
Drop it. There's no point in fighting among ourselves.
Yeah.
Now that I think about it, it went bad because we weren't being serious, did it not?
Because we didn't like those girls, we unconsciously didn't try very hard.
I get it. It won't work without serious feelings.
Like hell it was.
What a dumb excuse.
What is it, Yuuji?
All right! Let's try one last time on those two!
Yeah, let's.
Excuse me!
A-Actually, we're lost.
We're looking for the beach. Do you know—
You idiot! This is the beach.
It just came out of my mouth when you said we were lost.
Her hair... was dyed?!
Yes, because I really have black hair.
Sh-Shouko!
Crap!
Forgive me, Akihisa.
Voyeur! Why?!
Because I'd be dead right now if I'd refused.
Don't... tell me... they found out about the flirting?
Your right arm...
Ah, my right arm. It's gonna hurt. I don't wanna go back.
Your right arm is the only thing they wouldn't smash to bits.
Akihisa, don't move, okay?
We have a full course of punishment prepared for you.
Just you wait, Aki!
Your sister is so sad. I wish I didn't know you.
Run, Akishisa! These three are gonna—
Akihisa, the moments we shared were fun.
No!!
Yuuji.
Yes?
On your knees.
Eh? But we're in the...
But... we're standing in the sea.
Will you make me say it again?
On your knees.
Question 2.
The two primary components of seawater are water and...?
Tears of regret and repentance.
Is something wrong?
Next time: Me, yukata, and the uproar at the festival.
This will be on the test.