When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
The government is about to make
a grave announcement to the citizens.
Please do not turn off the TV or change the channel.
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
What? Don't go straight to the opening as if there was nothing first.
Besides, what's this "grave announcement"?
What? Mi-Milady?
Oh, I've chosen my words carefully, Persian.
What did you just say, Milady?
Perhaps you should have done the same.
I said you don't have to work anymore.
This is blasphemy! This is madness!
Hey, why do you look depressed?
Does that mean... I'm fired?
Huh?
No, that's not what I meant.
Your last test was right on the passing mark, right?
If you fail the next exam, you'd seriously be in danger.
So I'm saying you can take a break from your work and concentrate on studying until exams end.
Wh-What are you saying, Milady? I can handle both!
You don't have to worry about me like that.
Then shall we make a deal: I'll fire you if you get a poor grade?
So?
Why not accept her offer?
Maria-san.
It's a gift from your Master.
Right?
Yeah. So relax and get lots of studying in.
Yes...
In exchange!
Once the exams end, I'll have you play with me a whole bunch, so be ready.
Got it?
Y-Yes. I got it.
'Sup. What's with the gloomy face?
I don't understand why I had to be smacked there...
But still, I'm a little worried.
Klaus-san is out and away, too.
Oh no, what are you talking about, Maria?
I'm not a child. I don't need a butler constantly by me.
So you say, but I wonder who's the person who always gets in life-threatening trouble when a butler isn't by her?
It's coincidence!
In case of a situation like this-
Come on Klaus, don't waste a TV.
Oh boy.
I have something prepared in case of a situation like this.
Prepared?
Yes.
A new emergency butler.
Um, was it all right to have you come with me?
It's fine. You're working hard for Nagi's sake, right?
Then it's my job as her partner to help you out.
You aren't making any progress!
What do you think you're doing, spacing out?!
Is it really all right to skip work and study?
It looks like you don't have to worry about that.
I heard a new butler's coming.
A new butler?
Yeah. I overheard the SPs talking about something like that.
Oh really? Wow. Wow. I never knew that.
What? You're worried about it?
N-No. I'm not worried about it.
But, since she doesn't break the ice with people easily,
I'm sure it'll be hard for her to deal with anyone other than me.
So you say, but the new butler and Nagi might get along while you sit here, and...
I don't see anything bad in them getting along.
Rather than talking, I need to get to studying.
I have to meet Milady's standards.
Let's see, atarashii shitsuji: new butler.
New butler comes soon... coming soon...
Stop mumbling ominous stuff in English.
If it bothers you so much, why not go take a peek on your way to the bathroom or something?
But, I don't think you have to be so agitated.
Even Himegami asked you to take care of Nagi, right?
Have some confidence in yourself.
You're the only butler for Nagi.
You should trust the bond between you and Nagi more.
Bond between Milady and...
You're right.
I'm sorry for losing myself there.
Don't worry about it.
Let's turn our focus back on this, shall we?
Yes!
But, before that.
I'll go the bathroom and freshen up.
I'll pick up the pen after that.
After I go to the bathroom .
So you are still worried...
No, no, no!
I don't need a new butler!
I won't accept a butler other than Hayate!
B-But this new one is highly skilled,
and I'm sure he'll be more useful than Ayasaki.
I don't care.
I don't even want to breathe the same air
as a butler other than Hayate.
Besides, I'm-
Please don't worry.
I'm sure you will come to like me.
Y-You're!
Nice to meet you. I'm Mecha Butler 13.
Okay. Send him back to Makimura-sensei.
What? Lady Nagi?
Oh, so it was something like that.
This is boring.
I can stop worring and bury myself in studying.
You're right.
You better get some quality studying in, you hear?
Yes.
But, this was a bad move on Hayate's side.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I guess it's proper manners to reply back.
But, was I really being thanked in the first place?
This is...
Is this a manga you drew, Lady Nagi?
What do you think you're doing,
reading it without my permission?
Go back home already, you idiot!
Your manga is horrible.
Wh-What did you say?!
How could a robot like you ever understand my manga?!
But the characters definitely had great impact.
I see strength in the formatting of the pages and lines, too.
The picture isn't bad, either.
However, the development is too sudden, so you're killing all the good parts.
You have to be more considerate of the reader.
That's how it goes?
Yes. Because you're smart, your comprehension is greater than the average person's.
On the other hand, readers will be seeing this for the first time,
so the same statement doesn't apply to them.
Have you read that manga up there?
No, since I can't reach.
Then I suggest you read it since it's a good reference.
It's a very good work.
I-Is it?
Here you go.
I guess I'll skim through it.
It's rose tea.
It'll calm you and let you read in a relaxed manner.
When did you make it?
I'm a Mecha Butler after all.
I know the way around the sky
and can move faster than humans.
I see.
W-Wow...
So, Maria-sama. I'd like to help with the housekeeping, if you'll let me.
Ah, yes.
Then let's start here.
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
But please don't move.
You look like you have stiff shoulders.
Relax.
Y-Yes.
Although you can do everything yourself, it's not good to work so hard.
Y-You think so?
But wow, he's good.
It feels good.
Thank you, 13-kun.
It was nothing.
If you give the order, I can do the rest of the work myself.
B-But...
It's the stupid male instinct of wanting to
act cool in front of a cute girl, so please let me.
It feels awkward not to do any butler work.
Come to think of, did that robot butler leave already?
Hey, you're pretty good.
Okay, I'll win the next round.
I won't let you so easily.
Wh-What is going on...
They look...
...all so well together.
In an old episode from D****mon, there was an episode where his shadow switched places with him.
Don't say such an ominous thing!
Su-susu... Sumo-ru Raito.
Su-susu... Sumo-ru Raito. = S-S-S-Small Light.
Tototto totto. Toutou boku no sonzaiga.
Tototto totto. Toutou boku no sonzaiga. = M-M-M-My existence is...
What? Hayate's feeling jealous?
Yeah. Looks like how you're all getting along with that robot is hitting him really hard.
Oh my.
On another note, butler robot, eh?
Sanzenin technology's really amazing.
Thank you for your compliment.
So, how good are you, exactly?
Someone tell her.
I'm asking you, fool!
I jabbed at him instinctively.
As expected from Lady Sakuya.
You don't miss the smallest opportunity.
H-He did that on purpose?
He is excellent!
This butler robot is extremely excellent!
Hayate is feeling jealous over me?
Jealous, eh...
Gosh, he's such a cute guy.
Excuse me, Milady.
Why do you look so happy?
Well, Hayate's being jealous. It gets me going a little.
You're such a naughty girl.
Gets you going...
Is that a positive emotion to humans?
Oh, there are things even 13-kun doesn't know?
Yes. My main computer does not come with an algorithm that promotes negative emotions towards people installed.
I don't think it needs to be installed.
This is correct, too.
Good, I got them all right.
I can concentrate more when I'm a little down.
Humans are made strangely.
Yes, his back looks melancholic.
So that's what jealousy looks like.
I see, I see.
Stop grinning and go comfort him already.
Yeah. Since I'm sure it's about time he gets tired from all the studying.
I guess I'll make some tea for him.
Please wait a moment, Milady.
What's wrong, 13?
If you go now and comfort him, you're only playing the game as he wants it played.
I see. A gamble between grown-ups, eh?
Yes.
So let us...
Yes?
Um, Hayate-kun.
I made some tea.
Maria-san? Thank you. Sorry to make you have-
No need to worry ~nya.
A-Are you making progress with your studies ~nya?
Y-Yes...
How is this a brilliant idea, 13-kun?
What is Hayate doing?
He's licking Maria with his eyes.
No, he isn't.
I'm going to quit ~nya!
Damn Hayate! How dare he drool over Maria!
Hold on, Milady.
I'm sorry. Looks like this strategy failed.
Okay, that got one person out of here.
Let's try a different strategy this time.
I get it! A night snack.
Although, it's not night yet.
Then I shall put everything I've got into it and-
Denied.
What?
Why? I was about to make a dish filled with love for him.
That's exactly why!
Everyone can expect an explosive ending out of this!
Don't misjudge me!
You can't even prepare a cup noodle!
What did you say?!
May I ask for Lady Sakuya's assistance?
Me?
Wow, this is amazing.
You made all of this?
Yeah. Chow down and keep up the hard studying.
You're a great cook, Sakuya-san.
This isn't much.
What are you doing, getting energized by Saku?
Looks like that Hayate-san gets along with Lady Sakuya very well.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Hayate is... Hayate is my...
Wow, this is really relaxing.
It's no time to relax!
Why, Hayate? Why?
Mi... Milady... What are you mad about?
She doesn't look too pleased, so it might be better to have you leave for the moment.
She's such a child.
That's because you're more mature than Lady Nagi.
You're such a flatterer.
All right then. I guess I'll step out.
There goes the second one.
All that's left is...
Besides, have you made any progress in studying?
Yes, so-so.
Hey, you've got lots of stuff down.
Yes. Thanks to Sakuya-san drilling them into me.
How about me?
Do you like Saku's favors better than mine?
What?
Milady?
I-I never said anything like that.
Hayate, you idiot!
Mi...la...dy...
Why, Hayate? Why?
Oh dear.
13.
Looks like he's a really impotent butler.
No, that's not true.
He doesn't look too smart, either.
Wouldn't he fail as a Sanzenin butler at this rate?
13... What are you saying?
At this rate, wouldn't I be a better choice as a butler for you?
What?
Hey!
Let's forget about him.
I'm more capable than him.
But!
How pathetic. He looks so depressed because of something like this.
Hayate...
Yes... If I do think about what's best for Milady...
Hayate, you can't.
Even if I'm around, she won't overcome the foods she doesn't like...
She watches TV until late at night...
Skips school and plays MMOs all day long.
She's starting to develop an interest in
the Maiden Road and making SPs go secretly buy goods, too.
Also, behind the cabinet is-
Enough! That's enough!
Milady...
You are my butler.
You're the only one.
It's a better fit for me not to be completely capable.
Milady...
Hayate.
Milady, was that a compliment?
Well, um...
Hayate.
Yes?
Anyway, right now, focus on studying.
Yes, you're right.
Did he arrange that for my sake?
"It's a better fit for me not to be completely capable", eh?
Humans are complicated.
Eight! Please, stop!
Let me go, Honey!
If it's going to take you away, then I'll break him and then I'll...
I'll...
Eight!
Eight, you idiot!
Are you all right, 13?
Why was he angry?
I didn't do anything to him.
I'm sorry. I think he was jealous of you since I paid so much attention to you.
Jealousy?
I can't comprehend it. That emotion is not yet installed.
Don't worry. I don't understand it well myself.
Plus, he's not as well-made as you.
I still don't understand it, no matter how well I'm made.
My existence here will only lead to being in the way of Milady's happiness.
I'll leave the rest to Hayate-san, and I'll just...
We have an emergency!
What? What's going on?
A large meteor is closing in on Earth!
It will crash into the Nerima Ward in Tokyo in a few minutes.
What?!
It's within sight!
What kind of turnaround is this?
Or rather, I'm surprised that the scene before the opening had meaning.
It'll crash at this rate.
Let's get out of here fast.
No. Judging by its mass, running away won't get us anywhere in time.
What?
Then what do we do?
Hayate-san. Please take care of everyone.
Y-You aren't going to...
I'll destroy the meteor in outer space before it causes any damage to the surface.
If I use my self-destruct module, it should possible.
Self-destruct?
S-Stop it!
You can't go, 13!
This is your Master's order!
Milady.
It's a butler's job to protect
the Master even at the cost their life.
Forgive me for disobeying you.
You can't! I won't let you go!
I won't forgive you if you go!
You can't, 13!
Hayate-san. Please take Milady away.
Milady, you need to get away.
Let go! Let go!
If I have the chance to be reborn,
I'll be sure to get the emotion of jealousy installed.
I wish the best to you all.
13...
Farewell, everyone.
13!
Farewell, Lady Nagi.
He was such a good guy.
13-kun...
Milady...
13-san.
The huge meteor disappeared for an unknown reason right before crashing into the Earth.
Thanks to Mecha Butler's courageous act,
Earth's peace and the happiness of Lady Sanzenin were saved.
Thank you, 13.
Farewell, Mecha Butler 13.
Nagi and,
Hayate's
Butler Network!
The burning heat! I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
Hey, this is Hayate's character song.
The Hayate no Gotoku character song rush ended, so they were able to play my song again.
Maybe they just couldn't get the next song ready in time.
That's not true. Although there are some people who haven't gone yet.
Anyhow, we prepared Hayate's service shot today.
Cross-dressing Hayate is good too, but for the female Hayate fans around the world, today's is Hayate in his butler uniform.
When did you take this picture, Milady?
But I do like it better than the cross-dressing one.
Bye bye.
This is... a letter without a "sender" name?
Someone's got some courage to send me a love letter.
But who?
Could it be-
Hinagiku-san.
Hayate-kun?
So this letter is from you?
Next week, Hina Love.
Episode 48 is a must-see episode for Hinagiku fans.
Though, I don't have much screentime.
Next week, Ai! Zen! Claws! to Hayate no Gotoku.