A way of expressing gratitude.
I can sense that
I am needed elsewhere!
It's my way of repaying you!
Did I really lose?
But how many would bind him
with a scarf made
with embedded wires?
[snoring]
[NISHIYAMA]
She's asleep!
Well, I guess it's
finally the season, huh?
Yes, it is, isn't it?
The season when
it's almost time...
Any month now my heating
bill will finally decrease.
Not what I meant!
Just me, or is anyone else
having a bit of a
déjà vu moment?
[FUTABA]
It's almost Valentines!
That's an extremely
important day, y'know...?
A day meant for
gorging on chocolate!
[YOKO] That's not
actually what it's about...
[HAYAMA thinking]
Definitely a déjà vu moment.
So, Yoko, what are your plans?
Do you think you'll give
chocolate to anyone?
Well, no... I doubt it.
[FUTABA] It doesn't have
to be anything romantic...
You can give someone chocolate
just 'cause you're
thankful to them.
I see. A way of
expressing gratitude.
Oh, I just remembered!
Something happened
the other day...
[mewling sounds]
Aww... That poor kitty...!
I don't think he can
get down all by himself
But... what should I do...?
It's really high up.
And I don't know if that
tree will take my weight
if I try to climb it.
Still... I need to
rescue it somehow.
[YAMAJI] I can sense that
I am urgently needed elsewhere!
I have more important
things to do than this!
[SHINO]
More important than cake?
[YOKO]
He dropped everything...
rushed right over to
help me rescue the cat...
Wasn't that sweet?
Huh... That kinda
seems like something
that should've happened to me.
Why is that?
[FUTABA] So, anyway,
what happened to the cat?
We got it down...
...but it ran away
before I had the chance
to pet it or anything.
[HAYAMA]
That's how the story ends...?
That's all you can offer?
Well, forgive me if I
couldn't meet your expectations.
[FUTABA] I wonder if it
will come back to repay you.
The cat, repay me?
Yeah, you know,
the thing from stories
where animals repay
people who help them.
I'm not entirely certain
what a grateful kitten
would look like, but it sounds
rather adorable, doesn't it?
[FUTABA]
Well, maybe...
Uh-huh? Uh-huh?
[FUTABA]
Thanks for the help, human.
I got you some fish.
[YOKO]
Er, salmon?
[FUTABA]
Thank you for the help.
I got you some money.
[YOKO]
That's better!
[HAYAMA]
As a sign of my gratitude,
I suppose I will let
you stroke my paw pads
just this once, fortunate human.
[YOKO]
That's all?
[FUTABA] Doesn't sound like a
very grateful cat if you ask me.
Huh?! Where's Yamaji?
Oh. He's probabl--
I am at your service.
[sighs]
I have a request...
Uh. Yes...? Go on...
[HAYAMA] Well...
this might sound... weird...
...but if the kitten comes
back... to repay you...
...do me a favor...? Please...
Capture the moment on this
so that it can be
immortalized for all eternity...
[YAMAJI]
I'm not sure I understand.
[HAYAMA]
Please, I beg you!
[BEL]
Teru. Teru!
Huh?! Bel?!
Hey, thanks a lot...!
You've been a great human!
I'm thankful to you
for taking me in
and looking out for me.
You've been so kind.
So, here... Take this...
It's my way of repaying you!
That felt like Bel
was saying goodbye
and leaving and
never coming back!
Oh, cause of that
story Yoko told us.
Still... it was
just a dream, right?
Meow!
[HAYAMA]
Oh, um... thanks, Bel.
Yeah, so that was my morning...
Wow.
You see, it's just
like the stories say...
Bel repayed you after all.
You're right, thanks.
[HAYAMA] Of course, cats
show love very differently
than humans do.
And... I guess your
ability to receive that love
is a good measure of
your success as a pet owner.
[FUTABA] Hey, if anyone
knows about pets, it's you!
[YOKO]
You're a model pet owner!
Oh come on,
you've gotta be kidding me!
Just because she likes animals
doesn't make her
a good pet owner!
There's more to it than that!
I'm sure there is a lot
that you can teach me
in that department...!
Your sweet one must have
given you so many gifts.
[NISHIYAMA] Uh?!
Of course she has!
But the only gift that really
matters to me in the end
is having Eternal by my side...
I don't know who could
ask for more than that.
Yeah?
Let's all calm down.
Hey, I know!
You could have a competition
to see who cats like more.
[FUTABA] You're all
about kitty pictures, right?
So why don't we just agree
that whoever takes
the better picture wins?
[HAYAMA]
Come on, Bel... Stay still.
Wait...! No...! Hold on...!
We can snuggle later!
My wrists were about to collapse
from holding this
camera for hours
and now suddenly,
they feel completely healed!
I worship you, Beelzebub!
How'm I supposed to pick one
when they're all so cute?!
It's freakin' impossible!
[NISHIYAMA]
I brought my picture.
[HAYAMA]
Me too. This is my best shot.
The three of us will
be in charge of judging.
[FUTABA]
Well, they are cute.
[KONDO]
Yeah they are!
Both kitties are adorable...
but... it's a bit like comparing
two peas from the same pod.
[HAYAMA]
Huh?!
What do you mean?
That obviously isn't true!
I guess Beelzebub
is pretty cute.
Eternal is, too,
so I can see why
they'd have a hard time
picking just one of them.
D'you think I could keep this?
How about we
just make it a trade?
[FUTABA sighs]
I honestly don't know
if I'll ever
understand cat lovers.
Some competition.
That was nothing but a
big waste of time if you ask me.
I got a cute new kitty
picture out of it,
so I'd say it went fine.
Huh?! If it's a competition
you're looking for...
Futaba Odagiri!
We've got a volunteer.
Tsuji alert.
Lemme guess:
you're here to challenge me
to an eating competition...?
Not this time,
cause today I'm gonna be
the one challenging you!
What?!
Whaddaya say
to jumbo hamburgers?
[HAJIME]
Uh... You're on!
No fair! They wouldn't
even let me sit down!
I take it this was
one of the places
that had the good
sense to ban you?
That's the reason?!
You had actually forgotten that?
[HAJIME] Ha ha ha! They let
me in no questions asked...
I believe that would make
me the winner by default.
[gasps]
[HAJIME]
Tsuji 1... Odagiri zero!
Ha ha! You suck! Woo-hoo!
Hehe! Woo-hoo...! Boo-ya!
Did... I really lose?
[HAYAMA]
I'm not so sure.
Let's think about
this for a second.
[gasps]
Hey, you're right, Hayama...!
They wouldn't let me in
because I'm a bigger
threat to them than he is,
and therefore that makes me
the winner by default...!
Stop dancing, you little monkey!
So... I suppose some
congratulations are in order?
I recognize you...
What's your name again...?
Errrr... Nishi-something?
I don't understand
how you would know my name.
[HAYAMA] Technically,
he only knows half of it.
It's "Nishikawa"...!
To you that's Miss Nishikawa...
Never forget to
use the honorific...!
You'd better learn
to show some respect
to your superiors, boy!
Yamaji...! Be quiet right now!
Huh? That is a cool trick...
Just like Sasame told me about.
Right... you know
her from your sister.
Yup...
She told me that you're one
of her friends from class.
Me?!
[HAJIME] Well, anyway,
thanks for looking out for her.
She can be kinda
fragile sometimes.
Oh...! Well,
I don't think... Uh...
I'm happy she thinks
of me as a friend.
[YAMAJI gasps and thinks]
That smile! I may go blind!
[HAJIME]
Sasame!
Guess what...!
I won against Odagiri.
I wouldn't call that winning...
You can't win if the other
person doesn't enter the fight.
Yuh-huh...!
There were witnesses;
that friend of yours
even congratulated me...
You know... that girl...
Nishi... hara...? Kawa...?
Something like that.
It's Yoko Nishikawa.
That's it, she's
the one I talked to...!
Don't worry,
I was totally polite
and told her thanks for
looking out for my sister.
[SASAME]
What?!
Sounds pretty mature, huh...?
Yep... Just like a
big brother should be.
You are you such an idiot!
Jeez...! How could
you say something
so embarrassing like that...?
I bet you made her feel super
awkward and uncomfortable.
Think it's a normal thing
to say for most people.
[SASAME] Maybe if we'd been
friends for a really long time.
It's not like Nishikawa and I
are childhood friends,
so we're not nearly
that close yet.
[HAJIME]
Really?
Idiot...! I hate you!
She's going to think
I'm a total loser now!
I don't get why it's such
a big deal. Just calm down!
[SAKURA]
Help me here, I need ideas.
When I give him the
chocolates, I want it to be
the most memorable experience
that he's ever had!
Not asking for much, are ya?
I wonder how much
chocolate I can buy
with my allowance this year.
I've been dreaming
about this for months.
[SAKURA] Hello, we're
talking about me, not you!
I think if you
knitted him a scarf
and made some
chocolates from scratch,
that would be pretty impressive.
[FUTABA] Really?
Don't plenty of people do that?
[HAYAMA]
Sure.
But how many would
bind him with a scarf made
with embedded wires and then
force-feed him chocolates
drugged with an exceptionally
powerful aphrodisiac?
You're my hero!
They aren't serious, are they?
[SAKURA]
I have to get going.
There are a lot of
preparations to make!
[HAYAMA]
Careful walking home!
I'm off to trap my man!
[YAMAJI] That sounds
like quite an elaborate plan.
I'm sure that the young
master will be surprised...
He's in for a
lovely Valentine's.
And... I have
also been thinking...
Hmm?
This Valentine's...
I believe I would like
to make chocolates as well.
Sorry could you
say that again...?
My hearing seems
to be a little bit off.
I said chocolates...!
I want to attempt
making chocolates.
Ah, I think I understand now.
You wish to stockpile it
for emergency rations.
[YOKO]
No, for Valentine's!
And may I ask who will be the
recipient of said chocolates?
There's my friends, of
course, and I'd like to send
a whole mountain of
them to my father, too.
What were we
talking about again?
[YOKO]
Valentine's!
Guess what...?
I've decided that I am going
to try to make chocolates!
Good... This time of year
is as busy as Christmas,
so I'll gladly take
all the help I can get,
even if it comes from you.
I didn't mean make
them for the shop...!
I want to create
delicious chocolates
and give them to the people
in my life I'm thankful for.
It won't interfere with
my duties here, I promise
[SHINO thinking] Miss Yoko
making chocolates from scratch?
She'll start out
energetically enough.
But disaster will strike,
and she'll wind up
exhausting herself.
Then she'll end up sick
in bed, unable to work,
and I'll be understaffed at
the busiest time of the year!
It's horrible!
[SHINO]
That's my situation.
Please, say you'll help...!
I'll be lost without you!
No way!
And I don't see why
you want me so badly...
Can't you just
ask somebody else?
I feel like you're
the perfect person
for the job, that's all.
[NISHIYAMA]
Why?!
Because I'm assuming
you don't have any plans
for valentine's day.
Now you're insulting me?
[YOKO]
What are you doing here, Sonobe?
[SHINO]
I was asking Nishiyama
if she would give me
a hand at the shop.
Ooh, pick me! I can help.
I know how to do everything,
and you won't have
to pay me, either.
You can compensate
me with cakes.
If I do that, there
won't be any more goods
to sell to the customers,
so I have to pay you
Fine... suit yourself.
[SHINO] I would
appreciate your help, too.
[HAYAMA] I'm willing to do it
as long as I don't have to wear
that maid getup.
Well... I don't know, I mean,
it's kinda like a "my house,
my rules" situation...
[HAYAMA]
I can't hear you!
All right...!
Is everybody ready
to sell some cake?
Yes!
[SHINO]
Please, Miss Yoko,
I really think you should
conserve your strength.
[HAYAMA]
Hey! I thought we had a deal...!
Why am I wearing this?
[SHINO] Oh, good...
It fits you perfectly.
[HAYAMA] This is a direct
violation of our agreement!
[SHINO] As I recall,
you said you did not wish
to wear this maid outfit,
and so I made
you a different one.
[FUTABA]
Calm down, it looks good on you!
[YOKO]
Lovely...
I had really hoped
that I would be able
to make some for
the two of you, as well...
...but I just
didn't have the time.
I didn't know getting ready
for Valentine's Day
was so intense.
I stayed up
forty-eight hours straight
trying to make Hayama's
new outfit for the occasion.
Ugh! That's your fault!
Thank you for waiting.
As you can see,
we are quite crowded today,
but I promise we will help
everyone as quickly as we can.
[NISHIYAMA]
Welcome to Secret Garden...!
Please decide what
you would like to order,
and I'll be happy to ring you up
right here once you're ready.
Ugh! I still don't get
why she made me come!
We're gonna need
all hands on deck today...
Just look at how busy it is.
Where's that other guy...?
You know,
the creepy butler dude.
[YAMAJI]
Sorry, I can't help right now.
I'm busy making this special
chocolate cake for Miss Yoko,
and I don't know how
much longer it's going to take.
That can wait 'til later...
Tell him, Sonobe!
[snoring]
[NISHIYAMA]
She's asleep!
[FUTABA] She has been up
for two days straight.
We need her help.
How can she sleep
when it's this busy?
[FUTABA]
It'll be alright...
With you here, I'm sure
we can pull through!
Absolutely! Let's get to it!
Welcome to Secret Garden!
[FUTABA]
It's almost too easy.
[YOKO]
Thanks for your patience.
I'm sorry for the wait!
Don't worry... I expected you
to be busy... It's Valentine's!
[gasps]
That's so kind!
Awwww...
Man... I'm getting tired.
Sonobe! We need you to wake up!
Come on! Sonobe...!
What's the matter, Hayama?
Running out of steam already...?
It's a little early for that.
If only I were
as tireless as you.
Too bad...!
I've got hours left in me!
[HAYAMA]
Well, in that case...
...I'm sure you won't mind
if I just take a quick break.
Wha--!
Excuse me.
Sorry, how can I help you?
Thanks, Nishiyama. I know
I can always count on you!
[YOKO thinking] She could make
life a lot easier on herself.
Thank you very much,
and have a nice day!
One limited edition
Gâteau Chocolat, please.
Sure, one Gâteau Chocolat
coming right up!
It's the Tsuji twins again...!
What are you doing here?
Stop looking at me like that...!
Guys can buy cakes on
Valentine's Day too, y'know.
Of course they can!
It's totally no big deal!
There are lots of special,
limited edition items
during Valentine's
and Christmas.
He saves up money especially
for this time of year.
I know it's no big deal,
but it's still a bit unusual;
I bet you get weird
looks from some people.
[HAJIME]
I don't care...
I get plenty of chocolate
from girls at school,
so it's not like
I'm really worried
about my reputation or anything.
Wow... seriously?
That's right...
I don't know why you look so
surprised that he's popular.
Yeah, and you know,
I'm even the mascot
for my school club.
How cool is that?
Way cool...
[NISHIYAMA]
Thank you so much for coming...
I hope we'll see you again soon!
[KONDO]
Hey there!
Sorry, but I just
couldn't pass up
the chance to see
you hard at work!
Sounds like a waste of time
to me, but suit yourself.
[SHINO] You could
start working here, too.
I'm sure I could find
a position for you.
[NISHIYAMA]
She's awake?!
Oh... that's not really
my thing, but thank you.
[NISHIYAMA thinking]
What's not her thing?
[GIRLS]
Goodbye! Thanks for coming!
[SHINO]
Listen.
I want to thank all
of you very much
for your hard work today...
I would have been completely
lost without your help.
The best part of it is,
after that nap I feel
about ten years younger!
[YOKO grunts]
Sonobe...! I could kill you!
[sighs]
Yesterday was exhausting, huh?
Yknow, after seeing
you in that maid outfit
I kinda wanna try one myself...
Maybe I should ask Sonobe
if she would make one for me.
That isn't gonna work.
Yoko said she only seems to like
making people wear them
if they don't actually want to,
which isn't too surprising.
Yeah... sounds like her...
I guess that's why
Nishiyama's a maid, too.
[GIRL STUDENT 11A]
Nishiyama... a maid...?
There's no way.
It was the uniform that she
asked me to wear, okay...?
She didn't have anything
else so what could I do?
I... I wasn't wearing
it because I wanted to!
Sure... of course not.
It's true, whether
you believe it or not.
I never want to wear
that outfit again...
Really, I would rather die.
It was totally hideous.
Yeah, I completely
agree...! I mean,
it fit you well enough, but it
wasn't exactly flattering.
It might work for someone else,
but you looked so
uncomfortable...
...that's probably the reason
you always pick such
boring outfits. Right?
Well, I don't know if I would
call my clothes boring, but--
Uh...
I dunno, I actually thought
it looked pretty cute on you.
Uh?! Uh... You're
always making fun of me!
Ahh... Nishiyama!
I was being serious,
why'd she get mad?
I don't think you can blame her
for being a little suspicious.
It was so nice of you to
help out in the shop yesterday.
And I... I wanted
to say thank you...
For that and for
everything else you do.
Here!
I'd been hoping someone'd
give me a bag of rocks.
They're Valentine's Day truffles
that I made from scratch!
[FUTABA and HAYAMA]
What?!
They're filled with
all the gratitude I feel
toward you for being my friends!
Homemade truffles.
That's pretty ambitious.
[FUTABA] They're not
what I'd call "melty,"
but they're edible.
There, you see...!
I can make some things
if I put my mind to it.
Well done, Yoko...
Quite impressive!
[HAYAMA]
Is it melting at all?
No, Not so far.
[YOKO]
Oh, Tsuji!
Huh?
I have a little
something... For you.
What?! Chocolates...?
Are they really for me?
Yes... I hope you like them.
[SASAME thinking]
Nishikawa gave me chocolates?
What should
I give her in return?
I-I-I I don't know
how to thank her...
What would be appropriate?
[SASAME thinking]
Something really awesome...
Like a puppy... or a car...
or a house, maybe?!
Yamaji... I made these for you.
What...?!
A beautiful girl made
chocolates for me?!
Thank you so very much...!
I will put these on the
family altar immediately!
Or maybe you
could just eat them...
There should be
a big batch of them
arriving for father
today, as well...
So I guess all of my
Valentine's work is done!
[SHINO thinking]
What? That's it...?
That's all of them?
[SHINO thinking]
What about me?
I don't get any
Valentine's Day chocolates?
Miss Yoko?!
[YOKO] The next
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
is the last episode!
[HAYAMA] Let's have
Miss Yoko say the title.
[YOKO]
Okay, I will.
Next time is, "I Am
Graduating from Bread Crusts."
I hope you enjoy it.
[FUTABA]
Well, that's not happening.
[HAYAMA]
Nope.
[YOKO]
It will!