Rukako...
please calm down and listen to what I have to say.
You used to be a guy.
This again?
Wait! Don't cry.
Just let me finish!
All of this is for Mayuri's sake.
I need you to go back to being a guy.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mono kodou no kazu sae
is a trivial matter with little glamor for you
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Even trapped in the past and lamenting the future
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
The dreams that stretch into "infinity" and the future we imagine
"mugen" ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
are vain privileges we allowed ourselves
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no kenri
"Finity", that's what the two hands of the clock show
"yuugen" sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
towards a cruel agreement and choice
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
and protect your smile
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
And once again, a solitary observer
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
is sucked into a time loop without sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
Fractal Androgynous
What's wrong?
Your face looks like that of a man who failed at cooking instant noodles
and tossed them into the sink.
I'd prefer you say that
I look like someone who tried to use all his coupons,
only to find they've all expired.
I guess you aren't so depressed that you can't joke around.
Okarin, Mayushii is very disappointed in you!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Don't try to fool me!
You made Ruka cry, didn't you?
H-How did you know?
When I asked her to come to the lab,
she just started crying,
and when I asked her about it,
she said you told her she's a guy!
You heard about the D-mail?
D-mail?
I told you not to lie to me!
You should apologize to her.
Okabe...
you said something that awful to her?
Wait! That's not it!
There's a reason for it—
I don't care.
Come with me, assistant.
Come on!
Wh-What is it?
So the next D-mail I need to erase is the one
Rukako sent to her mother's pager before she was born.
She was really a guy?
I can't believe it.
But it's true.
It was true.
She was a guy.
Was she like Hashida?
That was mean.
No, she looked just like she does now.
That's okay then.
Anyway, to save Mayuri,
I need Rukako to return to being a guy.
But you already know
what the D-mail she sent said, right?
Then you don't have to tell her.
You could just do it yourself.
I don't know the number for her mom's pager,
and I thought it would be better for her
if I told her the truth instead of lying.
Your brilliant idea made her cry, didn't it?
That's just how you are, huh?
It's some kind of joke, right?
That's mean!
I didn't think you'd say that to me.
You think that was a flag?
A flag?
I never said anything like,
"Once this battle is over, I'm getting married."
That's a death flag!
I'm talking about a love flag.
Love?
Her beloved Okabe told her she's really a guy,
and it damaged her maiden's heart.
No way. Rukako is a guy, though.
That was in the previous world line, right?
Sender: Rukako
No Subject
Dear Okabe,
I have something important to say.
Would you come to the shrine?
I'm waiting. I'm waiting, okay?
"I have something important to say..."
Could you come to the shrine?
Okabe.
I'm sorry about earlier.
No, I'm sorry for crying.
So...
what did you want to talk about?
Right. Well, I have a request.
A request?
I believe what you told me.
And so, um...
I'll become a guy again, but in exchange...
p-please...
be my boyfriend!
B-Boyfriend?
Why would I be your boyfriend?
Because I love you.
Because I love you, Okabe!
So, tomorrow, just for one day,
won't you be my boyfriend?
N-No, but you're a gu—
Fine...
I'll do it, so don't cry!
Very well.
I'll be your boyfriend for a day if that's really what you want.
Really?
Why are you crying?
Because I'm so happy.
That was actually pretty cute.
So you'll be going out with her tomorrow?
Yes.
A mad scientist on a date with a high school girl.
Don't say it.
That's why I'm enduring the mortification
of asking a mere assistant for dating advice.
I told you I'm not your assistant!
You're going on a date with someone, Kyouma?
Here you are!
Two iced coffees.
Are you going out with Mayushii?
Or with her ?
No, this is my assistant.
Even if it helps you perfect your ultimate technique,
you're chasing far too many girls.
Too many girls, huh?
Hey! Don't say things that'll be easily misconstrued right before you leave!
Hey, would you...
Would you do anything to perfect your ultimate technique?
I-I mean, would Hououin Kyouma do anything?
Why are you talking about this too?
I don't understand.
J-Just curious!
I was just wondering if you'd do anything to perfect your ultimate technique,
even if you already had someone you loved...
There's no real meaning behind it, okay?!
Why are you getting mad?
I'm not mad!
Anyways, if that's how you're gonna act,
why not go on a date with her?
I already told you that I was going to!
Okarin...
I'd really appreciate it if you'd fill me in on the details.
If you want to know where to go on a date,
I've kissed dozens of girls.
I'll tell you everything you need to know!
There's Nene, Shiori, Honoka, Rinko...
All those girls are from games.
I'm talking about a real date.
I heard you usually go to Aoyama, Omotesandou,
or Nishiazabu.
Fashionable and trendy...
A premium night...
A special dinner...
It's hopeless.
This is a different world...
None of it exists in reality.
What do you get by denying it?
I, Hououin Kyouma, was born
with an IQ of 170, just like Isaac Newton.
I am a mad scientist,
and I prefer research over girls—
Definitely a virgin!
Thank you very much.
So what about you?
Do you have enough dating experience
to talk down to me?
See?
You've been so busy with studying and research
that you've never been on a single date, right?
You had a lonely youth, didn't you?
Shut up! Is it so wrong to be a virgin?!
With first dates, the most important thing
is making yourself presentable to your partner.
Regarding clothing,
there's no need to wear expensive brand names,
but something clean—
I'm fine there.
There's nothing cleaner than a lab coat.
Who goes on a date in a lab coat?
The same applies to your destination.
There's no need to pay for an expensive high-end restaurant.
The places you normally go are fine.
Places I'd normally...
Guess here won't work.
Of course not.
You can't take her somewhere gloomy like this!
I suppose the other place I frequent would be...
May Queen.
A maid café for a first date?
The weapons store.
Why are you buying a weapon?
You're just reading from a dating book,
so stop shooting everything down,
you American virgin.
Who's an American virgin?
Who else but you?!
Yeah, yeah. You're a virgin too.
Hey, wouldn't this be a better book to read?
That's a dating sim walkthrough!
Who cares?!
Erotic things happen on dates all the time,
like holding hands and stuff. That's erotic!
Or when she takes your arms and presses her breasts against you,
that's erotic as fuck!
And at the end of the date, there's a kiss.
Damn it all!
Screw all you normalfags!
So it's morning, and I have no plan.
Stop complaining and get dressed!
Take off the tags.
Who ties their tie like that? I can't believe you.
You're a mess, you know that?
Here.
I feel like someone just put a chain around my neck.
Here's a handkerchief too.
You know how to use that, right?
"I'm still waiting for you."
That's for the yellow handkerchief of happiness.
Where did you learn these things?
That's old, anyway.
Yet you knew it.
Well, my bad.
The correct answer is,
"You spread it out before she sits on a bench."
Well, whatever.
I'll tail you and text you advice.
You're coming with me?
So is Hashida.
Operation Valkyria begins!
Why Norse mythology?
It's critical that you're not late.
Be 15 minutes early at the very least.
Okabe!
I'm sorry!
I thought I left early too.
Were you waiting long?
No... I just got here.
Oh, good...
Th-Then shall we go?
Yes!
I've never seen you without a lab coat on.
Th-This is a date, after all.
When you're walking with a girl,
you should subtly take the side with oncoming traffic.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
What's that?!
That wasn't subtle at all!
When a bike or car approaches, subtly protect her.
Did he protect her?
Okabe!
Are you okay?
No, he just tripped,
and then a maid helped him up and gave him tissues!?
What on Earth...
Miss Makise, you seem upset.
I-It's nice out today, isn't it?
Yeah.
But there are some clouds.
Yeah...
This cake's very good.
The coffee is too.
Why?
I've spoken normally with her my whole life,
but the moment we're on a date...
This is a wonderful restaurant.
Do you come here often?
No.
This is bad.
A smooth flowing conversation is imperative.
Th-This is actually my first time here.
He actually answered her question?
Today, August 14th, is Patent Day
to celebrate when the first patent was issued in Japan.
What kind of conversation is that?
You sure know a lot, Okabe.
I-I guess.
Wanna go home, Miss Makise?
We're just watching. We can't help at all.
No, we must see this to the end.
Thank you.
Um...
Is it boring?
Going on a date with me, that is.
What are you talking about?!
Next, we'll walk around town.
Come with me!
Ruka?
So hot...
He's just walking the whole way to Ueno and back?
Okabe...
do you remember the first time we met?
Yeah...
You saved me after some men with cameras accosted me.
Yeah.
Thank you!
But I'm really sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because...
I look this way, but I'm a guy!
Who cares if you're a girl or a guy?
That doesn't matter at all!
Back then,
what you said made me so happy.
It was those words that made me start to like you.
"That doesn't matter at all," huh?
Wait! Aren't those memories from when you were a guy?
I... What am I saying?
I feel kind of strange...
It's just like it was with Feyris.
She's remembering the last world line.
Thank you for today.
I'm so happy... so happy...
so happy you were my boyfriend for today.
Hey...
This is the number for my mom's pager.
"Meat, meat, vegetables, vegetables, meat, meat, vegetables, vegetables."
If she sees this, I'm sure Urushibara's mom
will assume the last one was a prank.
We're ready!
What's wrong, Okabe?
Hey, hey...
Mayushii saw Ruka on a date with someone!
That was Okarin.
No way.
It definitely wasn't Okarin...
He was wearing normal clothes,
and he looked like a gentleman—
She's right.
It wasn't me.
That wasn't a date with the real me!
Okarin?
The date isn't over.
But Okabe...
Kyouma!
Have you forgotten my name, Rukako?
Guys, girls, boyfriends...
I was the one who was confused.
None of that matters!
I finally realized...
I am me, and you are Rukako, my protégé!
Right!
So bring me the dark blade, Summer Rain!
That's right!
That's exactly right!
Yes!
Listen, Rukako.
Listen well.
The legend of this dark blade goes back
to the age of Yoshitsune.
On the night of the full blood-red moon,
a traveler was lost on the roads.
Look at him go.
Good.
He made up with Ruka.
I guess he doesn't need us anymore.
Please save Mayuri.
The old PC you're looking for...
The IBN 5100?
Until last New Year's, it was in our storehouse,
but I broke it...
while I was cleaning the storehouse,
so it's all my fault!
Okabe, please...
save Mayuri!
I was so happy to have the chance to train with you.
Ruka—
Please go.
If you don't, I think I'm going to cry...
I should say the words, shouldn't I?
El Psy Congray.
Congroo.
El Psy...
I really don't want to go back...
Because... Because...
If I go back,
I'll have to hide the feelings I have for you!
I don't think I'll be able to love you if I'm a guy...
Rukako...
If I go back to being a guy,
I'm going to forget all about today.
That we went on a date...
That the two of us trained...
That I was able to hold you like this.
If I had to suffer like this,
I should've never wished to be a girl!
Even if you go back to being a guy,
you'll still be Rukako to me.
Nothing will change!
That's right.
It doesn't matter if I'm a girl or a guy, does it?
But just for a little while,
please remember me
as a girl...
I'll never forget.
What's wrong, Okabe?
Urushibara Ruka,
the mannerisms and voice of a woman...
No, more feminine than any woman.
Hey, Rukako...
Yes?
Do you like me?
Wh-What are you saying?
Do you?
Um... Well, I respect you!
But... he's a guy.
Just one message left.
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten