All performances are finished!
Seriously, stop moving!
You don't need to...
This has to be done.
It's a beauty contest.
A festival dedicated to beauty.
How cute do you think you are?
In the end, her father couldn't make it to the pro wrestling show.
Kushieda, who has always cheered for Taiga, didn't come backstage.
This is 2-C, right?
You have twenty more minutes until the meet up.
Crap!
I'm a host, so I still have to prepare for that!
Takasu-kun, how's the clothing going?
Oh, I'm done with it.
I just modified Taiga's dress a little bit.
It looks good, Takasu-kun!
R-Really?
The image is aimed to be Juliet's type of dress, an empire silhouette.
It's light and elegant...
Takasu-kun is dangerous.
It's not his face, but it's still a bit scary...
There are some other props.
Taiga, do you want to try it-
Are you still waiting for your dad?
He won't be coming now.
I'm not waiting for him.
He's probably late because of his job,
so he's going to get me something to make up for it.
Anyway, I think your lines should be modified a bit.
There's no need to change them.
They're fine as they are.
But you're...
Kawashima-san, it's almost time!
Sorry, I'm coming right now!
So is it really all right?
You're annoying.
I see, that's fine with me.
Hey, what do you mean by lines?
It's nothing.
It's time to get changed.
Takasu-kun, please go outside.
Sure...
Aisaka-san, let's get going.
Yeah.
I can't just stand by and watch a friend get hurt.
Taiga's father...
You'll come for sure, right?
Regardless of how late you are...
...you'll rush here, won't you?
That has to be it, because that's what it means to be a father.
You guys must've waited a long time!
The Miss Ouhashi Contest is about to begin!
Ouhashi High School Cultural
Festival (Final)
Ami-chan! Ami, Ami!
Ami, Ami, Ami is the best!
Everyone, quiet down.
I'll punish you if you don't...
...so quiet down,
you bunch of worthless fools!
A pig who can't fly is merely a pig!
Just kidding.
Even though she says she's just the host, all the attention is focused on her.
Let's begin now.
Entry number one, Mitsui Yuriko from class 1-A!
W-Welcome back, M-Master!
She's such a cute maid, isn't she?
You're going for the look of a Victorian maid, correct?
Y-Yes!
Thank you very much!
No one is listening at all...
Now, let me introduce our next contestant!
She's also a maid, but she has a great smile.
Entry number two...
A text message?
You've got to be kidding...
Can you please relay this to Taiga for me?
Tell her I have to leave for a bit due to my job.
Something's come up,
so we can't live together.
Please help me apologize to my princess. Thanks.
Why did I believe him?
I...
I believed that this was a good thing, and I supported Taiga,
but honestly, somewhere inside me, I felt lonely.
Taiga's father appeared and caused us to drift apart.
She couldn't look at the useless me.
What the hell is that?
Don't joke around.
This is it...
It was all because I was selfish...
I...
Takasu, are you all right?
You don't look too good.
Taka-chan?
How should I face Taiga?
What face should I put on?
Everyone, the wait's over!
You're all familiar with the Palmtop Tiger from 2-C, right?
Here comes Aisaka Taiga-san!
No way...
Is she the Palmtop Tiger?
Amazing...
She's cute.
Um...
Today, in this auditorium...
...Aisaka-san's father is here to cheer for her.
The lines they were talking about are...
If it's possible, may Aisaka's father please come up and say something!
Uh...
He didn't come, did he?
Next, next!
Tai-
H-Hey, Aisaka-san?
Are you okay, Aisaka-san?
Hey, the delinquent Takasu is cheering for his mate.
Actually, the Palmtop Tiger is pretty cute.
All right! The Palmtop Tiger is the best!
But she's super clumsy!
Don't worry about your father!
He-
Who the hell cares about fathers?!
Chop them up and throw them into a mor... mor... morgue!
It's showtime.
Hey, give me that!
O-Okay!
Zip it up!
Um...
Don't pick it up!
Open it!
O-Okay!
I couldn't do anything for her.
Miss Ouhashi Contest
This year's Miss Ouhashi is...
Aisaka Taiga-san!
You're amazing, Taiga!
Thanks to the praise from everyone, she...
No, that's not it!
Isn't she
alone?
Takasu?
I have to go.
I absolutely have to go.
Perhaps it won't work, but...
Even if that's the case...
What's going on?
It's pitch black!
What is this?
Now that the "miss" contest is over,
it's time for the "mister" contest!
The method of examination will be this:
Mr. Lucky Guy
Mr. Lucky Guy!
Mister?
Lucky Guy?
What's that?
A course has been laid out on the campus.
At any rate, just run.
Whoever comes in first will be the winner of the "mister" contest!
A race during the Cultural Festival?
I don't feel like it...
By the way, I should mention what Mr. Lucky Guy will win.
You will be able to crown this year's Miss Ouhashi with this tiara and dance with her.
And you'll also get the notes from all my classes;
the class time memos, questions, and the answers to the tests from these past three years.
The president's notes?!
Dancing with Taiga?!
This is impossible.
I want it!
Taiga...
I don't want the prizes.
I don't care about being Mr. Lucky Guy.
Anyway, no matter how...
Everyone, don't get hurt.
...no matter who, no matter what...
Got it?
I have to...
I'm scared.
Move!
Crap, the delinquent!
He'll kill us.
On your marks...
Get set...
...get back to Taiga's side.
A lap around the school!
Run! Run! Run with all you've got!
Yeah! Takasu's down!
All right, it's our chance!
How can I...
...lose to them?!
They're here!
Go! Go!
Takasu's back!
That's right, I...
I'm sorry!
That hurt!
Damn it!
Get out of my way!
Oh, Takasu-kun!
Seriously?
That's cheating!
Why is he trying so hard?
Shut up!
I have my reasons, so mind your own business!
I absolutely will...
...never lose!
Why did you let him through?
You did too!
They're here!
The ones that left first are back.
Wow! It's the delinquent Takasu!
Ryuuji...
Mi-
Kushieda?
Why is there a girl?
Is that all right?
It's fine! Girls can participate too!
Takasu-kun, did you not examine him carefully when you met him?!
Did your eyes not look at him carefully?!
She was right, I missed everything.
He just gives her money every month and then ignores her,
he doesn't think about what Taiga wants, and just takes her to random places.
He breaks his promise and sends
a text message as an apology...
He hasn't ever cared about Taiga.
But...
...I didn't see through him.
I'm so stupid!
Ryuuji...
Minorin...
Damn it!
The spirit of the track team!
Kushieda!
What are you doing to girls?!
Aren't you men?!
Kushieda-senpai, take this!
All right!
Takasu-kun, go!
Run for the sake of Taiga!
What are you-
This is our chance!
I'll take you all down!
Attack!
Kushi-
Go!
Be faster than everyone else.
Be faster than me!
You guys don't have to worry about me, you know.
You can see it, can't you?
Even if I'm all by myself, I can stand up again.
That's why...
It's all right...
...you don't have to worry about me.
...I can stand up again all by myself.
Even if I'm all alone...
...I will survive.
Our class! The beauty contest and the title of Mr. Lucky Guy!
Our class has won both of them!
The Cultural Festival was a huge success.
Yes, it's your last Cultural Festival.
I'm glad I could become the student council president of this school.
It was great being with you guys.
I still have some private matters to deal with.
Go and have fun, Kitamura.
But...
You're the reason the Cultural Festival was such a success.
A-All right, I'll go!
I shouldn't have cared about that guy from the beginning.
He doesn't matter at all.
But Taiga, you-
Putting that aside, you were so close to Minorin.
When did you two make up?
Seriously...
Minorin!
Taiga, so you're here.
Minorin! Minorin! Minorin! I love love love love you!
All right, I get it get it get it.
Taiga, you look so cute.
That tiara looks good on you.
That's because you put it on for me.
Takasu-kun did too, didn't he?
I don't know. I didn't see it. I didn't hear it.
Oh, stupid chi' is flirting again!
Ami-chan, please...
Ami!
Hey, what are you doing?
It was exactly a year ago.
Taiga's father showed up exactly the same way.
I was really happy that they could finally live with each other,
but in the end it was no different than now.
Her father just suddenly disappeared...
I'm sorry, Takasu-kun.
W-Why?
I should be the one apologizing!
No, it should be me.
I knew her father's true nature, but I didn't tell you about it.
Taiga didn't say anything to me.
I really treasure Taiga.
That's why I was jealous of you...
Why didn't Taiga say anything?
She knew I'd get mad.
Taiga doesn't want people to think ill of her father.
That's why, since this day last year,
Taiga hasn't told me a single thing about her family.
Seriously...
Where did stupid chi' go?
Aisaka.
Are you alone?
If you don't mind, will you dance with me?
I guess that's a no because I'm not the Lucky Guy.
Again...
Why are you always...
Aisaka.
It's nothing.
Thank you.
Then...
How do you dance?
We hold hands and look at each other,
then we go in circles until we get tired.
That's it.
Am I a lesbian?
Huh?!
I have this thought...
I-I don't think you are...
You're probably right.
I'm speaking normally?
What are you doing, Taka-chan?
You're such a party pooper!
We should have fun together because our class is the best class!
That's right, you two should come too!
Taiga?
All right, let's dance on the night of the Cultural Festival!
Tonight is a special night.
A lot of emotions are mixing together.
When I try to laugh, my heart hurts a little.
When this night ends...
I think...
...everything will be all right.
Next Episode Preview
The Happy Palmtop Tiger
Everyone in front of the T.V.,
this is the duel of destiny.
I will activate the ultimate magic: "Legend of the Happy Palmtop Tiger!"
After this, it'll always be my turn.