This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
Last time, she had her first
television studio recording
but she just kept forgetting things
and messing things up!
She almost didn't get
to sing her song "Myself"!
But with a veteran singer's
warm words of encouragement,
everything turned out well
for Full Moon!
I may have become an expert
in the show business world!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Thanks to this photo you took,
the popularity of
the Guitar Fighters has plunged.
I see...
You've made quite
a few enemies, haven't you?
One of these days,
they'll come to haunt you.
If I was scared of some
stupid ghosts,
I wouldn't be able to be
in this line of work.
So? What do you
need from me, Chief?
I want new material.
Weekly tabloid magazines don't sell
without a good scoop.
Then, how about this girl?
Your next target?
Full Moon...
She's a 16-year-old idol
who's been popular lately.
However, there's no data on her.
Not even her real name
has been made public.
I see. Full Moon, huh?
And now,
Next from "Fullta Moontaro,"
we have a question.
"Miss Full Moon, what kind of artist do
you want to become in the future?"
How about it?
Do you have some kind of goal?
Oh, umm...
Umm...From here on,
I want to keep singing,
and send out my feelings.
Send out your feelings.
So is there someone specific?
What?!
Uh, well...
It's a secret.
A secret?
Come to think of it,
your real name's also...
Oh, yes.
That's also a secret.
Hmm... I see.
Everything's a secret, huh?
Yes.
Tomorrow's the magazine
cover photo shoot, right?
You'll be with Shirakawa
from Shonen Drill.
Whoa, really?
That's right.
It's your first collaborative photo...
Huh?
We're going to take
a little detour!
Miss Oshige, is something wrong?
We're being tailed.
Huh? Tailed?
Don't look!
You'll get your picture taken...
by Saegusa,
a tabloid photographer .
He's this jerk who specializes
in exposing
details of celebrities' private lives
and their romances.
We've been followed from the studio.
I bet he was taking your pictures
the whole time you were on the air.
Huh?!
Darn it.
Miss Oshige...
Late!
They're late!
What're those two doing?
Hm?!
What's this?
Lens?
He's really persistent!
At this rate, I won't be
able to drop you off.
I'm kind of scared.
All right!
Damn!
We lost him, huh.
Saegusa is like a hyena.
He doesn't let the prey
he targets escape, no matter what.
There isn't an entertainer
who has completely escaped
after being targeted by him.
But, I don't have anything
to be targeted.
You haven't had your real name
and profile made public, right?
For a person like him,
you're an object of extreme interest.
No way.
It'll be okay.
If something happens,
the management office and I
will protect you with all our strength.
You're not alone.
Okay.
Have a good evening.
Oh! Mitsuki.
Yes?
Maybe I should take you home.
No, I'm okay.
Really?
If something out of the
ordinary happens,
contact me right away, okay?
If my real name is found out,
I might not be able to sing.
I won't let that happen,
no matter what.
Hey, don't turn around,
Huh? What is it?!
We're being followed.
Wh-Why?
We weren't able to
get away completely.
Oh no!
What should I do?
Just walk normally as is.
Turn around that corner.
Okay...
This is bad.
This means I won't be able to
turn you back to normal.
No way...
What shall I do?
Hey, over there!
Go into that tunnel!
Got it...
Good! It's okay, now.
Let's go.
It's that guy...
I told you it'd be okay, right?
Yeah... But I was scared.
No kidding.
You had a rough time, huh?
But thanks to Takuto being there,
I was able to get away completely.
Don't mention it.
Well, I have an early start
tomorrow,
so I'm going to take a bath.
Hey, Takuto.
Yeah?
Huh?
What is it, Meroko?
It was difficult to say
in front of that girl.
A new job has come up.
Something preventing
her death, again?
Hm?! What's this?
The letters are backwards.
It's backwards,
so that means the pattern is
the opposite of the usual.
In other words, it doesn't mean
something will delay her death,
but hasten it.
Hasten her death, you say?!
It says, "Lens."
Lens?!
Saegusa's camera?
We should stop her from
going to work tomorrow.
What're you saying?
I can stop that guy on my own.
Impossible.
That'd be absolutely impossible
for a rookie like you!
Then, what're you saying we do?
I'll do something about it.
Is that really okay?
But, this is all there is
for us to do.
Let's see, this and this.
I have this, too...
All right.
It's just a dream.
It's not a dream!
What're you doing, Meroko?!
Oh, uh, well...
I thought I'd try turning into
Full Moon and go out today.
Why?
Um...I-I wanted to let you
relax for once.
Work's rough, isn't it?
That's not a problem.
I like work.
Sorry, but I have work, too.
Hmm? What do you mean by work?
No, it's all right, Meroko.
Takuto?
You just stay here.
But...
It's okay. I'll protect her,
no matter what!
What was up with Meroko?
It's nothing.
Now, let's hurry!
Yeah.
No matter what happens...
I'll protect you.
Okay, it's a wrap!
Thank you very much.
What?! That Saegusa has
his eye on her?
That's right. What a pain...
We've also had
bad experiences with him.
We had people quit
on account of him.
Yes... It's a real problem, isn't it?
Miss Oshige!
The shoot is done.
I-I see.
That's it for today.
All right. Then I'm going home.
Oh, shall I take you?
No, it's okay.
I see... Be careful
going home, okay?
Okay! I'm sorry to be
leaving so early.
Miss Oshige's such worrier, isn't she?
Yeah. But actually, that Saegusa jerk
hasn't come since then.
Excuse me.
You're Miss Full Moon, right?
Could you take
a picture with us?
Uh, sure.
Yay!
Get a nice shot.
Get a bit closer.
Okay! I'm going to take
the picture.
Say cheese.
Please do your best.
We'll be cheering you on.
Oh, thanks.
Geez, making me panic like that.
I was scared.
I thought it was Saegusa again...
It's him!
Let's go!
Y-Yeah.
Damn.
I won't be able to sing if
my secret is known.
And I won't...with Eichi...
Impossible.
That'd be absolutely impossible
for a rookie like you!
That just can't be true.
Hey!
What're you?!
But...
He's going to catch up.
Okay! Let's go!
Huh? H-Hey!
We have to change you back to
a 12-year-old while we have the chance!
O-Okay.
SUMMER SALE
GOING ON NOW!
Hide over there.
But...
Quickly!
While we're at it,
wear this just in case!
- Now!
- Okay!
Yes, it's right on target...
I understand. Bye...
Has he noticed you?
Run away while you can.
It can't be!
Oww!
What're you doing?
I'm sorry...
My, I'm sorry.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Oh, I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
That girl.
Oh no!
You jerk! Take this!
What the—?!
And this!
W-What?!
Go while you can.
Okay!
Okay, I'll go at it like crazy!
Here's a bonus!
W-What's going on?
What's that?
What? Is it
a supernatural phenomenon?!
It's a poltergeist!
Oh no, how scary...
He's a groper! A pervert!
No, you've got it wrong.
It's not me!
Where'd she go?
Oh my...
Which way was the station?
Damn it. That was horrible...
She slipped through my fingers.
It's not like me.
There she is.
Takuto couldn't possibly...
I wonder if he's okay.
Where am I?
What should I do?
And Takuto isn't here...
I know! The whistle!
You!
Mitsuki!
Where is she?
I saw you yesterday, right?
In the tunnel.
As a matter of fact, an idol named
Full Moon went through there then.
Did you notice her?
Strange. You're the only person
I saw down there.
I-I don't know.
Then why do you run away?
Could it be that you're
affiliated with Full Moon?
You can't answer?
I-It's nothing like that...
Then, could you please
talk to me a bit?
No!
H-Hey!
No. I won't be able to see Eichi
ever again if my picture is taken!
You little brat.
Hurry... Hurry...
I've been waiting for you!
Say, could you give back
my camera?
Fine. I won't ask you
anything anymore. Okay?
Now, that's enough!
H-Hey!
It's dangerous for you
to be out there!
Hey! Come back here!
Takuto, help me...
Takuto!
Man, making me worry...
That jerk...
W-What? She's floating.
Yikes!
What in the world
are you?
I'm the vengeful ghost of
a celebrity you ruined.
V-Vengeful ghost?
That's right.
I've come to settle the score.
W-What're you going to do?!
I won't be satisfied until you have
a taste of your own medicine.
Stop it...
Please! I'll do anything
if you forgive me.
I beg you!
Then, you must vow never
to do a thing like this again.
Otherwise, I'll haunt you for
the rest of your life.
Okay. I understand!
I'll never do it again.
Then, get out of here!
Well, that's that.
You did well.
Hm?! It's vanishing.
You did it, Takuto!
And now! Continuing from last week,
Miss Full Moon has joined us again.
I'm glad to be here.
By the way, Miss Full Moon.
Yes?
Could you please tell us at least
one of the things you've kept secret?
Secrets are meant to be kept secret.
You're just one big secret right,
Miss Full Moon?
Right!
Then, shall we go with the song?
Here's Miss Full Moon with "Myself."
Why do I like you so much...
You don't need to worry
about Saegusa anymore.
I don't know what happened,
but it seems he suddenly quit
his cameraman job and went back home.
Really?
I wonder if the medicine
worked too well!
Maybe!
Oww! Hey, what's the meaning of this?
I can't get into Mitsuki's house!
Hold on. Let me check on this.
What?! A barrier caused by
the Saint's Stone?
What's that?
Anyway, it's some kind of barrier
that WE can't pass through!
This is bad. We have to get back
and transform her.
Next time on Full Moon:
"Green Onion Ramen and the Saint's Stone."
- Don't miss it!