Go berserk, Selfish!
It's empty here, so what the bike are you stopping me for?
You're a hazard to anyone walking through here!
Bike!
What is giving you so much trouble?
Cure Ace!
You were here?
An enemy this weak should give you no problems!
Strict as ever, I see...
Pedestrians can move it!
You're taking far too long!
We shall meet again. Adieu.
Huh?!
She ran off...
Bikeikeikeike!
Girls, we must concentrate!
Yeah!
Love Heart Arrow!
Mach 1000!
Huh? Mach 1000?
That's absurd!
Sword, aim for its tires!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
You'll have to do better th—
Precure Heart Shoot!
Love love loooooove!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
It's Out of the Bag?!
Cure Ace's One Weakness!
I do think she's a bit hard on us,
but it's thanks to Cure Ace that we became stronger.
Though we still don't know anything about her.
She seems to come and go like the wind.
Yeah.
Oh, that's where my mom takes her tea classes.
It's Madoka Mari's house.
Madoka?
So you had to deliver some snacks?
Yeah.
My dad made them himself!
They're for tomorrow's tea ceremony.
Tea ceremony?
It's an outdoor tea party where you serve guests.
Coming!
Oh?
Cure A—
Madoka!
... Aguri is my name.
Oh, Mana.
You must be delivering the snacks.
Um, yes...
Thank you.
These will make tomorrow's ceremony a fine one.
You're familiar with my granddaughter?
Huh? Granddaughter?!
Cure A—
The other day!
I met them at the festival.
Oh, I see.
Could I have a minute?
Uh...
When my grandmother is around,
please don't call me "Cure Ace"!
So you really are Cure A—
I never thought you lived so nearby.
It's like you were hiding right under our noses!
I'd prefer it if you didn't put it that way.
I never ran or hid.
That said, right now...
is a bit inconvenient.
Oh, I have an idea!
Dangit, they make my stomach turn!
If you keep that up, we won't have a hideout left.
How can I not stuff myself?
True, the Precure's sudden boost in power was most unexpected...
If we do nothing, we very well may repeat the failures of Bel's team.
Perhaps we should try the combination technique, too.
What, you and me?
Your wild side really appeals to me.
Wild?
That's got a nice ring to it.
And that top hat of yours ain't bad.
Oh, how nice. Now then...
Let's give it a try!
I'm pleased you could make it.
Hello!
You have our thanks for inviting us.
I'm kind of nervous about the ceremony,
but this is a great chance to learn more about Cure Ace!
You're right.
Please, follow me.
Now, I shall begin instructing you in the Way of Tea.
Well, we don't want to go tha—
The Precure's Five Vows!
Listen!
A Precure
A Precure must be a first class lady!
must be a
first class
lady.
Really?
Before I serve you tea, you must eat your snacks.
S-Sure!
It's yummy!
Want it?
A tea ceremony is for serving others.
A server would never eat her guest's food!
She acts pretty cute whenever sweets are involved...
Yeah.
Where are your manners?
Oh!
Uh, rub a dub dub?
No, Mana.
"I humbly accept your service" is the phrase.
The Yotsuba family knows their etiquette!
Um, I think there's something you need to do before drinking...
Good thing I studied for this exact situation!
Take the teacup, and...
turn it!
That's not the kind of turning they meant!
Huh?
These are big!
I can't drink!
A-A little more...
Oh dear.
I suppose Ai is a bit young for tea.
Girls!
Sorry! We'll be serious now!
My legs fell asleep...
Makopi, are yours all right?
Of course!
Slee...
They fell asleep!
She was faking it.
Um, Aguri?
Well, you were all just so silly!
I'll end the ceremony here for today.
By the way, outdoor ceremonies don't require all the formalities of indoor ones.
You strung us along?
I did no such thing.
Geez!
You seem to be enjoying yourselves.
Grandmother!
This is the first time you've invited friends for a tea ceremony, no?
Please, be good friends with Aguri.
Sure!
Please, Grandmother!
I'll go take a stroll with my friends.
Toll!
Have fun, then.
It's so pretty!
This river's water is famously clear.
It feels great.
It does!
This is so nice!
When Aguri isn't Cure Ace,
she's actually a normal girl.
I'd like to apologize for being so hard on you all until now.
I just wanted you all to grow stronger.
You must have much you want to ask me, no?
I'll answer anything.
Why did you make us stronger?
You could probably take on King Selfish alone!
I couldn't possibly do it alone.
I am a Precure born in this world.
I once lost in a battle against the Selfish.
After that,
my partner, Ai, returned to being an egg,
and we had been separated ever since.
But one day, Ai suddenly returned to me,
and led me to you girls.
That must have happened while she was supposed to be with Joe.
I have a question, too.
Go ahead.
Why do you get bigger when you transform?
That's the power of my feelings.
Power of your feelings?
I want nothing more than to protect worlds that are terrorized by the Selfish!
Those feelings allow me to grow up.
That's amazing!
As we speak, many worlds are being engulfed by King Selfish,
bringing him ever closer to resurrection.
To stand against him,
I need you to rise to the Precure's true stage and fight by my side!
We understand.
Now that we've grown strong—
There's still a long way to go!
You must become even stronger!
There is no choice!
The terror of the Selfishes is no trifling matter!
My grandmother knows nothing of what we've discussed.
So I beg of you, keep it a secret from her!
I don't want to put her in danger.
Of course. Right?
We promise.
We have to try harder.
Regina needs us, too...
No Barbecues
This spot looks good.
Hey, barbecues aren't allowed here.
No Barbecues
Aw, who cares?
Nobody's lookin'.
You sure we won't get in trouble?
Yeah, we should probably move.
Aw, just...
barbecue here.
We shall grant...
your desire two-fold!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish.
That's a Selfish!
It's enormous!
There you are, Precures.
Surprised?
This is the fruit of our teamwork, the Combination Selfish!
It's two times as big, five times as strong, making it ten times the Selfish!
It's truly nothing like what we've fought before.
I shall fight with you.
We will finish it within five minutes!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Oh poor grill who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Ai.
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
Our first ever group project...
is all yours!
Let's BBQ!
Fire!
It's hot!
Gotta grill that meat!
M-Meat?
That's not meat!
It's a meatsile!
Gotta cook those veggies!
Got room for seconds?
There's no stopping him!
I must end it in three minutes...
Combine your attacks!
I will pin him down!
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Turn up the heat!
Oh no!
He broke her Ace Shot?
Should you not worry about yourselves?
This is for yesterday!
Girls!
Two minutes left!
How about we finish with dessert?
Dessert?
Ooh, I smell something sweet and tasty!
Let's go, Selfish!
Where are you going?!
This was supposed to be a team effort!
That way leads to... Grandmother!
We have to chase it!
Only one minute!
Here it is!
I smell sweets!
Selfish.
What have we here?
Yummy!
Who are you?!
And have you no shame for wearing shoes to a tea ceremony?
Huh?
Want me to eat you, too?
You shall not!
Grandmother!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Oh no, time's up!
Grandmother!
Stop right there!
Girls!
Why aren't you transformed?
I can only stay in my adult transformation for five minutes!
That's why you've always left early until now!
Don't worry!
We'll protect the people you hold dear!
Selfish!
Grill 'em well done!
Let's BBQ!
Now's the time to show what the strength Aguri... no, Cure Ace gave me can really do!
Fire!
For our hearts that support each other!
For the feelings we hold dear!
For our hopes for the future!
Have another helping!
What?
Seeelf!
For the strength that lets us rise when we're fallen!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love looooove!
This is all because of your gluttony!
Shut it! I live to eat!
I'm fine, really.
Thanks to those mysterious girls, anyway.
I failed rather spectacularly today, huh?
Not at all!
Aguri, you were great.
Here, this one's for you.
You didn't eat it?
Thank you so much for today!
No, thank you!
I look forward to your continued guidance.
Then from now on, I'll be even stricter!
Huh?!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
It's summer!
Festival time!
Yukatas and fireworks!
No!
You have no time for playing around!
You have to focus on training!
But can't we ju—
No means no!
But there's a stall selling Super Special Scrumptious Sweets...
What a shame.
Huh?
Super Special Scrumptious Sweets?!
Dokidoki Precure:
Heart Pounding!
Aguri's Summer Vacation!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!