I thought it was called "Miso"
or "Malt" or something like that.
To keep the nasty pests from staring,
we'll be quick and stealthy.
Wow!
It's the ocean!
The beach is a must during summer!
It was worth waking up early for this.
Viewing the ocean from a train
like this is a first for me.
Ah, because you're a rich girl, huh?
She was one.
At the beach, we've got to...
Relax on the beach?
Make sandcastles?
And split a watermelon!
But...
Yeah...
We came here to work, huh?
Veggies,
Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Meat, Fish
Summer.
Summer means the ocean!
The ocean means a beach hut.
This August, I present Himitsu no
Hanazono, beach hut version!
It's tough working there as it is...
And now she has a beach hut version.
Don't worry.
Mitsugu found this suitable place for me.
Yamaji...
Always there to serve.
Of course, the shop is temporarily closed today.
That's not what we were worried about.
Wait, I've been wondering since earlier...
...what's "Himitsu no Hanazono"?
It's the name of my shop.
What?!
Oh!
Secret Garden...
...is English for "Himitsu no Hanazono"!
Did you know, Miss Youko?
She would know the name of where she works.
Er...
Well, I thought it was called "Miso"
or "Malt" or something like that.
Those are totally wrong!
It's a western cake shop!
Well, if it were based on Miss Sonobe,
it should be called "Den of Thieves"...
...or "Shop of Chaos.'
As I said, it's "Himitsu no Hanazono"!
Same difference.
Quite right.
It's completely different!
It's perfect for someone
who reeks of the 80's.
Oh, Yamaji.
So you knew, Yamaji?
Yes.
Every time I get a receipt,
I cringe with embarrassment.
Anyway, from today we'll be Himitsu
no Hanazono, beach hut version!
Ah. Um, I have a question...
What is a... "beach hut"?
Miss Youko...
Are you serious?
Th-That's right!
Of course Miss Youko wouldn't know!
You're a rich girl who
knows nothing of the world.
I-I have a least heard of it before!
I just do not know what it is exactly.
Sonobe!
Explain to me what a
beach hut is in plain terms.
Huh?
With interpretive dance!
Waves.
Wind.
I do not understand.
I do not understand at all.
I do not think I can work then.
Sand! I am sand.
Uh, what is this?
Is it a ritual or something?
W-Well, we've come all the way out here...
And she said she would pay us, too...
I suppose there is no other choice.
Then, let's go change.
Yes, let us.
All right, let's go!
I'm getting excited!
Truthfully, I didn't approve
of this beach hut thing.
There's nothing good about getting
sunburned and heat stroke.
To keep the nasty pests from staring...
...we'll be quick and stealthy.
I see.
Good luck.
Shaved Ice
And I was playing—
Yum!
What is this? It's so good!
Wow, it's delicious!
I'll have the melon and orange one, too!
Oh, but I want to try all of them!
What's that? It sounds good.
I want to try it, too!
It's so obvious she's a fake customer!
Well, as usual, I'm forced to help out, too.
Thank you very much.
Please work hard so nasty pests
don't notice Miss Youko.
I think it'll be fine.
What is it?
You seem dissatisfied.
Well, you look different
from what I had imagined.
I do?
Yes.
I had imagined...
Summer!
Under the bright sun!
A summer time for girls bursting with youth!
The sweet lure of a flushed body.
A sweets paradise by the shore!
Himitsu no Hanazono.
Open this summer at the beach hut.
Mwah!
Something like that.
Absolutely not.
Old-fashioned, as usual.
And you could get sued for
that disguise at the end.
If you could at least wear
something like Hayama or Futaba...
I do not wish to get an unsightly tan.
How about working in a bikini to avoid that?
Like your uniform is a bikini.
Miss Sonobe, you can wear one.
This place is, more like a fancy
café than a beach hut, huh?
That's true.
We'll have a summer menu with
gelato, frappes, and gelatin desserts.
What about ramen?!
Curry?! Fried noodles?!
We're a dessert shop.
Isn't fried noodles a dessert?
What?
It's not a side dish?!
Himitsu no Hanazono!
Beach Hut
Open today, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Man, the shop's name is embarrassing.
Should we move somewhere else?
What's that?
Big Sister! Big Sister!
Big Sister!
Big Sister.
Yuu?
I heard that you were
working at a beach hut.
I'll help with the sales!
I'll just have some of everything!
Oh?
But the whole menu is
ice cream and drinks.
Oh, really?
What should I do?
Need some help there?
Maybe it's not a good idea.
I'm cold after eating so much.
You do not have to push yourself.
But, you made this.
Here's the peach lassi.
I'll finish it all.
Thank you for waiting!
Big Sister wasn't the one making them?
Yes.
So immature.
He's really immature.
Just because you're an adult doesn't
necessarily mean you're mature.
I thought you were aware.
Yup.
It's true.
Closed for the Day.
Today was our pre-opening,
so I've closed the shop early.
Thank you for your work.
We were only open for half the day,
but sales were excellent.
It was harder than I expected.
And very hot.
We're not used to it.
I've prepared a barbecue to restore our
energy since tomorrow will be a full day.
Meat?!
Meat!
I-I want some, too...
Are you all right, Yuu?
I'm fine.
I'm a man, that much is nothing.
Especially...
...if you'll cook the meat for me...
Everyone, the food's ready!
What?!
You really don't learn.
So immature...
Wow, so enthusiastic.
Apologies.
Is my cooking not to your liking?
No, I don't feel like eating it.
Well, I'm actually glad...
Then, we'll have some.
Let's eat!
Food is so nourishing after hard work.
Yamaji!
Grill with the ratio of veggies, meat,
meat, meat, meat, meat, meat, fish!
Our profits today...
Teru!
Wow, it looks so yummy!
Big Sis!
You were up early for work today, huh?
I came to help...
What?
We're done already.
Your sister is very kind.
Would you like some, too?
I'm jealous since I'm an only child.
Yeah, thanks!
You have told me that before!
Ah, it's the little boy!
H-Hello!
You're not going to eat any meat?
That's not good.
You won't grow bigger.
I know!
I'll make some for you.
Oh... Thank you very much.
Yuu...
This might be the last straw.
Oh no, barbecue should be fine.
Raw meat has more vitamins, did you know?
I'll call an ambulance, just in case.
Beach hut, Himitsu no Hanazono!
Here's the mango frappe.
This is our last day working here.
We made it through, somehow.
But we didn't get to play at all,
even though we're at the beach...
We've been working this whole time.
Thank you both for accompanying me this whole time.
Still...
You got tan, Futaba.
More like burnt.
Well, it's summer!
Even so!
Summer means curry!
Aren't I kind of like curry?
You're okay with that?
Anyway, I have a farmer's tan now,
so I want to even it out.
We'll be done working, so let's
go all out and play tomorrow!
We haven't gone into the ocean
so we need to take this chance now!
You are right.
I'm pretty much done with homework
so let's have fun for the rest of summer.
H-Homewor—?
What is it?
I'm not sure I know that word.
Our modern Japanese homework is a reflection essay.
Will you be okay?
Then, I will prepare lunch for you as thanks.
Really?
Do you have any requests?
Barbecue!
We had that the first day.
What's the beach without barbecue?!
There's more to the beach than that!
How about curry?
It's enough just looking at you.
You can leave it up to me, then.
Regardless, let us enjoy the beach tomorrow!
Yeah!
The ocean is plentiful.
You're going to catch stuff?!
All right!
Let's make the most out of tomorrow!
Shark Sighted
No Swimming
It depends on the species, freshness,
and cooking preparation.
What are you talking about?!
Geez!
What the heck?
I can't swim!
How disappointing.
It would have been nice if it were
a dolphin rather than a shark.
Yeah...
Big Sister!
Yuu!
You're not working today, right?
You can play, right?
That's what we thought...
There's a shark—
Not to worry!
Southern Sea Resort Hotel
I brought tickets for the hotel pool.
So let's go here!
Oh, can we?
Yeah!
Can we barbecue there?
I said it was a hotel.
Wow!
A pool!
It's so pretty!
It is all thanks to you, Yuu.
It was nothing.
Oh, it's been a while since I've
gone to a pool with you.
Y-Yeah...
Now, make sure to stretch.
Here's a floatie.
It's like you came with your mom.
Oh yeah, where's Miss Sonobe?
The lunches are taking longer than expected.
She said she would meet us by lunch.
Well, Big Sister, let's pla—
Futaba!
Sakura.
Usuda. Why are you here?
Oh, yeah...
He's not good at dealing with Sakura.
I just happened to come here with my family.
Hm?
Yuu!
I found you!
It was probably emotional
damage rather than physical.
I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Wait, Sakura went with him.
Oh...
Miss Youko, be nice to Yong Master next time.
I should.
Now, let's enjoy this pool!
Yes!
We will enjoy it in Yuu's place, too.
Wow, this is amazing!
Hotel pools are great!
Stop, it's embarrassing.
But, it's so amazing, Nishiyama!
Your swimsuit is pretty amazing too, though.
Th-This is normal!
By the way, it's amazing you
got free tickets for this pool.
Someone gave them to me.
Gave them?
Hayama's sister gave them to me.
What?!
How did that happen?
You see...
First
place
It's so heavy!
Excuse me...
Do you need some help?
Really?
So that was Hayama's...
Then, she gave me the tickets she won.
I can't really enjoy myself now that I know.
Well, it's not like Hayama is here.
Oh, it's Hayama and the others.
What?!
They're totally enjoying themselves.
Just ignore them... ignore...
They're totally enjoying themselves...
I-Ignore them.
Got some turban shells!
What are you doing?!
Oh, Nishiyama.
I'm practicing catching
sea urchin or abalone and stuff.
Don't do that here!
Yeah.
It's against the law unless
you're a fisherman.
That's not the problem here!
Oh, you are—
Oh, Nishiyama.
Why do you always follow me?
No way, do you like me?
Don't make up gross things like that!
Oh, it's the nice girl from before.
Oh, Hayama's sister!
Even her sister's here...
Is she your friend, too?
She's just my classmate, Nishiyama.
Oh, right!
Since we're all here let's all play together!
Wai—
I-I have some friends here...
Huh?
You do?
Come on, let's go!
Nishiyama!
Now, I'll go finish my sandcastle—
Teru!
You should swim, too!
Y-You should know. I can't—
Ah, you can't swim, huh.
Is that true?
It's pretty scary if something happens, huh.
Like, if your boat sinks in
the middle of the ocean.
That's true!
Let's practice swimming!
In case you really need to some day.
When I really need to...?
There!
Like now?!
You can do it, Teru!
Th-The sisters share a resemblance.
Come on, Teru.
You need to try harder.
No way, no way, no way!
Hayama, you don't like the water?
It's not about liking or not,
I just can't swim.
I've lasted this long not
knowing how to swim.
I'm fine just the way I am.
Hayama...
Teru...
Then, let's go practice in the kiddie pool.
No!
You can do it!
Please try your best.
Everyone! I brought lunch.
Oh, Miss Sonobe.
I'm saved.
You took a while.
Sorry, it took me longer since there
were so many unfamiliar things.
This is your lunch.
I've been waiting for this!
Yeah, it really took a while since
it was a first for me, too.
By the way, why are you both beat up?
It was just harder than expected.
And it was wild.
But, we got a hold of a rare ingredient.
Rare ingredient?
Oh.
I don't think the shark will be
bothering us anymore,
but I still don't recommend swimming
since there are many jellyfish.
Oh my, is that so?
Don't tell me...
Delish!
You ate it?!
It's ground meat.
They seem like good friends.
You do get sleepy after swimming.
You can use me as a pillow, too.
N-No, thanks.
Go ahead, you can lean on me.
Th-That would be improper.
I can't eat another bite.
She would...
Was she sleep talking?
She's probably having a feast
in her dream right now.
I can have a feast if I sleep?
No, that's not...
Go to sleep. Go to sleep!
Sleep. Sleep.
I don't think you can sleep
if you try that hard.
Go to sleep. Sleep.
Sleep. Sleep.
Miss Youko...
Go to sleep...
Sleep. Go to sleep...
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade.
Rock, paper, scissors!
mumble
I can't eat
another
bite...
I can't eat another bite...
Maybe not... probably...?
Maybe
not...
...prob-
ably...?
Seriously?
Seri-
ously?
I cannot.
Not
any-
more...
I cannot
eat any-
more....
I cannot eat anymore....
I want to take the rest with me...
I want
to take
the rest
with
me...
I can-
not?!
Ahhh...!
I cannot?!
I can-
not?!
Ahhh...!
A     A
Wah
Next time: Ten Yen Short
A nightmare.
A
night-
mare.