Yui, are you still in bed?
Are you feeling okay?
Want to stay home again?
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
Quit beating
around the bush!
How about laughing more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
That comic was pretty cool.
Time for some curry.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Curry hot pot
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
me yui
We should get married
I love youuuuu
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
The whole world
Let's go
to Disneyland
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry, I can't
go out with you.
Seriously.
Done tomorrow's
homework?
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
Hey, Yaegashi!
Finally decided to grace us with your presence?
Yeah, something came up.
I feel sorry for you, man.
You missed out on seeing your darling's big scene.
Yeah, it was awesome.
My darling?
The girl in your club.
You mean Nagase?
Oh, so you've got your sights set on Nagase.
Wh-Why would you say that?!
You, Inaba, and Nagase are the
only SCS members in our class.
And when I mentioned your darling,
you immediately brought up Nagase.
You tricked me!
Watase!
The soccer team's supposed to assemble in the locker room for a meeting.
Ugh, it's lunchtime.
Well, you know where to find me if you need relationship advice.
You can always rely on me. Later!
H-Hey!
Big scene?
Taichi,
why were you late?
Did something happen?
Yeah.
I probably had one of my desires unleashed—
Other people can hear us, idiot!
Can you try reprimanding me in a less painful fashion?
There wouldn't be any pain
if you didn't do anything stupid.
I've never used violence without just cause.
What?
Really?
Huh?
Never mind.
So what desire was unleashed?
I'm guessing it was...
...my desire to sleep.
Huh?
What?
Falling Apart
Ow!
Don't scare me like that over something so stupid.
It was pretty serious!
Well, I was asleep, so I don't remember any of it.
Hey, wake up! You'll be late.
C'mon already!
Wake up! Wake up!
Oh no!
Wake up, Taichi!
My mom had to calm my sister down before she would go to school.
I heard everything from my mom when I woke up.
They didn't call the hospital?
If I hadn't woken up, they would've called an ambulance.
I'll need to apologize to my sister.
I sent her an e-mail,
but I should get her something...
Shut up, sister lover!
It's only natural for a brother to love his sister!
If she couldn't wake you up,
your desire must've been unleashed.
While you were asleep, something happened,
and your desire to sleep a little
longer was unleashed, I guess.
I've been wondering...
Was Nagase's desire to sleep also unleashed?
Taichi wants an answer.
Hey, Taichi...
Have you ever had the urge to break the tension when everyone's acting really serious?
Not really.
Don't tell me...
There was a quiz this morning, so everyone was on edge.
And suddenly I had an urge to shout...
Yahoo!
Quiz
Yahoo...
I managed to convince everyone that I was half asleep at the time.
The class thought it was hilarious.
Plus, they seemed to write it off as Iori being herself.
That was the worst part!
If everyone thinks I'm being myself when I suddenly shout,
"Yahoo!" in the middle of class, what does that say?!
That you're the kind of person who likes to shout,
"Yahoo!" in the middle of class?
Don't join them!
Anyway, you guys have some tame desires.
Yui didn't come to school?
I told her about Heartseed.
I mentioned that the five of us needed to talk together.
I called Yui earlier and said we might drop by.
Don't bother.
I'll be back at school by the end of the week.
By then, everybody will have gotten over what happened yesterday.
Yui...
Damn...
Heartseed's messing everything up again.
If he makes Yui cry again,
I'll make him pay!
Aoki!
Name five good things about Kiriyama Yui!
Cute! Cheerful! Strong! Super cute!
Pretty hair! Small! Innocent!
Childish, but in a good way.
Wait! I need more than five!
You shouldn't've used "cute" twice, then.
So, did that help you calm down?
Huh?
Avoid intense emotional outbursts.
It won't matter if your desires are unleashed
if you don't have any meaningful desires.
You're right.
But I can't help it.
Yeah, if all it makes you do is shout, "Yahoo!"
then we can all laugh it off.
Wait, Taichi.
Is this a new form of bullying?
Are you bullying me?
So when I get irritated or angry,
I should think about Yui and calm down.
Yeah, that works in your case.
But I'm still worried about Yui.
She's probably still in shock after beating up those guys.
I have to help her!
I have to go.
Wait, Taichi?
Not good!
His desire was unleashed!
Wait, Taichi!
Wait! Wait!
Get a hold of yourself, Taichi!
I have to go help her!
I have to go help Kiriyama!
You really like to help people, huh?
It's kinda creepy.
Let me go! Let me go!
Wake up, Taichi!
Calm down!
Okay, Iori!
Throw yourself on Taichi!
Gotcha!
Wait, why me?!
Aoki's stronger!
No, we might be able to change things up or stop this
if we override his current desire with a stronger one.
Are you sure that'll work?
It's worth a shot.
Do something like crawling up his body to awaken his dirty side!
Wait, wait.
Well, I don't really mind...
Iori, do it for Taichi's sake!
Hey, stop messing around!
Got a problem?
It would've been dangerous to let you go.
Of course the white knight rises for those in need.
Hey, did he calm down?
Huh?
Oh...
Yeah...
I guess our desires aren't unleashed for that long.
Nothing will happen if it's something that can't be done right away.
But generally, spur-of-the-moment desires are driven by your current circumstances, right?
Your mind tends to focus on your surroundings.
Aoki made a valid point!
Why are you so surprised?!
I have my moments!
What's Heartseed up to this time?
It's the same as when we were swapping bodies.
He wants to watch us and be entertained.
This phenomenon just serves as a catalyst.
Don't ogle me.
I wasn't ogling you!
Wait.
Do I look like I'm ogling people by default?
I'd say that you're in the most danger this time around.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Well, you were willing to die for Iori when you were in your right mind.
What if that desire was unleashed?
You might...
actually die this time around.
I checked Class 1, but Yui was absent again.
She said she was okay when I called her yesterday.
I hope she's not letting this get to her.
What do you mean by that?
Just like last time,
one of us could break at any moment.
We need to go to Yui's house today.
Yeah.
Lose the long faces.
If you show up looking so grim,
Yui might end up feeling worse.
Yes?
Kiriyama, let's play!
Huh? Wait, Iori?
No way, why?
And I'm here, too!
Along with Inaba and Taichi!
There aren't any cameras.
Kiriyama
Everybody's here?
Yeah, all of the SCS members are here.
We came to see you.
Can we come inside?
Is someone else there right now?
No one else is home.
But you can't come in.
Please leave.
You don't want any boys inside?
Is it okay if only Inaban and I come in?
That's not it.
Just...
Oh.
Are you Yui's friends?
Come on, Yui. Open the door.
Your friends are here.
Tell them to leave.
I'm sorry.
She's locked herself in her room
and refuses to come out.
It's okay, ma'am.
She's just a little upset right now.
I'm sure she'll cheer up soon.
Yes, "Mom"!
Let us handle this!
Thank you for being so good to my daughter.
It's nothing.
Let me know if you need anything.
Yui, you shouldn't make your mom sad.
Anyway, can we talk for a bit?
We've got big trouble.
Please leave.
I appreciate your concern.
I'll be back at school soon.
This is a pain.
Are you gonna do something?
No, I'm just going to say the magic words to make this door open.
What are you, exactly?
Okay then.
I'm going to reveal Kiriyama Yui's secrets now.
First, her BWH is an A—
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I'll let you in, so stop!
It would've been more fun if I got to say more stuff.
You're too scary, Inaban.
Sorry about dropping in without warning.
But...
No, it's okay.
I should be the one to apologize.
Are you feeling sick or something?
We can go if you are.
Wait...
There's a big zit on your forehead...
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't look! I made a huge mistake!
Did you go on a binge?
Th-That's not it!
Yesterday, I suddenly had the urge
to gorge myself on sweets.
I wanted to die when I started
counting all the calories.
Wow, that's terrifying.
You must've had an episode
while you were hungry.
You wouldn't've stayed home
from school because of that zit?
I'm not that stupid!
Then it's because Heartseed's
been unleashing your desires?
That's silly.
We're all in the same boat.
But...
I don't want to hurt anyone else.
When I saw those girls surrounded by a bunch of guys,
I really wanted to help them.
Then I went berserk.
That was because Heartseed did something funny to you.
But I was the one who wanted
to hurt those guys so badly.
All because I have a strong hatred for men.
Who knows what might happen next time?
I can't go outside like this!
Stop playing the victim.
Inaban?
You don't get to be the only
one who hides in her room.
Well, if I don't run into anyone, I can't hurt them.
Do you understand the current situation?
Obviously not.
Hey, Inaba...
Nothing can go wrong if you
stay away from everyone else.
Sure, I considered trying that.
But the problem is that Heartseed might not be amused.
He's looking for entertainment.
And if need be, he'll take steps to make sure he gets it.
Like having one of us jump in the river,
or something even worse!
All five of us may be put in danger!
Do you realize how much worse it is for everyone else if you bail?!
Well?!
I don't know...
What should I do?
Take control!
Don't expect someone else
to help you out if you cry!
Inaban!
Sorry, Yui.
I didn't mean to be so hard on you.
I must've had an episode.
But that's how you really feel.
How would I know?!
Don't ask me!
What?
I just wanted to know what was
going on with that Kiriyama girl.
That's what I wanna know!
What are you snapping at me for?
Oh, um...
No.
Well, I didn't mean to yell at—
You think you're better than me
because you have a cute face?
I don't.
Hey, shouldn't you help out?
Stop, that's enough.
Huh?
Sorry, Setouchi.
Kiriyama's absence is sort of a sensitive issue.
She lashed out at you because everyone keeps asking her the same question.
Isn't that right, Nagase?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I'm worried about her too, so I just...
I'm sorry.
It was all my fault.
You don't have to apologize.
I was the one who kinda
embarrassed myself at the end.
I'm sorry.
Fujishima is so awesome.
Inaba...
I'm going home.
Huh?
Bye.
Wait, Inaba.
Why are you leaving?
Do you have something to do?
Not really.
Not really?
Kiriyama was absent again.
So?
We need to go see her again today.
My presence would be detrimental.
Is that why you stayed out of it
when Nagase got in a fight?
I can't afford to do anything
that makes the situation worse.
So I won't be going to the clubroom.
But Kiriyama's hurting right now.
Sure, I understand that
yesterday was hard on you...
That's no excuse.
How can you just give up?!
We have to do something!
Not everyone puts other people
before themselves the way you do.
There are times when I'm too
busy with my own problems.
That doesn't make it okay to
ignore someone who's suffering!
You can't force other people
to follow your sick ideals!
I'm disappointed in you, Inaba.
I never thought you'd give up on your friends.
I thought you were better than that.
I guess I'm not good enough for you.
Student Cultural Society
Inaban, Taichi, and me...
we all have the worst timing.
I've been trying to call Inaba,
but she won't answer.
I'll apologize when I see her
tomorrow morning.
Yeah, the best response would be
to apologize and move on.
Inaba knows that you meant no harm.
Okay, it'll just be the three of us visiting Yui today.
Yeah, Yui should be feeling better now.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Yui
(No Subject)
Don't come over today.
Next Time
And Then There Were None
I told you guys to cut it out!
Today, I'm doing things my way.
You're just a sick white knight who doesn't want to see Yui look sad!
It's getting lonely.
Well, you were right.
I've always thought that humans are supposed to hurt each other.
I see you're busy shakin' out that thin red velvet cloth
But before you take your leave, might I ask where you're off to?
Me, I'm headed for the morning, travelin' to the west
Then may God be with you
Your eyes, reflecting up to me from the teacup
look just like a rabbit's in a cage
Must be because we forgot to add the sugar
But who cares about that
Your love is sweet enough
I cry out, again and again to the dawning sky
Are there really things in this world that I truly cherish?
This aching in my heart, and the place where I belong
Maybe even those are things that I hold dear all the same
Cry out