When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
He's out training again?
He did say he was going to come up with an ultimate move over summer vacation, so I think he's a little under the gun.
Shirt: Namidabashi
From so early in the morning...
Is he a sixty-year-old boxer in training?
I must work hard for Hinagiku-san's sake, too.
Yup, you're right, for Hinagiku's sake, too-
Wait.
But how he can put full effort into everything is one of his good attributes.
It's not good!
Because summer is about to end,
shouldn't we be spending time together?
Imagine what Ro*** must have felt when he lost Adri**!
Seriously, what's on his mind?
Milady.
Ayasaki Hayate at your service!
What's this about, Klaus?
I thought I should relieve your loneliness.
And you came up with this prank?
Yes.
Klaus-san, I think your character setting is coming apart.
Like this?
No, I do not mean physically.
Besides, I'm not lonely.
I'm only a little bored.
Well, if you're that bored, why not make a S*S Brigade?
Consider your age; it's not good to mix anime and reality.
GAH!
To be told that by Milady...
I can't live on as a human anymore!
I guess I'll read some manga to pass time.
Study a little!
Mangas: I Love Fishing Sanpei
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
That was it for my screentime.
By the way, this is Klaus speaking.
What? Milady has?
She looked pretty irritated.
Saying you won't play with her
when summer vacation is coming to an end.
I see.
Yeah, I was too absorbed in my ultimate attack.
So, what is she doing now?
She's reading manga rather than studying, as usual.
Then I'll go right up to her.
That will not be necessary.
Most of the time, after she finishes reading one...
Hayate!
...she gets influenced by it.
Let's go fishing!
Heh?
Lake Sanzenin?
Yeah.
Do you have more than one lake?
Yup.
Although they're small ones, about 2 km wide.
Small...
But can you really catch fish in a lake inside the fence?
Of course you can.
It's natural spring water, so the water is really clear.
Plus her grandfather has transplanted fish from all over the world,
so it has created its own balance.
It's like a cosmos on its own.
It's a very convenient lake where you can decide
what to have for dinner based on what you catch.
Which means...
...you've been catching the fish we eat?
I never knew we were aquafarming the fish we eat.
This is a pretty amazing lake!
It is a beautiful place.
We'll catch all we can!
First, it's fly fishing!
Fly fishing? Isn't that challenging?
Don't worry.
In "I Love Fishing, Sanpei", Sanpei-kun was catching one fish after another using flies.
There isn't anything I can't do that Sanpei-kun can.
Milady, it's not good to mix manga and reality.
Tag: Won't let you!
Although this is an anime.
We should start with worms and something with actual bait.
D-Don't be ridiculous.
Fishing with worms is scary.
Then how about dough balls instead?
Fishing starts with catching crucians and comes back to crucians.
Um, are you going to fish, too, Maria-san?
Yes. I thought I'd let myself forget about
the menu and enjoy catching crucian carp.
It's making me wonder if the Sanzenin are actually amazing or not.
Let's see...
First of all...
Right, dough ball.
Hayate!
Yes?
There was something huge in the lake!
"Something"?
What is it?
It's probably the lord of this lake!
It has to be!
There you go again.
I'm not lying!
Maria-san, does something like that exist in this lake?
Her eyes are too serious to talk to.
She's scary.
Well, it's fine. Hayate, you catch some small fish around the shore.
I'll catch the lord of this lake!
Please do.
Then I'll use the lure.
I need to watch out so Milady won't get tangled in the line and get hurt.
Pop?
Hayate...
The rod went flying out of my hand.
It's dangerous if you don't hold it tight.
Hit.
DAAAHH!
Eh?
What?
Not a bad one.
Maria-san, you're fast!
Looks like I have a hit, too.
Look Milady! You can catch a lot from this lake!
Really? Can you really?
All right, I'll do it, too!
Fishing is boring.
That was fast.
It's because the rods fly away!
It's because you don't hold them tight.
Then it might be better to go offshore on a boat.
Boat?
We're all alone, Milady.
I'm so happy, Hayate.
But fly fishing off a boat is hard.
I think it's better to fish from here.
Let's go Hayate!
Milady!
You see, you hold the rod like this.
See, you can cast it properly, right?
Y-Yeah.
I-I didn't expect Hayate to come so close the moment we were alone.
He's bolder than I'd thought.
If she swings the rod on a boat, she'll definitely fall in,
so I have to make sure to hold her still.
Summer's coming to an end, isn't it?
Y-Y-Yeah.
A lot has happened over the summer, hasn't it?
Like going to the beach class with everyone
and going to the amusement park together.
Y-Yeah.
I was planning on coming up with an ultimate move over the summer, but I couldn't in the end.
Even with all your help...
I'm such a failure.
Th-That's not true.
Would you like to set off some fireworks later?
Ones that are cute like you.
But I hope you can catch the lake's lord before that.
I really don't mind not catching one...
Milady!
You've got a bite!
Come on, Milady! It's pretty big!
It could be the lord!
Wh-What is this?!
It's dangerous, Milady!
Hayate! Where do you think you're touching!
Milady! Let go of the rod!
You're the one that has to let go!
Are you all right?
We shouldn't have gone out after all.
Since you're small.
Shut up!
Hinagiku's aren't any bigger than mine!
Eh?
Milady?
Anyways, let's get Maria-san and head back.
Like I said.
Fishing starts with catching crucian and comes back to crucian.
Y-Yes.
It's definitely the lord...
So, how did you catch it?
It's classified.
For your info, since it couldn't be eaten, they released it.
Dakara hera da'chuuno, hera.
Dakara hera da'chuuno, hera = I told you, it's crucians. Crucians.
Rakki! Cha Cha Cha! Jyanai!
Rakki! Cha Cha Cha! Jyanai! = Lucky, cha-cha-cha! Not at all!
Milady, you have to get changed out of those drenched clothes.
Shut up! It's your fault this happened, you know!
I'm sorry.
You should both get in the bath before you catch colds.
I-Idiot! Bathe with Hayate?
How could I possibly do something that embarrassing?
No one said "with Hayate-kun".
What should I do...
I made Milady angry again.
You shouldn't be so depressed.
Let's go get warmed up.
Um, "let's"?
Do you mean get in the bath together?
Huh?
Obviously not.
What is on your mind?
I'm a coward.
Why did I act as though I was rejecting him?
Looks like another event that causes misunderstanding between them happened.
Baths are great.
It's the greatest cultural achievement made by Lilim.
When having a big bath like this to myself,
I forget all the small mistakes.
Well, it'd be best if I could get in with Maria-san.
Could it be Maria-san?
Ma-Maria-san.
You're... so bold...
You seem to not like temporary body contact.
Are you afraid of physical contact?
What was that for?!
Shut up!
So, how have things been going recently?
"How?" Nothing special really.
Hey, isn't the water a little lukewarm?
You think so? Isn't this about right?
Nah, it's definitely lukewarm!
I was born in Edo. I need hot water!
Click.
Hey, are you sure about this?
Can you play with this?
Don't worry.
All right, this is it.
Damn, it's hard to press it with pads.
Hey, if you hit it so hard-
What was that sound?
I'll go take a look.
Hayate-kun!
I just heard a really loud sound!
Maria-san?
Crap!
Tama! You!
You plan on getting out of this?
Wait, Tama!
Tama?
Hey, don't run!
Hayate-kun, what's going on?
Um, would you like to use this for now?
Th-Thank you.
I'm done for.
Should I apologize to Hayate for acting so cold?
Hayate.
Of all people, Maria-san had to see me like that...
Hey! Hayate!
Hayate?
I CAN NO LONGER LIVE IN THIS MANSION!!!
Maria-san...
What should I do...
Hayate's so depressed because of me.
At this rate, our love will end with the summer!
I must do something!
Hey, debt-ridden butler!
Why do you look so depressed?
You...
Don't take it so hard when you're still young.
Whose fault do you think this is?
Then how about an atonement by death?
Isn't there something I can do before dying?
Then how does this sound?
First of all, let's fix the bath and the boiler you broke.
Sure, although you're the one who broke it.
What?
Sanzenin's boiler's main power is Aki**?
We're stalking about this mansion's boiler.
It wouldn't be like normal ones.
I see signs that indicate we shouldn't be touching anything.
An amateur shouldn't touch anything since everything's dangerous.
I don't want to hear that from a tiger.
Hey, are we sure about this?
Stop blabbing, will ya?
Let's see...
Is someone in here?
Maria-san.
Hayate-kun.
And Tama, as well.
What are you doing here?
Well, I thought about fixing the bath I broke, so I came to the boiler room to start.
And what are you doing here?
That's...
For the same reason as you. I came to fix the bath.
She turned away from me.
She probably doesn't even want to see my face.
It's hard to look at him because of what happened earlier.
Wh-Wh-Why are you crying, Hayate-kun?
Because... Because I'm...
Ah, this is all getting to be a big bother.
A man shouldn't be crying openly.
This is the boiler, right?
Let's fix this and get out of here.
What?
Damn it, pads really make it hard to press stuff.
Maria-san!
Are you all right, Maria-san?
Hayate-kun.
We'll drown at this rate, so I'll drain the water.
B-But how?
I'm going to borrow this.
If I can put a crack in the wall,
the water pressure should do the rest.
We'll catch that wave.
Hold on tight.
Hayate-kun!
Here we go.
Are you all right, Maria-san?
Y-Yes, I managed.
But...
The boiler room is a mess.
I-I'm sorry.
Package: Firework Set
Hayate!
Hayate! Where are you?
This is the only way I can respond to Hayate right now.
But one day, I'll definitely-
I really am no good.
I'm always causing trouble...
Maybe I'm not suited to being a butler.
You really are filled with mystery.
You can do anything above average,
yet you cannot do anything perfectly to avoid mistakes.
But how you work so hard on everything...
I really like that.
Thank you very much!
In order to repay your kindness, I'll keep working hard!
But please do fix the bath.
Yes!
Then right away!
You don't have to do it right now.
M-Maria-san...
Hayate-kun...
Hayate!
M-Milady.
To touch Maria when you already have me...
Is she serious?
You lustful fool!
The debt-ridden butler's summer memories went scattering into the night sky.
And so next week will be a start of a new semester.
We'll fight against the student council staff
and the teachers' conspiracy.
Tamaya!
Isumi and...
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Good morningurt.
I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I am Saginomiya Isumi.
Isumi-san, this song's very soothing.
Hayate-sama.
Hayate, you said the same thing to Maria's song.
Eh? Did I?
Looks like you can't be the MC of this section.
I'm sorry, Milady.
Both Nagi and Hayate-sama look like they are enjoying themselves.
So next time, we will have Sakuya-san in this section.
Adios.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Makimura. I'll be your homeroom teacher from today.
What? Why is that nursing robot developer here?
Crap, at this rate, my position in Hakuou, in this anime, will be in jeopardy.
Therefore, Ayasaki-kun, I'll have you help me.
I refuse.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
A Genius Teacher, Who's Not Small, Appears.
Don't be so depressed, Hayata-kun.
Since, you know, I kind of like being picked on, too.
Can you have faith?