Kumi!
Oh my. You're getting better and better!
Thank you.
If you weren't so anxious, you could've taken down the center.
Y-Yeah.
I want to win against Keishin again on the next match.
Absolutely.
Right, right. I'm looking forward to it.
It should be a good incentive for you that you'll face off against Keishin again.
That's right.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best, too.
That's the spirit!
Rena?
Why did you come here for?
I thought it was about time I played basketball, so I came back.
You are in no position to come back.
Everyone was practicing hard while you weren't coming to practice.
You're holding back the team.
Hmph.
Please wait, coach.
I know I'm in no position to say this...
but please let her come back.
Miyu?
Tomo!
Got it!
Just one week left 'till the tournament, huh..?
I do think their level of play has increased, but...
They did everything they could in the one month that was available.
But their opponent is Suzuridani.
Besides, there's a girl called Rena-san Natsuhi-kun was talking about.
Ashihara Rena never used the same technique when she beat my sister's team.
So you're saying that Rena-san has mastered all kinds of skills?
Yeah, I've only seen them once, though,
so I don't know if I could do them well.
That's good enough.
Could you show me all her techniques you can remember?
Okay, here I go.
The techniques Natsuhi-kun mimicked...
I never thought a grade schooler could do them.
If Rena-san really used those techniques...
I'll tell Tsubaki-chan and Hiiragi-chan how Rena-san does them.
As long as they combine their power...
One more!
Hey, Tsuba! Pass it!
Right!
Thank ya.
What the heck are you doing, Hii?
It's your pass that failed.
Hey now, you can't just blame the other...
What's wrong with you, Maho? We aren't gonna win if you treat it that lightly!
Okay. One more time!
Damn right! Come on, Maho!
Geez... What the heck...
We're gonna beat Rena for sure and win against Suzuridani!
That's right!
We'll have to train real hard for that.
Sure.
You're right.
It's pointless if we won't win.
But you're missing your shots!
You gotta train hard!
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
I'm training way harder than you!
L-Listen, you should stop this.
Everybody has a bad day every now and then.
Yeah, exactly.
You too, Gettan! Your movements are way too stiff.
A-Are they?
Pull it together, will ya?
And you need to pass more, Mimi!
I am passing when I see a chance.
Anyway, I'm not gonna approve of failing!
We gotta train more!
Easy there, easy there.
If you're that fired up you're going to get tired.
Huh?
Yeah, yeah.
You need to make sure you're in a good condition when the game is coming up.
Oh~, it's also important to take a good rest.
You should eat a lot of food, too.
Let's save up our energy, okay?
They said that...
But we can't win if we don't practice.
Our current training schedule isn't exactly fantastic.
Right, right.
I want to be taught more hard.
Otherwise it doesn't make much sense
I can certainly agree with that view.
There's only one week left. We have to train more.
All right. We'll tell the coach about it tomorrow.
Yeah!
Only one week left...
That's all the time we have.
Oh~? What's wrong, Kage?
I'm sorry to make you worry, Nee-sama.
I get a bit nervous when I think about how there's only one week left until the match.
Oh~, calm down.
I know you can do it.
I hope so.
Hiiragi, Tsubaki and Masami all think too much about winning.
Kagetsu's movements are stiff because she's so nervous.
All that's left for me is do my best.
How's the practice going?
Are the fifth graders listening to you?
I guess.
As for now, the sixth graders are teaching them about each position, too.
I do think it'll be all right.
Well, if even you say that...
I have high hopes for you, as always, coach.
Ouch! You're hitting me too hard.
It's the first and last major match for the sixth graders.
You're right.
Ah... Seems like it really is difficult to teach people.
Well said.
It's really difficult to explain stuff to your team mates in a way that they can understand it.
Coaches must have a hard time.
Oh~, our Onii-chan is always so amazing when he teaches us!
You're right.
I'm really grateful how Subaru-san is always coaching and watching over us!
Oh, that reminds me!
Tomo, have you decided when you will do that?
Uh... Um... Maybe after the match ends.
You'll have to do it to him for us, too!
Y-Yes. I'll do my best!
You never change...
Never taking a break, are you?
Even in this cold...
Because that's all I can do.
I really want to hear those words from Rena.
You realized that we have to have Rena on our team, too.
Thank you very much.
Well, we all know how good she is.
Could it be...
that Rena reminds you of how you used to be?
Believe what you want to believe.
We have something to ask you, coach.
We want you to be more strict.
Exactly! We aren't gonna be able to win like this against neither Rena nor Suzuridani.
There isn't much time left until the match.
We want you to teach many more things.
Please tell them to practice.
That's right! Everyone is so unmotivated!
Please!
For now...
Let's do a mini-game, shall we?
Huh?
I wonder what Subaru-san is up to.
All right, let's get started!
Here you go, Tsuba.
Okay.
Huh?!
Wha—?
Maho!
Gotcha. Mokkan!
Airi!
Maho-chan!
Hey, what're you doing?
Oh, what Subaru-san wants to point out is...
Hey, Subaru! Could it be...
All right!
Saki!
What?
Airi!
Got it!
None of my shots go in.
We can't stop them.
I can't see through her fakes.
So we really need to practice more.
We can't win against Rena like this.
That's right...
We have to work hard.
You're wrong.
What do you mean, "wrong"?
We lost because we haven't practiced enough, no?
Why else would we lose?
It's just like Tomo said.
You all move so stiffly that you leave a space.
Normally you'd be talking points.
Huh?
You're probably too obsessed about winning and training.
Oh~, that's why your feelings are all over the place.
I've already told you, but training can only take you so far.
I think there's something more important than that.
Do you really think there's something more important than winning a match?!
She's right. We have to win against Rena this time!
She did something mean to Masami!
It may not concern you at all,
but it's very important to us!
Of course it concerns us!
It's frustrating since we're a team!
Isn't that obvious?!
Sorry, I didn't want to...
It is only natural we want to win the match.
But you're so fired up right now that you're burning out.
You're not even able to do what you could do earlier.
I want to win just as badly as you do.
Before I met everyone... Before I transferred here...
I was thinking about nothing but making the team win and getting stronger myself.
But we're all here now,
and we can play basketball together.
I very much feel at ease when I think about it like that,
and I can feel the power even more.
I'm so happy, now that I can play basketball.
Suzuridani is really a strong team.
So I think we won't be able to win if we're too fired up even if we normally could.
It may be difficult but let's relax, rather than sweat it.
Besides, we've finally all become friends.
We should enjoy ourselves.
Oh~! Tsuba and Hii, didn't you have fun playing basketball with us?
Well... I guess we did.
I think you were never able to get to play an official game, Sis.
You had an even more difficult time.
Let us try it once again.
We will do it properly this time.
All right! Let's do it one more time!
Yeah. Let's do it.
Oh~, roger that.
Yeah. Let's do our best.
Mokkan!
You're slow!
Sorry! Let's do it!
All right, let's do it!
Those girls are growing up so fast...
Yeah. I'm happy when they think of something and learn to do it.
That's what you may say, but you're actually lonely, aren't you?
You've hit the nail on the head...
Their growing up means that we won't be needed anymore.
I suppose.
Thanks, Subaru!
For what?
For letting me be a coach.
I'd never thought it could be this fun.
But I think this very day is even more fun.
Yeah, you're right.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
Let's do our best game as one team... and as friends!
Yeah!
By the way, there's a three-word motto in mini-basketball that you mustn't forget.
Oh~?
A motto?
Friendship, smiling, fair play.
That's exactly what we're doing!
Right. You've always been fighting with that in mind.
So...
We won't forget it today, either.
We're going to fight till the end as one team!
All right!
Have fun with everything you've got!
Keishin Girl's Basketball!
Fight on!
Yeah!
It won't be good if it'll be like before.
Let's go with all our might!
Maho-chan!
Thank ya!
Saki!
So the sixth graders are playing on the first quarter?
I guess it's because of the rule that says the whole team can only go to the field on the third quarter.
Yeah, the fifth graders will come on the second quarter.
Suzuridani will probably come at that time, too.
Those girls probably know that already.
We and they will probably just wait and see at the start.
They should do what they can for now.
Yeah.
This girl...
Wait until she's close enough.
Now!
Oh~, nice shot, Airi!
We got the first points!
That girl in the center seems like a different person both mentally and physically.
Just wait and see.
I should be able to push her away.
So fast!
Amazing, she's pushing a lead against Suzuridani!
The level of Keishin has improved overall.
Yeah.
Tomo!
Maho!
Thank ya!
Hina!
No way!
They're beating us!
I never thought we'd be losing... and they're just a puny, no-name team, too.
R-Rena...
You'll fall over if you treat them like that.
Especially the center and the small forward are better than before.
Their real power is showing.
If we study how they move in the second quarter,
the third quarter will be a success.
I'm sure you'll be able to gain the lead.
Do your best!
Yes!
You don't really need to try hard. We're winning since I'm on the team.
Good job, everyone.
It's amazing that you're in the lead! You've made a great start!
How's it feel to fight?
It's intense.
Attacking is paying off in no time.
Oh~, everyone is moving so fast!
The Chibi Ribbon is strong, after all.
I think we still haven't seen their full potential.
Most of their energy is most likely still stored up.
Treasure this point difference and bring it over to the third quarter.
Make sure to do that, fifth graders.
Bring it over? No way!
We're gonna make the gap even bigger!
We won't lose, even if Ashihara Rena comes on the field.
We'll do our best.
We'll enjoy it with all our might.
Work hard.
You don't need to tell me that.
Fight on!
I'll put what you taught me into practice, Master.
Don't go overboard.
Of course not!
I'm looking forward to seeing what you two will do.
Look forward to it!
The center must support everyone.
Got it.
Let's see. Maybe I should test the girls in despair first?
I'm going in!
Masami!
I'll make you apologize for what you did at the gourmet convention.
Haven't I told you it wasn't my fault?
I wouldn't apologize anyway since I'm not gonna lose.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Here I come!
Is she seriously going to use that?
Heh, that's not gonna work.
I'll start with the magical vanishing ball.
Do you get it now? You're not not even close to my level.
It does seem that way.
Don't we need to hurry up?
Don't say that!
The time is running out!
We have to hurry!
Oh~, everyone should talk one after another.
Let's try it.
Hey!
Just once.
You're all so old.
What makes you think so, Mimi?
Anyway, let's all do our best!
Yeah!