When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Looks like it'll be a hot day.
Milady, good morning.
Yup. And I'm off to school.
Yes. Then allow me to accompany you.
What?!
What's gotten into you, Milady?
How are you possibly up so early on your own?
And you're actively going to school?
Rather than that, summer vacation starts today.
Just kidding.
Did I surprise you?
That was a joke.
A joke?
Oh, I see.
It's summer vacation! I can't possibly waste time in bed!
I'll play MMOs and watch anime and draw manga and fool around to my heart's content!
I think you do those even on school days.
But to be so exuberant about it, you must be really happy.
I'll be able to spend the entire day with Hayate from now on.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
I thought I had just started my school life, and it's summer vacation already?
Other than saying hello to classmates and the fight in the Kendo Club, did I do anything else?
I love summer vacation!
I can drink all the booze I want!
Plus, I can do this all I want, too!
Doing nothing is the ultimate luxury!
Katsura-chan.
Let's play.
What are you guys? Grade school kids from the 1950's?
We figured you'd be bored, so we came to invite you out.
I'm sorry, but I'm busy right now.
Let's go catch beetles.
How about wandering through the forests around Mt. Fuji?
Hey, what's this about? Let go of me!
Um, Maria-san. Do you have
an ultimate attack or anything like that?
Um, what is this out of the blue?
Well, I met those who I take to be
professional butlers at Hakuou Academy,
but according to them, professional butlers are to have an ultimate attack or two.
I see.
So I'm thinking of learning one, too.
I see why now.
But why do you ask me?
"Why?"
This is just my guess, but...
...you look like you can use the art of assassination.
I can't.
But my instincts tell me-
Please trash such useless instincts right now.
What? You can use it, can't you?
Nagi... Even you...
I thought you could at least use Gotenshou Bakushinken.
Right?
Yes.
Please. Do not make me become a fighter with manic skills.
Besides, ultimate attacks aren't easy to learn.
I agree, but since it's summer vacation, I'd like to master one.
It'd be nice if there was a book that I could learn one from.
A book, you say?
As expected from the Sanzenin's book vault.
It's an amazing collection.
That's why cleaning this place is real work.
But books are nice.
Indulging in reading surrounded by books makes you feel intelligent.
I see. Well said, Milady.
And I guess these are the shelves reserved for Milady.
How did you know?
Well...
This place is filled with manga.
H-Hey, I read books other than manga, too!
Of course, I know.
I see so many walkthroughs for games, too.
Listen!
Reading books does make you feel intelligent, doesn't it?
Stop making fun of me!
I can't find it.
I can't understand why you're so attached to ultimate attacks.
I can understand it.
I'm sure he's trying to show his good side for me.
With my elegant attack, I will protect you, Milady.
You're amazing, Hayate.
What is the matter?
N-Nothing.
All right, Hayate, I'll help you, too.
I'll search for the book that might help you
come up with an ultimate attack with you.
Thank you very much, Milady.
Seriously... Ultimate attacks?
It's not like there's a correspondence course for karate.
You can't possibly find a book that'll teach you one.
You just might find one.
Ultimate Attacks 4 Dummies! Includes colored charts!
Who knew such a useful book slept here?
Really.
But what's this "Sanzenin Secret Techniques"?
Oh, I remember Himegami-kun using it.
Himegami-san?
Um, I hear his name on occasion, but...
Oh, we haven't told you about him?
He was Nagi's butler before you came.
Well, a lot happened and he left us.
I see. And that Himegami-san also had an ultimate attack.
Which means, could Klaus-san possibly have one, too?
Are you interested in my ultimate attack?
No, not right now.
Stop fooling around and get back to work.
Anyway, there's nothing you can't do that other butlers can.
Milady!
Hayate, let's begin the training!
Yes, Master!
I'll do my best!
Don't call me "Master"!
Call me "Undefeated in the Four Directions and the Center"!
That's a little too long...
Silence.
Follow me.
Are you all right?
I scratched my knee a little.
What an unreliable "Undefeated in the
Four Directions and the Center" legend.
It's really hot.
Milady, wouldn't it be better for you to stay inside in a cool room?
No, this is for your ultimate attack's sake!
Let's get this started.
Yes, please begin.
We'll start with the basics.
Yes.
Case 1.
Ultimate attacks for those who were once burned by their enemies.
Let's see...
Um, isn't there an ultimate attack that can be used before being burned by the enemy?
I don't see anything like that.
I don't think I can handle such over-the-top moves right off the bat.
Why don't you give it a try, Tama?
First, you must have a body that won't even burn in fire, like a ruler of the millennium.
The prerequisite is wrong.
But if you can't do this, you can't do Case 2, ultimate attacks when pushed off a cliff.
Like I said, let's do something before I'm pushed off.
Then...
What's wrong, Milady?
N-N-N-Nothing.
It's nothing.
I-I never imagined such a skill would be in here.
But...
...I'd love to master this!
So master it.
Milady?
W-W-What?
I want to read it through to see if there's anything useful written in it, so may I borrow that book?
No! I refuse! I reject!
W-Why?
It's too early for you.
What?
I want to see it.
Anyway, when I say I can't show it to you, I can't show it to you!
Milady, it's dangerous that way!
Milady!
So, how do we become lovey-dovey?
Are you a moron?!
The prerequisite is wrong!
Milady! In front of you! In front!
If I could do something this embarrassing-
Milady!
Hayate.
Hey, Hayate. Are you alive?
Are you all right, Milady?
Yeah, I'm...
Thank goodness.
I'm glad I was able to save you.
Right, even without relying on
an ultimate move, Hayate and I are...
Thank you.
Hey, this book is almost entirely useless, but there are
some moves that use chi and several more practical ones, too.
Really?
Yeah. With effort, you should be able to master these.
Yes.
All right, I'll master an ultimate move over the summer!
Yup.
I must work hard for Hinagiku-san's sake, too.
Yup, you're right, for Hinagiku's sake, too-
Wait.
For whose sake did you say?
Hinagiku-san has been helping me a lot, so...
And I promised her I'd show it to her when I master an ultimate attack.
Promised?
I see...
No, the skill book!
Why did you do such a thing, Milady?
Ha-Ha-Hayate...
Hayate, you jerk!
Maria-san.
Oh my! What's wrong?
Would you teach me the ultimate move to calm Milady down?
That'll require a lot of training.
It'll be a while before Hayate learns an ultimate move.
Therefore, please keep watching Hayate no Gotoku!
Suika no tane. Pe!
Suika no tane. Pe! = Watermelon seeds. *Spit*!
Pero-san faito!
Pero-san faito! = Pero-san, fight!
What?
Milady ran out of the house?
Yes. The SPs are after her,
so there's nothing to worry so much about, but...
But I'm still worried.
Things she does are always spur of the moment; I can't always tell what their reasons are.
I wonder what happened to her.
I am sure the reason is you, Hayate-kun.
Okay, as her butler, I must chase her and discover the reason.
Damn it, Hayate.
What's this "for Hinagiku's sake" about?
Does he care about Hinagiku more than me?
What if...
What if Hayate comes to like Hinagiku more than me?
No, you can't. You mustn't, Hayate-kun.
You already have Nagi.
What are you saying, Hinagiku-san?
You're the only person I can think of as my destined one.
Hayate-kun...
Hinagiku-san...
Screw you! Stupid, Hayate!
What's so good about Hinagiku?
Hinagiku's only a little cute.
She's kind-hearted and smart.
Plus she's athletic and everyone trusts her.
Even I aspire to be like her a little.
Hmm.
Our breasts are about the same size.
What did you say?!
And my grades are no worse than hers!
Even though the summer break's started, I don't feel cheerful at all.
I wonder what Hayate-kun's doing now.
Rather than that...
Why was Hayate-kun at such a gorgeous mansion?
And...
Who was that girl?
I have so many things I want to talk to and ask Hayate-kun about when I meet him.
Seriously!
Let's just go home and go to bed.
Hey.
Besides, Hayate is the one to be blamed for everything!
You!
Hey, you're the burglar hamster from sometime ago.
Who are you calling a burglar hamster?
Then a trespassing hamster.
Lockpicking hamster.
Could you at least take the "hamster" off?
Anyways, it's the fated reunion.
I finally caught up, but...
Um...
Why is Milady with Nishizawa-san?
First of all, is there a meaning to this camouflage?
I thought it'd be better to have one rather than not.
By the way, Hayate-kun, I wanted to ask earlier,
but what is your relationship with that Nishizawa-san?
Ah, well...
I love you, Hayate-kun!
W-We're friends.
She was my classmate at my old school.
I see.
I wonder what they could be talking about.
I bet it is about you.
What? You're the owner of that mansion,
and you took in Hayate-kun when he was lost in the streets,
and now he's employed as your butler and living under the same roof?!
Yeah, you got a problem with that?
I'm so enviou-
No, I mean, what a sense of defeat.
You're so mean, God.
This is so unfair.
See ya, Hamster.
Don't ever come near our property.
Hold on!
If I step away now, I'll only be a miserable loser.
And my pride won't allow that.
Fight me!
A face off between us with Hayate-kun as the prize!
Sure. I'm conveniently in a bad mood.
I'll send you home.
What is this place?
It's a karaoke box, obviously.
You've never been to one?
So this is?
It's my first time coming to a strange place like this.
But, wow, this place is smaller than our bathroom.
What?
If you stay in a dark, small room like this for hours,
even if you're not the son of the Mendou family, you'll become nyctophobic and claustrophobic.
Anyway, let's order our drinks and start the fight.
What do you want for your drink?
I don't mind paying if it's only one.
Totally unimpressive.
Then Shiun green tea and Périgord foie gras terrine.
I-I don't think they have those here.
I don't really get it, but looks like they're going to karaoke.
What should we do, Maria-san?
Maria-san?
I-I-I'm sorry.
I rented this box for now, so let's go in.
Yes.
But why did Nishizawa-san bring Milady here?
Hayate-kun, Hayate-kun!
Yes?
Wh-What is this device for?
You punch the number in to request a song.
So that's how this works.
Wow, you can even adjust the pitch.
You can search using this book, too?
Wow, it's so thick.
Um, since we're here, would you like to sing?
What are you saying, Hayate-kun?
I can't. I do not know any pop songs.
Besides, I'm worried about Nagi.
Don't worry. We can see their room from here.
And I'd like to hear you sing, too.
But...
Then if you sing first, I guess I'll try one song.
Okay, then I'll take the first song.
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku.
Yay!
So what's the score?
Tada!
35%?
Why?
Obviously, it's because you missed so many notes.
Then, you're up next.
Sure.
A girl who's come to karaoke for the first time ever can't possibly sing well.
I sang that one as a warm up,
but if I sing seriously, I'll win for sure.
Watch me, Hayate-kun. I'll save you with my song.
Hayaku koi!
Hurry and come here!
Chotto okotteruzo
I'm a little mad
What?
Hayaku koi!
Hurry and come here!
Mahha kousoku dazo?
Mach high speed, you here?
What is this bright radiance coming out of her?
Hikikomori nichiyoubi.
Hikikomori Sunday.
She looks like Tsukishima ***-chan to me.
Suguni tone konakucha
You have to come running to me
Forget that, she's really good!
Dame~
Or else it's a no-no!
Tonikaku dame dame.
It's a no-no.
Obviously.
It's because she's had special lessons from when she was little,
Dame~
No-no~
and her courses included voice and song training by professionals.
Hayaku konai kana?
Will he be here soon?
You may have forgotten, but Nagi is a hyper-rich girl.
Even if this may be her first karaoke experience, she won't lose to an average high school girl.
Looks like the match's settled.
No! The match's only begun!
Songs require love!
I won't lose!
Fine, then I'll floor you!
On to next round!
The two's battle heated up.
Bring it on!
The battle lasted late into the night, and finally...
Singing a lot made me feel better.
I ended up losing every song.
Hey, do you want to use my card to pay?
Forget it! I'll pay this much!
I don't want to be in debt to my rival.
Rival?
Isn't rival a word used when your levels are close to equal?
We've come to pick you up, Milady.
Ah, thanks. How did you know I was here?
We received a call from your butler.
From Hayate?
I see.
See you, Hamster.
Hold on!
Next time, we'll fight with something else, do you hear?
Come anytime you want.
I'll shut you down again.
All right, let's go home and play some games with Hayate.
The summer vacation has only begun.
Meanwhile, the maid and butler were...
Usotsuite mo omitooshi desu.
I can see through all your lies.
Watashino me ha fushiana jyanai
My eyes aren't blind.
Maria-san, how about we call it a night?
...still singing.
Romansu futarini-
Romance come to the two-
The end of the first day of summer vacation.
What should we do tomorrow?
You guys aren't planning to stay here the entire summer, are you?
They enjoyed their first day, too.
By the way,
Book report and English essay, complete.
there is approximately one diligent student.
Kids watching this, plan ahead in regards your homework.
Next week, we'll fight against height limits.
Isumi's...
Butler Network!
Hello, I'm Saginomiya Isumi.
Um, I couldn't make it in time for the actual show,
but I was put in this section.
Um... What am I supposed to talk about?
What? Talk about this song?
Um... This song is...
Hey, Isumi. If you talk so slowly, you'll run out of time.
Nagi-
Ah-
Butler uniforms aren't the best on you, after all.
What? Are you cross-dressing me again?
No, I don't think those clothes are suitable for going to the amusement park.
Amusement park?
With this new body,
the debt-ridden butler is no longer my enemy!
You robot there! What company's spy are you?
Makimura-san, even you?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Even Peter-san Has Had Enough.
Why does that robot look familiar?
The power of justice calls the storm!