When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
What? Hayate's left the residence?!
We will need to find a
replacement immediately.
Hey!
Mr. Klaus.
He has insisted on quitting himself.
It would be another story if
he had discussed it with us.
M-Maria, what should I do?!
Hayate's really gone and done it!
All because I was so awkward with him...
Nagi...
Hayate, where in the world
have you disappeared to?
Whosoever commands the
butlers, commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Part two of the advance final
episode! Startin' at last!
Um, is this the only screen time we get?
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
SIGN: Hurray for the Butler-in-Debt,
Friend to Good Children!
Merry Christmas!
Sis, don't tell me you've been drinking
all this time since Christmas Eve?
Yes!
White Christmas, my ass!
In that case, gosh darn it,
I'm gonna turn totally red!
Summer Beer
Beware of Fire
Hina!
I may not look it,
but I've received a couple thousand
Open Heart pendants, you know!
Drivers and treaters and Loch Ness Monsters!
Just lemme stay a college student!
Even though it's been a long time
since I've been a college student.
I'm a teacher, you know! Ahem!
What are you? From the Bubble Generation?
If you're lonely, you
could've just come home.
Me? Lonely?
S-Sis?!
To Sis
Merry Christmas
Hina
A white Christmas, huh?
Huh? Hayate?
What are you doing here?
N-Nothing. I just came for something
I forgot in our classroom.
But you seem to be empty-handed.
You are not accepting your
defeat graciously, Ayasaki.
I imagine you were visiting the
classroom that holds all your memories
and bidding your final farewell to Sanzenin.
Is that about right?
Farewell?
Have you found your resolve?
I will give the Superintendent
my answer in person.
What's going on?
What in the world is the
Superintendent up to?
Well, that is...
A rumor has been circulating in the
butler community since around autumn.
Sion!
It went like this: whoever defeats
the butler Hayate Ayasaki
will receive the vast Sanzenin inheritance.
What?
I thought it was just a wild rumor,
but it seems it was not altogether false.
Hey, Hayate!
Just show it to me!
Wait! That's...
Looks like you had a terrible Christmas...
Yes, well...
Could this be...?
This is blackmail!
Um, Hinagiku...
You make it sound so ugly.
Hand over the original file to this photo!
Taking advantage of
someone's weakness is low!
Oh-ho.
Please stop. Hinagiku has
nothing to do with this.
What are you saying, Hayate?!
Now, how about you hurry
up and take me to her?
Wait, Hayate!
Please don't breathe a
word of this to the Miss.
Hayate!
But this is...
You have done well to come, Ayasaki.
Have you found your resolve
to become one of my subjects?
If I become your butler,
you'll relinquish your claim
on the Sanzenin inheritance?
Yes, I will promise you that.
But why? You stole my butler powers from me.
You will be gaining even greater
butler powers than you had before.
And you will be reborn into a perfect butler,
who swears his devotion to me, body and soul.
Hayate...
Yes, this is the Sanzenin residence.
Oh, Hinagiku. What? Hayate is...
Hello? It's me!
What?!
He told me to keep it a secret,
but I just couldn't let it go.
And it seemed like he was being blackmailed.
Something to do with the
Sanzenin inheritance.
Hayate did this to protect
me and the Sanzenin family...
Nagi...
Damn that Hayate! Trying to
handle this all by himself!
A butler and his mistress are as one!
We must stand together, no matter
what difficulties or crises we face!
Then, as Hayate's mistress, there
is only one thing for you to do.
Yes!
Hold down the fort in my absence, Maria!
Yes, ma'am.
Sion, bring the item.
What?
Yes, Mistress Kuzuha.
Th-That's...!
A butler treasure from ancient times.
Huh?
Wh-What could this butler
treasure possibly be?!
To be continued in the second half!
Ramipasu, ramipasu, rerererere!
(Ramipasu, ramipasu, rerererere!)
Rerere and re, how are you doing?!
(Rerere no re, genki desu ka?!)
I obtained this treasure when
I was exploring the Amazons.
Th-The Amazons?
I originally went there to obtain
the legendary vanilla beans.
The cave we accidentally
discovered were the ruins
of an ancient butler super-civilization,
which had fallen eons ago.
Uh, um, what in the world is this
ancient butler super-civilization?
However, we unflinchingly proceeded
deeper and deeper inside.
Oh, she ignored me.
At the back of the cave was the giant
serpent Jörmungandr, Jör for short.
And there, he was protecting
the ancient treasure.
We, too, won his trust and became
guardians of the treasure,
and thus...
I gained the power to
wield White Serpent Magic!
I gained the power to become
a handsome young man!
Jör granted these powers to us!
So that we might protect
the treasure with him!
D-Doesn't that mean they're
being used by the serpent?
Oh, they really are being controlled...
Hayate Ayasaki, you should be honored!
I will allow you to also see
the treasure of the ancient
butler super-civilization!
This ancient butler uniform
still lies slumbering.
Sion and I have tried it with
numerous butlers thus far,
but no matter how superior
these butlers were,
they were rebuffed by the garment
and could not even don it.
Uh, but wait, that's not a butler's uniform!
However, you should be able to
don this garment, without fail.
Now, become a butler who
serves us body and soul!
But that's not a butler's...!
Incidentally, once you don this garment,
you will never be able to take it off again.
Furthermore, if you should
be rebuffed by the garment,
there will be a retaliatory curse
that turns you into a white serpent.
What?!
And now, we will conduct the ceremony.
Elohim essaim, elohim essaim,
I beseech you to indulge this fan girl.
Sacred ancient garment, awaken now!
The most powerful butler uniform
is finally about to awaken!
Miss!
That's...!
Hayate must be there!
Yes, ma'am!
There she is!
Hey! Over here!
So it's begun.
Hayate, are you all right?! We've come to...
Huh?!
Is it sweet, Mistress?
Yes, truly exceptional.
I'm so happy, meow.
Nice.
H-Hayate! Hey! What happened to you...?
Oh, my! We have guests!
I will prepare the tea right away.
H-Hayate, you don't recognize me...?
He is my butler now, body and soul.
Behold that design!
Truly, the legacy of an
ancient super-civilization.
Is he still called a butler even
when he's dressed like that?
A-Anyway, I'm taking Hayate back with me!
Hey, Hayate!
Let's start by getting that thing off him!
R-Right.
Do not interfere.
This snack time is a 30,000 year
old desire of mine, slither.
I see. Though this seems
a bit too simplistic.
That's right!
This serpent is controlling Hayate
and the Superintendent, slither!
H-Hey, move aside!
Stand in my way and I'll...!
Hayate Ayasaki has no need
of two mistresses, slither!
P-Protect the Miss!
Who are you, slither?!
Himegami?!
My name is Princess God.
Born in darkness, living in darkness...
Well, whatever.
I'll leave that guy to you!
H-Hey, Hayate! Now's your chance!
Hurry up and get that weird outfit...
Yes?
Since it's come to this, even
if I have to use force...
Wh-What are you doing?!
Just get that outfit off him, Nagi!
Right!
Please stop!
They seem to be having fun.
But it's too soon.
That garment has yet to
achieve its true awakening...
What are you plotting?
Hinagiku! Himegami!
Nagi!
Hayate is my butler!
I will let no one have him!
I don't need the mansion...
I don't need my fortune...
Hayate,
if you'll just be there for
me, that's all I care about!
Even if you've lost your butler powers.
So...
So, please! Wake up, Hayate!
Hayate, you...
Miss, I am so very sorry! I...
I...!
Hayate...
You'll be punished for this later.
Yes, Miss!
Hayate!
It's begun.
Stab!
Th-The impudence!
I'm your opponent!
H-How gallant, slither.
H-Hayate!
Come on! Run!
Not to worry, Miss.
But right now, your butler powers are...
I'll be fine. Even without such powers,
as long as I have you to believe in me,
I am...
I am still a butler!
Hayate!
Wh-What just happened?
"If one wishes to awaken
the sacred butler uniform,
"he must..."
Um, how do you read this?
Let me see that!
Let's see...
"...he must temporarily
lose his butler powers."
"The treasure exists to test whether
he possesses a true butler's soul
"and lies slumbering in
the guise of a maiden."
"However, when he is truly recognized,
the treasure will awaken"
"and it will surely reveal its
rightful form before his very eyes."
S-So that's how it works.
I would love to have this
strategy guide, slither.
There are too many mysteries to begin with
that you need a strategy
guide to figure out, slither!
So? Where did you buy this book?
On Yahoo! Auction.
Ah! This time, for sure!
This time for sure, the most powerful
butler uniform will awaken!
Uh, um, I'm Hayate Ayasaki,
a butler who protects the
Sanzenin family and Miss Nagi.
Yes.
So this is the legendary butler uniform!
Talk about tasteless.
Th-This is what I spent 30,000 years on?
Ah! You're sparkling!
So cool! You look super cool, Hayate!
Thank you very much, Miss.
Hey! Are you people blind?!
Infernal thing!
I will destroy that stupid item, slither!
I will be free, slither!
H-Hayate!
Come to me now!
The lethal butler technique
that's mine and mine alone!
Here I go!
Hayate.
Miss.
It's dangerous in here! Get outside!
Th-The academy's precious facility...
Himegami!
Thanks to you, I have this awakened
item in my possession now.
Himegami...
Please take good care of Nagi.
Don't tell me you used Hayate
just for that thing?!
What?!
I didn't want to wear it
myself to undo the curse.
What the hell is that glittery
outfit anyway?! Well, Himegami?!
I am not Himegami. I am Princess God.
In time, I will save this world...
Enough!
Just three more pieces and the legendary
God Butler Dragon will be...
Sheesh! What's with him?!
But if it weren't for Himegami, I
may have stayed like that forever.
Well, maybe, but...
Wh-Where am I?
What in the world have I
been doing all this time?
M-Mistress Kuzuha! Thank goodness!
It looks like those two are
free of the curse as well.
Which means...
Peace has returned to Hakuou Academy now.
Sion, your smaller form
is fine in its own way.
Oh, Mistress Kuzuha.
Uh, but they don't seem to
be all that different...
Oh, that reminds me! What about
the original file to that photo?
Oh! It's in here!
The memory card's probably
in a million pieces, too!
Mistress Kuzuha!
I see. Then please be
careful on your way home.
I will be waiting for you, Nagi.
Everyone should be arriving about now.
Have a good Christmas, you two.
Huh? I didn't know you were
still at school, Hina.
Wait... Whoa! The hell is this?!
Well, a lot happened...
Never mind that. What are you
doing out here at this hour, Sis?
Huh? Oh, I was just going
to buy some beer snacks.
I figured I'd go for a fresh round of drinks.
Want me to keep you company?
Oh, but I'll be having juice, naturally.
Sure!
Thank you very much, Miss.
Nah, don't mention it...
S-Say, Hayate...
Don't let it bother you so much. I also...
Th-This is bad.
Now that I'm face-to-face with him,
I feel self-conscious all over again.
But this is Christmas, after all...
We're going to take a little detour.
What?
Christmas Cakes
M-Merry Christmas! Everyone,
please buy a cake!
Wait a minute.
Could it be that if these don't
sell, I'll get to keep them all?
Um, Miss, what are we doing here?
You remember this, right?
Yes, of course.
In this past year, I've
grown a great deal, too.
Behold! I can even buy this
"warm" thing myself now!
Hayate, this is for you!
What?
Just accept it!
See? We were unable to obtain
this "warmth" that time,
but here it is now, in our hands.
This is the year that you
and I have spent together.
Thank you for all the "warm" days.
Miss...
Merry Christmas, Hayate.
A Merry Christmas to you, Miss.
Miss, what is the matter?
Could it be that you've grown sleepy already?
Ouch!
What was that for, Miss?!
I swear! You are just so...!
P-Please wait, Miss!
Nagi and my dear Hayate certainly
are taking a long time.
Seriously. After we prepared this
private gatherin' for 'em, too.
Let's just dig in already.
Oh, no, you don't, Young Sir.
Ladies and gentlemen watching
"Hayate the Combat Butler",
thank you for your support thus far.
Starting next time, we will
also have a fresh look
and we will bring you the 4th half-season
of "Hayate the Combat Butler".
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Report
Butler Report!
I'm Nagi Sanzenin, and my
dream is being creative!
I'm Hayate Ayasaki.
We've arrived at the final episode of
the Hayate the Combat Butler anime!
Thank you all for your support! Please
look forward to our next project!
Miss, the show isn't over yet!
It's just like a certain hermit once said,
"We're gonna keep going a little longer."
Oh, is that true? How annoying.
Starting next time, defying all expectations,
Hayate the Combat Butler enters it's next cour!
I'm going to keep working hard to be
a first-rate butler for you, miss!
O-oh! Well, I'm counting on you, Hayate.
Haiyaya!
Preview
Hayate!
What's the matter, miss?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
I'd like to see the first sunrise of the new
year at a place with a pretty view of the sea.
Just the two of us!
I'm not sure I see the point.
It's going to be really cold out.
Shut up, stupid!
Stop your whining and get ready!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
New Year's Food is Good,
But Have Some Hayate, Too
"New Year's Food is Good,
But Have Some Hayate, Too"
Did you know? In Vietnam,
it's supposed to be good luck
to eat watermelon on New
Year's! And in Hong Kong,
it's traditional to give New
Years gifts to adults, too!