Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Thanks for treating us today, Nee-san.
Don't mention it!
Anytime!
It was really good.
Wasn't it?
Doesn't it just make you happy when the egg tastes that good?
Eh!?
Gas prices are up two yen from yesterday.
I should've filled up the tank.
Why is it that even the most generous people...
...complain about a single yen difference when it comes to gasoline?
There Over Here
Speaking of which,
that book I loaned to you a while back.
I heard they're making a game out of it.
Obviously I'm not gonna buy it, though.
You're so behind, Kagami.
I pre-ordered the limited edition the moment the news broke.
I also bought the DVD box set for the anime and other related goods.
Whoa.
You're into it more than I am.
It's pretty common for someone to become more addicted than the person who recommended it.
That's how Yui-neesan bought her car.
Thanks to someone else's influence.
Her car!?
Yeah, I lent her a racing manga.
It surprised even me.
It's scary how much energy people can put into their hobbies.
Yesterday makes it three victories in a row, right?
Yeah, it's the start of a miracle!
If we keep winning like this,
the playoffs and Japan Series aren't out of the question!
What are they talking about?
I believe it's pro baseball.
Sensei likes that stuff.
All the way to the top!
Oh, speaking of baseball,
And besides, baseball is all about...
The famous poet, Masaoka Shiki, loved baseball so much.
He played as a catcher until the day he could no longer play due to his illness.
He changed his name to Noboru,
and wrote it using the characters for baseball, calling himself Noball.
Speaking of which,
the winners of the Major League are called the world champions, right?
Talking about the Japan Series reminded me.
Hm?
Yeah, that's right.
Even though it's only American teams.
They should beat our team first before they call themselves world champions, right?
She's quite pumped up, isn't she?
It smelled pretty bad.
That's true.
Oh, there you are!
Kagami!
Miyuki-san!
Oh, Konata.
Can you show me how to do these?
How rare,
you asking a question about schoolwork.
There are some pretty difficult questions in here, too.
Oh, that's because they're the questions from a quiz game at the arcade.
I'm not good with academics, after all.
There you go again...
Why don't you put more effort into studying?
You are a college applicant.
I might seem like that here,
but over there I'm considered a hero!
In that case,
why don't you just enroll in that academy of yours already?
Which is why I'm a little sleep deprived.
How long were you up doing it?
Miyuki-san, you always go to sleep around 11, right?
Yes.
That's pretty early.
Oh!
I get it now...
「Sleeping helps
you grow ☆」
Though looking at Miyuki-san reminded me,
despite the fact that you sleep a lot, you haven't grown all that much.
That's what Onee-chan told me.
And I'm so conscientious about the subject.
That night, around 9 o'clock
Excuse me for calling so late at night.
My name is Kobayakawa.
Is this the Iwasaki residence?
Ah, may I speak with Minami-chan?
She went to bed already?
Did she usually go to sleep this early?
Pittan.
La La moji-pittan!
You seem to be having fun singing.
Yeah, I can take care of that.
Yes, I'll let my father know.
Yes, right after the ground-blessing ceremony.
Yes, that's right.
Oh no, that's not true at all!
Please, there you go again.
I'm still underage, really.
You've got it all wrong!
It's not like that!
On that note...
Yes...
Yes.
You know, Kagami.
Hm?
They can't see the gestures on the other side of the phone.
I know that!
It just happens!
When I'm on the phone, I need to focus on the conversation,
so I have to put the controller down.
But then your hands just feel so empty.
Oh, I know what you mean!
So the other day, I took a roller and started cleaning up my floor.
I was just rolling away.
Stuff like that can actually get pretty addicting.
Like random doodles or menial chores.
But the thing is,
once you get off the phone, you don't want to do those tasks anymore.
It's depressing when you see that just the area around you is clean.
You could just finish the job.
My passion disappears when the call ends.
So you just leave it be?
That guy's pretty smelly, right?
Maybe it's okay once in a while, but...
Look!
**cky!
Poc**!
Oh yeah, I remember doing that...
Back in elementary school.
Geez...
What are you, a kid?
Oh, but.
Speaking of things we did as kids,
do you remember stirring your yogurt and going, "Bread Factory!"
Bread factory?
Eh?
Doesn't ring a bell?
No.
So...
What was that just now?
Bread factory?
Don't be shy and try explaining it to us.
Shut up!
You know the game I lent to you back during the first semester?
Eh?
Someone else wants to play it,
so do you think I could have it back?
Sure.
Is it for the squirt?
Yeah.
Which reminds me, I've lent quite a few to her.
I should get them back.
But you sure are amazing, Hiiragi.
About what?
Well,
I found some games the other day and I had no idea who they belonged to.
I'm impressed you can remember something like that.
Hey now.
And there are a few I've loaned to other people that I've forgotten about.
How careless can you get?
Now, now.
There's gotta be a Law of Equivalent Lending, you know?
It's a universal truth.
As if...
Yes, hello?
Oh, Hiiragi?
It's me, Misao.
Yes, what's u-
Dammit.
Not bad, Potemkin.
What, did something happen?
Oh, it's nothing.
Sorry about that.
So what did you want?
Oh yeah...
Ah, what was it again?
How should I know?
I'm sure it was something very important.
If it's important, don't forget it.
I was looking at the numbers for the Autumn Jumbo Lottery,
but I didn't win any.
I guess it isn't so easy to win these.
I submitted a lot of postcards, too,
but I didn't win any prizes from the drawings.
Is that so?
That's too bad.
When you lose so much,
you start to wonder if...
...the vendors or the editors are doing something fishy, don't you?
Konata!
You shouldn't be so suspicious of people like that!
Oh, I can't take it anymore.
I think I'll go to sleep for the night.
But before that, I need to use the restroom.
They say I talk too much,
but that doesn't matter!
I was sleepy earlier,
so why am I wide awake after saying such a stupid joke like that?
「Next day, dead of night」
I'm just no good at night.
I should just go to sleep while I'm dozing off.
Freezing!
I was really sleepy,
so why did I become wide awake when I got under the cold sheets?
「The day after that, dead of night」
It's no use.
It's warm tonight, so maybe I can fall asleep right away.
For some reason my feet are really warm, so I can't fall asleep.
Why is that?
Am I the only person like this?
It's certainly the season for yakimono!
You know, Kagami...
Yes, I know...
I know, so please don't remind me.
Want some?
Thank you very much.
But it'll make me fat.
So you said it anyway.
But I had no choice!
Once my eyes met with the old man's,
it'd have been rude not to buy one, you know?
You know what I mean?
"Oh, is she going to buy one?"
"Or is she just going to walk the other way?"
That look!
Oh, I totally know what you mean.
When your eyes meet at Comiket, it's hard to put the book back.
You keep on talking even when people have no idea what you're talking about, don't you?
Come on.
I'm talking about when you're standing in front of a circle's booth.
When you pick up a book in front of an artist.
Don't you feel bad leaving without buying it?
But you put it down anyway, right?
There have been a lot of light novels adapted into anime series recently.
That's true.
The novel I loaned you a while back,
has already had three anime adaptations!
And there should be a new volume coming out soon.
I watched the anime, but I haven't read the novels yet.
There are so many words, so I just get tired.
That again?
The games you always play have a lot more text than a novel.
That's what you would think, right?
It'd really help if they released them in a visual novel format.
Hey!
More importantly,
when is the fourth season coming out?
Um, what?
Is that supposed to be some kind of reference?
Yu-chan, what are you doing?
The lid keeps going on crooked.
Yeah, some people are like that.
I guess they're just clumsy.
It happens a lot.
Here.
It's those cute little flaws that make you similar to Miyuki-san.
Thanks.
You are amazing after all, Onee-chan.
What should I do, Onee-chan?
Now it won't open.
Ah, oops.
I closed it like I normally would.
You sure are a lot of trouble.
You can't open the bag?
Hand it to me.
Ah, Onee-chan.
Thanks!
Huh?
Maybe we should just tear it open along the notches?
No, I'll open it properly, so just wait a sec!
Fire!
It's okay.
Let's just tear it open along the notches or use scissors.
No, my pride won't let me!
It'll leave me feeling like I lost!
Onee-chan, is it a mosquito?
Mosquito?
Don't you get frustrated just knowing that there's one in your room?
Even though you haven't been bitten yet?
Once you know they're there,
you must take them down!
These are my hunters instincts!
I was just wondering...
Hm?
If a guy in our class confesses his love for me or Yu-chan,
does it make that guy a lolicon?
Well, they're in the same class year,
so technically it wouldn't.
But in this case, there would be an emphasis on your appearances.
Hypothetically,
if you were a 30-year-old who looked like a grade schooler,
then you could say that guy is into older women.
This is quite a complicated issue.
It's hard to come up with a strict interpretation.
You're definitely my dad.
If it were Kagami, she would just say, "Does it matter!?"
And end the conversation right there.
How about you, Dad?
Hm?
If you fell in love with Mom,
Mom
Daughter
and dote on a daughter like me,
doesn't it make you a lolicon?
Whoa, wait.
Hold it right there.
I think you're a bit mistaken.
I like normal girls, too, not just little ones.
So you should say I'm also a lolicon.
Though I suppose it depends on the character we're talking about.
Either way, you fail as a human being.
You know how you're so attached to me and follow me everywhere?
Would you still be like that if I was a boy?
Of course I would!
Okay, I think that's enough.
Aren't you glad I'm a girl?
I think the bath is almost ready.
Why don't you go ahead, Yu-chan?
Okay.
Well then, excuse me.
So you had to chase her away to keep your image.
Hey, Dad.
About Mom...
She was really short,
and was your childhood friend.
Doesn't she seem like a character out of a gal-game?
Right?
Kanata was always adorable since she was little.
I can see why you fell for her,
but why did she marry you?
I was like, "Because you wouldn't look at me,
I became this gal-game loving man!"
And then she just accepted.
You're despicable.
But it's the truth.
Isn't that coercion!?
No, no,
of course that wasn't the only reason.
And when you were born, Konata, she was really happy...
"Oh."
"I wonder if she got this mole from you, Sou-kun?"
"Well, she certainly has your eyes, Kanata."
"No matter how you look at her, you can definitely tell she's our child."
"I want her to grow up taking the good traits from both of us."
"I hope she doesn't inherit my height...
...or your personality."
"That was pretty harsh."
But why did you ask about Kanata all of a sudden?
Well, I don't really know much about Mom.
Konata.
Are you lonely without Mom around?
Not really.
You create enough excitement for two people.
And we have Yu-chan here now.
I see...
Kanata,
Konata's grown up to be a good girl.
A little otaku
Though maybe not quite as normal as you would have wanted.
Hey, Konata.
I ask of you,
please don't die before me, okay?
For now, I have no intention to do so.
That's good.
Kanata passed away young,
but until the very end, she smiled and said she was happy.
Though it's pretty hard for those left behind,
I hope I can be happy like that at the end, too.
Smiling?
So how do you want to die?
Let's see...
Maybe from a moé overdose?
Dad, you're not gonna have a proper death are you?
Oh, yeah.
I bought a digital camera for work today...
It's been a while since I've visited this place.
You're so annoying!
C'mon, just one more picture!
I wonder what those two are doing right now.
Okay?
I was in the middle of a game!
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, say cheese!
Come on, Dad!
All right, one more!
Haven't you had enough?
And Dad, you're way too close.
You're being really cold, Konata.
I just want to take some pictures to commemorate my new camera.
Wasn't it supposed to be for work?
Now, don't be so stiff.
Sou-kun hasn't changed.
One more picture!
Whatever.
That's right, you never did...
You're so persistent.
...pay much attention to other people's circumstances.
Take that!
That hurts, Konata!
You really haven't changed at all.
But you know.
You feel more and more like Kanata when I hold you.
It makes my heart race.
What!?
Don't just blurt out such dangerous comments!
I can see what Mom had to put up with...
What was that?
Indeed.
Your dad may be like that,
but don't just turn to bad behavior.
Oh yeah, Konata.
When you clear that game,
teach me how to play it, too, okay?
Sure.
That one's actually pretty difficult.
But,
I think I made a wrong selection,
they play games together as a family,
Somewhere along the way.
so I guess they're doing well.
I'm having a hard time getting to the H-scene with the character I want.
Wait, what?
What the heck are you letting our daughter play?
Geez.
Is this really okay?
Aren't you teaching her the wrong thing,
Sou-kun?
Hey.
Why did Mom choose you, Dad?
Because you're just an old perverted, lolicon, otaku.
Who would go for that?
That's a bit harsh.
You sure don't go easy on your old man, do you?
That's for sure.
Let's see how I should put this,
Honestly,
Kanata had a pretty good intuition.
you were always like this.
Sometimes I almost forget...
Maybe it was fate.
Why I chose...
Even though I failed as a human being.
To spend the rest of my life with this man.
There was one thing I was absolutely sure about.
One thing that you were absolutely sure about?
What was that?
Just that I...
...loved Kanata more than anyone else in this world.
That was it.
I was no match after all.
Results for the
New Writer Award
No recipients
He accepted my good traits and my bad ones.
And he was willing to show me...
...his good traits as well as his bad ones.
The place where I can feel most at ease...
The place that could make me feel the most at ease...
Like that?
Okay!
That's enough reminiscing!
Shall we take another one?
We'll take more with Yu-chan later, okay?
The fact that I can no longer be there,
That's enough.
And you said only one more last time.
is a little painful.
You bought this for your own hobby, didn't you?
Geez.
What are you talking about?
I'm just testing it out before I start using it for work.
But...
Man...
Just like how the two of them exist within me...
If I can live on inside of them,
I'll continue to watch over them.
There.
Here we go!
May the ones who brought me so much joy...
...be blessed with happiness.
Cheese!
I wonder if they'll be surprised?
D-Dad!
This picture...!
There's a person's shadow in the back.
A real ghost picture...
Eh?
W-What?
The bath's ready now.
Yu-
Yu-Yu-Yu-Yu-chan!
W-Wait!
L-Look at this!
What is it?
What's the matter?
Delete it!
We have to delete it!
Or we'll be cursed!
W-Wait, don't erase it!
Wait!
Erasing it may not be enough, don't we have to burn it, too?
Don't erase it!
Now that I've talked with her a bit,
I have a different impression of her.
But I still think Mina-rin is a little scary.
But she's really nice!
Oh, she's back.
Minami-chan.
Welcome back!
I'm home.
Those two sure are close.
You were in charge of the classroom chores today, right?
Was Sensei still in the faculty office?
This would be like,
"Yutaka, your tie is crooked."
"O-Onee-sama!"
I mustn't!
I can't look at my friends like this!
Even if it's been building up inside me...
Start!
So did you find them?
What, you can't find them anywhere?
And you can't find their manager either?
They must've ran.
They were gonna get fired, anyway.
Um...
Besides,
I had a bad feeling about this show from the start!
The camera's rolling...
You know?
In fact,
I actually refused in the beginning.
But it was all that politics crap.
Grown-up issues and whatever.
Um...
We're rolling!
Huh?
What's rolling?
Me? You?
Or the Earth?
No, that's not what I meant.
Then what?
I'm saying that the camera is rolling!
You idiot!
Turn it off!
Isono!
What is it, Nakajima?
Now, please listen to me!
This time...
This time, it's the medley version!
Sign: 1. Love Legend of Minoru/2. Forgot My Something/3. Sunny Sunshiny Happy/4. How a Man Should Live/5. Take it! Sailor Uniform/6. The Dentistman Song/7. My Dear Santa Monica
One, two, three, four!
Mi-Miracle...
For-For-For-Forgot my something...
One clear, sunshiny day...
Take it! For I'll...
I am...
Santa Mo...
Mi-Miracle Minorun-run!
For-For-For-
One clear, sunshiny...
Take it! For...
Shikaider!
Santa Moni...
For-For-For-Forgot my something.
I forgot my something.
That thing I left behind...
One clear, sunshiny day...
Take it! For I'll be...
I am Shikaider!
Santa Moni...
For I am Shikaider!
For-For-For-For-For-For!
Minorun-run!
For I am Shikaider!
You didn't change when I blew the whistle!
You kept ending on Shikaider.
Yep.
Why?
Just switch.
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Soujirou here.
Kanata here.
Then, Sou-kun,
I'll be heading off now.
You're leaving?
Yes...
Take me with you.
I don't know how to separate my spirit from my body yet,
but I'm sure I can learn!
Sou-kun, you're talking about manga or anime again, aren't you?
Then, see you later.
Ah, Kanata!
Next time: "A Fine Line"
「 A Fine Line 」
Sou-kun!
I can't fly with all the turbulence!
Hey now...