Before the tan from the
summer training camp fades away...
...another sales exhibition.
Where the heck do you have a tan?
How was the new one?
Yeah, it was fun making it!
Not whether you enjoyed it or not.
I meant the sales.
Ah, oh!
Of course it will sell!
It'll most likely sell double the usual!
Meaning 10 copies...
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
Ikebukuro
Brother, cheer up!
I'm sure something
can be done about it!
But that was an accident.
You're showing remorse, so if you
show them sincerity, they'll forgive you.
Sensei and the editor-in-chief
overlooked it for me.
Look...
But, sensei is already
busy with another job...
...so he doesn't have
time to redo it for us.
I could have put it in a plastic case
and so many other things too...
There are millions of fans all over the
country that are looking forward to it.
And because of me, that
popular manga is not in print.
Everything is my fault...
But there isn't a night
that doesn't come to an end.
If winter passes, spring comes.
When it rains, the land hardens!
I'm sorry! That didn't happen!
The rain thing didn't happen!
But before that, I need to hurry
and look for a replacement artist.
Meaning an artist to fill in?
Yeah, but finding one
on such short notice...
I have someone in mind!
11th Edition
Najimi's going to fly.
Thank you very much!
Yes, I was able to sell another copy!
I will too soon!
Even though I say that...
Today's book is the revised version
of the ocean training camp.
So to be honest,
it's still a little rough.
I'm in the same boat as you!
More like, why don't
you feel more resentment?
No, I am resenting!
Lies!
You aren't resenting at all!
What?
If you aren't resenting,
I'm going to resent!
What the heck is that...
Well, soon Hoshi-kun will come
and buy all 30 copies for me!
Again you count on Hoshi-san...
Najimi-san!
Hoshi-kun!
Najimi-san.
Clicking your tongue?
Oh, this is from the
ocean training camp?
It is!
It's the revised version,
but it's a self-confident work.
That's not what you said earlier!
Your brother came too?
Hey, you don't look so good.
Yeah, this is a Najimi-san manga!
Okay!
Hello, Beauty Love-sensei. Thank
you for taking care of me every time.
What does he mean
by taking care of him?
What?
Hey!
What? Toranoana sales division?
Yes!
I thought you were in college.
Until recently, I was
a T University student.
What?
You were smart.
But I realized the way
I should be going...
...is to spread the word
about Najimi-san's manga...
...so I quit.
He's not smart...
What a man of action!
Man, I'm flattered...
But is it okay that you
quit such a good school?
No, there's no problem.
Well, I thought my parents
looked at me in a certain way.
Like, this blank way...
But, it's my life!
Hey, I have to talk to you.
Don't tell me that...
...the person you have in mind to
be the replacement is that girl Najimi.
That's right.
Don't say such a stupid thing!
Regardless of how you
think about it, she's an amateur!
Please think about
the situation, Brother.
Right now, you're
desperate for anything, right?
Do you want our magazine
to put out just anything?
Hoshi-san!
Don't do it forcefully.
It's consensual...
No, it's forcefully!
Thank you very much!
We sold out.
Justice, we sold out!
Yeah. Thank you, Sora.
Justice!
Sora!
At Toranoana?
Distribution sale?
Yes!
Awesome! Good job, Hoshi-kun!
Wait, seriously?
It's okay.
I got the okay
under the condition that...
...if even one copy is left, I'm fired.
Are you serious...
Right now the anonymous
Najimi-san's book...
...will be read by a lot of
people and become a big hit!
And eventually you'll become
a business artist as you debut!
There isn't anything more honorable
than being able to be part of that!
Here Brother, read it thoroughly.
The book from the
shore house is really good.
The rest of Hoshi-kun's life
rests on Najimi's right hand.
It's... it's too heavy...
Ah, Junichiro, this is... as I thought...
No, right?
No, no, I'm not exactly saying no...
No!
No, no, no!
I can't agree on just
Najimi-san's book becoming famous!
What's that?
I can't agree on it either.
I guess I think a world where Najimi's
book is going to be a hit is too chaotic...
What do you mean by that?
Oh, don't take it the wrong way.
You can't take it a good way...
Well, we'll start by putting
30 copies on the shelf.
30 copies?
Yes.
Today I am going to
leave with a sample copy.
Please send the rest another day.
30 copies, huh?
Speaking of which,
the brother is with a publisher...
Let's have him read it!
Brother!
Yes?
It's not fair! It's all Najimi-san.
Please... please read mine too.
With this, I opened up the road
to become a business artist!
I'll see you around, Najimi-san.
Thank you.
U-Um!
Next time, not my brother, but...
...I wanted to introduce you
to my father and mother...
That kind of thing...
This is the one!
Well, um...
The book with the same angle faces
has been a popular topic on the web.
We've become fans!
That means...
Um...
I would like a copy of this!
Y-Yes.
Please give me one too!
Yes, thank you very much.
So things like this happen, huh?
Thank you!
Najimi-san's challenging new piece!
I'm going to sell a lot of them!
More like, what happened?
You've been quiet for a while...
Yeah, the one that
was selling this book...
You mean Nido-san?
Yeah...
Something bad has happened.
Something bad?
That girl has fallen for me too.
That girl has fallen for me "too."
I don't get what you mean.
Your eyes are knotholes.
She held my hand
and with teary eyes...
It's not fair! It's all Najimi-san.
...that's what she said!
That's what she said?
More like, what's up with her "too"?
You're going to make me say it?
You are definitely
wrong with Najimi-san!
It's your misconception, Brother.
You are the one
with the misconception!
If she remains the Najimi Osana
she is now, there is no hope!
Also, I have enough people
in mind for the replacement artist!
What?
She said her name is Kaneru Nido...
Then, Junichiro!
If you are going to back Najimi Osana
that much, then make me understand!
Okay.
Distribution sale?
That's wonderful news.
Well, I don't know if it's
going to go well or not, but...
Kaneru-chan, what's wrong?
I think it's because her
new book isn't selling?
Hey!
That too, but...
So it is...
Although not selling isn't
something that just started.
You!
Nido-san, do you want a drink?
Najimi-san, you're weird.
What, I am?
No, no, the weird one is Nido-san.
Najimi-san, you sold out,
but you don't seem happy about it.
Wow, you're right!
Congratulations, Najimi.
No, apparently it's the talk of the web,
it's selling because of how bad it is...
You're going too far away!
Najimi-san, you're going
somewhere too far above us!
W-What are you saying?
Kaneru-chan, Najimi
isn't going anywhere.
There, there, calm down.
Najimi-san.
Huh? Hoshi-kun, what's the matter?
Did you forget something?
You forgot to buy my book, right?
I don't think that's a possibility.
To be honest, it's about
the distribution sales thing...
That was canceled?
I thought so.
You can't get fired from the
company for something like that.
Please make it 100 copies!
Not 30 copies, 100 copies!
Wow!
Well, I don't think that is...
Then please send
100 copies in a couple of days.
Also, may I take
another copy as a sample?
Ah, it sold out earlier...
It sold out.
What did?
The new book.
Whose?
Najimi's!
Why?
I don't know why either...
Sold out.
Thank you very much.
Beauty Love House.
That's amazing!
This is possible. It's possible!
Hey, Hoshi-kun?
Why 100 copies all of a sudden?
I made a promise with my brother.
Promise?
Yes.
If the 100 copies of the book
sell out in three days...
...you will be drawing a
complete piece in his magazine!
Najimi, you've flown too far above us!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
When there are hello's,
there are good-bye's.
Next episode, the last episode...
Or in a way, a beginning.
12th Edition
I still want to do it, I want to do it more.