No, no, no, no...!
It's fine!
Don't do that during lunch time!
Seeing is better than kicking some random person!
So you better confirm it with your own eyes!
It's great, huh?
Aisaka coming back.
It is.
Hey, what are you screaming about?
Not like I need to ask with Valentine's coming up.
I doubt hyper-happy kids will listen to me.
Valentine's...
I forgot about it.
Stop acting like you didn't know! That won't fool me!
Sensei?
You're going to go make out when I'm not looking, right?
Doing stuff like that at school...
It's not like you have to give or get chocolate at school.
School's a place to learn.
Hearing that from Haruta...
Did I get it wrong?
Then what do you do at school?
Isn't it PE?
Oh, that's right.
Takasu-kun, Aisaka-san.
Please come to the counseling office after school.
Takasu-kun, you still can't tell me your career preferences?
And Aisaka-san, you still haven't turned in the one from first semester...
I'm sorry.
I'm still working out the details with my mother.
What about your mother?
She wants you to go to college, right?
Yasuko—
My mother has worked really hard, sometimes too much.
I don't want her to suffer on my part.
That's why I won't go to college.
That's what I want.
Aisaka-san, why don't you turn it in?
My family's rich, so I don't ever have to work.
I don't need to study, nor is there anything I want to do.
What's with you two?
Just because I don't want to go to college...!
I understand!
It's just that from now on, for the rest of your life, you have to decide on how you want to move forward.
You can't say it was someone else's fault, nor will anyone take responsibility for you.
That's why I want you think about it more carefully.
Takasu-kun...
You've never gone against your mother's wishes, right?
When you're done filling it out, bring it to the staff room.
"For the rest of your life"?
What are you—
Ta-da!
Hey!
That's the career plans form!
I don't need something like that.
There's no way I can think about my future.
I can't even appreciate who I am right now.
I've just been ignoring who I am for a long time.
"Why did it become like this?"
"What should I have done to avoid it?"
I don't know what I want to do in the future.
I can't even think of what I want to do right now.
I do have something I want to do.
I want to fall in love normally.
What are you doing?
B-But you don't even have someone...
Someone?
I may not have one, but what I mean is...
To be born to a normal family, raised as a good girl normally...
Meet a guy normally, become friends normally...
I wanted to fall in love normally like that.
Why is it past tense?
I told you, there's no way it'll happen.
It was off from the start.
I'm not normal.
What's "normal"?
What's wrong? What's right?
Who decided?
Hey, why are you yelling at me all of a sudden?
I didn't mean to...
Where are you going?
What are you going to do about the form?
I'm going home!
Who cares about that?
Taiga...
Excuse me.
Like I said before...
I decline.
I keep saying...
But...
Kawashima, won't you think it over again—
I don't have time to think it over.
Now then, Sensei...
I'm going home.
Wait, Kawashima-kun!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and catch her.
Hurry!
What are you going to do with my shoe?
Give it back.
Do you have a shoe fetish?
Gross.
I can't believe you did that.
Are you trying to set a long-throw record?
I said I'm sorry.
Hey...
Why did you get called in?
They asked me to be the model for the school uniform in next year's pamphlet, but I turned it down.
What's the big deal?
Isn't that your specialty?
I don't want to do it. No way.
I don't even know how long I can stay at this school.
You mean...
You're worried about your fight with Kushieda—
No!
Someone like Kushieda Minori can't change my life.
Then why would you say that?
I planned to quit school after first semester.
The fuss over the stalker had died down too.
You never said a thing...
At the time, I thought I'd try staying here a little longer.
Tomorrow, and the tomorrow after that, if I were here with these guys...
Then why?
I watched Taiga...
Get hurt.
Since I understood her feelings, and if no one else noticed them...
I thought, "I've got to save her."
But...
Now I think that if I hadn't been here,
everything would have sorted itself out.
Kawashima, you—
Hey, wait!
What now?
Taiga?
I'm really bu—
I wonder what's happening with the shop.
And my job at the cake shop...
Even though I had them give me a cute uniform...
I contacted both of them.
Don't worry about weird stuff, just get some rest.
Okay...
C-Co-Condition?
Yacchan's sleeping.
Ryuji, how's Yacchan?
She's fine.
I'm glad.
I was so surprised when I saw her faint through my window.
Ryuji?
Where are you going?
I'm going to go buy something that Yasuko can eat.
Hey, Ryuji!
What about your coat?
Ryuji?
You don't have your wallet, your keys, or your cell phone! Not to mention your shopping bag!
Get a hold of yourself, you idiot!
Hurry up and put this on!
And what about you, what's with that get up?
You wear this.
No way, I'm fine.
You're wearing it!
Ryuji?
Hey, you...
Go home.
No way.
Go home, really.
No way!
You're acting really weird!
Just go home!
Ryu—
What are you doing?
It's my fault.
Because of me, Yasuko fainted.
I am the one to blame.
What?
She has anemia!
It's a health problem!
It's not your fault!
If I had my act together...
Yasuko would have believed that I could really do it.
She would have relied on me more...
And then it wouldn't have turned out like this.
Ryuji!
Ryuji...
What... Should I do?
It's okay!
It's... Okay?
That's right!
It's okay!
It's okay.
Because Yacchan is an amazing mom!
Ryuji?
What's wrong?
You shouldn't go.
It's fine.
I have somewhere I need to go.
That puts me in a tough spot.
Tomorrow and the day after are really busy because of Valentine's.
I'm sorry, but she really can't.
I don't think I can find anyone else now...
I'm sorry.
I can do it.
You, really?
That'd really help!
Taiga?
It's not for you.
I want to do something for Yacchan too.
Please let me do it too!
Yacchan got fired from her job at the cake shop?
But—
Oh well, it happens all the time.
I'll find another good job.
Why do I have to be comforted?
W-Welc...
...come!
W-Welcome...
It's not selling...
You need to say it louder!
You're already at a disadvantage with your not-made-for-advertising face.
You...
You guys really are working!
Yo, Taka-chan!
What, it's you—
Haruta-kun, which one do you want?
They say if you ask for a big one at times like these, bad things will happen.
I think it'll be fine.
Then, the big one.
I'll take this please.
T-That'll be 580 yen.
You have a big sister?
She's not my sister, she's my girlfriend.
Good luck with it!
Isn't it kinda cold?
Let's go somewhere warm.
Yeah...
Why?
The world is really twisted.
Noto!
Why are you here?
No reason, I just happened to pass by.
Oh, yeah, did anyone else come by?
Like Ami-chan or Nanako-sama?
Kihara hasn't come by.
No!
That doesn't matter!
I just, see, I was just wondering if Kihara was going to make a big fuss and give Kitamura chocolate or something like that...
And then, how was it going...
I'm fine with it!
I'm fine. But Taiga, you care about it, right? About "that"?
What?
What do you mean, "that"?
Why do you care about Kihara Maya giving chocolate to Kitamura-kun...
Oh, I see!
You like her.
I guess it's one of those things you realize when you're fighting.
Wait a minute!
What are you saying!?
That's strange, Taiga!
It's not strange at all. It's a perfectly natural thing... A perfectly natural thing.
A boy's stamen and a girl's pistil...
Idiot!
You're crazy!
What's with him?
Crap.
If we keep messing around, we'll get yelled at.
Can't be helped then.
I guess it's time to summon our lethal weapon.
You're not by yourself?
I'm going home.
Now, now, since you came all the way here...
Here, Stupid Chihuahua, I'll give you this one. So hold it up.
No way.
Don't get me involved in weird stuff.
Ami-chan is beautiful, so I stand out.
Yes, yes, Stupid Chihuahua, you're really beautiful.
You really stand out.
So take this and try saying, "I really love the chocolate here," in a really loud voice.
What the hell?
You want me to promote it?
No way.
Why do I have to do something so dumb?
Now, now, Stupid Chihuahua.
I got it!
Why don't you buy one with your own money?
Then you could give it to Minorin and make up.
Actually, I was really watching you.
You want to make up with Minorin, but you can't do it correctly, the delicate Chihuahua's shaking heart...
Hey...
What are you saying?
If it's too hard for you, I can call Minorin for you.
Valentine's came around with great timing.
You!
Isn't that Kawashima Ami-chan?
You're right!
She's so cute! Her face is so small!
It really is Ami-chan!
Is she buying chocolate here?
Ami-chan loves the chocolate here!
It's a big hit among my model friends.
I'm going to buy it!
It's the same kind as Ami-chan!
Me too, me too!
What...
You really can do it.
Excuse me.
Yes!
Please wait a moment.
Ryuji, wait...
Excuse me.
I'll take this one.
Yes!
Hey, Kawashima!
You really like chasing after people.
You have potential as a stalker.
And what about you?
You seem to like running away.
Not just from me.
But from a lot of things.
Let me tell you...
I've never ever thought it'd be better if you weren't around!
If you left...
Everyone would be really disappointed.
Everyone really likes you.
Everyone?
Yeah!
Everyone!
Really...
You just don't get it.
Look, Taiga's having a tough time.
Crap!
It would've been okay...
Even if it wasn't everyone.
But I guess I didn't get it either.
Thanks!
I'll count on you tomorrow too.
We hit our target, so you didn't have to buy the rest.
It's okay, they're thank you gifts.
Thank you?
For all the people who helped me on the trip.
Like Kitamura-kun, Minorin, and Stupid Chihuahua, too.
And...
If I gave you chocolate, do you think you would be happy?
I don't know...
W-What don't you know?
What kind of guy would I be if I wasn't happy about getting chocolate from you?
Okay, I got it.
Then, I'll try my best.
Just giving them to you as-is isn't that nice, so I'll try to make something with it.
I hope everyone likes it.
Smells good!
You're already going to the shop?
It's okay, I'm fine, just fine.
I've got to thank Taiga-chan too.
Hey...
What are you trying to pull, calling us all here?
Today is Valentine's.
I brought some homemade chocolate to show my thanks.
You made it?
Wow!
It seems too important to eat!
Isn't that the chocolate you were selling yesterday?
You've gotten really good at telling lies...
No!
Wrapping is important, so I reused it, but everything inside is handmade.
Here you go.
Thanks for yesterday.
I won't do it again.
Yesterday was an exception.
Next is Minorin.
I heard you went to help save me during the school trip.
Thank you.
What's with this, all formal?
If you're in trouble, Minorin will always come to save you.
Minorin!
Ryuji.
You too, thanks.
Eat it with Yacchan.
And, Kitamura-kun...
I'll give you the one that came out the best.
You sure?
Of course!
You're the one that carried me up.
Crap, I haven't told Kushieda yet—
Were the whites of my eyes showing?
I didn't know what was going to happen!
I rolled down, and there were all these noises around my head...
Fainting feels like that...
It was like being in a dream.
I felt like I said a lot of incredible things, like I was half asleep.
When I woke up, I was really panicked...
What did you think you say?
I can't say!
There's no way I can say!
I can't even tell you.
Just say it.
No way, no way! Anyway, it was just my imagination.
Tell me.
It was something that no one should hear!
If someone heard it, I'd be done for!
It's a really awful thing, I wouldn't be able to go on.
Or something.
You didn't hear anything, right?
Yeah, I didn't hear anything, right, Takasu?
No one heard anything, it's alright.
Liar.
Planning on just leaving it with "I didn't hear anything"?
What are you saying, Minorin?
Taiga!
Are you also okay with no one else hearing it?
Takasu-kun saved you!
But he couldn't say it.
The reason lies in the words you're trying to hide, right?
Why, Taiga?
Why can't you just say this one thing, this one thing honestly?
It hurts!
Kitamura-kun?
What an awful face.
Stupid Chihuahua...
Hey, Takasu.
Is it okay with you to let Aisaka run away from here this way?
Is that okay?
Look here, Taiga!
Look at me!
What do you see?
No!
No, no, no, no...!
It's Minorin, your best friend, right?
You said you like me, right?
Then believe in me!
Let go, let go, let go!
I believe in you, Taiga.
I believe you're not the kind of person to blame others for your weakness, wanting something that Minorin wants!
Or were you that kind of person after all!?
That's not it.
I just wanted you to be happy.
The Minorin I love so much to be happy...
Who the hell are you kidding!?
My happiness...
Can only be made with my hands, and only with these hands.
I won't let anyone else decide what I need to be happy!
This is as far as we can go.
You're right.
Taiga?
Ami, you traitor!
Need to chase after her...
People who want to, that is.
Takasu-kun, I'm going to chase after Taiga.
I'm not done talking to her.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
Chase her, then what?
Find out how Taiga feels...
Then what?
Taiga's trying so hard to hide it...
Takasu-kun!
I...
Hey, Taiga...
Looks like it's going to snow.
I left the laundry outside.
Not just that...
I think I left a lot of things hanging out.