Hey, did you hear? There was an escape at Shonan Special Disciplinary School.
Really?!
Four of them, too! And they were all patients here!
But they're just kids. They'll be caught right away.
I want you to welcome him.
In order to fulfill her promise to Mario,
Setsuko steeled herself.
Setsuko!
Who's there?
It's me.
Maeda?!
Yeah.
He's weak, and his hand's badly hurt.
He's wounded?!
First, we need to find somewhere he can rest.
But we don't have anything.
I understand.
I'm drawing a map for you. Wait there.
Setsuko!
My relatives used to live in this farmhouse,
but no one's using it now.
There aren't any other houses around,
so you don't have to worry about being spotted.
Thanks, Setsuko.
We managed to stop the bleeding, but he's still unconscious.
That was the last of the medicine and bandages.
Plus, if we don't feed him something...
All right. Just hang on, Bro.
I'll get you something to eat!
Setsuko!
Where are you going, Maeda?
If you don't stay out of sight, you'll get caught.
I brought medicine and food, plus more clothing for you.
I want to help out too.
Setsuko...
Besides...
I promised that I'd come see Sakuragi, didn't I, Minakami?
Thanks, Setsuko.
That's a relief.
We couldn't have done this much ourselves.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'm glad Setsuko came for you, Bro.
How did you get so thin?
I will not die.
I won't let you die.
I... We're going to save you!
The three fell asleep with calm, proud expressions.
Since Uncovered and the others hadn't killed anyone during the escape,
they would not be sent to juvenile prison.
"No matter how the wind blows tomorrow, we did our very best."
From the start, they had been prepared for the worst.
Sakuragi would not awaken from his deep sleep.
Hey, where's Turtle?
I don't know. He went out early this morning.
I hope he's not off pilfering something weird again.
Look, guys!
Fresh enough for you?
Let's feed it to Bro!
Ow! He looks like he really wants to be eaten!
How are we going to explain this to Setsuko?
We're going to keep working on you until you tell us where those four are hiding!
Soldier!
Uncovered?
Yeah. You're not gonna tell them anything, right?
Tell them? Hell, I'd love it if they'd tell me.
Anyway, what about Cabbage?
Can't you hear him?
Snoring at a time like this?
I don't know if he's carefree,
or if he's just got a thick skin.
Oh, well. All we have to do now is survive Ishihara and Sasaki for another year.
Any regrets?
Idiot. I was ready for this. But...
a year without Bro...
It's gonna be a long year.
Even if they were punched, even if they were kicked, they would not be killed.
They had risen above the adults' tricks and traps.
Just thinking about meeting again under that tree in two years...
It warmed their hearts.
Those brats!
What should I do?
Kill them.
We should kill them.
I-Ishihara! You've recovered?
Prepare three death certificates.
I'll kill everyone who defies me!
He's awake, everyone! Sakuragi's awake!
Really?
He wants to talk with you.
Talk?
What did you want to talk about, Bro?
You should go back to the school.
Bro?
What's wrong? Sakuragi was a lot more fun.
Don't think you're walking out of here after defying me!
He's serious.
He's really going to kill us.
Ishihara! It's me!
What is it, Doctor?
He's back.
He came back.
Yokosuka Jou came back alone!
I don't know what you're planning,
but don't think we're going to let you off easy.
Maybe if you tell us where those three are hiding, I'll let you off the hook.
But if you try to trick me or something, you're a dead man.
You think you can kill me?
Don't act so cocky, Inspector.
Yokosuka! You-
Damn you! What are you trying to pull?!
Hurry up and put Soldier and the others back in my cell.
Quit fucking with me!
You want to go into solitary as well?!
Should you be talking to me like that?
What?!
Ishihara, murderer of Hagino Ei'ichiro.
Hagino wrote it all in his suicide note.
H-His suicide note?
He signed it with his own blood, too.
And Bro has it.
If we show it to the cops and the newspapers, you'll be sent straight to prison yourselves.
I hope you're looking forward to a living hell.
So, what are you gonna do?
Joe, why are you here?
Bro sent me.
Bro?
Calm down. I'll explain everything.
Go back to the school.
Bro...
Please!
Save Soldier, Uncovered, and Cabbage!
Please.
That idiot.
He's worrying about saving us...
when he can barely move.
So why did you come alone, Joe?
One of us would be enough.
So we decided with rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors? So you lost?
You've got no luck, do you?
Yeah, really.
Wrong.
I'm not here because I lost.
I'm here because I won.
Bro taught them how to be men who could endure losses.
The easiest thing to play in rock, paper, scissors is a forceful rock.
Mario and Turtle, without hesitation, tried to win with paper.
Joe saw through this.
Damn it!
We can't do anything. Sakuragi has the evidence.
You'd better not slip up again.
Maybe you should request a transfer.
I should lay low around here for now, too.
Sakuragi!
January, 1956
January, 1956.
Sasaki had disappeared from the disciplinary school,
and Ishihara had been relieved of responsibility for compound 2.
The remaining boys in cell 6 marked the New Year peacefully.
In hiding, Bro had made progress towards recovering,
but he could still barely stand.
With nothing but spare time,
Mario made himself a sandbag and spent every day punching it.
There was nothing they could do...
except rely on Setsuko for medicine and food.
We can't just keep relying on Setsuko.
Yeah.
Tomorrow I'll check out the black market in town.
Maybe something will turn up.
I'll go too.
Welcome! Thank you!
Tasty!
You there! Care to try your hand at boxing?
It's $20 for a KO, $10 for a win by decision, $5 even if you lose. How about it?
Where'd Turtle run off to?
Hey, Mario!
Mario! I found something great!
This boy's a boxer?
Are you strong?
What are you talking about, lady?
This here's the boss of Shonan Special Disciplinary School!
What?
Nobody there was a match for him!
Shonan Special Disciplinary School...
Why are you telling her that?!
Okay! It's all right!
Come to the American base in Tachikawa this Saturday!
All right! We found something, Mario!
Can you fight with your right hand like that, though?
Yeah, it's all healed and itching for some action.
All right, then you'll be fine.
I've gotta do it.
The victorious Americans and defeated Japanese staged inter-country boxing matches.
These were held weekly at the American army base in Tachikawa.
The red corner was for men selected from the American troops.
And the blue corner was for a motley crew of Japanese.
Okay, a KO is worth $20.
A win by decision, $10. Lose and it's $5.
That's it for sure.
I'm leaving with $20.
Yeah! Win, Mario!
Okay, okay.
Anything's okay!
All right! Let's go, Mario!
I'm going home with a fortune.
Hang on, Bro.
Those guys...
Mario! Mario!
What... What's going on?
What am I doing?
Dammit!
I've come this far.
I won't let myself lose!
Go for it, Mario! Don't lose!
Mario!
You shithead, we're gonna end up with $5 this way, not $20!
You didn't understand, did you?
What "winner takes all" means.
Wh-What do you mean, pops?
"Winner takes all" means that the victor takes the whole purse.
The loser doesn't get a cent.
W-Wait, no way! Quit pulling my leg!
I ain't even got the money for the bus ride home!
Mario!
Hey, stop it! Stop the fight!
He's already won!
Ref!
You bastards!
They'll kill you, kid!
Are you trying to kill Mario?!
Cut that out!
Is it so much fun to beat up the weak?
Fine, come and fight me, then!
Sorry, Mario. It's my fault.
I didn't land a single clean punch.
It's not your fault.
What do we have here?
Two whipped dogs licking each other's wounds?
I was looking forward to watching the undisputed champ of a disciplinary school.
But that was just pitiful.
And you call yourself a Japanese man?
Did you think you could beat that GI when you can hardly even use your right hand?
What?! Mario, you-
You're just a kid who talks tough.
What the hell do you know?!
You just whore yourself out to the Yanks.
What do you know?
Take that and go home.
What?
Damn men, always trying to prove something by acting tough.
I'm sick of seeing it.
I'm sick of seeing Japanese men lose to Americans.
Get stronger, then come back and try again.
Damn it!
I don't want to owe you anything!
I'll pay you back someday!
Of course you will.
I'm Lily.
Bring me back ten times that amount.
It was a total defeat.
Mario wasn't the only one hurt by it.
The woman called Lily also felt as if she'd been struck.
A one-sided loss made their pain four,
even eight times worse.
That day, Mario learned the huge difference between fighting and boxing.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Reborn demons.
Mario and Sakuragi head to the ring.
The serpent sneers.
The bell rings.
Good evening, everyone!
I'm the happiest girl in the universe, Satake Uki!
I have a big present for you tonight!
I'm handing it over to Oguri and Kanjiya at the ADR studio!
I'm Oguri Jun. I play Mario.
I'm Kanjiya Shihori. I play Setsuko.
We have a present to announce to our viewers.
We've both signed five copies of the script to give away!
If you're interested, check out the cell phone site.
We'll be waiting.
We will.
This is one of the signed scripts!
I want one too!