So where is Masaomi?
He left a bit ago.
He had something to do.
Leave it alone, and the tinder will keep
piling up and piling up...
We're over. Finished!
You did what you thought
was right, didn't you?
Is this the leader of the Dollars?
And if the Dollars are behind them,
we beat them up, too.
Don't let her get away!
Find her!
That way!
You guys, go that way!
Block the exits!
Why?
Why is Kida-kun...
The girl runs.
To escape from the shadows
that followed...
She'd just wanted to know the truth.
Geez! What a pain...
Where did they go?
They won't get away.
Why is Kida-kun...
She couldn't feel a thing.
Why?
The shock at what she'd seen
mentally overwhelmed her.
Anar
chy
I'm glad you're able to leave
the hospital early.
Thank you.
You've all been wonderful.
Here you are.
Thanks!
The Slasher incidents had
stopped that night,
and the city was regaining its calm.
A normal life awaited Sonohara Anri,
or it should have.
Sonohara-san!
I'm so glad I made it in time...
I was busy with the student council...
Ryuugamine-kun...
I heard, starting tomorrow,
you'll be back at school.
Are you OK now?
Yes! I'm fine.
I'll carry your things.
N-No, I'm fine.
Let him carry them!
He ran the whole way here
'cause he wanted to.
Anri, how many times today
do you think he's said this:
Sonohara-san's getting out
of the hospital today!
I wonder if she'll be OK
coming to school.
She's so erotic, so cute-
I didn't say that last one!
Thanks, both of you, for coming to see me
so often, while I was in the hospital.
Not at all...
By the way, Masaomi, you just
came out of the hospital, right?
Y-Yeah.
I just missed you.
Oh, right!
Sonohara-san, you can use my notes
for the time you were absent.
They might be a little hard to read,
but if you want them, they're yours.
Just a second. I'm sure I have
them here somewhere...
Something's different about Kida-kun.
The girl felt there was something different,
something wrong, about the boy.
Ever since he'd first come to see her...
You're OK now.
Kida-kun?
Anri... What happened?
It's nothing, really.
The Slasher kinda...
But it's nothing, really.
Sorry, gotta run.
I'll let Prince Mikado walk
the princess home.
Don't blow your chance.
See ya!
See you tomorrow!
An indescribable uneasiness
overwhelmed her.
Don't let them do anything till I get there.
OK?
<Tanaka Tarou> There are a lot more Yellow
Scarves around lately.
<Kanra> You're right.
<Kanra> You can see clearly them,
so they stand out more than the Dollars.
<Setton> They've been around for a long time,
but lately, they seem different.
<Tanaka Tarou> Different?
<Setton> I don't really know.
<Setton> I guess they're not like they used to be.
<Setton> They're kinda more violent now, I think.
<Saika-san has joined the channel>
<Tanaka Tarou> Oh, hey, Saika-san.
<Tanaka Tarou> Evening.
<Kanra> Evening!
<Setton> Welcome!
<Saika> Good evening...
<Saika> Um, I'm sorry.
<Tanaka Tarou> Why apologize?
<Kanra> You weren't used to the net at first,
<Kanra> so you got a virus, and that's why
you acted that way, right?
<Kanra> You couldn't help it.
<Saika> I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
<Tanaka Tarou> You apologize too much.
<Kanra> By the way, Saika-san,
<Kanra> ever heard of a color gang
called the Yellow Scarves?
<Saika> The people with the yellow
bandanas in town?
<Kanra> Yeah, those guys.
<Kanra> Another group, called the
Dollars, is a lot like them.
<Kanra> Because of the Slasher case, the two of them
are in a kind of dangerous situation.
<Saika> Um... What do you mean?
<Setton> Let's talk about something else, Kanra-san.
<Setton> You shouldn't just start talking about that stuff
to someone who doesn't know many details.
<Kanra> No, no.
<Kanra> If you live in Ikebukuro,
you should know this!
<Kanra> They never caught the Slasher, right?
<Kanra> And there are victims among both the
Dollars and Yellow Scarves, right?
<Kanra> Both think the other's responsible.
The Dollars don't think it's that big a deal.
But I think neither side knows much about
the other, and that's creating confusion.
Either way, if the two of them don't
find and lynch the person behind it,
a rain of blood's gonna fall on Ikebukuro...
It's pretty scary.
A real gang war!
You have a private message
from Setton-san
Don't worry about it, Anri-chan.
The two of them are just out of control.
You weren't behind it, so turning
yourself in won't do any good.
Don't do something you'll regret.
The cops are really scary these days.
Really scary!
Really scary, OK?
Especially the traffic cops!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Next time, I'll teach you how to use
private message mode.
I'm sorry. I'll be going.
Oh, OK.
Good night, Saika-san.
Night!
See ya!
<Saika-san has left the channel>
I'll be going, too.
Good night.
Good night!
<Setton-san has left the channel>
Kanra-san, about the Slasher...
I'll tell you anything I find.
And with a good discount.
Somewhere in this city is the real criminal.
Catching them will soothe the
misunderstandings between
the Yellow Scarves and the Dollars.
I don't know if it'll be that easy.
Neither the Yellow Scarves nor the Dollars
is really a single organization.
Some of them will probably take advantage
of the gang war to mug people.
If that keeps up, it'll be a real gang war.
I won't let that happen.
I dunno.
It may be too late to stop it.
There's no way for you to
stop the Yellow Scarves.
Even so, I'll keep it from happening.
I'll look forward to that.
I must do something,
thought the girl with the
cursed blade inside her.
I must do something,
thought the girl who'd watched the
world through a frame.
But...
The young boy who'd come, through the frame
and into her world, was already enslaved.
By the heavy chains of his past.
It was too late for him to escape.
Yeah?
OK.
Got it.
Be right there.
Sorry! A friend has something
he needs right away!
Yeah?
If you want to hate someone,
hate my friend all you like.
Hating someone's free,
and it doesn't hurt me at all.
Two birds with one stone!
Two chicks with one guy!
Two chicks and one guy?
See you tomorrow!
Was it really that important?
Kida-kun's been acting weird lately,
don't you think?
Really?
Sure you're not
overthinking things?
I'm sorry.
I have to do something.
Bye.
I heard some members of the Dollars got
mugged by the Yellow Scarves last night.
I heard that someone almost got killed.
The Yellow Scarves say that the Dollars
are behind the Slasher attacks.
Something had to be done.
The boy who led the Dollars knew this.
But he still didn't know that
he was one of the pieces on the board.
Come eat sushi!
Sushi is the soul of Japan!
It's enka!
I wonder if it's true, that he does a
cossack dance, when he delivers something.
Those kids last night were lucky
Simon was out on delivery.
Swing that pipe down, and you'll be
the main ingredient in sushi.
Human sushi...
It hurts, and it doesn't taste good.
Luck doesn't continue.
Geez... I don't like the look of things.
Does anyone know about the
Dollars and the Yellow Scarves?
Anyone?
Our boss is Kida Masaomi.
I've seen him with you, Mother.
He said he was going to
take revenge for you.
No...
Of course, she couldn't believe it.
But the children could not lie
to the girl, their Mother.
Where is Kida-kun?
He'll be coming to the meeting today.
Take me there.
And then...
She knew everything.
Kida-kun is...
Think she's back here?
She had to run.
It's simple.
Why is Kida-kun...
I'll love them all.
Kida Masaomi...
The yellow children, too...
All of them.
Cut them up
What would happen if she were caught?
and love them.
You can't love others.
I'll love them for you.
So much! So much! So much!
I don't want to hurt anyone!
The girl was terrified that the boy
would learn she was a monster.
It's too cramped.
I'll go.
Kida-kun!
Save me, someone!
Someone!
Hey, that's...
Standing in the pouring rain...
was the female Dullahan.
I'm here.
Where are you?
The only thing she'd been able to do was
seek help from one just like her,
another one who shouldn't
exist in this world.
She jumped over the wall on her bike...
She could do it.
She's going to move.
Seriously?
Celty-san!
You can tell me what's going on later.
We're getting out of here.
Get on back.
Right!
Thank you.
Hang on tight.
I've seen you around for a while.
I always thought that riding suit was
too curvy to be a guy.
I don't care about guys,
but if you're a girl, I could
love that suit alone.
If I fell in love with a nun,
I'd love even the gown she wore.
He's the one who's always
with Mikado and Anri...
I see.
She doesn't want him to see her face.
I don't know why, but I get it.
What?
Damn it...
Monster!
Don't!
She looked just like the headless
knight of legend.
The fragments of information
came together in an instant.
An intruder with a blade like the Slasher's,
the black bike coming to their rescue,
and the rumors that the black bike
belonged to the Dollars.
They all reached a single conclusion.
The Slasher was part of the Dollars.
The young boy didn't know
if his conclusion was right.
All he knew was that,
regardless of what he thought,
he could no longer contain his companions.
Hey, you ever heard of a Dullahan?
No, I haven't.
They say it's a headless knight,
with a headless horse,
who visits the homes of those about to die.
Like the grim reaper.
A sudden thought came to him.
One of them could die.
Why...
Why, at times like this,
do I want to see them first.
The sky has fallen.
A phrase meaning that everything
changes for the worse.
It was the phrase on the banners of the Yellow Scarves
in the Romance of the Three Kingdoms.
The sky ain't blue, yeah.
Ain't yellow either.
<Tanaka Tarou-san
has joined the channel>
<Kanra-san has joined the channel>
Evening!
Oh, is it just you?
Evening.
Seems like it.
Private message right away, huh?
There's something I want to ask you.
Um,
have the Yellow Scarves been in
Ikebukuro for a long time?
About three years...
They were a quiet little group at first.
The young boy who led the Dollars
learned of the terrible fight between
the Yellow Scarves and Blue Square,
not knowing that the girl
sacrificed to it was his
friend's former lover.
And not knowing that the
man telling him all this
controlled her heart and had inflicted
terrible, lasting wounds on his friend.
So in the end, the Yellow Scarves
were the only ones left...
But Blue Square didn't die.
What do you mean?
The leader of the Yellow Scarves
got sick of fighting
and left.
After that, they joined the Yellow Scarves.
So they merged?
Basically, yeah.
Outside of the leaders, no one would bother checking
who was part of which organization.
They just had to take off their blue clothes,
say they wanted to join,
and that was it.
But then the leader who quit...
He doesn't know, I imagine,
that the ones who sent his
girlfriend to the hospital are
with his old gang now.
You take care, too.
Some people are part of both the Dollars
and the Yellow Scarves, it seems.
That's why, if I send word
around the Dollars
that we had nothing to do with it,
they might tell the Yellow Scarves.
If it really isn't the Dollars behind it.
The Dollars don't have any rules,
and you don't watch them all.
A part of the Dollars may be the Slasher,
and you simply don't know it.
That's how the Dollars work.
If you're going to be a part of this world,
you should know that.
I'll keep that in mind.
Morning!
Good morning.
What's wrong?
You seem down.
Are you still not feeling well?
No, that's not it.
Morning!
Morning.
Oh, I saw Kida at the station.
He said he was staying home today.
Why?
Dunno.
He didn't say.
I see.
See ya.
Thanks.
You can't run from your past.
The reason you're worrying is
because of your past, right?
If you can't run,
then fight and win.
If I could only fight and be rid of
my past with you,
I'd love to.
Why can't you?
I couldn't fight with you.
He wanted a place to be.
That was all.
Each time he'd told his friend about
the new city he lived in,
he'd realized that he wasn't really a
part of the things he talked about.
Now he knew
that his sole place in the Yellow Scarves
had been only Mikajima Saki.
And now he was working for his dear friend,
who was his new life.
Geez. It's raining again.
Kadota-san.
You came back?
Yes.
Let's talk somewhere else.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
A New King
Will Arise
A great man once said that the world isn't real.
A great man once said that the world is symbolic.
A horrible past is the product of a delusion.
It never existed.
Isn't that enough?
Next time:
The Old King is Dead.