Riru...
It's been a while, Suzuko.
You have been chosen
to be a Selector.
After talking with Kiyoi-chan and the
others, I thought it might happen, but...
A new Selector battle has begun.
It's already started.
It was finally over,
after everyone suffered so much...
I can't go through that again!
I'm sorry, Suzuko.
I didn't want to come here.
I knew that if I met you,
I would make you suffer again.
So the rules are the same this time, then.
Battles where you fight
someone for their memories.
I don't know the details myself.
What I do know is that everyone
starts with three coins,
and if you win, you can
alter memories to your liking.
There's a new element called a "key card,"
and if you lose, your LRIG is taken.
Alter memories?
Huh? Yeah...
Erase memories, or bring them back.
Erase or bring back memories...
Does it have to be my own memories?
Can I recover someone else's memories?
I haven't been told anything about
what memories can be changed.
It might be possible.
If I could get back someone else's memories...
Suzuko...
I might be able to get
Chi-chan's memories back.
Chi-chan...
You're right. There is a possibility.
If you can take back memories by winning,
that means the stolen memories
must be kept somewhere.
All the lost memories must be somewhere...
Chi-chan's memories...
All those important memories we shared...
But, Suzuko, this is all just my guess.
There's no guarantee.
If you don't participate, you can keep
your peaceful, ordinary life.
That may be what's best for you.
You really are nice, Riru.
But if there's any chance,
no matter how small,
I want to bet on it.
If I can get Chi-chan's memories back...
Suzuko...
Okay.
Let's fight together again.
Yeah!
She's wonderful, that girl.
Mizushima Kiyoi...
I won't let you have your way.
This time, I will put a stop
to these Selector battles
and this endless cycle of despair!
Another Selector was chosen
this evening, then?
I won't let it end.
There's no escaping this eternal cycle...
Why?
Explain it to me, Hanayo-san!
Why did I become a Selector again?
First Hitoe, then me?
Then, is Ruuko also...
I don't know.
But even now, more and more
Selectors are being chosen.
The battles have already begun.
I think I feel a little better
after talking to Yuzuki.
Looks like you're getting along
well with Yuzuki and Ruuko.
Yeah!
The three of us just entered a
WIXOSS tournament as a team!
Ruuko and I are trying to play carefully,
but Yuzuki keeps pushing harder and harder.
Afterward, we all meet up to
discuss how we can improve.
I'm happy for you, Hitoe.
I've finally found you.
I'm Layla.
I was chosen to be a Selector,
but I couldn't find anyone to play with.
I was starting to get really frustrated.
So come on! Give me a quickie!
I'm rock hard and ready to go!
Hitoe...
I once fought a Selector like you.
She was self-centered, and aggressive...
She didn't care about other people.
She would abuse the people
around her to satisfy her lust...
You smell just like her.
It smells rotten, like a drainage ditch, right?
So what?
All I care about is being
able to do a Selector battle!
Will you fight or won't you? Which is it?
Hitoe, there's no reason
to accept her challenge.
Let's run.
I don't want to get involved in
a battle with memories at stake.
There are many memories I don't want to
forget, memories I don't want to lose...
But that's exactly why I can't let
people like you have your way!
If I don't stop you here, people will suffer!
Hitoe...
Oh? Looks like you're more than
just a gloomy girl in glasses.
This'll be fun.
Open.
Hitoe, I didn't think you'd
agree to this battle.
Neither did I.
I'm actually so scared, I'm shaking.
So, Midoriko...
Will you fight with me?
Of course.
Grow!
Huh? That girl...
She has no LRIG. What's going on?
Here I go.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
What?
This body is so much nicer than my other one.
I feel alive.
Wh-What happened?
The Selector herself became an LRIG?
Why?
If you do that, you'll suffer all
the LRIG's damage yourself.
You'll be badly hurt!
That's great, isn't it?
I only feel alive when I
expose myself to danger!
This is the real battle
I've been looking for!
She's betting not just
her coins, but herself?
That's... That's crazy!
Yeah, I'm crazy! I went
crazy a long time ago!
Midoriko!
It's no fun fighting if you won't hit back!
Entertain me more!
Hitoe, calm down.
Don't get sucked into her pace.
Thank you, Midoriko.
I'm okay.
Just a little scared.
Alraune, Kyuuso.
Okay.
Nice!
That was great!
Get Wave!
That was close.
Hitoe, you've gotten stronger.
It's because everyone was there for me.
Ruuko and Yuzuki, and Midoriko...
You're not bad.
Let's see you go a little harder!
Grow!
Hitoe, let's use our coin, too!
Yeah!
Coin bet!
Tentacle!
Now!
We won't lose.
Hitoe and I will keep winning to the end.
This is the stuff!
Thrills and terror that rip at your flesh,
burn your bones, and grab your heart...
This is the battle I wanted!
What is she saying?
Here I go!
Coin bet!
Doping.
She used a coin to buff herself.
Hitoe, build up Ener and
let's use a gamma burst!
It's the only way to win!
Yeah.
In High Spirits!
Okay, we'll defend, and on our next turn...
Not yet! Not yet! Not yet! Not yet!
What are you doing?
Your attacks can't hurt me.
And your enhanced attack
power is hurting you!
So... why?
This is great! I can't get enough!
This is the joy of living!
Ride!
I've never seen an LRIG like this...
She's completely different from us.
Insanity... Ecstasy... No, chaos!
This isn't...
Hitoe...
Midoriko! No!
Wait!
Midoriko, don't go!
Not yet...
I'm not satisfied yet.
I want more Selector battles
where I risk everything.
Midori-san...
Confirmation.
Kiyoi-san sent us information
about the new Selector battles.
Did you learn something?
Of course.
This time, if you lose,
your opponent takes your LRIG.
Oh, my!
So if you lose deliberately,
I'll be taken by some strange Selector and
spend the rest of my life as their plaything!
Anger. An LRIG is the core of a deck.
I would never be so foolish
as to let someone take mine.
Oh, dear. What a shame.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
A Selector is approaching.
Satomi Kou...
No, Carnival.
I'm happy to see you again, Mikage Hanna.
Coincidence.
I was thinking the same thing.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Oh?
Question. Why are you participating
in these battles again?
You were an LRIG. Are there
memories you want back?
Memories are chains that bind you.
These chains stop people from going forward.
I've seen far too many Selectors like that.
Selectors whose lives are ruled by
their memories, and who suffer for it.
The joy and powerful stimulation of
being able to see that up close...
That's what Kou and I wanted.
Anger. We're not here for your entertainment.
And...
Memories can drive people forward, too.
This won't go the way you're hoping it will.
Kou failed.
But, Mikage Hanna,
I can get along with you just fine.
The same with that other girl, Homura Suzuko.
I'm sure the look on her face when she
sinks into despair will be exquisite!
I'm overjoyed that I'll get a
chance to face her so her soon!
Revenge?!
Suzuko-san isn't a Selector!
I see. You didn't know yet.
What do you mean?
I'm a little better informed than you.
That's all.
Don't tell me you...
Obstruction!
Suzuko refuses to delve into this world!
I won't let you touch her!
Open!
Um... I'm s-sorry!
Don't apologize when you
haven't done anything.
I've told you again and again.
I'm s-sorry!
We're going first.
Let's go.
Deploying two tricks.
That's their LRIG, huh?
Understanding.
That deck is built around
deck manipulation tactics.
H-How did you know?
Why did you tell her?
Th-That was a lie!
I was just making it up!
Um...
So she knows my combos, huh?
Attack!
Right! Here I go!
Shut up!
I-I'm sorry.
Hanna-sama, did you notice?
Naturally.
Her reactions are too slow.
She's probably waiting
for a chance to counter.
That's my Hanna-sama!
Carnival, I'm putting a stop to your plans.
Coin bet!
Blind.
What is this?
Blind, of course.
But it won't be enough to stop me.
Mikage Hanna, I'll show you something nice.
Unlock. Coin bet.
I'm back!
It's everybody's little sister, Aya!
A second LRIG?
This is the effect of the key card.
Yay! Yay!
Hey, why do I have to support Slow-ko here?
It's normally the other way around, right?
I-I'm sorry!
Enough talking.
Coin bet.
Don't screw this up.
Holograph!
I'm sorry!
Magical WIXOSS! It's me, Slow-ko!
Screw the Blind effect!
Just keep hitting her!
'Kay!
I'm sorry!
Where is Hitoe?
She's not answering her phone.
Hitoe!
Hitoe, I was so worried!
Yuzuki!
I couldn't protect Midoriko... Midori-san.
If you lose, they take your LRIG?
What the hell kind of rule is that?
These Selector battles are totally
different from the ones before.
You and Ruuko have to stay
out of it, no matter what!
I'd have loved to, but...
Hanayo-san!
So you're a Selector, too?
Yeah.
If we can't avoid these battles,
then let's work together to win.
I'll get back Midoriko!
Yuzuki...
I need to do something, for Hitoe's sake, too.
I warned you via text.
Awareness.
But when I saw that message, I thought
that now was the time for battling.
Unless I have coins to spare,
I can't fight battles to figure out
the rules or how my enemies think.
You're crazy.
But I didn't intend to lose,
so I feel bad for Anonymous-chan.
I'm glad you're okay, though.
Even though you lost your LRIG,
you still remain a Selector, right?
I still have coins.
But I don't know how to
fight without an LRIG.
We both learned some things
after we fought battles.
If you lose, your LRIG is taken.
With the key cards, you can use two LRIGs.
Even if you lose, you remain a Selector.
And Carnival's goal...
What she said was probably true.
But I think that's only part of it.
She has a goal beyond personal pleasure?
Hypothesis. Carnival is
still hiding something.
And...
I see. You didn't know yet.
I'm a little better informed than you.
That's all.
Certainty.
Carnival is deeply involved with the
heart of these Selector battles.
Things are clearly different than before.
There's still so much we don't know.
Agreement.
We'll need to investigate further.
Addition. There's one more thing I've learned...
I was curious about what Carnival
said, so I called Suzuko-san.
And she said...
It really is fantastic...
That's right.
Continue enjoying the battles any way you want.
I brought more.
What's wrong, Tama?
I hear a voice...
I don't hear anything.
Crowding / Loser and Winner
I'm getting back Chi-chan's memories.
You may be able to pay the price to get one.
So it'll be better to work in a group.
How much of this had you predicted?
I saw Morikawa Chinatsu...
Gathering / Vortex and Turbid Water
Gathering / Vortex and Turbid Water.