What's taking Mizushima so long?
I want to hear how her date went quickly!
Come on, S-S-Suzu. Don't be so restless.
Celebrating Mizushima's
six monthiversary
S-S-Stay calm and wait for her.
You're the one who needs to calm down!
Don't get your hopes up. They might get dashed.
Celebrating Mizushima's
six monthiversary
Anyway, Sayo sure is taking her time.
Meeting for the first time in
six months rekindles their love.
As the two of them cuddle,
their hands locked in a gentle embrace...
Smooch
And then...
You're getting too excited!
Well, this is a relationship we're talking about here,
so no matter how it unfolds,
let's continue our interrogation unfazed.
'Sup.
Celebrating your
six monthiversary
Where've you been, Sayo?
You're late!
I got tired of waiting for you.
Well? How'd it go?
The school found out about my boyfriend.
Also, I decided to quit the student council.
Huh?
What was that?
What?
What?!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Wait, what're you talking about?!
That Smile...
Ichikawa caught me red-handed in a picture.
What?
I guess I was underestimating
her due to how stupid she was.
I'm amazed she tailed me without me noticing it.
She might've been pretending to be dumb.
This's no time to be impressed!
So yeah, if anyone asks you,
say you didn't know anything about my boyfriend.
What the heck?
Don't tell me you're taking all the blame yourself!
You think you can just go and sacrifice yourself? I—
I-It's... not a good thing, you know?
Yeah.
It was my own decision, and my error in judgment, to date a guy and meet him yesterday.
Since there's evidence of the fact, denying it would be meaningless.
And it'd be stupid to make a
mountain out of this molehill.
Basically, this is different from the time you got in trouble, Kurahashi.
Later.
Wait a sec!
Sayo!
How do you feel?
Do you wish to quit the student council?
Yep.
I'm done here.
Bye.
Celebrating your
six monthiversary
No...
Enomoto?
This can't be happening!
H-Hey!
Suzu.
Hey, Suzu!
Dammit. What the hell is going on?
What now, Maki?
Maki...
Stop it.
Don't do that kinda stuff anymore!
Fill out this questionnaire honestly. No lying, okay?
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
"Friends you're close to," huh?
We've talked quite a bit since we're both in the library committee,
but she's a bit weird,
so it doesn't exactly feel like we're "friends."
Everything she says pisses me off,
but well, she's fun to hang out with.
I guess I could call her a "close friend."
But it'd be really embarrassing if
she didn't put my name down too.
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Mizushima Sa
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Mizushima Sa
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Okay, time's up.
O-Oh no!
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Tanaka Kanami
Hibino Mayumi
Write down the names of friends you're close to.
Enomoto.
Here.
Jeez! We'll never finish if you keep
reading the books people returned!
Did you know?
They say you get fat if you stay mad all the time.
What? You're lying!
Yeah.
Oh, come on!
You're so easy to trick.
That's why you're always left out and alone in class!
That's fine by me.
That a fact?
Does that mean you answered today's
questionnaire with "I have zero friends"?
How sad.
I didn't.
Huh?
Wh-What'd you write?
You're the only one I can talk to like this.
Well, I don't care either way.
Oh, right. I had something to do.
Huh?
Bye.
Sayo!
Eno.
Let's come up with some kinda plan...
We don't have much chance of success.
Why are you so quick to give up?!
What else can I do?
I won't quit the student council.
I'm never again going to irresponsibly abandon my post.
I'm gonna be the vice president till the bitter end, you hear me?
So... So...
So you'll end up all alone after school!
It'll be really sad, you know?
Not much I can do about that either.
I'll make a motion.
Excuse me?
I'll make a motion to get relationships approved.
I'll appeal to people by saying,
"She pretended to only be interested in money,
but in reality, she was in a wholesome lovey-dovey relationship.
Let's save the innocent Sayo."
I'll make fliers detailing the start of
your relationship and hand them out.
I'll hijack the broadcasting room again and appeal to every student in this school.
I'll post it up on the Internet for the whole world to see.
You're kidding, right?
Shaddup!
If you're not gonna fight, I will!
You idiot!
Please tell me you're kidding!
You're the idiot here, Eno.
Excuse me.
Here are the documents you asked for, Ms. Sugihara.
Thanks.
You shouldn't overeat.
I get hungry. I eat. Cause and effect.
It seems they're not happy with their association status.
Minami, ask me for help if you need anything.
As your former advisor, I'll help you out.
Or at least try.
Wow, how reassuring!
If you'll excuse me.
Um, Ms. Sugihara.
I had no idea Mizushima would go and do that.
Sayo?
Are you talking about the Mizushima in my class? She do something?
I hear she was dating a guy in secret.
What?
That has to be some kind of mistake.
It seems a girl from the newspaper association caught her on camera.
Apparently her punishment will officially be decided in the meeting tomorrow.
Nana?
Where could Ichikawa be?
How could you?
I...
I liked your pictures!
What should I do?
Also, I'll quit the student council.
Huh?!
I'm going to hang on to this for a while.
You'll have to testify too, okay?
What?!
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Ichikawa.
Tanahashi.
Did you tail Mizushima?
Huh?
Was it all part of a "Play Dumb" scam?
What're you talking about?
Is it true you took a picture of Mizushima and showed it to the teachers?
W-Well...
And here I thought you were a great photographer.
How could you do this?
N-No, I...
I...
Don't cry!
If you cry that badly,
then I'll... I'll...
You idiot!
Nana.
You know,
I couldn't deal with her.
What a coincidence.
Me neither.
She's kinda wicked.
Keeps hitting people where it hurts and all that.
Plus, she loves money and shows up at
unexpected places at unexpected times.
Not to mention, she wears glasses.
Indeed.
Girls with glasses rank pretty high in terms of popularity, and she's one of them.
Wait, glasses have nothing to do with this.
Yeah, Suzu wears them too.
And most importantly, she lies through her teeth.
Yeah, and she does it with a straight face.
So that was...
...also a lie.
Hey, what're you making Suzu cry for?
Wh-Why are you crying?
Why are you crying too, Nana?
You too!
You're not crying, huh?
You can decide who's the biggest crybaby later!
Get inside already!
Celebrating Mizushima's Rescue Operation
Now, let us begin.
Yeah...
Okay, now we know how things ended up this way.
I-I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
Yeah, Mizushima's also partly to
blame for being so foul-mouthed.
I heard they were officially going to decide on her punishment in tomorrow's meeting.
Oh no.
The problem here's the picture, isn't it?
That's the biggest piece of evidence.
Um...
What kind of guy was he, by the way?
The sun had gone down, so it was dark out.
Plus, I couldn't get a good look at him from behind.
Which means the picture's not that clear either, right?
We can just say that it wasn't Sayo!
You can clearly see her glasses.
That's a no-go, huh?
If you can't see the face,
we could say she was actually with a girl.
He was wearing a boys' uniform.
It's not going to fly.
You can't see the face?
A girl...
Sayo's also fessed up to it,
which just makes things harder for us.
And at this stage, the act of destroying evidence
might end up becoming undeniable proof in itself.
Right now,
we should instead make use of that evidence!
That wig's thoroughly negating the sagely wisdom of your speech and expression.
Ichikawa.
Y-Yes?
You said you couldn't get a good look,
but Mizushima's boyfriend didn't have a mohawk, did he?
What are you doing?
That's what I'd like to know!
Where did you even get that wig?
Well...
I guess I could call it a fated encounter.
Quit blushing this instant!
There you go again, bringing more weird stuff in here!
Forgive me!
I beg your forgiveness, Riko!
Fuji's Princess
Ow!
Ohh! Ohhh!
Stop making weird noises!
These are the true colors of Fuji's Princess.
This is what the student council's really like.
What's the problem?
They're even better than we expected.
The super
embarrassed
vice president
and secretary
I can see why Sayo looked like she was having fun.
Hear me out!
This is just one small part of a bigger,
more important plan.
Plan?
Yeah.
His time is now.
The next day
Has she always been so calm and composed?
Let's have Mizushima quit the student council.
I'll ask you one last time.
There is nothing untoward about this photograph, correct?
Y-Yes!
She was having a really friendly chat!
With a really cool guy!
What?!
Could you talking about me, perhaps?
Wait, Makio?!
Who?!
Does the guy you saw look like this?
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Wig
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Fake
Mole
Shoulder Pads
Fake
Mole
Chest bound tight
Was he about as tall as Mizushima?
Shoes with
thick soles
And did he sound like this?
Nothing could make me happier than
watching this beautiful sunset with you!
There's no doubt about it! It's him!
What?
That's right, this is...
Makio Evolved!
Makio Evolved
The mole's right here.
You're Maki, right?
Are you trying to tell me it was you in this picture too?
Yes. That's me.
R-Ridiculous.
How are we supposed to believe that?
No way that's gonna work!
If you still wanna go ahead, I'll...
No.
This calls for someone who the teachers trust most.
For someone who's worked hard for that.
This is a role only I can play.
You're lying in order to cover for Mizushima!
It's the exact opposite.
Mizushima's the one covering for me.
Yeah, and she's covering for me too!
And me too!
Stop! You're all terrible at acting!
It's okay.
You seem cold-hearted at first glance,
but in truth, you're just really shy and really nice.
I know that all too well.
You're their advisor. What do you think?
Tanahashi's not a liar.
I had no idea Mizushima was like that!
You've got it all wrong!
Wait! Give us an explanation from the top!
Now this is where things get real.
If all we did was lie, it'd seem preposterous.
So we'll pepper our lie with a few facts.
To tell you the truth, we found this in the broadcast club's request box.
I was the one who submitted that,
so the rest of the students won't be affected by this.
This is the risk that I should be taking.
The student council got a request for love advice?
What is this supposed to be?
It's our fault. It seems that lunchtime broadcast caused some weird misunderstandings among the students.
We're also fully aware that this school
forbids us from getting into relationships.
But...
You know how she is.
You know that she never turns down a request.
W-Well, yeah...
But none of us have any links with boys,
so after great deliberation, this is what we came up with.
Dress like a man, feel like a man!
I'm a perfectionist, you see!
Mizushima was only playing along with me.
And yet she's gonna be dealt such a severe
punishment just because of one photograph?!
Them's the rules.
That's how it goes.
But who would've thought that our teachers were so narrow-minded
that simply talking to a guy would be an issue?!
So Mizushima took the fall for us.
But we never in our wildest dreams would've imagined
that you all would just believe her confession without investigating the matter properly!
That's just cruel!
I frequently act on my impulses.
That broadcast was one of my impulses too.
And I ended up causing problems for Kurahashi due to that.
Come to think of it, I jumped to the conclusion that Kurahashi was to blame back then too.
All blame lies with me.
So if Mizushima is going to quit, I'll quit with her!
What?!
Hang on a second.
You guys...
You've done enough!
Don't take the fall all by yourself!
Knock it off.
You're calm and composed enough to know the best method to get out of this situation, right?
How nice of Mizushima.
I didn't know she had a heart of gold.
And she tried to protect all of her juniors.
Smells like teen spirit!
The best method
Shut up and
deal with it
Very well. I understand.
Each member of the student council is to submit an apology letter.
There will be no other punishment.
Yes!
That went better than expected!
What was with those barefaced lies?
If they just look into it for a minute,
they'll find proof that I have a boyfriend.
Nah, they won't.
Well, yeah.
Left her boyfriend
alone for half a year
Still, your stocks have definitely fallen.
Especially yours, Maki.
What of it?
It's much better than losing a friend.
In return, your stock has hit a record high.
Sayo's actually a nice girl
who cares for her friends
I wish I could sell the lot of you!
I'd like it if you didn't look down on my capabilities.
I'll get my stock back up immediately.
And I didn't even have any stock in the first place.
I'll list myself on the exchange now.
I don't really get it, but I'll buy all of your stocks!
Crap, did we go too far?
Did we move her to tears?
I never expected to find three other stooges like Eno!
It's a rare sight for me too, you know?
Be thankful and pay your respects.
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry it's such a strange phenomenon, okay?
Thank you, Ms. Sugihara.
Must've been difficult to borrow the camera, right?
Not really.
Besides, I'd feel bad for Mizushima and
Ichikawa if they got punished just for that.
Wasn't it harder for you?
You were the one who investigated the data.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to take a thorough look since I'm her homeroom teacher.
Sure.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Growl
Here's a lunch box.
Reminded me of how chaotic things get before deadlines. It was fun.
Are you okay with not getting promoted to a
club and missing out on the summer contest?
At first, I wanted to mess around with the student council and have them promote us to a club again,
but if Nana can get her confidence back and we both have fun putting out newspapers,
I don't care if we're a club or an association.
The underground paper seems like more fun anyway.
I'm glad the student council's in one piece.
That is one evil look.
Momo!
I, Ichikawa Nana, have pulled it off!
A real deal scoop that won't harm anybody!
Take a look!
Let's use this to put out an interesting article!
Great going, Nana.
B-But...
First, get me down from here!
Miss!
What's wrong, Enomoto?
I lied even though you told me not to!
What?
I thought Mizushima wouldn't put my name down, so I erased hers!
But it's not like that!
C-Calm down, okay?
We're actually close friends, so...
Enomoto, you're too funny!
Why are you here?!
I just said I had something to do, didn't I?
My sides hurt.
Oh my god! If you really had something to do, why'd you have to leave with such a sad look on your face?!
Not my problem!
If we did that questionnaire now,
I wonder whose names we'd write.
Did you say something?
Nothing.
Man, today was a tiring day.
Guess I might as well say it.
Thanks, Eno.
Don't mention it.
I got to see something nostalgic in return.
What are you talking about?
It's a secret.
What the heck? Tell me.
You're creeping me out here.
It's a secret.
No matter what?
It's a secret!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Next time is the long-awaited "teasing Sayo" episode!
Prepare yourself, Sayo!
I'll get you back for all the times you messed with me!
Huh? You're calling me something different now.
That's because I feel we've grown a little closer.
Y-You could've ignored that.
Oh, what's this? You're cute when you're embarrassed!
Um, Enomoto, would it be all right if I called you Eno?
Wh-What?
D-Do whatever you want!
The Very Best of the Student Council
(By Publisher Request)
You stammered. How cute.
Sh-Shaddup!