Like a cruel angel
Become a legend, young boy
When a blue wind
Knocks on the door to your heart
You just gaze back at me
And smile oh so gently
So eager for something
You touch so softly
Those innocent eyes
Know nothing of the fate that awaits
But one day, you will realize
That upon your back
You have wings
You can fly to the faraway future
The cruel angel's thesis
One day, you'll take off through a window
If your overflowing pathos
Leads you to betray your memories
Then embrace the heavens and shine bright
Become legend, young boy
IN THE YEAR 2015 A.D.
THE 3RD ANGEL,
SACHIEL, ATTACKS
CONVENTIONAL ORDNANCE INEFFECTIVE
UN FORCES HALT OPERATIONS
FULL COMMAND AUTHORITY TRANSFERRED
TO SPECIAL AGENCY NERV
LATE THAT NIGHT,
ANGEL ARRIVES ABOVE NERV HQ
THE THIRD CHILDREN
REQUISITIONED THAT SAME DAY
SHINJI IKARI
CONSENTS TO BE PILOT
EVANGELION UNIT ONE
MAIDEN SORTIE
NERV EXPERIENCES ITS FIRST BATTLE
FIRST BATTLE ABOVE NERV HQ
CRANIAL DAMAGE TO EVA-01,
CONTROL LOST
COMPLETELY STILL
THEN...
BERSERK
Although the damage we suffered
as a result was extremely heavy,
a young boy with zero experience
went into battle for the first time
against an unknown enemy and defeated it.
This achievement by Shinji Ikari
deserves special attention.
UNIT ONE CORRODES TARGET'S A.T. FIELD
But it is the view of Operations that this
hard-won battle highlighted further issues
and has left us with multiple lessons
that we must learn from.
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
SOME INTERCEPT FACILITIES DESTROYED
EVA-01, MODERATE DAMAGE
NO OFFICIAL ACKNOWLEDGMENT
OF CASUALTIES IN THIS INCIDENT
My little sister is still
in the second grade.
She was hurt in that ruckus a while back.
It wasn't the enemy that hurt her,
it was that crazy robot!
That's stupid! How can I put up with that?
I want to show the grown-ups
who built that robot
how bad my sister's suffering is,
and how mad I am!
THE 4TH ANGEL,
SHAMSHEL, ATTACKS
AT THE TIME, SURFACE-TO-AIR INTERCEPT
SYSTEMS 48.2% OPERATIONAL
TOKYO-3 BATTLE CONFIGURATION
TRANSFORMATION, 96.8%
My friends and I had gone through
so many evacuation drills at school
that it didn't seem like
anything out of the ordinary.
The boys were rowdy,
acting like we were on a field trip,
so it never really
occurred to us to be afraid.
ANGEL ARRIVES ABOVE TOKYO-3
SECOND BATTLE ABOVE NERV HQ
DESPITE ACCIDENTAL SEVERING
OF EXTERNAL POWER CABLE...
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
NERV OBTAINS SAMPLE
FROM INTACT ANGEL
HOWEVER, FINAL REPORT ON ANALYSIS
FINDINGS STILL NOT RELEASED
THE FIFTH ANGEL,
RAMIEL, ATTACKS
IN RESPONSE TO
THIS IMPREGNABLE TARGET,
CAPT. KATSURAGI PROPOSES, RECEIVES
APPROVAL FOR, OPERATION YASHIMA
THE FIRST CHILDREN
DESIGNATED PILOT OF EVA-00
REI AYANAMI
MAIDEN SORTIE IN
NEWLY-REINSTATED EVA-00
THAT NIGHT, PART OF ANGEL
BREACHES GEO-FRONT
NERV CARRIES OUT
OPERATION YASHIMA
Ikari won't talk about it,
but I think that Unit 00 used itself
to shield Unit 01 from
the enemy's particle cannon.
No, I'm sure of it.
I'm certain for one reason: Ayanami.
I feel like Ayanami has a tenuous
grasp on her own existence.
I think she already has something
that isn't quite pessimism.
It's hard to believe she's only 14,
the same age as us.
THE SIXTH ANGEL,
GAGIEL, ENCOUNTERED
This incident deviated slightly
from our scenario.
Yes, but its outcome falls
well within our predictions.
Adjustments can be made.
THE SECOND CHILDREN
DESIGNATED PILOT OF EVA-02
ASUKA LANGLEY SORYU
HAS MAIDEN SORTIE
IN EVA-02
CLOSE-QUARTERS COMBAT
ON THE OCEAN'S SURFACE
AS WELL AS
FIRST UNDERWATER BATTLE
DURING ENCOUNTER ACTION
OFF THE COAST OF OLD ITO,
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
This encounter cost the UN Navy
a third of its vessels.
The lost ships belonged
to your country, did they not?
An inconsequential matter, overall.
Indeed. It is most fortunate that
our losses were limited to just those.
THE SEVENTH ANGEL,
ISRAFEL, ATTACKS
FIRST ANGEL WITH ABILITY
TO SPLIT AND RECOMBINE
HOWEVER, IN TWO-POINT HEAVY ASSAULT
BY EVA-01 AND EVA-02,
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
THE EIGHTH ANGEL,
SANDALPHON, DISCOVERED IN CRATER
OF MT. ASAMA
NERV ISSUES ORDER A-17
GRANTED SUPREME AUTHORITY,
CAPTURE OPERATION MOUNTED
TARGET MOMENTARILY CAUGHT
IN ELECTROMAGNETIC PHOTON CAGE...
HOWEVER, SCREEN RUPTURED,
OPERATION ABORTED
OPERATIONAL OBJECTIVE IMMEDIATELY
CHANGED TO ANNIHILATION OF ANGEL
EVA-02 CARRIES OUT OPERATION
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
EVA-00 REPAIRS,
REFITS COMPLETED
RETURNED TO SERVICE
THE NINTH ANGEL,
MATRIEL, ATTACKS
AS RESULT OF FIRST OPERATIONAL
DEPLOYMENT OF ALL THREE EVAS,
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
THE 10TH ANGEL,
SAHAQUIEL, ATTACKS
IN RESPONSE TO TARGET
THAT DESCENDS FROM STRATOSPHERE,
ALL THREE EVA UNITS DEPLOYED
FOR DIRECT INTERCEPT
ANGEL ANNIHILATED
THE ELEVENTH ANGEL
ATTACK UNCONFIRMED
AT THIS TIME
This is most troubling.
-It is much too soon.
-Indeed.
There was no contingency for
an Angel intrusion into Nerv HQ.
And to think it was even allowed
to enter the Central Dogma.
If contact had been made, all our plans
would have gone up in smoke.
The report made to the Council
was erroneous.
There was no Angel intrusion.
So you claim that there was no intrusion
by the Eleventh Angel, Ikari?
Correct.
Consider your words very carefully, Ikari.
False statements before this council
are punishable by death.
You are more than welcome to review
the records kept by the Magi.
You will find no evidence
of such an incident.
Don't make us laugh.
Burying the truth is what you do best!
The timeline is proceeding
as set out in the Dead Sea Scrolls.
Very well. We will not deliberate
your negligence or guilt in this matter.
Just remember that there is no need
for you to write out a new scenario.
I am well aware. Everything will proceed
according to Seele's scenario.
Mountains. The heavy mountains.
Something that changes over time.
Sky. The blue sky.
Something we can't see.
Something we can see.
The sun. Something there is only one of.
Water. Something that feels nice.
Commander Ikari?
Flowers. Many of the same thing.
Many things I don't want.
Sky. The red, red sky.
The color red. I don't like red.
Flowing water. Blood.
The smell of blood.
A woman who does not bleed.
Human beings, made from red clay.
Human beings, made from man and woman.
The city. Something created by man.
Evas. Something created by man.
What is man? Something created by God?
Man is something created by man?
All I have is my life, my heart.
Entry plug, the vessel of the heart.
The seat of the soul.
Who is this? This is me.
Who am I? What am I?
What am I?
I am myself. This object is myself.
The shape that forms my self.
This is the me that can be seen.
But I sense that I am not me.
It's very strange.
I feel my body melting away.
I no longer recognize myself.
My form is fading away.
I sense someone who is not me.
Is someone there, beyond here?
Shinji?
I know this person. Major Katsuragi.
Dr. Akagi.
Everyone. My classmates. Unit 02's pilot.
Commander Ikari?
Who are you?
What are your first impressions
of Unit 01, Rei?
It smells like Shinji.
PILOT INTEROPERABILITY TEST NO. 1
SUBJECT: REI AYANAMI
Her synchronization rates are
essentially the same as in Unit 00.
Well, Unit 00 and Unit 01's
personal patterns are very similar.
That's what makes it possible
for them to synchronize.
Margin of error, plus/minus 0.03.
Harmonics are nominal.
No issues in the compatibility
of Rei with Unit 01 detected.
That concludes the test.
Rei, you can come out now.
Yes, ma'am.
UNIT SYNCHRONIZATION TEST NO. 87
SUBJECT: ASUKA LANGLEY SORYU
-Unit 02 data banks complete.
-All harmonics at normal values.
No issues with pilot.
Of course there isn't!
PILOT INTEROPERABILITY TEST NO. 1
SUBJECT: SHINJI IKARI
What's the status of
Unit 00's personal data?
Rewriting already complete.
We're currently reverifying it.
The subject?
He seems a little nervous, but his
nerve signal patterns are normal.
It's his first time in Unit 00.
It's a different Eva, so it makes sense.
What an idiot. Why can't he just do
the job without stressing out about it?
Shinji's not the kind of person
who can do that.
Yeah, I know. That's why he's an idiot.
About that interoperability test
they're doing...
Shouldn't I be tested, too?
I thought you didn't want
to pilot any other Eva, Asuka.
Well, I guess you have a point.
The fact is, Unit 02 isn't compatible
with anybody else.
Entry sequence has started.
Ionizing LCL.
Commencing primary contact.
Well, Shinji? What do you think
of Unit 00's entry plug?
It feels a little strange.
-Strange, as in uncomfortable?
-No, it's just...
It smells like Ayanami.
It smells like her?
What kind of perv talk is that?
Data received. Reverifying. Pattern green.
Main power connection complete.
All restraining gear, green.
Roger.
Let's proceed to stage two
of the interoperability test, then.
Unit 00, initiating level two contact.
Well?
As I expected, his synch rates
aren't as high as with Unit 01.
All harmonics nominal.
Still, these numbers are good.
It looks like we'll be able to put
our other plan into action.
You mean the Dummy System? With all
due respect, Senpai, that plan seems...
I understand your misgivings.
But we must always have a backup plan.
If humanity is to survive.
I have nothing but respect for you
and I'll do my job.
But I don't think this is right.
Being too principled can be painful.
It makes it hard to be around others.
That's a lesson you'll learn
the first time you feel dirty.
Initiating level three connections.
Self-psychograph stabilizing.
Like being back at
Mommy's breast, Widdle Shinji?
You're causing cognitive noise.
Don't bother him.
Whatever!
Geez, how come everybody around here
coddles Shinji all the time?
Initiating A10 nerve connection.
Harmonics level, +20.
What is this? I feel something
coming straight into my head...
What is it?
Ayanami... Rei Ayanami!
It's Rei Ayanami, isn't it?
That's what I'm feeling!
It's Ayanami... Or isn't it?
-What's wrong?!
-Abnormalities in pilot's nerve pulses!
-Psychological contamination setting in!
-Impossible! Not at this plug depth!
It's not from the plug! The corrosion
is coming from the Eva itself!
We've lost control of Unit 00!
Break all circuits. Shut off its power!
Eva has switched over to auxiliary power!
Unit is still active!
-Shinji's status?
-Feed is down!
I can't monitor him!
Unit 00 is rejecting Shinji?
It's not working!
Auto-eject mechanism isn't activating!
Is this a repeat of that other time?
Is it trying to absorb Shinji?!
Rei! Get back!
Unit 00 system shutdown in ten seconds!
Nine! Eight! Seven!
Six! Five! Four!
Three! Two! One!
Zero!
Unit 00 has ceased operation.
Rescue the pilot! Hurry!
Could Unit 00 have been
trying to kill Rei?
Is there a connection between
this incident and that rampage earlier?
That one with Rei?
I can't say for sure yet.
We'll have to revert its data
back to Rei's
and run a follow-up synch test
with her right away.
As Ops Director, I ask that it be done
as soon as possible.
Before it can hinder our work.
I know, Major Katsuragi.
It was me that Unit 00
was trying to hit. I'm sure of it.
Our next world-class surprise talent
is a doggie who's a taxonomist!
Wow, that's amazing!
And now, allow me to introduce Kana,
a truly gifted doggy from Niigata!
Let me ask the question first!
Can you understand us?
-Woof!
-Wow, really?
So let's get right to it
and have you answer a question!
Woof!
What's the common name for the animal
with the scientific name of Canis lupus?
Woof!
Gosh, "wolf" is right!
You're a bona fide scientist!
I hate this. It's this same
stupid ceiling again...
Shinji's regained consciousness.
No contamination aftereffects.
He says that he doesn't remember anything.
I see.
I'm fine, but there was another terrorist
attack over the Spratly Islands.
Misato and Mr. Kaji
won't tell me anything.
And Shinji is clueless about everything.
The First... What kind of girl is she?
An unpredicted Angel intrusion...
The Council found out about it,
and they're using it to pressure us?
What a worthless bunch.
Their one job is to complain.
We hold all the cards.
There is nothing that they can do.
Perhaps, but that doesn't mean
you should antagonize them.
Things would get complicated
if Seele got involved now.
In various ways.
Everything is proceeding according
to our scenario. It's not a concern.
What about that accident with Unit 00?
That certainly wasn't in my scenario.
It affects nothing.
The re-synchronization of Rei
to Unit 00 was successful.
You're too fixated on Rei, Ikari.
What about Project Adam?
Proceeding smoothly.
We're not even 2% behind schedule.
And the Spear of Longinus?
Also on track.
Rei is carrying out the operation.
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
As her friends get married one by one,
Misato starts to feel the clock ticking.
Has she been given one last chance
through her reunion with Kaji?
Next episode! "Lies and Silence"!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming