Cal, what are you doing?
Cooking. Can't you tell?
What did you use to make it?
Those.
Just try some.
I used to cook for Judy every day.
It's good.
I know, right?
Then I took an even more expensive pot down from the shelf,
and I handed him a fifty dollar bill.
The face the shopkeeper made was hilarious.
You know, then...
So you mean you want to train that girl into a hitman?
Cal.
What is it?
Do you know how to use a gun?
Yeah.
"Do I feel lucky? Well, do ya, punk?"
That was an Eastwood reference.
Oh, and also...
I'm being serious here.
In other words, this is related to avenging Judy.
Let me make it clear.
Five million isn't enough.
Really?
But you only need a little more.
You could make it even by yourself.
What should I do?
Become my assistant in the meantime.
I know how you feel.
But...
Wow!
Wow! I'm going to become Phantom's assistant?!
Hey...
Come on, don't worry.
Hey, so if I become your assistant,
I'll be able to see the moment when Judy gets avenged with my own eyes, right?
Before that, there's something you need to get.
What's that? A new gun?
New clothes.
Let's go buy some tomorrow.
You're going out?
Yeah, work.
Then, can I...
Your mission today is to wait here.
But that's so boring!
Work is supposed to be boring and not enjoyable at all.
Be a good girl and wait.
Fine...
Five million were stolen and four men were killed.
On top of that, it was in your territory.
Even so, you're not going to apologize or compensate?
I offer my condolences for the deceased ones,
but we're not going to shoulder any responsibilities for incidents that occurred before our deal was completed.
You bitch...
Muroto.
However, it's true that our business has been interfered with.
We'll do whatever we can to find out who was behind it.
So you'll be able to take back the money, right?
That's included too.
I hope you will stay in Los Angeles until the conclusion is reached.
Of course, we can guarantee you a pleasant stay.
But originally...
Our money was stolen.
Our men were killed.
I doubt we'd be able to go back to Japan empty-handed.
Hey, Shiga, let's extend our vacation.
How are we going to explain this to the boss?
Just say we're not acclimatized.
The one behind this is Isaac Wisemel.
Wisemel?
There's no evidence that the details of our deal got leaked.
It was done by someone from within.
But Wisemel is also a victim.
You're right.
No one would think that he'd start trouble in his own yard for a measly five million dollars.
He planned it out well.
Wisemel's goal is to stop the
Godoh Group from joining Inferno.
He probably doesn't want to see me gain such a huge backing.
That's too coercive.
Do you think he became an executive with his rude mouth?
He's the type of guy who forces things when it's needed.
He'll definitely target the Godoh Group again.
Then just ask them to go back to Japan-
That'll be troublesome without bait, won't it?
We're fishing for a shark.
The Godoh Group is the bait, and you're the hook.
Yeah, it turns out we have to stay here.
We need you to stay with us for a little longer.
Understood.
This is just a backup plan in case something happens...
Leave the pointless talk for later.
The wine is losing its taste.
I'll contact you again.
I hope you have an enjoyable vacation.
I finally found a coordinator that has no link with Inferno.
That Giuseppe guy?
If he really knows everything about the underworld,
then it's pointless to plan the whole thing out.
That's true, but...
Whatever, just drink.
It's a gift from Inferno.
This booze is thirty years old, Shiga.
All right, I'll drink with you.
Bait, huh?
Reiji!
Everything was OK at the base!
You shouldn't say that out loud.
Sorry!
So is this part of the pleasant stay you mentioned?
What do you think?
Don't worry.
I meant it when I said "I can't go back empty-handed".
It seems like you have dissatisfied subordinates though.
You mean Shiga?
Don't worry.
He was just voicing some ideas.
That's his job.
I see.
You should worry about yourself.
It hasn't been going well recently, right?
Just as you said.
No matter what country you're in,
trying to live in the underground is the same.
However,
3000 people of the Godoh Group will be protecting you soon.
How reliable.
Have you decided yet?
Hold on.
It's already been two hours.
But I don't know...
There's nothing you want?
No, there's a lot!
Then...
Even though I have a lot I want...
If you ask me to pick one, I don't know which one to pick...
Just pick the one you want most.
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I just picked one, I'd have to give up the others, right?
Don't worry.
This isn't the only chance that you'll get to shop.
I'll bring you here again if there's something else you want.
Really?
Yeah, so pick a set of clothes you want to wear today.
Then...
Just to tell you, we won't be coming here every day.
I know!
Do you really?
Hey, hey, is it cute?
Does it look good on me?
Yeah, it looks really good on you.
This is my first time wearing such light clothes!
Reiji! Hurry!
Go back on your own.
A SIG Sauer, huh?
It's the same as the Beretta you're using now. 9mm, 15 shots.
But this one has a smaller build,
since you said she hasn't used a gun before.
This should do.
I'll give it a try.
Thanks.
So?
Huh?
I doubt you came here just to give me a gun I never asked you for.
That girl Cal was mentioned in today's executive meeting.
Was it Wisemel?
Even worse, McGuire.
He said he wants to see how much she's grown.
You should at least teach her how to use a gun.
Welcome home, Reiji.
Oh, you changed already?
Those clothes are for going out.
This is enough to wear inside.
Yeah, that's good enough.
We'll begin firearms training now.
Really?
Is this the training ground?
I haven't been here for a while.
Such a lonely place.
Let's begin.
Hold it properly with the right amount of force.
Right hand out and left hand supporting.
Yeah. Just like that.
Use the sight to aim at the target.
Can you see it?
My hands are shaking...
Use your fingers, not your arms.
Good, that's it.
Pull the trigger slowly.
You rushed it.
Do it slower, like you're squeezing something.
I hit it! I hit it!
Did you see that, Reiji?
Yay!
Try reloading it.
Her reloading is cautious and well done.
All right, try practicing by yourself.
Lonely place, huh?
What do you want from me?
So? What do you want from me?
Who are you talking to, me?
OK.
You're dead.
I missed...
Cal.
You know, um... That was a De Niro reference...
Do that again.
Do that De Niro or whatever reference again.
What do you want from me?
So-
Cut the dialog.
Next time, don't shoot immediately.
Strike your pose, stop for one beat, and then shoot.
All right.
I hit it?
Yay! I hit it!
Yes.
Are you ready to fish for the shark?
The Godohs are tired of sitting and waiting.
They plan on going out and having some fun tonight.
Your mission is to watch over them and catch Wisemel in the act.
All right!
I'm not even close...
How easygoing can they get?
All right!
Today isn't my lucky day.
Don't be so depressed.
You'll never get the Goddess of Victory if you don't have confidence.
She's already opened up for you,
so what's the point of me trying to get her?
You're giving up?
This is the only thing that won't betray me.
Don't drink too much now.
Why can't they act like Japanese and stay together?
Shiga-kun!
Yes, Bro?
Hey, does the mafia really control this place?
No way...
This isn't a De Niro movie.
That girl is probably a genius.
But should I let her walk the same path as me?
No, I should set her free as soon as possible.
Let's go play poker.
Umm...
Yes?
My friend was supposed to be here.
Oh, the Japanese guy?
It seems like he returned to his room with a young woman.
Got him.
Don't tell me...
Elen?
No, it can't be her.
Elen is dead...
She was killed by me, so...