Cure Moonlight.
You shall be destroyed, together with the Great Heart Tree!
Protecting the Great Heart Tree is my mission.
Gather, Flower Power!
Moon Tact!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Dark Power, gather.
Dark Tact!
Precure Dark Power Fortissimo!
So the legendary warrior, Precure, lies defeated.
With this, the Great Heart Tree shall wither,
and the world shall belong to us, the Desert Apostles!
The flowers have fallen, so why has the tree not yet wilted?
Seems your luck has run out.
Even if I fall,
other Precure shall appear before you to protect the Great Heart Tree!
Dark Forte Wave!
Cure Moonlight!
Chypre! Coffret!
Pass the Heart Perfume onto the next Precure!
Out of the way!
My fairies... seek out my replacement!
What's the matter, Tsubomi?
It's nothing...
That same dream again...
Grandma!
Tsubomi, welcome to Kibougahana.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
I'm Hanasaki Tsubomi.
Since my parents opened up a flower shop in Kibougahana, where my grandma lives,
we moved here.
However, I'm the easily-embarrassed, shy type...
But since I'm transferring schools, I'm going to try and change that!
No, not can...
I will change!
I found one!
A four-leaf clover!
In flower language, it means happiness.
Four-leaf clover, please grant my wish!
All right, here I go!
I'm Going to Change!
Just Watch!
All right, before we begin, I'd like to introduce a new friend to you all.
Hanasaki, come on in.
O-Okay!
Time to say goodbye to the old shy me!
I'll change! Just watch!
I'm going to change!
Hanasaki, write your name on the
board, and then introduce yourself.
Be brave and speak loudly...
Hanasaki Tsubomi
Nice to m—
Teacher!
Her name is way too small to read!
Hanasaki Tsubomi
I don't think I'll be able to change, clover.
Hanasaki, go ahead and write it again.
You seem to be rather reserved, don't you, Hanasaki?
Well, introduce yourself.
My name is Hanasaki Tsubomi, and I just transferred here today.
My hobbies are tending flowers and...
Even her voice is reserved!
Erika, you're talking too much.
Give her a chance to speak.
I see... I kinda forget how loud I am.
Sorry about that!
Hanasaki, is there anything else you'd like to say?
Oh, uh... It's nice to meet you all!
It's nice meeting you too, Hanasaki.
Let's get along, okay?
Let's see, where's an empty seat...
Right here, Hanasaki!
Next to her?!
I'm Kurumi Erika!
If there's anything you wanna know, just ask me!
Okay...
I'm really no good with girls like her...
Flowers that bloom from the moonlight are beautiful,
yet flowers that bloom from the sun shine brightly...
Hey, Hanasaki, where did you move here from?
From Kamakura...
Wait, we're in the middle of class!
Kamakura? Kamakura is awesome!
So, why did you move here?
I came to live with my grandma...
What do your parents do, then?
Well, at the moment they run a flower shop...
Hanasaki! Stop talking during class!
I'm sorry!
Tatsuya, please continue.
Tsubomi, Ms. Tsurusaki may seem like a bit of a tomboy,
but she's a really nice teacher who's kind to her students.
Kurumi, we aren't really that close, so can you stop using my first name—
You can call me Erika.
Okay.
You're from Kamakura?
I've been there three times. It's nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
You're right next to the ocean.
Yeah, it's a really nice place.
So here's where you ran off to!
Oh, fried chicken!
I'll trade you my omelette for it.
I was saving that for last...
Huh? Did you say something?
No...
So tasty!
Oh, you like to save the best for last, don'tcha, Tsubomi?
Sorry. You can have it back.
It's fine. Really!
Guess so.
Hanasaki, Erika does stuff at her own pace, so you need to be pretty blunt with her.
R-Right...
What're you talking about?
This is just how I work!
That's why we said you do stuff at your own pace.
Oh.
Myoudou!
Fight! Fight!
I'm beat...
What?!
You're all quitting?!
Sorry, we're busy with cram school, so...
Wait a sec!
If you all quit, I'll be the only one left in the Fashion Club!
Well, we all already decided to quit...
Sorry.
Wait!
Jeez!
What should I do?
If I'm the only member left, this club'll be demoted to an association!
Wait right there!
Join the Fashion Club!
You haven't joined a club yet, right?
I'm begging you!
Hold on a sec!
I was planning on joining the Gardening Club—
Your family runs a flower shop, right?
Forget about flowers while you're at school!
Come join the Fashion Club!
It'll be fun! We're girls, after all!
There's no way you can't be interested in fashion!
I'm interested in flowers!
Don't just go deciding things on your own!
She's still following me?
I'm pretty sure I said no.
Kurumi!
I told you to call me Erika...
So, Erika, why are you following me?
I won't join the Fashion Club no matter how many times you ask...
My house is that way.
That so?
Huh? We're still going the same way?
This is my house!
What?!
Why're you so surprised?
Welcome home!
I'm back!
No way! You live right next door?!
Seems that way.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the daughter of the shopkeepers next door...
Erika, right?
Your mother told me just now.
Oh, she did?
Well, I'm in the same class as Tsubomi!
Are you now?
Isn't that great, Tsubomi?
Y-Yeah...
I'm going to borrow Tsubomi for a bit, ma'am.
Let's go, Tsubomi.
Go where?
To my place!
I can't believe our houses are next to each other!
It must be fate or something!
It's just a coincidence!
Sorry, but I have some things I need to do!
Please excuse me!
All right! I point-blank refused her!
Maybe I really have changed...
Oh? You wanted to change, huh?
Um... I...
Why didn't you say so sooner?
I've got just the change for you!
Whaddya think? It's really fashionable, ain't it?
I made this dress myself.
You can have it.
Will you give it a rest already?!
Hey, what's the matter?
Didn't you say you wanted to change?
What I wanted to change was
my personality, not my clothes!
Just because I don't have any friends yet... doesn't mean you can do what you like!
Here, have it back!
No! I gave it to you, so it's yours!
Tsubomi!
What's with you?!
Just cause I was... trying to help you change...
That was your fault, Erika.
Momo...
You speak before you think.
That's a bad habit, you know?
It has nothing to do with you.
Just leave me alone!
You sure aren't honest with yourself.
I'm so very sorry for that!
Momo's so pretty, modeling while in high
school, and is super popular with the guys!
Compared to that, I'm...
Arghhhhhh!
Did I go overboard?
I guess trying to change yourself is really difficult.
I'm sensing the presence of a Desert Apostle!
We need to reach Cure Flower ASAP!
Another dream about Cure Moonlight...
Wow!
Cure Moonlight.
The legendary warrior, Precure...
Why am I so hung up about it when it's just a dream?
What?! What on earth?!
We're being chased by bad people!
Please help us!
Why are the plushies talking?!
We don't have time to explain!
What are you doing? Stop! It tickles!
Hey, missy.
Don't suppose a couple of fairies fell around here, did they?
Tch.
What's with her? She was kinda suspicious...
She's Sasorina.
She's one of the Desert Apostles! They're evil-doers who steal people's hearts!
By the way, I'm Chypre.
And I'm Coffret.
I'm Hanasaki Tsubomi.
Well then, Tsubomi, if you'd please carry us like this to Cure Flower...
Like this?
Hey, missy, you haven't seen any fairies, have you?
Whoa! A weirdo!
What an insolent child.
Oh?
The Flower of your Heart is wilting from your suffering...
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
She pulled out the Flower of her Heart!
This is of no use to me.
Look at this!
Erika!
This happened because the
Flower of her Heart was stolen!
Until you take back the Flower of her Heart from Sasorina,
she can't be returned to normal!
Excuse me! Can you give back the Flower of her Heart, please?
Oh, you're the girl from before.
So you had the fairies hidden in there.
Oh, that'll do nicely...
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Doll!
Run for it!
Doll! Doll doll!
Doll!
We're finished!
I hate you, Momo!
Just cause you're kinda pretty and stylish
doesn't mean you can act so damn proud!
No!
Doll. Doll!
What's it talking about?!
It's the screams coming from the heart of the girl whose Flower of the Heart was stolen!
Erika...
I mean, I'm trying my best too!
But I'll never be as pretty as Momo!
I can't help being envious!
These are Erika's worries?
If the Flower of her Heart stays separated
like this, it'll weaken the Great Heart Tree!
The Great Heart Tree?
You know of the Great Heart Tree?
It's a phrase that's appeared in my dreams countless times.
Your dreams?
It can't be...
Is she...
All right, I think playtime is over.
Now hand over the Heart Perfume.
The Heart Perfume belongs to the legendary Precure!
I won't hand it over to a Desert Apostle!
I just wanna be like Momo!
Erika.
How useless.
Stop worrying about that stuff and go capture those fairies!
It's not useless!
Using Erika's worries to make that monster rampage is just cruel!
I've had it up to here with this!
Why's this happening?!
The Heart Perfume is responding to Tsubomi's heart!
Then I shall entrust Cure Moonlight's wishes to Tsubomi!
Cure Moonlight's wishes?
It's a transformation item!
Transformation?
To turn into the legendary warrior, Precure!
Precure?!
Put all your heart into the Heart Perfume!
And shout, "Precure! Open My Heart!"
Huh?!
Just say it!
I don't really get it, but whatever!
Go forth, Seed of the Precure!
Precure! Open My Heart!
P-Precure?!
Doll.
W-What the heck is with this costume?!
Amazing!
You really are a Precure!
A name! You need to choose a name!
I can't really do it at the drop of a hat...
I've got it.
I'll definitely save Erika.
My name is...
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
I'm a protagonist and I've already been petrified?!
You're a protagonist, Erika?
Wait, I'm not? No way...
Even if you aren't a protagonist, I'll give it my all to save you!
Please, Flower Tact! Defeat my foes!
"Your all" is way too weak!
HeartCatch Precure:
I'm the Weakest
Precure in History?!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!