An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
Ga-thunk!
I'll be saving little girls all over the world again today!
#02 Lowee's terror (lickorrist)
Wow, what a picturesque town!
I've always wanted to visit Lowee.
I had an inkling you felt that way.
Rom and Ram told me to come visit.
Apparently Blanc doesn't let them leave the country.
Yeah, Blanc can be a real party pooper sometimes.
Someone should tell her she'll end up as a loner like Noire if she keeps that up.
Hello? Did you forget I was right here?
Wait!
Who are you calling a loner?!
My bad!
But hey, someone laying it on you straight like that
might give you the little push you need to change yourself!
Big words coming from Goddess Lazybones herself!
Maybe it was a mistake to come here after all.
She fell for it!
It worked...
Rom, Ram!
What do you think you're doing?
Run for it!
Wait!
Are you certain about this?
Putting this plan into action
will bring revolution to this world.
Hold it right there!
I'm aware.
Help!
We definitely need to keep this under wraps until we begin.
Rom! Ram!
Run for it!
You lot...
How many times do I gotta tell ya to keep it down when I'm tryin' to work?!
I-I'm so sorry!
Sis...
Lookie look!
Huh?
What the...?!
It's you!
Ram and I drew it!
My precious book...
You two are dead!
Look, the drawing came to life!
Hold it right there!
Run for it!
Nepgear! Uni!
You came!
Yup! We came to play!
Heyo, Blanc!
I came for you!
Teehee.
So, like... yeah!
We heard Lowee had this brand spanking new amusement park,
so we all decided to
come and take a look-see!
Histoire contacted me and said she wanted me to teach you what it meant to be a CPU, though.
Aw, don't bother your pretty head with that!
It was all in one ear and out the other last time, y'know?
Well, excuse me.
I've heard about the amusement park too.
Wouldn't it be fun if we all went there together?
Super Nitten Land?!
I wanna go!
Take us there! I can't wait!
Could you take my sisters along?
What about you?
Sis...
Aren't you coming?
I... can't.
What? More work?
Why don't you just quit already?
The wise men of the past once said,
"Only fools and horses work."
I don't think those men were all that wise.
Either way,
I can't go.
Wait for me, Ram!
Put on your coats, you two!
You're forgetting the tickets, Nepgear!
Nepgear!
Uni!
Where'd you go?
Here!
Right here!
A Dogoo coin!
This one's got a Kupocat!
Ah, it's just a Tertis block.
And this one's a Tesrit.
Lame!
I'll take some!
Other nations' CPUs have come all the way, you know.
Blanc should've come along.
I seriously don't understand
what goes through her head.
Indeed. What she needs is a little maturity.
Like me.
Oh yeah, why are you here—
Zoinks!
This turtle's after my peaches!
Nooo!
Someone help!
Zoinks!
Look, Rom! It's a Guardragon coin!
A rare item!
That one too.
Oh, and that one too!
They're all Guardragons!
But, uh, I think I've had enough.
Let's take some back for Sis.
Why bother?
Not like she bothered coming.
Yeah, but...
Fine.
Let's take a whole lot back for Sis.
Okay!
Yay!
Lick!
Huh?
What's up, Nepgear?
Where did Rom and Ram run off to?
I saw them go that way earlier.
Rom?
Ram?
Ah-kekekekeke!
Rom! Ram!
What's the meaning of this?!
Post-pubescent hags need not apply!
Looks like it went off without a hitch, Trick.
Our delicious banquet of fun
has only just begun!
Rom...
Ram!
I'm extremely sorry.
Blanc gave me specific orders not to allow anyone through.
What's the big deal? We're all buddy-buddy CPUs, right?
I can't. I'm sorry.
At least let us apologize!
It's our fault Rom and Ram got kidnapped!
We've already mobilized the guard and sent them out to look for them.
We know that!
Leave.
You guys are always causing trouble.
Rom...
Ram...
It's all my fault.
I'm your sister...
If only I'd been
more responsible...
I've gotta do something. Anything.
Oh, yeah. That—
Ga-thunk!
Found you!
Who're you?
I'm Abnes!
Ally of little girls everywhere!
I'm the anchor of Abnes Channel, a super-hit web show.
Don't you recognize me?
Come now, let's get this broadcast started!
Broadcast?
Hello to all our viewers across the world!
This is Abnes, idol to little girls everywhere!
Today, we're here to visit Blanc, Lowee's little girl CPU!
Hey, knock it the hell off before I—
By the way, is it true that Rom and Ram, your little sisters, got kidnapped?
How'd you know?
It is true!
I'm so worried!
So, Blanc, how does it feel to have your precious little sisters snatched away from you?
Good heavens, that Blanc.
This is an emergency! Why does she have to keep up that stubborn facade?
Yeah, that's supposed to be your shtick, Noire.
Excuse me?!
Um, ladies...
In truth—
Sis, what's going on up there?
Well then, Blanc, are you saying it's all your fault your sisters got kidnapped?
Well...
Get a load of this!
The little girl CPU can't say anything at all in her own defense!
Little girls just aren't cut out to rule a nation, after all.
They should be living carefree lives full of fun and games!
Abnes Channel stands wholly opposed to little girls playing CPU!
Hey! What's going on here?!
Who are you?
I'm Neptune!
Planeptune's CPU!
You're a CPU too?
I guess you technically look old enough to be a teenager,
but your body's too underdeveloped!
You're a little girl!
Certified!
Wha? Did I really just get certified as a little girl by an even littler girl?
Huh? In what way am I a little girl?
It takes one to know one, you know!
So that means you are a little girl!
You're the one who's calling people little girls left and right!
Did you just call me a little girl again?!
Hold it right there!
I'll let you off the hook for today,
little girl CPU!
Say what, pintsize?!
Yeah, get outta here, little girl!
Your face makes me wanna hurl!
What in Gamindustri was that?
I wonder how they got in.
Blanc!
Pull yourself together!
I-I'll go get help!
What's wrong?
What if lots of Lowee's residents saw that broadcast just now?
Maybe it caused her Shares to crash or something.
Oh, yeah. CPUs can't use much energy when their Share reserves are low.
I don't think this has anything to do with Shares.
Public opinion can't be swayed that quickly.
Then...
Ladies.
There's still something we can do.
I know how we can find Rom and Ram.
Blanc and I were trying to put a certain plan into action.
You're aware Lowee used to offer a satellite imagery service, yes?
If I remember correctly, it was called Terra View, wasn't it?
The one that was closed down around a decade ago, right?
Yes.
That satellite's still functioning, actually.
It can still take and send pictures of the surface.
They're pretty low-resolution, though.
Leanbox's research institute developed software that could analyze the data
and produce images of a much higher resolution.
Wow. Your country's crazy advanced!
And so I made Blanc an offer.
I said we'd let her have this software if she provided us with photographic data of Lowee.
What?
That means that you two would have data on the whole world to yourselves!
Huh? Having you peeking at us all day would be no fun at all!
No, we were thinking of sharing this information with everyone.
It was Blanc's idea.
"We signed a treaty of friendship, so all four nations should have equal access."
Really?
So we were looking for a good opportunity to announce it.
A bit like a surprise present.
Pretty nice, eh?
Analysis complete.
Time to find out where the kidnapper's hiding.
Oh my.
Is this...
Lickety lickety lick...
No!
Rom?
The little girls awaken! It's happening!
Can I lick you two all over?
What do you think you're doing to Rom?!
Stop it!
N-No!
Stop!
Trick!
I called them and delivered our ransom demands.
Wait, what are you doing?!
Healing them, of course!
My saliva is a miraculous panacea that cures any ill!
Th-That so?
I'll have you two feeling better lickety-split!
Who would've thought they'd be hiding within a ride that was under construction?
All right, time to crash this party!
Hold on.
What's up?
In situations like these, you need to make sure the hostages are safe first.
No!
Stop!
Let us go!
That's quite enough!
Sis?
Who's that? Another delicious young morsel?
Vert!
Let those girls go.
I'll take their place!
Huh?
I'm a gentleman, you know.
I only like little girls.
I've no interest in those cancerous growths on your chest.
Wh-What's wrong with being well-endowed?
All I can see is how much
they'll sag one day.
Looks like you've managed to anger me.
Y-You're a CPU?!
Green Heart,
transformation complete.
Oh, shit!
Screw the ransom, our
lives are in danger here!
Kekekeke! Did you seriously think you had me licked?
We'll see about that.
Have a taste of this Drill Lance!
Rainy Ratnapura!
Nooo!
That was easy.
Oh?
Where are Rom and Ram?
Crud, CPUs!
Sis!
She was in on it too!
Got it.
How dare you think you can make a fool out of us?
Oh, that was just Trick.
Also, we only carried out this whole kidnapping deal because some weird woman put us up to it.
Hm?
Sounds like just the kind of thing an underling would say.
Y-Yeah!
I'm just a plain ol' underling.
So, I'll be taking my leave now.
Did you think it'd be that easy?!
Lace Ribbon Dance!
Not happening, huh?
I'll keep these little girls safe,
even if it should cost me my life!
That is my duty as a gentleman!
Where are you,
my delicate flower buds?
What spirit!
Little girls really are the best!
Lickety lickety lick!
Get your filthy tongue off my precious little sisters.
You'll pay for this,
ya frickin' pedo.
Pedo?
My, you flatter me!
Oh, really?
Then let me flatten you as well.
I hope you're ready,
ya stinkin' pedo!
You damn deviant!
Sleazebag!
Tanzerin Trombe!
Little girls forever!
You picked a fight with a goddess.
Don't come crying to me later.
Rom.
Ram.
Sorry for putting you through this.
I'm a failure as a sister.
Sis!
We brought you these.
Guardragon coins!
Get out here, kidnapper!
I'll smash you all the way to Planeptune!
Sis...
Emergency Exit
Maybe it's all over already.
Whaat?!
Lack of sleep?
Yeah.
That's why I lost consciousness,
and why I didn't go out with you.
What the heck?
I've been pulling all-nighters for a while now,
so I was in no state to face you guys.
And yet you saved Rom and Ram. Thank you so much.
Vert. Noire.
You too, Neptune.
Thanks for sticking up for me during that broadcast.
Oh, it was no big deal!
I just did what anyone would do—
chased that annoying brat away!
Look, Sis.
That's nice.
Ram!
Stop doodling on those things!
You've got so many copies of the same book.
Express Mail
Doesn't matter if we draw on a few, right?
It does matter!
How?
W-Well...
That's the story I spent night after night working on!
So... They're fanzines, basically?
What?
What's it's about, Uni?
Apparently, there's a girl who fell from the sky
and a boy born with a special power,
and they save the world together.
Oh, so you're supposed to read this as "destiny"?
Don't read it at all!
Amazing!
The protagonist awakened to a new power!
That's so cool!
Stop reading it!
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
I've gotta do something. Anything.
Oh, yeah. That—
Ga-thunk!
Found you!
A weekend (girls' night out) at Leanbox
Oops. Wrong room.
Hey! Help us!