It's you, Kiritsugu.
Utw
Presents
Will one last miracle come to pass?
あと一度だけ奇跡は起こるだろう
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
優しい声で描く歪んだ未来
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
もう誰も泣かない世界の為に
Mou dare mo nakanai sekai no tame ni
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
紅く汚された空の何処にも
Akaku kegasareta sora no doko ni mo
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
届かず消える叫びと祈り
Todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
慰めは捨てて行ける
Nagusame wa sutete yukeru
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
綺麗な月の光が始まりへと沈み行く
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga hajimari e to shizumiyuku
Into the distance
その彼方へ
Sono kanata e
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
閉ざされてく瞳でまだ遠くへ手を伸ばす
Tozasareteku hitomi de mada tooku e te wo nobasu
I believe in your sorrow
君の嘆きを 信じて
Kimi no nageki wo shinjite
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You really...
...came to see me again.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
Lastly, I need to return this to you.
You're the one who'll need Avalon from now on.
When you fight your final battle, I'm sure it'll aid you.
You know...
I really am happy.
I've loved... and I've been loved.
I've had a husband and a daughter for nine whole years.
You gave me everything.
All the happiness in the world that was never meant for me.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to show you more of the outside world.
No.
It's fine.
If there's any happiness that I have yet to experience, give it all to Ilya.
Your daughter...
Our beloved Ilya.
Don't forget to bring Ilya to this country one day.
Show her everything I wasn't able to see.
The cherry blossoms...
The summer clouds...
I will.
Well, I'll be going now.
Okay, take care.
My love...
Saber is heading to Rider's hideout, right?
Yes. She's on her way.
I'll go and kill Tohsaka Tokiomi.
When Saber and Rider fight, there's a
good chance Archer will appear there.
I'll use that opportunity.
You continue to watch over Iri.
Understood.
Um... Kiritsugu.
You... finally look like your old self.
I don't sense a Servant's presence.
Packs:   Body Warmer
There's no magic field.
What could this mean?
Does that taste good?
Nope. It's awful.
Japanese food has really reached new lows.
Boy, you walked right past Okonomiyaki Shouki in the new town.
Their modanyaki was absolutely superb.
Pity you didn't buy any.
If you want to eat there again, hurry up and recover enough to assume corporeal form.
You know what this place is, right?
It's where I summoned you.
The Fuyuki ley lines most compatible with you run through here, right?
You should be able to recover much faster.
I'll be staying here all day.
I won't do anything except sleep,
so take as much mana as you want, as long as it doesn't kill me.
It should help you recover.
So you already know? You should've told me when you found out.
Finding out later that someone's seen right through you is, well...
It's a little embarrassing.
You idiot!
You're the one who should've spoken up.
I'm the one who'll be in danger if you aren't at your best when I need you!
Why didn't you say anything?
I thought I could hold out a little longer,
but the energy expenditure from the
river battle was greater than I expected.
So in the end, your trump card uses up a ton of mana.
I just ignored it at first.
You didn't pass on any of the costs to me, so I thought your Noble Phantasm was ridiculously efficient.
Rider.
You used the mana from your own stores
in place of mana I should've supplied, right?
You even did it twice, reckless as it was.
What the heck was that all about?
Well, you see...
When you get right down to it, I'm a Servant and therefore a natural soul eater.
If I made you bear the cost while expending
my mana at full force, it could endanger your life.
I'm fine with that.
This is a battle I chose to fight.
If I don't shed blood or make sacrifices,
there's no point if I end up winning.
I just want to prove it.
That I...
That I, too, can win such things!
But that only applies if the Grail actually exists, boy.
You know, I once fought for something that might not have even existed. Just like you.
Ôkeanos.
That's right.
I told everyone I'd show them Ôkeanos,
and they all believed me and followed without a doubt.
Many died.
They were all dreaming of this
Ôkeanos I spoke of, right until the end.
When I gained the knowledge of this era, it really hit me.
I had no idea the Earth was round and closed.
What a bad joke.
But even so, when I saw the map,
I had no choice but to accept it.
I've had enough of people dying for fairy tales.
Were the Grail's location certain, I'd have no objection to you risking your life.
But unfortunately, it isn't.
Even so...
Even so, I...
I'm your Master!
Boy...
You've really learned to talk back, haven't you?
It's also true that your Magic Circuits are flowing far better than usual.
If we rest during the day, we'll be ready for more action come nightfall!
And?
What exactly do you mean by more action?
Let's see.
Why don't we start with Saber this evening?
At this rate, how much will you recover by tonight?
If I use the Gordius Wheel only for flight, there shouldn't be a problem.
However...
I think I'll only be able to use Ionian Hetairoi one last time.
I see...
We should probably save it for the fight with Archer.
In that case, Rider...
Why do you want to fight Saber?
Saber is someone I have to defeat.
It's my duty as a Heroic Spirit.
What the heck's that?
If I don't show that stupid girl the right path, she'll never learn.
That would be too sad.
Well, do what you want.
Just go ahead and sleep, boy.
Rest is the battle you face right now.
I am the repugnant.
The scorned.
The despised.
Who are you?
My name is unworthy of praise.
My body unworthy of envy.
I am the shadow cast by the light of a Heroic Spirit.
The darkness born from the shadow of a shining legend.
Thus, do I hate.
Thus, do I resent.
I feed on the cries of those who sink into darkness
and curse those who shine brilliantly.
Her image is my shame.
Her honor remains untarnished, and
thus I am forever looked down upon.
You are...
...the sacrifice!
Healing won't help me.
I'm going to die soon.
Damn it...
Really, look at how pathetic you are now, Kariya.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not blaming you.
To be honest, I never even imagined that you'd last this long.
And so, I shall give you the ultimate
trump card I've stowed away for this stage.
Now...
That was fast.
The worm I just gave you was the first to feed on Sakura's purity.
How does it feel, Kariya?
For an entire year, it's been devouring the girl's life energy.
It's a magnificent mana source.
Now, go and fight, Kariya.
Make good use of the life you've stolen from Sakura.
Use every ounce of your flesh and bone to acquire the Grail.
If you even can, that is.
Hey, Maiya-san.
Why do you fight for Kiritsugu?
Because I have nothing else.
I don't remember my family or my name.
Hisau Maiya was the name on the first fake passport Kiritsugu made for me.
All I remember about my home country is its extreme poverty.
The wars never ended, even though there was no money to maintain the armies.
But each day, they continued to kill one another.
And then, someone had an idea.
Rather than conscript and train soldiers,
they decided it'd be cheaper and quicker to kidnap kids and arm them.
Maiya-san, you...
Aim at the enemy and pull the trigger.
That was my sole function.
I threw everything else away.
As a human being, I'm dead inside.
But my body continues to move,
still working like it did before.
That is my life.
But Kiritsugu took me in anyway.
So he can use me however he wants.
That's the reason I'm here.
In fact, Madam, it's your passion that's surprising.
You've been shut inside the castle where you were born, living without experiencing the outside world.
So I can't imagine why you'd fight this hard to help Kiritsugu change the world.
I...
You're right.
There's no way I could truly understand Kiritsugu's ideals.
It's as you say.
I don't understand a thing about
the world Kiritsugu is trying to change.
I simply borrowed all of my ideals from him.
But don't let him know that.
I've always told him that he's doing the right thing.
I've told him those ideals are worth my life.
And I pretended to understand him.
Then, Madam, do you have no wish of your own?
A wish?
No, I have one.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber to win the Holy Grail.
Is that the Einzbern desire, the attainment of the third true magic?
No.
What I desire is an end to the conflict.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes true and
all the fighting everywhere ceases,
the fight for the Grail here in Fuyuki City should be no exception.
I want this fourth battle to be the last Holy Grail War there will be.
For your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail, it will be Ilya's turn next.
It is the destiny of every Einzbern homunculus.
That's why I want to be the last one.
If that comes to pass, Ilya'll be able
to live out her life as a human being.
Maiya-san.
What will you do after Kiritsugu reaches his goal?
I don't expect to survive.
Even if I do, there'd be no reason for me to exist.
I'm sure that's what the world will be like once Kiritsugu has changed it.
No, that's not true.
You think so?
You have to look for your real name and family!
Those aren't things you should forget.
You have to find out and remember them forever.
So live, Maiya-san.
For me, too.
I'll do my best.
But that will be after the battle has ended.
Right now, we must be cautious.
He and I must stay on guard.
It was Tohsaka Tokiomi who died.
You really are...
Maiya-san!
Iri!
By my Command Spell, I order my puppet...
Saber!
Go back to the storehouse! Now!
Kiritsugu...
This is...
Maiya!
Saber...
Don't speak.
Hurry...
Go outside and chase him...
Rider took Madam...
But then...
I'm... fine.
And soon, Kiritsugu will...
So... hurry.
Maiya.
Please hold out until Kiritsugu returns.
I will bring Irisviel back.
Did Rider really...?!
Rider...
Yes, I see.
You shouldn't cry.
Save those tears for your wife...
You can't cry here.
You're weak.
That's why you shouldn't... break down just yet...
I...
This morning, you finally looked like your old self.
You can't waver now...
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, you have fulfilled...
...your purpose.
Maiya.
Maiya...
Episode 20
Return of the Assassin
Doushite sora wa konnani aokute
どうして空はこんなに青くて
Why is the sky so blue?
Nanimo kanashimi wo shiranu you ni
何も悲しみを知らぬように
As if oblivious to sadness
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita e to kuzureochiru
いつも躊躇わず明日へと崩れ落ちる
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuru no ne
命は足りないまま生まれてくるのね
I suppose we are born with our lives short
Kakeochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
かけおちた心にあなたが触れて
You have touched my torn heart
Futari de yuku mirai wa kegare no nai tsuyosa de
二人で行く未来は穢れのない強さで
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
空は高く 風は歌う
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Yume wo miteta yorokobi e to
夢を見てた喜びへと
Men will one day come to realize
Hito wa itsuka tadoritsukeru
人はいつか辿り着ける
The joy of chasing after a dream
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
子供の瞳であなたは信じた
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
Soba ni iru yo
そばにいるよ
I'll be right beside you
Kooritsuita mori wo nukete
凍りついた森を抜けて
As we pass through the frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni mayowanu you ni
その瞳が世界の嘆きに迷わぬように
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
Where is Irisviel?
Don't forget. Tonight, at midnight.
Nothing can stop me!
Don't underestimate me, King of Conquerors!
It's his fault!
If it weren't for him...
Oh, scary, scary.
Are you satisfied, Kariya-kun?
Next Episode
Knight on Two Wheels