Vengeance, huh...?
Dammit! It's Scar...
Marcoh must've told him
about his role in Ishval.
[Hawkeye] I'll let you
know if I hear anything new.
The Fuhrer's basically
hired you to be his hostage...
Will you be alright?
Well, it's all in how
you look at it, I guess...
This close to him,
it just means
I'll have a better chance
to kill him in his sleep.
You scare me.
Oh, yeah...
Pass this on for me...
Tell the Colonel
that Scar is back.
Sure thing, no problem.
Hey, Lieutenant?
Yes? What is it?
I just want to say thanks...
For telling me about Ishval.
[dog bark]
Ruff!
[Ed] Al!
[Al] Brother... What's wrong?
[Al] That's terrible...
It's tough to even
hear about Ishval.
[Ed] And she
didn't hold back...
even though I'm
practically a kid.
They say "an Alchemist is one
who seeks after the truth"...
And yet... I knew nothing
about what happened in Ishval...
You think the
Colonel's concerned
about what happens after
he gets what he wants?
I know I would be if
I were him... Y'know...?
Hey, Al...
What are you gonna do when
you get your real body back?
I mean afterwards.
[Al] Well, let's see...
First thing...
I really wanna eat
some of Winry's apple pie.
[Ed laughs]
Ha! Hehe!
And what about you?
[Ed sighs]
Hmmmm...
I've been so busy trying
to get our bodies back
that I haven't even thought
about what happens next.
I guess the first thing...
I'll make some courtesy calls...
Let Granny and our
teacher know we're alright.
Yeah, of course... They've
both helped us out so much.
[Al] And you know what...?
They'll be smiling
when they see us.
Yeah.
That'll be nice...
Just to see them smile.
[Ed] Yeah.
[Al] I know things
are rough right now...
but I'm starting to cheer up.
Well I've found a
trace of hope for us.
[Ed] You know how our
alchemy wouldn't work
when we were
under Central command?
Well guess what...?
It wasn't working
above ground either.
[Al] But... What about
Scar and that girl?
Exactly... They were the
only ones who could use it.
[Al] Well if that's the case...
They're doing
something different...
something with their alchemy
we don't know about...
Yeah... Which means we
haven't hit a dead end yet.
[Ed] You mean she's gone?
The little obnoxious girl left?
[Knocs] Yeah...
Sometime this morning.
[Ed] But she...
Where was she going?
[Knocs] She didn't tell me.
We can still find her!
[Al] But this city is huge...
And we don't have any clues.
But we do have a clue, Al.
What the hell is that?
They're a gift from me.
Oh, come on...
Couldn't you have just gotten me
some magazines
with girls in them?
These should keep you from
slacking off while we're gone.
Leaving already?
[Breda] Yep... Gonna eat some
of that famous western cuisine.
Hold down the
fort 'til we get back.
Right... I'll see ya later.
Here ya go, boy...
You eat up so you
can grow big and strong.
You be good...
Look after everyone.
Sergeant Fuery.
Hey.
Oh, Officer Falman...
I thought you'd already
left for the north.
I've gotta return something
to the Colonel first.
[Falman] Ah, man...
We really weren't in
Central for very long.
You're being deployed to
Southern Command, right?
Yes, sir...
The opposite from you.
It's gonna be so cold.
I always get
the worst posts...
Well... I've gotta
get moving...
You take care, Sergeant.
Yes, sir... I'm sure
we'll meet again some day.
[door knocks]
[Hawkeye] Sorry
for the interruption.
Oh. Sure.
I just came by to get
something that I left.
[Roy] Ah, right.
[Hawkeye] I've got intel that
Scar is back on the prowl.
[Roy] I guess I'll have to
watch out for him then...
Things are gonna be
tough without my bodyguard.
[Hawkeye]
Just don't get killed, sir.
Sure... You must
be anxious, huh?
Maybe I picked the wrong
person to side with after all.
Then go ahead and shoot me,
if that's what you think...
You promised me that you would.
You haven't gotten
quite that bad.
You're too kind, Lieutenant.
Well, then, Colonel...
See ya later.
Until then.
One other thing...
Try not to slack off too much.
Right.
[Roy] My pawn.
Yeah... It started
off as a hobby of mine.
[Roy] My bishop.
Yes, sir...
I consider it an honor.
[Roy] My rook.
Hello, sir.
[Roy] My knight.
I doubt that I'm the
brightest guy you'll meet
but I do know how to shoot.
[Roy]
And... Worst of all.
I'll follow you
into hell if you want.
[Roy]
They've even taken my queen.
But... I'm still
not in checkmate.
Not yet anyway.
[Ed] Hey! Have you
seen this cat...?
I'm trying to find the
little girl who owns it.
Look familiar...?
How 'bout you...?
[Al] No, it looks like this...
I promise it's not
some weird alien.
[Ed sighs]
Seems like this search
is getting us nowhere.
[Al] Y'know, they might
not be in Central anymore.
Fullmetal.
Colonel?
[Roy] You don't say...
Xingese Alkahestry.
Sounds promising...
I'll ask around and
let you know what I find.
Thank you, but I really
don't wanna get any deeper
in debt to you
than I already am.
Speaking of...
You owe me some money...
So how about you cough it up.
Eyes on the road!
You remembered...?
Come on...
How much did I borrow...?
500 cens?
It was five hundred and
twenty cens...! Don't con me.
I'm not conning you...!
I'm just not a
penny-pincher like you are.
[Al] I'm sorry, Colonel.
[Ed] I'm just gonna
hold onto this...
but I promise to pay you
back when you become Fuhrer.
[Roy]
Who told you?
[Ed] Lieutenant
Hawkeye told me...
And she told me
about Ishval, too.
Fullmetal.
Go on and keep
that money for now...
but you will pay me back.
Alright, and
when that day comes
I'll borrow some more change...
And pay that back when
this country's a democracy.
But when that day comes,
I'm gonna ask to borrow
even more money from you.
You're not planning
to let me off the hook
for a very long time, are you?
Now you get it...
And you better not worry
the lieutenant, either.
Thanks for giving us a ride.
Sure... See ya later.
You took long enough.
I was getting tired of waiting.
Hey.
It's Roy! Well I'll
be damned! Long time!
Hello, Vanessa...
You're looking well.
[Madam Christmas] My, has
it been a blue moon already?
[Roy] Well good evening
to you, Madam Christmas.
How're you holding up, Roy?
I'm barely holding up at all...
I was hoping you
could cheer me up.
You wanna drink?
[Roy] It's probably
not the best idea...
I just got out of the hospital.
But I could use something
special... Eh, Madam?
My pleasure.
General Grumman,
you have an outside call
from a Madam
Christmas in Central.
Oh?
Please, sir... you really
shouldn't be giving out
our secret line to civilians.
Not too bad for
an old fart like me.
The ladies still come a
callin' for my services.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
You lost your arm...
You couldn't protect the prince.
[Fu] And look at you now.
[Slap!!]
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
How dare you call yourself
a member of the chosen clan!
Cut it out, old man,
she hasn't recovered yet...!
I told you to stop!
[Fu] It's really gone.
Your arm... You lost your arm.
[Lan Fan] Please forgive me,
Grandfather... I'm sorry.
[Fu] You fool.
You damn fool.
[Ed] I promised Lan Fan
that I would introduce her
to an automail engineer.
We decline.
We appreciate
such a kind gesture...
but you've already
helped us enough...
We can find an engineer
on our own if we must.
[Al] But... We have
to do something.
The enemy has now clearly
seen Lan Fan's face...
We refuse to risk the life
of your engineer friend.
Alright then... Thank you.
You're the only reason that my
granddaughter is still alive...
You have my gratitude.
What...?
Do I look like the kind of
doctor that wants gratitude?
Thanks, Doctor Knocs...
Thank you for saving me.
Eh... Just clear out already...!
I'm not such a pushover
that I'm gonna let you
take my bed for an extra night.
[Knocs] Now get out.
[Fu] The emperor's health is
only growing worse each day.
We don't have much
time to find the prince...
But he must return to Xing with
the means for immortality...
Let's go.
Right.
I promise... I'll seek
out the evil here...
Remember us... we will return.
I'll always be indebted to
you for taking care of me.
Thanks, Doctor Knocs...
Thank you for saving me.
Treating me like
a real doctor...
What's the world coming to?
Yeah, yeah...
Whadda ya want?
Uh. Good evening, Dad...
Good to see you.
It's been a while...
How are you?
[Knocs] Fine...
[Knocs' Son] We were in
the area, so we thought...
Well you sure have
grown up... And you, uh...
It looks like you've
lost some weight.
I think both of us have.
How's work going...?
Keeping you busy?
Yeah... I'm surrounded
by corpses as usual...
Well... I actually
spent the last few days
treating some live patients.
It's absurd, huh...?
Just try to picture
me saving lives.
Hey, Dad...? I...well,
I wanna become a doctor.
[Knocs' Son] I know that you've
been haunted by the things
that you were ordered
to do in Ishval...
No matter what...
You never gave up
on helping people...
That takes courage...
For that... For being a
doctor... I love you...
You stubborn jackass.
Come on in...
It's not gourmet or anything,
but I'll brew us up some coffee.
[Knocs' Son] Oh, man...
It's a disaster in here.
[Knocs' Wife] C'mon...
Why don't we try
to clean up a little
before he can tell us not to?
[Knocs] I don't know if you
actually exist or not, God...
but cut me some slack.
Even a guy like me
needs a break...
Just please let me
enjoy the happiness
of having a cup of
coffee with my family...?
[Official 2]
The battle is over...
Ishval is now
under our control...
And all thanks to you...
Well done, Major Kimblee.
[Official 1] So tell us...
How did the Stone work out?
It's beyond amazing...
It lets you bypass
the equivalent exchange
to harness an immense power.
[Official 2] Excellent...
Write up the details in
your formal report for us.
[Official 1] But we'll
need the stone back first.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
[Kimblee] Now let's see...
I guess this makes you
the only ones who know
that I'm in possession
of this stone.
Traitor!
[loud explosion; screams]
Ahh!
[Guard 3] What happened?!
[Guard 4] Was that a bomb?!
[Guard 5] What's going on?
Hahahahahaha!!
Visitors...
On your feet, Kimblee...
You've been released.
[Kimblee]
So who made this decision?
[Jailer] I didn't say
you could talk, Kimblee.
[Kimblee] Must've been
someone pretty high up.
Shut your mouth...
You must have some
kind of big connections
to avoid the death sentence...
It makes me sick.
Nope, no connections...
I just deserve to go free.
[Jailer]
You really are psychotic...
What kind of political
move is this...?
Letting a nut job like you out.
Y'know, Warden... I appreciate
you taking care of me.
I hope I never see you again.
Just my way of saying thanks.
What is this...
I can't get it off! Help me!
Don't do this to me!
Kimblee, please!
[metal spring sound]
Tweet! Tweet!
It's nothing but
a harmless toy...
I thought you could give
it to your kid or something.
[Kimblee] Farewell, Warden.
Now then... what next?
It's been a while... Kimblee...
Congrats on the early release.
So I take it I have
you guys to thank?
Yep... We could use
a little extra help.
My first day out of jail
and I already have a job.
[Envy] You remember
Doctor Marcoh, don't you?
[Kimblee] The scientist
who created the
Philosopher's Stone...?
How could I ever forget him?
[Envy] It appears he's
escaped... Or, we think he has.
You think?
We're still sorting
out all of the details.
One of the Chimeras that
we had watching over him
has gone missing...
Marcoh's specialty was
transmuting living tissue...
He might've used the
Chimera in his place...
And if that
wasn't bad enough...
We think he might have escaped
with an Ishvalan
warrior known as Scar.
[Envy] Well how about it...?
Considering you were
the one responsible
for the extermination and all.
You do have a point...
It's inexcusable if
I've let a survivor crawl
out of my path of destruction.
[Envy] You're free to
kill Scar if you want...
But we do need Marcoh alive.
You released me just
for this little errand?
After you've nabbed
Marcoh for us,
there's a certain little town
we'll be asking you
to wipe off the map.
That's your kind of job, right?
It's remarkable
how cruel you are.
It's been too long
since I've used this.
[Envy] I don't know if that one
is going to be
enough for this job.
[Kimblee] A new stone...?
Did you use more
Ishvalans to make it?
We actually used
Dr. Marcoh's assistants
who helped make the
first stone for us.
Your cruelty's infinite.
Why didn't you kill
me back there...?
After all I've done...
We haven't finished our
conversation yet, Marcoh.
Tell me everything you
know about Kimblee... Also...
You might be able to
help me decipher some
of the research notes
my brother left behind.
Research notes?
[Scar] Before he died,
my brother told me
there was something strange
about this country's alchemy...
His notes should explain why.
You are apparently
skilled with alchemy...
Can you tell me
what he meant?
He said that our
alchemy was strange...?
I don't know.
Sir...
[Yoki] That little girl
was able to find us.
Looks like you made
it out, Mr. Scar!
[May Chang]
Do we have a new companion?
He's not our companion...
His name is Marcoh.
[Scar] He created the
Philosopher's Stone
and he killed my
people to do it.
The Philosopher's
Stone...? Immortality!
Mr. Marcoh...!
Please teach me how
to create the Stone...!
How did you make it...?
I'm begging you to show me!
No... I can't.
Quiet!
You shouldn't
desire such things.
[muffled pain]
[painful screams]
Argghh!!
[Scar] I only
destroyed the surface...
You can stop the
bleeding, can't you?
Right!
[Scar] It will be
easier for us to travel
if your face is unrecognizable.
It's time to leave.
Huh...? Where are we going?
We need to get to the place
where I hid my
brother's research notes.
[Scar] The north.
[Narrator] A hidden
figure emerges
from its disguise of innocence.
But it continues
to smile sweetly
as it patiently
waits for the flames
that will ravage
the city of Central.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 32...
"The Fuhrer's Son."
Is it true that
ignorance is bliss...?
Or is it a freshly dug grave?