Haruka-chan... it's okay.
Nayu-chan...
Don't rush it...
Tie!
So that's the bra unhooking race I came
up with when I couldn't sleep one night.
How about we present it for the culture festival?
There's no way that it'll be approved for the culture festival!
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Stick Out Your Chest
Timpani, you're falling behind.
Oh no, it's crooked. What should we do?
With a bit over here...
Please stay up, please stay up, please stay up...!
As I said, in the culture festival lots of people will see us.
If you're not careful, the boys will come looking for something erotic!
It'll be fine.
I have a great idea.
What, you ask... I'll call it the Thrilling Bras for Boys Corner!
That will probably attract an extraordinary crowd.
The best way to understand underwear is to actually wear it.
Even "men's bra" exist.
"Men's bra"?
Yes! It's a brassier marketed as underwear for guys.
Apparently, wearing one will create affection.
Senpai!
Tamaki...
From now on, can you help me put my bra on?
Yes, I'd be happy to!
W-What?
Don't stare at me...
Oi! You're imagining something strange right now, aren't you?!
Hey, Amahara-san, do you have any idea-?
Are you about to pull off your finishing move?!
Merely an exercise.
What's the matter all of a sudden?
Nothing really.
It shouldn't matter what it is.
By the way, I can't attend society activities for a while.
I have to prepare for the photo shoot.
Photo shoot?
My mother's maker is about to release a new line of teens' underwear.
And so I'm going to be their catalogue model.
Model? Amazing!
This is the first time I've heard of it.
Pretty incredible!
Your mother's an underwear maker?
Perhaps I didn't tell you?
She's the president of Orarisu apparel makers.
Eh?! Orarisu- you mean that Orarisu?!
You know about it?
Of course I do!
Orarisu's underwear has distinct and stylish designs!
Amahara-san, please!
Invite me to the photo shoot!
Please!
Pweeease!
I guess I have no choice.
If you're so eager to come, you can help out.
With all kinds of things...
Thank you! I'll do anything!
Well then, I'd like you to push them up firmly with your skills.
Is this the thing they call a "push-up bra" I've heard about?
Amahara-san, don't push me...
Well, it's cramped in here!
This is the first time I've seen one...
Really now?
Indeed, it's something you wouldn't need, Shiraishi-san.
That's not what I meant...
Hmm, so there're pads inside it?
With this, it pushes up from below.
Then the pads on the opposite side lift up the chest and create cleavage.
It's kind of high tech, huh?
There's nothing high tech about it. Hurry up and put it on.
Ah, right.
All right! I'm done.
Hold on.
What is this?
Is this all the pushing it can do?
You say that, but...
Ah, Amahara-san, you don't have a lot of extra skin on the front or back...
Well, it'll suffice.
If I leave it on like this, my breasts will grow, right?
Eh? I'm not sure that it'll make them grow...
What? You wanted to make your breasts grow?
N-Not at all!
I want to look my best for the photo shoot, that's all!
Get out!
Here overflows the light clothing that wraps a maiden's soft fair skin!
P-Pardon, are you searching for something?
Searching indeed!
My request is for underwear befitting these costumes!
I'm afraid we don't have any...
Oh how we have searched, only to find darkness!
Our days of hope have so swiftly vanished!
Angela! Do not forget.
Wherever you reach out your hand, I will be there!
Sir Charles, you are the very light that shines through the darkness!
Bravo, Angela! Bravo, Charles!
Those are our school uniforms...
They're not the type I would like to get to know.
I'm terribly sorry, but determining from this illustration would be difficult.
Oh, my beloved Angela!
Let us join our hearts together, and overcome this tribulation!
Excuse me?
Excuse me!
Underwear that would fit with this, hmm...
Thou art...?
Nayu-chan! Amahara-san is calling you!
My discussion's not over yet-
Whenever you discuss underwear, there's no end to it!
Okay...
Bust up! Bust Massage
One, two, cross, cross,
circle, circle, three, four.
Build pectoral muscles and bust up!
Bust up! Diet
Sign: Underwear Appreciation Society, activities in progress
Plus minus zero...
Hold it, what's going on?
We've been working so hard, but they're not growing.
How about you try pulling them out?
With a vacuum cleaner or something.
There's no way I'd do something so stupid!
Plus minus zero...
She really did the vacuum thing.
They say stimulating female hormones works.
Like looking at pictures of macho men and stuff.
That sounds stupid!
You're full of idiotic ideas, aren't you?
Plus minus zero...
She really did the macho thing.
It's tomorrow!
We did everything we could, so it's okay. It'll be fine!
Of course. There's no need for you to tell me.
But still...
You people helped quite a bit.
Isn't youth wonderful?
But what are you doing about the culture festival?!
I can't wait to go to tomorrow's photo shoot!
Amahara-san really did her best.
To be honest, it's my first time seeing her trying so hard.
My opinion about her has changed!
Up until now, she hasn't cared-
You've been selected
for the Kyoto office, right?
Good job. Congrats!
Keigo-san? It's burning, Keigo-san.
Be careful!
Ah, I can't wait to go to tomorrow's photo shoot!
Exposure's okay.
Quite a bit of tension here, eh?
It's completely different from when we take pictures with digital cameras.
Of course it is.
Nice to meet you.
I am Kiyono's mother, Amahara Reika.
I've heard about all of you from my daughter.
Thank you for letting us come today!
I love underwear,
and my brother is actually in the underwear business, too.
Hmm...
Hayama-san right?
Yes!
Could your older brother possibly be Paradiso's underwear designer Hayama Keigo-kun?
I believe he was with Jewelleries originally.
Yes.
Jewelleries?
Ah, are you prepared?
It's Hayama-san's grandmother's brand.
The designs were all wonderful.
It was an excellent brand.
Thank you very much!
Let's get some test shots!
Hmm, you're a bit stiff.
Right, that's the spirit.
Now then, let's get some close-ups of the chest area.
Turn your body...
Look this way.
Ah, Suzuki-san!
My, are you finished?
Thanks to you, somehow.
Hmm?
Isn't the bra loose?
Eh?
It really is! It's loose.
How could this happen- the size isn't right.
Eh? But on the paperwork we received-
Kiyono, did you really put yourself down as one size larger?
Excuse me, please take a break.
What's all this?
It looks like it's becoming a big problem.
Honestly, you're making yourself look dull...
Come now, let's get you changed quick-
Kiyono...?!
Amahara-san...
Amahara-san, may I come in?
This is terrible.
Amahara-san...
Even though he came...
I'm going home.
Y-You're going home?
Everyone's waiting for you!
That's right.
To abandon your mission violates the warrior's-
Leave me alone!
What I do has nothing to do with you, right?!
Hey, what's with that attitude?!
What are these?
Those are trial products.
They're not meant for me.
But these would be better for you...
What? Those unsophisticated ones?
But they look comfortable and-
That doesn't matter at all.
If a man doesn't think it's cute, there's no meaning to it!
But we're too young for that kind of underwear.
Are you calling me childish?
That's not it-
I just think that these would fit you better.
Absolutely not.
Wearing those would only disappoint men.
A decorated cell phone...
I know!
I think that it'd be fun to make your own underwear cute by decorating it.
Please!
I see...
I understand.
I'll leave it up to you girls.
I'll have anything you need prepared quickly.
Thank you very much!
Cute!
Look at this!
I think this would look great.
You've got to be joking. That's far too childish!
It's all right.
I think this strap would fit better.
Very cute!
I wonder if there's anything here that would match that colour.
That's it!
This ribbon's cute too.
We could use it as decoration.
Why don't we try matching it with lace?
We could one-point this one.
Ah, that's nice too!
It accidentally caught my eye, I wasn't really-
Hurry up!
Almost there, almost!
Coordinating your own underwear, hmm?
This could make a nice magazine page.
It's not like I don't understand your feelings.
It takes courage to bare yourself in front of others.
Especially girls like ourselves.
What exactly are you trying to say?
Well, uh... just try your best.
Finished!
How cute!
It looks fantastic on you!
Really? It's not unsophisticated?
Nope, nope!
It doesn't look childish?
Quite nice!
It fits her- it feels mature and it's cute!
That's right.
She might even look more mature than before!
Good work, everyone!
Wow, I got some great pictures.
Thank you very much.
Amahara-san, you did great!
How was our coordination?
It's pretty good considering you made it.
Come now...
Give your thanks to Hayama-san.
Thanks.
Allow me to express my gratitude as well.
Thanks to you, I've come to understand what kind of underwear teens want to wear these days.
No, I couldn't have... It feels like I did something disrespectful.
Not at all.
As expected of Hayama-kun's sister.
I was delighted.
Ah, right.
Anyway, it seems Hayama-kun, young as he is,
was chosen for a large project.
Could you congratulate him for me?
Sure, thank you very much.
Also, if it's all right,
I'd like to present you all with some of our trial products.
Is that all right?!
Yes. They're in the waiting room.
Choose whichever one you like.
Thank you very much!
Let's go and have a fitting!
Wait, Nayu-chan, there's no need to rush-
I wonder if she'll end up leaving for Kyoto as well.
Haven't you heard?
Hayama-san's older brother...
No...
Isn't this incredible?!
Looking at this confirms her sense of style, huh?!
M-Master! Did you go to the photo shoot as well?
There's no reason I would have gone!
And who's a "master"?!
Hey, isn't that her?
Yeah! My heart's kind of pounding...
Even the way she walks is fabulous.
Should we get her autograph?
We saw the magazine!
The Underwear Appreciation Society is amazing!
No way...
Isn't it just going to their heads?
Yeah, they're just the bra-panties club.
Can you believe that they're still active?
At last I find you, Angel of the Cloth!
With your shining wings and dazzling eyes, carry us to heaven!
We're from the Acting Club and we need your help.
Basically, we found out that the girl who spoke to us before in the underwear department...
...is running the Underwear Society from this magazine.
So what do you want from us?
Please observe this.
This is that thing from before...
We had leapt into the Shangri-la of the Arts,
only to lose our direction on the way!
Ah, we are but lost strangers!
Wandering without method, despair filled our days when...
Before us, you descended!
You Angels of the Cloth!
We've created a rough sketch of our costumes,
but we know nothing about underwear.
Then we found out about you... and here we are.
Sir Charles, will angels and humans be able to understand each other?
Angela, there is nothing to fear.
For your pure heart, they will surely answer us!
Yes, Sir Charles!
So could you help us if we cooperate in the culture festival?
That means we can be in the culture festival...
Nayu-chan...
It's the obvious answer, right?
Yup!
I look forward to working together with you!
We did it, huh, Nayu-chan?!
Let's all do our best, okay?
And so it was decided that we'd be in the culture festival!
Hmm? That's excellent.
It's finally time for the age of the Underwear Society.
It might be...
Ah right!
Something great happened for you, right?
Eh?
Yesterday, I heard from Amahara-san's mother...
You've been chosen for a large project, right?
So you heard about it?
It means I will be going to Kyoto.
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
Hey, don't boys ever feel like
wearing underwear with lace or frills?
There's no way they would!
Why's that?
Yeah, I wonder...
You two aren't going to get anywhere.
Afternoon
with
Her
Look forward to the next Chu-Bra.