I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Truth About the Historic
Classic Lit Club
Classic Lit Club President
Sekitani Jun
Off-limits
"I'm sure that ten years from now,
I won't regret spending this time."
"It was in no way a heroic tale"
"Sacrifices"
"Offering"
Itoigawa Yoko
Koriyama Yoko
"Yoko"
Geshi ('Height of Summer')
When the sun waxeth hottest,
and the day is at its longest
Hyouka
When the sun waxeth hottest,
and the day is at its longest
Librarian's Office
Rally
"On strike! Right is on our side!
Teachers accept our demands!"
Expulsion
Kamiyama
Sekitani ('Kanya')
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Committing a Cardinal Sin