If it's the way you suspect, Hotaro,
it would mean that at the very least,
our Kanyasai came at the expense
of someone's high school life.
Still, I'm surprised.
At what?
By the very fact that you even
tried to solve this mystery.
I'm surprised, myself.
Ever since we enrolled at Kami High,
you've solved a number of mysteries.
I know the reason why you'd
go to all that trouble, too.
It's for Chitanda-san, right?
It's Chitanda's fault.
That works, too. But today was different.
You could have bailed out on us, Hotaro.
The responsibility for unraveling that mystery
today was split between us four ways.
If you had said "I don't know" and taken off,
I don't think anyone would have said a thing.
That being said, why would you go so far as to lock
yourself in the bathroom to look for the answer?
Was that for Chitanda-san, too?
It's because I've finally gotten
tired of being so gray.
As far as Chitanda goes, no one
is less energy efficient than she is.
Being a club president,
creating an anthology, taking tests,
and solving riddles from the past?
I'm amazed she isn't exhausted.
You and Ibara, too. It's highly
wasteful the way you do things.
Well, that may be true.
On the other hand, the grass is
always greener on the other side.
Sometimes when I watch you,
I start to feel restless.
And I want to be relaxed.
But... even so, I...
don't enjoy doing anything.
That's why I thought at least...
well, you know...
I'd try reasoning it out, and let myself
get involved, the way you guys do.
Well, say something!
Hotaro...
Hotaro, were you envious of our rosy lives?
Maybe.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away
the awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Truth About the
Historic Classic Lit Club
Rosy life, huh?
Is that what a rosy life is?
I don't know.
Chitanda, who's on a quest
through the past...
Sekitani Jun, who stood
up for the Kanyasai...
Classic Lit Club President Sekitani Jun
Is that what I want to become?
Do I really want a rosy life?
I don't know.
What is a rosy life in the first place?
Speaking of rosy lives, there's Sis.
"I'm sure that ten years from now,
I won't regret spending this time."
When I'm 25, how will I look back
on my life ten years before?
Sekitani Jun wouldn't have
had any regrets. But I...
Yes, Oreki residence.
Huh? Hotaro?
Is that you, Sis? So you are alive.
How rude. You think I can't
survive a mugging or two?
So that's the kind of trouble
you got yourself into.
I just reached Pristina yesterday.
No problems with my health or finances.
I'll send you another letter
when I reach Sarajevo.
That's all I have to report.
How are things there?
Huh? Oh, we're making
an anthology. Hyouka.
Ah, yeah, Hyouka!
We're researching Sekitani Jun.
Sekitani Jun? There's a name
that takes me back.
So, his story is still going around.
Then, is "Kanyasai" still off-limits?
Off-limits
What was that?
That was such a tragedy, huh?
It sure put me off.
Off-limits? Tragedy? Put you off?
Hold on here, this is
Sekitani Jun we're talking about.
Yeah, I know. The
"kindhearted hero," right?
Are you sure you know who you mean?
No, apparently, I don't know.
Sis, tell me about Sekitani Jun.
I don't have enough time! Gotta go!
D... D... Damn you, Sis!
I'm not done yet.
The theory I presented to
Chitanda and the others is...
either incorrect, or insufficient.
I'm sure that ten years from now,
I won't regret spending this time.
If he is still alive,
would Sekitani Jun have any regrets
about his high school years?
I didn't think he'd have any reason to.
The "hero,"
who left high school as a martyr
for his and his friends' passion,
would have no reason to
lament falling on his sword.
Somewhere along the line
I convinced myself of that.
But is that really true?
To be driven from school
over a mere culture festival,
and have a whole phase
of his life altered like that...
High school life is all roses, after all.
But is the intense rosiness of having that
high school life cut off midway through...
something you can still call rosy?
That can't be true.
Forgiving everything after you've
sacrificed yourself for your friends?
It was in no way a heroic tale
I don't buy there being
too many heroes like that.
What's more, Sis called it a "tragedy."
Was Sekitani Jun's high school
life really that rosy?
I'm going to nail this down.
Ah, Fuku-chan!
Hey. Mayaka, did you get
called in by Hotaro, too?
Mm-hm. He said to come to the club room after
school, because he had something to discuss.
Imagine, Hotaro taking the
trouble to call anybody in.
In my memory, this is
an unprecedented event.
I'm busy with my Manga Club, too.
Hello. Thanks again for yesterday.
Mm-mm, I had fun, too.
I'm more curious about where Hotaro is.
Um...
Looks like he's here.
You're all here.
What did you want to discuss?
I have something to add
to yesterday's matter.
I think this will put it to rest.
Huh? Listen to you.
Oreki-san, it sounds as though
there's something more to this matter
that I need to know about.
It's all right. We should be able to
pretty well fill in the gaps today.
Okay.
What do you mean, Oreki? Fill in what gaps?
By gaps, I mean gaps. I'm working
to amend something that is incomplete
to make it more complete.
Incomplete? Hotaro, are you saying
your theory was incomplete?
I don't know. It might be off
in the wrong direction,
or it might not have gone far enough.
You don't know? And yet
you still called us all in?!
Unbelievable.
Just listen.
We should have given
more weight to Hyouka.
It clearly states in the foreword
that Sekitani Jun's story
is in no way a heroic tale.
We read that yesterday
and excluded it, didn't we?
We said that ultimately, that was
the writer's own mental image.
Yeah. But it's also possible
that we were misled.
Well, when you start saying that...
Also,
there's this passage about "the conflicts,
the sacrifices, and even his smile."
Are we sure "sacrifices"
here really means "sacrifices"?
Sacrifices
It can also be read as "offering," right?
is spelled differently, right?
Offering
It starts with the character for "alive."
No, you can write it as "sacrifice"
but read it as "offering."
Originally, the two meant the same thing.
Leave it to our academic
all-star to bottom-line it.
Okay, so we get that there's
a different way to read it,
but unless you're the person who wrote it,
there's no way to tell which way
is the right way, is there?
Indeed there is. We could always ask them.
Ask them?
The person who wrote the
foreword... Koriyama Yoko.
45 years ago, she was a
1st-year in high school,
and today, she'd be 60 or 61.
You searched for this woman?
I didn't have to. She's right nearby.
Isn't that right, miss library assistant?
Ah! Is that right?!
Yep.
What's right?
What do you mean, she's right?
Our librarian, Itoigawa-sensei, right?
Itoigawa Yoko-sensei... her
maiden name is Koriyama, right?
Itoigawa Yoko
Koriyama Yoko
That's right. The "Yo" that spells "Yoko"
Yoko
isn't a common one, right?
Not to mention that Itoigawa-sensei
is just the right age.
Add to that the way she reacted when she
found out that we were the Classic Lit Club.
You really are weird, Oreki.
Even though I've been next
to her this whole time,
I didn't notice that when
I heard the name.
You sure you don't want to let Chi-chan
peek around inside your head?
Like I said before, I just luck
into these flashes of brilliance.
That's why I don't need
Chitanda dissecting me.
Th-Then, if we ask Itoigawa-sensei
about all of this...
we'll find out what
happened 45 years ago.
Why it wasn't a heroic tale,
why the cover picture is what it is,
why it has the odd-sounding
title of Hyouka, as well as...
what happened to your uncle.
But do you have any proof
that it really is Itoigawa-sensei?
I wasn't born yesterday. In fact,
I've already confirmed it.
From her, directly?
Yeah. She said that when she was
a 2nd-year, she was the club president.
I also set up an appointment
to talk to her.
Come on, it's almost time.
Let's go to the library.
You are awfully fired up, aren't you?
I guess so.
Geshi ('Height of Summer')
When the sun
waxeth hottest, and the day is at its longest
Hyouka
Itoigawa-sensei!
Ah, the Classic Lit Club.
I'm sorry, but I still have
a little work left.
Would it be okay if we spoke out here?
I'll give you a hand.
Thank you, Ibara-san.
I understand you have
something you'd like to ask me.
Yes. Before we do, though, I'd like to confirm
something once again, in front of the others.
Itoigawa-sensei, your maiden
name is Koriyama, right?
Yes.
Then, you are the one
who wrote this, right?
Yes, I am. Though I'm surprised
that this is still around here.
I have a fair idea of what
you'd like to ask me.
You'd like to know more about that
movement that took place 45 years ago.
Bingo. She does know, all right.
But why would you ask now about
something that happened so long ago?
I thought everyone had
forgotten it by now.
Yes, if Chitanda here wasn't such a wild curiosity
monkey, taking an interest in every little thing,
we probably never
would have come upon it.
Wild curiosity monkey?
I beg your pardon. I meant junkie.
O-Oh, my! I mean, a
junkie, of all things...!
And why are you so interested
in that movement?
Because Sekitani Jun...
is my uncle.
Oh, is that right? Sekitani Jun-san...
That name brings back memories.
Is he doing well?
I do not know. He has
gone missing in India.
Oh, really? I've always wanted
to see him once again.
I want to see him once again, too.
Itoigawa-sensei, please tell us,
what happened 45 years ago?
Why was the incident involving
my uncle "not a hero's tale"?
Why is the Classic Lit Club's
anthology named Hyouka?
How much of Oreki-san's
supposition is correct?
Oreki-kun's supposition?
What would that be?
Sensei,
Oreki took some fragmentary
information and tied it together,
inferring what took place 45 years ago.
Please have a listen to what he has to say.
Yes, well, why don't you tell
me all about it in my office.
Librarian's Office
Indeed. And that's why you
assume that his expulsion
was put off until October?
Yes. That is the extent of my conjecture.
You put together this story from
only the material you have here?
I just brought together
everyone else's reasoning.
I'm astounded.
Am I way off base?
No, it's like you witnessed it yourself.
Oreki-kun, what you say
is almost entirely true.
What more would you like to ask me?
Well, Hotaro says that there is
something about it that's incomplete.
There is one thing that
I would like to ask.
Did Sekitani Jun willingly take the hit
for all the other students?
Did he act on behalf of the student body,
heroically holding his head high,
and forfeit his rosy high school
life to leave the school?
You really do see right
through things, huh?
Yes... This was such a long time ago,
but I still remember it quite well.
At the time, Kamiyama
High School's culture festival
was almost like the whole
purpose in life for all of us.
You might say that the energy that
was surging throughout Japan
had taken on the form of
Kami High's culture festival.
However, the year that I enrolled,
the movement went too far,
and came this close to
becoming a full-blown riot.
That year, the principal
apparently dropped a bombshell.
"We can't content ourselves with being a
small-time school in a sleepy little town."
Everyone thought that he meant
the culture festival was abolished.
He unilaterally gave notice
that the culture festival schedule
was being shortened from
the usual five days to two days.
That acted as the trigger
that set off a huge uproar.
Rally
The whole school was on edge.
There were banners, and
public speeches, and then,
the movement got to the point where
they tried to assert their collective will.
They must have been pretty serious.
Well, it was a world that we
couldn't even imagine now.
It wasn't as glorious as all that.
The truth is, we were acting like
our toys had been taken from us,
and we were throwing a
tantrum because of it.
Oh, no...
Well, looking back on it now,
I think I can say that.
So, a countermovement against shortening
the culture festival was organized.
Nobody came forward to be the leader.
We were afraid of being punished,
as pathetic as that sounds.
The one who ended up
drawing the short straw
was Chitanda-san's uncle, Sekitani Jun-san.
It was someone else who
actually ran the show,
but that person never made his name public.
Eventually, the plan to shorten
the culture festival fell through,
but eagerly worked up and whipped
into a frenzy by our protest movement,
we went too far.
Teachers accept our demands!
On strike! Right is on our side!
As part of our movement,
the students were boycotting classes,
and when it had reached
a full head of steam,
we boosted morale with a bonfire.
That was the night the incident happened.
A fire broke out in the
combat sports building.
The building was partially
destroyed under the fire hoses.
That was something that
the school could not excuse.
The school didn't have
the police intervene,
but later, when the incident
was called into question,
there wasn't a single student
who could rebut them.
As a result, the school decided to make an
example of the nominal leader of the movement,
Sekitani-san, by expelling him.
Expulsion
We, the students, could not do anything,
and just watched on as it happened.
Nonetheless, Sekitani-san
remained quiet, right up to the end.
You asked if Sekitani-san came forward by choice
as a martyr for the other students, didn't you?
You know the answer to that now, right?
Several years passed,
and bit by bit, the culture
festival was shortened.
It now runs for three days, right?
That's the end of the story. Is there
anything else you'd like to ask?
So then, the cover of the anthology
depicts what happened back then.
The dog is the school,
the rabbits are the students,
and the rabbit that is taking the dog
down with him is Sekitani Jun.
Is the reason why the combat sports building
is by far the oldest facility at Kami High
because it was rebuilt at the time?
That's right. 20 years ago,
when the school buildings were rebuilt,
the combat sports building
was not yet that old,
so it was left as it is.
Um, Sensei,
you don't use the term "Kanyasai," do you?
By any chance, does the
"Kanya" in "Kanyasai"
Kamiyama
stand not for
"Kamiyama," but for "Sekitani"?
Sekitani ('Kanya')
Fuku-chan, what do you mean?
The origin of the term "Kanyasai."
To honor their hero, they took "Sekitani-sai"
and switched the reading to make it "Kanyasai."
Oh...
But calling it that is misleading.
Sekitani Jun didn't become
a hero because he wanted to.
If people knew that, they wouldn't
use the term "Kanyasai," huh?
Is that true?
Yes. That name was banned
within the Classic Lit Club.
Sensei, do you know why my uncle
gave the name Hyouka
to the Classic Lit Club's anthology?
No. Sekitani-san, sensing that
he was going to be expelled,
was uncharacteristically insistent
on selecting that name.
He said it was the most that he could do.
But I'm sorry,
I don't know the meaning behind it.
You don't know?
Do you really not know?
Are you saying that
nobody ever interpreted it?
That... ridiculous message?
Oreki, what is it?
Don't you know? What we just
heard should make it clear.
Hyouka is just some silly wordplay.
Wordplay?
Sekitani Jun made sure to express
how he felt to the Classic Lit Club,
all the way down to its
successors, including us.
He put it right in the anthology's name.
What do you mean? Oreki-san,
do you know what Hyouka means?
Do you really know?
Tell us, Hotaro.
Hotaro?
What do you get if you translate
Hyouka into English?
"Ice cream," you mean?
Ice cream... That's what the message is?
Like I said, it's wordplay.
Um, guys?
Uh...
The real statement that
Sekitani Jun was making is this.
I... remember.
I asked my uncle what Hyouka meant.
When I did, he said to me...
Yes, he told me to be strong.
That someday, if I was ever weak...
If ever... Yes, if the day ever came
when I couldn't even scream...
If that ever happened,
I would be eaten alive...
I was so scared of being
eaten alive that I started crying.
Thank goodness. I remembered.
Now, I can let my uncle go for good.
All thanks to you, Oreki-san.
Thank you very much, Oreki-san.
Yeah, well, I just chanced upon it.
Right. You chanced upon it!
"Ice cream."
"I scream."
So, I drew up a rough draft
and schedule for the anthology.
This is how you make a rough draft, is it?
This is amazing, Mayaka-san.
I-It is?
But where did you learn
how to do something like this?
That doesn't really matter, does it?
Hey,
about this "The Case of
the Kindhearted Hero:
The Truth That Was Hidden
For 45 Years" special feature...
What?
Why am I in charge of writing it?
You're the one who solved the mystery,
so it's only fair that you write it, right?
It runs for the most pages.
Well of course it does.
After all, it is our featured article.
Is that all right, Oreki-san?
If it's too hard for you,
I can try to write it.
Oh, that sounds...
No, Chi-chan! This is about the only
time that he's good for anything!
Yeah, yeah, we have to work him hard, huh?
Hmph.
No complaining, Oreki, just
start thinking of an outline!
Now, Fuku-chan, about the
column you'll be in charge of...
You know, it's surprising.
What is?
The anthology article.
You ended up accepting it after all.
I wouldn't say I accepted it
so much as I couldn't get out of it.
Although, I guess it might count
as a tribute to Sekitani Jun.
Speaking of things that are surprising...
Yes?
Earlier, I suggested that you ask
for Satoshi and Ibara's help, right?
You were reluctant at first,
so why did you suddenly decide to?
Oh, that.
At the time, you said that if I
didn't solve my uncle's mystery,
someday, the statute of
limitations might run out.
It's true that ten years
from now, I might not care,
but the feelings that I'm having now...
They're something that
I don't want to think...
will mean nothing in the future.
After all, it's the present
that I'm living in.
Which is why...
I'm sorry.
I'm still not sure I understand it.
That's okay.
It's the same for me.
Well, anyhow, good job.
Right. Well then...
"Dear Oreki Tomoe-dono,
I'm sending this letter to ask a question.
How much did you know
about the Classic Lit Club?
What was your intention in making
me join the Classic Lit Club?
You know the style of person I am.
Right, an energy conservationist.
If I hadn't joined the Classic Lit Club,
I never would have even
reconsidered my style.
Did you anticipate that, by me
joining the Classic Lit Club,
I would be shaken up the way I was?
And as for Hyouka...
Now that I know about the Sekitani Jun
incident through the anthologies,
I've come to think that this
style of mine isn't so bad.
I mean, relatively speaking, that is.
But then, Sis, that would
almost make you...
No, that's silly.
Consider everything I've written
here to be an update from me.
Have a nice trip.
Thanks for the advice.... Oreki Hotaro."
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "Committing a Cardinal Sin."
Committing a Cardinal Sin