At last...
At last, I've become Numero Uno!
O-Ouch...
Wait, not good, not good!
Pretty pathetic of you to get swallowed up by the Egogy you were trying to swallow.
Mammo!
Ira!
Save me, please!
We can't! It's too late!
That is unmistakably him!
The one whose immense power once conquered this very universe!
The dark monster that even Cure Empress's Precures failed to eliminate!
Indeed.
I am the Proto-Selfish.
And I have finally reawakened after ten thousand years!
I shall once again enshroud the world in darkness
and rule over all life as I see fit!
We'll never, ever let you!
As long as we're here,
You shall not do as you please!
As long as breath yet remains in our bodies,
We'll fight with every ounce of strength we have!
Mana!
Prez!
You mustn't.
Please escape.
But...
Don't worry.
Let's believe in those girls.
I'll fight too!
Regina!
I want to settle the score myself!
Let's go, girls.
This is our final battle!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
From Me to You!
My Sweet Heart!
Rosetta Reflection!
Girls, follow my lead!
I'll handle this!
Holy Sword!
Thanks, Sword!
Oh no you don't!
Regina!
Rosetta! Sword!
Twinkle Diamond!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Egogy!
Girls, are you all right?
Yeah, nothing serious.
Just a scratch.
It's too much!
I can't go on!
You're down quick!
Where'd that motivation go?
I was joking, silly.
I'm with Mana, so I won't quit until it's all over!
Regina...
Let's go, girls.
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Nice try!
Begone!
We're not safe here. We have to run!
Run where?
Bro?
If those girls lose, the whole world'll be engulfed in darkness!
So I'd rather see their fight through to the end!
Then I'm stayin' too!
Don't die on me, Mana!
Rikka, hold on!
Alice, you can't lose!
Makoto, stand up!
Agwee, Wejeena, hold on!
Mana, stay strong!
You're our only hope!
If you give up, it's the end of the world!
Fear not.
Your friends and family will soon join you.
The world... nay, the universe...
all belong to me!
Do you realize what you're saying?
If the world is yours alone, you can do whatever you want...
but if you're all alone in the world,
you won't be able to cut in line or jaywalk.
What?!
Because what selfishness comes down to...
is bothering others with your actions.
If there's nobody else in the world,
you can't truly be selfish!
Silence!
Silence, silence!
You dare lecture me?!
Cure Heart!
You're the selfish one!
I'll tear out your insolent psyche myself!
Agonize before my strongest Egogy!
You can't, Mana!
Keep your heart strong!
Don't give him your psyche!
Mana!
Stooooooop!
I've finally taken a Precure's psyche!
The entire world is now mine!
Mana!
Get back here!
Sorry I worried you, girls.
Looks like you wasted your time!
Even if we should lose our flesh and bones, our souls...
nay, our love is everlasting!
Please girls, lend me your strength.
Sure!
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Mana!
Cure Heart,
Parthenon Mode!
I won't be fooled!
How fast!
She's nothing like the Cure Heart I fought before!
Powerful emotions give people strength!
Any girl with a powerful enough emotion to protect others...
can become a Precure!
And that power can rival even our universe's Big Bang!
There were those that opposed me ten thousand years ago as well...
A team of girls that always stood up no matter how often they were knocked down!
Could it be...
that history is repeating itself?!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Indeed, history repeats itself!
As long as humans possess selfish, egotistical hearts,
I will always return.
Always, I tell you!
I know.
Even I have a selfish heart.
What?!
I've had times where I've been jealous or just wanted to run away.
But I think the pain and struggling that come with it...
can make people stronger.
Loo—
And even if I lose sight of my love,
I have my friends!
Loooo—
As long as I have friends by my side,
I'll always stand up and fight back!
Loove looove loooooooove!
What happened to us?
I remember these monsters appearing...
We've been saved!
Guess that wraps everything up!
But the princess will never return...
Trump Kingdom is finally at peace once again,
yet she'll never see it for herself!
Makoto...
Look!
Princess!
Ange!
Ann!
I'm sorry, Father, Jonathan.
I can no longer return to my previous form.
Both Regina and Aguri were filled with love,
causing them each to grow as individuals.
Don't worry!
I'll always be by Daddy's side!
I shall live to carry on your will!
Thank you...
Jonathan...
Ann...
I'm happy.
The love you gave me was more than I could ask for.
I'm happy too, Ann.
Cure Sword.
Princess!
You've been in great pain because of me.
But finding friends enabled you to resolve this conflict.
You have my heartfelt gratitude.
Your gratitude is fine, but...
all I ever wanted...
was to stay by your side!
Tears don't suit you.
Smile and let the world listen to your beautiful voice.
I can't!
If the world doesn't have you in it...
how could I ever smile again?
Makopi!
Do not be sad, Sword.
Princess...
Didn't I tell you to call me Ann?
My life force now lies within Ai.
So I'll always be watching over you.
Princess...
Thank you, everyone.
I truly mean it.
Makoto!
Ai...
I love you!
Whoa, what're you—
Lemme go!
Look at you now.
Pretty lame there, Bel.
It matters not.
I'll just build more power over another ten thousand year slumber.
What? Another ten thousand year nap?
Well...
those girls were still here.
What're you doing?
We're leaving.
I know.
I'm hungry.
Go dig through garbage.
What?
Shortly after that,
everyone started leading new lives.
Good morning!
'Sup!
Morning!
Morning, Jun!
Used to student council work yet?
I'm still far behind you, Prez.
Come on, aren't you the president now?
Sorry...
Hey, that ribbon is against the dress code!
Dress code?
What's that?
It's a code that—
Morning, Mana!
I had some trouble with my homework, so help me out!
Hey, Regina!
Need help with anything?
Charles!
If you insist...
King me.
What?!
Regina's father retired from the throne.
Chea's here!
Charles!
Thank you.
Rikka's studying even harder.
I don't want to regret not working hard enough!
Hundred Poets
Then what's this for?
Wait!
Don't touch that!
Cooking Class
Aguri started to get along with her classmates.
Yummy!
You could serve this at a restaurant!
Aguri, you could totally be a pastry chef!
Oh, you're too kind...
You've gotta come over and teach me this!
Me too!
Me three!
We're connected to Trump Kingdom by the portal King Selfish opened.
Everyone seems to be doing well.
You seem pretty busy too, Joe.
Well, I was elected to be the inaugural President of the Trump Republic.
The times have changed.
The kingdom Ann left has had much cultural exchange with the human world,
giving birth to a new country!
And just like that!
So this is the kingdom's automated cleaner that Makoto spoke of.
It's magnificent!
May we purchase one million of them?
O-One million?!
If you'd like, please sign this contract.
C-Certainly!
Makopi became a worldwide hit as a star from Trump Kingdom!
I always thought it strange.
Why do people in this world sing together so much?
Aren't songs supposed to be listened to in silence?
But since I met you, I've understood why.
It's wonderful to do things together!
Sing your heart out...
so your songs can touch theirs!
I will!
Thank you, everyone!
This is the finale!
Hello, Cure Heart speaking!
We have another request for you.
A giant satellite has fallen out of orbit and is headed straight for Oogai City!
You're late!
Sorry!
I guess you're taking requests from everyone now, Mana.
I suppose you can't help it.
You're a Happy Prince, after all.
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Okay!
Precure Love Link!
Precure Dress Up!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
It's the Precure's 10th anniversary show!
The warrior of love appears in the nick of time!
And her name is Cure Lovely!
I'm a real princess, so I call myself Cure Princess!
It's a story of love, courage, and kindness!
Hey now, don't forget the friendship and romance!
It's a new program filled with everything nice!
HappinessCharge Precure:
I Love Love!
The Birth of Cure Lovely!
We'll give everyone a full charge of happiness!
Thanks for watching!