Is that you, Sis?
I'm home!
Feel free to leap into my arms.
I'll pass.
Even though we've been apart for so long?
You're no fun.
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
To Be Needed
You brought this from South America?
Yeah! You wanted something, didn't you?
Not really.
Good morning. Up next is today's forecast.
How rare to see you watching TV.
What's wrong with the paper?
Water
A Pacific anticyclone ensures clear
weather over most of western Japan.
I don't feel like thinking right now.
You look like you've got time to spare.
Some areas may experience severely high
temperatures climbing over 33 degrees Celsius.
My schedule's packed today, actually.
Oh? What with?
Napping.
Please take precautions against heat exhaustion.
I know a part-time job that pays
you 5,000 yen just for sitting there.
And now, the rain forecast.
Well?
While it will be clear during the day, humid Pacific air masses may bring light showers in the evening.
You in or you out?
Then it's settled. I'll tell them you're in.
Tomorrow morning will bring cool temperatures typical of fall,
Here.
but it will heat up considerably during the day.
Don't forget to put some on while you're working.
Hello, this is Oreki.
Oh, Satoshi? It's been so long!
Yeah, I arrived just a little while ago.
Houtarou? Sure. Just a moment.
Houtarou, Satoshi's on the phone!
Houtarou, have you finished that book you borrowed from me?
If so, can I have it back?
Can I pick it up today?
Once I'm back from work.
Huh?
What? You? Working?!
Did the heat fry your brain?
I just went with the flow.
I'm filling in for some friend of
my sis as a lifeguard at the pool.
Ah, your sister. That explains it.
Seeing you breaking a sweat
would certainly be something.
I need to get going, so I'll catch you later.
Okay. I'll stop by later to see the legend at work.
Whatever. Bye.
Later.
Ice Cream
Open
Houtarou!
Hey. We're here!
I wasn't expecting all three of you.
I told them they could catch a glimpse of the rarest sight in the world.
Fuku, you meant this?
Yup! Houtarou working!
Honestly, it's quite a letdown.
Come on.
Now that we're here, let's enjoy ourselves.
I guess.
Now that we're here.
Hey, you!
You makin' eyes at my woman?!
Hey, don't.
I'm not—
Sir, please calm down.
What the hell?
May I never have to deal with troublemakers. Please.
Okay, I'm throwing it!
Here it comes!
Got it!
Nope.
Chitanda! Give it a good smack!
You're hopeless, Chi.
Penalty dare for Chitanda!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
We're ready!
Here we...
go!
My turn!
Sliding time!
Hey!
Shift's up. You can take a break.
Oreki.
Mind if we join you for lunch?
I would've made something nice if you
hadn't dragged us out at a moment's notice.
Address your complaints to Houtarou.
Why?
Come on. He's like a walking pile of laziness.
Then all of a sudden, he decides to work.
We couldn't miss this for the world.
Right, Houtarou?
But it's lots of fun getting everyone together like this, right?
I guess.
Too bad he still sticks out like a sore thumb.
What do you mean?
Houtarou. At a pool.
Can't argue with that.
You two are being mean.
Or Oreki in swimming gear.
Yeah!
Or just Houtarou in the sun!
Oreki in the sea!
Houtarou and summer!
Come on, stop it.
Right, Oreki?
Well, let's head back to the pool.
Right. I'll clean up the trash.
Then I'll return the chairs.
There.
Come on. Don't cry, now.
Let's go buy another one.
That startled me.
Yeah.
How do you like your job?
It's okay.
I'd like to try it too, one day.
They're so fast!
Do you think they're planning to become professional swimmers?
Some of them might end up winning gold medals.
Dunno about that.
If they're born to win one, they will.
Special people can do that.
Ordinary people can't.
Do you want to be special, Oreki?
Not really.
Come what may, I'm just an ordinary guy.
You are special, Oreki!
You're special to me!
Fukube and Mayaka are too!
Everyone who's close to me is special!
From your point of view, yeah, but I meant on a more gener—
What's wrong with that?
You don't have to worry about being special or ordinary compared to other people.
If there's just one person out there
who considers me special, I'm happy!
Uh, I mean—
Excuse me!
White Dew
As the shadows lengthen,
the grass glitters ivory with dew.
Hyouka
Wait!
You are special, Oreki!
What's wrong with that?
Oreki, shift's up!
Go take a break.
Um... Oreki.
There's something I just can't stop thinking about.
In fact, it's basically part of your job.
Do you see that lady in the red swimsuit?
When we finished lunch, I saw
something white on her left ear.
But it's not there now.
How did you even notice something like that?
Oh, it was just by chance.
So? What does that have to do with me?
Quite a lot, you know!
What if it was a stud or an earring?
If someone stepped on it, they might get hurt!
Oreki, could you help us search for it?
Across the entire pool grounds?
Are you serious?
Are you sure she had something on her ear?
Yes.
Then why don't you ask her before you go looking?
I'd like to do that, but...
she isn't exactly easy to approach.
It's not like you're asking her something dumb.
You'll be fine.
Then you go and ask her.
I'll pass.
Please, Oreki!
You're the lifeguard here, right?
Well, Houtarou?
I can't stop thinking about it!
Huh? The girl with that guy who flipped out?
Man, this is gonna be a pain.
I really don't want any trouble, so could you just look for it or something?
Yeah, but I can't do it alone.
Then I'll tell the other lifeguards to check the poolside.
Can you look in the pool?
Sure.
I'll help too!
Me too, of course!
Guess I gotta, huh?
Thanks.
But... however should we look for it?
We'll have a better chance if we split up.
That's right.
What do you think, Oreki?
Up to you.
Come on, show some spirit!
Indeed! It's time to earn your lifeguard's wage!
At least decide how we should split up.
Oh, fine. I'll take care of it.
Okay, the area around the stairs is yours, Chitanda and Mayaka.
Houtarou gets the slide,
and I'll handle the diving board.
Okay?
Got it!
Sounds good.
Thanks.
Houtarou,
is this job something you have to do?
Dunno.
Oh, come on.
What's the point of your motto, then?
So sorry about that.
That's what I wanted to hear.
I don't care if you're griping, but at least react somehow.
Otherwise, it's no fun.
See you around.
Oreki!
No slacking off.
I'm not slacking off.
I just got out to dispose of a piece of glass.
Yeah, right.
Seriously, Oreki, just looking at you tires me out.
It's a real pain.
Feel free not to look, then.
In the past, you could piss me off just by being there.
That was a pain too.
You're a pain either way, but if I had to pick,
I'd rather you went back to your old self.
Even that was better than this
unresponsive lump you are now.
Better, huh...
Did you find it?
No, but I'm thinking we might not have to.
So you figured something out, Houtarou?
It's fine.
Chitanda, are you sure it was an earring?
Not really...
But I'm sure she had something white on her left ear.
If she was only wearing one, it's more likely it was a stud.
That's not it. I'm not asking
what kind of accessory it was.
More like, are you sure it was even an accessory at all?
What do you mean?
Look at her.
If she had pierced ears, she wouldn't be pounding them like that,
So?
So she probably had something
stuck on her ear without knowing it.
But what could it be?
Well...
Satoshi, could you pick up Ibara?
Sure.
Wait, here?!
Then how about Chitanda?
Having Chi pick me up isn't any better!
It's like I'm a little kid! It's embarrassing!
That's the idea. I want to see how a kid would do it.
Why do we even need to do this?
To test my theory.
Your theory? For this case?
Yeah.
I don't mind.
Fine. I give up.
You're quite strong, Chitanda.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Nothing! I just meant... it takes a lot of strength to pick up people, you know.
I knew it.
You knew what?
Her hands. They naturally rest on the shoulders.
Can I get down now?
Sure, go on.
There.
Look at that.
Earlier, that woman had that kid in her arms.
I assume they're mother and son or something.
What if she picked him up while
he had an ice cream in his hand?
I see!
The ice cream would be right next to her ear!
Exactly.
So if it's not there now...
It might have washed off in the water,
or someone might have told her about it.
Something like that.
Um... Oreki...
What?
Uh, well...
I think the way you solve these cases is really amazing!
Your praise falls on barren ground with me.
Right.
I've missed that cynicism of yours.
Problem?
Yup. When you're not like that, it throws us all off.
Oh right. I haven't thanked you yet.
Thank you very much, Oreki!
Sorry for the trouble I caused you.
I, uh...
No, Chi...
I was the one who thought it was
an earring or a stud or something.
Sorry, Oreki.
Whatever. Just stop apologizing.
All right! All that searching made me hungry.
Maybe I should grab some ice cream t—
Huh? Why'd you freeze after saying ice cre—
Hyouka!
Fuku, you promised you'd have your manuscript for Hyouka done today!
Well? Is it ready?
I-I guess you could say that... More or less...
So you're not finished, are you?!
I-I guess you could say that too...
There's no "too" about it!
Fuku, you're coming with me right now, and you're finishing that manuscript!
I'm not letting you out of my sight until it's done!
I-It's just a little more! I can do it myself, honest!
Not on your life!
Chi, Oreki, sorry.
We're gonna head off now.
See you tomorrow!
Farewe—
I hope they get that manuscript done.
Does it matter?
Well, they say one should be glad to be needed.
They should just do their best.
To be needed...
I needed your help today once again.
Sorry for all the trouble.
You should be. It's a real pain.
That's mean.
But I guess I don't mind.
Uh, nothing.
By the way, Oreki, how did you know the white thing was ice cream?
Ah, that?
Look around. It's the only white thing here.
Well, except for that.
I suppose I'll take my leave.
Good luck with the rest of your work.
Thanks.
Hey!
Your turn.
Okay.
What a drag.
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep