When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Sploosh!
Dun-dun!
Synerg SP
Ta-da!
End of the Century Legend
Magical Destroy
Ma-Ma-Magical Destroy!
My name is Britney!
By all appearances, I'm a fine florist.
But the truth is...
What are you doing?!
Hey, why are you interrupting me?!
This will have people wondering
what in the world is going on!
As you can see, it's a new opening sequence.
A new opening sequence?
Yes, to commemorate the 44th episode,
we have decided to animate my manga!
Didn't we do something
similar once before, too?
Furthermore, starting next week,
we'll have it properly sung by Kotoko!
No, we won't!
And now, please start
the real opening sequence.
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of
the wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
This episode of "Hayate the
Combat Butler" is a work of fiction
and is in no way related
to real people or organizations.
It always is.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
The Mystery of the 120
Employment Rate (Temp.)
What do you think? It's the completed
version of "Magical Destroy"!
You always tell me it's hard to understand
so I tried making it easier.
Um...
Yes, yes?!
It doesn't seem
that different from before...
What?!
After I restrained my own style
and took it upon myself to make
revisions targeting the masses,
are you saying it's still
beyond your comprehension?!
Well, that is easy for you to say, but...
Look here!
The storminess of the Sea
of Japan here represents the ferocity
of the battle that's about to start, see?!
"Fwahahaha, I have finally
found you, Britney!"
"Hm? That voice...
Surely not! Who are you?!"
"I have come all this way to the
Sea of Japan to defeat you. I am..."
"...your enemy!!!"
"Damn it, my enemy, huh?!!"
"Then, surely, I have
no choice but to fight!!"
"That's right!! You have
"But since you call yourself my enemy...!!"
"You must be strong!!"
"No, I'm sorry."
"I am not very strong!!!
Because I am an early enemy."
Wh-What's wrong, Maria?
Um, is this a game of "you lose
if you poke fun at this"?
What's that supposed to mean?
An enemy has already
appeared on the 3rd page!
It's a thrilling, suspenseful development!
But he's even saying himself
that he's not strong...
What is this journey about anyway?
This is interesting, Nagi.
What?!
Or wait, Isumi, when did you get here?!
Ah! That's Isumi for you!
It was so very interesting that I tried
writing the continuation to it, too.
Twinkle
What?!
"A Kitten's Life".
"There was a kitten
with wings flying in the sky."
"Upon inspecting it from various angles,"
"it turns out it was going
at 23km per hour."
Wow! That's incredible, Isumi!
This is the feel I wanted!
Right?
Looks like they're at it again, huh?
Oh, Sakuya. And when did you get here?
Aren't those two incredible?
Yes, their conversation is just
so out there in another dimension...
Seriously. And they understand each
other, so it's really somethin'.
But is it really that hard to draw a manga?
Well, if your art is decent
and the story is carefully told,
you have a reasonable chance
at winning prizes.
Don't make problematic statements like that!
That reminds me, you've won
a manga award before, haven't you?
What?!
Wow, that's amazin'!
I have yet to read your manga, too.
I would like to read it as well.
W-Well, not that I mind, but...
"My name is Britney."
"As you can see, I'm an energetic
part-timer at a flower shop."
"Normally, I'm making a mess of things,
enticed by the scent of flowers."
ROOOAAAARRR
"So I'm always getting
chewed out by the owner."
"But enticed by the sweet scent
of those flowers come the bad guys."
"But it's no problem!"
"I make short work of guys like
that with my magic!"
"That's right, I'm secretly a magical girl."
"The magical girl of flowers, Britney!"
This manga plays it so safe,
it actually kinda ticks me off.
And it's colored to boot.
Plus, the art is adorable, but there is
something unwholesome about it.
Well, it doesn't seem
to be very well-received.
What do you think, Isumi?
It feels like it is aiming
to be popular from the start...
What?!
Right? With a mocking style like
this that's pretending to curry favor,
maybe you can fool the judges,
but you won't be able to
impress the true readers!
I-I see, pardon me.
More importantly, what happens
in your manga after this, Nagi?
Ah, I'm still in the middle
of laying out the rest of it.
How 'bout ya at least tell us the plotline?
Yes, I agree.
Ooh! What's this?
You guys want to know
what happens next, too?!
No, that is not quite why...
Then you leave me
no choice! I shall tell you!
Yes, yes.
Emerging from the 12th dimension,
*Illustrative Images
the great defeated warrior general,
along with the dark defeated warrior,
turns all of humanity into worker ants
and tries to conquer the world.
To do this, they first begin buying up
sugar in the futures market.
Futures Market
Due to this, there's
a worldwide shortage of sugar,
so Britney hardens her resolve
to travel into the 8th dimension.
Because she super loves cake
and stuff! Because she's a girl!
But Praying Mantisians come invading
right around then from nebula M2983
Fan Service Images
with their eyes on Earth's
petroleum resources.
And the ancient Aztecs...
Um, stop there, Nagi.
Why did you stop me?!
It was just getting to the good part!
How was that getting good?
Miss, if you don't figure out a way
to make it easier to understand,
you won't get through to people.
Yup, yup. It's all nonsense.
What?! I was explaining it all to you guys!
Right...
I've made up my mind!
Let's see, I was told that it
should be around here somewhere...
Miss, where in the world are we...?
That's it!
Ramen Taro
Wait. Ramen?
Welco...
Animago
P-Please take the table in the back.
Good.
Now, I will use the facilities here
to show you how fantastic my manga is.
I see...
Um, how in the world are you going to
use the facilities of a ramen shop?
Looks like we're here.
What is this place?!
Could this be that rumor I've heard...?
What?
Quick, quick, quick, quick! Stare!
Cut 82, key animation work done.
I've come to collect the finished work.
Here.
Thanks for your hard work!
Crash! Boom!
I've brought the finished work.
Good.
"Woohoo! But Dad's not here..."
Here.
Thanks for your hard work!
Key animation has been
checked for performance.
Thanks!
What in the world is this place?
It's a rather anime-ish place...
Yes, this is an anime production studio.
What?!
Just like I suspected.
So the urban myth that anime studios
disguise themselves as ramen shops,
hidin' at all costs from
the general populace was true.
I see...
There's an urban myth like that?
My, how mysterious.
Furthermore, this show is a work of fiction
and in no way related
to the actual industry.
Wow, so this is where they make anime.
It totally has that "studio" feel about it.
I feel like we came here around
Episode 35, too, though...
That's Miss Segawa,
Miss Hanabishi, and Miss Asakaze!
Why are they here, too?
Hey, hey, where are the voice actors?
What? Uh, those people are over
at the recording studio.
What?! They're not here?!
And here I thought
I'd get to meet Ms. Yahagi!
Wow! It's really moving!
Let's see, I think
I'll draw something up, too.
Rip Roaring Student Council Tankenger
What's wrong, Maria?!
Th-That...
Poke. Poke.
Looks like she's just sleepin'.
I'll manage it somehow
by the end of the day...
She is not sleeping. She passed out.
A warrior's rest.
By the way, Miss, what
in the world are we doing here?
I'm going to have them animate
the continuation of my manga.
What?!
Your manga?!
Animate it?!
Yes, I thought it would be easier
to understand as an anime
rather than a verbal explanation.
But, but, doesn't the manga
usually have to succeed first,
before it gets animated?
So exciting. So heart-pounding.
To be continued in the second half!
Terere, terere tte.
Is "terere" some kind of magical spell?
(Terere tte nanika no jumon nano?)
Conference Room
So, with this scene...
It's like Unicron preying upon a planet.
Naturally, we won't be using
any CG and it'll all be drawn!
And it'll be huge, like
the climax scene in "Laputa",
and then impressive like
the opening of the "Patlabor" movie!
Oh, I mean the first movie.
And to finish it off, we have
the last scene from "Saint Seiya"!
We'll run through the crumbling temple!
Is an explanation like this really
going to get across to them?
Do it in Mr. Shingo Araki's style.
Who knows?
That's all. Get it done in a week.
Impossible.
This is ridiculous.
You think producing anime
is easy, don't you?
Hello?
What?!
Y-Yes, I understand!
Hey.
Whisper, whisper, whisper.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
We will begin the production
work right away!
Oh, really? I'll be counting on you.
Off we go!
Hey, Nagi, what the heck did ya do?
No idea. I didn't do anything...
Oh, come to think of it, since this
company will be making my anime,
there was intel out there
that their stock would probably go up.
That's gotta be it.
So exciting. So exciting.
Not to sound like a broken record,
but this is a work of fiction
and is in no way related
to the actual industry.
So exciting.
And so, yet another anime
of questionable quality gets made...
Good luck to this show, too!
Are the storyboards still not done?!
I think it's almost done,
but the director said something
about going to Toys 'R Us
to buy a limited edition figurine...
Send an assistant to do that!
This is part of their job!
R-Right...
We have quite a bit
of the design elements in place,
but we don't have enough key animators!
What?!
There's trouble! The animation
director has suffered tenosynovitis!
What?!
What's going on?
The thing is, we're short
on animation staff members.
Hey, now, you can't make the anime then.
Can't you poach them from other companies?
Like Kyoto Animation?
Uh, that's a bit...
Well, whatever the case,
the anime based on Miss Nagi's
original work has entered production.
Looks like we'll make it in time somehow.
And we've managed it
without casualties, too.
Though, a couple people collapsed.
That's superb.
I guess anime is a harsh industry.
There's trouble!
The company doing the animation
and finishing work has fled overnight!
What?!
Is it game over?
Hmm, no choice then.
Since it's come to this,
we will have to utilize that method!
What in the world do you plan to do, Miss?
Now, what should I have for dinner today?
Nishizawa
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha?!
What in the world just happened?
Okay, we've dropped the color
from the hamster's scene,
so you can shuffle over
as many staff members as you need.
Are you sure it's okay to do this?
What? What?
This is mean, Little Nagi!
Hey, hey, what is this?
It's called an outline take.
If the art isn't done by the time
they record the audio,
they make this working footage.
Oh-ho, so it's like a making-of film
that the general audience never gets to see.
Wow, I had no idea this
was how they made anime.
Yes, and furthermore...
Nishizawa
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha?!
What now?!
When the schedule gets tight,
they'll sometimes use art
from the planning stages.
They may also just use
the storyboards as is,
Nishizawa
or show only a line made
with a colored marker.
There's a whole lot of various ways!
They don't use film anymore,
so this no longer happens.
Outline takes are so funny!
This is pretty much how it looks
when we're recording.
Hey, hey, that's a taboo topic.
It's not like we do that because we want to!
In truth, we'd like the recording
footage to be in full color.
If only we had more time...
Oh, and a bigger budget.
Complete Magical Destroy
Well, we'll leave the inside stories at that
and the anime was finally completed!
I'm starting to get nervous somehow.
Indeed, Miss.
So exciting. So heart-pounding.
I can't wait!
I intend to cry 3 times during this film!
Ah! It's beginning!
Now, let's see what kinda secret
treasure outrageous anime it's become.
So heart-pounding. So exciting.
Since we have come to this point,
let us brace ourselves for the worst, Maria.
May as well be hung for a sheep as a lamb.
Hello to all the 130 million
Girl A's across the nation!
Right now, at Animate,
we're holding the super popular
"Hayate the Combat Butler" fair!
Grab the merchandise
in your passionate fists
and slam it down at the cashier along
with the contents of your wallet!
Toranoana
Miss, what are all these?
Tie-ins. Since it's a rare opportunity,
I thought we'd get some commercials, too.
I see...
The show is about to start.
Synerg SP
End of the Century Legend
Magical Destroy
Ma-Ma-Magical Destroy!
My name is Britney!
By all appearances, I'm a fine florist.
But the truth is I'm a magical girl!
Original work by Nagi Sanzenin.
A promising new author the entire
universe has been waiting for.
Here we go!
With a cute heart and a cheery mood!
Britney is always gazing
upon her senpai from afar.
Britney
Huh? What's with this art?
Um, Senpai?
I made lunch, but...
Won't you join me?
Oh, sounds good. I'll have some.
Huh? I'm in this...
So what is going on here?
Britney is desperately
in love with her senpai,
but, but, she can't tell him how she feels.
Because she's a magical girl.
No, that's not the reason.
Why? Because her senpai has...
Because her senpai has...
Child
Wife
...a wife and child already.
Th-This turn of events
is actually really quite shocking...
I'm still not sold on the art, though.
The more you mix...
But you see, because
of the evil witch's powers...
...the more it sticks!
...her senpai was turned into a star!
Due to this, his wife fell ill
and his child became a delinquent.
If I'm in danger of losing
an online match, cut the connection!
The tension's building
more than I'd expected.
Britney resolves to turn her
senpai back to how he was.
But even if she can accomplish this,
her senpai will only return to his wife.
He and Britney will never be together.
But if she continues this journey,
she will get to spend time with
her senpai. Even though he's a star.
What will she do? What will Britney do?
And Britney's decision was...!
A Kitten's Life
A Kitten's Life.
Tmp, tmp, tmp, tmp.
Running speed is mach 5.
But no matter how fast you run,
you can never reach the sun.
The End
The end.
Y-You really are a genius, Isumi!
Right?
Well? Do you now
at least see how my manga...
Wait, what's wrong?
Come in.
Oh? Maria?
Oh, Hayate.
Could it be that you are also...?
If you are asking if I am "also",
does that mean you are also...?
Yes, I thought I would read
the Miss's manga one more time.
Since she worked so hard
to write it, after all.
Yes, we should try to understand her better.
Also, I was rather curious
to know what happens after that
to Britney and her senpai.
I was a bit, too.
But Hayate...
What is it?
Which do you suppose Britney
will choose in the end?
Will she wish to be with him? Or...?
But it looks like Nagi hasn't
written past that point.
Then I suppose that means the Miss
is having a hard time deciding as well?
As to how to end this romance...
But if it were you, which would you choose?
What? M-Me?
Hmm, let me think...
If that senpai were you,
maybe it wouldn't be bad to keep you
in the shape of a star forever.
There you go again, teasing me.
Oh! Then you try writing it!
What? M-Me?
But I've never drawn manga
or anything, so...
Then all the more reason to.
I-I could not, Hayate. Please, I...
If I'm a man, I'll conquer all
the heroines simultaneously!
Gloom...
Wait, so who is this, Maria?
You.
No, please, "conquer all the heroines
simultaneously"? What am I, a brute?
Do you have a problem
with that? In that case...
Huh?
You must be sure to make your choice.
Okay, now you try drawing it, Hayate.
What? But...
Honestly, you are such an indecisive person.
This was a story about how fiction
sometimes reflects reality and vice versa.
And now, next time...
Hold it! Hold it!
Whew. We almost forgot the fan service shot.
Or rather, even the fan service
is too avant-garde!
Please enjoy these
to take away the bad after-taste.
These are not to make sure
the episode is long enough.
"Hayate the Combat Butler"
has fantastic fan service!
Let's be sure to watch again next time!
Wait! Does this count as fan service?!
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Student Council Girl Trio
Lettering by Sayuri Yahagi
The student council girl
trio's Butler Report!
Butler Report
I'm Izumi Segawa.
I'm Risa Asakaze.
Hey, I'm Miki Hanabishi.
At last, the fruit of our
friendship and hard work...
The student council girl
trio's theme song is complete!
It was a long process.
This song is perfect
for broadcasting at school.
It'll be great to play it at cleaning time.
It's also perfect for going
for a drive with your girlfriend.
Even she'll fall head over heels
with this song playing on the car stereo!
It's also perfect
for lonely people living alone!
It might give you the energy to live!
Starting this week, we'll be showing you
fan service scenes of ours
for the next segments!
It's me this time!
Next time, it'll be me!
Adieu!
Preview
Where in the world are we
going out to all of a sudden?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Oh, I wonder where.
You'll have to wait to get there to see.
I see...
And so, we call it "Thank you
for everything, Maria.
"The big sister appreciation
day relaxation plan!"
Thank you for always working so hard for us!
Staying in a midtown hotel,
going to the spa and
getting beauty treatments...
Forget about work
and just sit back and relax!
Next time, "It Is Maria Appreciation
Day! In February (heart)".
It Is Maria Appreciation Day! In February
Prism Flash on "Hayate
the Combat Butler" again next time!