Ah, Hideyoshi, about
today's remedial class... Huh?
Wh... What is it, Yoshi... I mean A-Akihisa?
You... seem to be different from usual.
R... Really? I... I'm always like this, right?
My height and even my face
are the same as always, right?
Hmm... I feel like you're
usually more girlish and cute.
Hi!! Mondai: hitori to
futari docchi ga suteki?
Colorful mawari dasu watashi no shourai
Doko made hanasou ka? Minai furi?
Assou, ookina sekai
wa kibun de hirogaru
Kyou mo daisuki, hontou ni daisuki
Watashi no baka...
Hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
Sunao ni narezu ni,
kimi to aruku yume o mita
Gomen ne... Datte!
Koi to shiranakattanda
Kotaette kimi to nazo tasu
watashi wa mugen no JUMP!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
So... Ms. Takahashi,
how are things progressing?
Yes, Principal...
"Episode 3 Me, That Girl, and a Stuffed Toy!"
How about Yuuko Kinoshita in Class A?
She's a top-notch student and outgoing.
I see...
Her twin brother Hideyoshi
Kinoshita even manages operas.
We can have high hopes for his
sister Yuuko being a talented singer, too.
That's great! Having a
student that can handle anything
gives me great pride as a principal.
Yes. It's rare to see a model student
who's as exemplary, good-looking,
top-notch, and outgoing as she is.
Ahh... Pretty boys really are the best.
Especially the scene where Yuuichi
attacks Shinji with a blunt object...
Oh wait! This is no time for that!
I'm home!
Sis?
Hm? What's the matter?
To see you threw your favorite novel...
Why am I incapable of doing
things that you are capable of?
Hm? What do you mean?
Today, Ms. Takahashi insisted
that I sing the school song
in the Fumizuki Academy's promotional video.
What?! When you have
no sense of pitch or rhythm?
"Stomach"
"Fist"
What's your damage? Are you picking a fight?
If it'd be a problem for you,
you could've just turned it down, right?
Absolutely not!
I've been trying hard to play an
honor student who's good at anything.
That sure is some
hard-core vanity you've got.
"Vanity" "Hard-core"
"Clap, clap, clap, clap..."
That's the Kinoshita Family way, right?
You act on the stage and I act out being
an honor student in our everyday life.
When you look at it that way,
you and I might be alike.
Of course we are! I don't
wanna admit it, but you and I are...
...twins...
Wh-What is it? What is it, Sis?!
You're good at impersonating people, right?
I'd prefer if you'd call it acting.
Hey, don't tell me...
Hideyoshi... your sister has a
really important favor to ask of you.
Sis! Th-That's not asking a favor. That's a threat!
"Favor"
"Fist"
Are we really going to do this, Sis?
I'm attending the remedial
class for you. What's the problem?
But what if my classmates figure it out?
What if they do?
From tomorrow on,
they'll seriously call me a girl.
So they won't think that we switched?
Oh, take this with you.
What's that?
A hidden microphone.
I'll keep an eye on you with this.
Sis, where'd you get this?
From one of your classmates.
New pictures have arrived.
This classroom is as shabby as ever...
Sugawa escaped!
Sugawa violated our
contract and approached a girl!
He's no longer our leader! He's a traitor!
Pursue Sugawa!
"Yuuko (Dumbfounded...)"
"Curse"
"Yuuko (Super dumbfounded)"
Ah, Hideyoshi! They said
we'd be doing worksheets today.
Is that right?
At any rate, what a stupid thing Sugawa did...
Urgent report! Urgent report!
We've acquired the testimony of
the girl who Sugawa approached!
She's not interested in him, instead,
she repeatedly said, "Tell me about Aki."
--I repeat! The female
student said, "Tell me about Aki"!
--Farewell!
--I repeat!
--Hold it!
--The female student said, "Tell me about Aki"!
Nothing but idiots.
Well... I wonder if Hideyoshi is doing okay.
Thanks, Kinoshita.
Is this voice... Kubo's?
Thanks to you, I feel heartened.
Don't worry about it.
What? What on earth
are they talking about?
Well, just knowing that
I have a classmate who shares
a common interest is comforting.
I never thought that you'd be
interested in homosexual love.
O-Oh, Hideyoshi. Is something the matter?
S-Sis! Could you come with me?!
What?! Hey! Hideyoshi? Si--
Hideyoshi! Tell me what
you guys were talking about!
It was just a petty chitchat.
How messed up do you have to be to
say I'm interested in homosexual love?!
But the novels you read are...
Stupid! You're really stupid!
That and this are totally different matters!
That makes it sound
like I'm interested in girls!
I didn't mean it that way at all!
If you say something that can
cause a misunderstanding again...
Okay! I get it!
Did he really get it?
Yuuko, can I talk to you?
What's the matter?
Rep?
That darn Hideyoshi... He'd better keep up.
Yuuko... your skirt is turned up.
What?
Th-That idiot...!
Thank you, Rep. But... it's okay...
But... your skirt...
...because...
Because...?
I'm wearing underwear today.
Sis!
What's your excuse this time?
What I said earlier...
I meant it's okay because I'm wearing leggings.
How is that underwear?! You made it
sound like I normally don't wear panties!
But aren't leggings a kind of underwear?!
Stop saying stupid stuff
and be careful about your skirt!
But your skirt is quite
loose around the waist and...
I-I'll be careful! I'll be sure to be careful!
Seriously...!
K-Kinoshita...!
Who's this guy?
I'm Kouji Yokomizo.
Kouji Yokomizo? I don't know him.
I-I'm in love with you!
P-Please go out with me!
Love confession? What am
I gonna do? I'm flattered, but...
I'm sorry. I do appreciate your feelings but...
Good! That's a safe way of handling it.
Th-Then tell me your type!
I'm sorry... I...
I-I...?
I'm only interested in young pretty boys.
I'm not someone who likes girls,
who wears no panties, or is a Shotacon!
I analyzed your taste in my own way.
That's my taste in fiction, right?!
I'm hiding those things
outside the house, right?!
O-Okay. This time for sure,
I'll act as you do outside the house.
"Sigh..."
Ah, Hideyoshi!
Yoshi... I mean, Akihisa.
You don't have to run around any longer?
Nope.
Since those guys heard that
Yokomizo confessed his love to your sister,
they're devoting all their energies on that.
I-I see.
Yokomizo...
I feel sorry for you. Myself excluded,
you're the worst victim in all of this.
He never learns, does he?
What?
To think that he confessed
his love to your sister this time
just because you turned him down.
I withdraw what I just said!
Speaking of your sister...
What?
Your sister really is incredible, isn't she?
Wh-What is this, all of a sudden?
Because she's cute... and smart.
She's a great athlete, too.
She's a sister to be proud of, isn't she?
Y-You think so?
On top of that, look.
No matter when I see her, she's very pretty.
Pretty... huh?
That's precisely why it's unfortunate.
Huh?
I heard that your sister is a Shotacon
who likes girls and rarely wears panties.
Forget that stuff!
What?! Why?!
I don't know what's going on, but breasts...!
I faintly feel soft breasts!
What do you mean, "Faintly"?!
I do have some, more or less!
For some reason, there's a rumor
these days that my breasts are growing.
What a coincidence.
Actually, there's also a rumor
that I'm a Shotacon who likes girls,
and in addition, that I wander
about the school wearing no panties.
What're you gonna do about it?
As it stands, they're gonna
treat me more and more as a woman.
That's no different from
how they treat you now, is it?
They'll see me as a triple-threat perv!
It was your fault to
suggest that we switch places!
It's your fault that you acted
like a messed up version of me!
Oh well... We'll just let it be.
Yeah, being upset won't get us anywhere.
Our school has plenty
of interesting rumors, so...
Idiot Test!
"One year in the past..."
Don't move, everyone!
Put your bag on the desk and
open it so that I can see what's in it.
Stop this futile resistance!
Sakamoto... Show me
what you have in your pockets.
Dammit!
I'll confiscate it.
Damn! Why just me?!
Yoshii! Take off your school uniform
and change into your PE clothes.
Why?! You're being too vigilant, Teacher!
Please trust me a litt--
Hey, Akihisa. Your game console fell.
Oh, thanks, Yuuji.
Please trust me a little!
In your case, don't even
bother with the PE clothes.
I'm summoning my Avatar! Summon!
Today, Year 1 students are doing
Avatar summoning training together.
Boy... Our luck's been bad
since we got to school, hasn't it?
Crap! I bought that just last month!
My personal costumes
and props got taken, too.
--Well, as for me, my cell, game
console, video games, DVDs, CDs,
--What exactly are you coming to school for?
--Well, as for me, my cell, game console, video games, DVDs, CDs,
--light novels, manga, trading cards,
--Oh?
--celebrity pictures, spinning tops...
Hm?
Himeji is gonna do it.
Oh? Aren't you taking
her picture, Muttsulini?
My digital camera got confiscated.
That's unfortunate.
Since she's in a different class,
you rarely ever get a chance to
take pictures of her in PE clothes.
I'm summoning my Avatar! Summon!
She's cute, and on top of that, she's smart.
It's natural to admire her, isn't it?
Come to think of it, don't you
and Himeji know each other?
Yeah. We were in the same
class in elementary school,
but we haven't talked all this time, so...
Next! Akihisa Yoshii!
Ah, yes, Sir.
Yoshii will fight... Shimada!
Shimada! Minami Shimada!
Ah, yes, Sir!
Yoshii!
What's the matter, Shimada?
You were in a daze.
Are you hungry?
Humph! Don't confuse me with you!
Hm? Oh, I get it!
Your Avatar is so feeble
that you got disappointed.
I'm glad that it's you I'm fighting, Yoshii...
Hm?
...because it feels so good to beat you up.
Wait! It's our Avatars who
beat each other up! It's not us!
That's right. We don't beat each other up.
I-I'm glad you understand.
I'll be... the one doing all the beating up, right?
"Aaah!"
Shimada...
S-See? The teacher is also...
Just today, okay?
Yes, Sir!
Why?!
I've had bad luck all day long today.
Hm?
I-It's Himeji!
All right! I'll summon my courage and talk to her!
Th-This is too much for me!
It can't be helped. I'll retreat!
I beg of you, please!
Hm?
I want that Noin no matter what! Please!
What a bind...
Excuse me, is something wrong?
Well, this young lady wants
that stuffed toy no matter what,
but she doesn't have enough money.
Say... why do you want it so badly?
My older sister isn't cheerful these days.
Your older sister?
Yes. She said she wanted
that stuffed toy before.
So...
I see...
So you wanted to cheer her
up by giving her a present, huh?
I'm sure she's having a tough time
at school since we just moved here.
But...
But she still does cleaning
and laundry... and plays with me...
Whoa! Please don't cry!
I'll do something about it!
Really?!
Yep.
Big Brother... Thank you!
So, how much is that stuffed toy?
25,000 yen.
Argh!
I'm sorry... I tried my best,
but it wasn't possible.
"Shocked!"
Ah, but I have 10,000 yen with me!
In other words, even with 1,000 yen,
my entire fortune, it'll only be 11,000 yen...
That's about half of 25,000 yen, right?
It's a little short, though.
Then, tear up the stuffed toy...
...and let us buy about half of it!
Are you really a high school student?
You're such a stupid Big Brother.
"Reserved"
This should buy us some time.
But if we don't have the money...
Yeah... 25,000 yen, huh...?
It's about the total of the stuff
confiscated from me this morning.
Oh yeah!
What's the matter?
Let's meet up in this park
again tomorrow, Haduki.
Tomorrow?
Yep!
Okay!
All right!
Take back the stuff we had confiscated?!
Yeah, I want you guys to help me out.
To do so, we have to get
the key to Iron Man's locker.
The key is in his jacket pocket.
Then how about... throwing
a bucket of water on him,
and stealing the key while he's changing?
So... good luck, Akihisa.
Me?!
The target is coming!
Don't mess it up!
Go for it!
Aren't you gonna help me out?!
Now that it's come to this...
My foot... slipped!
What?!
I won't let you get away!
Well, I'm sorry. My foot sli--
I thought I heard "I won't
let you get away" or something.
I had a hell of a time, but I got the key.
Okay then! Let's open
Iron Man's locker while we can.
I found them!
Well then, let's get out of here already.
Okay!
Hm? Old books?
If they're gonna ditch them anyway...
Boy, that was close.
If it wasn't for those old books,
it wouldn't have been
enough for 25,000 yen.
Ah! Stupid Big Brother!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all!
Hm? That's...
Uhm... before you came,
a pretty Big Sister came.
Pretty Big Sister?
Yes! She told me to give
this stuffed toy to my sister.
She also said that if you brought
Noin, then this would be mine.
Well... then this is yours, Haduki.
Mine?
Yep! And, give this one to your sister.
Ah! Noin!
I hope this'll cheer your sister up.
Uhm... Big Brother...
Could you squat down?
Hm...? Like this?
Thank you, Big Brother.
Big Brother, although you're stupid,
I like you a lot because you're so kind!
I'll marry you when I grow up!
There was an incident yesterday.
Someone took the confiscated
stuff and my personal old books.
He was so gutsy that he
openly showed his student ID
when he sold off the old
books and the video games.
What do you think, Yoshii?
--He's sure got guts!
--Indeed.
"Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha..."
Yoshii! Clench your teeth!
I'm sorry! There's a reason for it!
Yoshii. I'll give you the position title
best suited for an idiot like you. Take this.
Hm?
Akihisa Yoshii.
From today on, you are...
...a probationary student!
Hirameite, kagayaite, denkyuu pikkanko
Shinten shinai yo.
Dareka jama shiteru... No, no!
Zenzen tarinai, sore
ga mondai no koubaisuu
Ryoukai sorenai. Nani ga
hontou no koto... Baby?
Mitetara koko de zukai shite yo, Baby!
Kotoba mo kazu mo kimi o arawasenai
Kokoro ga biribiri
suru S to N no jiryoku de
(S, S, Super kuttsuite
Number, I say No. 1 boy!)
Omedetou! Imakara kimi
wa My, ma-my "otakara"
Tokubetsu nanda, dou nattemo
Gyutto ne gyutto ne hanasanai
Watashi wa koi shitai.
Yume ni genkai wa iranai
Tokubetsu dayo ne, acchatta mon
Konna watashi mo yurushichae
Hirameita, kagayaita, seikai pittanko
Big Sis! Here you go!
Th-This is...
Will this cheer you up?
Thank you, Haduki! This cheers me up a lot!
Japanese is difficult so things are tough, but...
Yeah. Let's do our best together.
Besides...
Besides...?
There's someone...
I'm interested in these days.
What?! What's he like?
Well, he's a classmate of mine,
and he's really stupid.
Question 4.
When you add all the numbers of
the 52 playing cards, what's the total?
1 plus 2 plus 3 plus... uhm...
Good luck.
Next episode!
"Me, True Colors and a Man's Dignity!"
This will be on the test.