It's all wrong!
You idiot!
Ow...
I don't care if it hurts.
It may be a replica,
but you're still wearing the same armor that the Blue Knight did in old stories.
Yeah, but...
Plus, you're not listening to me when I teach you to act gallantly like a knight.
You can't even draw your blade properly.
H-Huh?
It won't come out!
How stupid are you!?
The sword is a knight's soul!
You need to be more careful with it!
You're going to get it if you break that sword!
I-I understand.
Your Highness, Satomi-sama,
tea is served.
Ruth-san!
Oh well.
I guess we'll take a break.
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
sho
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
and annoying
mu
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
But really, I was surprised.
My Knight
I can't believe Satomi-sama's physique exactly matches the knight from the legends.
I thought the armor might've malfunctioned since it didn't automatically adjust itself,
but I guess there are some amazing coincidences.
By the way, Ruth, what about the ship we saw?
We haven't detected anything since.
What ship?
Another Fortorthen ship appeared near this planet the other day.
We detected a space-time quake when it arrived,
but we haven't been able to
determine anything more since.
It's Clan. The second crown princess to the Fortorthen Galactic Empire,
Clariossa Daora Fortorthe.
It has to be her.
She's your rival, then, Tulip?
But you don't have any evidence, right?
Why do you think it's this Clan girl?
The absence of evidence is evidence itself.
Clan's ship, the Rougetsu, has a stealth system she developed herself.
However, it reduces her combat capabilities.
Anyway, let's get back to practicing.
What? Already?
Come on. Let's go!
Can't it wait a bit?
No. We might as well...
You don't have to pull my arm.
Hercules-chan, here's some food.
Say, Yurika, how long do we have to keep him?
I dunno. The club's vice president still hasn't finished moving.
Those are some big pincers.
We, uh, well...
What type of bug is that?
You don't know, Ruth?
No. It's my first time seeing one.
His name is Hercules-chan.
I see. He's pretty cute.
Are you okay, Satomi-kun?
I heard you went through a lot of training, but...
Yes, I'm fine.
I'll do what I must to help the play!
The Neanderthal messed up again.
How many times do I have to tell him?
Don't you think his posture and gait have gotten much better?
You must have worked
pretty hard, Theia-dono.
So Kiriha, why are you wearing that?
Weren't you supposed to be a stage-hand?
The guy who was supposed to play the priest caught a cold.
She fits the role, so I asked her to take over.
I haven't had much time,
so I've yet to read through the whole thing.
Don't cry after you read it all.
Hey, everyone!
We're going to start rehearsing the first scene.
Okay, let's do our best.
Yes.
Koutarou, if you forget a line, I'll help you out.
Right. I'm counting on you!
Koutarou?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. I've just never seen that girl before.
But now that we've been dethroned, siding with us
will mean turning against all of Fortorthe.
You may be correct, Princess Alaia.
Then, you shouldn't...
But my pride and loyalty do not allow me to be an enemy of the Fortorthen Kingdom
and the hearts of its people.
It feels like the real scene.
But why am I here?
Why isn't the Blue Knight
trying to protect me instead?
Then, tell me just one thing.
Anything you wish.
You have a crest on your chest marking you a knight of the royal house.
Your appearance, your mannerisms, and your proud heart...
There's no question you're a knight of Fortorthe.
However...
However I do not recognize that house crest on your sword.
From whence have you come?
I have come from beyond untold time and untold distance.
Where are you from, Mister?
Those are the exact same words that person said.
But why?
Did the Blue Knight...
Watch out, Theia-dono!
The light!
Are you injured, Your Highness?
The Blue Knight...
I'm glad you're okay.
Can you stand, Tulip?
Blue Knight, you're hurt!
Oh, I guess I am.
Don't worry. It's no big deal.
But the Blue Knight got hurt because of me—
It's fine, I said.
I'm not really the Blue Knight anyway.
S-Sorry...
I was kind of confused there for a second.
O-Oh.
This was no accident...
You think this Clan person was trying to get Theia?
Yeah. She's stealthy,
so things like hide-and-seek would be right up her alley.
Always skulking in the shadows.
She's a disgrace to royalty everywhere.
Do they not get along?
Yes...
They're rivals in both house and name,
and since their personalities are polar opposites,
they often clash with each other.
Right. She mentioned that at the hot springs.
She can't afford to lose this competition, because of her mom.
You can't show your rival any weakness, huh?
Theia-dono, I assume you'll be
thinking of a way to deal with her.
Yes, but this proves that we're safe for now.
If Clan really were trying to get rid of me, she wouldn't leave any evidence behind.
If any word of it ever reached Fortorthe,
Clan would be excised from her right to the throne.
She's not so short-sighted, then.
If she really wanted to take you out,
she would have attacked you with her ship or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's still
something to worry about.
You should see to my safety, then, Neanderthal.
Isn't that your job, Blue Knight?
You know, you only call me the Blue Knight when it's convenient for you.
Okay, we're finished
with the last rehearsal.
Have fun at the party tonight,
and rest up before the play tomorrow!
Dismissed!
Right!
No!
I want to go to the party too!
I want to have fun!
No way.
You're practicing more so
you become a proper knight.
Come on, Theia. I wanted to
have some fun with Koutarou.
Don't worry about it, Sanae.
If Koutarou really wanted to leave, I'm sure he'd find a way to escape.
You mean Koutarou wants to practice?
You know, he can be really nice at the weirdest times.
Why can't he only be nice to me?
Neanderthal!
Your stance is off again!
You know, Tulip,
it's pretty hard to draw a sword without changing your stance.
No excuses!
If you have time to complain, you have time to practice!
Get going before I beat it into you!
I'm going to get you back for this, Princess Theiamillis!
Fat chance.
Like this.
Like this, right?
No!
Okay, how about this?
No, like this!
Satomi-kun never acts that way around me.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
How was the party?
It was fun,
but I need to give
Hercules-chan some food.
Weather Forecast
The skies will be clear until about noon
and overcast in the afternoon.
It's a new show!
We're back with more fighting after you asked for it!
Rhinoceros Man, Second Impact!
Rhinoceros Man
i    mpact
i    m  pact
i    m     pact
i    m   p     act
i   m  p    a      ct
i  m  p   a   ct
i m p  a  ct
i m p a ct
impact
The legendary Yamato Beetle is back!
Along with three others:
Atlas,
Caucasus,
and Hercules.
You need to see these
rhinoceros beetles fight!
Rhinoceros Man, Second Impact!
I see.
So Hercules-chan is a rhinoceros beetle.
Shoo! Shoo!
Please stay away!
Shoo!
Well, I guess that works.
R-Really? That was good?
There are still some problems,
but I'll let you off with that.
Yeah! I'm done!
I told you to act like a knight
when you're dressed like that.
S-Sorry.
What is that?
The dance music for the party.
A dance, huh?
I haven't danced in a while.
Teach me how to dance.
You taught me how to be a knight,
but you haven't taught me anything else.
It's something important to nobles, right?
Ow!
Don't step on my feet!
Sorry, sorry! It's difficult to follow the steps—
You're going to give me
compound fractures in my foot!
What's going on?
I thought he'd be bored with all the practice.
Thanks for watching the place.
Did anyone enter the gym while I was gone?
Nope!
Harumi-chan stopped by,
but she left without coming inside.
I see.
That's fine.
Keep guard.
Right!
So Theia-chan's involved in a family quarrel?
Guess she really is a princess.
She acts like she's not in danger at all, though.
Save me, everyone!
Yurika? What's wrong!?
Ruth-san found out that
Hercules-chan is a rhinoceros beetle,
and she looks really angry,
and she's chasing after me!
What are you doing!?
Anyway, we'll need to hide you.
How about that shed over there?
Once Ruth-san comes, we'll make something up.
Sis, Ruth-chan is coming!
Come on, Yurika!
Hurry!
Y-Yes!
R-Ruth!
Why are you here?
Did something happen?
You're over there?
This is bad.
She's so angry that she's not even listening to us.
What should we do?
You're really bad at this.
It's my first time. You can't blame me.
You messed up again.
You're supposed to go right.
It might be right for you, but it's left for me.
Silly.
Your Highness... and Satomi-sama...
Where am I?
What was I doing?
Sis, emergency alert!
We've detected a spacial
distortion within the gym!
What?
Theia-dono, Koutarou, we've got an intruder!
Clan, huh?
That's correct, Theiamillis-san.
Clan!
She's Clan?
She was...
I didn't think you'd try to attack me directly.
Did you build that weapon on this planet!?
This planet is technologically in the stone age.
It took quite a bit of time.
If she created the weapon from
materials she gathered on this planet,
Fortorthe won't be able to determine anything!
I went through all this effort, and it's just going
to end in one shot. It's kind of anti-climatic.
Something's off.
Why was Clan here before?
She was hiding this entire time...
Why would she risk exposing
herself to mess with that light?
Maybe there's a reason behind why she had to come here in order to get rid of Theia.
That's enough!
I'll just have to attack you directly.
Blue Knight, pulse laser!
As you wish, My Princess.
Cancel it, Tulip!
N-Neanderthal, don't get in my way!
She wants you to use your weapon!
What are you saying!?
Believe me, Theia!
Your Highness! Satomi-sama!
Are you okay, Theia!?
I-I'm fine. You saved me.
Wh-What just happened?
It seems that Clan had set things up so that if a weapon appeared, it would explode instead.
She knew that if she provoked the princess, she'd use a weapon.
She didn't come here just to mess with the light.
She also came to set that explosion.
Why'd you have to go and do that?
I won't let a commoner from some backwater planet ruin my plan!
Koutarou!
We're here to help you!
No problem!
You guys, protect the princess.
I'm counting on you!
Wait, Koutarou!
You can't fight by yourself!
Let me help!
Your Highness,
the battlefield is for your knight.
An imperial princess
mustn't dare to enter it.
B-But...
If you won't believe in me,
then who will?
I am your knight.
Koutarou...
My knight...
Here I come, Clan!
Don't make me laugh, you Blue Knight wannabe!
And you're just a fake princess who
thinks only of bringing people down!
What did you honestly hope to achieve with that blunt sword?
Wh-What's going on!?
This can't be!
A replica can't have the same power as the real Signaltin!
That light from the sword...
That light... It's the same as...
That sword should have that power...
Could it be that you're the real...
I just need to take you out first!
Koutarou!
I'll handle it!
Sanae-chan Tulip Part II!
A cat, huh?
That's what you're worried about, Shizuka-sama!?
Hey! What was that!?
People call me the Schweiger Moon,
and I was defeated by some Neanderthal?
Give up.
You've lost.
This is all your fault.
No one back home should mind if I attack you with my ship, Rougetsu.
What?
This is bad.
Run, Koutarou!
Run? To where!?
It's too late now.
Rougetsu, atomize this Blue Knight!
As you wish, My Princess.
Burn in Hell.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Here you go!
That's...
Foiled by your own trap.
Bye!
Clan got away.
You're not going to chase after her?
It doesn't matter.
Trying to find her would be a waste of time.
You did a good job today.
I guess.
I'm pretty exhausted, though.
There's something I have to tell you.
Sorry, it broke.
I see.
I guess it did.
Huh? You're not going to get mad?
You kept saying that the
sword is the soul of a knight.
You don't understand anything, do you?
Huh?
The sword represents the oath of a knight.
It is the oath that shouldn't yield,
not so much the sword itself.
Why don't you understand something so simple?
All right!
You're going to start knight
training from the beginning!
Wh-Why!?
I thought we finished!
We're not even close!
If I let a half-hearted knight like you go,
I'll be an embarrassment to the Mastil family.
Training starts tomorrow!
No!
Let me go!
This is not happening.
I can't believe I lost.
I don't have a choice here.
I didn't want to use this while I was developing it, but...
Goodbye, Theiamillis.
Farewell—
Oh no.
I'm going to fall!
Ow...
Who are you!?
I'll just cast a spell and pretend that nothing happened.
For Hercules-chan.
Hey, what happened to Yurika?
Yurika-sama was here?
Don't worry about it, Ruth.
Right...
Shouharu
Festival
And so the festival ended without incident.
Princess Clan returned home.
You performed your duties well.
I would normally reward someone with whatever they requested.
But unfortunately, I cannot do that for you.
I hereby bestow the title of a knight upon you
as a symbol of my appreciation.
However, I imagine you'd dislike it if I treated you like my subordinate.
That is why I have come at this hour.
Ruth is my only witness, as well.
Forgive me, Koutarou.
I know of no other way
to demonstrate my gratitude.
You may laugh at the fact that I have been sheltered my entire life.
Until I came to this land,
I was unaware I could live my life differently.
Satomi Koutarou, I, Theiamillis Gre Mastil-Sagrada Von Fortorthe,
grant you the position of knight
and the title of "Theiamillis' Blue Knight".
Rest well, my knight.
What's this game?
I'm no good at this.
I always strike out...
on the first turn.
An Evil Magical Girl Appears!?
Next Episode
That's...
...pretty impressive.