This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
This is Oreki.
Hello, it's Chitanda speaking. Sorry for bothering you during the break.
Would you happen to have any plans for the day after tomorrow?
Nope...
Thank God!
Um, Oreki...
I know that this is asking a lot of you,
but could you please carry the umbrella?
Carry... the umbrella?
Yes.
I don't really follow.
Sorry, I didn't explain it properly.
The thing is, we're having a Hina festival at the shrine near my house.
Hina festival?
It's already April!
It's held according to the lunar calendar.
Actually, one of the umbrella holders for the dolls had an accident,
and there's no one else who can wear the costume.
I think the size should fit you.
Wait a moment. Someone has to hold the umbrella?
Yes.
Could you please help us?
Okay, I'll be there.
Really?
Thank you so much!
I just have to stand there, right?
No, you need to walk too.
Walk? With a doll?
Yes. That's right.
The dolls walk?
Yes.
How?
Oreki!
Could you stop saying "dolls" all the time?
It's a bit embarrassing...
Don't tell me...
Yes, at the Mizunashi Shrine's living Hina festival, girls take on the dolls' roles.
Ah.
I've played the Hina doll for a few years now.
Mizunashi Shrine
The usual slope
|
v
follow the little
<- river upstream
just follow the road
^
|
cross the Choukyuu bridge
^
|
cherry trees (one of them is
blooming out of season)
"Follow the little river upstream,
then cross the Choukyuu bridge after the cherry trees."
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
Dolls in the Distance
Ah, is that the cherry tree blooming out of season?
Chitanda didn't know they were fixing the bridge?
Excuse me, can I cross?
Sure, go on.
We'll start work soon, and the bridge will be closed after that.
Excuse me!
Hey, I've brought it.
Ah, just put it down in the hall.
Sure.
Um...
Who're you?
I'm Oreki. I've been asked to hold the umbrella.
Didn't Chitanda tell you?
She asked me to help out by holding the umbrella.
Ah, instead of the Hazawa kid?
Sorry, sorry. Just come in.
Say, who's taking care of the booze?
I asked Nakatake to do it.
Nakatake, is it gonna be all right?
Sure, everything's going well.
And what about that thing during the day?
I asked the women to handle it.
I see...
Hey, where are the lanterns?
In the hall.
I see. I'll take a look.
Oreki!
Yes?
You'll be holding the umbrella for the Chitanda girl, right?
Yes.
Mr Hanai, phone call!
It's from the newspaper!
Oh, jeez.
I just can't get a moment's rest...
Nakatake!
Where's the booze?
It'll be here by one.
You idiot!
The procession gets back at half past twelve!
Does one pm sound like it'll be on time to you?!
Make them hurry!
Right away.
For crying out loud.
Ah!
Yes?
You're the guy Chitanda asked to help?
Yes. My name is Oreki.
Sorry for asking you to come out all this way.
We're short on people, so we really need your help.
I'd greatly appreciate your assistance today.
I'm sorry to barge in as an outsider.
I'll do my best not to get in the way.
If there's anything I can do to help, please let me know.
You're a good boy.
First time in my life anyone's told me that.
Oreki, was it?
Please take it easy.
Mr. Fukiya, have the worshippers' representatives arrived?
All here.
The children in the procession?
The living dolls?
Just a little longer.
Okay.
Tanimoto, will the Choukyuu bridge be all right?
I asked Mr. Murai to do something about it.
So we can get them to delay the work, right?
Yes.
He told me to leave it to him.
They've already started work on the Choukyuu bridge.
What?
Tanimoto, you made sure, right?!
I asked Mr. Murai!
Oreki,
are you sure about this?
Yes...
Sono!
Yes?
Take my truck and check.
Roger.
Tanimoto!
Yes?
Call Murai... No, call Nakagawa Construction.
Roger.
This should do, right, Hanai?
Yes...
Is something wrong?
The procession is supposed to cross the Choukyuu bridge.
Oh.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
Why are you staring at me like that?
It's true! They've already begun work!
Tanimoto, what the hell have you been doing?!
I-It doesn't make any sense!
Mr. Murai contacted the construction company!
He asked them to put the work off until tomorrow.
Then why haven't they?!
Someone called them two days ago to say the work could go ahead.
Who did that?
They didn't name themselves.
I heard that too.
We've got more important matters to deal with.
Can't we ask them to stop the work?
It's too late.
The TV crew's here already. What if there was an accident?
Why don't they follow the same route back?
They could just walk down the east bank of the river then back the same way.
The people on the east bank will appreciate that, but what about the west?
No doll parade for them?
Then how about walking down to the Choukyuu bridge,
doubling back, then doing the same on the other side?
We can't make the procession walk the whole distance twice.
Then what if we walk half way, then come back and do the same on the west side?
How could we do something so half-assed in front of the cameras?
Then what can we do?
Why don't we walk down to the Tooji bridge?
If we go as far as the Tooji bridge
then come back on the Kaya bridge,
it'll be just a bit longer than the original route.
The Tooji bridge, huh?
I don't know...
Um, is Mr. Oreki here?
Yes, how can I help?
Mr. Chitanda's daughter is looking for you.
What does she want?
Who knows...
Living
dolls
Make-up
and
dressing
room
Are you Oreki?
Yes...
Sorry for calling you this way, but I'm still in the middle of getting my make-up done.
That's Chitanda... isn't it?
I sent for you because I heard there was some trouble.
Yeah.
Is it serious?
Seems so.
I see.
Please tell me what happened.
We don't have much time.
The Choukyuu bridge...
So someone suggested a route that crossed the Tooji bridge instead,
but then everyone...
Are you listening?
I am.
But then everyone looked as though that was the worst option possible.
That's it.
You've summed it up well.
Thanks.
Oreki, could I trouble you to deliver a message?
Sure...
I'll talk to the priests leading the procession.
I'll ask my father to call the worshippers' representatives.
Please tell them that.
That's all?
They should understand.
That's what she told me.
Okay then, that's that.
Everyone, we're crossing the Tooji bridge.
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and get to work!
As the Sun crosses the middle of the heavens,
the day and the night are equal.
Spring Equinox
Hyouka
Couldn't you play this role?
The costume doesn't fit me.
That's true.
This procession's a once-in-a-lifetime sight. I came all the way home just to see it.
And I couldn't do that if I had to take part in it.
That's true.
Done.
How is it?
It doesn't really fit you.
I must agree.
The 62nd Kamiyama Living Doll Festival
It's freezing.
Is that... Irisu?
Damn.
This is bad. This is really bad.
I definitely shouldn't have come here.
My low-energy lifestyle is in mortal danger.
I can't see Chitanda...
I can't stop thinking about it.
I can't stop thinking about it!
What if I caught a glimpse of Chitanda's face,
taking in the makeup on her skin and her eyes, cast modestly downward...
Houtarou!
That was great!
Chitanda and Irisu looked amazing!
Yeah, it was so pretty!
Where are they now?
In the main hall.
They're purging impurities.
Oh?
By the way, that outfit really didn't suit you.
Cut it out.
You were such a waste for that role.
I don't recall asking for criticism.
I'll go get another one of these.
Oreki, thanks...
For what?
For what you did at Valentine's. I hadn't had an opportunity to thank you yet.
How did it go?
It's going.
I see.
I blew my top too.
Almost ended up punching him.
I heard.
Irisu!
Ah, Oreki.
You were one of the dolls, right?
It's a long story.
By the way, I heard about the Choukyuu bridge.
There are a bunch of things that don't make sense.
What do you think?
Hmm...
I wonder. Who knows?
I see.
I hoped you'd be able to solve this mystery.
Stop it, please.
Oreki.
Huh?
I played my part back then.
This time I'm just a doll.
Today, you'll see only the real me.
Okay...
Oreki...
Oreki!
Wh-What?
Today was so hard! I had to put up with it the whole time!
Ah, having to play a doll? Must've been tough.
Not that!
The Choukyuu bridge! The incident with Nakagawa Construction!
Ah, that...
I wanted to figure it out, but I was too preoccupied with my role for the procession.
But I wanted to ask you so much! I—
Let me guess. You can't stop thinking about it.
Exactly! You've noticed lots of clues, right?
I've got a vague idea.
Me too!
How about we write it all down and look at everything together?
Sure, but what do we have to write on?
Ready? One, two!
Konari's son
The brown-haired guy
Konari's son is brown-haired.
So we suspect the same guy?
Yes. Why did you think of him?
First, we know for sure that someone called to tell them to go ahead with the bridge repairs.
Yes, I agree.
So, who would have done that?
Everyone was in a rush today,
and only one person acted on the premise that the Choukyuu bridge would be closed.
And that would be Konari's son, right?
Yeah. I talked to him when I was changing.
He said the procession was a "once-in-a-lifetime sight".
Did he?
But that doesn't make sense. This festival is held every year.
It's not something a local would call "once-in-a-lifetime".
You're right, that is a little strange.
But this year, it really was a once-in-a-lifetime sight.
Do you know why?
The route was changed,
so we had to cross the Tooji br—
Ah, the cherry tree!
Yeah, the cherry tree that was blooming out of season.
The only way you can see it is via today's route.
Seeing the living dolls pass under a blooming cherry tree
really would be the sight of a lifetime.
Was it all just for that?
I wouldn't say "just".
Oreki?
Anyway, why did you think it was him?
Well, I guess...
He was the only one I could think of who'd be able to
keep his cool after causing so much trouble for so many people.
I see...
But after hearing your explanation, now I'm certain.
What do you mean?
It's his dream to become a photographer.
He's attending a technical school in Osaka for that.
Ah, I get it.
He must've wanted to take pictures of that rare sight.
Well, then...
Oreki, I said in the dressing room that I was going to call the head priests, right?
Yeah, and the chaos calmed down instantly.
This isn't much of a story, but please listen.
Sure.
Do Not Cross
Nakagawa Constructions
Long ago, this area was divided into the north and south.
Our village was to the north, and another village was to the south.
Choukyuu
Bridge
There were fights over land and water.
That's long since past, but at religious events like this,
crossing over into their land can still spark conflict.
Ah, I see.
We need to give advance notice,
but only a few people have the means to do that.
That's where you come in?
If I let the people of the south know, we can pass through their land with no issues.
I see. Satoshi was right to call your family powerful.
I wonder.
This world is so tiny.
All I did was smooth over a problem
between the north and south halves of a small town north of Kamiyama city.
Of course, I'm not saying what I did was totally insignificant,
but I don't think it's anything major either.
I guess... that might be true.
Even if I go to college, I'll return here one day.
Wherever I may roam, I'll end up coming back here.
Oreki, what did you decide to major in from second year onward?
I chose arts.
I chose science.
I see.
I don't mind coming back here, nor do I find it sad.
I want to fulfill my duty as the daughter of the Chitanda family.
I've been thinking all this time of a means by which I could do that.
A means, huh?
There are two that I can think of.
One would be gaining wealth for everyone by producing high-value crops.
The other would be optimizing production by management so that no one will end up worse than they are now.
In the end, I chose the former.
That's why you chose science?
Yes.
Yeah, I'd say the latter wouldn't really fit you.
During the culture fair, I caused so much trouble for everyone that it made me realize.
I'm probably not fit for managing a company.
Yeah, I guess that's right.
Please look, Oreki.
This is my place.
All we have is water and soil.
The people aren't getting any younger either.
I don't think this place is the most beautiful ever,
nor do I see that many possibilities here.
But...
I wanted to show it to you.
Speaking of which...
That whole optimizing management idea you gave up on...
Why don't you leave that to me?
Speaking of what?
Ah, um...
I guess this is how Satoshi felt back then.
It's gotten cold lately, hasn't it?
No. It's already spring.
Choukyuu
Bridge
Do Not Cross
Nakagawa Constructions
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?