I wonder when I gave up on trying to escape from this picture.
I can't even remember that.
I really can't get out of it?
I'm sorry. I'll write it for you, so...
That's me.
Mother...
Are you all right getting up?
I feel much better today.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yeah.
I had always wanted to star in this director's movies.
It lasted for a short time, but my dream came true.
Your dream?
I hope yours will come true too, Kyou-chan.
It doesn't have to be grand, but as long as it comes from your heart...
A dream that will last forever.
I'm fine, Mother... since I've found it.
Is it fun?
Sorry. Am I disturbing you?
No, not really.
That was a really nice shot.
Can I see that?
Okay.
You're bad at shooting videos.
You took mostly my face, ignoring the shot of the ball.
Well, I didn't really intend to take that one.
Take a video of me again without my permission and I'll use my right hand.
This is why I'm not in a sports club.
But...
Hmm, which eleven o'clock is it?
So Kei didn't come to wake me up today.
Umm... Is it okay if I kiss you?
Renji-kun.
Renji-kun, right?
Yeah, that's right.
You're early today.
I have nothing else to do.
Umm, about yesterday...
Yes, I know.
That was unintentional...
I think I'll write a novel.
But as of now I can only remember thirteen hours worth of memories.
It would be impossible for me to do it alone.
It'll be all right. I'll help.
Yes.
Let's try doing it...
together.
Thank you.
And also, you are responsible, Renji-kun.
Responsible?
Because you embraced, confessed to and kissed me, right?
Eh? That kiss didn't happen!
But you did the other things though, right?
That was inevitable...
Were you just taking advantage of the confusion?
It's not like that...
Chihiro,
did you write that in your diary?
I forgot.
It's a dream that I gave up a long time ago.
You made me remember it again, Renji-kun.
Chihiro...
I want to try doing it again.
Miyamura-senpai!
What is it?
Umm, Shindou Kei-chan.
I need to talk with you.
Will you come with me?
Will it take a lot of time?
Probably.
Then I'm not interested.
I want to go home.
Huh, you're going home?
If you really need to talk, then you can follow me.
As long as it doesn't involve coming to school.
Well then, where should we do our activity?
Yes, good question.
What's the matter?
I'm confirming the time to have lunch.
I had breakfast at seven today so lunch time should be soon.
I see. We can go to my house and cook something...
Or maybe we can just go somewhere to eat.
Would you like to come too, Chihiro?
Will it be all right?
It will.
It surprised me for a bit.
I'm interested in Renji-kun's homemade food.
Eh? Me cooking food?
Didn't you just say you can go home and cook?
Did I say that?
You did.
Don't tell me you're actually really good at remembering things?
As long as it's within thirteen hours.
Oh my my, welcome.
Nice to meet you. I'm Shindou Chihiro.
Thank you for being polite. I'm Asou Sumire.
Renji-kun's sister?
His wife.
Sorry about that.
I don't want to believe it myself, but she is my mother.
Renji-kun's mother?
Yes.
This is our neighbor, Kuze-san.
Hello, I'm the man with the shining smile.
Good afternoon.
I see!
So I'm wondering... what is Chihiro-chan's relationship with Renji?
Relationship? I think we're just friends.
Well they say that there is no such thing as just friendship between a man and a woman.
I wonder if that's how it is...
Usually it ends up as a one-sided love from the man.
Umm, I don't think Renji-kun is someone like that.
He is just kind.
My goodness.
Oh my.
I wonder which things about Renji make him really good.
Since in my own eyes, I think he's an idiot.
Eh, I don't think he is.
Maybe that sparked the maternal instincts?
Is that so?
But, I was worried because there wasn't much news about girlfriends; Mom is so happy now though.
I just think it's interesting to watch.
So Chihiro, why did you fall in love with Renji?
Stop that already!
Don't you see that you're bothering Chihiro?
That's not true, right, Chihiro-chan?
Yes, it's fun.
See that?
So you ended up following me after all.
Well, I was the one who said I wanted to talk.
So hard-working, aren't you?
Don't tell me you're aiming for a perfect attendance?
That doesn't matter!
So what is this all about then?
T-That is...
Hirono-senpai is at a really important time in his life right now.
He has bad grades, his attendance is minimally safe, and there is a chance that he'll be held back.
But he can still recover.
If he just continues to go to school and study properly, then he can become a third-year student.
That's why you shouldn't make Hirono-senpai skip any more classes or confuse him!
I guess we both wasted our time.
It's not a matter worth giving up the perfect attendance award to talk about.
I thought I would hear something more interesting.
It's not a problem of  it being interesting or not!
Onii-ch-... This concerns Hirono-senpai's future.
Isn't that something that Hirono-kun should be thinking about on his own?
It's up to Hirono-kun himself to decide what he wants to do.
It's not something an outsider should worry about.
Outsider? That is...
Or are you saying that you can take responsibility?
Can you guarantee that as long as Hirono-kun goes to school he will have a good future?
That is...
Can Hirono-kun be successful as a mangaka by not doing something that he wants and to just study?
Hirono-kun is an adult. So wouldn't you think that he thought properly about drawing manga, skipping school, or studying?
Am I wrong?
But... Onii-chan is still just a student, so he should study for now.
Is being a mangaka really so easy in that you can just quit or start at any time?
He worked so hard that he hurt his own wrist.
If all of that effort was wasted, then would you be able to take that responsibility?
Kei-chan, just a note for you...
You're being honest at the wrong place.
If you can't realize that, then you will hate yourself someday.
If you go back now you can still be on time for sixth period.
Thank you for the food.
I never thought that Renji-kun would be really good at cooking.
Well, that's the only thing I'm good at.
Oh, you're writing what you ate?
Yes, since I might be taking in excessive nutrition.
Today, lunch is ten points. It has been a while...
Ten points?
By the way, my breakfast was four points.
Yesterday's dinner was seven points.
Is that a method of scoring?
It's hard to record them because it happens so often...
and it's difficult to evaluate them so I use an easy scoring system for it.
Won't that be scary to those who cook?
Can you cook, Chihiro?
It's not like I can't cook, but I shouldn't put whatever I cook into my mouth.
Our family is not so fond of cooking.
In other words, you can't, right?
Shall we start?
Then, take this.
It's a collection of ideas for the novel.
Please read it only after I leave.
I don't feel comfortable when someone reads something that I wrote in front of me.
I see, then I'll take them.
So what is especially difficult for Chihiro?
Difficult for me?
I just thought that it would be a good idea to know and confirm what Chihiro can't do.
Just think of it as editing.
I see.
For me, the biggest barrier would be having to finish everything in one day.
So it is time after all.
I forget details and subtle things...
and that changes the stage, story and even character impressions.
I always had to redo the novel halfway through because it didn't flow with the story.
By the way, I've been attempting it thirty-one times in a period of four years.
Thirty-one times, eh?
Then I will be the one to challenge that.
I don't know what to do myself. I'll leave it to you.
Roger. Is there something else that I need to watch out for?
Umm...
Huh?
Nothing.
What is it?
Please tell me anything that worries you while you're here.
Err... there was this problem during Math...
A sheep is tied up on the field.
What is the area of the grass the sheep go around and eat?
It should be the length of the leash squared, then multiplied by Pi.
It is said the sheep eat even the roots.
The grass will not regrow, so if you clear them it will turn into a desert.
When I heard this problem, I pictured the tied up sheep slowly dying.
I... This novel...
No, it's nothing.
Oh?
It must've been my mistake. It's nothing.
But...!
Please forget what I just said.
I see. Then I'll note that in my diary.
So you have a diary too, Renji-kun?
Nope, not at all.
Kei-chan, you're being honest at the wrong place.
You don't have to tell me that.
But...
What are you doing?
Just some drawing practice.
You're not going to draw manga?
Manga, huh?
You need to make a story for manga so...
A story? Shall I make one?
Chihiro will?
Yeah!
Because I like doing those things.
Onii-chan, I bought the magazine for this month!
Let's read it together.
So the main character will be...
Hey, Onii-chan, between Shiori or Shimiko, which girl do you like?
I wonder...
This is hard...
Show it to me.
Ah, don't read it yet. It's embarrassing.
It's fine, show me.
Onii-chan, let's go to the sea.
But today I promised Chihiro to draw manga together.
Chihiro said she has something to do today, so... okay?
Onee-chan?
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan there, there!
Yay, we did it!
It's all my fault.
Kei...
It's because I tried to gain an advantage.
I don't have the right to tell him my feelings.
Is that an excuse you made for yourself?
You've been running in the same place all along...
Eh?
while wishing and waiting for someone that will come and take you away.
Hello?
Ah, Kei? I need to talk with you.
I can't talk over the phone, so can you meet with me?
Yes, I can.
Thank you for your hospitality.
You are welcome here any time.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Chihiro, see you tomorrow.
Yes, see you tomorrow.
Umm...
What is it?
Have we met before, Kuze-san?
Well, I'm friends with Himura so I know everything about you, Chihiro.
I see. As I expected.
I'm sorry.
No, don't worry about it.
Well then, shall I teach you a poem?
A poem?
How many mountains and rivers...
must I cross before I reach that country...
where my loneliness will end?
Today too I shall journey.
It's by Wakayama Bokusui.
What does it mean?
How big of a mountain or river do you have to cross in order to go to a country without loneliness?
We know there is no such thing, but let's start a new journey today.
It's about sadness, but the poem is pretty cheerful.
I learned this poem from Himura.
He must have remembered the poem for someone for a long time.
Welcome back.
I'm home!
Did you enjoy it?
Yes.
I see. I'm glad.
Ah, sorry for calling you over at this hour.
Is someone here?
Something like that.
Anyway, come in.
Yo, good evening.
The guy from this morning!
You know him, right? Tsutsumi Kyousuke.
He is my classmate and a Film Club member.
Make that ex-member now.
He has something to tell you, Kei.
Me?
Yeah.
Actually, I want you to go out with me.
"The girl is only one in the world."
The girl is only one in the world.
That made her the god of this world.
She found herself on an island when she began to understand things around her.
The island was small, and one could go around it in half a day by foot.
Stretching as far as she could see in a 360-degree view at the beach...
there was only the sea, the clouds and the horizon.
There was a castle on the island.
There was a huge amount of preserved foods inside the warehouse of the castle, so she did not have to starve.
There was a mountain of books that one could never finish in their lifetime too.
Those things were her world.
The books were all about humans.
"Humans cannot live by themselves." That sentence was everywhere in the books.
But the girl was alone.
She continued to live despite being alone.
Neither laughing nor crying.
She did not need anything that was written to be important.
She was deciding.
She was finishing.
"In the history of man, she was the first human to be balanced."
"The statistical balance of a single person...
is identical with one's self."
"That is why everything she does is correct."
"But at the same time, everything might be wrong."
The sheep...
The area of the circle is the square of the chain's length multiplied by 3.14.
The length of the chain is twelve years.
The same length since the accident four years ago.
The farthest that the hands can reach out is thirteen hours.
That is everything of the me right now.
Fear and anxiety flow together with the raining time.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Rain.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?