All the upperclassmen look so graceful and mature.
Would you expect any less from a prestigious academy for girls?
That girl was kind of scary.
I guess even Fuji Girls' has people like that.
There they are, the Fuji girls.
I'll kick this ball, and you'll save them and move in.
Be sure to introduce me to them later!
Idiot! You kicked it too hard!
This is no place for balls!
We're very sorry!
Are you all right?
W-We're fine.
Th-Thank you very much!
No problem.
Later!
She's so cool!
What's the word? "Wild"?
Exactly.
She's Kurahashi Riko, Fuji Girls' awesome bad girl,
also known as "The Wild One."
The Wild One
Fujisaki Girls Middle School
Second-year
Kurahashi Riko
The Wild One is so dreamy!
Oh, look. It's Maki.
Her beauty never fails to amaze me.
Not only that, she's the student council president and has excellent grades.
How I want to be her!
She's every bit Fuji's Princess!
Fuji's Princess
Fujisaki Girls Middle School
Second-year
Maki Natsuo
Fujisaki Girls Middle School
Second-year
Maki Natsuo
Poor thing.
What an embarrassing nickname to have.
Has
an
even
worse
nickname
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Their Fateful Meeting
It's already been a year since I studied my butt off to get into Fuji Girls'.
I wonder where it all went wrong.
Hey, Kurahashi! Wait up!
Would you be a dear and take these to the student council room?
What? Why me?
You just need to hand them off to Maki.
Could you, please?
This sucks.
Maki, eh?
This place is full of serious and quiet girls led by that super honor student.
Oh, come on. It's too quiet here, even for them!
Why can't something big go down?
Like l-l-love, maybe?
Now I get it.
I just find all of this boring.
Smooch!
That was just an illusion.
Mind explaining what that
drool-covered thing is to me, then?
This is a fairy.
Worst fairy ever.
I'm done for!
Someone saw me practicing how to kiss!
Don't worry about it!
It was so pathetic, I can't even make fun—
Soon the entire school will know about it,
and then it'll dominate airwaves across the globe!
I'll have nowhere to go in this world!
Naturally, I'd have to take refuge elsewhere...
Oh, Father, Mother,
forgive me for leaving this life before you.
Would you listen to me?!
Given the circumstances, I have no choice!
H-Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Now that you've uncovered my secret, I cannot just let you leave.
Say what?!
Is this supposed to be a bribe?
Relax, I won't tell anyone.
What?
I did this kinda stuff when I was a kid too.
I've been training in secret because I really want to experience love.
Do you know what I mean?
I do!
Will you help me out, then?
Of course!
Huh?
First impressions are crucial when it comes to love!
Time to practice bumping into someone 'round the corner!
It's so clichéd, it's almost refreshing.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
This is stupid.
Hey!
We can't make a connection if you avoid me.
That's not a connection, it's a collision!
I figured it'd be more memorable that way.
It's more likely to cause amnesia!
Curb your enthusiasm a bit, will ya?
Okay!
Very well. Start.
Are you trying to start a relationship or a fight?
You've got it all wrong!
If it all goes according to plan,
I'd bump into a guy, only to have my hair get tangled in his button,
causing him to say, "Your hair's so silky."
Even though it's tangled in his button?
Don't be greedy or overdramatic. Just act naturally!
You've got it easy, since you're pretty—
Pretty?
Pretty weird.
Pretty weird?!
You say some harsh things, but they're very informative.
Are you a love expert?!
Huh?
Riko, age six
I like the one on the right better.
You'd better keep this a secret, Riko.
Riko, age eleven
I like your friend Noriko.
You're like one of the guys.
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
Former
schoolmates
Riko, age thirteen
I'm glad we don't have to worry about falling for you.
Present-day Riko, age fourteen
Kurahashi?
I-I guess?
I do have a few guys wrapped around my fingers and all...
I knew it!
I'll be counting on your help, then.
Sure thing!
After school the next day
Great. I made it through another day.
Hey, Riko!
Outta the way!
Look at this!
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Never thought I'd see the day when you joined the student council.
What the hell was that?!
Welcome.
Why drag me into this mess?!
Kurahashi, you're hurting me!
Damn you!
Unbelievable.
Y-You don't have to do any work.
Huh?
I just wanted the chance to talk to you more.
Am I asking for too much?
Well, not really...
Great!
Can we practice how to hold hands, then?
I'd like to tender my resignation.
Rejected!
Can we make it so that the "assistant" thing never happened?
I'll still help you with your love training or whatever.
N-No!
As long as we'll be using this room to practice, I'll need you to be part of the student council.
What if we had to do it outside and someone saw us?
That'd completely ruin my image!
Did you forget we practiced in the hallway yesterday?
What have I done?!
Does she even need love training?
She's smart and attractive.
What more could you ask for?
This is all your fault, to begin with.
Huh?
All because you saw Huggy and me practicing how to kiss!
She could afford to suck less at coming up with names.
By the way, this is an illustration of my ideal boyfriend.
She's not very artistic, either.
My bad, but it's not like I did it on purpose.
More importantly, you can't seriously be using that.
What?!
But you said you practiced how to kiss too!
Th-That was a long time ago!
Oh, right. You're a love expert.
There's no need for you to practice kissing anymore.
Gulp!
I-It happened on a steamy day in summer.
Oh my god! You're amazing!
Please, master!
Teach me how to hold hands!
A-All right.
Okay, so we've been dating for two weeks.
We started off as friends,
so now it's too embarrassing for us to act like lovers.
That's awfully specific.
I can't believe we're going out.
We have to start there?!
Do you remember that day at the beach?
Not a clue.
You meanie! That was the day our love blossomed!
I don't give a shit!
You refuse to hold hands!
And you don't understand how I feel!
You suck at this!
Now fully gets
how guys feel
when they have
to deal with an
emotional woman
Stop being so melodramatic!
I-I figured it'd make things more exciting.
Besides, it's important to get the mood right.
Who cares about that?!
The end result's not gonna change, so give me your hand already!
Once again gets how guys feel...
I'm kinda shocked.
So am I.
Once again gets how guys feel...
Retry
Ow!
Oh? Was this supposed to be a crash course in self-defense?
Forgive me!
I was trying to show off how cute I was by playing a harmless prank!
I had no idea holding hands was so dangerous.
It is if you dislocate some fingers every time you do.
How was the first time you held hands with your boyfriend?
What?!
W-Well...
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Okay, then. I'll see you here tomorrow.
S-Scratch that!
Nope. See you tomorrow.
Kurahashi Riko - Becomes the president's assistant
Maki Natsuo, the student council president,
is extremely talented.
She handles the planning and execution of all kinds of school events, keeps tabs on each club,
makes decisions at committee meetings,
and negotiates with the faculty.
All sorts of things, as you can see.
And she does it precisely and promptly.
Truly a super duper middle schooler.
I may be an assistant in name only, but all right.
Hey, need help with anything?
Huh? Oh, don't worry about it.
Yeah, but...
I'm only compiling the love research I did with you, anyway.
So you weren't working?!
Oh yeah, where's everyone else?
At least summon the vice president and have her help.
I can't do that.
Wh-Why not?
Because I'm the vice president as well!
Huh?
That's what I originally was.
I was assisting the president, a third-year.
Hey, is there any work for me?
Oh, I did all of it already.
I see. Then let's settle the matter from the other day—
Including that.
Didn't a teacher ask us to—
And that.
Just be the president then!
All because I was too talented...
That girl has issues, but so do you.
Also, the treasurer was a cut above the rest when it came to handling money, but...
...-box.
Is that our budget for this semester?
PlaceStation4...
Mintendo GS...
iBat...
She was being so scary that I banned her from here.
Don't you have a single normal member?
The secretary, a first-year, is a nice girl.
She's really shy, though,
so I've never gotten a proper look at her.
Is she even real?
She is.
Completed paperwork will sometimes appear in front of the door,
or the room will be cleaned.
Sounds like a fairy's doing to me.
Either way, I mostly get things done by myself, so it's okay.
No, it's not.
You're talented, I admit, but what are you gonna do if you take on too much and break down?
Kurahashi...
Gosh, did you say I'm talented?
Praise me more!
You've got a pretty nasty personality, don't you?
Anyway, guys seem like they'd avoid a girl who does everything perfectly.
You won't get yourself a guy if you don't screw up from time to time.
It's super effective!
The next day
Oh no! This is bad!
I'm such a klutz!
How forced.
I accidentally handed out the wrong papers to the entire school!
Yeah, whatever.
I mistakenly turned in the love lab results...
Maki's as fast as ever, I see.
Love Lab Results
Maki Natsuo
It has come to light that we made a grave error!
We're recalling these!
We apologize for causing a fuss!
She really is fast.
I'm so glad they hadn't read it yet!
If you're gonna cry about it,
don't spill the milk in the first place!
What should I do with this fool?!
You were right, Kurahashi.
People make mistakes all the time.
That's exactly why we need someone by our side to correct them!
Maki...
You thought that'd fool me?!
I'm sorry.
Ahem.
Let's take it from the top.
Today, on our love training agenda: first impressions!
We already did that one, though.
That's... a pretty good technique, but it's got a crucial weakness: it only works in the morning.
I don't think it works then, either.
So today, we'll be perfecting...
"Operation: Drop Your Handkerchief
and Have a Guy to Pick it up for You"!
Yay!
That's a classic!
First, you must casually drop your handkerchief.
Him again?
And when he calls out to you, saying,
"Hey, you dropped your handkerchief,"
you run away!
What happened to being casual?
We'll innocently run through the city together.
Man, he's such a nice guy.
And before you know it,
you've reached a flowerbed on a cape.
Where the hell is this?!
I finally caught you, Natsuo.
I like you. No, I love you!
Me too!
I'm never gonna let you go!
Hold it right there!
First, get this delusion outta your head!
Why would you run away in the first place?
Simply accepting it won't lead to love.
But if I run away,
love might blossom while he's chasing me.
What the hell are you expecting from a stranger?
Besides, running away would just piss him off. It's rude.
You're right. If it's obvious that I'm running away...
Oh, I know!
I'll make myself look as graceful as a swan,
but behind the scenes I'll be running with all I've got!
How's that?
That's not behind the scenes at all!
Come, now. Catch me if you can!
Don't wanna. You're creeping me out.
Why?
Stay away from me!
A-Are you really as smart as they say you are?!
Don't tell me you're using a body double outside here...
So mean!
H-How rude.
Talented as I am, I always strive to be
able to handle whatever comes my way.
See? This is what it looks like on the back.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
That reads like some kind of questionable ad.
P.S. This handkerchief represents a lot of my
memories of my grandmother.
The postscript on the bottom-right will seal the deal for me!
What an awful strategy.
My grandmother's still alive.
That's just a scam!
Jeez, don't use this!
Revealing your personal information like that's too dangerous!
Good grief. What part of her is talented?
Let's continue this tomorrow.
Okay!
Riko!
Are you also on your way home, Mika?
Yeah.
Seriously though, you in the student council?
Hell's gotta be frozen over.
Can it, dumbass.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Yeah, later.
You too, Prez.
Sorry about that.
Do people always call you Riko?
Yeah. Or well, the people I'm close to do, at least.
Then can I call you Riko too?
Or maybe Rikoriko?
Wait, R-R-Rikopin!
What am I, a nutrient?
I-I'm sorry.
Just call me Riko.
O-Okay, Riko!
You can call me Natsuo too—
Nah, I'll stick to Maki.
What?!
It's way easier to say.
No way!
The next day
Kurahashi!
There you go with your flashy hairbands again!
You know that wearing one with decorations is against the rules!
I'm sorry.
Your skirt's a bit too short as well.
You're a student council member now,
so why don't you learn a bit from Maki?
O-Over my dead body.
And I really mean it.
You mustn't give up so easily!
Anyway, don't disgrace this
school with your appearance.
Who cares if I dress up a little?
I'm sure Maki wants to do it too.
Maki isn't like you.
Yeah, yeah, she's an excellent student,
but "not like you"? The hell's that mean?
We're not all that different on the inside.
Riko!
Let's study how to seductively show off the nape of your neck today!
I take that back. We're completely different.
Oh? You don't have your hair tied up today.
Doesn't matter, does it?
But you usually—
Did you realize the potential of neck exposure too?
Ow, ow, ow...
Doesn't matter, right?
That hurts!
Crap. That wasn't Maki's fault.
Anyway, what was that about necks?
I hear guys get excited when they see the back of a girl's neck.
So I thought we could figure out an effective way to give them what they want.
Just tie your hair up normally.
Normally's fine?
Got it! I'll give it a shot!
I don't have anything to tie my hair with...
Oh, I've got that cov—
This is the first time I'm getting my hair tied up by a friend.
Kinda makes me happy.
Also, your hairband was really cute.
Hear that, Teach?
All done.
Do I look cute?
Yeah, totally.
Does looking at my nape excite you?
Um, Riko...
Thank you for joining the student council.
That aside, what should we do next?
More love research, obviously.
In order to show off my neck...
There!
Doing this makes it clearly visible from every angle, right?
Yeah, it does.
What do you think, Riko?
Does my nape look good?
Is it shining?!
Yeah, totally.
You're spinning too fast for me to see, though.
Hey! You okay?!
I feel sick.
Are you stupid?!
If your admirers could see you now, they'd cry.
If that happened...
I'd cry first.
I-I'm so sorry!
H-Hey!
Was that the first-year secretary?
That was a fairy.
A fairy, yeah...
Hey! Don't try to escape reality!
Come back!
Get back here, Maki!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Hey, Riko.
I really do think beginnings are vital for everything.
Where's this coming from, Maki?
That's exactly it!
Please, just call me Natsuo!
What?
If that's too hard to say,
"Nacchan" and "Nuts" sound pretty cute to me.
All right, then. I'll take the O from Natsuo
and call you "Old man."
Maki, please.
Nah, but...
Yes, Ms. Maki, ma'am!
The Cool, the Shy, and the Voyeur?