Please revoke my guard orders.
Miss McCunnen.
I have something important to do.
What if I say...
...there is something more important than that?
What would that be?
Can't be...
That's right.
This is your passport.
The real you,...
your past,
is here.
Ein.
Be careful.
I didn't know...
There was no way we could have known...
the destiny that awaited us from then on.
Our future.
You can take a look, you know?
Are you afraid to reclaim your past?
I have been killing people at the organization's demand.
Yes, you've rendered such brilliant services.
But that was...
...because I have neither memory nor past.
You were following orders like a machine.
You felt no sin.
If you return to your old self...
...the guilt of your sins may haunt you.
That's what you're afraid of, isn't it?
But that's the reason why I want you to take it back.
The real you.
By your own free will.
My will...
Distance, 249 yards.
Intermittent wind from the south.
Return to the real you...
...while accepting all of it.
The identity as Zwei.
What a selfish request.
You people took my memory...
...and stained these hands with blood.
And now...
It's a revolution.
The organization is about to be reborn.
When that happens...
Zwei...
I want you.
But no matter your competence,
I don't want a mere puppet that follows orders.
What I want is a comrade in arms.
A subordinate I can trust.
Someone who would follow me of his own will.
Once I know my past...
I... I'm not sure I can be myself...
If it comes to that...
My mission is to back up the attack.
These are my targets.
Take this!
What organization are they with?
The cargo!
A sniper?
We did it!
Not yet, Aniki.
Just go!
Aye!
To pin us down like this...
They sure have guts.
Try saying your name.
Azuma...
Reiji.
So you've remembered it all.
That's right.
I was...
...on a trip...
...and then...
How many people...
So many people... with these hands...
I only...
...wanted to live.
It would have been better if I had not remembered anything.
Like I told you.
I don't want a mere puppet.
You must wake from your dream.
Return to yourself.
The past and the sins...
Accept and face them.
Through your own will.
Azuma Reiji.
Phantom?!
Scythe, that bastard!
What do you want me to do?
Follow me,
Reiji.
By your own will.
There are people here that need your strength.
This is your destined place.
If you're willing to stain those hands further with more blood and follow me carrying your sins,
I can promise you a wonderful world.
However...
This is not coercion.
You have one more option.
Another...
Another option...
That is...
Return... to Japan?
If it is what you truly wish for,
I can arrange it for you.
You might doubt me, but...
I'm serious about this.
I would really return you...
...to your hometown.
What I want...
...is a subordinate with a strong will.
You idiot! What're you doing shooting your own people?
I don't care if it's Scythe's order,
stop being a puppet!
You won't have anywhere to run!
Think it through!
That snake bastard is just using you as a sacrificial pawn.
Return...
...to Japan.
This is a big decision for you.
I can give you time.
Think this over by yourself.
Yes, Azuma speaking.
Hello?
There's no way I can...
...ever return.
Find her!
That bastard Scythe has done it now.
Have you heard how many casualties we incurred?
He will get just what he deserves.
Naturally...
...Phantom as well.
Ein! What's wrong?
Are you here to kill me?
What are you talking about?
You haven't heard anything?
Then hurry up and get back to the organization.
You are still able to...
Ein!
Ein...
It's me.
Sudden change of plan!
Scythe has betrayed the organization.
He used Phantom to attack Inferno's cargo hold.
Scythe went into hiding,
and Phantom has escaped as well.
She took a bullet from Lizzie, though.
The organization is currently looking for them with all its manpower.
Neither have been found yet.
They suspect you too, but...
I can prove where you were.
There is no more time to deliberate.
You have to make a choice soon.
Come to my side...
or...
But I need to tell you this:
Both Scythe and Phantom are our enemies.
If you choose to side with them, the organization will...
The bleeding won't stop.
The bullet is still in there.
I need to find a doctor.
I can't!
The hospitals have probably been compromised by the organization.
I have to do it myself.
Hang in there.
Ein.
All escape routes have been blocked.
They are like caged birds now.
They can't flee from the organization.
Not even Phantom.
The only thing left is choosing the predator for the prey.
Please don't die.
Ein.
You still can't find them even after looking for them with so many men?
The freeways? Block them!
Shit!
If only I'd killed her back there.
Clau, what about him?
Zwei?
He's Scythe's pet dog as well.
Chances are he goes over to their side.
If that happens, Lizzie...
You will be the one...
...to kill him.
Ein.
The truth is...
Miss McCunnen gave me a passport tonight.
My passport.
And I remembered everything.
My hometown,
my family.
I have a place to return to.
I remembered my name as well.
My name is Reiji.
Azuma Reiji.
It's a lot better than the crude "Zwei", isn't it?
But somehow...
...it didn't really make me happy.
I'm no longer the me from back then.
I'm a human that isn't supposed to exist.
Do I have no choice but to return to the organization?
Ein...
Will you return with me...
Both Scythe and Phantom are our enemies.
If you choose to side with them...
the organization will...
...kill you.
I can't!
If we return, Ein will...
In that case...
Leaving Ein...
and returning by myself...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Don't mind me.
The wind...
Blue, white and green.
That's all that's left.
The rest is a place of emptiness.
But it's so bright and dazzling...
The wind blows...
A really strong wind.
Ein.
Be careful.
You too.
We, having no names...
...only followed our orders.
We were used as pawns and discarded afterwards.
Don't mess with us.
Such a meaningless life...
Ein...
Ein.
The only one to protect you now...
...is me.
I won't leave you behind.
I will never hand you over to the organization.
Let's run together.
From this town.
From Inferno.
Reiji...
Let's go, Ein...
Together.
I'll give you a new name.
Not like Phantom or a number.
Your name.