Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
Takamatsu-kun, your report please.
Yes.
Weapons Storage reports that we're almost out of gunpowder.
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
We need to replenish our supplies before the next battle.
We've got new recruits too, so we probably need new weapons too.
That's true.
Understood.
Let's make today's mission a descent to Guild.
D-Descent?
What's wrong, Otonashi?
I'm kind of not good with heights...
What are you talking about?
We're not descending from the sky, we're going down underground.
Oh what, just underground?
Wait, underground?!
It's a place deep underground that we call Guild.
Our comrades are making weapons there.
It's there so that Angel doesn't find out about it?
That's right.
If she took down Guild, we'd lose our source of ammunition and any chances of winning.
Yo!
It's me.
We'll be headed your way tonight.
We'll leave deactivating the traps to you.
Understood, tonight then?
We'll be waiting.
Okay.
We'll be going with everyone present here.
Huh?
Is it okay to leave Noda behind?
That idiot's probably just doing whatever he wants again.
Gymnasium
And heave!
Alright, let's go!
Come on don't stand around, we're going.
In there?
This is the entrance?
It's been a while since I've been to Guild.
Guild Accessway B1
It's pretty dark.
Hey, there's someone here.
There's an idiot here.
Otonashi, I don't recognize you as one of us yet.
Why on earth did he go out of his way to wait here for us?
Noda-kun likes to stress the importance of the moment.
I don't understand him.
I don't particularly want to be accepted by you.
Why you little...
This time it'll be 1000—
Defensive positions!
The traps haven't been deactivated?!
What's going on?
It's exactly as you can see.
The route to Guild has several anti-Angel instant-fatality traps set up.
This means that they're all still active.
Which means...
Maybe they forgot to deactivate them?
Are they trying to wipe us out?
No, Guild used their own judgment and reset the traps.
Why?
There could only be one reason.
Angel has appeared.
Down here?
Just wild then.
What a blunder.
The guys at Guild would do this even though they know we're on the way?
It seems you don't understand yet.
Whatever happens, it's not like we'll die.
Although, we will experience the pain of it...
That's the part I don't like...
But if Guild's whereabouts are discovered and they fall, we'll no longer be able to replenish ammo or replace broken weapons.
How would we be able to fight Angel in that state?
Guild's decision was correct.
Should we go after Angel?
While the traps are still set?
Angel will be taken down by the traps right?
Let's just go back.
The traps will only slow her down.
We'll give chase.
Advance!
Guild Accessway B3
By the way, what kind of traps are there?
There are all sorts.
Look forward to them.
Damn, one's coming!
Huh? What is?
Run!
Fuckin' crazy.
This way!
Quickly!
Takamatsu's voice...
He got caught, then.
Everyone else seems to be okay.
Let's go.
Was it okay not to rescue him?
It's not like he'll die.
If we leave him alone he'll find his way above ground on his own.
Really?
Come on.
Sorry.
Thanks for the help.
It's fine, I quite like you.
Are you...
No!
Guild Accessway B6
Will it open?
Not a chance.
Damn, I forgot!
This is a trap that shuts you in!
Don't forget something so important!!
How thoughtless...
Something dangerous is coming.
Duck!
Get down!
What was that?
What happens if you touch that?
It'll cut your body clean in half.
The second beam is coming!
What do we do?
Get under it!
The third beam is coming!
What was the third beam again?
X'er!
How are we supposed to avoid that?
Everyone, just do what you can!
Hurry up and open it!
Don't look!
You don't want to see that.
What happened?
It opened, hurry!
The victim this time was Matsushita-kun, huh.
There was no helping it with his build.
That guy needs to go on a diet.
That must have been a pretty terrible sight.
Right in front of him, too.
I'm glad you made it through.
Incidentally, even if you get cut into pieces, you'll return to normal after a while.
Guild Accessway B8
The trap's been activated!
Damn, I forgot!
The ceiling comes down in here!
I said don't forget things like that!
TK!
Hurry up!
You can make it!
Oh! Run to her and hug her tight!
Thanks.
See you.
Sorry.
TK's sacrifice will be—
You guys sacrificed him.
Like I said, it's all good.
Don't let his sacrifice go to waste, let's go.
Guild Accessway B9
What's wrong?
Something...
Damn, I forgot!
I said don't forget!
You're too heavy, I can't hold on!
Should Otonashi and I drop down?
Wait a second, don't decide things on your own!
It wouldn't be good to lose our forces all at once here.
I get it, hurry and climb up!
Can you do it, Otonashi?
I don't really have a choice, right?
You're quite a sadist, aren't you.
Shut up!
Shoulders next!
What are you doing? Stop resting and hurry up!
Where should I grab?
Anywhere! Do what you like!
Hurry up.
Yeah...
You'll fall like that.
You're right...
Why does she smell so good?
This is bad...
Gotta climb up.
Why are you facing this way?
I can't help it!
W-Will you hurry up and climb?
Yeah...
Don't hold yourself up using that!!
Idiot!
Um... Hinata—
He became a precious sacrifice.
I see.
We're down to four.
You did well to survive, newbie.
I guess.
The next one will be you.
Guild Accessway B13
A water trap...
So he can't swim?
The exit is this way. Come.
Guild Accessway B15
Here.
Thanks.
Yuri! Over here!
Shiina-san?
Let's go.
Why is something like that—
That's—
That puppy's going to be washed away!
Shiina-san, no!
What a blunder!
It was a toy!
Even Shiina-san fell prey to a trap!
That an anti-Angel trap?!
Or rather, you can tell just by looking at it...
Her weakness is her love for cute things.
Oh?
That's actually pretty cute of her.
But she'll be okay, right?
Guild Accessway B17
Looks like you're the only one left.
Seems so.
If this were a real army, everyone would be dead.
I'm a horrible leader.
There's no helping it.
They're anti-Angel traps.
They'd be useless if they weren't this effective.
Um...
Why don't we take a break?
You're right.
I want to dry off these clothes.
It's amazing how you can command those crazy guys.
Why did you get chosen as the leader?
Because I was the first to rebel.
That's the only reason.
Against Angel?
Right.
I had siblings.
Unlike you, I kept my memories.
When you were alive, before you came to this world?
Right.
Including me, four siblings.
I was the eldest, with two younger sisters and a brother.
My parents did well in their jobs, so we were a really wealthy family.
Our house was surrounded by nature.
It was almost like a holiday home.
It was during summer vacation.
Our parents were out that afternoon.
Some men we didn't know came into the house.
They were wearing balaclavas even though it was the middle of summer.
You could immediately tell that they were up to no good.
I thought that as the eldest, I had to protect my siblings.
But there was no way I could, right?
They were after money, of course.
But they couldn't find anything.
They ran around smashing windows and TVs, and started to get angry.
Then they thought up the worst possible thing for us.
Little girl, you're the eldest.
They must have told you where the valuables are.
Like, "If there's an earthquake, take it and run," or, "If a burglar comes, give it to them and tell them to go away."
They must have told you something.
They didn't.
They didn't tell me anything like that!
Come now, why don't you go search for something?
If we don't like it, you might have to say goodbye to one of these kids here.
One every ten minutes.
Come back with one in ten minutes.
I desperately searched the house.
My head was in so much pain.
I was nauseous and about to collapse.
But their lives were on the line.
I had to find something.
But I didn't know of anything valuable.
The time!
I need to hurry! I need to hurry!
If I bring this big vase...
It's heavy!
If it's this heavy, it has to be really valuable!
The police came thirty minutes later.
I was the only one left.
Me alone.
I don't really care if I become a water flea or whatever.
All I want to do is fight God if he really does exist.
It's just too unreasonable.
We hadn't done anything wrong.
Yet on that day, even with my confidence as an older sister,
everything I wanted to protect was stolen from me within the space of 30 minutes.
How could it be that unreasonable?
I can't accept that kind of life.
You're strong aren't you, Yuri?
If I had memories like that, I think I'd want to vanish as soon as possible.
But you're fighting.
That's right.
Hey...
Can I ask you one thing?
What?
How did you die?
Idiot.
I didn't commit suicide or anything.
Why would someone who committed suicide bother fighting?
And anyway, there's no one in this world who died by suicide.
Come on, let's go.
I'm going to protect you.
This is Guild?
Guild - Deepest Point
It's Yurippe!
She's here!
She got here safely!
These guys make weapons here?
You managed to fight your way through all those traps!
That's our Yuri!
Never mind that, where's Angel?
She stopped for a while, but she's on the move again.
She set another one off!
She's close...
Yurippe...
We're abandoning this place.
No way!
Are you serious, Yurippe?
Yeah, we can't just stop making weapons!
What's important isn't locations or weapons.
It's your memories.
Have you forgotten that?
No...
What do you mean, Yuri?
In this world, nothing that has life can be created.
However, things that just have form can be.
If you have the method and means to make something, there's no problem creating it.
You can even create it out of dirt.
However, efficiency became prioritized and now all we do is make replicas in this factory.
Chaa-san...
Is this guy in high school too?
Basically, we just breathe life into something that looks like what we remember.
We'll head for Old Guild then.
It's a place we abandoned long ago.
There's nothing left there, but there are mountains of dirt.
We can get up to ground level from there too.
And this place...
We'll blow it up.
We won't hand over Old Guild to Angel.
That's the sole remaining place for us.
But...
She's right above us!
Your only necessary belongings are your memories and your pride as a craftsman.
That's all.
Am I wrong? Well?
No!
Alright, prepare the explosives!
Show me your teamwork!
Okay!
There are no more traps left.
Hurry!
Where are you going, Yuri?
To buy some time!
Oh, you came?
Aren't you scared?
There's nothing for me to do down there anyway.
Here she comes.
Let's go!
Guard Skill: Distortion
She's responding too quickly!
Amazing...
She can hold her own in close combat?
Load the barrel!
Can we really do that here?
It's fine, just do it!
One, two! One, two!
Hurry up and raise it!
Guard Skill: Delay
Dammit!
Otonashi-kun!
Move it, you two!
Looks like you guys can pull through if you try!
That doesn't look like it was easy to make.
This way, Otonashi-kun!
Here we go!
All hands, take cover!
Fire!
Are they okay?
The cannon...
I guess we can't just put together stuff we don't know remember...
Don't just put random things together!!
Angel's getting up!
You guys!
Use these on her!
Hurry to the shelter!
The evacuation's complete!
Okay!
We're blowing up Guild.
You sure?
Do it.
Here goes!
I wonder how many years its been...
There seriously is nothing here.
Old Guild
It's almost funny.
You'll get as much dirt as you want if you poke around the walls.
This is one run down joint.
We're counting on you again.
Yeah.
Alright, let's get to work!
Are you idiots awake yet?
We blew up Guild, and Angel with it.
Relay this to everyone.
Head to Old Guild.
We'll replenish supplies as quickly as possible.
Head to Old Guild before Angel recovers.
I repeat, hurry up you idiots.
I saved her without thinking...
What am I doing?
All I want to do is fight God if he really does exist.
It's just too unreasonable.
Too frustrating.
You really are amazing.
No wonder everyone follows you.
You're a fine leader.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
Why is the new song...
Christ!
...a ballad?
...is what you can call me.
You couldn't sing the song you like.
Angel's home.
Really bad fever.
Also, pump it up!
Memories
So what's happening exactly?
One second you guys.
Angel's appeared.
This is the worst setting.
End of the line.
I see you in a different light.
And also...
don't touch it!