Seconds!
Sure thing!
What the hell am I doing?!
What?
How did you end up eating breakfast at our place?!
And you! Why aren't you bothered by it?
Why would I be? Since Taiga-chan is so small, she takes up so little space.
Besides, it's more delicious when you eat breakfast with everyone.
Give me another helping already.
I cooked enough for three. How much do you intend to eat?!
T-Timoten.
Ryuuji and Taiga
Sheesh, are you trying to make your pet molt from stress?
Don't let it get any uglier.
Don't call it ugly!
In truth, pets are similar to their owners.
Why, you...
You ungrateful little—!
Have some respect for me! I made you breakfast and  prepared a lunchbox!
Shut up, you mongrel.
Mon—! Calling me that again!
Give the lunchbox back! Give my kindness back!
Shut up and rot.
Wait up, Aisaka!
Ever since that late-night attack, Aisaka Taiga has begun appearing at our dinner table.
School Road
I told you to wait!
And now...
More importantly,
once we get to school, make sure that you properly...
um... mediate things...
between Kitamura-kun and me.
You promised me you'd work like a dog for me, after all!
...things have ended up like this.
If things seem to take a bad turn...
Minorin!
You're late, Taiga!
Good to see you perky today, too!
Good morning, Minorin.
Huh? What? You're kidding me.
I'm so sorry, I had no idea that
Taiga and Takasu-kun are now in a
companioned, commuting relationship!
You've got it all wr—
You know, people don't use
"companioned" like that these days.
That wasn't the problem!
Oh, you're right. These days, they say...
Egads, I don't know what they call it these days!
Wait, how about "togethered"?
I'm telling you, that's not it!
I just happened to stumble upon Aisaka over there.
Isn't that right, Ais—
Oh, so it was just a coincidence?
Apparently we live close to each other.
Really?
Um...
Well, see you later, Takasu-kun!
Yesterday, I was watching TV and...
I get it now.
In order to get closer to Kushieda, I'll first have to mediate between Aisaka and Kitamura.
Let's bring it!
And that's it for shooting practice. Onwards, we'll pair u-
Hey, Aisaka. Let's pair up.
Yes, let's pair up, Takasu-kun!
Yeah!
...up and pass balls!
Takasu, Aisaka, you two are really fired up.
Taiga?
Is it that kind of a day today?
The plan is simple.
I'll lightly peg Kitamura's partner with the ball.
And then...
you'll cause a big fuss and take his partner to the infirmary.
Thus, Aisaka and Kitamura will lose their partners, and pair up instead.
Maruo! Let's pair up!
Who'll be wanting to team up with Haruto-kun today?!
Sure thing. And stop calling me that.
But you're so similar!
What the?
K-Kitamura-kun's pairing up with that weirdo!
What's up with that?
Events have taken a turn for the weir—
Kushieda!
Want to pair up?
Okay, let's do this!
Even Kushieda...
The plan will continue regardless.
Wha—? But then...
It doesn't matter what gender his partner is.
And the swelling bulges drawn in the Jouan era...
What's wrong, Haruta?
I'll throw the ball without using my thumbs!
That didn't reach me, Kushieda.
The road to understanding the Satoru-ball is steep.
Huh?
Don't mind me, not everyone knows about this.
That Noto...!
Hey, pass!
Hey, hey, hey! Hey! Pass, pass! Pass!
Here I go, Maruo!
Yeah.
Nice form.
What're you saying, Maruo?
No, really, that was very good.
Hey, pass!
Pass, you say...
There you go again!
But pegging a girl with the ball...
Here I go!
PASS!
I'm sorry, Kihara. I will atone for this.
Clone...!
I'm sorry, Maruo!
What happened?
The Palmtop Tiger got taken down by Takasu-kun!
O-Oops.
Home Economics Practice Room
The Palmtop Tiger snarls at whoever's around.
Even so, she's trying so hard that she makes a fool of herself,
so you just end up wanting to help her.
Listen up, you have  to hand them over casually
Don't overdo it.
O-Okay.
As nonchalantly as possible, right?
Thoughtlessly, informally, frivolously...
Let's go.
Huh, where's Kitamura?
If you're looking for Kitamura, he said he had some business over at building B or some—
T-Takasu-kun!
He just left, so he might be that wa-
There he is!
Follow him!
Y-Yeah!
What?
Get out of the way!
She's fast!
At that speed, she'll catch him—
Ryuuji!
Are the cookies okay...?
Huh?
Just as I thought. It's swollen.
Did you find the cookies?
Were they undamaged?
I-I see...
Hey.
I might just be a klutz.
She wasn't aware of that already?
If I write a love letter, I end up putting it in the wrong bag.
If I try to invade a house, I fall over from hunger.
If I play basketball, I get a ball right in the face.
If I try to hand over some cookies, I fall down the stairs...
Dropping the cookies...
Now, now, there's more.
Like forgetting to put the love letter inside the envelope.
There was that, too...
Give me one of those.
Huh? Wait, they are  smashed into pieces...
And besides they t—
They're great!
They came out okay, didn't they?
It's a shame. Let's try harder next time.
I did  see them. They were buying things like spring onions and radishes at the supermarket. Are they like, married?
Statement, Witness #1, Year 2 Class C, H-To K-ji
They left the same apartment building together with naughty looks on their faces.
Statement, Witness #2, Year 2 Class C, K-hara M-ya
Also, they were feeding each other homemade cookies saying, "Here, open up!"
Statement, Witness #3, Year 2 Class C, N-to H-mitsu
Statement, Witness #4, Year 2 Class C, K-shii N-nako
Really? Are they like that? No way!
Hey, Minorin. What's up with your best friend?
What the?
Hey, get inside already.
My.
"My"?
May I have a moment?
The sun is dry...
What's up with Kushieda-san?
I don't know.
Takasu-kun.
Yes! What, me?
Please take good care of Taiga!
Huh?
Taiga is my dearest best friend!
Please bestow happiness upon her!
Wait, Kushieda. Are you saying you're—?
Happiness?
So that's how it was.
You must be happy!
Kitamura? What're you doing up there?
I was wondering why you were together so often,
but now that I think about it, you two fit together so well!
Aisaka! Get yourself together!
You! Stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you make Taiga cry... I won't forgive you.
Kushi... eda...
I'm sorry.
Minorin misunderstood everything because I was intruding at your house.
No, that's—
Your place was...
really cozy.
You see, I struggled so much with my parents that when I said I wanted to leave,
they simply gave me that apartment.
I knew they were those kind of parents, but...
The cookies were salty, weren't they?
I was frustrated when I found them in pieces, so I ate some.
They were horrible!
Yet you ate all of them.
You even lied about their taste.
Even as a mongrel, your fur will shed if you keep being so nice to everyone.
Mind your own business.
Hey, do you also get troubled while thinking about Minori?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I guess you would...
Aisaka?
Why doesn't anyone understand us?
Even when we're so troubled, why doesn't anyone support us?
In truth, everyone...
Everyone's... Everyone's... Everyone's...
PISSING ME OFF!
Pissing me off!
Who's the Palmtop Tiger?!
I'm not okay with being that at all!
Minorin, you idiot!
Kitamura-kun, you idiot!
Why won't you listen to me?!
Even mom, even dad, no one...
Understands me...
I'll help out.
Do you have a problem with me being small?!
Stop calling me a delinquent just because of my appearance!
Do you have a problem with us being together in front of everyone?!
I'm sorry for having evil-looking eyes!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, Ryuuji, isn't this pole tilted now?
Huh? That's not poss—
It is  tilted!
See?!
Yes!
We won, we won!
All right, I've decided!
Tomorrow, I will confess to Kitamura-kun.
It'll all be over then.
Over?
Your services as a dog will be over.
As of tomorrow, we're just classmates who live close to each other.
And that's all there is to it.
Bye bye, Takasu-kun.
Yeah...
Ryuu-chan...
Aren't we having breakfast really early today?
Yacchan likes canned mackerel, but...
Is Taiga-chan still sleeping?
I don't know.
Did you have a fight?
No, we didn't.
I'm so bored.
Right?
Yes.
H-Hey.
Did she...?
T-Takasu, we're sorry.
We spread all those weird rumors...
Aisaka-san got mad at us.
Huh?
"There's nothing between me and Ryuuji."
Saying you're not a delinquent, making a huge mess.
She really is scary, the Palmtop Tiger.
But I said that Takasu isn't as scary as he looks, right?
What, when did you?
More importantly, shouldn't we clean this up real fast?
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun, I'm sorry.
A-About what?
You see, Taiga was saying...
"I'm absolutely not going out with Takasu-kun."
"So this is all a misunderstanding."
She especially wanted me to be aware of this...
And she had this kind of desperate, serious look about her.
But does that mean she...
Does that mean she—
Do you know, Takasu-kun?
Takasu-kun?
What does she think she's doing?
Weren't you going to confess to Kitamura today?!
This isn't the time to be worrying about me!
As of tomorrow, we're just classmates who live close to each other.
And that's all there is to it.
"And that's all there is to it"?
Kitamura-kun!
Huh?!
I... Kitamura-kun...
I have feelings... um...
Um, uh... I, uh... That is...
Why are you doing it right after arriving at school?
If things don't turn out well, this will be one hell of a bad day, you know.
Um, uh...
Wait up.
I think I get how this conversation will spell out.
But before that, I would like to verify something.
Aren't you dating Takasu-kun?
That's just Minorin misunderstanding things!
There's nothing between us!
So you don't like him?
It's not like that!
Our houses just happen to be close to each other.
It has nothing to do with liking him or not.
Then, do you dislike him?
I don't dislike him.
But it's not about that!
Um, you see, Takasu-kun is...
Yes, fried rice!
Ryuuji made me delicious fried rice!
He cheered me up...
He even lied to make me feel better...
Being there for me...
Because Ryuuji was there, because he was supporting me...!
Because of that, I'm now capable of standing here like this!
I'm in love with you, Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, you're amazing.
I see.
It's okay, I think your feelings were properly relayed.
Kitamura-kun...?
Do you recall one year ago?
Yeah.
Unlike that time, you now have this
funny-looking face!
Funny face?
Yeah, when you're around Takasu, you have this funny-looking face.
Takasu's a great guy.
And you, thinking of him like you did earlier,
makes you a wonderful girl.
Like I did earlier...?
What did I say?
But I'm relieved you're on such good terms with Takasu.
W-W-Wait up!
Ryuuji doesn't have anything to do-
My face was looking funny?
My feet, what about my feet? Wait, what am I saying?
Was I able to tell you I love you?
It's going to be okay, Aisaka.
It's okay.
What's going to be okay?!
You haven't understood what I was saying!
It'll be okay, from now on, I'm sure we'll be great friends.
Like I'm saying, not friends, I was confess—
Friends...?
Yes, friends.
Oops, we'll be late for homeroom.
Better hurry up, Aisaka!
I thought you were going to start crying.
Y-You! D-Did you see all of it?
I did, but I didn't mean to..
"Didn't mean to"? You—!
But what're you going to do?
I'm going home.
I see.
I'll make you food.
You haven't had breakfast, have you?
And did you even eat last night?
I'm sure you went to the convenie—
Stop it!
Why? If you do that again, people will start misunderstanding again.
I've told you you don't have to do this anymore!
I don't get it either.
But I can't leave you alone!
I'm telling you it's enough already!
You're no longer my dog!
I see.
Yes, I am not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
Thus, I'm able to be by your side!
Ais-
Taiga!
"Taiga"?
Since the ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast that could equally stand with a tiger.
I'll become a dragon.
And thus, as a dragon, I'll be able to be at your side, tiger.
There's a limit to how impudent you can be!
Oww....
Know your place already!
Why, you...
Hey!
Hurry up, I'm hungry, you know.
Huh?
And we're going to make a new plan.
I'm not giving up on Kitamura-kun from just that.
Does that mean...?
It doesn't matter whether you're a dog or a dragon...
Since you said you'd be at my side, you better work hard, Ryuuji.
Did I decide on this too quickly...?
Come on already!
Yeah, yeah.
He said, "Taiga."
Your Song
Next Episode Preview
Club activities-girl, Kushieda.
Heart-warming girl, Kushieda.
Ah, you're Kushieda!
Always shining so brightly with joy!
Eat that, a home run!