Listen well, girls.
New Year's Cleaning is meant to show thanks for the past year and meet the new one with a clean slate,
so be certain not to miss a spot.
Okay!
Don't miss a spot!
Oh, so you're spending the holiday with Kanata.
Yes, Mr. Nishikido invited me.
That's wonderful, Towa.
You're going on a family trip, Minamin?
Yes, my father is taking us to see wild penguins.
Wild penguins?!
Figures.
I'm thinking of chilling at home.
Since Dad's finally coming home, you know?
Are you helping at the store, Haruka?
Of course!
The store's always busy this time of year!
I've lost everything...
I've left Dysdark...
for good.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Amazing!
It really snowed on thick!
It doesn't happen often.
It's so pretty!
Incroyable!
It's never snowed this much in Hope Kingdom!
Then let's go somewhere wider!
Huh?
Beautiful?!
The Wandering Shut and the Castle of Ice!
Yay, we're the first ones on the field!
Come, Towie, the first step is all yours.
I wanna go, too!
What a nice snow angel!
I'm gonna make one, too!
I can't move...
I. Am. Done!
I've finished mine as well!
We're finished here!
Not bad, if I say so myself!
My, how adorable!
You should make something too, Towa!
Indeed, what should I make?
Haruharu?
Sorry, Haruno!
My hand slipped!
Yuuki?
The boys are here, too?
All right, returning fire!
Man, you suck!
Geez!
Towa, what are you making?
A castle.
A castle?
Yes.
Hope Kingdom's castle.
I'll help!
Let's build it in the hopes that you
can return to Hope Kingdom soon.
Let's make it big enough for Perf to fit inside!
Certainly!
Whatcha making?
A snow hut?
No, a castle!
A castle?
That sounds like fun!
We might as well make it big enough for us to fit!
That'd be simply splendid!
Hey guys, out shoveling snow?
No, we're building a castle!
A castle?
That sounds wonderful.
So, which castle is it?
Right! It's, uh...
It's an original work.
Like this?
Right!
Nanase, what are you drawing?
Well, it's...
There are so many people now!
Akagi!
Kanda! Segawa!
We heard you're building a snow castle!
Can we join in?
But of course!
Everyone's working hard!
Allow nous to cheer them on!
Oh, what a nice song.
It'll probably collapse if it's only made of snow.
Can we build the frame out of something else?
Maybe...
Shirogane, dorm mother.
Why not use some of the materials we cleaned out?
Ah!
I heard your pleas.
Oh, Ichijou Ranko.
A snow castle makes for a catchy headline and might turn some heads,
but taking the world by storm doesn't come easy!
Allow me to assist!
Sure, do whatever.
Our special soup lunch is ready!
Everyone, come here to warm up!
Have this, too!
Over here!
Don't look at me...
Don't give me that look...
Could it be that I'm even lower than that pigeon now?
Me, of all people?
It's finished!
It's perfect!
We all worked together, so of course it is!
It's beautiful!
It looks like the real thing!
I couldn't have made this alone.
This is thanks to my many friends.
All the better, Princess Towa.
Indeed!
Ugh, I gotta change or I'm gonna catch a cold!
Me too! I'm chilled to the finger bones!
I seem to have forgotten my gloves!
Please, go ahead without me.
I'll get them for you!
Worry not, I can handle my own affairs.
She's a model Noble Academy student now.
Shut?!
Why are you...
Why?
I... can't say myself.
Is that... Hope Kingdom's castle?
Even the elements mock me?!
How dare you!
Right, I'll just destroy them...
I'll destroy you, this world,
and everything else that ruined me!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
I sense a Dyspairvil!
Shut!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Scarlet!
Girls!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
With strength, grace, and beauty?
Beauty, you say?!
What beauty do you lot have?
Beauty is allowed...
for naught... but me!
Scarlet?
I won't let him destroy any more!
Yeah, he won't!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Bubble Ripple!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Is he powering up on his own despair?
I'll just destroy this world!
And everything I despise!
Begone!
Shut! What has driven you so far?
Silence! You're one to talk!
Scarlet!
Twilight!
I know now that it was our encounter that sent my fate spiraling!
If it weren't for you, I'd have never fallen so low!
Yes, if it weren't for you, I could have...
I could have regained my status with beauty!
Scarlet!
This is who I am!
My strength is almost as beautiful as me!
Beautiful?
Puh-lease.
What?!
You should look in a mirror.
Ice!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Hideous!
This... is me?!
Duh. You're just throwing a tantrum.
You're simply blaming others.
I don't believe there's an ounce of beauty to that.
Sh-Shut up! Shut up! Stop talking!
Lock looked down on me,
Close looked down on me,
and even Dyspear abandoned me!
I have naught but myself!
I can trust in naught but me!
What the...
Shut?
Let's save him.
Yes.
Shut, settle down!
Precure!
Scarlet Illusion!
Now!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
What are you thinking, Twilight?
Twilight was a lonely woman
who could never think of others.
Refinement, majesty, and elegance were the world to her.
But I think differently now.
Because I've received so much warmth that I hold dear.
Warmth you hold dear?
The strength and grace we display in protecting it...
is what I now feel gives us true beauty.
We can change, Shut.
Just come with me.
I suppose the castle was destroyed.
Don't worry, we've got time!
If we start rebuilding now...
Haruka!
Girls!
Yui, did you...
Well, you're always protecting our dreams,
so we at least want to protect our castle.
Yui...
It's...
absolutely beautiful.
With strength, grace, and beauty, eh?
You wouldn't look too beautiful with a cold.
I'm home!
Oh, Harukaaaaa!
Welcome home, Sis!
Perfect timing!
Can you help out?
Okay, you got it!
Have a great year, everyone.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
I wonder if I'm getting closer to the fairytale Princess of Flowers?
H-Haruharu, that dress—
Whaaaa?! I really am the Princess of Flowers!
This is simply splendid!
What is the meaning of this?
It's suspicious... I have a bad feeling!
Go! Princess Precure:
Like a Flower,
With Strength, Grace, and Beauty!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Kanagawa Prefecture - Wakana (Age 10)
Tokyo - Chisaki (Age 5)