Good morning, Run-chan.
Good morning.
Got your panties on?
Of course! No more sleepyhead mistakes for me!
C'mon, let's go!
Run-chan...
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Sure enough, fizzy drinks really wake you up!
Normally it's COFFEE, though.
It is? But they're bubbly and make my
eyes sparkly, so they wake me up in a flash!
Is that how it goes?
Hyaa!
Nice shot.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Toru today.
She has class duties today,
so she'll be busy till afternoon.
Oh...
We're always together,
so with her gone, it's kinda lonely.
Yeah. But if she has class duties,
it can't be helped.
Oh.
What's wrong, Nagi?
Say... Don't you want to have a look?
At what?
Toru the freshman!
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
CLASSMATES
Ah! Look at this graffiti!
It's still there.
They can't get rid of it because it's carved,
I guess. Anyway, let's get a move on.
Hey, wait!
Freshman-year classrooms...
Takes you back, huh?
It wasn't that long ago, though.
Ah! Ain't that it? Toru's classroom.
What's Toru like in class?
Do you think she's scared?
Toru's actually a top student.
No way! I imagine her just running wild.
Yeah! S-swinging a bat around,
staining the classroom with blood...
I don't think she's doing that.
Ma'am, I'm finished.
Thank you as always.
Um, the number of boys on here was wrong,
so I corrected it. Is that all right?
Oh, really? That was my mistake.
Thank you. You were a big help.
No, not at all.
TO~ORU!
"Not at all," she says. What a good girl!
The teacher counts on you, huh?
You little so-and-so!
Why are they
here?
The teacher counts on you, huh?
You little so-and-so!
Why are they
here?
Um...
I forgot my textbook,
so do you mind if I see yours?
Sure.
Thank you very much!
Sorry. I forgot my contacts today.
O-oh.
Argh, I can't see!
TOO
CLOSE
Thank you very much! You were a big help!
No problem.
My name is Yutaka.
The truth is, I've wanted to talk to you for a long,
long time! But I never had the chance.
Ah.
From now on, let's be friends...
Torun!
TORUN
I'll buy you a drink as proof we've gotten closer!
Wait...
What was that?
Huh? Toru?
What's the matter?
Whoa. This is unusual.
GRIND GRIND
A-ain't that a little tight?
Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
GRIND GRIND
What's wrong with Toru?
Beats me.
Sorry for the wait, Torun!
I went and bought us some more!
Huh? Torun? Where did you go? Torun!
Um, excuse me.
Sorry?
Your forehead is pretty. It's very nice.
Run's talking to some strange guy.
Oh, thank you.
Like...
In any case, where might the nurse's office be?
What's with that shirt?
That way.
I see. Thank you.
Well, see you.
Nagi-chan!
Hey, who was that?
The new school nurse, he said.
It looks like he got lost.
Oh, is that it? I thought
he was some suspicious guy.
Also, he said my forehead
was pretty and very nice!
Isn't that a bit strange?
Huh. A new school nurse?
He looks pretty suspicious.
School Nurse
Mr. Sato
He looks pretty suspicious.
But I think he'll be popular with the girls, and...
There he is again!
Thank you for earlier. You were a big help.
Not at all. No need to thank me!
Say, you should come have some fun
in the nurse's office.
I'll get a special bed ready.
You're funny!
Come by anytime.
Something's been moving around since earlier...
Who are you?
Don't be so casual with Run-chan!
Huh. So you're "Run-chan," eh?
Mind if I call you that?
Sure!
Ah. "Run-chan."
How cute. Run-CHAN.
You look like a sea urchin,
so you're Urchin-chan.
She sure looks depressed...
It's like showing kindness to the enemy.
That really is cute, Run-chan. Your forehead.
Thank you very much!
That's right. It really is...
Really is... Oh, yes...
Get away from Run-chan!
M-my apologies. It's time for my medicine.
Oh. He has a weak constitution.
That's right. Look at THIS! Ta-daa!
Note: A single by okinawan artist Cocco that came out in 1996 and was a
big hit; the phrase was later adopted as the slogan for Tower Records.
"No music, no life"!
Note: A single by okinawan artist Cocco that came out in 1996 and was a
big hit; the phrase was later adopted as the slogan for Tower Records.
Whoa! You bought one of the
limited-edition-color models!
Oh, I did?
Nice. I really want one, too.
You sure are high tech!
What kinds of songs do you listen to, Run?
Um...
I still have a no-music life.
You haven't entered any songs?
I tried different ways, but I couldn't put
any songs on it, so I thought it was broken.
Like that...
MD Combo Unit
It won't
connect...
MD Combo Unit
It won't
connect...
And this...
Cassette
It won't
connect
Cassette
And this...
It won't
connect
Cassette
And that...
Like
with a
TV
Slap it
at a
with a
TV
Yeah...
But sure enough, it didn't work!
What was that last thing?! The last one!
You took it apart?!
Well, I thought it was broken.
You thought an amateur like you could fix it?!
There are other options,
like sending it to the manufacturer!
Just calm down. It's not like it was yours.
If it were mine, I'd take YOU apart!
It's all right.
I'm not broken, so that wouldn't be necessary.
That's not what I mean!
It turned on!
Ah, thank goodness.
Run, you gotta use a computer
to put songs on that.
Huh?
I don't have one.
Then why did you buy that?!
Um, where do you go
whenever you have free time?
I won't let go until you tell me.
I-It's not true! Torun, wait!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Are you mad?
I'm not mad.
It's so stretched out...
It will shrink when I wash it.
No. We must use it like THIS!
Now then, where shall we go?
I, Yutaka, will take you there!
Run-chan...
Oh. She has PE next, does she?
Todokisou nanoni todokanai kankei
A relationship that looks like it will reach you, but doesn't
Nani ga hitsuyou? Nani ga tarinai?
What is required? What is there not enough of?
Sagasanakutemo honto wa shitteru
The truth is, you know even without searching
Hon no sukoshi no yuuki to tsuyogari
Just a little courage and bravery
(I miss you) Ke-tai nara ima sugu ni
(I miss you) on the cell phone, right now
(I miss you) Koe no kimi ni wa aeru kedo
(I miss you) I can "meet" you in voice
(Hold me tight) Boku ga kowarechau kurai
(Hold me tight) But I want you to squeeze me
(Don't you feel me?) Gyutto shite hoshii nda
(Don't you feel me?) So tight I could break
Calmly
and
Quietly
(Don't you feel me?) Gyutto shite hoshii nda
(Don't you feel me?) So tight I could break
Calmly
and
Quietly
(I miss you) Ima sugu ni demo aitai
(I miss you) I want to see you, right now
Calmly
and
Quietly
(This ain't right) Koi to wa dokoka chigau kedo
(This ain't right) It's different from love, somehow
Koko ni ite kurenakya imi ga nai yo
If you aren't here for me, it all means nothing
Dakara gyutto shite hoshii nda (Never get enough)
So I want you to squeeze me (Never get enough)
Run-chan...
In the end,
it was Toru's job
to put songs on it
IN USE
I mean...
STILL using these tiny things
in this day and age is just strange.
True enough.
Other schools use knee-length shorts.
These things are little more than panties!
Putting them on though we're wearing panties...
It's panties on panties!
Nagi?
Having class in our panties is just strange!
Are you not embarrassed
because they're not panties?
It IS embarrassing!
You're more embarrassing than our shorts.
Yelling that over and over
makes you sound like you like it.
Aaand begin warm-up exercises!
Hup!
Say...
What is it, Yuko-chan?
Are we supposed to pull?
We PUSH, don't we?
Oh, really? Well, on "three".
Okay, bring it!
One, two!
What are those two doing?
Hup!
Looks like we were supposed
to pull earlier, huh?
That's right, Yuko-chan.
This one we're doing right!
Look like you're having fun. Hey.
You play around too much and you'll get hurt.
No problem!
Note: she got spooked, reminded of Sadako, the creepy J-ghost girl.
Huh?
What's the matter, Nagi-chan?
N-Nothing at all!
Okay, here's the next problem...
Torun, are you looking at me, Yutaka?
No doubt about it!
Can I do something for you?!
Move.
Well, who can solve this problem?
You certainly are eager.
You mean me?
That's right. Come up front.
Torun!
Yuko-chan!
Try keeping that out instead of tucking it in.
My PE shirt?
She's not wearing any.
Nagi-chan! Look, look! Yuko-chan's not
wearing any! She's not wearing any!
Run, keep your voice down!
And that's what happened.
Toru, YOU'RE wearing PE clothes, right?
You're telling me to tuck it out?
I don't think it'll meet your expectations.
It's just...
A regular dress!
You're so good at packing things away!
She praised me.
Torun...
What's this?
Okay, class will now start. Everyone,
make pairs to do your warm-up exercises.
Torun!
You MUST pair up with me, Yutaka!
Oh. Miporin.
Yutaka, you're going to pair up with ME, right?
But I have to pair up with Torun-
With ME, right?
WITH ME, RIGHT?
Okay, come this way.
Miporin!
Say, Yuko, do you have any bandages?
What happened? You hurt?
No, I just fell in PE class earlier
and skinned my knee.
Oh, that's bad! You gotta hurry and sterilize it.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
For something like this, washing it with water
and putting a bandage on it is plenty.
No way! If it gets infected, it'll get really bad!
Look, it's fine. The next class
is about to start, anyway.
C'mon, hurry.
Hey, wait!
I'm telling you, really, I'm fine.
No way!
I wonder if something happened.
Excuse...
Yuko-chan!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I never thought you'd be THERE.
Yeah... I had a fit and fell over. Thank you.
Yuko-chan!
What happen... ed? Huh?
I'm sorry, sir. I didn't see you.
No, no. If anything, it was my honor to be
stepped on by you, Run-chan.
Um, you seem to have taken a shine to Run,
Mr. Sato. Just what is it about her?
Hrm? How she seems able to talk
without reservation...
How truthful she seems...
True enough.
Also, her mild, air-headed sadism.
And her forehead is pretty.
The width of her forehead is the best.
Also, her forehead's...
Th-this doctor is...
Sorry for the bother.
Come by anytime.
Class already started, huh?
Sorry for making you late, too.
No. A scrape is nothing to take lightly.
Understood. I'll be careful.
Still, I wonder if that Sato person will be okay...
How so?
He was on the floor earlier, right?
I wonder if he's fine all by himself.
It's a little worrisome.
That's right!
It's dangerous!
Dangerous how?
He has...
S-some strange inclinations.
Oh. That kind of danger.
He complimented me,
said my forehead was pretty!
True, that sounds dangerous.
Right?!
Aah, whatever.
Torun, please explain this to me.
Sure. What don't you understand?
All of it!
Fine, I'll start from the beginning.
Okay!
Toru-san sure is kind, huh?
Yeah.
Why don't you understand?
We've gone through this over and over!
I'm sorry! This is like this, right?
No, it's not right! It goes like THIS!
But this goes like this.
If it were me, I would've given up.
No, it goes like THIS!
Sure enough.
Understand?
Not at all.
Yutaka.
Oh, Miporin.
Yutaka, you've been bothering
Toru-san too much recently.
Sorry, Toru-san. You don't have to indulge her.
It's really a bother, isn't it?
C'mon, we're going.
That was a big nuisance for Toru-san. If you just
can't understand something, then ask ME first!
Being lonely when someone's not around...
I'm not thinking that! I'm not!
Toru! Toru, wait!
GRIND GRIND
No! No, I said!
I wonder what happened to Toru.
GRIND GRIND
Beats me.
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
Uncle! Uncle! Uncle!
I'm NOT lonely.
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!
And so! I, Yutaka, and Miporin
played a prominent role this time!
In any case, it's already summer!
What, already? Isn't that a bit fast?
Yes, well, there are reasons for it. Like a
swimsuit episode or a hot springs episode.
No, I don't think there'll be any hot springs.
But before anyone changes into a bathing suit,
there will be great, difficult problem...
Next
Episode!
Next time on A-Channel: "Kilogram"
A diet, huh?
I, Yutaka, have a nice body,
so that word is foreign to me!