How long do you plan on sleeping?
School's already over.
What is it?
You could've woken me up some other way.
What?
Actually...
I want to discuss something with you.
Is that the sort of attitude you should have when you're asking for something?
So what?!
It's something that you'll benefit from anyway.
Why do you look so skeptical?
Tell me about it.
Before I do, I want you to come to the roof.
Why did you bring me here?
So what is it?
Just come along.
Umm...
If I remember correctly, you're from the class next to ours...
Umm, Sanae...
On second thought, I...
Can't hear you! Can't hear you!
Well, see you later.
You're Elen's friend, right?
Fujiwara-san, was it?
It's Fujieda.
I'm Fujieda Mio.
So you know Sanae.
Yes, umm...
We were in the same class during freshman year.
Oh...
By the way, did you want something from me?
Actually... I just wanted to ask you something.
Is it something about Elen?
No, it isn't...
Umm...
What I want to ask about is you.
Reiji-san, do you...
Do you have anyone you like right now?
But I guess it wouldn't be someone like me.
That means...
No... Umm...
Mio?
Elen!
Brother, what are you...
...doing here?
I was wondering who you were talking to.
You know Mio?
No...
Why are you here?
I was looking for Mio.
I suddenly wanted to eat Kanekoya's waffles,
so I wanted to ask Mio if she'd tag along.
Hey, wanna go?
I have something to do today...
Bye!
Did I intrude on something?
You barged right in.
Did something happen?
She was confessing to me...
Huh?
Like I said, Fujiwara-san was about to.
It's Fujieda.
Wait, seriously?
Mio confessed to you?
Yeah, I guess...
Mio's taste is odd.
What's that supposed to mean?
So how did you reply to her?
You barged in before I could, then-
Go after her!
I think Mio would really want to hear a reply.
This might sound weird coming from the one who barged in...
...but you can't just ignore her!
But I don't know how I should...
Think about that yourself.
Like I said...
Just go!
Jeez, I went all the way to set it up for you.
Why don't you just get to the main points?
I'm sorry.
You should've just followed the game plan.
"I like you, so be my boyfriend."
Like that.
Then just strangle him until he agrees.
It won't take longer than five seconds.
Confessing is a blitzkrieg!
What's there to think about?
But, I...
I don't think I can do it!
Oh, goddammit!
This is the final spring of your school life!
Do you plan on wasting it?
Sanae.
Great timing!
We were planning to look for you after this.
Thank goodness I found you guys.
I have something to say to Fujieda-san.
So get out of my sight.
Oh, really?
All right, Master.
I'll get the hell out of your sight right away.
Please take your time.
What are you doing, Sanae?
Well, well...
Fujieda-san, umm...
Yes?
About what just happened...
It was just too sudden...
How should I put it?
Quit peeping.
Okay...
Like I said...
Yes?
Well...
So how did you reply to her?
"Let's just start off by being friends."
That's such an ordinary reply.
There's no taste in it at all.
Leave me alone.
So, did you make any plans with that friend of yours?
We're going into town tomorrow.
Brother...
What?
Be a good escort.
Mio is my friend.
If you were to embarrass her...
Bang!
That's violent.
I'm supporting you guys.
Mio's a nice girl.
Yeah, I could tell right after our small chat.
So!
Give me some temporary pocket money!
I already gave you this month's.
Really? Really?
I can't believe you're already going on a date.
This is a great step forward for our late blooming Mio!
That's great.
What are you girls talking about?
Oh, Auntie.
Sorry for intruding.
Same here.
No, don't worry about it.
Auntie, this is a major event!
It's big news!
What is it?
Tomorrow, Mio's going on-
Don't say it!
Let me guess, a date?
How do you know?
Did you bring your boxed lunch?
I got it.
I'm off.
Wait a sec.
All right, now it's 40 points.
That's low.
Review what I told you yesterday.
I like you!
I love you.
It's not about money.
What kind of host are you?
Thank you for the meal.
It tasted really good.
I wanted to take you to a restaurant...
You live alone with Elen, right?
Our parents died in an accident.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
It was a long time ago.
I don't feel anything special about it.
You're strong, aren't you?
I live alone with my mom, too.
But knowing that my mother works so hard...
I sometimes wish I had a father.
That's what I think.
You have to support your mom.
If you need a guy for anything, I'm always around.
Thank you!
Let's see. Next is...
What's that?
That looks like Sanae's handwriting.
Go to a place that you can't say...
Reiji-san, what sort of a place is "a place that you can't say"?
After boarding the staircase that leads to adulthood,
you'll become Cinderella!
I'm a guy.
As long as you complete the schedule I gave you,
your date will end perfectly!
Damn that Sanae...
It's a woman.
It's amazing that she's riding such a big motorcycle.
I'd never be able to buy such an awesome bike since I'm destined to be poor-
Huh? When did...
Reiji-san?
Most of the sound was hidden by a silencer.
The sound of a 9mm parabellum bullet, huh?
That woke me up from my dream.
Traveling from Mexico to Peru by land.
Then from the Palau Islands to the Philippines.
And then it's been half a year since we've settled in Japan.
We should've forgotten our past and continued to live on here... On this piece of land.
This is your hometown.
You've changed a lot after coming to this country.
I can tell just by looking.
Your heart is opening up slowly.
That's what a hometown is, right?
But this is the end.
They're here.
Inferno?
I don't know.
But I received a silent warning.
I see.
So it's time we wake up from our dreams.
If it were possible, I'd like you to keep staying in your dreams.
To forget what you've been through.
What about you?
I...
I still need a confession of my sins.
Confession of your sins?
To who?
To God directly, because I'll meet with Him one day.
Elen...
Inferno is finally here.
Even though I don't want to...
We'll make use Fujieda-san's feelings.
Fujieda-san's feelings?
What do you mean, Elen?!
Right after giving birth to her, Fujieda-san's parents...
Yeah, I heard about it from her.
Everyone around her told her that her father had disappeared.
Even now, she still believes that lie.
Lie?
Her father is important enough to be in the newspaper.
Who was it?
Godoh Kaiten.
The leader of the large-area mafia group - the Godoh Group.
Godoh Group?!
Correct.
Fujieda is a surname from her mother's side.
That Godoh Group...
Does she know...
No, she doesn't.
Even inside the Godoh Group, only a few know of Mio's existence.
The entire reason was to protect his separated wife and daughter from the power struggle.
Then Mio and Godoh Daisuke are...
Yeah, siblings through the same father.
Godoh Kaiten doesn't want his daughter involved in any mayhem,
but he can't protect her out in the open.
Mio is Godoh Kaiten's biggest weakness.
How do you know that?
I heard it from Scythe Master.
Scythe Master?
It was from a long time ago,
but I told you that after Master escaped from Inferno,
he was hiding in Japan, right?
Yeah.
Back then, Master thoroughly investigated the Godoh Group.
Master also planned on using this weakness if he had to.
Weakness?
Don't tell me you want to use Fujieda-san to threaten the Godoh Group?
Just in case, it can be our ace card.
Right now, the young leader holding the Godoh Group's power is Shiga Toru.
A member of Inferno.
Now you understand the situation, right?
Even if it's Inferno you're going against, as long as you hold Mio as a hostage...
Why didn't you tell me?
That's right. I should've told you sooner.
If only I had known that Mio was interested in you.
If only I had known that they'd be here so quickly.
Our life here was surprisingly short.
We have to make preparations to escape.
Yeah, you're right.
We should escape.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It's okay to cry right now.
Right now, you can still be like how you were before.
That would be too selfish.
It's only natural to be prepared for something like this.
Since we're refugees.
No, you've already forgotten.
But that's good.
I was happy because of that.
Elen...
For the past six months, your smile and sleeping face were filled with happiness.
Just looking at you like that made me happy.
If the hometown you were born in can bring peace to your heart...
Someday, I'll also...
That's the dream I have.
Because you promised me that one day you'd bring me back to my hometown.
I don't want the happiness you had up until now to be a lie.
We can come back another time.
Even if we leave, this country won't just disappear.
You'll definitely be able to come back to your hometown some day.
A day will come when we can live truly normal lives.
But that day is not now.
What?
Reiji left in the middle of the date?
It wasn't a date...
Also, Reiji-san said he had something important to do.
For young people in their prime,
nothing is more important than love!
You're too loud...
Jeez.
I even gave him a schedule!
Maybe you should just mind your own business.
That's too bad.
I guess...
Oh, "I guess"?
Speak of...
...the devil!
Hey, that hurts!
Sanae...
Come on, Sanae.
Reiji-san, I had a lot of fun yesterday.
Me too...
Did you take care of your important matter?
Yeah, I did.
You're pretty good to be able to block my attack.
You're just a little worse than me.
I have some business with Elen, so I need to go first.
Bye.
Where do you think you're going
and leaving your girlfriend behind?
Is he upset?
Something feels different...
About Reiji-san.
Why... Why are you here?!
No, putting that aside... Is it really you?
Were you still alive?
Cal!
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you... the Old Phantom?