I want you to do another job for me in Los Angeles soon.
But I thought we were shifting our activities to the East Coast...
McGuire and the others didn't order this operation.
This is for me to get some points.
You want to do an unexpected job,
to make the higher ups owe you one?
Yes.
That's why we need to do this in a clandestine manner.
I'm not personally against such plotting.
I thought so.
Very well.
I'll make sure everything is done secretly.
This will show how important Phantom is.
That was the weekly weather forecast.
We will continue with the breaking news.
Who was that?
I have a shift change where I work part time.
They asked me if I could come now.
I see.
I'll drive you there.
I was planning on practicing my driving today.
You don't have to.
Isn't that normal for a couple that's living together?
I guess so.
In other news.
The drug market on the West Coast...
...has been under the rule of the Chinese mafia for a long time.
But lately, a Japanese organization has been very active with their interventions.
This has resulted in frequent fights within the vicinity of Chinatown.
According to the reports,
the issue could develop into a large conflict...
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I won't get involved in that.
I'm not talking about that.
I don't want anyone finding this place because of a commotion.
R-Right...
Were you going out?
Ms McCunnen.
Want to hang out with me?
I'm sorry. I have to practice my driving.
Then you can practice it with this.
I'll walk there.
So? Do you like this car?
It feels like you could go on forever, right?
Doesn't it feel like you're the ruler of the world?
No way.
It's just to show off.
I'm amazed you manged to stop.
A little more and it would have been the end for us.
End?
Nothing would end.
Even if I died...
Just because there's one less murderer...
You can't.
You can't die in vain.
I'll decide where you die.
The man who earned my trust has that right.
Move.
We'll keep moving forward, Zwei.
This mission wasn't part of the plan.
Well, think of it as a part time job.
Okay.
Looks like Claudia has some kind of attachment to Zwei.
Make sure she doesn't steal him.
Even if she did, that wouldn't pose a problem.
Zwei's existence isn't vital for me to carry out my missions.
That's true.
This pairing with Zwei is just the result of a coincidence anyway.
You can drive a bit longer.
Come back in about an hour.
What's going on?
Get used to driving a car like this.
Okay.
Have some fun, Zwei.
That's a pretty nice car.
Is it okay for you to meet me like this?
You needn't worry.
I made sure to cover my tracks.
That's why you can speak openly here.
I'm glad to hear that.
I thought about your plan thoroughly.
So, you provide the weapons and other necessary things,
and we provide the soldiers.
These are the conditions, right?
Correct.
Then we can have 500kg of cocaine
worth 200 million dollars, right?
That'll work in our favor.
We won't have to struggle with funding.
Right?
Yes.
Do you think this is too good to be true?
Ms McCunnen, I fail to see...
...what you would gain by offering such favorable terms to us.
I want the Godoh Group to owe me a favor.
Someone with a strong sense of duty like you would owe me a favor. That's all.
So you want someone to back you up?
Right.
I'll give you these 200 million dollars.
But I'll gain something even more valuable than that.
It certainly makes business sense.
That's fine.
Either way, we've made our decision.
We're on board.
This pairing with Zwei is just the result of a coincidence anyway.
I'm an INN reporter.
I have a favor to ask.
Take this.
What's this?
Just give it to the police.
I'm counting on you!
Hold on!
Why... did this happen...
I'm sick of this.
I'm hungry.
What day is it?
I want to go back to Japan...
It's quiet...
Maybe this is my chance...
No. If I go out, I'll be found immediately.
She'll kill me.
He's still alive after causing so much trouble for Phantom?
He sure is something.
While suppressing his hunger and fear,
he chose to shut himself inside here.
He judged that this was the only way to survive,
and his instincts kept suppressing his urges.
Interesting.
He's very interesting.
Zwei...
Zwei. Wake up.
We're going out. Get ready.
We have a mission for tonight.
We'll scout the place while it's still bright outside.
Tonight at 2200, 500kg of cocaine will be brought here.
And Inferno will take that?
Our mission is to back up the raid squad.
Is that raid squad reliable?
Looks like Claudia has some kind of attachment to Zwei.
Make sure she doesn't steal him.
I haven't heard anything.
So this is a mission for Phantom, huh?
Let's go back.
We have to get the weapons.
Ein, do you dream?
Dream?
Seeing a place you haven't seen before.
Meeting strangers.
I wonder if...
...such dreams are actually my memories...
I don't know.
Don't you dream?
Sometimes I dream of colors.
Colors?
Yes, colors. And...
Wind.
Blue, white, and green.
That's all there is to it.
There's nothing else here.
But it's so bright there...
And the wind is blowing.
A very strong wind.
Is that the scenery of your hometown?
I don't know.
But...
So what?
What will you do if you know about your hometown?
Don't you want to confirm it?
The place left in your memories.
That's not our home.
Murderers have...
...no place but here.
There's nothing.
Dreams are just illusions.
They just get in the way of reality.
Yo. It's me.
Lizzie.
I have a message from Clau.
Zwei, go to her place at eight.
That's too sudden.
What's going on?
There's been a little change.
I have something big to deal with tonight.
It's been decided that you will protect her in my stead.
Please wait a minute.
We have another order for tonight.
What? I didn't hear anything about that.
Whose orders are they?
Scythe Master's.
It must be one of his arbitrary orders.
Just ignore it.
Clau is your boss, got that?
But...
Be there at eight.
Don't forget it.
Go, Zwei.
Ein.
I'll carry out Master's mission alone.
You should follow Ms McCunnen's orders.
No way...
It's too dangerous.
I'll be fine.
You can't do that all alone...
The one who decides that...
...isn't us.
Yes...
Seems like he's doing stuff without me.
Scythe Master isn't stupid.
He's most likely proceeding on his own.
Yes.
Then satisfy his happy little ambitions under your control.
Take the car I hid on Fifth Avenue.
Got it.
Let him have money, drugs or whatever he wants.
But when he crosses that line...
I know. I'll take responsibility for that when the time comes.
I'll quickly bury him and his puppet.
Ein.
Be careful.
You too.
If I know my past... myself...
I'm not confident that I can keep going as I am.