Year 845.
Instantly, the walls were shattered, along with the illusory peace of everyday life.
Thus, driven by a century of hunger, the Titans
descended upon mankind once again.
No!
Mankind abandoned Wall Maria.
They lost a fifth of their population, and a third of their territory,
as human activity was pushed back to Wall Rose.
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
Night of the Disbanding
Restoration of Mankind (pt 2)
Year 850
2 years after enlisting
You're slow!
Run, you shitheads!
What's wrong, Arlert?
You're falling behind!
Is it too hard for you?
Do you want to be the only one who puts down his equipment?
If this was a real mission, you'd be Titan food already!
Dammit!
Give that to me!
You'll end up dropping out this way.
We're being graded on today's training!
But now, they're gonna punish you too!
Then do your best so they won't find out!
Don't make me change my mind!
Reiner Braun.
He possesses great mental and physical fortitude.
His comrades trust him deeply.
I'd rather die than live as a burden!
Armin Arlert.
What he lacks in physical strength,
he makes up for with extraordinary academic aptitude.
Annie Leonhart.
While her fighting skills are outstanding,
she doesn't work well as part of a team. A lone wolf.
Bertolt Hoover.
He is highly talented, but he lacks initiative.
Jean Kirstein.
His 3D control skills are top class,
but his overtly blunt personality causes friction.
I can't fight like them. I need to find my own Titan first!
I will get accepted into the Military Police!
Thanks, Jean!
I knew following you would work!
I did it!
Sasha Blouse.
She's talented at operating unconventionally,
but that mentality makes her unfit for organized activity.
Connie Springer.
He's skilled at making sharp turns, but his mind is nowhere near sharp enough.
Here they come!
Shit! I still didn't cut deep enough.
Mikasa Ackerman.
Her performance is exemplary in every subject.
She is truly a genius of historically-unprecedented significance.
Eren Jaeger.
While he lacks any outstanding talents, he improved his grades through outstanding diligence.
In addition, he possesses an exceptional sense of purpose.
Ouch!
Sorry, man.
I suck at holding back.
You play the bad guy next.
What's wrong?
I just don't see the point of training like this.
It's not like soldiers fight other humans.
Plus, only a fool would go bare-handed against an armed opponent.
That's irresponsible thinking.
We're soldiers.
There are times we can't back down,
no matter how hopeless the situation.
We can't always be sure who or what we're up against,
so we master artillery and hand-to-hand combat too.
That's our responsibility as soldiers.
Would you look at that?
Oh, it's Annie.
The officers never notice her sneaking off like that.
Hey, Eren.
Let's teach that slacker a lesson.
We'll show her how true soldiers ought to behave.
Huh?
You looking for a headbutt from the instructor?
If you don't wanna get any shorter, I suggest you recall your first day here and get serious.
What are you talking about?
She's furious.
I've always thought she wore a scary face,
but that's nothing compared to right now.
Let's get moving, Eren.
Me?
Annie, you know what to do, right?
Here I come!
What? She kicked me in the leg?
Can I go now?
No. It's not over until he lets go of the dagger.
Wait, Annie!
We're supposed to do it the way—
Here.
Now it's your turn to attack me.
I don't...
Do it, Reiner.
You're gonna teach her the responsibility of being a soldier, right?
Yeah. Sometimes a soldier can't back down.
Like right now!
Your technique is incredible.
Who taught you to fight?
My dad.
Your father could—
Who cares?
Doing this is pointless.
You mean this training?
Anti-personnel techniques don't factor into our scores.
So people just take it easy until it's over.
The right to join the Military Police and live in the secure Inner District
is only granted to the top scoring 10 graduates.
The people who bother participating in this are either stupidly serious like you,
or seriously stupid.
Crap, it's the instructor!
Why is it that the people most capable of opposing the Titans
are the only ones given the privilege of avoiding them entirely?
How do you think it got to be such a farce?
Who knows?
Maybe it's just human nature?
Point is, I can't even pretend to be stupid
enough to play soldier in this insane world.
Then you're not fit to be a soldier.
I was so obsessed with getting stronger that I didn't notice.
It's such an obvious contradiction.
They're just improving their Titan-killing skills so they have a chance to get further away from them.
It's just natural.
Before the fall of Wall Maria,
only the few soldiers of the Recon Corps actually utilized the 3D Maneuver Gear.
With limited usage or innovation, the entire practice would naturally fall into decline...
You should rev it up hard, but just for a second.
Using inertia that way, you can minimize gas consumption.
You make it sound so simple.
Sure, it's not something anyone could master.
But it's still worth remembering
if you're trying to get into the Military Police.
It'd be great if I could get in...
There's no higher honor than working near the King.
C'mon, Marco!
Stop being such a goody-goody and just tell the truth.
You want to join the Military Police so you can live a simple, comfortable life within the Inner District.
No, I actually want to—
So interior life's simple and comfortable?
Five years ago, this place was also part of the interior.
What's your point, Eren?
Jean, you're such a simpleton, you'd be comfortable wherever you go.
Damn you...
Don't you think it's crazy?
Learning how to kill Titans just to run away from them?
You bring that up now?
This farce should be kept going for my sake if nothing else!
You damn bastard!
Fuck off and face reality!
Eren, stop it!
Stop this.
Dammit, you asshole!
Fuck you! I backed off!
Who cares! I'm so jealous!
What the hell are you even talking about?!
I see.
He's just blowing off steam, just like I did back then.
But not this time.
I'll use my skills to resolve the situation.
That hurt...
That was a move I learned while you were slacking off.
If you think reality is just living comfortably and following your own whims,
can you seriously dare to call yourself a soldier?
I thought I just heard some kind of loud noise.
Someone care to enlighten me as to what's going on?
Sasha just ripped a giant fart, sir.
You again?
Learn some self-control!
Thus the graduation of the 218 trainees drew near.
Hands upon your hearts!
Yes, sir!
For you trainees graduating today, three paths now open before you.
You can be stationed at the walls and defend the cities as members of the Garrison!
You can put your lives on the line
to fight the Titans in their own territory as members of the Recon Corps!
And you can serve the King by controlling the crowds and protecting order
as members of the Military Police Brigade!
Of course, only the ten people with top scores we
announced earlier are allowed into the Military Police!
Finally, I made it this far.
Now, it'll be our turn
to devour the Titans!
Currently Disclosable Information
Top 10 trainees by score from the 104th training class (pt 1)
10. Krista Lenz
9. Sasha Blouse
8. Connie Springer
7. Marco Bott
6. Jean Kirstein
Currently Disclosable Information
Top 10 trainees by score from the 104th training class (pt 2)
5. Eren Jaeger
4. Annie Leonhart
3. Bernard Hoover
2. Reiner Braun
Top of class.
Mikasa Ackerman
Did it! I'm in the Military Police now!
We'll never worry about having food again!
Why am I below Eren? That bastard...
You don't wanna join the Military Police, Eren? Are you serious?
But you've got one of the top 10 scores!
I've been dead-set on my goal since the very beginning.
I didn't train to live comfortably within the Inner District.
I worked this hard so that I could fight the Titans.
But you can't possibly win!
You know full well...
You know just how many have been eaten by them.
We've lost more than twenty percent of the entire population already.
Mankind doesn't stand a chance against them.
So?
You're just giving up because you think you can't win?
Well—
It's true. We've suffered only defeats so far.
That's because we knew hardly anything about them!
We can't defeat them using sheer numbers.
We may have lost,
but the knowledge we obtained from those battles is our guiding beacon of hope.
Yet you'd discard the tactical progress bought by hundreds of thousands of sacrifices,
just to serve yourself up on a silver platter?
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'll kill every last one of them and break free of these walls!
That is my dream!
Mankind hasn't lost everything yet!
Wait, Eren!
Go outside those walls, if you're so keen on it.
I'm going to the Military Police.
Eren, can we talk about your dream?
Yeah.
After all, I got it from you.
Breaking free of the walls, and all that...
I'm going to enlist in the Recon Corps.
Are you for real, Armin?
You're our top theoretician! Put that to better use!
I don't care if I die as long as I can be useful.
I'm going to the Recon Corps too.
You got the top score, didn't you?
Go to the Military Police!
I'll go to the Military Police if you do.
If you go to the Garrisons, so will I.
You'll die an early death
if I'm not there for you.
I never asked for that.
I don't want to lose what's left of my family.
They're here!
It's the main force of the Recon Corps!
Commander Erwin!
Kick their Titan asses for me!
Look!
There's Captain Levi!
They say in battle, he's as strong as a whole brigade!
Shut up already...
They look completely different from five years ago.
People really count on the Recon Corps a lot.
It's cheering everyone up.
The past won't have to be repeated.
The artillery has been improved as well.
That Colossal Titan won't come again, right?
Yeah.
How can you be so naive, you old married couple?!
Don't call us a couple!
Don't be so hasty, Eren.
Hey, you there.
Hannes!
You guys graduated yesterday, right?
I can't believe they really let you kids through.
I heard they made a drunkard like you Captain of a Garrison.
Touché!
Sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't save your mother.
It's not your fault, Hannes.
I'm no longer ignorant.
I won't let that sort of tragedy happen again.
I will defeat the Titans.
Should I be happy or not that he's grown into a man?
Just don't die.
What?
You enlisted in the Recon Corps?
Connie!
You were going on and on about joining the Military Police!
Yeah, I know.
But...
Seems like he was listening to your lecture yesterday.
Shut up!
This is my own decision!
Don't be so shy about it.
You're not the only one.
Thomas...
Are you serious?
Um, guys...
I borrowed some meat from the officers' morning rations.
Sasha...
You wanna get solitary confinement?
You're a real idiot!
Real idiocy's scary...
Let's all split it up together later.
We'll slice it up and eat it with bread!
Bring it back!
Yeah!
Meat is a luxury now that we've lost so much land!
Don't worry about it.
Once we retake the land, we can keep pigs and cows again.
I'll take that meat!
Me too, so save my part!
That goes for me too.
Guys...
What do you say, Eren?
They'll find us out if we don't get back to work.
It's still a while before lunch.
Five years have passed since then.
Mankind's finally regaining its dignity.
We can win.
Mankind's counterattack begins now!
The hell?!
Samuel!
Sasha!
Samuel! Don't move!
That was close.
The gate's... broken.
Again... The Titans will get in again!
I'll kill them all! Every single one of them!
Every... fucking... one...
Ready the artillery! Four groups!
Prepare for battle!
The target's right in front of us!
It's the Colossal Titan!
This is our chance! Don't let it slip away!
Hello there.
It's been 5 years.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
Hell's gates have opened once again.
Without even time to catch their breath, soldiers are consumed.
Amidst the chaos, Armin stares death in the face. Can Eren save him?
First Battle
Defense of Trost (pt 1)