The festival was great!
Say, Nishimi, I'd love to hear you play the piano again!
I want to hear more, too!
Want a persimmon?
Uh...
I'm with the photography club! Let me get a shot!
Stand next to each other, you two!
It's like we're witnessing the birth of a legendary duo!
Stand closer to each other already!
Like this?
Yes!
So when did you two become friends?
Where do you practice?
How do you play in such perfect unison?
Sen...
Let's get out of here. When I count to five, run left.
You don't have to hide anything from us!
Tell us!
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one!
They're escaping again!
Ritsu!
Aw, come on! Where are you going?!
Darn.
The girls were supposed to be chasing after us...
Look at 'em. They're just like the Beatles!
They've taught me something valuable.
Forget about next year's festival...
I'm looking even further ahead.
I'll go so far that they'll never be able to catch up.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Pops!
I know it's been a while...
Huh? He's not here.
Maybe in the basement?
Sen... What's wrong?
Richie, can you check to see if Brother Jun's down there?
What are you talking about?
Summer vacation's over, so why would Jun be—
Oh,
a lot's happened while you boys weren't around.
He's not here now though. Left last week.
Either way,
it sure has been a while.
I'm sorry...
I've been waiting for you, Richie-rich.
My piano trio is finally together again!
Junichi was disowned by his father right after he came back this summer.
Disowned?
Well, first he went against his parents' wishes by going to college in Tokyo,
then stopped going to school.
Instead, he got wrapped up in some political activism.
So, when the prodigal son wandered back on home,
his father was understandably furious.
Junichi wasn't allowed to set foot in his own house...
And not long after, I ran into him at the bar,
blitzed out of his mind,
so I let him take refuge here.
Pops...
Is it my fault that Brother Jun left?
Oh, no. That's not it.
He happened to find a cheap place for rent.
It's not your fault.
But I...
Sentaro!
Don't just mope your life away!
One good session'll drive those blues away, right?
N-Never mind!
Pretend that never happened.
I get it, Mr. Bill Evans, I get it!
All right!
What d'you say we play some to stop me from moping?!
Junichi?
What are you doing here?
Wait!
Don't ignore me!
What made him change this much?
That day last winter, in the basement... What was that about?
Did he just do it on a whim?
Even if I knock,
he might not open the door...
Or would he just look at me again with those vacant eyes?
Sorry, but that doesn't suit you.
You win.
That angry face of yours just kills me.
You had that same expression when we first met, too.
I remember it well.
What are you gonna do?
Just go home?
Or...
Hey, Mukae!
Excuse me...
Could you give this to Nishimi for me?
Um, wouldn't it be better if you gave it to him yourself?
Oh, no way!
I'd be too nervous!
So, please!
Nice work!
For me?
It's been a while since the festival,
but you're as popular as ever, I guess.
Thanks.
What am I staring at?
What, am I jealous?
It has nothing to do with me...
Ritsu!
Hey, which scarf design do you like better?
Actually, y'see, there's this guy I kinda like
and I'm thinkin' about making one for him...
Who? Who?
I can't say yet...
But how about you, Ritsu?
Is there anybody that you'd wanna knit for?
Come on, let's knit together!
But I don't have anyone to give it to...
Oh, please.
Be honest with yourself, Ritsu.
You were totally staring at a certain someone just now...
It's not what you think.
Don't get the wrong idea...
Yeah, yeah.
Nishimi is just a friend, right?
Sorry! Just a sec!
What a nice color...
I bet Kaoru would look good in this...
Huh? Wait a second...
What's wrong with me?
Why is my heart beating so fast?
That day in the basement?
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot about that...
You wanna know why I did it?
Was it a little bit too much for you?
Sorry. I was just feeling kinda mischievous.
N-No!
What's wrong?
Didn't you come in because you wanted this?
What were you hoping for?
A declaration of love?
Sorry to disappoint you, young lady.
But this is the kind of guy I am.
You stopped fighting back...
You just gonna take it after all?
Yes.
"If I act like this, she'll probably take off."
Is that what you're thinking?
I'm not afraid of you.
You can do what you want with me.
Dammit!
Go home,
and don't ever come back here.
I'm not the same person I was before.
I dropped out of college and got disowned by my own flesh and blood.
Society gave me the boot, so it's all over for me.
Just being close to me will ruin your life, too.
If you know what I'm sayin', just get the hell out of here.
What the hell?
I'm sick of being called a young lady.
So I'll just remove everything that makes me one.
If you're not the same person you once were,
then I can become someone else, too.
Katsuragi,
I'm gonna become someone else, a new me.
Don't!
Don't go wasting something so precious for a loser like me.
So you're the Katsuragi I've heard so much about...
How about a few words to mark the occasion?
Me?
I know I'm just passing through,
but I'd like to talk to you about what a college should be like.
Katsuragi...
You're my inspiration.
Every Rebel has a Cause
Hey, Muroi...
Listening to your speech
made me feel so down on myself for doing nothing but studying and playing music.
The Decline of a False System
Strike Against
Rising Tuition
All Students
on Strike
Hey, Katsuragi,
in the next battle, if something happens to me,
you'd take over for me, right? Even for a little while?
Arita, I...
Japan Communist
Youth Union
Hey, Muroi.
Come over once in a while and play sax with us.
Katsuragi! Arita's been arrested!
The bones are shattered,
so the doc told me my fingers won't be able to move like they used to.
B-But the sax...
I can't play anymore.
Don't look so glum, Katsuragi.
Now I can dump everything I don't need and just focus on the movement.
I'm gonna become someone else, a new me.
What am I doing here?
Katsuragi?
Hey... Wait!
Where are you going?!
I don't wanna see any more people get hurt because of me...
I don't know what happened to you.
You don't have to talk about it.
But I can see that you're hurt deeply.
Why don't you let me support you?
Am I being too pushy?
Yeah.
You're a pushy woman.
Maybe I better stop takin' naps on the roof...
Hey, wasn't that Yurika?
Did the teacher call her aside again?
Yeah.
Yurika's been acting so weird lately.
She's totally changed...
It seems like her innocence is completely gone.
Maybe something happened to her?
I asked her that, but she wouldn't answer...
Well, since she cut her hair like that,
could it be...
A broken heart?
What the hell happened?
What'd he do to her?
So you're Sentaro, huh?
Do you like jazz?
Ever since I first met Brother Jun, he's been like a big brother to me.
I wanted to get good at jazz like him...
Be strong like him...
Be cool like him.
I tried to follow in his footsteps, every step of the way,
thinking I'd eventually catch up.
Hey, Sen-boy...
Your woman forgot something.
If he'd just sit down and talk to me, maybe I'd understand...
But if he did something to her,
I'll...
B-Brother Jun!
I need to talk to—
Son of a bitch...
Shit.
He's the one person I didn't want to find out about this.
But what else could you do?
He was bound to find out sooner or later.
I knew it...
I knew she was out of my league from the start...
Or I thought I did, but...
I just can't figure it out...
I know for sure that when I'm with Kaoru,
I feel completely at ease and I have a good time...
No.
I decided a long time ago who I should like.
Hey, Ritsu.
Is Sen around?
Yeah, I think so.
Knitting?
Why would she bother hiding that?
Huh?
Hey!
Sen!
What happened?!
What d'you mean?
You're obviously acting strangely today.
Tell me about it.
I saw 'em.
Saw who?
When I went to Brother Jun's apartment...
She was there.
Y-You're sure you saw her?
Yeah.
And of all people, it had to be Brother Jun...
That's what hurts the most.
Anyway, it's done.
There's nothin' I can do.
You've still got it good.
Even though you were rejected, you've still got someone who cares for you.
Can't see the forest for the trees, I guess.
And those trees are so tall, you obviously can't see a damn thing.
Why don't you try opening your eyes?
Isn't it about high time you noticed?
W-What're you talkin' about?
Figure it out for yourself.
I told him...
Kaoru?
You just got here and you're leaving already?
Yeah. I've got some things to do.
Are you done knitting for today?
Sorry.
I couldn't help but glance over before...
I'm sure he'll really like it.
Aw look, you're blushing!
Was I right on the money?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Wait a min—
I'm sure this is for the best...
Don't have a relapse! It shouldn't hurt at all!
I won't have it!
You and this man from God knows where...
Yurika, you're being deceived.
What do you know, Father?
Shut your mouth!
I'll bring home a suitable partner for you soon enough.
So don't meet with this man again, Yurika.
Do you understand?
Yurika, your father is just being so harsh because he's so worried about you!
Girls like us have to take better care of ourselves.
Just in case, keep next Saturday open, okay?
I made an appointment for you at the gynecologist.
Are you eating properly?
Here's a letter that came for you.
Love, Mom
To my comrade,
from Isao Arita
Richie, that rat...
Throws out hints, then just leaves.
Someone who cares for me?
Did he mean my family?
Is that it?
So you're gonna be the Virgin Mary in the Christmas play, huh, Sachi?
Yeah.
But I'm really nervous...
Hashiguchi will be there to see you too, so you have to do your best, right?
D-Don't mention him!
I don't care if he—
Oh c'mon, you're the one who said you're gonna marry him when you grow up!
What?!
That was forever ago!
Um,
Sentaro, I...
When we grow up, let's get married...
Isn't it about high time you noticed?
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change