“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
He comes by sometimes. But only in front there.
It's been a while, hasn't it, Kida Masaomi-kun?
What the hell is this?!
They've disappeared after getting in a gang fight.
You mean you can't just ask Orihara Izaya?
You've pulled me back in. Damn it.
Damn it!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
So one of your friends was hospitalized?
Who'd you hear that from?
I could see you from the window.
You were coming here every day.
Is it a girl?
A high school girl whose appeal comes from the imbalance between her glasses and her nice body.
Do you like her?
Yeah.
Right now, I'm in a love triangle with both her and my best friend.
If you add me, it's a love rectangle.
We're already through... Finished.
The end. Done. Aren't we?
Then why are you still coming here?
Do you want things to go back to the way they were?
Sorry. I'm going home now.
You'll be back, Masaomi.
There's no way you won't.
So I don't care if you start liking other girls.
Because when it's all said and done,
you love me more than all those other girls.
I know that without having to be told. It's the same thing all over again.
"No matter how many girls you date, you'll come back to me."
And then you'll love me more and more,
with more love than you've had for anyone else.
However, I didn't want to hear the words that came after that.
After all, that's what Izaya said.
It feels good to sit back and look at things.
I've fallen under the impression that I'm a god.
Man, it feels good!
I love three-way battles.
Although the three leaders are all very close to one another.
Kami-sama attack!
The deeper a relationship is,
the higher the despair will burn when it all falls apart.
Look! The chess pieces look like rubbish.
And now, all that's left to do is to watch how all the other cards react.
Kadota's group, Shinra, Simon...
The king is Shizu-chan, I guess.
Celty is the queen.
In that case, the joker is...
I don't care.
This is really getting to be a lot of fun.
Don't you think so?
Life and Death Orders
She isn't dead, you say?
Isn't that fortunate. Anything can happen as long as she's alive.
Izaya-san...
You're smart, aren't you?
You know that you're the reason she's in her present condition.
I commend you for not hitting me in a fit of rage.
Correct.
It's perfectly natural to turn your anger on me like you just did.
Because I was teasing you, and with ill intentions.
She's unconscious? I hope she comes to.
Or maybe you hope that she'll never open her eyes again?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean. You're afraid, aren't you?
You think that you'll be responsible for her forever if she wakes up.
However, what if she died right now?
Wouldn't that leave you with an unbearable sense of guilt for the rest of your life?
In other words, whether she lives or dies, there's no point in you feeling guilty.
You can't escape.
The past indiscriminately follows you around.
Intently, intently, intently, intently.
Do you know why that is?
Because it's lonely.
The past and your memories are complete loners.
I don't believe in God, because existence itself is indefinite.
In a world where the future is indefinite, the past exists for sure.
Even if it's troubled with misunderstandings and delusions,
if you believe in the past,
it can't be anything but the truth.
If you determine your actions, or your way of life, based on the past,
I suppose that makes the past a kind of god.
I have no idea what you're trying to say!
You know very well. You can't run away from her anymore.
The guilt that you feel for her is going to become the past,
and she'll turn into your god.
Well, I guess it's not a bad thing.
You do love her, after all.
Anri's back to normal, too.
I'm glad you and your erotic self are okay, Anri.
You don't need to say erotic, Masaomi.
Still, it really is a good thing. Really.
Thanks, you guys.
Don't thank us.
As long as you and your erotic self are okay, Anri, that's enough for me.
Same here, except for the erotic part.
Hello?
Right. Got it.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry! My friend says he has an emergency.
Really?
If you're going to get mad, get as mad as you like at my friend.
It won't cost you anything to get mad, and it won't hurt me.
You'd be killing two birds with one stone, giving one man two wives!
One man two wives?
Well, I'll see you tomorrow!
Is it really that urgent?
Don't you think that Kida-kun has been acting strange lately?
Really? Maybe it's just you.
I had never talked to Mikado about the Kokinzoku.
Where he is and where I am feels like reality to me,
yet I feel like we're so far apart...
Every day we would fight and fight.
We were a group of friends who had nothing in common beside that.
I wanted someone to confirm who I was.
That's when I first met Saki.
Those yellow rags are really nice.
You're way cooler than you're rumored to be,
Kida Masaomi-kun.
What? How do you know my name?
Esper? Or are you Esper Ito?
If you can read my mind like that,
you should put it in a bag and take it home! Here!
Okay! Stop talking so weird!
It's not me, though.
There's someone else I know who has ESP.
Who? Is there a ghost-whispering girl here?
Or should I say, an amazing person.
He knows everything.
That was also when I met someone I wish I hadn't.
Hey, nice to meet you, Kida Masaomi-kun, right?
Who might you be?
I'm Orihara Izaya. I'm an informant of sorts.
I'm more or less this girl's guardian.
I'm not her boyfriend or anything, so don't worry.
It's my pleasure.
Shogun!
I've told you before!
Don't call me Shogun, call me Kida Masaomi.
But Kida-san is so...
We can't find anything on the Dollars.
There are some among us who were members of theirs,
but they don't know who was in charge.
They couldn't even tell who it was back at their first meeting.
Have they been up to anything?
Apparently, they've received an order from their leader to find out about the slasher.
I guess it's a lie that the slasher is one of them.
Even so, there's something fishy going on.
What else?
There's talk that Horata-san got beaten by the black rider.
Horata-san?
It was a little while back.
There was some weird-looking bastard in a white gas mask, and we started making fun of him,
but then the black rider got us...
The black rider?
Yeah, she wrapped us up with some kind of black oil, or...
I wonder who the black rider really is.
There's a rumor that she's one of the Dollars.
Whatever.
Anyway, you guys are older than us, right?
Yeah, well...
Don't pull people older than yourselves into this.
If people start talking about unknown persons from unnamed organizations,
it's all over.
We're just kids.
No matter how many of us there are, we can't win against adults,
and if they start taking advantage of us, we're through!
Just like Orihara Izaya did to me.
If I ever had any problems, Saki would tell me to ask Izaya and it'd be all right.
I'd tell him about the problem and get his opinion.
See, this way everybody wins.
At first, everyone thought he was annoying,
but in the end, it would all go well.
I couldn't trust him.
I didn't want to get any closer to him than I needed to.
Izaya-san really is amazing.
He knows everything, and he's never wrong.
Well then, if he told you to die, would you do it?
Probably.
I felt sorry for this girl.
I wanted to free her from Orihara Izaya's spell.
Would you say that we're going out with each other?
Would I?
Why are you always hanging around me?
Because I like you.
Did that Izaya guy tell you to like me?
Yeah, but only at first.
Izaya-san doesn't stick his nose into people's love affairs.
Why do you still like me?
Because you're cool.
No, maybe it's because you're cute.
What about you, Masomi? Do you like me?
I would like you more if you stopped blindly trusting that guy.
I can't help it.
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop pointing out my faults.
So you know that it's a fault of yours?
Well, yeah. I don't plan to fix it though.
If it's a fault of yours then fix it.
I'll help you.
That's how we started going out.
There wasn't a single person who begrudged my relationship with Saki.
I was serious, but in fighting the Blue Squares, the Kokinzoku weren't.
The way the Squares fought was dirty.
They would attack small groups of people in great numbers.
They wouldn't pick a fight unless they knew they could win.
Over a hundred of my friends were killed. We were all afraid.
Including me.
I was afraid I'd have to dissolve the Kokinzoku and lose my place in the world.
And so...
You should talk to Izaya about it.
I ended up asking him...
the man whom I feared so much.
Welcome!
Don't just stand there and stare.
I kept telling myself that I was doing this for my friends.
Let's sit down and have a nice chat.
The information he gave me changed the Kokinzoku drastically.
He not only gave me information on the Blue
Squares, but also told me how to fight them.
We may have been outnumbered, but our
position changed in the blink of an eye.
Your information skills really amazes me, Izaya-san!
At some point I lost the apprehension I felt toward the man.
We kicked their butts!
On the contrary, I trusted him.
You should have seen their faces!
I was enjoying our victory.
However...
Kida-Masaomi-kun?
Who's this?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Izumii-kun, the leader of the Blue Squares.
You're the contestant on today's game show!
I'm about to put our special guest on the line. Who is she?
Hint: It's someone very, very, very, very important to you.
Hey!
Time's up!
No, I'm kidding, but did someone just come to mind?
Well then, ding ding ding ding!
You bastard, what... What have you done to Saki?!
Now, here's question number two:
What does the woman you love look like right now?
Question number three:
Which one of her bones did I just break?
Hint: I don't think she'll be able to walk for a while.
Here's the final question:
What's going to happen to this girl if you don't get your ass down to the parking lot,
where you set us up, in the next twenty minutes?
I regretted it. I had gone soft.
I had thought that no matter what anyone said,
we were just middle schoolers, and this was just an elaborate fight between children.
That wasn't right. This was war.
Moreover, I was the one who had started it.
Pick up. Pick up.
Your call has been forwarded...
You're kidding me. Damn it!
Izumii-san. The girl just passed out.
What a shame. All she's got is a few fractures in her leg.
I ran. I had no choice but to go.
To go and kill all the guys who had just made Saki scream like that!
Your call...
And so the Kokinzoku guy is trying to beat their leader!
I told you, I don't care.
No, they kidnapped his girlfriend.
She's just a kid, but she's still a nice-looking girl.
That alone should make it loads of fun!
Kidnapped?
Is that right? In that case, I'll go right now.
There you go! This is why you–
When you come to, tell that Izumii guy I said,
"So long, asshole."
Suddenly, I couldn't move.
My feeling had disappeared,
and my legs cramped as the reason why Saki was in danger struck me.
Why? Why was I so afraid?
I thought I'd do anything if it was for Saki!
I was just a powerless, middle school student.
Don't you think she'll die at this rate?
No, she's fine.
She's not bleeding, so she'll be okay, right?
Hello!
Oh my, oh my, oh my, you really did kidnap her.
What, Yumasaki? What's up with Kadota?
This girl is in a mess, since in reality, nobody's going to come save her
like they would in a movie or in a manga.
And so I was thinking...
If some hero like me were to come and save this girl,
the world might turn two-dimensional,
at which point I would turn into some superhero from another world with superhuman powers,
and start making out with all the girls,
so I've turned toward that dream. Here we go!
You make me sick, as always.
And now, I will commence my superhero, 2-D world, happy-ending plans!
Cheers!
Hurry!
Kadota! You bastards!
We should try not to move her around too much.
Let's take her straight to the hospital.
Are you guys really okay with this?
We're just following you, Kadota-san.
We don't care about the Blue Squares.
To tell the truth, I never really liked Izumii or Horata.
Same thing back here.
It would've been really cool if you had thrown it out the window.
I make it a rule not to litter.
Eventually, Saki woke up. From her testimony,
the police were able to arrest the leader, Izumii,
and the crippled Blue Square gang was forced to dissolve.
Hey.
You're Kida from the Kokinzoku, right?
Who are you guys?
How should I explain this? My name is Kadota.
I heard you guys went back on your gang and saved Saki.
Thank you for that.
No. We just went to visit her.
She says you haven't gone in yet.
That isn't any of your business.
She gave us a message for you.
That girl can see the entire area from her hospital room.
She says: "Thanks for coming by so often."
She heard that you were surrounded by Blue Squares on the way
and were just shy of making it.
She doesn't blame you for anything. Well, see ya.
Why? Why did you tell her that?
When did I tell you to say that?!
You can tell me not to, but I already told her.
I know that! I... I ran away.
My legs froze, and I couldn't move.
Yeah, I know.
Incidentally, you're also running away from that girl right now.
Are you telling me to lie to her?!
Me, who ditched her and ran away?!
Hey, don't get carried away.
If you're still feeling guilty about running away,
then at least live with the lesser guilt of lying to her.
It's something you can do to make it up to her, anyway.
However, if you don't want to lie to her,
then look her in the eye and tell her the truth.
I can understand you running from the past.
However, you can't run away from today or tomorrow!
Kadota just said something really cool!
Amazing! We should call Dotachin "Poema Poetan" from now on!
In the end, I couldn't bring myself to go.
I tried to go.
I picked up my feet over and over,
if only to give her one parting word.
But I couldn't. I left the Kokinzoku.
Do you know what high school you're going to, Kida-kun?
I'm going with Raira Academy. It's nearby.
I kept saying good things about Raira.
I was lonely.
When I talked to Mikado, it helped me to calm down.
So you,
should go too.
And then, Mikado and I met up again.
And I met Anri.
I thought that I'd finally be able to live a peaceful high school life.
And yet...
Damn it! You've... you've pulled me back here.
I had absolutely no intention of coming back.
You can't run away from her anymore.
The guilt you feel toward her is going to become the past,
and she'll turn into your god.
That's exactly right. That's why I'm here.
I'm going to take down the slasher who hurt Anri... who hurt my friends.
If the slasher is with the Dollars, I'll take down the Dollars too.
I'm not freezing up anymore.
This time, for sure, no matter what...
Who's there?!
What's wrong?
There was a girl looking in here. I've sent them after her.
A girl?
Think she was one of the Dollars?
I want to ask her some questions. Be gentle with her.
Sir!
I'll go around this way.
There was no way I could get lost. That's why I came back.
That was all, and yet... and yet, why...
Why was I still feeling so insecure?
That way!
She's not there!
Why? Why...
Why is Kida-kun...
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara
The Dead Blue Sky
A girl runs.
She runs for her life.
Just to get away from the shadows that pursue her.
And to get away from the horrid truth she has just discovered.
Next time: The Dead Blue Sky