No matter what I do, I can't stop loving Ryuuji.
I want him to be with Minorin,
but it's just too painful.
It hurts. It really hurts.
I can't-
Taiga!
U-Uh...
Sorry.
I-I was half asleep...
It's all right.
Yeah, I guess it can't be helped.
This all must be very traumatic for you, considering you're such good friends with Aisaka-san.
Since you just had a nightmare, Takasu-kun,
let me remind you that the printout is due tomorrow.
I'll repeat it again for everyone.
Please don't forget it.
Understood?
Yes.
Let's stop here for today.
The Scene With You
In the end, we weren't seriously injured, and the rescue team saved us;
then Taiga's real mother came to pick her up at the resort.
Can you contact her?
Kitamura...
The teacher told me that Aisaka isn't doing so great,
so she's resting at her parents' place...
Did you hear anything about that?
No, I couldn't reach her cell phone.
I see.
Kitamura,
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Pretend that you're the one who saved Taiga.
If Taiga asks about it, tell her she was unconscious the whole time and said nothing at all.
Please.
Is this related to the favor Taiga asked me on New Year's?
It is, isn't it?
Yeah...
All right.
Taka-chan!
Want to go out somewhere nice?
Somewhere nice?
Yeah, let's eat some good food!
Don't let Taiga be the only thing on your-
It's nothing!
It's cold!
Aren't the people inside taking a bit too long?
Takasu, I'm not keeping you from cooking dinner, right?
I'm sorry for forcing you to come.
It's okay; I won't go home until I taste the food here.
I don't want to go home either.
My parents will just ask what I'm going to do with my life.
There's no need to be so nervous.
This career assessment is just so they can decide how to split up the classes.
Notocchi, you're going into liberal arts, right?
Yeah, I want to go into liberal arts and become an editor for a music magazine,
then finally become a freeloader.
I'd be happy just to graduate.
Well, I'll have to work for my dad anyway.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry for being surprised, but you guys are actually thinking about your futures...
Gosh, what are you talking about?
Taka-chan, you're smart enough that you won't have any problems.
You're going into sciences, right?
It should be easy for you and Master Kitamura to pass the national testing.
Not really, I still haven't decided if I'm going to college-
All right, next!
Oh, we made it!
Come on, find a seat and sit down!
So how's it going? Have you checked on her yet?
Who?
Kushieda, of course-
Liberal arts!
K-Kushieda, why are you here?
I'm working.
W-What about club activities?
They're already over because daytime is shorter in winter.
So, what kind of noodles do you want?
By the way, I'll poke your eyes out if you say a hottie.
"Ikimen" is Japanese slang for a hottie, a play on words for "ramen".
A hottie!
I'm sorry, three ramen please.
Okay, good choice!
Three ramen!
Another new job, huh?
Yeah, the hourly wage is pretty nice, so I'll try two hours.
Why do you have so many jo-
Stop.
He's going to open his eyes.
Open his eyes?
What?
Endless Circle of Transmigration!
Thanks, please come again!
She never changes.
Next please!
We would never have guessed she rejected you if you hadn't told us.
Yeah...
Girls are such unpredictable creatures.
Speaking of which, how are things going with Maya-sama?
She's still ignoring me...
A girl's feelings, huh?
Is she not back because she's really not feeling well,
or is her mother being selfish like her father and not letting her come?
Or...
I can't stop...
...did she realize I heard her say that?
...loving Ryuuji.
Career assessment?
Just put something like "I'll study hard" and you'll be fine.
Even if I make it to a four year college, how much money do you think it'll cost?
It's all right; don't worry about money.
Here, fermented soybean bomb!
Don't worry?
You...
You're different from me because you're smart.
After receiving a good education,
your talents will launch!
You'll be able to live a wonderful life!
Look, isn't there a saying- what was it?
Um, gold jewel... something polish...
Golden stone... shining or something?
"A jewel won't shine if it isn't polished"?
Yeah, that's it!
Ryuu-chan, you're like shining when you study!
If I work and make around fifty thousand a month...
No, no working!
Even if you say that...
Working at Inage-san's is just an exception within an exception.
How do you know about it?
You won't be able to study if you work, right?
Also, we won't be able to have dinner together.
A life like that is pointless!
You won't be happy at all!
But you always tell me to go to college-
It's all right! There's always a way!
She's always been like that.
It's all right, you're no different from other children even if you don't have a father.
I'm an amazing mom!
You'll be perfectly happy forever!
Perfectly happy forever, huh?
Don't worry about Taiga.
Taiga said before that she's on good terms with her real mom.
I think she's probably happy to be around her.
That'd be great.
Oh, Kushieda.
Oh, Takasu, you're here too.
Don't tell me you're here for the budget estimate.
I'm sorry, I'll turn it in later!
Yeah, I'll be counting on you, new team captain!
See you later.
My, the new Student Council President is sure busy.
New team captain?
Weren't you already the team captain?
Well, Kitamura's student council is really busy,
so they merged the male and the female softball team,
and I was appointed the new team captain.
I'll probably become as busy as Kitamura-kun because I'm unlucky.
T-Then why are you getting another job?
Won't that make you busier?
No, no.
Haven't you heard the saying that young people must endure hardship, Takasu-kun?
Wouldn't that hinder both sides-
Nope.
I'm working hard because I don't want to hinder anyone.
That's because it's something that can be seen.
Something that can be seen?
Oh, it's A-min!
You're beautiful as usual today!
What's with that attitude, Kawashima?
Don't come near me.
Stupidity is contagious, you know.
Isn't it great?
When the child is not here, the father can do anything he wants.
Where are you going, Kawashima?
Later, Takasu-kun! I'm going too!
Hey, class is about to start!
Do you plan to skip first?
Why must it be you?
Never mind.
You know...
I wanted to tell you this a long time ago.
Huh?
What is there left to say after all that?
Actually, there's a...
ghost in that gap!
S-Seriously?!
It appears between those two vending machines.
I heard it was a heartbroken girl who took her-
Why didn't you tell me earlier?!
But nothing has happened so far, right?
Huh?
I think ghosts have their own personality too.
They'll only appear in front of people who they want to see and understand them.
I think I've seen a ghost before, however...
I don't want to yearn and get caught by something I can't see...
and lose the things I can see.
That's why-
You talk too much, I don't want to hear the whole thing.
You'll understand after you've heard the whole thing!
Really?
You want to say that if I just watch and don't interfere, everything will turn out fine, right?
Whatever, talking to you feels like having a period.
I won't hesitate anymore!
I will look forward and try to get what I want!
Gosh, shut up already.
I won't hesitate anymore, I swear! I swear!
I definitely won't!
Shut up.
Well, this is about your career assessment.
I'm sorry, I still haven't talked to my family about it.
Then do you still feel the same as at the beginning of this year?
Probably...
You're an overachieving student and I expect a lot from you,
that's why I'm concerned over this.
That's how being a teacher is.
Please don't have expectations in me; my family is poor.
So the problem is financial?
If you need it, there are different scholarships and financial aids-
Is it strange to not go to college?
No, that's not it.
It's just that I couldn't tell with just this career assessment...
Huh?
How you feel about it, not how others feel about it.
How I...
Huh? Why is it so dark?
Yasuko!
Still sleeping?
I found a part-time job, I'll be going to the shop after work from now on. Love, Yasuko.
Wha-
Job?
So that's what she means by "It's all right! There's always a way!"
Didn't she also say it'd be pointless if a mother and son didn't have dinner together?
Ryuu-chan, you're like shining when you study!
Uh...
How can I give it to her now?
How is a love letter embarrassing?
Disgusting, isn't it?
Since I don't have the guts to confess to her, I just have to imagine like this.
It's horribly miserable, but I don't think of it as embarrassing!
That's right, the feeling of liking someone is not embarrassing.
I can't say that to the person who likes me!
I just can't say it even if I want to!
Moreover, she's not answering my calls!
What should I-
Yasuko?
Seriously, why are you work-
T-T-T-T-
What?
Taiga!
Where were you and who were you with?!
You nearly killed me. You idiot, pig, dog, yaksha, asura, gorilla!
No running!
W-What were you doing?
You tried to strangle me and look at me with weird eyes...
I-I was just surprised because you appeared out of nowhere!
Y-You didn't even call me. I was really worried...
Oh, the battery died.
What was that?!
You have to explain everything to me in detail!
Don't tell me you didn't come back because you-
W-Why did I say that?
Look.
The wound isn't that bad.
The thing about me not doing so great was a lie. I'm fine.
I just wanted to skip school.
I-I see, so you're all right...
Then...
Huh?
I hadn't seen my mom for a long time.
We stayed at a hotel,
and we went shopping, and to restaurants and movies and stuff.
I was just being a child!
So...
Anyway, let me in first.
Didn't you say you weren't going to come over anymore?
I lost my keys.
I'm going to go in through the window from your room.
I'll use the three-second rule.
C-Can you do it within three seconds?
Whatever.
Sorry for intruding.
W-Wait!
Hey, why don't you have dinner here?
There are some fermented beans left, so I'll just add some onions-
It's okay, I already had dinner.
O-Oh yeah, Inko-chan wants to say hi to you!
Isn't he sleeping?
No, this is...
Yeah, it's his new greeting! He learned it recently...
Did that ugly bird get fatter?
Really?
E-Exactly! It's because you're not here to stress him-
Scratch that! He's eating too much because he's so lonely.
He's as ugly as ever.
As I thought, being with Taiga is the best.
Hey, Ryuuj-
Huh?
Why are you crying?
How disgusting.
I-I wasn't crying.
I was just yawning.
I see. It's late, isn't it?
Bye, ugly one. I'm leaving now.
What's wrong?
No... This is actually...
I was just cleaning out stuff because I had time...
Look, I didn't have time at the end of last year...
I see.
I'm really clumsy, but I finally understood after what happened.
Even if I'm clumsy, I can still be serious.
I can't stop thinking about it...
Hey, did you find out Minorin's true feelings yet?
Why?
Don't tell me you didn't ask her because of the fuss I caused...
Why is she worrying about me?
I promise I won't be clumsy anymore...
Because you...
It's all right, don't worry.
Things will definitely turn out fine between you and Minorin.
Taiga...
Hey, Ryuuji! Don't just stand there, come and help me!
It worked!
I always forget to lock the window.
A highly secured mansion isn't always convenient.
Hey, be careful...
Oh yeah, I nearly forgot.
Thank you.
You, Kitamura-kun and Minorin went to look for me, right?
You don't remember, do you?
I mean, you were unconscious.
Yeah, but I had a dream.
In my dreams, Kitamura-kun was carrying me on his back,
and I muttered something stupid to him...
It was a dream, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Something stupid, huh?
Does she want to pretend she didn't say anything?
If that's the case...
It was a dream.
Kitamura-kun did carry you on his back,
but you didn't say anything because you were unconscious.
That's what I heard, at least.
Really?
Thank God!
For a second, I was worried that it had been real.
Yeah...
All right, later.
Good night...
Taiga?
I'm all right...
Once again, good night...
Taiga, you're really a...
clumsy girl, aren't you?
Next Episode Preview
The Road We Must Advance on
Thirty-year-old rock-paper-scissors: scissors!
Yay, I won!
Here I go!
Chocolate!
Valentine's Day is awesome!