Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
On a spring night, Virgo is spread out widely.
My favorite star, Spica, is this Alpha star.
If you stretch this line from the Big
Dipper, there's the North Star.
And if you pull the handle of the ladle,
there's the star of the cow
herder, Arcturus, then Spica!
This line is called the Great Arc of Spring.
During the cherry blossom season,
try looking for it in the southern sky!
A Sad Smile
For the Astronaut Training Course,
we're all together for PE,
but everyone can choose their own subjects, so sometimes
I have different classes than the others.
In any case, this sure is a large school.
Isn't it? Getting around is a little rough.
Hey, look, Lion-san!
It's Fuchuuya, the annoying brat!
'Morning!
'Morning...
That's Kei-chan and Suzuki-kun.
What's with that guy? He doesn't have eyebrows.
Oh, and that's Marika-chan over there.
Ah, Lion-san's intrigued by her!
D-Don't be ridiculous!
H... h-hey...
Lecture Room
Sano-sensei!
Hm? What do you need?
Well...
Hurry and go to the classroom.
Class will start soon.
Sano-sensei!
Did you say something to Asumi...
I mean, to Kamogawa-san?
Kamogawa-san has been acting weird lately, so...
Since you're not responding, does that mean
you feel guilty about something?
I don't know what you're trying to ask, but I can't
respond about something that I don't recall.
Why are you coming to me about
Kamogawa in the first place?
Did Kamogawa say something?
Asumi won't say anything.
Asumi isn't the kind of
person who tells on people!
She keeps everything inside,
no matter what people say to her!
That's why I'm worried!
What's Kei yelling about?
Something about the little seagull, perhaps...
Really, they all go on about
Kamogawa, Kamogawa...
Then I will respond.
It's fine to worry about your friend.
But instead of worrying about other people, why don't
you worry about getting them out of the way?
Huh?
There aren't enough seats to allow everyone
to be friends and become astronauts.
If there was just one seat left,
would you let Kamogawa take it?
With the other courses, even if you don't
proceed into the space program,
you can receive other qualifications, and it's advantageous
for employment and further education.
That's also one reason why so many
people apply for this school.
On the other hand, with the Astronaut Training Course,
there's not much value if you don't go through with it.
I knew that from the beginning.
No one believes that everyone can go to space.
And that Sano guy...
Someone believes.
Huh? What?
There's one person who believes
that everyone can go to space.
There's no mistaking it. It's that girl.
But if it's that girl, why is she in
the same grade as the little one?
Lion-san.
Are you worried about what
that teacher said, little one?
It's true that by looking at the cost of training,
and the number of rockets that are to be launched,
it will be impossible for everyone to
go to space before they graduate.
John Glenn was 72 years old
on his second space flight.
Huh?
In 1962, he became the first American astronaut
to orbit the Earth as part of Project Mercury.
You knew that as well, right, little one?
Yeah.
Last year, a Russian cosmonaut celebrated his
birthday on the International Space Station...
What was his name again?
He was pretty old as well.
However old you are, there is
still a chance to go into space.
With you and everyone else being so young,
there are still many opportunities.
Lion-san, I...
Hm?
I'm going to go find a book on the
history of space at the library!
I'll definitely be able to go with everyone, right?
There don't seem to be a lot of people.
I wonder where Kei-chan went...
If you're wondering about Oumi-san,
I saw her at the cafeteria.
She's probably planning to strike.
Strike?
Just leave it alone.
Well, there are times when
you just want a day to rest.
But...
Now then, page 80 in your textbook.
When you go out to space in a rocket,
different forces act on the rocket
than upon your return to Earth.
After taking off vertically, the shuttle turns
horizontally in order to gain speed.
On the other hand, when the spacecraft re-enters
the atmosphere upon returning to Earth,
we use that resistance provided by
the atmosphere to our advantage.
The resistance in the atmosphere helps to
lower the speed without expending fuel...
This is troublesome, Sano-sensei!
There are complaints from the
students' parents as well!
"Getting them out of the way..."
And worse, this is at a time when people are
complaining about the strength training!
Please don't say things to lower the
students' motivations any further!
I do not recall saying anything strange.
The truth is the truth, is it not?
Even if you say that, it's a fact that there
are students boycotting your class.
Something is wrong with
your attitude these days!
There are even rumors going on
about you between the teachers.
The head teacher is planning disciplinary action...
Space Physics
There is no need for that.
I've already submitted my resignation.
S-Sano-sensei! I didn't mean
to have you go that far...
Do you have a bit?
I was wondering why you had
such a problem with Kamogawa...
I felt bad, but I looked into it a bit.
You were in the JAMSF Shishigou
Development Team, right?
Weren't you and Kamogawa's
father there at the same time?
That really was an unfortunate accident.
That was not just an accident,
it was a willful disaster!
It is true that Kamogawa Tomorou
and I were there at the same time.
But my work was scrapped because
he wanted safety first!
My design that I had worked on for years...
Just because he was liked by the team leader...
He had no right!
And then that happened!
Decades after that accident, at every
opportunity, people would say...
"So, you were part of the death team?"
Even though I was taken off the
team and couldn't do anything...
I heard.
You were a participant in that
big mistake, weren't you?
It was thoughtless of me to ask you.
I won't ask you for anything again.
Everywhere I go, that
abominable incident follows me!
You said you chose Kamogawa Asumi
because of her eyes, didn't you?
Those eyes... what was it about those eyes?!
I was also...!
I was also...
If that man hadn't taken
everything away from me...
I think that's enough misguided resentment.
What?!
You didn't know?
Right after you were dropped from the team,
Kamogawa Tomorou was dropped from
the Shishigou Development Team as well.
T-That can't be possible...
I don't really know the details myself,
but I heard an unsettling rumor.
Rumor?
As soon as Kamogawa was
dropped from the team,
the budget for the Shishigou
was drastically reduced.
What did you say?!
Also...
The Shishigou, famous for being all-Japanese...
wasn't actually made entirely within this country.
The reason behind the accident
is still a state secret, though.
Good morning, Marika-chan.
Umm, where's Kei-chan?
She was here.
But instead of entering the campus,
she made a U-turn and ran off somewhere.
Eh?
Isn't it because first period is Sano-sensei?
Hey!
She went that way!
Okay!
Really... we always have to
take care of that dummy!
Good work.
Found you, Kei-chan!
Class is going to start!
Let's go.
No.
You didn't go to Space Physics
yesterday either, right?
If you drop this credit,
we can't graduate together!
I don't ever want to take lessons
from Sano-sensei.
But...
You were told all that, but
you don't feel anything?
I didn't think he was a teacher
that would say those things!
What's wrong with caring for your friends?
I don't want to be a person who
can't treasure her friends!
Kei-chan...
You couldn't say anything back to that, though.
Marika-chan...
I know.
I'm pathetic because
I couldn't say anything back!
But it's frustrating!
It wouldn't be too late to tell him now.
I don't want to go because
I can't think of what to say!
You don't have to say anything back.
Let's just go to class, okay, Kei-chan?
So are you coming to class, or not?
Come on, it's going to start!
Oh, fine!
I get it! You want me to go to class, right?
For crying out loud, why did it turn out this way...
She's got such a happy face.
The little seagull's smile sure is cute.
How could that stupid look...
Trying too hard...
Dammit, everyone around here...
Here he comes...
I'll be teaching this for a while, starting today.
My name is Shiomi. Nice to meet you all.
What's going on?
Umm, sensei!
What is it?
Did Sano-sensei... well...
Sano-sensei has decided to leave the school
for a while, for his own reasons.
What? Does that mean he quit?
Well, to put it simply, yes.
Hey, hey...
Listen to me.
There is one thing I'd like to get
out of the way to begin with.
The Astronaut Training Course has just been established,
so explanations may have been lacking
and facilities might not have been
up to shape, so I apologize for this.
Also, it's true that it isn't possible for everyone
to go to space by the time they graduate.
It is also a fact that very few
people will probably be able to go.
But I don't want you to be pessimistic about this.
In the near future, the use for
astronauts will surely increase.
When that time comes, the fact that you have graduated
from this school will put you at an advantage.
Many things may happen, but no matter
what sort of situation you are put in,
do not throw away your vision and dreams of
going to space until the end and do your best.
This is what the teaching staff
wishes from their hearts.
Now, we will proceed with the lesson.
But still, I wonder why he
suddenly decided to quit.
Well, of course he did, after those thoughtless
remarks in front of the students!
He wouldn't quit over just that.
Something else important must have happened.
What is this "something?"
Who knows?
Who cares what it is?
It's probably something stupid anyway.
Those eyes were scary anyway.
I had no idea what he was thinking.
That's right, and plus, listen to this!
What is it?
That teacher said that Asumi...
Professor's Room
Sano
Sano-sensei!
It's the same, isn't it?
Sensei, it's the same for you, isn't?
You were looking at the same thing, right?
There certainly was a time like that for me.
But before I knew it, I couldn't see it anymore.
Don't lose sight of it!
Why is it?
Why do adults have those sad expressions?
Even Suzunari-sensei... even Lion-san...
Even Dad...
Even Sano-sensei...
If only everyone could go into space...
Sensei, I'm sure you'll be able to see it!
You'll be able to see it again!
Surely...
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
We don't know anything about
Marika-chan's early life.
I end up making Marika-chan angry.
Suzuki-kun cheers me up nonchalantly.
My past is connected to the Shishigou accident...
Many things have happened, but I believe everyone will
be able to understand each other much, much better soon.
Then, one day, Marika-chan fainted.
Next time on Twin Spica:
Alone.
Alone
End