“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
I think that this development means she's suddenly gonna turn into a shocking heroine.
You're...
Help me!
What do you propose we do with this head, which seems to be attached to a living person?
I want to meet with that girl, at any cost.
Those guys were with Yagiri Drug Manufacturing.
Okay. Let Nee-san take care of everything.
To tell the truth, I half doubted it.
The chess pieces are now in my hand.
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
I have to go. I have to go find her.
It can't be Nee-san. It has to be...
It has to be me.
She wasn't there, you say?
Yes. Apparently, she had already left by the time our men arrived.
You said that the name of the student who lives there is "Ryugamine Mikado," right?
What about him?
They questioned him after he came home, and they were considering bringing him along,
but it seems he had some company with him.
They should've brought that "company" along with him.
How pathetic.
What should we do?
Hello?
Is this Yagiri Namie-san?
Who is this?
My name is Ryugamine Mikado.
Would you be willing to make a deal?
Storm and Stress
Welcome, welcome!
Russian sushi! It's tasty! It's cheap!
Okay, nii-san? Are you hungry?
"What is life? For what reason do people live?"
We have good toppings today, yes?
When someone asked me that earlier, I beat him to the brink of death.
Right! This is a good price, you try it?
That's right.
Welcome. Onee-san, wait. Welcome.
If he were a middle-school poet, it'd be one thing,
but isn't it a crime for one of the yakuza that's older than twenty, to say that?
That's right.
Simon-san, you don't understand a word I'm saying, do you?
Have I changed without noticing...
while living in this city for the past twenty years?
It hasn't been a waste.
The last twenty years of your life have been far from a waste.
As long as you make the most of your life from here on out, nothing will have been for naught.
Make the most? What the hell is there left to do with my life?
For example,
you should marry me.
Shinra...
Are you Mikado-kun?
You look a lot older than I imagined.
Or is this the "dangerous kid" look now?
That being said, what is this "deal" you were talking about?
I'm sheltering the girl you're looking for.
Right. How much do you want?
No. I don't want money.
Then what do you want?
The truth.
What did you just say?
I want you to admit to what your brother did to Harima Mika-san, and what you did to Mika-san's body.
Unfortunately, I only have circumstantial evidence.
I'll be blunt. Please give up.
Right. You're one of those people.
I will not allow you to get in my brother's way. You can't.
I can't allow anyone to get in my brother's way!
I see. She is...
like that type of person?
Hey, tell me.
Where is Nee-san?
I have to go. She needs me.
I have to be there!
Hey. Tell me!
Is that the reason?
The reason why somebody died, and had "that" done to their body...
You even came after me!
That's the reason why you took a life?
Why you're acting in your own self-interest, even if it makes Yagiri-kun unhappy?
Isn't it a bit late for you to say that? At your age, you've stepped out into the world;
if you only have childish things to say, then keep your foul mouth shut.
It's going to be all right, isn't it?
They may only be nice words, but then if that's the case, what are you saying it really is?!
You actually killed someone.
Isn't it you who is deliberately ignoring that fact?!
You've been watching too many dramas.
Those are all meticulous schemes and make-believe harmony... This is reality.
We're not on television or in a magazine. And you're not some kind of hero.
It's all gonna work out.
Know your place, kid!
What's so bad about that?!
Make-believe harmony, meticulous schemes, opportunism,
and even nonsensical happy endings: I love all of those!
What's so bad about striving for those?!
You wouldn't say that if it were for a single person's sake, or for the world's sake.
I just want to see it! I want to believe it.
That's right. I believe. I believe it.
All of it, for sure.
That may be something you hear a lot.
However, the fact that you hear it a lot means that everyone thinks it's the truth!
Is that all you wanted to say?
I don't have the power, nor the wisdom to take on an opponent who refuses to listen to reason.
You won't even take the time to try. Therefore...
I'll rely on strength in numbers!
What?
Wow! Is everyone getting the same thing?
Amazing! It's just like that supernatural phenomena in Missing!
Bou-chan, you have mail.
Wanna try dying?
It's here!
Are you serious?
Well then. Togusa. I'll leave the rest to you.
Let's go.
Just how many people are there?!
My, oh my, I'm surprised that so many people turned up at the first ever meeting!
This is... the Dollars?
Hey, Isaac!
What is it, Miria?
Are all of these people one of "Dollars", too?
Exactly, Miria! You got that?
Listen to me.
This makes us part of the most happening, young, super-in crowd that there ever was walking the streets!
What is this? You don't mean, all these people?
How about it? That's what you call a franchise!
No way. No way!
What? When I just found out about it today?!
That's amazing!
In my hometown, the sky stretched far and wide... However...
there was nothing.
Even this town was full of adventure when I was little.
How long have things been the way they are now?
I wanted to change something, but I had neither the reason, nor the courage to go off on my own.
That's when it happened.
Let's see, double click... double click...
Many different worlds could be found there.
Worlds that I never knew and could never reach before.
I even started exchanging e-mails with Kida-kun, who'd moved to Tokyo.
I also made some new acquaintances.
Then, I suddenly got an idea. At first, it was no more than a simple thought.
A gang?
Right.
I've heard that there are a lot of gangs in Tokyo.
You're making a gang on the Internet?
No. In reality, it's going to be a real-life gang.
I'm going to make it a gang based in Ikebukuro, and spread rumors over the net...
We didn't openly call ourselves members of the Dollars.
We kept spreading rumors we made up, making it sound like we heard it from somewhere else, until it became well known.
I even made a website, with a perfect password system, for the gang.
I spread the password around through text messages and posts on various message boards.
We also used a lot of the posts from our members on the message boards.
Of course, there were a lot of people who didn't believe us.
However, there were always people around to back us up,
so we were all happy.
Really?
They're all buying it!
Idiots! They're all idiots!
I did have a bad feeling, though.
People calling themselves "Dollars" started showing up in real life.
That's not all.
Without me knowing it, the other members kept recruiting more people.
Even though I stopped spreading the password around; it was as though an informant somewhere, spread it around.
Everyone, are you watching?
The other founding members of the Dollars all went away, as if they were afraid.
Despite that, I didn't give up. No, I couldn't give up.
I don't even know why. Still...
That's not true.
There may be some bad people, but there are also plenty of people who aren't.
Shouldn't we work together in order to make the Dollars a good group?
For example, doing good things and therefore erasing the impressions left by the bad people?
We could pick up trash around town, or clean the graffiti from the walls...
...the local residents are also mystified.
The graffiti that was on this wall until last night has,
as you can see, been cleaned.
The locals are puzzled, since it is hard to believe that any one person
can clean such a large amount of graffiti in a single night.
Couldn't be.
On Kida-kun's invitation, I went to Tokyo. And there...
Dollars?
I don't know the finer details,
but anyway, there are a lot of them, and it sounds like they're pretty crazy.
They're like a Color Gang, only we don't know what colors they wear.
I wouldn't get too close to them out of curiosity.
Don't go investigating them for no reason.
But right now, the strongest in Ikebukuro has to be the Dollars, wouldn't you say?
So, what kind of gang are the Dollars?
You could say they're colorless and clear.
Dollars? I know of them.
Or I should say, I am one of the Dollars!
After I joined the Dollars, I got a girlfriend!
You write silly things on the message boards...
...and someone always replies.
At my age, you don't get many interpersonal relationships outside of work.
Did you hear?
The Dollars rescued a guy who was about to be kidnapped by those man-hunters!
The Dollars are awesome!
Not really... It's fun, so why not?
There are more than I thought. What fun.
This oughta be fun!
What? What's going on?
Who are these people?!
Hey, hey. I wonder which one of these people started the Dollars.
Is there anyone out there who looks like an Arabian oil tycoon to you?
There isn't.
Togusa-san, the guy who replied to us was the real founder of Dollars, right?
It sounds like it, but...
Togusa! Red light, red! Red! Red!
The silent treatment, huh?
Dotachin, Dotachin!
I told you not to call me that.
Look! There's a reply on the Dollars message board!
My plans are now in place. I'm going to have you meet with her.
In return, I'm asking you to help me.
Certy.
He's gone. Don't just stand there!
Find him!
Right! Move!
Where'd he go?
Damn it!
Move!
Scram!
Where is he?
That's it!
Who said that?
Yeah, I don't have a head.
I'm a monster. I have no mouth to speak with, and no eyes with which to show the enemy my passion!
I hear something.
What is that voice?
Even so, so what?
What's so bad about it?!
Certy.
I am here.
Without a doubt, I exist right here, in the now.
What do you want?!
You...
If you say I have no eyes, then you'd better watch my movements closely.
Listen to the screams of those who feel this monster's wrath! Listen to your heart's content!
T-The headless rider.
The headless rider.
That's... the headless rider?!
I'm here. I am here... I'm right here.
I'm already screaming... I'm screaming.
Hold it.
Right now, my purpose is...
to carve my existence into this city!
Are you Ryugamine Mikado?
Certy...
Give back Certy!
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Harmony of Opposites
Next time on
Durarara!!
That's right. I've discovered one truth in this city.
I looked for and found something trifling and common.
That boy will probably...
Next time: Harmony of Opposites