You...
Have you...
Courage, love, friendship, kindness, sadness, and joy.
Within all our hearts lie countless emotions.
I shall fight!
And I shall protect everyone's hearts!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's glow!
Cure Moonlight!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Cure Moonlight...
...has returned!
C-Cure Moonlight?!
Yuri finally managed to become Cure Moonlight again!
Y-You don't even have a fairy!
How did you become a Precure again?!
Cologne's body may indeed have been destroyed back then,
but his spirit was protected by the Great Heart Tree!
Back then...
Dark Forte Wave!
Out of the way!
My fairies... seek out my replacement!
Lord Coupe?
I should've finished you off back then when I had the chance!
Damn you!
I won't give up...
until every heart is filled with light!
What Incredible Power!
Cure Moonlight!
I'm not the same as when I lost Cologne.
Moonlight Reflection!
There you go.
You three?! What are you doing here?!
Sabark's orders. He asked us to keep an eye out for you.
Cure Moonlight has returned?
Things certainly have gotten interesting!
I'll be the one to defeat Moonlight!
Don't interfere!
No can do, I'm afraid.
Moonlight's foiled our splendid plans many a time too, after all.
That was but my greeting, madame.
Dark Bracelet!
Moonlight!
Kobraja! Don't interfere!
We have to save Moonlight!
You'll be fighting us three, I'm afraid!
Dark Bracelet!
You see, the Dark Bracelet doesn't merely empower our Desertrians.
It powers us up as well!
Here I come!
Let's go!
Marine Shoot!
If anyone is truly worthy of challenging my beauty, it would be you, Sunshine.
Sunflower Aegis!
I-It's not going to hold!
Adieu!
Sunshine!
You're wide open!
Blossom!
Gather, Floral Power!
Moon Tact!
Dark Power, Gather!
Dark Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
Dark Forte Wave!
Dark Precure, why do you hate me so much?!
Because you...
Because you are me!
Cure Moonlight!
What do you mean by "I am you"?!
If you are the Moon's light, then I am its shadow!
It's only once the light has been enveloped by shadow that the Moon can truly be whole!
Now the Moon shall become one!
Cure Moonlight.
Cologne?
Cure Moonlight!
That's right.
I'm not alone anymore.
I don't have to fight alone!
As long as Cologne watches over me,
there's no way I can lose!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Dark Power Fortissimo!
What?!
Sabark!
You're Dark Precure's...
Now I finally get to give you a
taste of my lovely poison sting!
Blossom!
Huh?
Say your prayers!
Curse you!
Moonlight Silver Impact!
Leave the rest to us!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Precure Shining Fortissimo!
This is bad. They're going to purify us!
Don't think we'll forget about this!
Cure Sunshine!
Now all four Precure are finally together!
Moonlight, what happened to Dark Precure?
Just as I was about to finish her, Sabark appeared, and they vanished together.
It's fine! Now that we have Moonlight, we're like a hundred times stronger!
Even if Dark Precure shows up, or the Desert Apostles, we'll...
What's the phrase I'm looking for?
It's "We'll beat them and be back in time for breakfast."
Yeah, that's the one!
You shouldn't treat the Desert Apostles so lightly.
That's true. The Desert Apostles will keep on attacking.
So let's work together and protect the Great Heart Tree!
You really did well out there, Cure Moonlight.
Not really. It's all thanks to you, Cologne.
I heard your voice when you called to me.
It looks like the Flower of your Heart has recovered nicely.
Thank you,
Cologne.
What?
Cologne?!
You really are such a crybaby.
Things got kinda crazy out there, didn't they?
I'm starving after all that.
Well, it has gotten pretty late.
There they are!
Erika! Where have you been all this time?!
Oh, sorry!
Some stuff came up, you see...
So did Yuri agree to appear in the fashion show?!
W-Well, the thing is... She hasn't actually given me the okay yet.
Whaaaat?!
Yuri, will you please come star in our fashion show?!
Please!
You mean it?!
All right!
But we haven't even made a single outfit for Yuri to wear yet.
We haven't even taken measurements yet. Can we really get it done in time?
Who do you think I am?
Who needs measuring when I can tell Yuri's three sizes at a glance?
Huh?!
Yuri's three sizes are...
How on earth did you do that?!
You really are amazing, Erika!
All right then!
Now that that's done, let's all go back to Fairy Drop and make Yuri some dresses!
Yeah!
We need to work hard!
Yuri, let's go!
Huh?
Here we go!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Let's have a cheer for the return of Cure Moonlight!
Hip, hip...
Hooray!
Nice to be working with you!
But now it's a mad dash to get ready for the school festival!
I'm really not sure we'll be ready.
No need to worry! We'll make sure it's all done on time!
I swear it as leader of the Fashion Club!
HeartCatch Precure:
We Can't Wait for the School Festival!
The Fashion Club's in a Panic!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!