Things have settled down for the time being.
But we are yet to come up with a
fundamental solution for our problem.
We haven't responded to the love advice requests,
and then there's the matter of the newspaper association's future.
Well, yeah, but we have more pressing matters to attend to, don't we?
Dolling Mizushima up for her date!
What?
She's right!
We haven't a moment to waste!
This is really urgent!
You can't relax on your date unless you're all dolled up, after all.
Hey! The next time I see him will be when I turn twenty or something!
What is he, a time capsule?
Suzu put in all that effort when
we were having big problems too.
The teachers were really scary,
but Suzu summoned up all her courage to face them.
And I had no choice but to crossdress in front of everybody. That was such a painful experience.
Pull the other one!
Oh, all right. We can make that our agenda.
But with this, we're even. Got it?
Start with losing the glasses!
Let's try letting her hair down too.
Cut it out!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
This was the mainframe?!
Excuse me?
She looks like a whole different person without glasses.
The Very Best of the Student Council
(By Publisher Request)
Man, her power's off the charts!
Damn, I can't see.
Give them back.
Where are they?
Mizushima's acting like a newborn fawn!
Using this contrast to make hearts skip a beat?!
I can't see!
My glasses. Where are my glasses?
What are you even doing?!
Are you okay?
A closet klutz?
How many heroine attributes do you have?!
No fair!
Silence!
If I look like a different person already,
I don't need any more dolling up now, do I?
What're you talking about?
You need to be cute, not different!
Anyway, give back my glasses!
I can't see anything without 'em!
You okay?
Here you go.
From my brother's strange glasses collection:
the Heart Lovely Max!
It's my present to you.
Mind letting me meet your brother in person some time?
I checked out the scenes of your date, but...
Don't make it your damn wallpaper!
What's with this half-assed outfit?
How long ago did you buy it?
Three years ago...
Back when you were an elementary schooler?!
...my cousin gifted it to me.
You didn't even buy it?!
Not to mention, this cousin of hers is a guy.
You wore an outfit some other guy gave you for your first date in six months?
How evil can you be?!
I'm telling you, the lack of putting on airs makes it really appealing.
Forget airs, I know you're just too lazy to put on anything fancy!
Yeah, she certainly is evil.
Huh?
This is all part of her calculations, Riko.
By taking off her pants,
she can set a guy's heart aflutter in an instant!
Using the charm of a guy's baggy clothes!
What am I, an exhibitionist?!
Streeetch
To avoid that perception, she'll drop a drink on herself and make it all seem natural!
H-How erotic!
Eroshima!
No one's stripping!
At least show some leg.
Go on, try it.
There's a perverted old man right here!
How about making a compromise and wearing a short skirt?
The only skirts I have are part of the school uniform.
I have just the thing for you right here.
C is for Costumes!
What's your favorite era?
Era?
Primitive
That'd turn even the Wild One pale!
Knock it off!
Ninja
She specializes in the ninja skills of love!
Form-fitting
Experience that sweet and dangerous 80's bubble!
Hey.
You'd better not have used the council budget for this.
Gulp.
I'm waiting for you, my prince!
Middle Ages
I'd cry if someone saw me like this!
Hold it right there!
Te ach Us,
Big Brother!
Teach Us, Big Brother!
Why'd you make it a ponytail
instead of tying it up in a bun?
This thing says buns are the way to go.
W-Well...
"To show off your neck,
tie your hair high up in a bun," huh?
If you wanna show off your neck, it's gotta be a ponytail!
That, or pigtails!
That's what my big brother said.
Tell him to get a job soon.
Oh, and that I'll close the book on his life the next time he does that.
Love Lab!
Hey there.
This is Yamazaki Yuu, Mizushima's b-boyfriend.
You'll have to pardon the abruptness.
This is a story of the time she and I first met.
Mizushima
Sayori
I'm Mizushima.
Nice to meet you.
Your seat's over there.
What, she's gonna be sitting next to me?
Yamazaki, be a dear and share
your textbook with her, will you?
What?
What a pain.
Weird glasses.
You were in Fuji Girls'?
Wow! What's it like?
Is that skirt you're wearing the uniform there?
Girls are such posers.
They jump on every little fad.
After a while...
If you like Fuji Girls' so much you wear its uniform every day, why'd you leave in the first place?
Not to mention you transferred in at such a weird time.
Jealousy.
Well, yeah, we did basically skip town.
Also, I don't particularly like Fuji Girls'.
This uniform's really durable and I've got a bunch of spares, so I don't want to waste it, is all.
I-Is that so?
You've got it rough.
We're sorry!
Wh-What a weirdo.
What?
Is it true, what you just said?
It is.
Wouldn't you normally hide that?
It felt like things would only get worse if I kept it under wraps.
She's pretty resolute.
You can take precautions against girls, but...
Mizushima!
I heard you and your family skipped town?
You're always wearing that same thing.
Is that why you're tiny? Because you can't afford food?
I knew it.
My parents gave it their all and came up bust. Big deal.
Besides, it's not my fault.
You guys really suck at drawing conclusions.
I see you've got tiny minds.
And brains.
Want me to take advantage of my family situation and complain to the teachers and your parents?
What do you say, pipsqueaks?
We're sorry.
S-Strong as hell!
Soon after we that, our seats got changed, severing the link between the two of us.
Though it was more like nobody had any links with her.
She wasn't trying to act tough or anything.
She was always just aloof, detached, and alone.
Man, Mizushima's got a massive ego for her size.
She's not the loud, annoying type,
but she's always so expressionless.
There's no telling what goes through her brain.
He could say that again.
She was a real weirdo.
But once in a while,
her tiny frame would look massively reliable.
Moppin' Race!
On your mark, get set...
Go!
Whoa, I got a great jumpstart!
I'll win the race if I keep this up!
Hey, Yamazaki! Look forward!
Huh?
Wow. This is the first time I've seen her with this kinda expression.
The next day, every girl in class gave me the cold shoulder treatment.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Goodbye, sweet allowance.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Yamazaki Yuu
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
with snacks
until we
change classes.
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
This comes into effect today, got it?
Contract
As compensation, I'll provide Mizushima Sayori
You're one unlucky guy.
You did do something terrible, though.
Mizushima's not really bothered by it, you know?
She was expressionless when she hit you too.
Was I seeing things back then?
She was completely unfazed.
That's no girl, dude.
Isn't Mizushima kinda cute?
What?!
Are you... losing your marbles?
That's the first time I've seen her wearing pants.
And thus, we arrive at the present day.
What I want right now is for her to
meet me just a little bit more often.
This was Yuu, Mizushima's boyfriend.
Te ach Us,
Big Brother!
Teach Us, Big Brother!
Oh yeah, Suzu. Could you make a slapstick?
I'm going to Eno's place today, you see.
What?
One with as much attack power as possible!
What?!
No! It's Sayori!
Go away! Don't say a word!
Stop making me face reality!
I'm not a natural-born masochist like your boyfriend.
I am but a fragile flower!
He dived into your skirt, and then you kicked his ass and ripped him off. What kind of relationship starts like that?!
Don't you think you're rewarding him a bit too much?
It's not like I'm jealous though, okay?!
That said, sticking your head inside a girl's skirt is every guy's dream!
This is hardcore.
Big Brother!
At least use the slapstick, will you?!
I didn't want to waste any time bringing it out.
You should be a lot stricter with him too.
But he took care of me when I was little.
Though he did bully me a little.
Oh! Yuiko's covering for me!
Thanks!
At this rate, you might have to take care of him forever.
Once he finishes his journey
to find himself, I'm sure he'll...
I-Is this what they call the sister fascination?!
I'm so happy!
I think he's starting to find a side of himself he'd be better off not looking for.
One more time, s'il vous plaît?
Wow, so cute!
Cute!
What's that a picture of?
Remember how "Memories with a sibling"
was the theme of one the spring events here?
Well, Suzu's came back.
It's my brother, Sayo.
You said you wanted to meet him, didn't you?
I just want to pay him back for the strange glasses.
Hey, what's with the dog ears?
Oh, back then,
I loved the dog bus from My Neighbor Tororo.
The dog bus is so cute!
My Neighbor
Tororo
Remastered Edition
My Neighbor Tororo Remastered Edition
Hey, Bro?
Do you think I'll be able to ride the dog bus someday?
Let's see...
If you be a good girl, I'm sure that day will come.
Am I a bad girl?
No, you're an angel!
It'll be here before you know it.
Maybe it's the dog bus!
Suzu!
I'm home.
Are you here to welcome me back?
Oh, Sis.
Welcome back.
Huh?
Because of you, I got welcomed back with a dejected expression! Do you have any idea how that feels?!
What? That's my fault now?
It is!
Here's the evening newspaper!
What're you gonna do about this?! She's totally into it now!
But...
Oh, for crying out loud!
Delivery for you!
Udon
This is all because you said it'd be here soon.
She was so cute, I couldn't help but say that.
Here's your milk!
Was I a bad girl?
N-Not at all!
Apparently the dog bus is really busy right now!
Yeah, it's currently breeding season for it—
Hell no!
In that case...
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
To tell you the truth,
the dog bus asked me to take care of this!
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Tororo's
Dog Bus
Franchisee
Come now, hop on...
Here
The bro bus!
Dog Bus
Bro Bus
"Bro bus"?
Are you serious?
It's super effective?!
Bro bus comin' through!
What do you think, Suzu?
This is dumb.
You're amazing, Bro!
Takin' a U-turn!
I love you, Bro!
Sis bus!
Sis Bus
(Self-proprietorship)
A rival company?!
No ripping off allowed!
It's not a rip-off! It's a piggyback ride!
Also, I smell nice!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Suzu's already made reservations!
Bro... Sis...
Cancel them, then!
What about my cancellation fee?!
Don't fight.
I'll definitely be canceling that!
Don't...
What the heck? That makes no sense!
(Partnership)
Brosis Bus
Business partnership!
(Partnership)
Brosis Bus
Brosis bus!
(Partnership)
Brosis Bus
That's how this photo came to be.
They dote on her too much.
Suzu's brother's a bit weird,
but he's a great brother, isn't he?
Her sister's great too.
Come to think of it,
you got your picture back too, right, Eno?
I'm, uh... leaving early.
It's in your bag, isn't it?!
Show us!
Wait a second!
Cut it out!
Don't worry about it.
Listen to my anecdote too, dammit!
Te ach Us,
Big Brother!
Teach Us, Big Brother!
Why'd you bully me so much back when we were kids?!
My friends ended up consoling me, you know?!
Back then, eh?
Sorry, Yuiko.
Things were quite complicated back then.
What?
Yours truly thought
the pompous sadist types were popular.
You know, the indiscretions of youth.
I hadn't realized it.
I hadn't realized that I was clearly a masochist!
If I'd been like this back then,
I would've been so nice to you!
Masochist
Rather than nice,
it'd be more like me begging to be your slave!
My big brother may be done for.
Took you long enough.
Love Lab!
How can you trip on a flat surface?
Sayo.
Thank you!
I see you're as clumsy as ever today.
Bravo.
I want to fix this, but things aren't going well.
She's always so calm and collected.
What about assigning yourself penalties?
Every time you screw up, you pay me a thousand yen.
My allowance wouldn't even last a day!
You flick me on the forehead every time I screw up, then. How does that sound?
Why me?
Okay, I'm gonna do my be—
Dear me.
Caution
This is hard to do.
I'll still do it, though.
You're merciless.
The path to becoming reliable is a long and arduous one.
Look!
It's the president!
So pretty!
Maki's the object of everyone's adoration again today.
Oh, Suzu.
Moving to your next classroom?
Too dazzling!
It amazes me that she'd talk to someone like me.
My.
It's red and swollen.
Looks painful.
T-Too close!
Too dazzling!
Hang on a second, okay?
I've got my basic first aid kit in here somewhere.
Considering it just came out of her pocket, that goes way beyond "basic"!
All done.
See you after school.
Th-Thank you very much!
That's Fuji's Princess for you!
She's perfectly prepared to help students out.
Nah.
It's probably so she doesn't miss out on a chance for romance.
Nobody knows about President Maki's cute hidden side.
It's a secret that only the student council members know.
It makes me feel special.
As if!
You two!
Stop slacking off and start cleaning.
It's Eno.
She has a strong sense of justice,
but she's too harsh sometimes,
which is why she often gets misunderstood.
You listening to me?!
We're very sorry.
Jeez.
Come on, let's get this done with.
Huh?
You too?
Well, duh.
Working in a group of three's much faster.
If it was just the two of you,
you wouldn't finish in time for the next class.
S-Sorry.
As long as you understand.
That's our vice president!
This is my worst subject, and long-distance running is the thing I suck the most at.
Hang in there, Suzu!
Most people are done already.
Tanahashi's dying out there.
She's two laps behind.
This is so embarrassing!
R-Riko's watching this miserable side of me?
You...
can...
do...
it?
2nd Lap
They made her stand up!
Riko.
Hey, Suzu. What's up?
U-Um, earlier you...
Man, you were so slow!
Yes.
I'm sorry you had to stand because of me.
Huh?
It's not your fault.
I really hate math.
I get yelled at all the time because I'm not paying attention.
Attagirl, Suzu.
Huh?
Running is what you hate most, right?
But you still gave it all you had.
It was really cute how you were panting.
Here's your reward.
All okay!
Yeah, I certainly do suck at running.
Growl
Would you like some candy?
But when I'm heading for that door, and only then,
I don't hate it one bit!
Sorry I'm late!
Okay.
Grit your teeth.
Please stop!
What are you, a demon?!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Now that we're through with our short stories,
the next episode will kick off a new development!
The love lab will face a new situation!
Who will make it to the end alive?
Just what kinda situation are we facing?!
That's wonderful!
Fate brings a guy and girl together as enemies on the battlefield,
and they're drawn to each other even as they fight!
You don't have to create a scenario on the spot.
Love is war.
Love Lab?
It pisses me off how you look like you think you said something clever.