Five million dollars!
Five million dollars were stolen on my territory.
There's no way I can just let this slide, is there?
Find the culprit and drag him before me!
If you have to...
...you can kill him.
Thank you, Reiji.
It's always been my dream...
...to have a mountain of burgers in front of me,
and stuff myself until
my stomach wouldn't take them any more.
So, Cal. About what you said earlier...
You saw who killed Judy?
About that...
I was wondering what I'll do about it.
What do you mean?
Will you really avenge Judy?
How?
They used machine guns, you know?
You can't trust me?
Yeah.
Because you don't seem that strong to me.
Is that so?
I can't be trusted, huh?
But you don't need to worry.
I'm not really the one who would do it.
I was planning to ask my friend.
Your friend?
Yeah.
You have such a friend?
I may not look it, but I know a lot of people.
If we know what the murderer looks like and what he wears,
I can have my friend look for him.
So, the one who shot her...
I want to see it for myself.
What?
I want to see it when you kill the guy who killed Judy.
Hey, Reiji. Let me see your friend.
I won't.
Why? Take me with you when you ask your friend.
Okay?
It's not a world ordinary people can associate with.
But...
No means no.
I'm sorry, Cal.
But...
Fine, I get it.
I lose.
I'll ask her if you can see her or not.
Really?
Yeah, but...
Alright then, let's talk about it when we see your friend.
People like her can't be contacted right away, though.
I will arrange it tonight.
Let's talk about it again tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Is there a problem with that?
The rent on Judy's room was piling up,
so I got kicked out this morning.
Can I stay at your place tonight?
How is it going, Lizzie?
Is the investigation proceeding smoothly?
Phantom has the girl.
I'm checking out another lead.
Wait a little bit longer.
I'm expecting some meaningful information.
Who ruined my deal?
The Goudou clan's existence is indispensable to strengthen Inferno's position.
This sort of incident will not topple me.
So this is your room?
It's kind of lonely.
It's more than enough to live in.
There's nothing inside.
What're you doing?
It's the leftover burgers.
Not eating them would be a waste.
Don't tell me you're going to stay here until you finish them all.
What?
Nothing.
Your bedroom is this way.
The bed is all yours.
Were you living here with someone before?
Why do you ask?
Just a hunch I guess.
It's all in the past.
Your girlfriend?
No.
Say...
Can I use the shower?
So I just have to act like that "friend" of yours?
Yeah, do me the favor please.
Fine by me. Having you owe me a favor isn't bad at all.
Hey, do you really think that girl is any good?
I don't know.
What an unreliable answer you give me there.
Reiji.
Sorry, I forgot to bring a towel.
I'll bring it.
What?
Nothing.
I never thought the venerable and almighty Phantom would be toyed with by a little girl.
Letting her stay in your room doesn't mean you can do strange-
He cut me off.
What are you doing sneaking around in someone else's back yard, Lizzie?
Really?
Yeah, she said we can see her.
She will contact us tomorrow.
Thank god.
Say, Reiji. Do you have a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
I see.
Yeah.
Just like me.
Have your parents passed away?
No idea.
I ran away from the worst father there ever was.
And Judy found me.
If she hadn't, I'd probably be dead by now.
So that's why you said you're her sister?
Yes. She was the only family I had.
But now she's dead.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What should I do now that Judy is gone?
Where should I go?
What should I do?
I don't know anything.
I've been through it too.
I didn't know.
Even death comes in many forms.
Some leave behind deep anguish for those alive,
and some die without anyone to grieve for them, slowly forgotten.
Judy is happy, since she has you to cry for her.
You think so?
Yeah.
What should I do?
Where should I go?
I don't know anything.
Is the witness in here?
This is a pretty dull place to stay in, isn't it, Phantom?
What do you want?
Don't put on airs.
I saw Lizzie sneaking around and searching for some rats downtown,
and heard some pretty interesting stories.
Let me talk to the little girl.
I'll make her spill the beans.
Is she in there?
She knows nothing.
You're in my way.
An untrained girl wouldn't be able to see anything in that dark alley.
She lied when she said she saw the shooter.
Move!
Phantom!
You'd protect her even if it means spilling blood, huh?
I want to meet her even more now.
So everything is just as I suspected.
You and Claudia are cooking something up.
This is a misunderstanding.
Ten o'clock tomorrow.
Come to headquarters.
I'll have you tell it all in front of McGwire.
Then we'll know...
...who the traitor is.
Sorry, Phantom.
I couldn't talk my way out.
It's fine.
But isn't this bad?
How will you convince them tomorrow?
I'll make excuses somehow.
So is she really...
Yeah.
She doesn't know anything.
I see.
You don't know anything,
do you, Cal?
Shall I hear your story?
That's...
Judy?
Judy!
I don't know anything after that...
As I thought.
So you saw through my lies?
That man just now was Isaac Wisemel, wasn't he?
The leader of the Bloodies.
Yeah.
Why did you cover for me?
Everyone called you Phantom.
I heard about it from Judy's friend.
You're the one who has been killing gang members all over America.
So you're a real assassin, huh?
You're an assassin, aren't you?
The Assassin, Phantom.
Yeah, I am.
Cal...
This is...
Those Yakuzas brought this money.
I counted five million dollars.
You stole it?
I didn't!
I didn't even use one cent of this dirty money!
I was looking for someone like you.
Someone I could hire with this money.
Reiji, you're Phantom, right?
Please kill everyone with this.
The people who were there in the alley yesterday, the ones who fired guns,
and those who were supposed to receive this money.
Kill everyone who killed Judy without exception.
Will you do it?
I'm going to estimate the price for the killings.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
I'm sorry I lied.
Me too.
The situation is going bad.
The assailant is nowhere to be found.
Only the five million dollars were.
If the organization found this money, I couldn't make excuses.
Kill everyone who killed Judy without exception.
What should I do?
How can I balance both Cal's and the organization's demands?
What's the meaning of this, Reiji?
I can't explain it here.
If we discuss this matter in private, it will arouse Wisemel's suspicion.
I'll talk about everything in front of the rest.
Let us hear your explanation, Phantom.
Yes.
First, I would like to clear up a misunderstanding.
Oh? Misunderstanding?
It's true I gave shelter to the girl who witnessed the attack.
She was just passing by though and got dragged into it. She knows nothing.
How can you be so sure of that?
Because I'm Phantom.
I'm capable of seeing such things.
A stupid excuse.
It sounds like that to me as well.
It's completely meaningless without proof.
Did you use drugs to make her talk?
No.
Any recorded data?
None.
So in short you're telling us to trust your word.
Indeed.
Drop it already, Phantom.
Miss McCunnen, do you have something to say?
Is there anything else?
I have my reasons not to use drugs.
Is that so?
Is it for the same reasons you pointed your gun at Isaac?
Yes.
Let us hear it.
I didn't want to break her.
Humanism at this point?
No.
I saw a different potential inside her.
And I didn't want to ruin that.
Potential?
Correct.
She has a rare resourcefulness about her.
You can call it a talent if you like.
The yearning to kill someone.
Hellish solitude.
A spectre with nowhere to be.
"Talent".
I heard the same word a long time ago.
In other words, you want to train the girl into another hitman?
Correct.
She might become a skilled
right hand to me in the future.
Any proof of this girl's talent?
My intuition.
Don't mess around, bastard!
This isn't something I can explain through words.
A human who has his eyes clouded by suspicion might not be able to see it.
Phantom!
One question.
Do you really wish for a new assistant that badly?
Are you saying there are problems with the teamwork between Lizzie and you?
Well, we have problems alright.
Phantom and me contrast too much.
Phantom is a genius, yet I'm just an ordinary person.
If there is a different partner he set his eyes on,
I'd trade places with her any day.
About that prostitute, Judy Devens, that died along with the Yakuzas...
Are you positive she has nothing to do with this case?
Yes, absolutely nothing.
I left no stone unturned.
What do you think, Isaac?
Are you telling me to accept this, Ray?
If you cannot give rise to something...
You know what happens, right?
I do.
Well then, let's see how skillful you can shape her to be.
That was an interesting playact, Reiji.
Ya can't fool me.
Ya can't fucking fool me!
You damn watchdog of a fox!
Sorry about that.
Don't worry.
It was my fault to begin with.
But...
I know.
You don't want to create another of your lot.
It's just a way to protect her, right?
But now that you've sung her praises,
you will be held responsible.
I know.
In the end, nothing is solved.
The assailant,
the five million dollars,
avenging Judy.
What should I do?
She's probably a genius.
But is it okay to let her walk the same path I took?