I heard that some Raira Academy
students were attacked by the Slasher!
But make her body the center of it all...
And throw those around her into the fire.
Haruna, did you make sure to eat?
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yeah, the strongest.
If I weren't the headless rider, I'd be dead right now.
Alright, I'm gonna kill him!
I'll hunt him down and kill him!
Shizuo!
I'm flying...
I'm flying?!
All I wanted was to learn.
About Ikebukuro;
about the source of energy for this refuse-packed city,
about the truth behind this city that
continues to swell with desire every day.
That's mine!
And...about the strongest man in town.
About six months ago, I was writing a seasonal
feature story about the troubled times in Tokyo.
And I met a man while researching the
legendary strongest person in Ikebukuro.
The air; the air around him was different.
That's the only way I can describe—
You ass, making me resort to violence!
Are you a god?! Are you just pretending to be one?! Huh?!
Hey, Shizuo, we're going.
Okay.
Who's next?
That teacher who sexually harasses his students.
Amazing.
Amidst my everyday life of writing gossip articles for a third-rate
magazine, he'd revived that pure feeling I'd felt during my younger days.
A curiosity.
Yes, an intense curiosity.
I wanted to know everything about him.
However...
Due to the uproar that followed soon after, my article was postponed.
I don't know the specifics of the incident, but it seemed
there were more evil spirits writhing in this magic capital...
And something was about to happen.
So, this strongest man had to be involved in some way.
As I'd resumed reporting for that feature article on Ikebukuro,
I decided to start collecting information from those around him.
Oh, Shizuo?
He's a good friend.
Have some salmon roe.
Umm, I didn't order that...
Oh, Shizuo's friends are my friends.
Thanks for your purchase.
Does he use that kind of Japanese on purpose?
The strongest...?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Shizuo's a good guy.
Have you ever seen him in the middle of a fight or something?
Oh, fighting isn't good.
Peace is good.
You should look.
Giant clam is good?
One order of giant clam!
Wait...!
It's useless, sir.
Simon's a pacifist, so there's no use talking about fights.
No, I was just asking him who the strongest person in the city is...
You should ask a field expert about something like that...
If you really want to know...
The strongest in Ikebukuro, you say?
Yes, I heard from someone that you're
particularly knowledgeable of matters in this field.
If you're talking about fights, you do understand that that era has already passed, don't you?
We now use our brains more than our bodies.
Yes, it's clean work.
"Clean," huh?
Of course, were someone to make us look like fools, that'd be the end of it.
If someone wants to start a fight, then it doesn't matter whether
they're an amateur, they have a blade, or they try to muscle us out;
We'll thoroughly crush them.
However...
The ones who act out are amateur brats, not pros like us.
Yes, like the Dollars or the Yellow Scarves.
Well, as long as they don't interfere with our business, we won't touch them.
Recently, people of urban legend like the
headless rider or the Slasher have appeared...
Hmph, I guess it's him.
The strongest person in this city is...
Heiwajima Shizuo.
So you do think it's him, sir?
I've heard he puts up a clean fight.
Either way, there's an information dealer who's more knowledgeable about this kind of thing than we are.
Is that true?
Would you please introduce me to him?
It's not like I'm asking for anything in return...
But, as for our line of business...
You understand, don't you?
So, who told you about me?
Well, I can't reveal my sources...
Whatever.
You're here for that "troubled times in Tokyo" thing, right? They
showcase things like strange happenings and gang member introductions.
So, the next issue's about Ikebukuro?
Since you know all that, that makes things easier.
Actually, I'm thinking of writing an article that
decides who the strongest person in Ikebukuro is.
The strongest, huh...
There are tons of strong people in that city...
In a bare-fisted fight, it would be Simon from that sushi place.
If there aren't any rules, it'd be Shizu-chan.
Sh-Shizu-chan?!
I mean Heiwajima Shizuo.
You came to ask about him, didn't you?
Well, yes...
As for Shizuo...
He's unpleasant.
Huh?
It's enough for me just to know something about him.
I try to learn some things about him since I'm no good at dealing with him...
But that's unpleasant, so I don't want to talk about it.
Could you please try?
By the way, Mr. Niekawa...
How's your daughter?
As her parent, you must have been worried
that she had to transfer over something like that.
You're the magazine writer who, six months ago, came into contact
with Heiwajima Shizuo and ended up in the sky along with a streetlight.
If you go sniffing out things around that city,
you might end up interfering with my work...
Just who are—
I'm sure you're already aware of it...
But there have been some dangerous occurrences in that city.
Do they have anything to do with the conflict
between the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves—
That's part of it, as are the Slasher incidents that started it.
The Slasher?
Even though there's already one uncontrollable urban legend here...
Oh, that's right.
If you want to know more about Heiwajima
Shizuo, I can introduce you to a close friend of his.
Mr. Orihara the information dealer
introduced me to a rather odd individual.
Oh yeah, here's a piece of advice:
You shouldn't talk to Shizuo about his younger brother.
If only I'd known that six months ago.
I was caught off-guard by the mention of my daughter.
I have a daughter who's in her second year of high school.
We've been living by ourselves since my wife ran off.
Honestly, I don't think she looks up to me.
She's the reason I started writing articles just for the money.
Hello, I'm Celty the courier.
That's...
Shizuo's a trustworthy friend. At least to me he is.
I guess he can be scary when you make him mad, though.
Actually, I'm planning to write about who the best fighter is...
The magazine you work for really likes that kind of thing, huh?
You publish motorcycle gang rankings and whatnot.
Well, thank you...
Anyway, there are some people around town
who'd consider you the strongest person here.
It looks like she's laughing...
As if! Shizuo's way stronger than me!
He's so insane it's almost moving!
How do I put this...
It's not just about fighting or combat styles...
Maybe you'd understand if I said he's a lone wolf or has magic powers.
Or maybe, "He's an alien?"
That doesn't quite work...
That sounds like a little gray alien experienced something traumatic.
Anyway, no matter how well-trained a fighter you are,
if you get shot, you're done for.
That's it!
His strength is like that of a gun!
Comparing them was nonsense from the start...
I was moved.
I'd experienced Heiwajima Shizuo's strength with my own body.
For an urban legend herself to speak so highly of him...
Right, that strength is of another dimension.
Perhaps, due to a cranial process involving adrenaline...
He's able to utilize some supreme power.
The momentary power that transcends the
limits of humans is completely off the charts.
I understand.
Um...this is just out of curiosity, but...
What is it?
If possible, could you please show me what's under your helmet?
You don't have to if you don't—
No way...That can't be...
That's it; Ms. Celty must be a magician.
After I pulled myself together, I continued my investigation.
I kept hearing rumors about the rivalry
between the Dollars and the Yellow Scarves.
They said that the leader of the Yellow Scarves—their shogun...
Would move on the Dollars, who assume they're being ignored.
So, what kind of guy is he?
I dunno.
I doubt the young members of the Yellow Scarves know, either.
The only thing I know about the shogun's true identity is that
he's ordered everyone not to get involved with Orihara Izaya.
It couldn't be...
That strongest...
The recurring Slasher incidents...
The Yellow Scarves apparently believe that the Dollars are behind it all.
I'd heard that a single girl was spared in the incident a few
days ago, where some high school girls were attacked here.
I unconsciously likened that girl to my own daughter.
A father who'd risk his life to protect his daughter from the Slasher...
However, right now my daughter is like an
alien to me who I have no hope of understanding.
This is no good.
Today's the day I go face-to-face...with the daughter I love.
Did you hear?
The victim of today's Slasher attack...
Was apparently writing an article on
Tokyo's troubled times for "Tokyo Warrior."
Whoa.
So he's a magazine journalist?
Eh?! Really?!
C'mon...have I ever lied to you before?
Is he alright?
Do you know him, Setton?
Uh, no...
I'm a fan of the article.
Huh, maybe I should read it sometime.
Anyway, that's pretty scary.
I wish the police the best of luck.
Saika has entered the chat room.
It's here!!
Huh?
Eh?
I Cut.
It cut!
Today, I Cut.
I'm the one who wants to cut you!
But, Still, No Good,,, Strong People, Like
Evenin', Saika.
It's no use, Setton. It won't reply to anything we say.
I have to cut, more.
That's rather eerie.
Cutting people and all that...
With this whole Slasher thing...
Ahahaha.
Nice.
Strong People,
Want To love.
I Found.
Purpose
Love
Found
Shizuo.
Eh?
Heiwajima Shizuo,
Do you know Shizuo?
Heiwajima
Shizuo
I Love
I Love, Shizuo, I Love.
Cut Heiwajima Shizuo. I, Love Heiwajima Shizuo, Cut.
Heiwajima, Shizuo, Cut, Love, Heiwajima, Cut, Cut
Love, Heiwajima Shizuo
My Mother's Wish, Heiwajima,
My Mother's Wish, Shizuo, My Mother's Wish, Shizuo, I Love
Heiwajima, My Mother's Wish, I Cut
I Love, Shizuo,
I Cut, I Love, Heiwajima, I Love,,, I Cut
I, Cut, Heiwajima
I Love, Shizuo, My Mother's Wish
My Mother's Wish
Shizuo,
Saika has left the chat room.
Eat up, Anri.
You'll get fat, Anri.
It's alright, I'll just exercise.
I was joking. Eat up.
We'll be together forever, won't we, Mom and Dad?
The girl had a dream every night...
Of a happy family; one you'd find in a drawing.
However, that was a fleeting illusion.
Her parents died five years ago...
In a horrible accident.
As the only survivor, she still has those dreams...
Dreams of that happy family she never had.
The tragedy that stole her parents away...
Was the first incident the Slasher ever caused.
Anri...
You're already making preparations for the sports festival?
Are you sure you're okay?
Y-Yes...
She thought she was a cunning person.
She could plainly see what his ulterior motive was...
Yet she never faced it head-on...
She'd close off her heart and simply wait for the situation to pass.
...might come after you again.
It's dangerous to go out alone.
Are you sexually harassing her again?
We can't have that now, can we?
She knew that she was leeching off of him.
Masaomi!
Sonohara!
Enter the coward.
Sorry. Were you waiting?
I thought I'd turn into a fossil waiting for you!
Eh?
Square root of three points.
A square root? What's a square root?
At least make your criticism easy to understand with something like "minus twenty points."
When I awoke, I was in a hospital bed.
It's okay. You'll get better if you just take it easy for a while.
You have to stay here for about one week, and after that...
There was a gap...in my memory.
No, you shouldn't get up!
I don't have time for this now.
Wait Mr. Niekawa!
See you!
See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
The voice inside me told me to "watch over her."
Mr. Niekawa from room five still hasn't come back.
That's too bad.
I hope his wounds don't open back up.
I'll kill it.
Shizuo,
I appreciate your concern, but you don't have to come if you don't want to.
This is my own problem.
First off, the Slasher won't necessarily be out tonight—
I'll never forgive that Slasher bastard.
Whether it's an ethereal sword or something else, breaking a katana means it dies, right?
Although even if it doesn't die, I'll kill it.
I'll kill it.
Hm?
Calm down, Shizuo!
This isn't the time to get involved with guys like...
You have something to say, you insect?
We'd like to say hello to that cockroach over there.
Listen, looks can kill.
Huh?!
There's at least a 0.000000000000000675%
chance that someone can die from a curse or a stare.
Huh?!
How many zeros was that?!
Hey, bartender...
A b-bartender...
It couldn't be...
So you can't complain if I hurl you into the air and you die, right?!
Niekawa Haruna...
What was with Mr. Nasujima's reaction...?
Excuse me, miss.
It's already eleven o'clock.
It's time for students to be going home.
S-Sorry!
I'll go home right away.
Are you alright?
If you live around here, I can take you home.
Umm...Well...
We've received an emergency call stating that a fight has broken out in Eastern Ikebukuro Central Park.
You've been dispatched, so please hurry.
Understood. We're going.
Let's go, Mr. Kuzuhara.
Sorry, miss.
If you feel like it, just wait at the police
box and I'll take you home when I get back.
Stop that!
Stop thinking that replacing the normal characters for "moment" with more pretentious ones will make the sentence look cool!
You're were that age where you wanted to look at
things from a different angle, weren't you, Yuma-chi?
And stop thinking that simply by rejecting the worldview of a normal adult
that it will score you points with middle and high
school students going through their rebellious stage!
Thinking that rejecting philosophy and society
will make you look cool is so shallow, huh?
It's pretty rare for Yumasaki to be bad-mouthing a book.
What're you reading?
Well...
A novel that he self-published a while back.
I might not be in a position to say anything, since I
was sleeping, but one of our comrades was attacked.
Let's be serious about gathering our information.
But, unlike Kaztano, we don't even know this person.
Even if they are a member of the Dollars...
At least try to sympathize with others a little bit.
I think it's sad, but I've locked that feeling away.
I don't want to forgive the Slasher, but I've locked that feeling away.
Anyway, why did we join the Dollars?
Don't you want to lead peaceful lives?
I want to have a cute, green-haired daughter in a foreign land...
And when we return to Japan, I'll live happily with three beautiful sisters!
It'd be nice if such a modest life were possible.
Is that "Yotsuba&!"?
Come to think of it, it was around here, right?
The place where the Slasher appeared.
What a reckless kid.
That's the type of kid who's most susceptible.
Uh, this might be bad.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
That guy back there had red eyes.
Huh?!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I was just reliving a traumatic experience.
What am I doing...?
Togusa!
Yeah!
Floor it.
What's up?
Hey, where are we going, Celty?!
Did he die?
You're horrible, Kadota!
This is how you act right after saying you want to live in peace?!
I had no other choice.
Either way, it was self-defense...
Run!
The headless rider and...
Shizuo?!
D-Dotachin! He's...!
Are you some kind of monster?!
You're...Heiwajima Shizuo?
I've wanted to meet you, Shizuo.
Heiwajima Shizuo...
I love you very, very, very, very much, Shizuo.
I get it. I'm going to kill you.
That's right. I'm going to interview Heiwajima Shizuo, the strongest...
If I can write a good article, everything's bound to go well.
My wife will come back.
My strained relationship with my daughter will get better, too.
It'll be like the good ol' days...
Definitely...
The Slasher incidents were supposed to have ended after that.
Yet they didn't.
Rather, it signaled the beginning of her destiny.
It's turned into a long, long night.
Next Time: Mutual Love.