Judy...
Let her be, Cal. She probably just ran out of alcohol.
I'm leaving now.
I plan to be home by morning as usual.
See you later.
This way!
Ah...! Phantom!
It's Phantom... of Inferno.
Apparition
Last year alone,
more than 20 dominant figures already fell victim to mysterious purges.
These assassinations are referred to as the "Phantom Assassinations"
and are sending chills down the spine of the US underworld.
Looks like that chick's organization is making a big show as usual.
It's not a laughing matter, bro.
Huh?
That could happen to us, you know.
Deluca Rezzo, who was practically No. 2 in the Gambino Family, is dead now.
They're powerless now, huh?
The east coast... is ours, too.
This is solely thanks to Phantom's services.
I was deeply impressed by the previous Phantom,
but that young man is even more brilliant, Claudia.
I'm impressed that you were able to tame him this much.
It's not that I tamed him.
His devotion to Inferno is of his own free will.
Eh, is that so?
I was sure that he's been working his ass off just so he can suck on your tits.
By the way, Mr. McGwire...
Hm?
Tsk.
Regarding the Godo Family matter... We've finished the investigation.
You mean the Japanese organization that's going to join us?
They cultivated a market of their own within Japan
and are making quite a profit.
However, because their supplier, a Southeast Asian dealer,
was struck a devastating blow,
the Godo Family currently has no product in stock.
If we establish a business with the Godo Family now,
we can become the exclusive supplier for the product in Japan.
Hm...
I've set up a five million dollar deal with Mr. Daisuke Godo,
who oversees the family's operations, for this weekend...
as a sign of our friendship.
Hold on a sec.
What makes you think that you can negotiate deals, too?
So you don't care what we think?
Enough.
But...
If the negotiations can go smoothly this way,
we don't have to appoint a different person.
Well then, I'll carry on with the negotiations.
Are you done?
Hey, aren't you pushing too hard these days?
You think so?
I'm sure you have your reasons,
but if you put too much support into one organization,
it'll end up causing you trouble.
Don't worry. I'm doing fine.
I'm surprised to see you back so early.
I just returned...
...Ms. McCunnen.
Zwei... I heard about the New York case from Lizzie.
Sounds like it was a great success.
Thank you.
I'll bring your car to the front right away. Are you driving?
No, you drive.
You're turning out to be pretty slick... Phantom...
So how did you like New York?
It was cold, that's all.
Isaac said that you're being Phantom just for my body.
That sounds like something he'd say.
As a man, do you think he's got a point?
Could be.
I've forgotten... my reasons.
Yeah... Who cares about that...
You're here of your own free will.
No way...
I don't have free will.
Right now... I have nothing.
You'll eventually come to feel nothing, too.
...doesn't have a past... or a future...
They have nothing.
You were right... Elen...
Your steering isn't very smooth.
Yeah... since we've got 25 kilograms of cocaine along for the ride.
Just the two of us?
The purpose of this deal is to strengthen our trust in each other.
If we bring many men with us, we'll give them a bad impression, right?
I see...
So who are we dealing with?
People from your country.
Then that yakuza guy?
Are we doing the deal in a place like this?
This area has been the Bloodies' turf for a long time.
Isaac Wisemel?
That's right.
No one's dumb enough to cause trouble here and start a fight with the Bloodies.
So... this is the safest place for Inferno.
Is that it?
No signal...
This is strange...
Zwei?
Stay inside.
The attacker was solo.
His weapon is a pistol with a silencer and...
a large knife.
Did he hunt the enemy one by one while they were panicked in the darkness?
He's got extraordinary skills.
I told you not to get out of the car.
What's going on here?
It looks like our deal tonight has been canceled.
Who on earth did this?
Beats me.
There's no use staying here and thinking about it.
You go on ahead and go back alone.
I'll head back soon, too.
What are you going to do?
I'll clean up this mess.
You sure brought a huge mess into my turf! You hear me?!
The police officers on patrol are out for blood,
and the dealers and women are too scared to work.
You've made a mess of my turf!
Well, Claudia?!
Are you trying to dodge your responsibility, Mr. Wisemel?
What'd you say?!
The responsibility for protecting the turf is yours.
My guest got his five million in cash stolen in your yard,
and on top of that, four of his men were killed.
I'd like you to think carefully about who should be blamed for this.
You bitch! Since when can you speak like that?!
This is inappropriate.
Claudia... What's the Godo Family's reaction?
Although they are furious, they seem to be under control.
Okay. I'll entrust you with keeping them entertained then.
Humor them as much as possible.
We have to return our guest's money right away...
together with the bodies of those who stole it.
That's your job, Isaac.
Hold on a sec!
You call those Asians our guests?!
I never agreed to it.
It's a matter of dignity.
Someone who came knocking on Inferno's door was attacked.
It makes no difference whether they're a guest or a beggar.
Are you going to allow such violence at our doorstep?
Fine. I'll try checking around.
Any change in there?
We've finished checking up on that body.
Her name is Judy Devens. 26 years old.
Looks like she's been in that area for a long time.
She didn't have any suspicious connections at all.
She didn't use a pimp and was on her own.
Where did she live?
I had someone check it out. There were no weapons. No guns, no knives.
It seems like she had a roommate, but we haven't found her yet.
Is something bothering you?
I'll leave things here to you, Lizzie.
Huh?
Jeez, what a demanding man you are.
Okay. Go. The police and the media should be gone by now.
Is this where Judy Devens died?
Who...
Who are you?
What about you? Are you Judy's acquaintance?
Were you her friend, too?
I'm her younger sister.
What? Is it strange if she had a sister with a different skin color?
No...
Who killed Judy?
You think I know?
You don't have even the slightest idea?
Are you saying that Judy had a reason to be shot?
I guess I asked a stupid question.
Huh?
Wait!
What are you going to do when you find the shooter?
I'll make her shooter get what he deserves.
You can do that?!
Yeah.
Then...
Then take me with you!
I can be of use!
No.
I know who killed Judy.
I was watching everything.
When she was shot here last night, I was with her!
It was on our way home after I went to pick up Judy, who was drunk.
But Judy... protected me and...
Please... would you take me with you?
What's your name?
I'm Cal. Cal Devens. What's yours?
I'm...
Reiji... Azuma...
I see. So you're Japanese.
Okay, Reiji!
Then, you and I are partners from now on!
Partners?
That's right. Inseparable partners whose goal is to avenge Judy.
I'll definitely be of use to you.
Huh?
Okay. We're partners from now on...
though it'll probably be for just a short while.
It was a small encounter.
And... I will continue to commit sins.
My life was thrown into confusion.
Hm?
And this time, in that swirl...
I will be throwing someone else's life into confusion.
Next episode
Disguise
What should I do?
Where should I go?
I don't know what to do.