“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
It's amazing!
It's more amazing than Ginza, Kamisakura-Machi.
Well, I don't know the whole story. So I don't know for sure.
There are still tons of dangerous folks around, so keep an eye out.
Speaking of which, I saw those black motorcycles today.
We haven't had something so tasty in a while, have we? A teenage girl.
Yeah. According to various sources.
At that moment, I noticed that I was shaking.
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Is the reality you see around you... really reality?
The scenery you're used to seeing never changes...
Ladies and gentlemen, congratulations on your acceptance to this school.
Right now, Japan is troubled by bleak issues, like declining birth rates and a stratified society,
but when I look at all of you sitting here,
I feel that our country's future is bright, and Japan is going to be all right.
I feel encouraged. Today is a fine day for you all, and yet at the same time...
...so of course, you believe that the things you're used to seeing everyday...
are still here around you today.
I-I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
A shy boy who just came to Tokyo.
I'm Sonohara Anri.
Nice to meet you.
A girl who is slightly detached from the world.
I'm Kida Masaomi!
I may look like a grown up, but on the inside
I'm just a fragile, tender-hearted fifteen-year-old like the rest of you!
The one boy who looks happy.
I'm Kamichika Rio.
Nice to meet you.
A girl who seems mysterious somehow.
The kind of people you think you see everywhere.
Harima...
Is Harima Mika here?
Absent.
Ordinary things you know you've seen before.
Oh, tardy from day one?
Everyone's introducing themselves. Why don't you do so now?
I'm Yagiri Seji.
Nice to meet you.
However, at a mere moment's notice,
the reality you know will sometimes give you a glimpse of another reality you've never seen.
Well, Mr. Yagiri, please take a seat quickly.
I will not.
I don't think I'll be able to come to school for a while.
No, I may not come at all anymore.
I came to tell you that. Now, if you'll excuse me.
Wait, Yagiri! What on earth does that...
It is what it is. It's a matter of great importance to me.
I don't have time to chat with you all.
Excuse me.
Hey, Yagiri! Wait! Stop right there!
A fissure that suddenly erupts in a peaceful, average life, is cause for a disturbance amongst people.
And, here we have a girl who witnessed such a fissure.
In all reality, she should have died two days prior.
There One Moment, Gone the Next
She was born into an average household, which you could find anywhere,
living life freely, and without problems.
But, when she entered middle school, it came to her as if ambushed.
What was in it?
A picture,
of my father, with another woman... it looked like they'd been having an affair.
And there was a letter attached, which asked the question: "Is this forgivable?"
It looked like it was the woman in the picture who sent it.
Your father did something pretty terrible, but so did she, right?
I didn't know what to do.
So for the moment, I decided to keep it a secret.
Then he let go and it flew it across the room. "Ow!"
Since that day though, everything around me seemed so unpleasant...
It must've been painful.
What's wrong, Rio?
I was only able to take it for about half a year.
Soon after, I thought it would be better to just expose the whole damn thing.
If it's hard to say, you don't have to push yourself to say it.
I have some things I can't talk about also.
It's okay.  I want you to know.
And just when I picked up my cell phone to check on it, it rang!
Nothing happened.
I didn't know if my mother was keeping quiet about it, or if they talked about it...
I bet that happens to you a lot, Rio!
But my father's jokes were still just as boring,
and my mother's cooking was still too sweet.
In the end, nothing changed.
I thought about disappearing just to see what would happen.
I've thought about it a lot recently.
I know how you feel.
This may not be as bad as your story, Magenta, but...
What happened?
I was going out with this girl, but then she hooked up with my dad...
That's terrible!
However, the worst part was my mom.
What did she say?
"This kind of thing happens all the time,
and we have our image to think about, so don't go making a big fuss over it."
I thought maybe our reputation was more important than I was,
but then again, maybe she was thinking about my future when she said it...
I don't think so.
Really?
She's not thinking about you at all, Nakura-san!
She's only thinking about herself!
Dinner's ready.
Okay.
Magenta-san, will you die with me?
If we die together,
then all of them will know what they should have valued the most,
whether they like it or not.
In hindsight, it was a foolish thing to do, but because of the way she felt, she went out.
Because she felt empowered by Nakura's words.
Because she wanted to see the face of someone who felt the same way she did.
Even if they were lying, she had nothing to lose.
Or so she thought.
Yes?
Magenta-san?
Yes.
Are you Nakura-san?
Good! It is you.
The minute she saw his face, she thought, "This man isn't Nakura, is he?"
How do you do? Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
The reason she followed him anyway was because she couldn't let herself back out after having come this far.
Shall we go, then?
Yes...
And so, even when the situation came to this,
Hello!
Hello.
Is anyone around?
Not a soul.
Well then.
Sorry... to fool you!
Surprise, resistance, regret and other emotions came, and went,
but just before losing consciousness, this is what went through her head:
"This is fate. Why should I try to protect myself at a time like this?"
"I should leave this world quietly... Just like this, without anyone knowing."
However...
There is one person here.
Even while the girl was lying unconscious, the world was moving.
Well, it doesn't look like it's going to be that tough a job, but be careful anyway.
Completely independent of her thoughts and her will.
I can't! No matter what I do, I can't seem to get all of the money!
I'm not saying I won't pay it back.
Still, if something were to happen to me, the Awakusu Club wouldn't stay quiet, now would—
Old man!
I don't have time for this.
It's not that I'm busy though.
It's just, I only have about two and a half more minutes of my life that I'm willing to share with the likes of you!
—one more person to not make enemies with...
Yo.
I know I don't need to say this to a superior smuggler like yourself,
but you don't need to do any more than I asked you to do.
Just deal with the guys on the other side in a befitting manner.
That's it. See you later.
The world was moving, and what the girl had believed to be fate, was slowly changing.
Hey.
W-What the hell are you?!
Yeah.
And, there on the phone, the words "There's someplace I've been asked to take you." was written.
The bike rode noiselessly, only occasionally whinnying like a horse.
It was simply unreal. Yet, the feeling of his body was unmistakably real.
The girl thought about what was on the inside of this warmth.
What did he think, what did he know, and how did he live?
From his own eyes, what did he look like?
I understand.
Magenta-san!
How do you do? My name is Nakura.
Are you really Nakura-san?
I'm the Nakura who also wants to stop living in the blink of an eye.
Nice to meet you.
Would it happen to have been you who saved me, Nakura-san?
Yes, it was me.
Thank you very much.
Were you scared?
Yes.
It must have been terrible.
Yeah...
But, how did you know?
Well, I'm the one who told them to kidnap you.
I'm also the one who gave the order for you to be saved.
What do you mean?
Getting kidnapped when you meant to kill yourself.
Wondering what you really are as you stand here all frightened, and slightly regretting it all.
Realizing that had you resisted, you would have denied yourself the chance to die,
and now you're thinking this must be fate.
Standing there and taking it as it comes,
but also feeling relieved that you've been saved;
I wanted to see all that on your face.
To sum it all up in a single sentence,
I wanted to see you standing there, speechless at how I saw right through you.
Why?
Well, let me see...  I think the answer to that question will sound very philosophical to you.
But, I suppose humans like to have things explained to them despite that.
Humans are so interesting, so intriguing.
You really can't blame me.
Ah. Don't get me wrong;
I like all humans, not just you.
That's important.
So it was all... a lie?
So you see the position you're in now, do you?
Come here.
Some people have jumped off from here, haven't they?
I won't call this spot well known, but it's pretty clear that you can kill yourself from here.
Hey, look at that stain over there.
You think you're the only one, don't you?
It's not true. We're all the same.
There's not a single soul in the world who can live their whole life being honest and innocent.
Even you have a secret or two of your own, don't you?
Have you ever thought about why it is that you're so good and your parents are so bad?
Well...
If you will hear out my final argument...
Even if we have affairs or find out about other people having affairs,
we all keep on living our lives, laughing at boring jokes and eating food that's too sweet.
Look. No matter what kind of problems we have, we're all just stains.
Stains.
Without exception, everyone goes to where God is; we're all equal.
Shall I let go?
Hey, now.
Well, for today,
I'd say it's a good thing your feelings got shaken up like they did.
Because it's not your worries that I'm interested in. It's your way of living.
In the end, you really have a dull way of living, just as I expected.
We now know that you never really wanted to die to begin with.
Well, see you later!
It's been fun, Magenta-san!
She was a bit confused.
Would she be able to hurt that man by doing this?
But then she thought that maybe she had been waiting for a chance like this.
Even if those were that man's words.
Just then, from out of nowhere...
Um...
Why?
Above and beyond the call of duty once again.
The girl thought about her parents.
About her father and his lover, her father and her mother.
She thought about all of the times she hadn't been there to see.
Maybe it wasn't colored by all the ill will, self-interest, and hatred like she thought.
Perhaps there was nothing being hidden in compromise and weakness.
As she found her way home, the girl decided she ought to forgive them.
Since that day, the world has looked different.
All the people's thoughts, and all the people's secrets;
All of it truly seemed to be a natural thing to her.
Where shall we go now?
I'll take you anywhere you wanna go. It's my treat today.
Let me see. In that case, how about a bookstore?
There are a lot of different kinds. Any one you wanna see in particular?
Even the people you see around you,
surely have their own secrets.
Well, we'll talk about it after we get home.
They have feelings they can't tell anyone.
Wait!
Yagiri-kun, there's gotta be something—
Don't ask.
B-But, you skipped the first day of—
I said, don't ask!
Wait!
Hey, what's wrong?
I wonder what's wrong?
I'm a guilty man too.
Huh?
That girl with the glasses has a crush on me!
I can feel it coming on; there are some wild, DANGEROUS and RISKY days ahead!
I'm sorry, would you speak Japanese please?
To him, and to her, that which is seen is not always real.
The girl wonders if she will ever be able to convey to someone else
that the world is not as terrible as they think?
I... didn't hear about you becoming a hero of justice.
I thought I gave a job to a superior smuggler.
Don't be silly!
The informant, Orihara Izaya, isn't that bad a guy, if I do say so myself.
Although, I'm not a good enough person to stop someone who wants to kill herself.
It's been fun, Superior Smuggler-san.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Pandemonium
Next time on
Durarara!!
Ikebukuro.
He, she, you, and I all come to this town to look for something,
to ask for something, to change something.
Next time: Pandemonium.
You eat sushi? It is good.
Oniisan, it's been a while!