I'm back, everyone!
Kaleido Star is about to start.
Let's make sure to watch Kaleido Star
according to the usual promise,
and have a lot of fun! Fun! Fun!
Is it all right if I keep on
thinking of myself as your dream?
No. You're not my dream anymore.
You're my pride.
Miss Layla...
Okay!
In the beginning I was a
little hyperconscious of you
I couldn't just let go and smile
It's strange, isn't it?
I couldn't get you off my mind
But our feelings just kept running in parallel
I want us to blend together
Like the coffee and milk in café au lait
Slowly and easily
(Blanc et noir, I'm sure we can) We should be able
to have that bitter-and-sweet relationship
(We are harmony)
Oui, with you the harmony would be wonderful
I want to play that harmony
with my special person
Okay, we're going to
start from where we left off!
"People of Our Time:
the Kaleido Stage's New Star,"
Um, are we recording the real thing now?
Sora Naegino," take five!
Please look at the camera.
Right!
Cue!
Today was your 200th performance.
Is it the power of the Angel's
Maneuver that brought you this far?
Yes! Because now the Angel's Maneuver
is something we all do together like zoom!
It is! It is!
There appear to be some fans who call
the Layla Hamilton days "The Era of Fire"
and these days "The Era of Light."
Sora...
That's one of those, you know,
Can't she do better than that?
completest possible honors...
Right now Sora's second to no one,
What?
not even Miss Layla.
The Angel's Maneuver...
Even the rest of the cast
become members of the audience,
the whole audience becomes one being,
and an angel stage is born.
A maneuver that makes the whole stage one...
I wonder if someday I'll be able to make one too...
This is the real one, right? I feel like, "bwaaa!"
It's like "eeee!", or "ohhhh," or maybe "kyaaa!"...
a stage that only I can make.
Uh-huh...
A new constellation is beginning to shine.
Fool!
The constellation Aries.
You mean Rosetta?
What's this about?
What? Er...
Who are you talking to? Huh? What?
No way, really?!
So does that mean Rosetta's
going to become the lead?
What?!
What?
What's Sora mumbling to herself about?
Fool...
Me, become the lead?
Er, what's this about Miss
Rosetta becoming the lead?
Mr. Yuri!
The truth is we weren't
planning to announce it yet, but...
Huh?
This is a good opportunity.
For this year's Kenneth
Corporation "Special Show,"
we plan to cast Rosetta Passel in a lead role.
What?!
Well, to be precise she'll
be co-starring with Sora.
I guess it kinda feels like
the moment's finally come.
No one told me about this!
Miss Rosetta, what are your comments
about being chosen for the lead?
I...
Congratulations, Rosetta!
Great job!
Good for you!
Thanks! I'll do my best to
meet everyone's expectations.
I'll do my best to meet everyone's expectations.
That was Miss Rosetta Passel,
expressing her enthusiasm
at the sudden announcement
of the lead role in their new show.
This is really just too sudden...
Mia, is this the script for the new show?
Uh-huh...
Can I look?
Go ahead.
So the title is
"The Princess Without a Smile"...
Come to think of it, when Rosetta
first came here she never smiled, huh?
So is it a Diabolo Master princess?
Huh? What?
Say, Mia, this isn't written in
invisible ink or anything, is it?
Of course not.
As you can see,
I haven't actually been
able to write a single page yet.
What? But it's already been announced!
Yeah, it has...
So, what are you going to do?
I sort of have a really vague concept, but...
It just won't come together somehow!
I'm sure you can do it, Mia.
Hey, where's Miss Sarah?
She's probably in her own room.
Thanks.
A catalyst. If I could just find a catalyst...
Miss Sarah, you have a package!
I'll do my best to meet everyone's expectations.
Okay, it's recorded.
Thanks, Fool!
You should title the video.
What kind of title?
Like "Kaleido Star: The Even More
Amazing Rosetta," or something.
That's amazing! That's great, Master Fool!
"Master Fool"!
Oh, how wonderful! It has a great ring to it!
Please, say it again!
That mask comes off?!
Master Fool!
Oh! One more time.
I guess it's not something
Master Fool!
Oh!
I should be surprised about...
Well, maybe it's good that
they get along. Maybe. Maybe.
Ugh! I can't believe this!
Miss Sarah?
Wait, wait! Wait! Miss Sarah, calm down!
I'll rip this thing apart! I'll burn it!
I'll torch it! Torch it! Torch it!
Torch it! Torch it! Torch it!
Just because they messed up your order
doesn't mean you have to treat it like garbage--
What's with this princess and jester?!
Give me my money back! Give it back!
What's this about "princess and jester"?
I smell a catalyst!
What? Hey, Mia!
I don't want it!
I'll throw this thing in the dumpster!
What's going on, Ken?
Well...
Just look at this, Sora!
They took a big chunk of cash from me,
and then they sent me this filthy painting!
It's only dirty because it's old.
Huh? This princess...
Doesn't she kind of look like Rosetta?
What?
You're right! She really does!
I wonder if Rosetta would look
like this if she were a princess.
Now, Ken, are you in love with Rosetta?
What are you talking about?!
There's one more person in that painting...
Yeah, behind the curtain, right?
He seems to be the jester.
Fool...
This jester fascinates me.
Anyway, I'm going to dispose of this painting!
That's crazy!
Hold it right there!
Show me that picture!
I will now announce the title of our next show.
It's called "The Princess and the Fool."
As you know, "fool" refers
to the court jesters of old.
They're what would now be called "clowns."
The princess, who has
shut her heart to the world,
is in love with a jester she saw as
a child, who exists in her memory.
The story is that the one who opens the
doors to her heart isn't one of her court jesters,
it's a prince who loves her
from the bottom of his heart
but can't even do a single juggling trick.
There will be three teams of jesters.
We'll divide up the cast later,
but the team leaders are
these three: Anna, Leon, and May.
I'm surprised Mr. Leon
accepted the role of a fool.
I wonder if he'll be able to get any laughs.
And in this show we'll have a special guest...
No, a team of special guests.
Um, Jonathan and I look
forward to working with you too.
A new performer arrives on the scene!
We've been waiting for you!
Jonathan is so cute!
Congratulations, Marion.
Good for you!
Yeah, thanks!
Everybody listen up!
This show was written with the
object of making Rosetta a lead,
but the director, Mia, wrote
it with a specific inspiration.
Mia.
Oh, yes.
I based it on this painting.
You can't tell on the computer screen,
but this painting has the
power to draw people in.
Everyone, please look at this painting
with your own eyes at least once.
The mood of the entire stage
is very important to this show.
The atmosphere of the era the
prince and the princess lived in,
and the feelings of the people...
I'd like you sense those
things from this painting,
and use that image to build your characters.
The success of this show
rests on each individual's preparation
and visualization of their character.
All right then! Mass
rehearsals start in three days.
Everybody keep in mind what
Mia just said, and get into character.
Dismissed!
Yes, sir!
All good to the right! All good to the left!
Nightly turning on of lights, complete!
Eh? What's this?
"Stage Training in Progress.
Do Not Disturb. Sora and Rosetta"?
Princess, please return my love!
You won't get my smile back for me.
You can't even juggle!
That's why today I've called
three fools here for you!
Here's the first one!
Now, make the princess smile.
Hi, I'm the first fool.
Actually, I'm standing in for the other two too.
Fool, come on! A little cooperation here!
I don't get the point of Fool playing a fool!
You can play the prince another time, okay?
You're lying! You always say "next time,"
but I never get to do it!
Jeez.
Oh, I've had enough!
We can just break off this practice here.
Why? Why?! You're trifling with me!
Already?
We don't actually have lines
in the real thing, after all.
Ah!
But Mia went to the trouble of writing lines
because she said they'd make
it easier to build the characters--
Rosetta.
Yes?
It's certainly true that it's better to build
a character physically than by saying lines.
Yes, Master Fool!
Okay, let's get started.
I'll teach you step by step.
Yes, Master Fool!
So, to begin with let's adjourn to the bath...
Wasn't that overdoing it?
No, actually I might not
have thrown him hard enough.
Anyway, Rosetta, about practice...
Is this really okay?
Rehearsals start in three days, you know.
Oh, don't worry, I'm fine.
Rosetta?
There's no need for me to study
this character and put it together.
Huh? Why not?
This story is about me.
Me from back when I was
called the Diabolo Machine.
So I know everything about this girl.
More importantly, Sora,
teach me the trampoline!
Okay, sure.
Really? I want to jump! Much, much higher!
My princess.
Wow, you're back alre--
Which would you like, the Legendary
Great Maneuver or the Angel's Maneuver?
Fool?
He's acting kind of strange.
And his mask is gone...
Fool?
What's wrong, Fool?
Is something the matter, Fool?
I will get back your smile no matter what.
My angel...
If I am, then you're a demon.
I would give even my life for your smile...
Fool. Fool? Fool!
Fool! You demon!
Oh, he's come around.
Fool, are you okay?
What on Earth was I...
You were kind of mumbling to yourself.
Yeah.
About "angels" and "demons"...
I'm...
Up I go!
Meow meow!
What do you think?
The animal costumes are good, huh?
Yeah!
All right, here we go!
Right!
Hey, hold it!
That's my move--
Stay away!
What's that supposed to be?
That's scary!
I-I-I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
This... really might be a tough role...
Actually, it's pretty funny.
Mia's a genius for
deciding to cast Leon as a fool!
No good. Do it again.
Um... From the beginning again?
You can just do the part where
the princess smiles at the prince.
Okay, we'll start there.
No good.
Give it a rest already!
I know this girl better than anyone!
Rosetta, calm down...
You're the one who's wrong, Mia!
I'm doing this character according to
my own understanding, just like you told--
Rosetta!
I think your performance is off too.
You said this princess was you from back
when you were called the Diabolo Machine,
but the smile you got back
from doing the Diabolo Battle
was really lively.
But your smile in performance
just now looked pained somehow.
Come on, let's do it again, Rosetta.
You sure you just don't want to do it?
May!
You're the lead, but you only get to
perform for a few minutes at the end.
For the rest of the time you're just
watching the clowns do their thing.
And what's more, in your big moment
to shine all you get to do is smile!
May...
If that's the way you're thinking about this,
quit your role right now!
May, Rosetta's doing her best...
You're Rosetta's partner, aren't you?
What good is it if you go easy on her?
Don't be careless,
go at her with all you've got!
I'm not being careless about my work,
and I don't think I'm going easy on her either.
Rosetta!
I think Rosetta gets
how important this role is...
She's feeling the pressure because she gets it.
She took on the lead role,
but it's different than she thought it would
be and she can't work up any confidence.
I bet she probably wants to run away.
Although you probably
wouldn't understand that.
Huh? No, I get that as
much as the next person--
The word "pressure" isn't in your dictionary!
Well, this isn't the kind of thing
that training will make any better...
I guess we've just got to wait.
I don't get it. What should I do?
So, which one of these three lovely
ladies is the one who's not wearing a bra?
Your prize is riding on this!
Fool! Fool, listen!
Uh-oh, what's wrong? I see sweat--
Hey, Fool, are you listening?
Fool!
Fool?
Hello, this is Layla Hamilton.
Oh, Sora!
It's been a while! Um, are you busy right now?
Cathy said she wanted to revise the script,
so we're not performing right now.
I heard Rosetta's the lead this time.
Makkoli is doing her best
to prepare for her debut too.
Miss, can I stop here for today?
Don't be ridiculous. You have
20 more to do today. Keep going.
Um, it seems like you're
in the middle of something.
Right.
It's no problem.
Did something happen?
Well...
Sora...
Um, do you think you'll
be able to come to the show?
Yes, I plan to.
Oh, good. Okay then, good luck!
You too.
Thanks.
Oh, it's no good,
I shouldn't lean on Miss Layla.
I have to do something myself.
Rosetta?
Sora...
Ken said he saw you come in here.
That...
Oh, you noticed too?
That jester looks exactly like Fool, huh.
And the princess looks like you too.
It sure makes you curious
about their relationship, huh?
It's snowing, so it must be winter.
I guess maybe he's trying
to entertain the princess?
Sora...
Hmm?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I'm sorry, I...
I'm sorry, Sora!
What's wrong, Rosetta?
I can't see Fool anymore!
What?
I was so happy.
When I heard I was chosen by the stage,
I thought, "Now I can be with Sora."
"And with Miss Layla too."
I thought, "I'm next."
But my dream is hopeless now...
Rosetta, calm down.
I wanted to do it!
It was my dream to do a
legendary great maneuver with you!
Let's go back to the dorm.
Hey, Rosetta! Rosetta!
♪ Oh, I want to give you ♪
♪ this home cooking filled with love! ♪
May's brought you a box dinner!
Um...
A special Chinese dinner
that can rid you of all your cares!
There you have it!
Huh? It's open.
Rosetta?
Are you here?
Could this mean...
Rosetta ran away?
This is bad! We have to ask the
police to search for her right away!
I'll have my dad get the car for us.
My theory is that she's gone to the airport.
After all, that's what she did last time!
What should I do? What should
I do? Oh, what should I do?!
Oh, please wait!
Excuse me!
Did we make it on time?
Have you seen this girl?
We think she got on a plane to Paris.
She's so cute; you must remember her!
Er, but the last plane to
Paris took off two hours ago.
That means she's not on it.
That's about when
I brought her back to the dorm.
Jonathan says to leave this to him.
Let's go.
W... Wai...
Taxi!
Sheesh. When am I finally
going to get to the airport?!
Not a single cab will stop
because they all think I'm a kid.
I'm tired.
And sleepy...
How filthy!
It's full of dust and cobwebs!
No way do I want to
camp out here for the night.
This is...
This is Fool's...
Fool...
Princess.
I'm going to try to master this
maneuver, for the sake of your smile.
My wish... is your smile.
Two people who, although they
wished for each other's smiles,
were never allowed to smile at each other...
Memories he'd sealed away
in order to hide his sadness...
And all kinds of feelings he's watched
play out as the Spirit of the Stage.
Sora's,
Miss Layla's,
May's...
Everyone's...
Me?
My feelings...
Why was I trying to run away?
Even if I can't see Fool
anymore, I still love the stage.
I wanted to perform on the
stage that gave me my smile
and give lots of other people smiles too.
Like Sora...
I'd started to forget that feeling.
Yep, she's here!
Rosetta!
Sora!
Thank goodness.
I'm sorry!
You made us worry.
I told you Jonathan had a good nose.
He's as good as a police dog.
So? You're coming back
to the stage, right Rosetta?
Of course!
Because I'm the only
one who can play that role.
Rosetta...
See, I almost forgot something important.
But I'm okay now.
I won't ever lose sight of it.
Right!
And I'm going to try to be a true star!
Rosetta...
Welcome home, Rosetta!
That's a good smile.
Fool...
You can see him!
Yep!
Rosetta Passel, who has
been chosen by the stage,
my name is Fool.
I am the Spirit of the Stage.
All the many wishes and feelings and
dreams that have been poured into the stage...
They must all be here in every age.
The time has come, huh?
Yep.
Rosetta, let's do this together.
A Kaleido Stage full of smiles,
made by true stars.
Sora.
What's the matter, Sora?
I think I spaced out for a second.
Come on, it's opening day! Get a grip, okay?
Sora, ten seconds to curtain.
Right!
Okay, let's go, Rosetta!
Gather around, o ye fools!
This is the Kaleido Stage.
Good fortune go to those
with wings in their hearts!