I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
Our ever-conflicting feelings
have vanished into the light.
I'm no longer sure if the path I'm stumbling
down is truly the right one or not.
I'm sure there are times when
people lose their way, but...
I believe the mistakes I made in the past are coming back to shape my future.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
April 26
Downtown Uminari City, within the barrier
Fate!
Nanoha!
Episode 7
A Third Mage!?
Are you all right? Return, Bardiche.
Yes, sir.
Fate!
Fate! Stop! It's too dangerous!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Fate!
Same day
Uminari City suburbs, Takamachi residence
Nanoha
Raising Heart is a Device that can
handle large amounts of mana,
and yet a single hit
damaged her this much...
Was it from Nanoha's and that girl's magic clashing?
No... even if it was, that still wouldn't
explain this much damage...
That really was... the Jewel Seed's...
Yuuno... is Raising Heart all right?
Yeah. The damage is pretty extensive,
but I'm sure she'll be fine.
Her automatic regeneration
system is working,
so she should be fine by tomorrow.
I see...
Are you all right, Nanoha?
Yeah... Raising Heart protected me.
I'm sorry... Raising Heart.
Same day, same time
Toumi City, residential area
I'm sorry, Fate! We're almost done...
I'm fine.
Thank you, Arf...
I have to report back to Mother tomorrow, so...
I'll have to get better soon, right?
If I went home looking like this,
I'm sure she'd be worried.
Would she really... be worried?
That woman...
Mother is just a little awkward, that's all...
I can tell how she really feels about me.
If it's just a report,
I can take care of it for you.
Mother... never really listens to
what you have to say, does she?
Even though you're such a kind, good girl...
W-Well...
I think tomorrow will go well!
Even though we just started searching for the Lost Logia,
the Jewel Seeds,
we've already found four!
I'm sure she'll praise you,
since you did a good job, right?
Yeah.
You're right.
April 27, Takamachi residence
Huh? Nanoha!
Ah, Miyuki.
You sure are up early today. What's up?
Well, I just kinda woke up.
I see.
Huh? Where's Kyouya?
Oh...
He went with Dad on a
long run this morning.
Um...
If it's okay with you...
can I watch you practice?
I don't think it'll be very interesting, but...
fine by me! I don't mind.
Okay.
Thanks!
Nanoha?
Yuuno?
What's wrong? You're up pretty early...
Ah... I just woke up early, that's all.
Oh, and Yuuno...
I've been doing a lot of thinking...
Hm?
I'm... really curious
about that girl... Fate...
Curious?
She's so strong...
and even though she seems so cold...
she has such beautiful, kind eyes...
And yet...
for some reason,
she looks... incredibly sad.
I really believe she has a reason for doing all this.
A reason for collecting the Jewel Seeds...
That's why... I want to talk with her.
So...
in order to do that...
Same day
Toumi City, residential area, condominium rooftop
This should be fine for a souvenir.
Sweets, huh?
Will this really make that woman happy?
I don't know, but it's the thought that
counts for this kind of thing, so...
Dimensional Transfer.
Dimensional Coordinates:
876C 4419 3312 D699 3583 A1460 779 F3125.
Open, Door of Invitation,
to the Garden of Time,
to the head of the Testarossa family!
Same day, same time
Dimensional Space
Time-Space Administrative Bureau
Interdimensional Patrol Ship   Arthra
What's our status, everyone?
Are we still on course?
Yes. At present, we're cruising at a steady level three nautical velocity.
We're calculated to arrive at the
target dimension in roughly 160 vecs.
There hasn't been
any overt activity,
not since they caused that small-scale dimensional distortion.
But the chance of those two
fighting again is very high.
Is that so?
Excuse me, Captain Lindy.
Thank you, Amy.
Time-Space Administrative Bureau Admiral
Captain of the   Arthra,Lindy Harlaown
Indeed.
Even on the small-scale, dimensional distortions can be... quite problematic.
If it gets too dangerous,
we'll just have to head straight
to the scene of the distortion.
Right, Chrono?
Time-Space Administrative
Bureau Enforcer
Chrono Harlaown
It'll be fine.
I understand, Captain.
That's why I'm here.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
High-order Dimensional Space
..Garden of Time
A mere four?
This is terribly disappointing.
Yes...
I'm sorry...
Mother.
Do you understand, Fate?
You are my daughter. The great mage Presea Testarossa's only daughter.
Nothing is impossible for you.
No matter what it may be.
Yes. You must accomplish everything, no matter what.
Yes...
You've made me wait all this time...
for such pitiful results...
There's no way I could have
welcomed you home with a smile.
I hope you understand, Fate.
Yes... I understand.
That's why... that's why...
I want you to remember.
Never disappoint me again like you've done today.
What the hell...
What the hell is wrong with her!?
This is just too cruel! That woman...
That woman... that woman
claims to be Fate's mother...
This isn't the first time she's been cruel to Fate, but...
It's just too much this time!
What the hell is wrong with her!?
Are the Lost Logia... are the Jewel Seeds worth all that?!
Those Lost Logia are essential
to fulfilling my dreams.
Yes, Mother...
They're key to everything...
The purity of the Jewel Seeds
are far beyond anything else.
You're a kind girl, so you might
hesitate to collect them, but...
if anything gets in your way, destroy it.
By any means necessary.
The power to do so lies within you.
Now go, and bring them to me.
My daughter. My dear Fate.
Yes... I'll be going then, Mother.
I'm going to rest for a bit.
Next time, be sure to bring me something worthwhile.
Yes...
Fate!
Fate, I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Why are you apologizing, Arf?
I'm fine... perfectly fine...
But...! If I had known something
like this would happen...
Even after you got what she wanted,
I never thought she'd do something this cruel to you!
If I had known, I would've stopped you, no matter what!
It wasn't cruel...
Mother... was thinking of me when she did this.
Thinking of you? Don't give me that!
What she did to you was just cruel!
No... after all, we're mother and daughter...
I'm sure the Jewel Seeds are
really important to Mother...
For a long time,
Mother's been so full of sadness...
so I want to do something that might cheer her up...
But... even so...
Arf, please. I'm perfectly fine.
I'm sure that...
once I return with all the Jewel Seeds,
even Mother will smile again...
She'll go back to being the
kind mother she used to be...
And I'm sure she'll even be kind to you, Arf...
So, let's go...
This time, I definitely...
won't make any mistakes.
April 27
Seishou Private Elementary School
Third Grade, Class 1
April 27
Downtown Uminari City
Bardiche, how are you feeling?
Recovery complete.
I see.
You really gave it your all.
Good job.
I can feel it... even I can tell that it's around here.
Yes. It'll be activated soon, it's close by.
April 27
Uminari City suburbs
Raising Heart... you're
all better, aren't you?
Thank goodness.
Condition green.
Will you give me your best again?
All right, my master.
Thank you.
April 27
Uminari City, Uminari Seaside Park
Emergency Barrier!
Expand!
Wow! Pretty arrogant of them
to put up a barrier already.
This one's stronger than the others.
And...
that girl's here, too.
Yuuno, run!
Flier Fin.
Fly, Raising Heart!
We have to go higher!
All right.
Arc Saber.
Let's go, Bardiche.
Shooting Mode.
Let's go, Raising Heart!
Blast through it!
Divine...
...Buster.
Pierce through, lightning!
Thunder Smasher.
Sealing Mode, Set up.
Sealing Form, Set up.
Jewel Seed Serial VII!
Seal!
It looks like we can't put any more
stress on the Jewel Seed.
Yeah. If it turns out like the one last night...
I'd feel sorry for my Raising Heart and your Bardiche.
But...
I can't give up.
Device Form.
I just want to talk with you...
Device Mode.
If I win...
and you see I'm not just an
innocent girl here by accident,
will you tell me your story?
Stop!
Engaging in combat here is too dangerous!
I'm an Enforcer from the
Time-Space Administrative Bureau,
Chrono Harlaown.
I'll need a detailed explanation from both of you.
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
After listening to the third mage, Chrono,
the true identity of the Jewel
Seeds has finally become clear,
and things have
gotten really serious!
I also learned
something unbelievable!
Yuuno is... Yuuno is...!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 8
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Episode Eight:
Lyrical Magical, doing my best!