Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
H-huh, ah!
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
I got a new cell phone!
Don't put it in the washing machine this time.
I'll put it somewhere I won't forget.
Hey Tsukasa, help me out.
Okay.
Desire
Ba.
L.
Sa.
Mi.
Annoyed
C.
Ah, there...
Vinega-
Daah!
I'll put it in for you, so give me that!
You're taking too long!
It's okay, I'm fine.
I'll do it myself.
I came over to play!
Ah welcome, Nee-san.
What are you playing?
A gal-game that came out recently.
Hm...
Well then, I'll just borrow some of your manga.
Okay.
Well, it's an adult game,
but either she didn't notice, or she's going to pretend to not see...
Which is it going to be?
Since it's Traffic Safety week we're cracking down.
I see.
Like doing thorough checks...
...or explaining all of the traffic rules.
It's pretty rough!
And sometimes people snap at me, too!
Looking at your daily life, Nee-san,
So scary, so scary...
it's not convincing at all when you talk about rules and safety!
I'm surprised!
Shiki Nashima Clinic
I heard that this year's cold is especially persistent...
I better get it taken care of soon.
Judging from my number, it's probably going to take a while.
I'll read a book while I'm waiting.
Ando-san.
Ando Shigeo-san?
Takara-san?
Takara Miyuki-san?
Takara Miyuki-san, are you here?
Well then, next...
Nishiyama Mariko-san?
Did they call me?
What's the time?
I need to pay more attention to my surroundings.
We are almost at the final terminal, Kamata.
Where is this?
So I was teaching Tsukasa how to send text messages the other day.
She's been playing with her cell phone so much, yet she still doesn't know how to text.
Maybe it's because she's so excited,
but she sends a text whenever anything happens.
It must be hard to be on the receiving end of that every day.
Well, I don't think you need to worry too much.
Sender: Tsukasa
She's the type that's all gung-ho in the beginning,
but loses interest as time goes on.
Yep, there are people who never grow out of that.
Ah, I got another one.
It's not that they get tired of it, but rather they just can't last that long.
Here.
"Want me to buy some soy milk on the way home?"
What's all the stuff after it?
I get the feeling she's having fun...
...but I can barely recognize half of them.
Oh, she's finally getting used to it.
Yeah. But I prefer the one
with
with an afro
Yeah. But I prefer the one
Really? But they probably aren't
actually
performing
Really? But they probably aren't
actually performing
Yeah,
might be
Yeah, might be
I see
Heh
You know...
I understand how you feel,
but how about we stop sending tons of texts to family members?
Do you guys have a moment?
What?
I'm not really sure how to send a text message on my phone.
Oh my~!
It's so easy, Dad.
My, you're so helpless!
I'll teach you, then.
Oh?
So you're the master now, aren't you?
Um...
I can't say much for that stench.
Yep, it smelled so bad.
Really.
You have a lot of entries.
Hey, don't look at that!
Is there something you don't want me to see?
Not really.
Just because.
It's a guy.
It has to be a guy.
I'm telling you that it's not!
She's not picking up...
I guess I'll call her house.
Hello, Kagami?
Oh, Konata?
Why didn't you pick up your cell phone?
Well, it stopped ringing, so I didn't notice.
Geez, what's the point if you don't notice it?
I don't even know where it is to begin with.
There really is no point in you having a cell phone, is there?
So about this weekend...
One sec, my dad's calling me.
Hey, hurry it up!
Hold on...
You spend too much time on the phone!
Ah, I'm sorry...
My dad got mad at me because I'm talking too much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
But I never thought your house would be so strict on that sort of thing.
I guess I was wrong.
Well, we were in the middle of a fighting game.
E-Eh!?
Tell me that in the first place!
Anytime, anywhere,
point cards possess mysterious powers.
When you finally realize it,
you've bought stuff you weren't planning to buy in the first place.
You really don't plan anything at all, do you?
I can kind of understand, though.
She's here...
In this town, there is an Animate and a Gamers...
Though she knows there are two anime shops in this town...
She is a person that will go to both and buy the same thing...
The Legendary Girl, A!
Time for the Legendary Girl A shift!
Welcome!
We just got the new Haruhi DVD Vol. 5 in stock!
Limited edition...
Normal edition...
All ready, desu!
And plenty more related miscellaneous goods!
That's right, as long as she notices as many new products as possible!
She will buy them all!
Ah.
I wanted to get the Aquarium Age special bookmark today.
I better go to Gamers.
It didn't work!
You're going to spend the night on Saturday and Sunday,
that way we could play all night.
Yep.
When we play, we always play at our house,
It's not that you can't,
but my dad's at home a lot because of his work.
Oh, is that so?
Yep, so I can't be responsible for what happens.
About what?
I wonder what Konata's house is like.
Yo!
Oh, welcome.
Pardon the intrusion.
Thank you for having us today.
Welcome.
I've heard all about you two.
Your house is a shrine and you two are shrine maidens, right?
What exactly did you tell him?
Do you guys normally wear yellow hakama?
And why is that the first thing he has to say?
Here you go.
Ah!
It's Kona-chan's room!
It's an amazing room, just as I'd expected.
Ah, cute~
This door...
This must be the "forbidden door" where all of your secrets,
that cannot be exposed, lie.
One that must never be opened.
Nah, I share that with my dad, so they're all in his archives.
Oh, you share it?
Speaking of which, your dad's an author, right?
Yep.
Then, do you get stuck on the novels or gal-games that your dad makes?
He doesn't write that kind of stuff.
Is that so?
Yep.
That's surprising.
He likes that kind of world, yet he's never thought about writing one?
I guess you could call it a bystanding...
Since he plays gal-games and simulation games whenever he's free,
he doesn't feel the need to make them in his work, too.
I see...
You've been surprising me so much that I don't even know how react!
As expected from the Izumi house!
The other day, my dad followed me around everywhere.
Yeah?
So I tried saying, "Dad, take a hike!"
Eh?
Isn't that a little too much?
Then he got mad at me,
"You could at least say, 'I hate you daddy!'"
Is what he said.
No, I'm not too sure about that correction either.
I think my dad's mindset and what you're thinking are slightly out of sync.
No, I just have no idea.
Wanna take a break?
It's here!
I think we see a lot more l33t-speak on TV, nowadays.
Maybe.
Not that I would know.
Speaking of which,
you're pretty deep into this stuff, yet you don't talk like that at all.
Normally, no.
When I chat it looks like this.
Amazing...
Is this even Japanese?
If you can read it, I'll consider it my defeat.
Do you need any help?
Oh, can you season the salad then?
Okay!
Let's eat!
It's delicious.
Yep, it's really good.
If you always do household chores, this is nothing.
You might get a little better, too, Kagami, if you actually did chores.
Mind your business.
Look, Konata...
It's perfect!
It's the image I've seen in my dreams!
One guy and three high school girls having dinner together...
It's Heaven on Earth...
Sakura!
...is a pretty common situation in gal-games,
Your sister is Tohsaka!
though completely unnatural.
Ah, is that so?
It sure gets cold at this time.
I should've worn a jacket.
Ah, a shooting star!
I couldn't say my wish three times.
When they come so suddenly, it's difficult.
But I'm going to succeed one day and have my wish come true.
Tsukasa, you sure like to dream.
But realistically, that's totally impossible.
I can only think the legend became true because no one has succeeded yet.
Do you ever dream at all?
Do you want to drink some too, Kagami?
Oh!
Thanks.
You switched hair styles.
Yeah, for fun.
Since you let us use the bath first.
They're the same parts,
but depending on who uses them, the image changes so much.
It's an album.
Can I look at it?
Ah, sure.
Ah!
Kona-chan's so cute.
You haven't changed much since you were little, have you?
And you seem really close with your dad.
Hm?
Oh, that's my mom.
No way!
So young!
Don't we look alike?
She better not be jail-bait!
I look at my dad and always wonder,
Eh?
"What exactly did my mom like about him?"
But you look so similar to your mom.
So what kind of guys do you like?
Me?
Hmm... when you put it that way, I can't think of anything.
Really?
Just spit it out.
Ah!
Maybe Mom could have been with anyone.
They said something about how they were childhood friends.
I-I don't think that's...
And after searching around, she ended up with Dad.
You're pretty brutal, even to your parents.
After looking at Mom, I wondered...
Hm?
There are a lot of characters in manga or games who seem mature for their age...
...or adults who seem very young.
What is this?
Do you want us to respond to that?
It would have been nice if Yuki-chan could have come, too.
Well, she said she was busy...
Oh yeah!
I'll send Yuki-chan a mail so she's not too lonely.
Miyuki may pay too much attention to it, so I wouldn't.
Ah, she replied.
"I'm glad to hear you guys are having fun."
"Right now, I'm working hard to take care of my homework."
"Please invite me next time-"
I forgot I had homework!
Kagami, do something!
My class didn't have any.
Can I go to sleep?
Wait!
Ah!
That shooting star earlier.
Hm?
If you make your wish shorter, it might be possible.
I wonder.
What are you doing?
Research on how to make your wish shorter for shooting stars.
Stop procrastinating and get it over with.
Hey, Yuki-chan...
I really didn't understand this part of the lecture.
Eh?
Oh, here?
Konata is Kona-chan.
Miyuki is Yuki-chan.
So what kind of nickname would you give Kagami?
Kaga-chan?
Gami-chan?
TL Note: Kagami means mirror.
【Kagami】
Probably Kyou-chan.
Take the other reading of "kagami" and call her Kyou.
Whoa, that totally makes sense!
【   Kyo   】
TL Note: Kyo also means mirror, strong and evil.
It really brings out her boldness and strength.
And you can turn it into this "kyou", too.
T-That's not what I had in mind,
but we'd better not mention this to Onee-chan...
If you had to give yourself a nickname, what would it be?
Tsuka-chan or Kasa-chan?
Hmm...
Hi-chan.
Since it's hard to use my first name.
I see.
I do have an image of Tsukasa going "hihi" all the time.
That wasn't my intention either.
All right!
Starting today, I'm going to call you Hi-chan!
Eh?
"Eh"?
What, why not?
But doesn't it feel a little awkward...
...when you decide your own?
How about that?
"That"?
Anything would do.
Do you want revenge, Sebastian?
It's Shiraishi.
Hey, Kyo-chan!
Kyo-chan!
C-Could she be calling me?
That's confusing, so stop it.
Then how should I call you?
Can't you just call me Kagami?
What's wrong with having a nickname like Kona-chan or Yuki-chan?
Hmm...
Then, Kagami-sama.
Hey, Kagami-sama!
Whoa, she actually did it!
What?
I was just trying it out.
Sorry for the wait, Kagami-sama.
What's the matter, Kagami-sama?
Okay, I'm sorry,
so please just use my name normally...
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
Believe it or not, Lucky Channel is now entering the 10th episode!
I'm the navigator, Kogami Akira.
Thank you.
I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Let's get down to business.
This week is character introduction #4!
Hiiragi Kagami edition.
In the series, she is the well-known "brunt end of jokes" character.
But isn't she simply the tsundere?
The setting is so easy to see and is so uncreative.
For your information...
Huh?
I believe it is rather crude to label Kagami-san as a tsundere.
Then what is she?
In other words,
do we truly understand the respective qualities of a tsundere?
Unfortunately, the word tsundere...
...has been so degraded that its definition has been muddled.
First of all, the word tsundere was first introduced in 2002...
This was the internet term,
but its original definition was,
"Someone who is tsuntsun at first, then later becomes deredere."
Yes!
In other words, it signifies the change in personalities over time!
Do you understand what you're saying?
But nowadays,
it's become the nom de jour to describe a character's bipolar tendencies.
Thus, someone who is outwardly tsuntsun,
yet deep down deredere,
is how it is generally understood to be today.
Therefore, I hereby declare!
That this is an obvious mistake!
We must now restore the original meaning of the word tsundere!
By bringing everyone's attention to the true meaning,
we can prevent the deterioration of modern language!
Stand up, people!
Not bad, Sebastian.
Who?
If Kagami isn't a tsundere, then what is she?
Are you talking to me?
I'm not too sure about this complicated stuff,
but if you say so.
Then, if she isn't a tsundere,
is there some other word that we can use to describe her?
U-Uh...
I don't think there is but...
Cool-dere or...
No, that's not it.
Dere-tsun?
You make no sense at all.
What's wrong with tsundere?
Well, that's...
That's not it!
Oh, right!
Let's have our viewers help us think of a new expression to replace "tsundere"!
Good idea!
Delegating it, huh?
Therefore, everyone watching TV right now,
yes, you, too!
Please help us think of a good word to describe characters like Kagami-san.
Let's rewrite the book of "common knowledge".
The Complete Tsundere Register.
Please listen to us on the radio or visit our homepage for more details.
We'll be waiting for your passionate responses!
Let's wrap it up.
Oh well.
Lots and lots, and lots, and lots...
Bye-bii.
Bye-bii!
Send us stuff!
Wow, I sure talked a lot today.
I think that was my best one yet!
Huh?
Akira-sama?
W-What's the matter?
Satisfied?
Y-Yes, well, I've never spoken this much,
so I think I did a pretty good job.
You know, I'm having dinner with your studio's manager and producer in a bit...
Eh?
Eh...?
Uh...
To discuss some matters that might concern you.
W-What's that?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, if the person just can't take the hints...
W-Wait...
Well, I mean, aren't you still working part-time at CoCo*chi?
That's just during the day, so I don't exactly make too much...
And at the barbecue restaurant?
I-I still work at the yakiniku-ya, too,
but what difference does it make?
That's getting a little too private, so please stop!
Next is my turn.
Tsukasa, how's this?
Ah, this is good!
Right, Yuki-chan?
I know this one.
Then, why don't you sing this?
Thank you, Kona-chan.
Thank you.
No problem.
Did you guys decide?
Yep.
Lonely kujikesou na sugata mado ni utsushite
Lonely　くじけそうな姿　窓に映して
Lonely, the window
reflects your broken body.
This song was really popular when we
were in kindergarten, right?
I'm not too sure.
Atemonaku aruita hito shirezu tame iki tsuku
あてもなく歩いた　人知れずため息つく
Walking aimlessly,
I heave an unseen sigh.
I don't know either.
I remember!
My sisters used to sing it a lot.
Songs from an earlier generation
that your older relatives know,
I'm proud kowaresou de kuzureso na jounetsu wo
I'm　proud 壊れそうで崩れそな情熱を
I'm Proud of this broken,
evanescent passion.
tend to be absorbed more naturally.
Tsunagitomeru nani ka itsumo sagashi tsudzuketeta
つなぎとめる何か　いつも捜し続けてた
I've always searched for something that will stop this.
Doushite anna ni yume ga sunao ni mirenaku natteta?
どうしてあんなに夢が素直に見れなくなってた？
Why can I no longer have those pure dreams I once did?
Machijuu de iru basho nante doko ni mo nai
街中で居る場所なんてどこにもない
There is no place for me in this city.
Karadajuu kara ai ga koboreteita
体中から愛がこぼれていた
Love overflowing throughout my body.
Oh, your voice cracked...
What am I supposed to do?
It's too high.
Hitogomi wo...
人混みを。。。
The crowd of people...
Preview
And next week on Lucky Star:
Kagami here.
There's nothing wrong with ordering soup when you're going out to have fun.
But it's pretty depressing when the soup splashes and a little gets on your shirt.
Curry roux is the worst with this!
And then if you're wearing one of your favorite shirts,
it could ruin your whole day.
Also, when you buy a boxed lunch that contains sauce at a convenience store,
you try to keep it as level as you so you don't spill it.
But when you get home and look inside the bag,
you see the soup all over the place,
and then you lose your appetite.
And, it's nice when they put warm and cold foods in separate bags for you,
but when they put cold drinks in a bag with your magazine,
the magazine absorbs all of the condensed water and gets soggy.
Making you wonder, "What was the point!?"
Next week: "The various ways to spend Christmas Eve"
「 The Various Ways to
Spend Christmas Eve 」
Look forward to it!