Your inhuman side is about to be unleashed.
Apparently the humans are dabbling in forbidden research that could destroy the world.
If I recall,
it was called something like the Seraph of the End.
Stop, Yuu-chan!
It's begun.
Y-Yuu-san! Please!
Come back to your senses!
Yuu-san!
Lieutenant Colonel Guren, what did you do to him?
How are we feeble humans supposed to survive in this ruined world?
Before your sister Mahiru
developed the demon weapons,
countless sacrifices were made.
As usual, humanity's greed
is impossible to keep in check,
and we vampires continue
to look down on the entire world
Battle for Nagoya
Wouldn't you agree?
The Human World
Shii-chan!
Lend me your power, Mahiru.
What's stopping you?
Feel free to finish the job.
What about you, Lieutenant Colonel?
Why did you let me get this close?
Because you have every right to kill me.
And that would atone for what you did to my sister?
She fell in love with you, even knowing it could never be.
Eventually, her greed consumed her,
and she turned into a demon.
And then...
Yeah.
And then I killed her.
But she lives on inside your sword, doesn't she?
You're obsessed with her, Lieutenant Colonel.
She developed the demon weapons, and betrayed the Hiiragi family.
Is she the one
telling you to manipulate Yuu-san?
What are you trying to achieve, Lieutenant Colonel?
Unless all this is supposed to be for Yuu-san's benefit,
I really wish you'd stop.
What, did you fall for the guy?
You're right, she is in this blade.
But I'm the one in control.
I'm not being possessed.
And what if I said...
I don't believe you?
I don't care.
Believe what you want.
Basic Interpretation
of Spellcraft
Lurking in here again,
Yuu-san?
You startled me!
Shouldn't you still be resting?
I spend too much time in bed.
I'm fine.
I'll believe that when the doctor says it.
Besides...
What?
No, never mind.
Understanding Biology of Vampires
and its Evolution Through Spellcraft
So you're looking at porn mags again, huh?
Understanding Biology of Vampires
and its Evolution Through Spellcraft
You boys are all the same.
Hey, give that back!
Give it back!
Let's see here...
Sheesh.
Turning Humans Into Vampires
Yuu-san.
Do you want to turn Mika-san back into a human?
I can tell you what I know, if you want.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes, please.
You're so cute when you're honest about what you want.
Shut it!
Just tell me already!
First of all,
it's very rare for people to be turned into vampires.
Because they don't like letting humans join them.
Furthermore, only nobles
have the authority to turn humans.
So Mika was converted by a noble?
Do you know who did it?
Yeah, I think so.
So, are you still planning to exterminate the vampires?
Nah.
As long as Mika's alive,
that's good enough for now.
So then, do you know how to change
a vampire back into a human, Shinoa?
I see.
That's too bad.
You're acting pretty mature, for once.
Has your reason to live changed, perhaps?
Special Private Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
Please proceed to the main office.
Does Guren want something?
No.
It's most likely a summons from the Hiiragi family.
The Hiiragi family...
They're the ones leading
the army to take back Japan, right?
You should probably get going.
Wait, now that I think about it...
isn't your last name Hiiragi?
Oh my! So you finally noticed?
That's correct!
I'm practically a celebrity!
Come, bask in my glory!
Jokes aside though,
the Hiiragi family are all pretty scary people.
Be careful.
Hey there, stupid Yuu!
Off to wag your tail at our great
and glorious leaders, are you?
Why'd you put it like that?
Have you forgotten, Yuu?
Long ago, an old man freed a crane from a trap.
As thanks, the crane wove a beautiful cloth for him, from its own wings.
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who saved you.
I'm also the one who taught you
how to live, and use a sword.
Where is all this coming from?
Why are you shoving all this favor stuff in my face?
If you even remotely feel like you owe me,
pay it back today.
But I don't even know what you're—
You belong to me.
So don't go bowing to the Hiiragis.
I see.
That's what this is about.
Yeah, that's what it's about.
Whatever.
I don't care about petty political squabbles—
Shut up, brat.
Even if you don't care, those squabbles are what make the world turn—
You don't need to worry about that.
Whatever happens,
I'm never abandoning or betraying my friends.
Oh?
Well you're wrong about one thing.
I'm not your friend.
Then what are you?
Your boss.
Your savior.
Your surrogate father.
Basically, I'm your god.
I don't think so.
Oh.
Did they call you, too?
How'd it go?
It was just a debriefing.
Apparently I'm being promoted, in recognition of my service in repelling the vampire threat.
A promotion, huh.
Naturally, that's just how useful I am.
That so?
Hey! Shouldn't you have some sort of comeback?
I mean, you know what really happened.
I didn't do anything at all during that battle.
Even after making all those bold claims.
I'm...
I'm weak.
And yet I'm probably the only one that's getting promoted.
Just because I'm a Sanguu.
Go ahead and laugh if you...
Laugh if you...
Mitsuba, I'm not laughing at you.
Actually, I didn't even know there was one,
much less two girls from noble families in our squad.
I mean, I only just realized today
that Shinoa's a Hiiragi.
Are you...
an idiot?
Oh, shut up.
But who cares? Take your promotion.
Keep getting promotions,
then help me out once you reach the top.
With your family?
Yeah.
They asked about that.
They think you might be a spy,
and told me to keep an eye on you.
Really?
So, what do you think?
I told them that's impossible,
because as far as I'm concerned
you're too dumb to fool anyone.
Sounds like something you'd say.
Still,
thanks for believing in me.
Yuu,
the Hiiragis are a scary bunch.
Watch your back.
Sure.
Thanks.
Something on your mind?
That was a pretty deep sigh.
Shinoa?
What are you doing here?
Nothing, really.
Just taking a little stroll.
Did they call for you, Micchan?
They promoted me to second lieutenant of the squad.
Oh, I guess that's a Sanguu for you!
You don't even have to do anything to get promoted!
Very impressive!
Did I strike a nerve?
Not really.
What about you?
Did you also get—
Nope.
And even if I did, I'd just turn it down.
You're just like everyone in the main family, doing whatever you want.
Oh, not at all.
I'm hardly even part of the family anymore.
So, how much did you tell them
to get your promotion?
What do you mean?
About what happened on the battlefield.
About Yuu-san's rampage.
I told them I don't know anything about it.
It sounds like they didn't know about it either.
Which means it's not something the army was researching, at least officially.
Do you know what that was?
I wonder.
You can never tell who your friends and enemies are in this world.
What?
Why is there a vampire here?
What's going on here?
That was a test, to see if you're a traitor or not.
Now then, let's begin the debriefing.
Who are you?
Hiiragi Kureto.
Lieutenant General of the Japanese Demon Army.
First of all, Hyakuya Yuuichirou,
show me how you handle a sword.
You may not activate your curse.
Fine by me.
Just don't start complaining if you embarrass yourself.
Yuu-chan,
you shouldn't believe
everything Kureto-niisan says.
Too late.
Possess me, Raimeiki.
You only see what's in front of you.
I see. So that's all you can do.
That's unfair.
Are you going to die on the battlefield complaining about fairness?
But that's fine.
You listened, and didn't doubt me for a second.
There's no way you're one
of that pesky Guren's subordinates—
This guy...
You'd be dead right now if not for your friend here.
Or would it be unfair to attack from behind?
I withdraw my previous assessment.
You're definitely one of Guren's underlings.
What?
Are we done already?
Shinya.
Really? I'd rather not.
Unlike you, Kureto-niisan, I don't like bullying the weak.
You were adopted into our family.
You have no right to speak back to me.
What a bother.
Cut the crap! Who are you calling weak?
You, of course.
Want to try me out then?
Well, that's what I was ordered to do.
Let's get it over with.
Byakkomaru, fire.
Bang.
My win.
By the way, Byakkomaru is most effective at distance,
so at close range I'd have no chance against Kureto-niisan or Guren.
Do you understand what that means?
But for what it's worth,
it doesn't seem like you've been taught how to use your demon weapon properly.
So don't feel too bad.
That clears up any suspicion about me, does it not?
It should be obvious now that he doesn't know anything about me.
What are you talking about?
Truth is, they're suspicious of me as well,
since I happen to be on good terms with Guren.
The Hiiragis aren't fond of the notion that there might be vampire spies running around here.
I don't give a damn about that.
In any case, there's no way I could be—
Let's go, bring him.
What are you doing?
Kimizuki!
Yoichi!
What the hell did you do?
We tortured them a little,
since you were acting suspiciously.
That's ridiculous!
Now, let's begin the interrogation.
Tell us nothing but the truth.
Disobey, and we'll kill your friends.
There isn't much information on you.
You received your demon weapon very quickly, so you must possess some talent.
Though I suppose that goes for them as well.
Normally, a thorough background check is conducted on anyone taking the demon weapon aptitude test.
This was not the case for you three.
Why is that?
Where did you come from?
What is your mission?
Mission?
We don't—
Do it.
Stop.
Tell me the truth.
Wait!
It's true!
Do it.
Please stop!
I'll tell you anything!
Of course you will.
Then let's continue.
You were raised in the vampire city.
But you managed to get out.
Your entire family was murdered by vampires during the escape,
causing you to carry a grudge against them.
This much is in the report.
Is it true?
Yeah, so there's no way I could be a spy—
Just answer the question, nothing more.
After escaping, Ichinose Guren took you in.
But why?
Why did Guren save you?
What are you to Guren?
That's...
Why is your last name Hyakuya?
Are you a survivor of the Hyakuya sect?
What?
Well, that was...
That was the name of our orphanage.
They were once the most influential group of spellcasters in Japan.
Back then, their orphanages collected orphaned children from all over,
and performed human experiments on them.
You were most likely also one of their guinea pigs.
What?
Do you see now?
Guren knows about this and
is using you for his own purposes.
Now,
join me, Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
I will guide you.
Let Yoichi and Kimizuki go.
That's enough.
I don't know what's going on between you and Guren,
but I do know that Guren
wouldn't resort to something like this.
Which is why he'll never catch up to me.
You can go back now.
Trust me, I get where you're coming from.
This is a pretty awful place, don't you think?
Are you that worried about Yuu-san?
I—
Of course not.
Why would I be worried about that idiot?
Oh, Yuu-san!
Yuu!
And Kimizuki? Yoichi, too?
What's wrong, you guys?
What happened?
It's nothing.
That Hiiragi whatever—
Guren!
You've got some explaining to do!
I heard from that guy Hiiragi Kureto!
Me and my family,
Mika and the others,
we were all subjected to human experiments!
Did you really only save me so you could use me?
That's right.
I don't have time to rescue people
who won't be useful to me.
So? Does that piss you off, kid?
No.
If you hadn't been there, I'd be dead.
Being able to help is all I care about.
If you need me,
then maybe you need Mika too, right?
I don't care about being a guinea pig,
if you'll just say that you want him as well.
So please, tell me how I can get him back!
Yuu-kun...
I already told you.
Everyone here is your
family now, including me.
We'll all work to get the rest of your family back.
Then...
if we're all supposed to be comrades,
teach me how to use my demon weapon already!
Well sure, that's the plan.
Damn it.
Why don't you give in and take a sip?
I really love the way you look right now.
Which is why this is the best time to—
Um...
Um, I heard we can get special favors
if we let you drink our blood, Ferid-sama.
Who told you that?
Mika-chan?
Say, Mika-chan,
how about you drink this boy's blood?
You know it's illegal to drink blood directly.
What a stick in the mud.
Could it be that you're afraid
Yuu-chan will hate you if you drink—
Just tell me what you want.
Oh, right.
I was thinking you could attend tomorrow's high noble assembly.
The high noble assembly?
Why me?
Because I think it'll be
more interesting that way, Mika-kun.
Let's go.
It hurts...
Yuu-chan...
Next time on Owari no Seraph:
Tangled Bonds
Tangled Bonds.