Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
Killed?!
Impossible...
Why would they kill the priest?
We can't allow this...
We can't allow this!
It must be difficult for you to lose the priest like this.
Yes.
Father Risei was like a second father to me.
It's been one unexpected thing after another.
It might prove necessary to
formulate some sort of plan right away.
Why didn't you tell Tokiomi?
What do you mean?
I pity your father.
He died, believing his son to be a holy man.
No...
Might that have been his salvation?
Does your father's death inspire no feeling within you?
He was killed, you know.
Shouldn't you at least look a little sad?
Yes, it bothers me to no end.
Does it really?
Is it because you didn't get to kill him yourself?
Saber...
Irisviel, how are you feeling?
Looks like I made you worry.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
As long as you really are all right,
I could ask for nothing more.
But...
It's okay.
This presence is Maiya-san.
From Tohsaka?
Yes.
Tohsaka Tokiomi requests an alliance.
An alliance? Now?
Tohsaka must be uneasy at the thought of dealing with Rider and Berserker.
We appear to be the team most inclined to form an alliance, so he invited us to meet.
In other words, he thinks us to be
the weakest compared to the others.
Tohsaka said he wishes to meet tonight, at the Fuyuki City church.
Tohsaka Tokiomi has been making elaborate
preparations for this Grail War from the very early stages.
It's also likely that he's controlling Assassin's Master, Kotomine Kirei, from the shadows.
If Tohsaka does exert some influence over
Kotomine Kirei, then we cannot ignore his offer.
Indeed.
Kotomine Kirei...
Remember his name, Saber.
If there is anyone who can defeat
Kiritsugu and win the Holy Grail War,
it is Kotomine Kirei.
We'll accept his invitation.
Father?
Father!
Rin, your father would like to speak with you.
Rin.
As you grow up, keep the Association in your debt.
Beyond that, I'll leave the rest to your judgment.
You'll be fine on your own.
One day, the Holy Grail will appear.
It is the responsibility of the Tohsaka family to obtain it.
Above all...
If you wish to be a Mage, that is the path you must follow.
Rin, take this.
Well, I'll be going now.
You know what to do from now on, right?
Yes.
Goodbye, Father.
First, please allow me to thank you for coming at my behest.
Let me introduce you.
This is Kotomine Kirei, my student.
While we were once competitors for
the Grail, all of that is now in the past.
He has lost his Servant and yielded his rights as a Master.
The Grail War is now heading toward its conclusion.
The remaining teams are, as anticipated, the Masters of the Founding Three Families, along with one outsider.
Now, how would you appraise the current situation?
Nothing I need to worry about.
Since we control Saber, the strongest Servant,
we don't need to wait for an opportune time to strike.
We will simply keep winning each battle.
I see.
In my opinion, it is unfortunate that the Matous erred in their strategy.
They have imposed a draining Servant upon a weak Master, hastening his own destruction.
Rider is likely to emerge victorious.
The Grail must not be allowed to fall into outside hands.
The two of us should be able to agree on that much.
Any alliance is out of the question.
However, if you wish to discuss the order in which we deal with our enemies,
we may be able to come to some agreement.
Elaborate.
We can settle things with the Tohsaka
camp after we defeat the other Masters.
That's a proposal our side can agree to.
So a temporary, conditional ceasefire?
A fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
First, you will share any information you have concerning Rider and his Master.
Very well.
Second, you will remove
Kotomine Kirei from the Grail War.
Remove Kirei?
I won't ask you to kill him.
But until this war is over, I insist that he leave Fuyuki—no, Japan entirely.
Before tomorrow morning.
Could you explain why you'd want that?
There is plenty of bad blood between
the Einzbern camp and the Executor.
If the Tohsaka camp continues to accept him,
we will find ourselves unable to
trust you under any circumstances.
What's the meaning of this?
Kirei.
Well?
How do you like Kiritsugu's present?
It's closer to a horse than a car.
It seems to suit me better.
I shall ride ahead and ensure that the route is safe.
Let us go as well.
M-Madam?
What's wrong?
Go ahead, Maiya-san.
But...
Tohsaka will realize something is amiss.
This isn't unexpected...
It was inevitable.
In fact, it's a miracle that I've been able to function as a human for this long.
Does Kiritsugu know about this?
Keep this from Saber.
She has a crucial battle ahead of her.
I don't want her to worry about me.
But Maiya-san, there's something I want you to know.
I am a homunculus created for the Grail War.
You know that, right?
Yes.
Old Acht gave the vessel an instinct for self-preservation,
so that it would avoid all danger and
safeguard the Grail to its completion.
He disguised the vessel under the veil of "Irisviel".
That's what I am.
But that's...
Does that mean...?
Very soon, I will go back to being what I was.
Next time, I won't even be able to talk to you like this.
That's why Kiritsugu left Saber's scabbard with me.
Avalon...
Are you familiar with what it does?
It halts aging and has infinite healing power.
That's what I've been told.
Its effects are what keeps the
shell that is me from collapsing.
Of course, it can't work as well when Saber isn't nearby.
Why are you telling me all this?
Hisau Maiya.
You would never pity me.
You'd acknowledge me.
That's why.
Madam, I...
I have always thought of you as a more distant figure.
That's not true.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Even at the cost of my own life...
Irisviel, I will protect you to the very end.
So...
Please die for Emiya Kiritsugu.
So his dream can become a reality.
Thank you.
I would've preferred to have known
of your dealings with the Einzberns.
I'm afraid I have no choice.
You'll withdraw from the Grail War, Kirei.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Who are you?
Will I leave this place without ever finding out?
You're still pondering about it?
How slow could you possibly be, Kirei?
The Grail beckons you still.
And you, yourself, still long to fight.
For as long as I can remember,
I've lived my life searching for just one thing.
I've spent all my time on it and endured
much pain, but all of it has come to naught.
And yet, I feel that I am closer to
the answer now than ever before.
Why do you still hesitate after all that self-examination?
I have a feeling...
...that I will destroy myself
when I've learned all the answers.
I see. Thank you.
Did you just learn of some exciting new information?
I've discovered the location of the Einzbern hideout.
You're incredible, Kirei!
You honestly amaze me!
You were going to continue this whole time.
I did hesitate.
I was prepared to stop.
But in the end, you're absolutely right, King of Heroes.
I know of no other remedy than to continue my inquiry.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
Jn424.
The Gospel of John.
God is Spirit,
and those who worship Him
must worship in spirit and truth.
However, Kirei...
A very serious problem remains.
Should you participate in the Grail War of your
own will, Tohsaka Tokiomi becomes your enemy.
In other words, you're in the same room as an
enemy Servant with nothing to defend yourself with.
Quite a dire situation you're in, aren't you?
No.
I've thought of a way to beg for my life.
Oh?
Gilgamesh...
Let me tell you the truth behind the Holy Grail War.
What?
The ritual in Fuyuki is an attempt to open a passage to the
Root through the sacrifice of the souls of seven Heroic Spirits.
One can activate the Greater Grail
by killing all seven Servants.
Yes, all seven.
You understand?
That's why my master tried so hard to avoid using his Command Spells.
He needs them to force his own Servant to
commit suicide once all the battles have ended.
So you're saying the loyalty
Tokiomi has shown me was all a lie?
In the end, my master is simply a Mage to the core.
He may worship a Heroic Spirit, but
he harbors no illusions about his idols.
Tokiomi...
You have finally proven your worth.
At last, that boring little man will be able to entertain me.
What will you do now, King of Heroes?
Are you still going to remain loyal to
my master and punish me for rebelling?
I don't know about that.
Disloyal he may be, but Tokiomi still supplies me with mana.
Abandoning my Master would hinder my ability to remain materialized.
Oh, that reminds me.
There happens to be a Master with Command Spells but
no partner, searching for a Servant unbound by contract.
You're right, now that you mention it.
But is that man a worthy Master
in the eyes of the King of Heroes?
He will suffice.
He's slightly flawed in that he's rather stiff, but he has great potential for growth.
He may prove to be a fine source
of entertainment for me someday.
I've been waiting, Kirei.
I came to have a word before leaving Fuyuki.
I'm still proud to have had you as my student.
I hope you will maintain good relations with the Tohsakas, as your late father did in life.
What do you say?
I could ask for nothing more.
Once this Grail War is over, I'd like you to
help me train Rin as her senior apprentice.
It's a simple one, but this is a will of sorts.
I thought it wise to prepare for the worst.
It leaves the Tohsaka family headship to Rin and
names you as her guardian until she comes of age.
You can rest easy.
I will do all I can to look after your daughter.
Thank you, Kirei.
What is this?
It's my gift to you.
Open it.
It's an Azoth dagger.
It symbolizes your mastery of the Tohsaka family magics and marks the end of your apprenticeship.
You are far too kind to me.
I cannot even begin to express my gratitude, my master.
It is I who must thank you, Kotomine Kirei.
I can now prepare for the final battle.
Look at the time.
I'm sorry to have kept you.
I hope you will make it in time for your flight.
No.
You need not worry, my master.
I never bought the ticket.
Master...
You're just like my father.
You never understood me, even to the very end.
Such a boring ending.
Look at how stupid his dying face looks.
He did have a Servant in spirit form at hand.
I don't blame him for lowering his guard.
So you've already learned to jest.
That progress is worth praising.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel slightly better about missing out on the chance to kill your father?
Do you really have no qualms
about this, Gilgamesh, King of Heroes?
As long as you continue to amuse me.
Otherwise, Kirei...
You're the one who should be questioning his own resolve.
Thou shalt come under my command,
and my fate shall be thy sword.
Abiding by the summons of the Holy Grail,
if thou dost accede to this will and reason...
I hereby swear.
Thy offering shall be my flesh, Kotomine Kirei...
My new Master.
Now, Kirei.
Let us begin.
Put an end to this farce however you see fit.
I shall reward you with the Grail.
Consider it done, King of Heroes.
May you have your fill of amusement.
Until the moment I find the answer I seek,
I shall gladly play the fool.
Episode 17
The Eighth Contract
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
Kerry, what do you want to be when you grow up?
Don't go to that mansion.
What is this?
You decide the rest on your own.
It's still too early for you.
Someday, you'll have the power to change the world.
Next Episode
Distant Memories