This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
Wow, they got that out fast. They're really into this.
But not as much as me!
Global Action Club
Hey, Fukube. You're late.
Hey! Morning.
This is bad. I can't let Juumoji get away with them around.
You're all here pretty early. You seem pretty fired up.
You too.
If these would-be detectives are still standing around here,
that means the theft hasn't been committed yet.
All right, Juumoji, if you're gonna strike then now's the time!
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
The Final Target
It's the last day! The most crucial moment!
I see.
I feel like I've met her somewhere before...
Using the Juumoji incident to help sell Hyouka wasn't a bad idea.
But that won't be enough to sell them all.
Should I consider the alternatives?
Dunno if it'll all work out though.
Nothing's happening.
That's true.
Juumoji's next target is the Quiz Society...
But no... What would he steal from them now that the main event's over?
I'm starving. Let's go.
Yeah, I've had enough too.
What's wrong, Juumoji? Is the mysterious thief afraid of a crowd?
What?!
Did something happen?
That bastard Juumoji faked us out.
Faked us out?
Was it the Quiz Society?
No, the Light Music Club.
They had some strings stolen.
The Light Music Club? But...
Are you sure about that?!
If you don't believe me, check for yourself!
Later!
Wait!
It's pointless.
Seems like the Light Music Club got hit.
Is that true?
Juumoji is far more flexible than I could have anticipated.
Conventional methods won't cut it this time.
I must rethink my strategy.
How else can I catch him, if not red-handed?
Target: Sell all 2OO copies!
82 sold
When it sells, it sells well!
The twenty copies that Chitanda gave to Irisu sold out,
so today she took another ten.
And we've sold another nine in total since this morning.
I have high hopes for the rest of the day.
It's Saturday all right.
Hey!
Saving energy as usual, I see.
Sis! You really came!
You should be grateful your big sister came all the way to check up on you!
Here.
Thank you very much.
What's that? It's not your style.
I'm carrying out my own One Red Paperclip trade.
That pen turned into this mirror.
You bartered your way up?
Yeah, pretty much.
Okay, then...
I'll take this.
In exchange... here.
What?
Dead at Dusk?
A manga?
You might be able to kill some time with this, but it all depends on you.
What do you mean?
Later!
Hey!
Anshin'in Takuha?
"How did you like Dead at Dusk?
It feels weird to say this myself, but I think it turned out pretty well.
Well, I only helped with the backgrounds and hardly did anything else.
If you enjoyed it, that's thanks to the author and illustrator."
So Anshin'in Takuha was a team name?
"Not all of us are members of the Manga Lab.
We simply share a fondness for manga, and as we talked, our ideas fit together.
We decided to write our own manga, and this is the result.
I think it's not half bad for a first try, but we shouldn't praise ourselves too much.
We'll let you, the readers, be the judge.
We don't want to split up after just one project, either.
We've already started on our next project for next year's Kan'ya Fair.
We decided to change the genre completely and do a mystery story.
We're thinking of giving a famous Christie novel a few twists.
We've already decided on the title, so without further ado:
The title of our next project will be "Kudryavka's Order".
Yes, another grim-sounding one.
Let us meet again at next year's Kan'ya Fair.
Anshin'in Takuha."
Kudryavka's Order?
I don't know who or what Kudryavka is, but the word "order" is interesting.
And "a famous Christie novel"?
You might be able to kill some time with this, but it all depends on you.
Sis, I sure hope you didn't bring something that's gonna cause even more trouble for me.
Radio Room
Excuse me!
You're Yoshino, the president of the Radio Club, right?
I am, but who are you?
Nice to meet you. I'm the Classics Club's president, Chitanda Eru.
I'd like to—
You're the president of the Classics Club?!
This is perfect! I was just going to look for you!
Would you like to join us as our guest for our lunchtime show?
I think it'd be awesome to promote you as the president of Juumoji's final target.
What do you say?
I didn't even have to ask!
I'd be very happy to!
Then I'll see you at twelve in the radio room!
The show starts at twelve-thirty! Thanks in advance!
Okay!
I'm back!
Hey, Chitanda!
How are we doing? Has anything happened?
They skipped "ku" and stole some strings from the Light Music Club.
We'll need to rethink our approach from the beginning.
What do you think, Oreki?
He's totally engrossed in some indie manga. He's been like that for a while.
That was good.
Really?
Huh?
What?
I think I've seen this picture somewhere.
Must be your imagination. My sister just gave me this.
No, I'm certain.
Chitanda, we don't have time.
I...
I can't stop thinking about it!
Here we go.
It's too much to bear!
Hold it back!
I can't!
Do something about it!
Show me another page too!
Here.
Thanks!
This picture!
This looks like the poster in front of the meeting room!
Are
you
telling
me
to forget
everything
that
happened?
You're right.
Oreki, please let me borrow this manga for a bit!
I want to compare them!
Okay, but bring it back soon! I need it.
Okay!
It's this picture, right?
Thank you very much!
I'm done!
What next?
Whatever you'd like.
I'll go and change the water.
Ah, thanks.
Photos won't do!
Whoops!
I-I'm sorry, Ibara!
I really didn't...
It's okay... It was khaki in the first place,
so it won't be too apparent... I hope...
Ibara?
Excuse me, president. Please take care of the rest.
You should take off the Rainbow Parakeet costume.
Please don't worry about it.
Mayaka!
Chi?
Do you have a minute?
Sweats?
Yeah, I changed.
So what did you want?
This!
How did you get this?!
It's not mine, it's Oreki's.
Why would Oreki...
He said his sister gave it to him.
Do you know this manga, Mayaka?
Yeah, kinda...
You know the culture fair poster, right?
I can't stop thinking about how the same person must have drawn both that poster and this manga!
Where's this poster?!
In front of the meeting room!
Let's go!
When light and dark are in balance.
Autumn Equinox
Hyouka
What do you think?
I'm 99% sure it's the same person.
The way the ears are drawn match perfectly.
I see! Thank you very much!
I feel like a great weight's been lifted off my chest!
It's interesting, isn't it?
Yeah.
Why don't we find out who drew it?
Good idea! I can't stop thinking about it!
Coming!
Good afternoon, Tanabe.
Hey, you're...
From the Classics Club.
What is it this time?
Sorry for the trouble, but do you know who drew that poster over there?
Ah, that was Kugayama.
You mean Kugayama Muneyoshi, the student council president?
Yeah. We pestered him to draw something.
Not half bad, is it?
Yes, I think it's wonderful!
He'll be happy to hear that.
Now I know both the author and the illustrator!
Should I ask him about it?
Maybe the dream team will reunite!
Earth Sci. Prep. room
We found out!
Was it really the same?
Mayaka, what are you doing in a sweatsuit? What happened to the Manga Lab?
I got away from my shift.
It really was the same person! We found out his name too!
That's wonderful!
It's Kugayama Muneyoshi! It was a real surprise!
Is he someone famous?
Houtarou, are you kidding?
Do you know him?
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
Organizers
Yasaki Keita (student
council vice-president)
Kugayama
Muneyoshi
(student
council
president,
executive
producer
of the
Kan'ya Fair)
The council president.
Oh, I see!
I thought he was Rikuyama all along.
So that means that Kugayama was the illustrator for Anshin'in Takuha?
"Anshin'in"? What are you talking about?
You read that as "Ajimu". It's a place in Kyuushuu.
Is that really something I can't live without knowing?
By the way, the reading is written here in small Latin letters.
Oh.
Kugayama did the illustrations, but the story is by Anjou Haruna.
You know about this?
I love that manga!
I bought it at last's year's culture fair!
Wow, Ibara just straight out said she loved it...
Oreki, can I have that?
Sure you can, but wait a little.
I'm still using it.
You're using it?
Oh right! I managed to get some airtime on the Radio Club's lunchtime program!
What?
That's amazing, Chi!
Not bad! That's wonderful news!
Now selling all the copies of  Hyouka might be more than just a dream!
I'll teach you the basics of how to speak on air.
Really?
Firstly, your time is limited to about five minutes.
So it all depends on how much you can impress people in that short time.
Ah, I see.
The Kan'ya Fair Guide...
Secondly, you must make the Classics Club famous!
The Gardening Club... The Cooking Club... The Light Music Club...
Okay! Leave it to me!
A very famous Christie novel... Kudryavka's Order...
I'll be counting on you!
What?
How is it?
Nothing...
Whatever.
I'm close to a conclusion.
I'll need to talk to them about it, but...
Chitanda is in the way.
If she found out what I'm about to do, she'd be against it.
Satoshi, could you come with me for a moment?
So you really did figure something out, Houtarou?
Really, Oreki?
Know when to keep your mouth shut, goddamn it!
You see that light in Chitanda's eyes?!
Did you notice something?
No! Nothing at all!
Then it's not about the Juumoji incident?
Well...
Hey, Oreki...
I've... I've been thinking about it all this time, so why did you only ask Fukube...
I shouldn't take this any further.
Yes, it's about the Juumoji incident.
Then please let us know too—
However, it's quite a dirty story. You okay with that?
So what's this "dirty story" of yours?
Sorry for dragging you out here.
Oh, I don't mind.
It's not like I have some grand idea.
There's just a few things that don't fit the big picture.
I think that means something.
Was there some hidden connection between the clubs that got hit?
No, that's not it either.
Then what? Did the mysterious thief Juumoji make some fatal mistake?
That isn't it either.
What?
It's neither?
There are over a thousand suspects.
Were you planning to find the culprit without a connection or a mistake on their part?
Kinda.
How?!
I don't know about the culprit yet. I just want to sum up my thoughts.
Let's hear it. I expect great things of you, Houtarou.
First: Why would Juumoji steal ten items from ten clubs?
That's just what we theorised he'd do, based on his name.
And that theory isn't holding steady either.
Second: Why did they leave greeting cards behind at the scene of the crime?
This, huh?
Third: Why do they use the word "lost"? It'd be more natural to say that they'd "taken" it.
lost
Fourth: Why do they leave the Kan'ya Fair guide behind?
That's not the only thing with a list of clubs in it.
So why are they sticking just to that?
I've got one too, by the way.
I picked it up after the cooking competition.
Fifth: Why the Gardening Club and the Cooking Club?
There are other clubs that start with the same sound in Japanese.
Especially the Cooking Club.
It's not even common to write it in that way.
And that leads us to whether the Classics Club or the Artisan Club will be targeted.
Sixth, and this is the weirdest: Why did they skip "ku" and go straight for "ke"?
That's was to elude watchful eyes.
You couldn't steal a speck of dust from the Global Action Club without someone noticing.
Seventh: this.
That manga has nothing to do with this.
That might not be true.
Satoshi, what are Christie's most famous works?
Let's see... And Then There Were None, Murder on the Orient Express,
The Murder of Roger Ackroyd, and The ABC Murders.
Those four, I guess.
If they came up with a retelling of one of those stories called Kudryavka's Order,
it'd most likely be based off the ABC Murders.
Kudryavka was a dog that was sent into space in a test launch and never returned alive.
Wouldn't that imply And Then There Were None?
This is still just a theory, so it's okay if we don't agree.
I think I understand what you're trying to say.
Satoshi, are they selling a manga titled Kudryavka's Order at this fair?
Nope, I heard nothing like that at from General Affairs.
And if the Manga Lab had something to do with it, Mayaka would've mentioned it.
Then...
They published Dead at Dusk at last year's fair.
In the afterword, it said they'd publish a manga this year based on a famous Christie novel with "a few twists".
That novel is probably either And Then There Were None or The ABC Murders.
And then this year, there's a series of incidents clearly inspired by The ABC Murders.
Is that a coincidence?
So you say that the Juumoji incident was originally announced in Dead at Dusk?
I can't imagine they're not connected at all.
I even feel like Juumoji is trying not to cause too much trouble or
disrupt the fair's events too much during their chain of thefts.
It doesn't feel like they're just doing it for the thrill of it.
But then why did they skip "ku"?
They had plenty of ways to pull it off.
Satoshi, this incident has some meaning to it.
I'm going back.
I'm a bit worried about Chitanda too.
You're right. I'll leave that to you.
I'll have a look through the stuff you gave me.
Satoshi!
Tell Chitanda to get something ready that starts with "ko".
Bait for the culprit, right? I thought about that one already.
I'll get some copy papers.
I'm counting on you, Houtarou.
On air
We'll be going on air at the cue.
Five seconds. Four.
You're listening to Yoshino Yasukuni's Radio Beat special!
Good morning to you all!
This is the one and only Yoshino Yasukuni, comin' at you live!
My guest today on the last day of the fair is the president of the Classics Club,
Chitanda Eru from first year class A!
Thank you very much!
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Next time: Kudryavka's Order.
Kudryavka's Order