How to lose weight?
I've never gone on a diet...
Really? But you're so thin!
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's like my body is just naturally that way.
Naturally?
I'm so jealous!
Kawashima became the center of attention among the girls.
Yeah...
If you go overboard, you'll stress yourself out. So just eat what you want in a healthy way.
I can't let you say that crap!
What are you doing?!
What?
Huh?
Let me go!
Here, here, here, here!
Sensei!
Kawashima-san is hiding fat in her stomach!
Did you know that you can't have more than 300 yen worth of fat?
Is this 300 yen worth of extra flab?
Bananas don't count as fat!
This part is from steamed buns!
This part is from expensive ice cream!
This part is from corn dogs!
Eat this! Convenience store attack!
High!
Calories!
This is for the Diet Warriors...
Who have lost their lives in battle!
Now then...
We did it! With convenience store power!
She was a tough opponent!
Those jerks...
A-Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Those jerks are so mean!
You poor thing...
It's like the calm after the storm.
So cruel...
So if you attack her that way, Ami becomes like that...
I feel so much better!
It's just like you, Minorin, to work hard!
Fights between girls are so scary...
As a Diet Warrior, I couldn't keep quiet.
It's because you stand up and fight against fat that the Goddess of Slim Figures smiles upon you.
That girl will understand someday.
Is that how it is?
What's up with that guy?
Oh, yeah...
Ryuji, shall I make salad for dinner tonight?
Y-You?
I learned it in elementary school.
I can even make my own dressing!
You buy lettuce, right?
You tear off the leaves, right?
You cut it up, right?
You put it on a plate, right?
There, all done!
You haven't washed the lettuce.
You haven't put it under running water.
Where did the dressing go?
You're too noisy about the little things, you old maid.
Old maid?
Takasu-kun!
W-What is it, Kawashima?
Please, could you come with me for a bit?
That guy... From earlier...
Hey, Kawashi-
You...
Hey, how long do you plan to stick together like that?
Completely ignoring me... Being all sticky, sticky, sticky...
Sticky, sticky, sticky...
Hey, Taiga, right now...
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
Here is my official greeting!
Hey, Kawashima, who was that just now?
He's not... Someone you know, right?
This sometimes happens when you're a model.
When a fan starts bothering you...
Even though I went all out to transfer schools...
Hey, you're going home now, right?
Yeah...
Could you let me hide in your house?
It'd be scary if I met that guy again.
I get it.
If it's something like that, leave it to me!
A drafty wooden house or a luxury apartment with an automatic door lock...
Which is better?
The luxury apartment!
Then it's settled.
Come to my house.
Wait a sec.
Why does Ami-chan have to go to your place?
It's okay, I won't force you...
But with Ryuji's place having so many security holes, even I could sneak in.
It's really okay, since it has nothing to do with me anyway.
W-Wait, Aisaka-san!
I said wait, dammit!
Well, I guess it's okay.
Here you go.
Sweet!
It's kumquat-flavored honey that Ryuji makes a lot of.
I tried to mix it with soda water.
This is way too concentrated!
Giving me this to drink...
What happened to being a "Diet Warrior"?
Has your brain shrunk along with your body?
You really do completely change...
I want to show the real side of you to everyone in class.
I have no desire to show my true self.
I see...
Now, since you drank the kumquat-flavored honey, your throat should be in great shape, right?
If you don't want to show your true self, then...
Let's see your fake self!
Thoroughly.
Good morning.
Morning...
K-Kawashima?
You seem tired.
Yeah...
I'm still tired from yesterday.
Yeah, that was pretty scary.
No...
In Aisaka Taiga's apartment, doing this and that for 5 hours... No, 6 hours...
D-Did Taiga do something?
Jackson.
Uganda.
U... ganda?
Falcon.
Akechi Mitsuhide.
Matsumoto Seicho.
Oda Nobunaga singing Chanson like crazy.
Dazai Osamu Cheering Japan.
And not only that but...
H-Hey are you alright Kawashima?
Juda.
Yeah, I made her do it. An imitation medley of 150 different people.
It was really fun!
I don't even have the slightest idea how you would do an imitation of Akechi Mitsuhide.
I told her that if she didn't do what I said, I'd toss her out.
B-Brutal.
No, I'm grateful, Aisaka.
Kitamura?
Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, I have a request for you.
Ami-chan, you don't look so good.
Shouldn't you go to the nurse's office?
I'm just fine.
H-Hey.
Come, you stupid Chihuahua. It's your feeding time.
Who are you calling a stupid Chihuahua?
You, of course. Pretending to be cute, but constantly barking while in heat all year long.
Anyway, come!
What the hell?
Why do I have to go with you?
I promised my friends...
Michael Jackson as a bus guide.
Mona Lisa going into a curve at 100 kilometers an hour.
A happy Le Penseur.
All the pictures I took have already been copied.
Some might accidentally be leaked to the public...
Stop it!
I got it. I'll go alright?! Dammit.
Um, Ami-chan?
Sorry!
I forgot I promised to eat lunch with Aisaka-san.
I'm really sorry!
Hey you! Wait!
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
What the hell is this?
As long as she's pretending to be a good girl, Ami can't make real friends.
So, I want you guys, who know about her real self, to help her.
I'm okay... But Taiga and Kawashima are clearly not on good terms.
Aisaka!
Please!
You are one the few female friends who I can rely on!
Like I said...
Thanks, Aisaka!
Kitamura, you bastard.
Pushing all the hard work on us and leaving for Student Council stuff.
Kushieda, your lunch looks great!
Even if it looks like a lot, this lunch is really low-calorie!
These are king trumpet mushrooms, this is konnyaku, and this is rice with string konnyaku.
Why the hell do I...
Hey, Ami. I'll let you have the kelp.
I don't need it.
Really?
Lucky...
Nothing.
Time to eat.
Huh?
Why does Takasu-kun's lunch have the same sides as Aisaka-san's?
Why?
Um... That is...
Now there's no problem, right?
I've got fried eggs and veggies while Ryuji only has dried seaweed and rice.
My sides!
Here you go.
Now you have a meatball lunch.
Thanks.
But why are you letting Aisaka-san do whatever she wants?
Am I?
Ryuji was my dog in a previous life.
It's a dog's pleasure to serve his master.
Yes! These two are destined for each other.
No way.
Minorin, you did it again.
Sorry! It was a joke!
Everyone, listen up!
Today is the Student Council sponsored...
Monthly volunteer area cleanup.
But we don't have enough people.
Are there any volunteers who will step up?
Sorry, Kitamura, today there's a special sale at the supermarket...
Hey, Takasu, you'll do it?
Then, please change your clothes and come to the schoolyard.
Why do I have to?
I'm telling you I'll take responsibility and participate with you!
You say that, but you just want to be with Kitamura. Even for just a little bit.
That's true too.
You're honest.
Takasu-kun!
I'm going too.
I just transferred, so I want to get used to the school.
Minorin...
As a Diet Warrior, I just had to help out a woman trying so hard to lose weight by exercising her body.
It's not like I want to lose weight!
Let's work hard together, Takasu-kun!
Y-Yeah...
Alright you bastards! We're going to take our balls and go!
If you try to skip, I won't forgive you, you bastards!
There, there, calm down.
Got your gloves on?
Got trash bags?
Checked which area you're cleaning?
Yeah...
Don't underestimate this town.
If that's all you got, you'll get kicked off the ship!
Put some energy into it and answer me!
Yeah!
The president's really something.
Alright! I'll explain today's program. First-
In the end, Kitamura-kun goes off with the people in the student council...
Sorry! Council members have a different route!
Then why did I...
Hey, this piece of trash is just like you, Aisaka-san. The part where it's so small it’s useless.
Then this piece of trash is just like you, Kawashima-san. See how it's swollen and self-indulged.
Let's go this way, Minorin.
Eloping? Okay!
Let's go, let's go.
Yeah! The trash is waiting for us!
They left.
Since we've been left behind, let's get along!
Picking up trash is kind of fun!
Maybe it's because I'm with Takasu-kun?
Kawashima, um...
Hey, let's go over there.
Watch out!
Hey, are you okay?
Gross! What the hell's this?
Dammit!
Kawashima?
I was surprised! My shoes are soaked.
Ew! Ew! Ew! Get it off me!
Kawashima!
Don't move, it's climbing up!
Don't kick my face!
Eww!
Alright, salvaged!
It's okay now.
See, the frog went home.
I don't want to do this crap!
K-Kawashima?
Just kidding!
Was it funny?
It's raining...
We'll get wet.
We've got to find some shelter. Right, Takasu-
Hey.
Isn't that enough? Stuff like that.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
I'm the one who doesn't understand.
Why did you go out of your way to sign up for this?
You don't... Understand?
Takasu-kun, so this kind of stuff doesn't work on you.
I've already figured out that you're always hiding your real self.
Why can't you be more...
I got it, more honest?
You know, I've...
I have to be like this.
You don't understand my feelings, right?
Yeah, to be honest.
That's okay.
I'm silly, after all.
Kawashima?
What's wrong?
Hey! Kawashima!
Hey, what's wrong?
If it's just shelter from the rain...
What?
That's the guy from yesterday...
Why?
Um... That guy is...
A stalker.
Why didn't you say anything?
Because...
I was frustrated!
Frustrated?
I didn't want to admit that a guy like that was messing up my life.
I moved here because of him.
I didn't want to burden my parents.
So I moved to my relative's house by myself.
I also took a break from my modeling.
Even though I've come all the way here, I'm still being chased by that guy!
Hey! Hey!
Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hey!
That's strange... I thought they went this way.
Who cares, let's go home, Minorin.
I found a cute little Yōkai!
Yōkai?
Taiga?
Watch out!
I don't want to be called a Yōkai by a shady guy like you!
What is she doing?
That guy's a stalker!
Why the hell are you taking pictures without permission?
You're really disgusting!
There's nothing wrong with it... It's not like you lose anything.
Of course it's wrong!
I'll crush that camera... And its owner!
Don't run!
Wait!
H-Hey, Taiga!
That idiot.
Why?
Isn't she scared?
That guy's a pervert.
Kawashima?
Because of that bastard...
I took off work, moved, and even transferred schools.
I got irritated, stressed out, ate a ton of sweets...
This means that Ami-chan is losing to that worthless bastard and to Aisaka Taiga, right?
Takasu-kun...
You told me earlier.
"Quit hiding things." You said that to me.
Um, yeah.
I got it.
Ami-chan will quit.
I'll quit... I'll quit, I'll quit, I'll quit, I'll quit, I'll quit, and then...
K-Kawashima?
I'll live on showing everyone my twisted personality!
I'm not going to lie down and take it anymore!
Hey!
Kawashima...
The Kawashima after that was amazing.
She was good enough to join the track team.
With her beautiful running form, she ran around town...
In front of the frightened stalker, she completely destroyed his camera.
The stalker was completely scared by the expression on her face.
Then...
You liar! This demonic expression...
You aren't the Ami-chan I know!
You aren't an angel! You have a bad personality!
What about it?
Ami-chan is this cute!
Her personality...
Doesn't matter!
Kawashima! Are you okay?
Hey, Kawashima!
I did it, Takasu-kun.
Yeah?
But...
I was scared.
Here, it'll warm you up.
This is... Kumquat-flavored honey.
Wow, I'm impressed you knew. Taiga likes it too.
Taiga?
You call her only by her first name.
You still doubt us?
That girl is lucky.
She's selfish and all over the place, but she doesn't try to hide anything...
Even so, she has friends, and Takasu-kun.
Takasu-kun, what would you do if I showed you my real self?
Would you... Like me?
K-K-Kawashima?
Hey?
W-Wait a minute.
I...
Taiga! Were they there?
Gimme.
Taiga!?
Waterproof, water repellant, and a little gradation.
You can install it with one touch!
How about this, Taiga!?
Fake Breast Special Combat Group!