Good morning!
Oh, good morning. It's been a while.
You got darker, huh?
I went to the beach.
Yuko-chan!
Yuko-chan, good morning.
Ah. Run, Toru. 'Morning.
Good morning.
School's started, huh?
That's right. I'm sad that summer vacation's over.
But it was fun, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
Ah. Nagi.
Nagi-chan, good morning!
Shh!
What're you doin'? You'll be late.
Good morning!
Ma'am! G-Good morning, Miss Kito!
What's the matter? It's the start of the
new semester, but you're lacking SPIRIT!
Now then, once again!
Now!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!
Not good enough. Once again!
Good morning! Go!
GOOD MORNING!
I'm sorry, Yuko.
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
THE NEW SEMESTER
First morning of the new semester
and you're already stifling!
The students will hate you.
I-It's not as if I want to make friends with them!
Also, the students need discipline!
But in all things, allowances are necessary,
are they not?
You have to be hands-off, to an extent. Right?
Sato. 'Morning.
The way YOU are hands-off,
Kamate-chan, is the best.
In a pinch, you'd just leave me on my own.
Aah, I feel all tingly.
Yes! The way you ignore me,
disavowing my existence!
Please don't blurt out such
nasty-sounding things! It's unpleasant!
Kito, you should just ignore him, too.
That's offensive!
Miss Kito, your bellowing rings in my head
and makes it hurt, so won't you stop?
If that's the case, why not go back
to the nurse's office?
Why don't YOU go to the classroom?
Back to your beloved students. Go on, hurry.
Just what's with that tone?!
I'm SO sorry.
These quarreling such-and-suches...
Look, why don't you just start dating?
I'm SO sorry.
These quarreling such-and-suches...
Look, why don't you just start dating?
There you go again!
These quarreling such-and-suches...
Look, why don't you just start dating?
My apologies.
These quarreling such-and-suches...
Look, why don't you just start dating?
Just cut it out!
If that's a joke, it's not funny.
Even your timing is the same...
That's too intense for first thing in the morning.
Oh?
Good morning, Run-chan.
Good morning. It's been a while.
Good morning!
Oh, you've got darker! Where did you go?
The boys are swarming again!
I went to Thailand.
Really? How nice!
There she is, the freshman
who really likes Run-chan.
Giving it your all from the new semester, huh?
Though you're tiny.
Toru?
She's so tall!
W-we're sorry.
You're all cruel! Leavin' me like that...
Sorry, Yuko.
It really was terrible. Huh?
Why you holdin' a chair?
Dunno.
Good morning!
Yes, yes. That's it.
It was in the tabloids this morning.
Torun and Miporin are chatting!
Oh, I read that.
I, Yutaka, want in, too!
Japan's political and economic climate is-
But regulatory reform
should come first, shouldn't it?
What's the matter? Yutaka?
Japan's political and economic climate...
Regulatory reform...
It's too difficult. For me, Yutaka,
the hurdle is too high!
Say, did you watch the show last night?
I did! That hot-blooded high school drama.
That teacher is a little stifling, isn't she?
But that makes it good.
Torun! Miporin!
Good morning!
Hey! That's too hot, Yutaka!
Okay, take your seats.
Good morning!
Okay, today begins the second semester.
Let's give it our all!
Good morning!
Stifling...
Begin warm-up exercises.
And no slacking. You'll hurt yourselves later.
Sure enough, she just doesn't care!
Say, Toru-san?
What?
About our earlier conversation...
Torun!
This time it's MY turn!
S-Stop.
Now look, you!
How I missed you!
Summer vacation was so long!
You saw her at orientation, didn't you?!
I don't 'member that.
Oh, really?
This is...
Okay, it's been three minutes.
Step away from Toru-san now.
Huh? Already?
Yutaka!
Okay.
The three-minute rule.
That's the agreement for your fans, Toru-san.
Um, you've said the word "fan" before.
Have I done something?
Toru-san, you can do ANYTHING,
but you don't brag about it...
That's right, that's right!
And she's always so calm and cool.
Right?
Still, I'm sure you've heard this a million times...
Huh? Toru-san? Where's Toru-san?
What's the matter?
Nothing at all.
Torun!
Toru-san? Do you have a moment?
I have a favor to ask.
Yes, Miss Kito.
Torun...
Sorry to interrupt you.
I'll be borrowing Toru-san.
I'd like you to get the notebooks for class.
Ma'am.
That's cruel.
What is?
Even if you're a teacher,
you have to obey the three-minute rule!
Hey!
Okay, so if you'd get started on that...
Ma'am.
That's it!
Just three minutes!
Any more is-
See you soon, Toru-san.
S-stop!
Here.
If you don't mind.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, I forgot.
Can I ask you to do these, too?
While you're at it, get some coffee
from the vending machine.
Miss Kamate! Please don't use
the students to run your errands!
That's not what I wanna hear, is it?
Fine, YOU can do it for me.
You can go yourself, can't you?!
Hey, you. 'Scuse me.
Um... Um...
K's POEMS
Whose notebook might THIS be?
You like your coffee black, right?
Thanks a lot.
Torun's taking so long. I'm lonely...
She'll be back soon.
Huh?
What is it?
It's the upperclassmen
who are always with Toru-san.
Sure enough!
That light-skinned upperclassman is pretty, huh?
Yeah.
That glasses-wearing upperclassman
looks so smart!
Yeah.
That girl who looks like a model is...
That's Upperclassman Broom, isn't it?
Is there a fire?!
Wrong. It's Upperclassman MOP.
Oh!
What's up? Caught a cold?
I know a way to stop them!
You have to slap the back as hard as you can!
That's for hiccups.
Wrong.
Who's that?!
It takes a blow to the solar plexus.
Toru!
Don't scare us like that!
It's Toru-san!
What do you think they're talking about?
They really are good friends.
Yeah...
We'll help you.
Thank you.
There.
I'll take this.
You don't have to take ALL of it.
You carried them this far by yourself,
so this makes it half, right?
I can leave my shoes here, right?
You carried them this far by yourself,
so this makes it half, right?
I'm sure it's fine.
You carried them this far by yourself,
so this makes it half, right?
She's blushing!
How charming.
Yeah...
Huh?
That upperclassman
started talking to some boys.
Huh? Torun went somewhere...
Oh, she's back.
With a bat. Will she be playing baseball?
K's POEMS
That should do it.
I'll be back.
GOOD MORNING!
G-good morning, Miss Kito.
She got me again.
That was unlucky, huh?
Got that right...
Say, Toru hasn't shown up today, huh?
She have class duties again?
We're fighting right now.
For real?
Everything okay?!
Yeah. It happens once in a while.
They're FIGHTING! What do we do, Nagi?!
What good will freaking out do?
Just calm down.
But! Fighting is just... I can't believe it!
I told you, calm down.
I-In any case, let's ask what happened.
Okay.
Well? Why are you fighting?
Um, well...
It's gotten late. I'll walk you back.
I'm fine.
But there've been perverts out lately!
If so, then after you've walked me, you'd be
in trouble coming back by yourself, right?
I'll be fine.
You'll be in trouble! But I'LL be fine!
Why are you being so stubborn?
YOU are! What'll you do if something happens?!
This is a residential area! I'll be fine.
Then the same goes for me, right?!
And it goes for me, too!
It goes more for me!
That's how our argument went.
So, what finally happened?
She stayed at my house.
While you were fighting?!
Yeah.
Can you even call that "fighting"?
Run and Toru, fighting...
I wonder if Toru's feelin' depressed.
Toru...
Run-chan, you idiot.
Wow. She's drinkin' like she's mad!
Doesn't feel like I can come out now...
Wait, did she notice me?
She got them all in!
Okay, I'll bring them next time.
Thank you.
Fighting, huh?
Toru seems like she'd be down,
but Run looks the same as always.
Unusual to see you reading a novel, Run.
Really?
What're you reading?
Run. This is upside-down.
Generally, when y = ax2 + bx +c is 1
and ax2 + bx + c = 0 is 2...
"When casualties result from
accidents or calamities,
"the people in those environments must,
by their own hands..."
Man, this is long. Everyone,
look over the rest of this yourselves.
What should we do?
Nagi, aren't you worried?
Yes, I am! But I don't know what to do.
Just watching them is so tough...
Yeah, I guess.
Aah, what should we do? How troubling...
If you have troubles, I will hear them!
Miss Kito!
I will listen to ANY trouble!
N-no! It's not like I have a trouble or anything-
Wait right there!
Keeping troubles inside your heart is the worst
thing to do! Come, open your heart!
I-I'm telling you, I don't have any troubles.
Don't hide it!
Be honest with your teacher!
Come! Come, come, come! Come!
What are you so shy about?!
I'm fine!
I won't do wrong by you! Come!
Look, I don't have any troubles!
Wait, Yuko-san! Don't hold back.
Open your heart to your teacher!
She really is unlucky, huh?
Wait, Yuko-san! Don't hold back.
Open your heart to your teacher!
Run-chan...
Torun looks pretty down. It's up to me,
Yutaka, to cheer her up!
What is it, Miporin?
Let's go back, Yutaka.
Toru-san doesn't look like
she's up for that right now.
But...
Come on, let's go.
Miporin! That hurts!
I finally lost her.
Toru?
Sure enough, we should make up!
I'm going to the co-op!
W-wait! Why are you going to the co-op?!
I need snacks so we can make up.
You're going to BUY her?
These, please.
Okay, that's 200 yen.
Five Yen
Should I pay?
Kumo ga dokoka ni fuwari tonde yuku
The clouds drift off somewhere
She beat me to it!
Sore o koko de tada miageteta
We just looked up and watch them from here
Where are you going now? Hey!
Sore o koko de tada miageteta
We just looked up and watch them from here
Jeez...
Sore o koko de tada miageteta
We just looked up and watch them from here
Sora o tobereba kimi to doko made mo
If I could fly in the sky, then I could go anywhere
Is something up with this?
Sora o tobereba kimi to doko made mo
If I could fly in the sky, then I could go anywhere
I'm
sorry.
Sora o tobereba kimi to doko made mo
If I could fly in the sky, then I could go anywhere
Ikeru ne, Nani ga matteru no ka na
With you, couldn't I? I wonder what awaits
Itsu datte taisetsu na mono wa
You always notice what's important
Toru!
Itsu datte taisetsu na mono wa
You always notice what's important
Naku shite kara kizutsuku kara
Once you've gotten rid of it
Sunao ni narereba tsutawaru deshou
If we could be honest then I'm sure you'd get it
Ameagari ni kakaru niji no shita futari
Those two under the rainbow after the rain cleared
Waraeteru ka na - Ima wa kimi to kono michi o
I wonder if they can laugh - Now, on this path with you
Zutto zutto aruite yukou
I'll walk on, forever and ever
Torun wasn't cheery.
I'm worried.
Yeah...
But maybe everything's okay now.
So it's settled, huh?
Yeah. That was a shock to my system.
You got a handkerchief?
Well well, Nagi. Moved, were ya?
Huh?
How could one NOT be moved?!
M-Miss Kito! When did you?
Well, let's go home, Yutaka.
Okay!
You think Torun will be cheerful tomorrow?
Probably.
So we can have fun together, huh?
For just three minutes.
Huh?!
K's POEMS
Okay, I'm goin' home.
Yeah.
See you.
Okay. Have a good night.
Drink it
Akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
Tanoshii ichinichi no owari
Tsukinai oshaberi mada mada aru keredo
Sorosoro o-uchi ni kaeranakucha
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Mail suru kara
Kyou no page ni minna osoroi no egao
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Itsumo arigato
Kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
Ru-ru-run, kaze to kokoro humming suru
Tsugi no kado de furimukinagara bye-bye
yup!
Once summer's done,
it's straight to autumn, huh?
That's fast! It's TOO fast,
don't you think, Miporin?
I'm not sure.
All of a sudden, it's Halloween?!
That's just unforgivable!
Still, what can we?
We haven't done any important stories yet!
Like gazing at the moon alone with Torun,
or Torun and I at the PE festival together!
The two of you ain't gonna happen.
Next
Episode!
THE PRESENT
Next
Episode!
THE PRESENT
Next time, on A-Channel: "The Present"
Of course, I'LL be there too, right?
Miporin, you're scary.