[RUKO] Poor Yuzuki.
She was crying.
Ah.
[HATSU] They're only one
building away from a Tetris.
[HATSU] And then the whole city
might just disappear on us.
[RUKO] If that does happen...
I wonder if whatever's
making Yuzuki sad
will disappear, too.
[elevator doors ding]
Hey, Grandma,
I'm finally--
[YUZUKI] About time!
We've been wondering when
you were gonna get home.
Yuzuki was nice enough
to help with dinner tonight,
such an angel!
Not to mention a real
whiz in the kitchen!
Oh, stop it! You're
embarrassing me!
What the what?
[YUZUKI squeals]
Wow, it's so tasty!
This stuff is incredible!
Thank you, and please,
eat as much as you want.
[YUZUKI] Yes, ma'am!
Ruko, you lucky punk!
You get to eat like
this every day?
Um. I guess?
[RUKO sighs]
It's fine. But is she
here 'cause she doesn't
wanna go home?
That bath felt so good!
So, Yuzuki.
Thanks to a belly full
of food and a hot bath,
now I'm all Ener-Charged!
Orichalcum, attack!
[RUKO screams]
--[YUZUKI giggling]
--[RUKO] No! Hey, cut it out!.
[YUZUKI] Take that!
--[RUKO] Please! That tickles!
Yuzuki, stop it! Quit it!
Knock it off! Bad girl!
[YUZUKI] Yeah so,
um... I'm sorry.
I was really
mean to you.
[YUZUKI] Why not?
'Cause I have no idea
what you're thinking, Ruko!
[WOMAN'S VOICE] I don't
know what she's thinking.
It scares me.
It's okay! No biggie!
It's nothing to apologize for.
[YUZUKI] The truth is...
I was so afraid of losing
to Akira the whole time.
I was upset. And then, it
just ended in the worst way.
[RUKO] Oh.
[YUZUKI] That's not all.
There's this boy I like.
[RUKO gasps]
But... We can never be together.
Wha--? C'mon now,
don't think like that.
Hey. I'm sure this
guy will fall for you.
[YUZUKI] Huh-uh.
It won't happen.
And it shouldn't, either.
[YUZUKI] I just wish...
these feelings would go away.
Hold on a sec. This guy you
have a thing for, it's not...
It's not...
[RUKO gasps]
--[YUZUKI] Attack!
--[RUKO screams]
[RUKO] Stop it,
you tickle monster!
I wonder what it feels
like to be in love.
I guess you get
really excited, huh?
Yeah, excited! You know
what makes Tama excited?
Battle!
[RUKO sighs]
[TAMA] Hm...?
Kazuki.
[cell phone vibrates]
[students chattering]
[KAZUKI] Oh, she
went home already?
[GIRL A] Yeah, a while ago.
Okay. Thanks so much.
[RUKO] Hitoe comes here to study
and practice battle strategies.
She takes notes and
that seems to help her.
So I figured it wouldn't
hurt me to give it a shot.
That's a fantastic idea!
Bet you'll be kicking butt
and taking names in no time!
[RUKO] Hitoe!
[HITOE gasps]
[HITOE screams]
[RUKO & YUZUKI] Uhh...
[RUKO] And she's gone.
[BOTH] Huh.
So, um...
I, uh, thought about it.
A whole lot. And my
answer to you is yes!
So let's be friends.
Just like you asked.
That okay?
Huh?
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO]
'Course it is!
We're friends! It's official!
Yuzuki, too.
Well, if you're
okay with it.
Talking to me?
Yeah, sure, why not?
[HITOE gasps]
Um... Two friends
at the same time?!
WIXOSS is just
so... surprising.
[RUKO] Huh?
You see, during that
battle I had with Akira,
things got so painful
I started to wonder if
I'd ever even want
to play again.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
I knew battling as a
Selector would probably hurt,
but no pain, no gain, right?
We are trying to fight
for a wish after all.
Thing is, I enjoyed my
battle with Ruko so much
that it completely changed
my tune! It was fun!
Awesome! I had fun, too!
Well, in that case,
why don't we all
play a round,
just for kicks?
Yeah, that's a great idea!
[HITOE] But we're all Selectors.
So if we battle
against each other,
that means somebody's
wish could--
[YUZUKI] Nah, don't
worry about it.
As long as none of our
LRIGs are in the deck,
we can play the game just
like normal people do.
[HITOE] Oh.
All right. You guys
wait here, 'kay?
[TAMA growling]
Take care, Hitoe,
and have fun.
Thanks!
[MIDORIKO giggles]
[TAMA squeals]
[YUZUKI] All right then.
Your turn, Hitoe. Let's go.
[HITOE] Right!
Mmman! When do I get to play?
We did rock-paper-scissors.
You're up next.
Finally!
[YUZUKI sighs]
[HITOE] Okay, Summon: Baromet.
What?!
Wait! Yeah... Lemme see...
Baromet's power level
is only 7000.
So if Yuzuki has her
card Grow on next turn,
she'd crush it in
one shot. Right?
[HITOE gasps]
Yeah, she would!
Wait... I...
Jeez, how would you like it
if I gave away your strategies
when you're playing?
Oh. Sorry!
[YUZUKI growls]
[TAMA growls]
Tama wants battle!
[MIDORIKO chuckles]
You and Ruko are really
alike, aren't you?
Well, I guess Hitoe's
wish already came true.
So she doesn't need
to battle anymore.
It seems not.
You okay with that?
I am.
[HANAYO] But, that
means you're...
It's fine.
[RUKO gasps]
No wait! Not that one!
[YUZUKI gasps]
Right. So sorry.
Well, you are helping me.
So there's no need to apologize.
We're friends now,
right, you big doofus?
So... friends tease and
call each other names, huh?
All the time! Try calling
us something dumb.
Like "stinky" or "jerk".
[HITOE wails]
Just do it. It's not
like we'll get mad.
Um... Okay,,. Well, here goes...
Hi... "Stinky."
Hi, "Jerk."
[YUZUKI laughs]
[YUZUKI] That almost
sounded painful for you!
[RUKO] So I'm Stinky?
[YUZUKI]
"Hi, Stinky! Hi, Jerk!"
[MIDORIKO] I've never seen
Hitoe smile like that.
I have to admit, I sometimes
wish I wasn't her LRIG.
Well, there's no point
in torturing yourself.
I suppose not.
Tama likes Ru!
[HANAYO & MIDORIKO gasp]
Likes Ru a whole lot!
Likes being her LRIG!
Yay, Ru!
Yes, but--
[HANAYO] It's okay.
After all, Tama
and Ru are friends.
Mm-hmm!
Wait a sec. You mean--
Right. Tama doesn't know.
[TAMA squeals]
[MIDORIKO] I see.
[RUKO] Yes! I'm next!
Geez, you really like
WIXOSS, don't you?
[HITOE giggles]
Yeah, I sure do! A lot!
[GIRL B] Yeah, I saw
her out at the front!
[GIRL C] Ooh, really?
[GIRL D] Yes, Akira's here!
[GIRL E] You mean
the famous model?
[GIRL F] Uh-huh!
[GIRLS chattering]
[AKIRA] Oh, no!
You're telling me Ru-ru
already went home for the day?
That's so mean... She broke
her promise to meet me.
[GIRL G] What a
lousy thing to do.
Yeah, tell me about it.
How dare she
stand you up?
Do you want us to
go make her sorry?
Uh-uh...
I'm sure she had
a real good reason.
Oh, well. Just have
to try tomorrow.
[AKIRA] Oh wait, what
happens if she leaves
before I get here again? I wish
someone could keep tabs on her.
But that's just crazy-talk
because who would wanna do that?
Ooh, I'd be happy to!
Yeah, me too!
Leave it to us, okay?
[GIRLS chattering excitedly]
[AKIRA giggles]
Awww! Thank you
girls so much!
I've got a shoot
to get to, so ta!
[GIRLS squealing]
[YUZUKI sighs]
[YUZUKI] I don't wanna go home.
[HANAYO] You can't keep hiding
from Kazuki like this forever.
Yeahhh, I know, but--
[KAZUKI] Yuzuki!
[YUZUKI gasps]
[KAZUKI panting]
It's Akira.
[YUZUKI gasps]
She was at school
this afternoon.
[AYUMU groans]
Dang, Ruko,
you won again!
Boo-yah! That means
you get me a milk tea!
I'll take some sweet
bean soup while you're up.
Sure, Grandma. Oh, man.
I lose a game and
all of a sudden
I'm you guys'
personal waiter.
Chop-chop, garçon!
Yes ma'am. Glad to see
you're in better spirits.
[RUKO] Huh?
Well? Are you ready for
a game against me, Ru?
The loser will have
to clean the bathroom.
[RUKO] What? No way,
you're too good!
[RUKO] I like playing for fun
against Grandma
and Ayumu like this.
[RUKO] But...
To be honest I like battling
along with Tama even more.
Not just for fun.
But on a battlefield.
In matches against
other Selectors.
[RUKO] It's weird, though.
In those battles,
everyone's fighting so hard
for their wishes.
And even though
I don't have one.
I want to keep
fighting harder, too.
What's that, dear?
[RUKO] Oh! I'm sorry!
It's my turn, right?
[crowd chattering]
[train clattering]
[RUKO] Akira's looking for me?
[KAZUKI] Yeah.
She must want to battle
against you pretty bad, Ruko.
That stalker just
doesn't give up!
Yeah, but...
I don't even have a wish,
like the other Selectors do.
So, I guess there wouldn't be
any harm in fighting her then.
Would there?
[YUZUKI] No, you're wrong!
Whatever you do, please
don't battle Akira! Okay?
Um. Sure.
[YUZUKI] Listen. She's gonna
do anything to get you to fight,
but you just have
to ignore her.
She might even try to
turn your friends against you.
Oh! I'm not worried about that.
It's just you and Hitoe
and I trust you guys.
[GIRL H] Ru-ru!
[BOTH gasp]
So glad you're
finally here!
Yeah, I'll say!
So what up, girlfriend?
[RUKO] Wha...?
Oh, guess what?
We all just got a really
cool text from Akira.
She's got a shoot
this afternoon,
and she said we can
come if we bring you.
[GIRL H] She'll give us
a tour of the studio
if we all go together.
There's a chance we might
get to meet Iona, too!
Sorry. Appreciate the offer,
but we've already got plans.
You weren't invited
so shut your face!
What?!
C'mon, Ru-ru.
Come with us!
Um... But I--
Watch yourself.
[MALE TEACHER] "There is no
stronger bond of friendship
than a mutual enemy."
Frankfort Moore.
All right. That's about
it for today, class.
Tomorrow we'll start with--
[door opens]
Ruko, time to go!
Yuzuki.
[GIRL G] Talk about rude!
Where do you get off barging
your way in here and ordering
our friend around like that?
She's not your friend! Ruko!
Uh... Coming!
[GIRL H] You're going with us!
Hey! What's all this about?
You stay out of it!
Stubble Face!
What?! Stubble Face?
[RUKO grunts]
[ALL panting]
After them! And send
out a text to everybody!
[GIRL J] I've spotted 'em!
[KAZUKI] Go!
Move it, you jerk!
[YUZUKI] Over here!
[RUKO] Right!
[RUKO & YUZUKI panting]
Wow. They really want
to hang out with Akira.
No. Yuzuki, look. It's okay.
It's no big deal if
I gotta battle her.
[YUZUKI sighs]
But it is. Let me
put it this way.
Remember when I said I wish I
knew what you were thinking?
Yeah?
Still do.
But there is one thing I
know for certain about you.
You really like WIXOSS battles.
You're so happy when you play.
[YUZUKI] But battling Akira
is awful. It's painful.
Trust me, I know
from experience.
And I'm worried that playing
her will make you hate the game.
I don't want that to happen.
Yuzuki.
[running footsteps]
[GIRL I] Down this way?
[GIRL G] That's what
the first-years said!
This isn't good.
I'll draw them outside
and distract them.
So you just stay put, okay?
[RUKO gasps]
No. Wait.
Hey, don't worry.
Be back soon!
But--
[door opens]
[crash]
[GIRL I] There they are!
[GIRL G] Don't let
'em get away!
[running footsteps]
Dang it all.
I'm grateful to have a friend
who's so worried about me.
But the truth is...
[RUKO] It's better
if she doesn't know.
And I can't even explain it.
But I still want to do
this for some reason.
Am I nuts? Why do I want
to battle Akira so bad?
It's all I can think about.
[TAMA] Ru?
[RUKO gasps]
Ru and Tama are the same!
Want to battle Akira, too!
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA giggles]
[RUKO] There's something
scary about her.
[RUKO] But she and I...
We're the same.
[WOMAN] She's
frightening.
[WOMAN] I don't know
what Ruko's thinking.
There's something...
...scary about her.
[RUKO gasps]
That's not true!
[door opens]
Hey!
[GIRL G] Ru-ru...
Come out and play.
[GIRL G laughs]
[GIRL G] Guess who's here?
[AKIRA] Whoa, awesome-sauce!
Ladies! Thank you so much!
You asked and
we delivered!
You are the best! Up top!
[GIRLS giggle]
[AKIRA giggles]
[AKIRA] Well, Ru-ru! Let's go!
[GIRLS groan]
Um, Akira?
What about us?
Yeah I've got a shoot. Get lost.
[gasps]
But, I thought you said we
could hang out with you.
A top model like me hanging
with a bunch of uggos?
Not likely.
[GIRLS whimper]
[AKIRA giggles]
No one's gonna bother
us in here, Ru-ru!
So you ready to
throw down, or what?
[AKIRA giggles]
[RUKO] This is it. I'm
gonna play against Akira.
[door opens]
[AKIRA growls]
[IONA] Hey.
If you're lookin' for a
battle, give me a shot.
[RUKO] That's-!
Dammit! You skank-ass ho, stop
trying to steal my opponents!
You misunderstand,
I'm challenging you.
What?!
It seems you only like
to prey on rookies.
Guess you're just
scared of me.
[AKIRA growls]
[STAFF WOMAN] Akira! I've
been looking all over for you.
Come on, you're up.
[AKIRA] No, wait, I, um...
I need a few minutes! Okay?
We don't have a few minutes!
[AKIRA] No, stop shoving!
[STAFF WOMAN] We've got a
whole crew waiting on you,
so get the lead out!
[RUKO sighs]
Um. Thanks for
that great fake-out.
What fake-out? I was serious.
[RUKO gasps]
You wanted to have a
battle, didn't you?
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA] Perhaps you had
a grudge with Akira?
No wait. That's not it.
You'll battle anybody.
Anything to get
your fix. Am I right?
I am right.
So battle me.
Wait a minute.
[IONA] You have no wish.
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA] Participating as a
Selector without having a wish
is more than just wrong.
It's blasphemy.
That won't go unpunished.
Wait.
[RUKO] Blasphemy?
[RUKO] A WIXOSS party?
[YUZUKI] I might even find
another Selector to battle!
[HITOE] All this time,
I never noticed.
[YUZUKI] I just can't get my
hair tied up right, that's all.
[HITOE] I don't want to hear
you talk like that ever again!
[RUKO] She was also
kind of scary.
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Invalidated Vow."