What could be the cause of the massive mosquito outbreak this year?
We ask Mr. Kafetch, a mosquito expert who has written several books on the subject.
Thank you for having me.
Well, let me get right to the point.
These mosquitoes belong to an entirely new species.
Therefore, I know nothing about them.
Get out!
Ah, excuse me.
Now, let's take a look at the areas likely to be hit hardest by the outbreak.
Man, Z City's in their path.
Now we've got a mosquito outbreak? What's next?
We interrupt this program for breaking news.
A large swarm of mosquitoes has been sighted in Z City.
Mummified remains of attacked farm animals have also been found.
If you encounter a swarm of mosquitoes, flee immediately.
This is an emergency evacuation warning.
Threat level: Demon.
No resident is to go outside under any circumstances.
I repeat, no Z City resident is to go outside...
Acquiring target.
THE LONE CYBORG
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration
ore wa tomaranai
He's not gonna stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
Voices praise him far and wide
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fights evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are as numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and he ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
Thanks to that warning, they're all empty!
Like anyone's gonna die from a mosquito bite!
What's losing a little blood if I get all this?
The wind...?
What the—?!
Come on, you guys. That wasn't nearly enough.
Go get some more for me!
Target acquired.
I see.
You make them suck the blood and then take it all for yourself.
You must be controlling the mosquitoes via some sort of signal.
That would explain their mysterious behavior.
So if I were to get rid of you, the leader,
would the swarm disperse too?
Our next meal is here. Go drain him dry.
Incinerate.
I am about to eliminate you.
Stay right where you are.
You, eliminate me?
Go on and try!
Got you.
Damn... mosquitoes!
Incinerate.
Maybe a leg next?
Wait, where are my legs?
Futile.
You cannot escape from me.
What the hell is that guy?
He's gonna get me if I don't do something.
The townspeople may all be hiding,
but there are plenty of animals around.
Come here, little ones.
Empty all your stored juices into me!
So many.
If she's been collecting blood from the whole town and beyond,
then it may not be a simple food source for her.
I should put an end to this as soon as possible.
Get back here, dammit!
You and I aren't done yet!
What's with this guy?
It's in my mouth!
You little—!
Huh?
What's that squirming over there?
They're... mosquitoes?!
You over there.
Evacuate now.
That swarm is conscious.
If it senses you, it will immediately attack.
Seriously?
That's bad. I gotta get—
Since you spoke, I thought you would have at least human-level intelligence.
But you were just a bug.
You brought all the mosquitoes together into one, easy-to-burn swarm.
When I spotted you,
I confirmed there were no living beings within 500 meters,
so I should have been free to fire away.
Wait, that guy might have—
Man, you saved me. You're amazing.
What was that just now?
You totally made them bug out!
Get it?
Oh, I was just trying to make a joke about the mosquitoes being bugs, and...
Imbecile!
I no longer need those little ones.
I mean,
look...
how strong I've become!
Your punches can't even kill a little mosquito?
Weakling!
I see.
The more blood she consumes,
the more powerful she becomes.
I think I'll have your head next!
I let my guard down.
There's no chance of winning.
All I can do is self-destruct.
Forgive me, Doctor...
Mosquitoes... suck!
Hold on!
Please tell me your name!
Oh. It's Saitama.
Please make me your disciple.
Oh, okay.
Wait. What?
Master!
You really showed up.
Uh...
It's "Genos," Master Saitama.
Could you start by not calling me "Master"?
Maestro!
Don't call me that either!
Go on home after your drink.
I'm not looking for disciples.
Wait, you're back in one piece?
Yes, my body is mostly mechanical.
As long as there are parts, repairs are quick.
You're an odd one.
What kind of parts do you use, Master?
Don't use any.
Then what about the
skin-colored armor on your head?
Yeah, that's my skin.
But that would mean you're bald despite being so young.
So I'm bald! What's your problem?!
Me? You'll listen to my problems?
No thanks. I'm good.
Actually, four years ago, when I was 15,
I was still a normal human being.
Did you hear what I just said?
Although we had to pinch pennies,
my family and I lived a peaceful and fairly happy life.
But one day, a crazy cyborg went out of control and attacked our town.
The insane cyborg...
Most likely, a failed body modification generated an irregularity in his brain.
He destroyed everything in sight.
Parks, schools, buildings, my house...
He even took my family's lives.
Miraculously, I survived.
However, I was but a helpless 15-year-old,
and I found myself alone in a ruined town,
at the end of my strength.
That's when Doctor Kuseno happened to pass through.
Doctor Kuseno, a scientist for justice,
was on a mission to stop the destruction
caused by the rampaging cyborg.
I asked Doctor Kuseno to perform body modification surgery on me.
That's how I was reborn as a cyborg who fights for justice.
I promised Doctor Kuseno that one day I would terminate the evil cyborg.
I see—
It's been four years since that day.
I'm now 19, and I've been wandering from town to town, eliminating evil.
I have destroyed countless monsters and criminal organizations.
But I have been unable to find any clues about the insane cyborg
and have become increasingly frustrated and restless.
I find myself chasing a virtual image of that cyborg each time I square off against my enemies.
Then last week, when that
mosquito monster appeared,
I let my concentration slip.
I was convinced I could not lose to anything but the rampaging cyborg,
so I neglected to even analyze the data on my opponent and rushed to confront her.
The result, as you know,
was that an opponent with immense strength bested me.
If you, Master Saitama, had not been in the area,
I would have undoubtedly been destroyed.
Master, you saved my life.
I owe Doctor Kuseno my life, but now I am indebted to you as well, Master Saitama.
That debt weighs heavily on me.
I must not die before destroying that cyborg.
And to do that,
I must continue fighting evil as a righteous cyborg until he appears before me one day.
I need to get stronger.
Last week, when I saw your attack,
I knew I had to study under you as your disciple.
If only I could be as strong as you, Master Saitama!
I have an old enemy to defeat,
and not just for my own sake.
It will be for my hometown, and for Doctor Kuseno too.
I realize I am still inexperienced.
But right now, I need enormous power so I can eradicate the greatest of evils!
Doctor Kuseno is—
Enough, you idiot! Keep it to 20 words or less!
Mosquito Girl was defeated?
With one strike, you say?
Well, she was merely a prototype, after all.
Why is he naked?
Unknown.
Well, whatever.
He'll make an excellent specimen.
We shall study his physiology—by force if necessary.
Send a messenger and invite him here,
to our "House of Evolution."
Master, here's the short version:
Please teach me how to become strong like you.
Genos...
Yes!
How old are you?
19.
So young...
I'm sure you'll surpass me in no time.
Do you mean that?
I'm 25 now, but I was 22 in the summer I started training.
Sure, I'll teach you.
But it won't be easy. Can you handle it?
Yes, sir!
Object approaching at high speed. It's here!
What?
My name is...
Huh?
Pay for my ceiling!
So...
Hm?
It seems our advance agent, Kamakyuri, is down.
I can't sense him with my telepathy anymore.
What? Wasn't he one of our stronger guys?
There are two more outside.
Master, leave them to me!
Don't bust people's ceilings!
Oh, never mind.
Can't you guys just come through the door?
M-Master!
No, I'm fine.
I kinda feel like a... bamboo shoot.
Elevated energy levels detected.
A cyborg?
Could it be?
You are not the target.
What's going on? I can't see.
You are in the way!
I have a few questions for you.
It would appear you're in what they call a "tight spot."
Well done, Ground Dragon!
Ground Dragon
It complicates things if they put up a fight.
Master!
You dare look away?
Quite courageous!
I am the pinnacle of the House of Evolution's science.
I am Armored Gorilla.
Your attacks have no effect.
The "House of Evolution"?
What do they want with my master?
It is none of your business.
And it is our rule that any who oppose us are eliminated without fail.
I must destroy you.
Hey, jackass!
What's with that look?
Being underground keeps you cool,
but at the same time, it's nice and warm.
I'm sleepy. Could you get lost?
It seems I need to put you in your place.
Listen up!
I'm gonna slice your eyes out with these!
Then we'll see if you resist!
The Beast King never lets anyone off easy.
Well, enough fooling around.
If you wanna apologize, now's your chance.
You guys smashed my ceiling!
Fine.
Then behold the true power of the Beast—
Aw man...
I got dirt in my special place.
Hey, are you listening?
Ground Dragon
Let me just shake this out.
You done?
One sec.
I'm done.
Then behold the true power of the Beast King!
Lion Slash!
You okay, Frog Man—
Outta the way, pissants!
Such is the law of the jungle!
And you're next!
Wait! Don't kill him yet!
Lion Slash: Meteor Power Shower!
Consecutive...
Normal Punches.
Oh.
N-No one told me he'd be that strong!
We should retreat now and regroup...
Found you!
Are you fucking kidding me?!
Huh?
Answer me or be eliminated.
Your choice.
It is you who will be eliminated.
You fool.
I am the third most powerful fighter in the "House of Evolution."
At your power level,
you will never beat the Beast King, the second most powerful.
You will be destroyed.
You mean this guy?
Apparently so.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I'll tell you everything, just don't kill me!
What the—? What happened to your robot voice?
Sorry, I was just trying to sound cool.
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I close my eyes and think of you
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I want to see you... I feel like crying
romantikku na kibun
I feel so romantic
todokete kono omoi
I hope these feelings reach you
datte zutto shitteiru no
I know very well
ganbatteru koto takusan
how hard you work all the time
daisuki na hito ga
You're the one I love
tsuyokute shinpai
You're so strong but I'm still worried
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
I'll find you before any stars
massugu kaette kite ne
Come straight back home
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
What do you mean? The hit team was wiped out?!
It was inevitable.
How did this happen?
Wait, don't jump to conclusions yet.
Confirm the data once more.
Hurry! I said, hurry!
It may be a mistake.
That's not it.
We should report first.
I'll confirm.
Be careful.
Just what happened?
What's all the commotion?
Next Episode
The
Obsessive
Scientist
Okay, time for Mosquito Girl's episode preview!
Next week's story will be about my birthplace.
I was born—
What?! Time's up already?!
Oh, all right.
Next time, on episode three of One Punch Man:
"The Obsessive Scientist."
Scientist, huh? Who could that be?