“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
You're a parasite.
It must be a nice way to live.
I want to get stronger.
Strong enough so that I can suppress my anger.
Takashi! Takashi! Takashi! Takashi!
Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi Takashi!
Saika's goal is to love humans.
Then we can all love each other!
It's okay if I let it all out, right?
I have lived my life depending, relying on Saika to love them for me.
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Look, Anri, you're up so high!
That is false...
Good for you, Anri!
That is real.
Heiwajima... Heiwajima...
He's strong.
No, he's scary.
No, he's cool!
I've always thought that he was really strong,
but not this strong.
Do you think that something's happened?
Want to go and check it out for me?
Either way, you're not doing anything right now, are you?
It's a special material, like my scythe is.
It should hold up against their blades.
Thanks.
Well then...
Shifts and Changes
That katana... is Saika?
Then, the one who attacked me back then was...
You... your parents?
Your baby Saika didn't teach you how to fight, did it?
Please... tell the other Saikas to stop.
If the parent orders them to, then the children should stop.
If you've been cursed by Saika, then I can order it with my own Saika,
since it's the parent of yours.
There's no way I am!
I overcame Saika. With the power of love!
If you know what love is, then don't tell me that!
I will let you listen,
to a few of the loving words that Saika constantly echoes inside me.
I love you. I like you. I really like humans.
That's not it. I love all humans.
That was false.
Stop it!
That was true.
Her father, an antique dealer,
expressed his resentment for his failing business,
through violence towards his family.
Consequently, she began to close off her mind against it.
That was when the slasher showed up.
I love you...
The slasher's true identity was her own mother.
I love you! I love you!
Our love should have been etched onto him!
When we hurt him,
our thoughts should have flowed into him,
along with our fears and pain!
Does Heiwajima Shizuo not feel fear?
Get it right already, guys.
Everyone's afraid of me, so nobody loves me?
Don't make me laugh. I'm the one who's afraid!
Afraid that I would fail to overcome your power and screw something up.
That's right. I'm the world's biggest coward.
What about it, though? Being a coward won't stop me from kicking your butts.
Also, I can't get beaten in front of the people who love me, right?
How can you stand that voice?
I'm a person who lacks many things.
Therefore, I live like a parasite to compensate for what I lack.
I don't have a heart big enough to love people, and that's why I can keep listening to its voice.
Always objectively.
I've done it!
There's no way I'd lose to you!
Why are you so afraid?
Cutting people is just the result of love.
You let me cut you on purpose? Why?
I'm about to do something terrible to you. So that way, we'll be even.
I'm going to cast a spell on your mind with my Saika.
I won't apologize.
If I apologized again, it would go against my personal code.
I think I'm being dishonest.
I'm trying to protect my own peace of mind by doing something terrible to you.
However, it can't be helped.
I am a parasite, after all.
Saika is a lonely being.
It may not seem like it to us,
but she truly loves humans.
So, Niekawa-senpai, please love Saika back.
Because unlike me, senpai, you have the capacity to love.
Stop!
Come on, stop!
What are we doing here?
What? What?
Not even a single one of you died?
Finally.
Finally, you listened to me.
Anri! Is that Anri?
That was the girl who stabbed me earlier,
so I made her change schools so that she wouldn't be a problem.
She hadn't given up–
Anri, let's get out of here.
Sonohara, I've kept an eye on you this whole time.
That's right, Harima!
Who do you have to thank for Harima being in the same class as you?
I've already paid you back for that.
Paid back?
You mean just now?
I previously thought that the black rider was the slasher.
And so I thought you'd get attacked, sensei,
but I lost myself trying to help you.
It's not because I liked you.
I just wanted to pay you back for what you did.
What are you talking about?
Why were you being followed by the black rider?
What did you do?
She was that guy?
What did I...
Anri! Why are you holding that thing?
You too? Are you the same?
Are you going to...
No. I'm different from Niekawa-senpai...
...in that I hate you, sensei.
A tsurupeta! It's this again!
Speaking of which, what was in the new volume of Dengeki Bunko?
A 3-D photo and more.
Nothing can go wrong if we use this car.
Oh, is that so?
That's right.
I wonder if they'll have the new volume of Kino's Journey.
I wonder if they'll have Shizu's Journey.
Look how neat the Samoeda Mask guy is!
I knew this would happen if we left it up to Yumasaki.
...like that other guy!
Dammit.
Maybe it's his attitude?
Togusa-san, your face is red.
Are you sure you don't have a fever?
Shut up!
Are you really okay, Sonohara-san?
Yeah. It's nothing serious.
I was surprised when Masaomi told me.
Are you really all right?
And, where did Masaomi go?
He went home a little while ago.
There was something he had to do.
Seriously, what could he have to do at a time like this?
It's really nothing.
Did you talk to the police?
There are a lot of people who got hurt besides you, Sonohara-san.
It's okay.
No it isn't!
I have a feeling that nothing else like this is going to happen.
Why?
Sorry.
Actually, a couple hours before I got hurt,
I was attacked by the slasher.
Then some people came to save me,
and a few of them were really cool.
C-Cool people?
What kind of story is this?
Yeah.
One of them was a bartender with sunglasses...
No way. Was that Shizuo-san!?
And the other one was super-cool.
Don't be too surprised, okay.
It was the headless rider!
Wait a minute!
We only talked a little, but she was really active,
and I'm sure she can love people...
You don't believe me, do you?
I do, or rather...
She's a woman!?
When I got attacked after that,
the headless rider saved me again.
Therefore, I think everything is going to be okay.
Well, I mean, that person...
I can't say it. If I say it...
Those people have a very different life unlike our own.
It's best not to get too involved with them.
Ryugamine-kun. Do you know what it means to have an unusual life in this world?
When nothing happens.
When you do the same thing every day, and nothing happens,
and nothing changes.
That's the real thing.
I'll have a doctor I know look at this girl.
Don't worry.
Celty-san. I...
Don't apologize. You did what you thought was right.
Actually, I think you did the right thing back then with your teacher too.
Well, knocking my head off was probably too much,
but I only have Saika to blame.
I'm not sympathizing with you.
I just don't think that I would've won if we had fought.
If you're still not satisfied,
then use the power you have to volunteer around town.
She obtained power. The power to manipulate to her will a group of over one hundred Saikas.
She felt that her power was a heavy burden. Nevertheless, it was also what she wanted.
She felt like she had pinned herself to the ground
with the pressure that came from grasping people's fates.
Just then, she heard a voice. "I don't love you, but I don't hate you."
Perhaps she only imagined that she'd heard it. Even if she asked it questions, it didn't reply.
Still, that was okay. It made her just a little bit happy.
She had finally returned to her normal life.
However, she couldn't tell them the truth.
About Saika, or about the person behind the entire incident.
She found out about "him" by controlling the other Saikas and by tracing Niekawa Haruna's memories.
She didn't know his goal.
Yet, if that person wanted to destroy the peace enjoyed by Mikado, Masaomi and herself...
Smeared with both insecurity and determination,
she remembered the name of the perpetrator.
His name was...
Orihara Izaya.
That sure is a weird name.
It may be a coincidence that I was raised the way I was,
but I think it fits me perfectly.
Do you believe in coincidence, Namie-san?
What do you mean?
They all probably think that a lot of what just happened was coincidence.
Although, I was the one who caused Nasujima to leave when he did.
He really was stupid, though.
He could've found out where Sonohara Anri lives
simply by stealing the class roster.
Well anyway, I did some research with the assumption that they really existed,
and sure enough they do exist... demon swords, fairies and the like.
That's right. When Nasujima took my money and ran, that was coincidence.
Nasujima, who was being hounded for the money he owed,
wanted to extort it from the father of his stalker, Niekawa Haruna.
He found out about me from the experts on dirty money, the Awakusu Club,
and came to find out more about her family.
Yes, what is it?
Why thank you.
Sure enough, he took the bait I laid out for him.
I had found out that Niekawa Haruna was a Saika.
I thought that by threatening him with the line, "You bastard, you took my money!" that I could lure Haruna out.
However, instead of a copy, the real Saika showed up.
What happened to Nasujima, you say?
G-Give me your money!
If you ask me, it would've been better if Shizu-chan had died.
Well, whatever.
It all worked out just like I planned.
Like you planned?
What is it?
There are a lot more policemen around, aren't there?
The media's having a field day, too.
Something happened in South Ikebukuro Park, right?
They say it was just a brawl.
It wasn't the slasher?
What was it then? That man didn't seem to know, either.
He didn't remember anything. It was like he'd been hypnotized.
The police say they think it was a fight between color gangs.
It's not just the police.
Wanna try dying?
Bou-chan, you have mail.
What's this?
Is this from the leader of the Dollars?
Calm down, Mikado.
In that case, what is it you're planning?
At this point, the city has been divided into three groups: the Dollars, the Kokinzoku, and an army of demon swords.
However, some of the demon sword army members are mixed in with both the Dollars and the Kokinzoku.
Honestly, Niekawa Haruna would've been fine as long as I could use her to make my demon sword army,
but Sonohara Anri is even more interesting.
And?
Right now, the kindled ashes are enough.
If we leave them alone, those ashes will smoulder, and smoulder...
I can't wait!
However, the Kokinzoku was formed by a middle school kid, right?
Are they really that big a deal?
The fact that a mere kid can gather that many people together,
is a threat in itself.
Well, he may be the Shogun of the Kokinzoku, but he isn't someone I don't know.
Don't pull me back in.
The Dollars are doing it! They think they can do as they please.
We won't do anything without our senpai!
Not your senpai! Your Shogun!
I'm sorry!
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm not a Shogun now. I'm just a normal guy.
Or should I say, just a...
Just a high schooler.
Yeah, I just wanted to be a high schooler.
I had found the peace that I wanted.
I was surrounded by friendly people, and only lived a moderately dangerous life.
I can't forgive you for taking that away.
I really can't forgive you for making a move on Anri.
No matter how many there are, we will crush the slashers.
If it turns out the Dollars are backing them up,
then we'll crush the Dollars as well!
You've pulled me back in. Damn it.
Damn it!
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Life and Death Orders
Durarara
Next time on
I'm back.
I didn't want to come back, but I'm still back here.
To settle the score between Saki, myself, and that man's past.
Next time: Life and Death Orders.