“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Why do you ask about the Dollars?
You don't want to join the Dollars, do you?
What did you say?!
Why does my head have another body in the first place?!
Maybe there was a freshly made corpse.
How exciting. How exciting! How exciting!
And what do you think will happen to us if the police catch so much as a glimpse of them?
I don't care if she's dead or alive. If you have to, eliminate her on sight!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Looks like I'm a bit tight on money this month.
Next I'll need a kitchen sponge, and...
Thank you very much!
The black motorcycle!
If I turn this corner, he should be there.
I-I'm sorry. Are you all right?
You're...
Help me!
Please!
The black bike!
Look! This is so cool!
I'm taking a picture! I have to take one!
Totally!
Oh my god!
The First and Last
So in short, a hot girl, who you ran into on the corner, was being chased by a bad guy, and what's more,
she's lost her memory, so she got tired and fell asleep on the staircase I just used.
And you want me to believe all this, which is, in more ways than one, a "dreamer's story"?
It's the truth. I can't help it.
It would be better if this was in the morning and we were about to be late for school, though.
And if it turned out she was transferring to our school, it'd be marvelous.
If, on top of it all, she was a princess of some country and you two happened to be childhood sweethearts, then it'd be perfect!
Do you realize that things are getting better and better by the second?!
Telling that to someone deliberately is probably the lamest thing you could do.
On top of not having any memories, she says she doesn't want to go to the police,
so I don't know what to do.
Guess we'll just have to wait and see what happens.
For the time being, we'll wait until tomorrow,
and then we'll hear her story from start to finish.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Thanks for coming out here this late.
Maybe the person on the black motorcycle recognized her face.
The motorcycle of urban legend.
If this means I'm up against that thing, what can I do?
I hated normal things.
I wanted to live a different life than everyone else.
Maybe it was because of those feelings that I decided to hide her.
There was one thing Kida-kun didn't know anything about...
...and that was her scar.
It looked like her head had been cut off with a saw and then forced back on.
This just in from the student store: the Jumbo Melon Bread is sold out for today.
Hey, Mikado! How did Sleeping Beauty do at your place?
Kida-kun!
What's that? What beauty?
You got my attention there!
Actually, Mikado here ran into a hot girl who is suffering from amnesia,
as she came around a corner while being chased by some scoundrel,
and now he and the hot girl are living together!
What? As if. Kirigamine wishes that would happen.
No, it's R-Ryugamine.
Hey, does anyone want the rest of my food?
There! Nobody believes you, so it's all right.
So, what's she up to? The hot girl.
She was still asleep when I left this morning.
Gorgeous must've crashed pretty hard. Well now, let's get to the real subject.
Real subject?
The reason why I came up to the fourth floor for an early lunch,
and why I'm using my break time as efficiently as I can, is this.
"Dollars Number of Members Estimate..."
It's gotten to be quite a popular topic in our class.
Everything about the Dollars is shrouded in mystery.
So, I'm asking people in our school to vote for who they think of as:
"Hey, that guy looks like a member of the Dollars,"
just for fun.
There sure are a lot of votes.
Each person can vote for multiple people.
Huh? This "Takeguchi" person from class 1-D only has one vote.
You noticed, did you...
That vote was cast by none other than Kida Masaomi.
He's in my gym class, and I think Takeguchi Ryou is, unmistakably, a member of the Dollars.
Why do you think that?
A hunch.
Therefore, I'm going to go find out right now.
Wait!
Excuse me! Is Takeguchi Ryou-kun here?
No, he's not.
Cafeteria?
I dunno. The roof maybe? I do see him go upstairs during lunch a lot of the time.
I wonder if Ryou-kun's having "smoking time" up there?
Shouldn't we give it up? There might be scary people up there with him.
I'm kidding. Smoking on the roof is something you only see in an old, clichéd manga.
Still, I don't think he'd tell us if we asked, "Are you a member of the Dollars?"
Let me handle it. I have an idea.
S-Smoking.
Hey, Takeguchi! 'Sup!
Yo.
Takeguchi, you write music?
Yeah, sorta.
What's up? Is there something you wanted?
There's something I want to ask you.
Fire away.
Are you a member of the Dollars?
K-Kida-kun! What are you–
Yeah, I am.
I knew it. I always thought you were.
See? My hunches are 100 for 100.
This guy is an old friend of mine.
I-I'm Ryugamine Mikado.
You're that famous guy?
Famous?
It's your name.
Want some?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey... Takeguchi-kun...
Why did you join the Dollars?
I kinda wish people would quit asking me that.
It was about half a year ago, I think.
I got a text from someone; I don't know who invited me.
It said, "There are no rules or restrictions for the Dollars."
At first I thought that there's no way a gang like that exists,
but still, if there was, I thought it'd be pretty cool.
I'm not the kind of person who likes being given orders.
So, what kind of gang are the Dollars?
You could say they're colorless and clear.
Colorless and clear?
Yeah. Unlike the Kokinzoku or the Blue Squares,
they don't compete with other gangs by getting people to wear the same color.
"Blue Squares"?
They're a gang that was at their peak when I was in middle school.
I don't know much about them, but apparently they caused trouble and destroyed stuff.
Kida-kun?
So you're interested in the Dollars, Takeguchi-kun?
Yeah.
Do you meet with the other members?
There are other members, but I don't know anything except for their screen names.
I have met some of them, however. At work, or around town.
Although only by coincidence. I could sorta just tell they were, and I was right.
Like, what kind of people?
Well, you guys would know. Ask people.
Just like you asked me. Most of them will answer you.
Oh, dang.
Gotta run!
I've never told anyone since I found out that Takeguchi-kun was a real Dollars member.
Mikado.
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
I didn't think he'd like having a fuss made over him like that. I also thought that only the people who asked should know.
Attention! Teacher's here.
Stand. Bow.
That is all. Our representative meeting is now over.
I wonder if Kida-kun's still in the public morals rep meeting?
It should be over soon.
Harima Mika-san, who had been stalking Yagiri Seji, was still missing like she had been the day before school began.
Have you found out anything about Harima-san since then?
No, nothing.
Ryugamine!
Kida says to go on home without him.
What happened to Kida-kun?
They're having some kinda big argument in the public morals meeting.
Well, I'll see ya!
Shall we go, then?
Yes.
I wonder what Kida-kun's arguing about.
Maybe uniforms, or hair, or–
Mikado!
Listen closely to what that hot chick says!
You gotta introduce me to her next time!
Great! See ya!
H-Hotchique-san is a French person we met at the Russian sushi place,
and... and, she has a nose piercing,
so Kida-kun must be arguing about nose piercings in there!
I've actually known you for a long time, Ryugamine-san.
Back when we submitted our entrance applications,
there was a paper, which had a list of all the people, where you had to check off your name.
I thought one of the names was really cool when I saw it,
and just then someone came and checked it off.
And now, it turns out that I'm acting as class representative with that person...
Wait a minute.
Isn't this just like what happened with Harima Mika-san and Yagiri Seji-kun?
This isn't good; I have a stalker! No, there's no way a cute girl like this could be one.
No. Wait, wait. She can't be. If I'm not careful...
I'll get stabbed! Or I'll get my house set on fire!
Wait, wait! If I had my family taken hostage...
However, if she's this nice of a person, maybe it's good that she's my stalker.
No, wait, she's not a good person just by being a stalker!
I'm kidding. You wouldn't want someone like me following you around.
W-Wait...
Don't worry. I'm not a stalker.
N-No–
I'm sorry.
No, I was the one making fun of you. Don't apologize.
I'll enjoy working with you from here on out.
The pleasure is all mine.
Takeshi! It's this guy! This guy!
Who does she mean by, "this guy"? It's not me, is it?
It's you, you! Don't play stupid!
Who are you exactly?
Thanks to your friend, I had to buy a new cellphone!
I'm not entirely sure what you mean.
You're a friend of the guy who broke my girl's phone, aren't you?
No, I wouldn't say we're friends.
Then what is he? Your dad? Your co-signer?
I find that reasoning a little biased.
Are you trying to preach to me?!
I'll teach you what the hierarchy is here–
I don't make a habit of hitting girls.
How admirable of me!
I would make you my girlfriend, but sorry,
you're just not my type.
Get lost!
You're so mean!
See you later!
Well, Ryugamine Mikado-kun,
I've been hiding, waiting by the school entrance so I could meet with you.
There's something I want to talk about.
By the way, why is the black biker here?
She's looking for her.
I forgot! Sorry. I'm in a hurry today.
Sonohara-san, I'll see you.
This is too surreal.
Still, at this rate these people will follow me all the way home.
If that happens...
Save me!
If you have any business with me, I'll hear you now.
I'll save mine until the black biker's finished.
Hello? Thanks again for your business.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
She can communicate her thoughts.
What exactly are you?
I'm looking for the daughter of a relative who's gone missing.
I found her yesterday, but for some reason she ran away.
She's terrible at lying.
P-Pardon me. That's a bit hard to believe.
How much do you know about me?
You're a kind of urban legend,
and you ride a motorcycle, without any headlights, that doesn't make any engine noise.
Also...
you have no head.
Do you believe that?
Would you show me? What's inside that helmet?
I didn't think I was brave enough to ask something like that.
You won't scream, will you?
However, I felt as if I'd been waiting for this moment for a long time.
I still don't know how to describe what I felt at that moment.
I just kept repeating to myself, "I knew it, I knew it."
Thank you.
After that, the legendary black biker told me the real reason she'd been following that person.
About how she was a Dullahan named Certy. How she had come to Japan looking for the head she had lost.
How the person with stitches around her neck had a face that looked just like hers.
Normally, all of it would seem unbelievable, but strangely, I believed her.
Are you a friend of that girl?
No. I just met her yesterday.
I asked her a lot of questions, but it appears she's lost a lot of her memories.
Certy-san?
Can you let me meet with that girl?
I think it's probably because you started chasing her for no reason,
but she's afraid of you.
I want to meet with that girl, at any cost.
Can you try and clear up this misunderstanding?
Understood.
Nothing like fruit milk in the afternoon.
In the end, I think that this development means she's suddenly gonna turn into a shocking heroine.
No, no, no, she's obviously a goddess-heroine!
Damn it, I'll teach you to mess with me!
Hey!
What the hell're you doing?
That bastard, he hit...
He hit my car with a pebble!
Calm down, Togusa!
I'm not letting that bastard get away with it!
Red light, red! Red! Red!
Wait here a minute. I'll try to explain the situation to her.
I don't want her to see you first and think I've betrayed her.
Got it.
Wise kid, isn't he?
That's the first time I've heard your name.
I didn't know you were a foreigner.
Liar.
Next time you throw a rock at my horse, I won't let it go just like that.
That's a horse, then?
Even so, he sure is taking his sweet time, that guy.
A cleaning company at a run-down apartment like this?
No way...
Come on, where did that girl you were hiding run off to, Nii-san?
That's all we want to know.
This hair that was on the futon, it belongs to a woman.
I really don't know! P-Please, let...
Let me go!
You've already seen our faces.
We may as well finish you here.
Hey! Someone's coming!
I-I'm saved!
No need to follow them. I know where they came from.
I recognized the van. Those guys were with Yagiri Drug Manufacturing.
Yagiri... Drug Manufacturing?
That's right. They're pretty much a puppet company that's about to fail and get sucked up by a big foreign capital group.
A woman who lost her head.
A Dullahan.
Missing people.
Harima Mika.
Yagiri Seji.
Slave trafficking.
And the Dollars.
What's he trying to start?
I hate normal things.
To tell the truth, I half doubted it.
I'm begging you, please help me for a little while.
I wanted to live a different life than everyone else.
The chess pieces are now in my hand.
And so...
Jackpot!
I...
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Storm and Stress
Next time:
Durarara!!
I hated normal things.
I wanted to live a different life than everyone else.
However, I didn't think that alone would alter the fate of so many people.
Next time: Storm and Stress.