We asked Dr. Wakaouji to be Full Moon's producer, but...
...for some reason, he wouldn't accept the position.
Producer's Chair
I tried all sorts of things, but to no avail.
We were ready to give up on Dr. Wakaouji...
Or, so we thought...
But then, he suddenly said that he would be the producer!!
Looks like something Takuto said made him come to that decision.
But I wonder what is was that he said?
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
It's Shii-chan's Music Power !
Hi!
Covering for Shii today... Oda Shizuo!
Is everyone feeling great?
Now then, let's go straight to this week's top news!
Full Moon's pro ducer
is someone from  the past!?
Full Moon's producer
is someone from the past?!
It seems that the former Prince of Route L...
...is making a comeback to the music scene as Full Moon's producer.
Well done, Ooshige-chan.
I never thought that you'd net that Wakaouji-kun.
Well, let's both do out best.
Yes!
And what's more, the song is one that everyone knows!
Route L's mystical and famous song...
It's a cover of Eternal Snow.
In fact, regarding this song...
...Takasu Kouhei is also planning on releasing this song with the new artist Wakamatsu Madoka.
How intriguing, it looks like the arrival of a powerful rival for Takasu Kouhei.
For pop singers back in the sixties...
...there were often problems where different singers would sing the same song,
but nowadays, we almost never see that happen.
That's why this is such a hot topic.
He's late.
Ah, he's here!
Wakaouji-sensei!
Eh?
Wakaouji-sensei...
Those clothes...
T-They don't suit me, huh?
Well...
In order to rediscover my feelings,
I decided to try this out.
No, they totally fit you!
You look cool!
R-Really?
Yep!
What I Want to Say...
Yeah, this is Takasu.
How's it going?
Ah, okay, okay.
I'm counting on you.
Bye.
Um, it'll be okay, right?
By okay, you mean...
...whether or not you'll win?
Yes...
You want to win.
That's why you called me, right?
Y-Yes.
Then, get that look off your face.
Have faith in me!
Y-Yes.
Yes, yes, that's the look.
That's the face of Wakamatsu Madoka.
Yes.
What?
You're already done?
That was fast.
No, no, that's great.
Send it my way then.
What?
You've already sent it?
You're fast, Kumi-chan!
I can't lose.
Delivered as promised.
There's no way I can lose.
Y-You haven't decided?!
Yes.
T-That's not a good thing, is it...
Even under these circumstances...
Full Moon's Second Single Concept Meeting
I don't think that planning ahead is what's important here.
Coming up with something that everyone agrees with...
...that's what our job is.
Even if you say that, our schedule is...
Ah, but...
If we went through a superficial routine to arrange a song...
...and only worried about the schedule, I'm not sure how things would work out.
Superficial?!
I just...
Ah...
We can do something about the schedule.
But if we don't decide on a concept...
Right?
That's right.
Without that, we can't decide whom to ask to arrange it.
We won't be able to decide which staff members to use either...
That's why, by all means...
...we'd like you to decide as soon as possible.
Full Moon.
Y-Yes!
Full Moon, through this song...
...what's the number one thing that you want to say to your fans?
Eh?
To my fans?
Um...
That's...
You don't need to be specific.
Ah, okay.
Um...
That's...
It's okay.
You don't have to answer right now.
Spend some time thinking about it.
I'll give you plenty of time.
O-Okay...
Full Moon's Second Single Concept Meeting
That's it for today.
See ya.
Full Moon's Second Single Concept Meeting
Man... what are we supposed to do?
I'm worried now...
Sure, he may have talent...
...but can he really do something like this?
Don't worry about it.
Have faith in that doctor.
Eh?
A... w-well...
You looked like you were fretting over something...
Ah, I was just thinking.
I've been only thinking about what I wanted to say to Eichi-kun this whole time.
I never realized it until it was mentioned, but...
What I want to say with this song...
Just what is it...?
A-Ah...
That's what it was.
Hmm... what you want to say, huh?
Children's
Dictionary
Japanese
Let's see...
Eternal... Eternal...
Edamame?
Of course that's not it!
What that doctor was saying wasn't about understanding the lyrics.
It's something much simpler.
Eh?
Here's an example.
Let's say someone hears you sing Eternal Snow...
Will they burst into tears?
Or will it give them courage?
Or will it force them to smile?
Or will it make them unable to hold in their laughter?
Hey.
You're overdoing it.
Sorry.
Like that.
That's what he meant.
So?
How about it?
Eh?
Well, try thinking it out carefully.
Huh?
Have you found an answer?
Nope...
Don't tell me...
You didn't stay up again, did you?
I slept enough.
But I woke up because something was bothering me.
What is bothering you?
What were my father's feelings when he wrote this song?
Hmm?
Hey...
That's right, what kind of a person was your father?
I dunno...
Not just my father...
Nothing about my mother, either...
Even though they're your parents?
The story that the teacher at the orphanage told me was that...
...my mother died right after giving birth to me...
When I was one, my father...
...became a star in the sky...
After that...
...she also told me that my father was a musician.
So, I started listening to the songs he wrote.
And then, two years ago...
I'll be living with you from now on!
I'm Mitsuki!
When Grandma took me in...
...I tried asking her about it, but...
There's nothing to say.
Grandma...
It seems like she hates talking about my mother and father.
Up to this every day, I haven't learned anything.
In that case, let's try asking that doctor.
Eh?
'Cause...
...he was in the same band as your father, right?
That's good!
Let's try that, Mitsuki.
You might discover some hints.
Well...
...I only knew the two of them while they were in the band.
Your mother, Hazuki-san...
...always helped out where she could.
In age...
...she was younger, but...
...she was like an older sister.
A very kind person.
Then, one day...
...I learned that Hazuki-san was pregnant...
You're going to elope?!
H-Hold on a second!
We're about to go on tour!
If you, the leader, disappear...
Hello?
Hello?!
Aoi-san?!
She was pregnant with me, right?
Yes.
But...
...your grandmother was against their marriage.
Our leader, your father...
...Aoi-san disappeared...
...and Route L was forced to break up.
After that...
...I had no idea what happened to Aoi-san and Hazuki-san.
But then, two years ago...
Come...
Mitsuki-san.
N-Nice to meet you!
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki!
Please take good care of me!
I thought that you looked like Hazuki-san, but...
...I never suspected that it was true.
Of course, when I was around your grandmother, I never said a word.
Father... Mother...
So?
Did you find any hints?
Ah... yes. Um...
Could it be that...
...my father wrote that song for my mother?
Could be.
I want to know more!
More about my father and mother...
Maybe there's a memento or something that they left behind?
Let's go look!
Yeah!
If we look around the house...
...there might be something.
You think there is?
We're talking about your grandma here.
She might have thrown it all out.
We won't know that until we look.
Where?
Ah.
If there is something, then is should be there ...
...in the shed!
Madoka can't answer the phone right now.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Hi!
Madoka?
It's me.
You've been so distant lately.
Let's play together like we used to!
Acting this seriously...
It's not like you.
Full Moon...
I won't lose to someone like you!
I might have come a little too early.
Good morni...
Takasu-san!
Takasu...
He was up all night...
Up until now...
...the people of this world...
Everyone has been cold to me.
This is the first time...
Takasu-san.
I...
In order to live up to your expectations...
...I'll do my best.
Huh?
This is...
Wow!
It's an old issue of Ribon!
My mother read Ribon too, huh...
I feel so close...
Lemme see. Lemme see.
Look at this, Meroko.
This is hilarious!
Hey!
Do you think we're playing around here?!
Ah.
That's right.
Come on...
Huh?
No!
A mouse!
It's a mouse!
Takuto!
This looks relatively new.
Over here!
This mouse is...!
No!
Takuto!
Look out!
Eh?
This is..
The box is the only thing here that looks particularly new.
Open it up and take a look inside.
Okay.
Hey, you... that was dangerous!
But...!
I was so scared!
Just from that...?
Ah... me?
What is it?
No...
This isn't me...
This is... my mother...
She looks just like you.
A jeweled music box, huh?
Eh?
Is it broken?
H-Hey...
This is...
To Hazuki, with love...
Eh?
So this is from my father?
Most likely.
The music box my father gave my mother...
They're inside of here...
My father's...
...feelings for my mother...
That's right.
I want to hear them...
My father's feelings...
It's a good song.
Yep.
Well?
Warm...
This warm feeling...
How can I describe it...
Ah... I can't put it into words...
Hey, that's your phone.
Y-Yeah.
Ah... Mitsuki?
Ah... a job suddenly came up.
Can you come out now?
Y-Yes.
I'll be outside, then.
I understand.
A job suddenly came up.
What?
Hurry up.
I'll stay at home.
Okay.
Eh?
What?!
C-Crap, she's found us!
Did she find out...?
I wonder...
Hazuki...
Eh?
Hazuki!
Where are you going?
I'm pregnant with that man's child.
What did you say?!
That man's child...?!
If you won't accept it...
I'll leave this house!
Hazuki!
With a body as weak as yours...
If you give birth to a child...
Hazuki!
Music...
I hate music...
Always... taking away everything important to me...
What's that?
It was a present from my father to my mother.
Ooshige-san.
I've found out what I want to say.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
What is it?
I want to make people feel warm inside with my music.
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I even want people who hate music...
...fall in love with music.
That's right, isn't it?
Father... Mother...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
Takuto! We've got a problem!
Full Moon  and Dr. Wakaouji...
A magazine says that they're having a steamy love affair!
Huh?
That can't possibly be true!
How did that happen?
It's gotta be the work of Wakamatsu Madoka again!
Even up to the bitter end... that girl...
One problem down, and another pops up, huh?
At this rate, we'll never get to the recording!
What are we supposed to do?!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
I Will not Lose
Look forward to it.