How would you rate Rider's Noble Phantasm?
Equal to Gilgamesh's Gate of Babylon.
In other words, it is utterly immeasurable.
Exactly as we anticipated.
Had we faced Rider
with no foreknowledge of
his Noble Phantasm,
we would not have been able
to formulate a defense.
The second act begins now.
We will use the information
Assassin gathered
to mobilize Archer and
exterminate our enemies.
And in the process, the way to
handle Rider will present itself.
Yes.
You have completed your part
as a Master admirably.
I believe
that every Assassin,
without exception, took part
in last night's attack.
Understood.
By the way, Maiya,
how is the new workshop progressing?
I plan to take Madam and Saber there
tomorrow morning.
Thanks.
Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
No movement from the Tohsaka estate.
Since Assassin’s sneak attack
at the war's opening,
Tokiomi's been holed-up
behind his fortifications.
It's so quiet, it's unsettling.
At first glance, the Matou
Master appears defenseless,
an easy target.
However...
Given Berserker's unusual ability,
if for no other reason than to keep
Archer and Tohsaka in check,
it's best to let him be for now.
Lord El-Melloi should now be
effectively incapacitated,
but Lancer is still active.
We should uncover his new Master
as soon as possible.
Caster's whereabouts are still unknown.
But last night,
several more children were reported missing.
Their unscrupulous rampage
continues unabated.
Rider and his Master always travel
in his flying Noble Phantasm,
which makes him difficult to track.
Despite his open-hearted exterior,
he is a fearsome and vigilant opponent.
Furthermore, given Maiya's report,
his Ionioi Hertairoi
has me concerned, as well.
But above all else...
Is it prudent to assume
that Assassin is truly finished for good?
But what of his Master?
If his plan was to ally with Tohsaka and
use Assassin to gather intel,
then he shouldn't have ventured
outside the Fuyuki Church.
But he did.
His ambush at the Fuyuki Hyatt...
His infiltrating the Einzbern forest...
It doesn't make sense.
This only explanation
is that I am his target.
But why?
Why me?
Until two days ago,
he couldn't have known that
I am Saber's true Master.
Kotomine Kirei,
who are you?
I see that you're in
a good mood again today,
Archer.
I'm still uncertain as to the
Holy Grail's true value,
but even if it's mere scrap,
I no longer care.
Something more interesting
has caught my attention.
Kirei, for once,
you appear to be in fine spirits, as well.
I'm simply relieved.
At long last,
that troublesome burden has been
lifted from my shoulders.
What becomes of your Command Spells,
now that they have vanished?
Theoretically,
they should return to the Holy Grail.
When a Servant is defeated,
the Master is removed from contention,
and the Grail reclaims the Command Spells.
Further,
should a Servant suddenly
find itself with no Master,
the Grail will redistribute the
unused Command Spells
to a newly chosen Master.
As long as the Command Spells are unused,
they remain in this world.
And at the war's conclusion,
any remaining Spells go to
the war's mediator.
Then, depending on how things play out,
we could see a new Master enter the fray?
Correct.
But bear in mind, the Grail acknowledges
very few indeed.
That's why, even if there's an opening
for a new Master,
the Holy Grail will prioritize
those it has previously chosen.
Well?
Continue, Kirei.
That is the reason the Holy Church
grants asylum to defeated Masters.
In the event that an opening
for a Master appears,
there is a high probability that one of them
will be chosen to receive
the remaining Command Spells.
Hence,
participants in the Holy Grail War
seek to kill, not merely incapacitate,
any other Masters.
Well, Kirei, by that logic,
it's quite likely you'll obtain another set
of Command Spells, no?
No.
If the Grail's expectation for me,
as Tokiomi surmised,
was to ensure the Tohsaka
family's advantage,
then I have fulfilled my role.
Tokiomi has already formulated a strategy
guaranteed to defeat the other Masters and Servants.
There is no further need for me.
How do you like driving, Saber?
This is a wondrous vehicle.
I find myself thinking how
it would have been,
having these in my era.
Irisviel,
are you sure you do not mind
my controlling this vehicle?
You always seem to enjoy a "drive,"
as you call it.
It's fine!
Seeing you happy makes me happy, too.
Another mysterious building!
As of today,
you two will use this as your base.
Oh, could you hold onto the keys, Saber?
As you wish, Irisviel.
Maiya,
what is this key for?
It is unlike all the others.
An earthen storehouse in the back yard.
It's quite old,
but I have determined that
it is structurally sound.
I had no time to prepare,
so this may not be an ideal place to live.
Don't worry.
As long as it keeps the rain out,
you'll have no complaints from me.
All right, Saber!
What do you say to us
exploring our new home?
Yes, let us.
It looks like this is one of this country's
traditional haunted houses.
I bet the halls have wooden flooring,
and the rooms have woven straw mats for floors,
with paper dividers between them.
I once told Kiritsugu I wanted
to see a Japanese house.
Maybe he remembered!
Well, does it meet your expectations?
Oh, yes...
I had my fun.
But as a mage's base,
it presents several obstacles.
Erecting barriers won't be a problem,
but it isn't really an ideal workshop.
All the open space
will let too much mana dissipate.
I would have preferred
a sealed room with stone or earthen walls.
Now, that's more like it!
It's a bit cramped,
but I can use the same spells here
that I did back at the castle.
For now, inscribing a magical circle
will solidify the area as my territory.
Let's begin preparing immediately.
Could I trouble you
to lend me a hand, Saber?
We need a magic circle over there,
about six feet in diameter.
All right.
I'll also need you to prepare the mercury.
Don't worry.  I'll help you to dispense it.
Okay, Saber,
could you run back to the car,
and retrieve the items we brought?
Irisviel,
may I ask a question?
I feel that you have deliberately
avoided touching anything all day.
Or have I imagined this?
The driving, the keys...
Those would hardly be a cause for concern,
but you are not even conducting
your own vital magical ritual.
If you aren't well,
please let me know
as soon as possible.
Should anything happen,
I have a sworn duty to protect you.
And I must be able to take
appropriate measures.
I'm sorry...
It's true
there wasn't any point in trying
to hide it from you.
Give me your hand.
Saber,
I'm going to squeeze your hand
as hard as I can, okay?
Yes...
Go ahead.
Irisviel?
This isn't a joke...
I'm squeezing with every ounce
of strength I have now.
Bending my fingers is hard enough...
Grasping or manipulating objects
is all but impossible.
Getting dressed this morning was brutal.
B-But what's wrong?
Are you injured?
I'm just a bit under the weather,
so I've cut off my sense of touch.
Shutting down one of my senses
allows me to suppress my spiritual energy.
But it won't prevent me from
carrying out other tasks.
This flexibility is one advantage
to being a homunculus.
It is not as simple as that!
To start with, where does
your weakness derive?
There must be a treatment!
You may have forgotten that
I'm not an ordinary human.
I cannot see a doctor if I catch a cold.
Think of it as
a structural defect originating in my body's creation.
It's fine.
Well, I say that,
but I'll have to inconvenience you
with a lot of requests.
From now on,
I'll have to leave the driving to you.
And you'll need to assist in
my spell-casting, too.
I apologize for all the trouble,
but I'm counting on you,
my knight.
Of course.
I apologize for prying
into affairs that were not my own.
Forgive me.
Don't worry about it!
Now, then...
Let's finish inscribing the circle.
If I rest within a magical circle properly
connected to the Earth's ley lines,
my condition should improve.
Understood.
I shall retrieve the supplies.
Saber's Master...
He's nothing but a mercenary
hired by the Einzberns, in the name
of their long-held obsession
to make the Holy Grail's descent a reality.
I'm glad that you finally realize that.
He's merely another mongrel,
just like the rest of them,
scrabbling after my treasure for the most
pathetic and mundane of reasons...
After all the trouble I went through
to discover their motives,
is that all you have to say?
It would seem my efforts
have been pointless.
Pointless?
What do you mean by that, Kirei?
All the hard work you and Assassin
put in has proven very helpful, has it not?
Do you mock me,
King of Heroes?
You don't see it?
Well, it's unsurprising.
You are a man who has yet
to understand the meaning of joy.
Even if you are unaware of it,
your soul instinctively pursues joy.
That instinct manifests on the surface
as curiosity or interest.
Thus, Kirei,
discussing with me those matters that
you have observed or learned of,
has been quite significant.
Your words have revealed
where your interest most heavily lies.
Let us first
disregard the man you've
intentionally omitted.
Any interest you're consciously
aware of is simple fixation.
Moving on...
Which of the remaining four Masters
interested you most passionately?
Berserker's Master...
Kariya, was it not?
Kirei,
you gave a report of exacting detail
regarding that man's activities.
His situation is extremely complicated.
Naturally, more information was
required to explain it.
I think not.
Rather, because you wished to understand
this "complicated situation,"
you ordered Assassin
to investigate him alone in such depth.
All to satisfy your subconscious interest.
I'll admit I made a poor decision.
In the long term, Matou Kariya
poses no real threat and
is not worth observing.
By misjudging his priority,
I have inadvertently invited
your unsought attention.
Is that so?
Can you imagine a scenario wherein,
by a miracle and sheer luck,
Berserker and his Master survive to the end?
Tell me what would happen next.
Come, Kirei...
Isn't it about time you realized
the true reason for my question?
Tell me, Archer.
What point is there in imagining
what might happen,
should Matou Kariya prevail?
There is none.
None at all.
Oh, don't look so angry.
Consider it...
How is it that Kotomine Kirei never
noticed the pointlessness
of this speculation?
Do you not find some undeniable
significance in that fact?
Enlighten me, Archer.
Had I posed to you
the same question, but about
one of the other Masters,
you would immediately have concluded
the exercise was pointless,
never even bothering to consider it.
But with Kariya,
the result was quite different.
Rather than dismissing
the thought instantly,
you allowed your imagination to
indulge in ridiculous speculation.
You completely forgot the futility,
not believing your effort wasted.
To put it simply, you enjoyed yourself.
Rejoice, Kirei.
You have learned
the meaning of entertainment.
Entertainment...
You speak of happiness?
Precisely.
There is no happiness
to be found in Matou Kariya's fate.
Every day he continues living
will only compound his agony.
His only salvation would be
a quick death.
Kirei...
Why must you define bliss so narrowly?
Where lies the contradiction
in seeing pain and suffering
as other forms of bliss?
There is no limit to the forms of happiness.
You remain confused because
you fail to comprehend this.
Because it is wrong!
King of Heroes,
one with your twisted tastes,
may find sweetness
in the misery of others.
But that reveals the soul of a sinner!
That is an evil which must be vanquished!
Above all, it is incompatible with my faith!
So you classify happiness itself as a sin.
You have utterly deceived yourself.
You truly are an intriguing man.
This pain...
Oh?
Just as I anticipated.
Though sooner than I'd expected, too.
It can't be...
There are no free Servants.
Why has a new Master been chosen?
Perhaps the Holy Grail
also harbors high expectations
for Kotomine Kirei.
Kirei,
you should heed the Grail's summons.
There is no question now
that you do indeed have a wish
for the Grail to grant.
I have a wish
for the Holy Grail?
If the Grail's power is truly omnipotent,
then it can show you the true form
of your deepest desire,
buried deep within your heart,
of which you are still unaware.
So you're saying that because
I have no idea of my desire,
I should take the Holy Grail for myself,
to learn my wish?
But...
First, I would have to destroy
the wishes of six others,
before that could happen.
If I truly sought the Holy Grail
for my own desire,
my teacher would become
my enemy, as well.
You'd better find the
strongest Servant you can,
if you mean to do battle with me.
You'll have to start
by stealing a Servant
still contracted to one
of the other Masters.
Then you could...
No, I won't say it.
What happens next is up to you.
Seek out your desire.
Your search will lead you
to entertainment.
That entertainment will bring enjoyment.
And that enjoyment will
give rise to true joy.
Your path is now clear, Kirei.
So clear, there can be no
room left to doubt.
Episode 12:
The Grail Beckons
I shall hit first!
If you wish to kill them,
here is your chance.
This ends now!
The world is filled with God's love.
Once more, we set out to
raise salvation's banner!
Next time
The Forbidden Feast of Madness