By my third Command Seal, I order you again.
Stop!
Saber, destroy...
the Grail.
How could he have figured me out,
having given me a mere three orders?
I never even knew the hearts of those
who served beside me.
Perhaps all of this...
is the punishment for a king who couldn't understand others...
That's...
Impossible...
It's impossible!
Kiritsugu...
What's wrong, Illyasviel?
I had a scary dream.
A dream
where I became a cup...
And inside me,
these seven big lumps appeared.
It felt like they'd tear me apart.
It was really scary.
But I couldn't run away...
Then I heard Lady Justeaze's voice.
On my head,
a big black hole opened up.
And then, the world burned.
Kiritsugu looked at it and cried.
Mother,
is Kiritsugu okay?
Is he scared and alone?
It's okay.
He's doing his best for you.
He'll make sure our prayers are realized.
So you'll never have to be scared again.
Yeah...
That's right...
That's right.
Kiritsugu always works hard.
He has an important job to finish
before he'll come home.
Hey, Sakura...
Uncle?
I'm here to save you.
It's okay now.
Let's go.
Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura!
Kariya...
Aoi.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
Thank you...
Father!
Fool...
That's what happens when you disobey Grandfather.
Where am I?
You're a difficult man to look after.
Digging you from the rubble was quite troublesome.
Gilgamesh...
What happened?
Who knows?
That mud spit me out.
I imagine it to be a message from Heaven,
telling me I should return to rule the world.
So you have achieved incarnation?
Infuriatingly enough.
I can't believe that thing was thought to grant wishes.
This play remained a farce to the very end.
I was shot...
I have...
no heartbeat...
Did you somehow heal me,
Gilgamesh?
I couldn't say...
You do seem dead.
But we were connected by the contract.
When I regained flesh within the ooze,
perhaps you were trapped in some alternate reality of your own.
You're saying it gave me life?
All the other Servants are gone,
so we are the ones who have won the Grail.
Kirei, behold the result.
If the Grail truly grants the victor's wish...
Kotomine Kirei,
what you see is exactly what you most desired.
What?
What am I?
What evil...
What cruelty.
This is my wish?
This destruction and tragedy?
This is my joy?
Could this twisted, disgusting thing
have truly been born of Kotomine Risei's seed?
Impossible.
It is impossible!
Did my father sire a dog?
Are you fulfilled now, Kirei?
No, not yet.
This isn't enough.
Yes, my life of questions
has found its answer.
But the path to it was bypassed,
and the key was simply handed to me.
How am I to accept this?
The formula that yielded this strange answer
should exist somewhere as a greater, clearer principle.
No...
It has to.
I must question.
I must search.
I must use the rest of my life
to understand it.
You never bore me.
As you like.
Your questions would slay the very gods.
I, Gilgamesh, shall watch you find the answer.
Angra Mainyu...
I will reach it again,
and next time, I will see it to the end.
Its birth.
Its proof of existence.
Emiya Kiritsugu?
I accept your challenge.
What's wrong, Kirei?
Nothing.
I remember that face...
With tears in his eyes at finding someone alive.
A man filled with joy, from the bottom of his heart.
He looked so happy,
it was as though it had been he,
and not me, who had been saved.
He's alive...
He's alive... He's alive!
And then...
So fervently that, even on the brink of death, I was jealous,
he said, "Thank you."
That he was glad he'd found someone.
That by saving even one person,
he had saved himself.
Episode 25:
Fate/Zero
And now, our next story.
Huge Explosion in New Fuyuki
The explosion that occurred...
Did Alexei make it back to England safely?
He called me this morning from Heathrow.
That idiot forgot about the time difference.
Oh, a phone call?
I didn't notice.
But that's just like him.
Hey, Grandpa and Grandma.
I'd like to talk to you about something...
What is it?
Actually,
I'd like to travel.
Oh, my...
Did you hear that, Glen?
Waver just said something that sounded like Alexei.
Anyway,
I'll have to prepare.
I'll need a lot of things...
First, I'd like to find a part-time job.
And so...
This is the real issue.
If you wouldn't mind...
Could I stay here until I get things worked out?
Of course!
It will be so wonderful to still have you here.
We'll have a party today!
Jeez...
He's just a ghost.
So how can he leave such a mess behind?
Really, I wanted him to take me, too...
So basically,
I'm just not there yet.
He never even opened this...
A pre-order bonus T-shirt.
Does anyone even like these things?
Honestly...
I know that my redeemer lives.
And that, in the end, he will stand upon the Earth.
And after my skin has been destroyed, yet in my flesh,
I will see God.
I, myself, will see him, with my own eyes.
I, and not another.
How my heart yearns within me.
Amen.
Rin...
An excellent debut for the new family head.
Your father would be pleased.
Well done.
Tokiomi's preparations were flawless.
The Tohsaka family magics will pass to you, Rin.
There will be no problems in that regard.
Why not bring your mother?
Yes, I will.
Come on, Mother...
Let's say our last goodbye to Father.
Ah, Rin?
Is it someone's funeral today?
That's right.
Father died.
Oh, my...
Then I should take out Tokiomi's black suit.
Oh, Rin...
Help Sakura get changed.
What should I do?
I have to get ready, too.
Dear, your tie is crooked.
You need to look good.
After all, you're Sakura and Rin's father.
I'll be leaving Japan again for a while.
Do you have any immediate concerns?
No!
I don't rely on you for anything.
Rin...
From now on, you are the Tohsaka family head.
To commemorate today,
I'd like to give you a present.
An Azoth dagger.
When my master accepted the results of my training,
he gave this to me.
Now you should have it.
This was...
my father's...
I'm here...
again.
Everyone...
Lancelot...
Because I could not stop myself from loving Guinevere,
I was never able to forgive myself.
But, King Arthur...
You never questioned me.
You never sought recompense.
You simply continued to stand before us
in your righteousness.
But I desired judgment at your hands...
Had your anger judged me, I might not have fallen
onto the path of madness in my search to atone.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I...
I am unworthy.
But this much I can say with certainty,
King Arthur...
Someday, I will get the Holy Grail.
You were the greatest among all kings...
All who served you
It was not I...
believed thus.
...who should have been king.
After that,
I visited the Einzberns many times.
But as I had not returned with the Grail,
Jubstacheit never opened the forest's barrier.
I never saw Ilya again.
However...
Ilya was the last person I ever lost.
My life was meant to be one solely of loss.
But everyone is still here, just like when we met.
I adopted the boy, Shiro, who I saved that day.
Five Years Later
Hey.
Hey, old man...
If you're gonna sleep, do it on your bed.
Yeah...
Actually,
I'll be all right.
When I was little,
I wanted to be a hero of justice.
What?
You wanted to be?
Did you give up?
Yeah.
Unfortunately...
You can't be a hero forever.
When you grow up, it's hard to call yourself one.
I should have realized that earlier...
I see.
Then I guess you couldn't help it.
No...
No, I couldn't.
The moon...
really is beautiful.
Yeah.
Since you couldn't do it,
I'll be one for you.
You're an adult now, so you can't do it.
But I can.
Leave it to me...
Your dream.
All right.
Yeah...
I feel better.
Kerry,
what kind of adult do you want to be when you grow up?
Well,
I want to be...
a hero of justice.
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
We had the chance to find our own happiness, just the two of us,
so no matter what cold flames we pushed through, we could smile
I want to cleanse the world
I will never be able to erase sadness
But I will shake the view
of those that are like that
down to zero we go
The moon's beautiful light
quietly rots away and all begins anew
The ambitions we hide still reach far into the darkness
All the days we spent together are a gentle song for me