The rebel: Hida Takahito.
One of the Kyotou style.
I see.
So this is where I will fall?
Everything that has happened was inevitable.
Miss?
You can see it just up ahead.
What business do you have on an uninhabited island?
It's not uninhabited.
A great man of the rebellion was exiled there.
After the great rebellion, Shogun Yanari, who quelled the uprising,
greatly feared the fighting style of the hero, Yasuri Mutsue,
and confined him and his family to this uninhabited island.
Twenty years have passed,
and not one person has come to the island since.
What a pain.
What are you doing, Shichika?
Sis...
Oh, it seems our water pot is nearly empty.
Don't come out here dressed like that.
It's cold, you know?
I'm fine.
It actually feels good for a little while.
Besides, I'm supposed to be doing the chores today.
You are?
Didn't I tell you to stop treating me like a porcelain doll?
I never intended to.
Just let it go.
This is a part of my training.
I don't recall teaching you to show unnecessary kindness.
There, you see? Now get back inside.
There's really no point in you training anymore, is there?
Sis...
What's the reason for preserving a style that's going to die out with you?
I haven't really thought of a reason.
Hey, Shichika.
It's already been a year since Father died.
Isn't it time you stopped?
You don't have to put it that way!
I mean, I even thought of a new finishing technique last night.
It's a really cool one... too.
Besides, the banishment only applied to Father.
I certainly couldn't, but if you took a boat by yourself—
Don't be ridiculous!
I suppose it was too early to talk about this.
I'll get breakfast ready, so hurry back soon.
All right.
As for your new finishing technique...
I suppose I'll look at it later.
Leave the island?
I've thought about leaving someday,
but this is the only thing that Dad left behind, so...
I want to preserve it while I can.
I don't have anything else, after all.
What a pain.
If Dad were here, he'd cut them down with one blow and get rid of them.
Hey.
Are you from the mainland?
You're the first one I've seen.
Is that a sword?
First time I've seen one of them too.
I don't really care that you're a stranger,
nor do I care that you've come to the island.
But...
bringing a sword here is strictly forbidden.
Is that so?
Yes.
Pardon me, then.
I wasn't aware of that.
Do forgive me.
Well, I didn't make the rules.
How did you get here?
Obviously by boat.
It's not that I'm particularly curious.
I've just been taught to do so at a time like this.
Next is...
"Why did you come here," right?
Right. Why did you come here?
I heard that Yasuri Mutsue, the sixth-generation master of the Kyotou style, lives on this island.
Do you know him?
My dad died.
A year ago.
I see.
I'm the head of the family now.
The seventh generation master of the Kyotou style, Yasuri Shichika.
Oh... I see.
That was inappropriate of me.
This concerns something that happened more than twenty years ago,
so I should've considered such a possibility, but...
I see.
He's got a pretty nice body.
He's not too hard on the eyes either.
Passing marks, if I do say so myself.
What are you talking about?
Oh, just talking to myself.
It seems you had business with my dad.
Sorry about that.
I did, but not quite.
My business is with the head of the Kyotou style.
In other words, the business I had with Master Mutsue now passes on to you.
Shichika, I haven't introduced myself yet, have I?
My name is Togame.
Togame?
What a strange name.
I'm the strategist who oversees the shogunate army.
First, I would like to test the Kyotou style.
This sword is an early work of Mibu Kasamaro, one of the thirty six swordsmiths of Mt. Fuji.
Test me?
My words exactly!
Here I come!
Die!
Gyafun!
Yasuri Shichika,
and the strategist, Togame.
These two people, who shared an unfortunate fate,
met at the beginning of the first month of the lunar year,
in a time when "Gyafun!" was not such an old word.
I'm home.
Togame the strategist, you said?
You're the first person who's ever visited this island,
so we're not exactly familiar with welcoming our guests.
No, I apologize for coming unannounced.
I am Nanami, daughter of Yasuri Mutsue.
You mentioned coming to seek our father's aid.
How are you related to our father, exactly?
I'm not really related at all.
You're not?
No.
You should think of me as someone who's just barging in, Nanami.
You'll have to leave your sword with us.
Bringing a sword to this island, or using one here, is prohibited.
A law of the Kyotou style, I assume?
It's written that the Kyotou style is "The Style of the Null-Blade."
A secret school of swordsmanship that doesn't use a sword.
The short moments that the style came out to daylight...
were in the generations of the founder, Yasuri Kazune, and the sixth master, Yasuri Mutsue.
The most powerful assassination style,
seen only in the chaos of battle during the civil war and the rebellion.
He's the seventh generation.
Togame,
I heard that you swung your sword at my brother.
I just wanted to get a quick glance at the basics of the Kyotou style.
But I really shouldn't do things that aren't of my expertise.
I'm a strategist, not a swordsman.
If you ask me, you weren't half bad.
I practiced that part numerous times.
You should've practiced swinging it, too...
A rather violent method, I'd say.
I don't blame you for thinking that way, but you had to pass my test.
I'd heard of the name Yasuri Mutsue before, but I've never seen his face.
It would've been unfortunate to get the wrong person.
Using a technique from the Kyotou style would have provided conclusive identification.
So it would've made no difference whether it was Mutsue or Shichika?
In that case, would you like to test him again?
Consider yourself lucky for tripping over that rock.
If you had managed to hit Shichika with your blade,
your injury would've been much heavier than the bump on your forehead.
No.
I'll accept your word as evidence that you are of the Kytou style.
As you wish.
Then we'll hear what you have to say.
Very well.
Have you ever thought about taking over the world?
Nope.
Of course.
It's only natural for anyone who's born in this world.
There's no shame in having strong desires.
No one can really deny the rebels their way of thinking.
If you really look at it, even the shogunate was originally a family that usurped its previous lords.
And so... what?! You haven't?!
No.
I don't really understand what you're saying.
You don't understand?!
Togame...
Please, being raised on the island has taught us nothing on the ways of the world.
I suggest you get straight to the point.
Oh, I see.
In that case, I'd like to ask if you could leave us for a moment, Nanami.
That's not possible.
There are two reasons why.
First, the Kyotou style is passed down through blood.
Even if you were talking to my dad, he would've had us both present.
The other reason is that I'm not good at thinking about things.
I see.
You're not good at thinking about things.
Then I'll ask of discretion from you and tell you why I'm here.
You've heard of the swordsmith, Shikizaki Kiki, right?
I haven't.
Of course you have.
Even living on an island way out here,
there shouldn't be any swordsmen who doesn't know his name.
Since the Kyotou style doesn't use swords,
Shikizaki could be viewed as your greatest foe.
Wait! You haven't?!
No, but I gather that he's some kind of a great person.
Shikizaki Kiki...
If I remember correctly, he was a famous swordsmith of the civil war era.
That's all you know about him?
All I've heard was that the founder of the Kyotou style had a slight connection with him.
Shikizaki didn't belong to any school and was proud of his isolation.
As a swordsmith, he was the most heretical of heretics.
But he was a swordsmith who was said to have controlled the civil war.
Controlled the civil war?
I don't understand what you're saying.
He wasn't affiliated with any country or clan,
and sold his swords to whomever he wanted to, without integrity.
In all, throughout the twenty five countries, he made a thousand swords.
A thousand swords? That's a lot.
No, not really.
Not really a lot, then...
The country that had the most Shikizaki swords won the most battles.
That's how he controlled the civil war.
Isn't it the other way around?
Since the winning countries were larger,
they were able to obtain more of his weapons, right?
That's a practical way of looking at it, certainly.
But the more fantastic explanation is also true.
150 years ago, a former shogun became obsessed with that illusion after taking over the country,
and was able to gather 507 blades — more than half of them.
How childish...
Afterwards, the shogun's new government, which had blind faith in Shikizaki's swords,
issued corrupt decrees for a sword hunt.
He said it was to create the Great Buddha, right?
That was the official reason.
I heard the real reason was to collect all the swordsmen.
No, his real objective was...
to collect all the swords created by Shikizaki.
That's right.
That's a rather shocking story.
At any rate, more than 100,000 swords were gathered and brought before the former shogun.
100,000 swords... that's not a lot.
That's quite a lot.
Quite a lot, then...
So, was he able to gather all of Shikizaki's swords?
No, in the end, the former shogun gave up.
Huh?
He was able to determine the locations of a thousand swords...
but only their locations.
Then he must've gotten them all.
He had the authority of the shogunate, after all.
That only covers the ones that were publicly known.
The last twelve of those thousand swords were unique limited editions.
The first 988 swords Shikizaki created were just practice to make the final twelve.
That's what we believe now.
He created a thousand swords just to make twelve?
Sounds crazy, doesn't it?
Kanna.
(Planer.)
Namakura.
(Blunt-Edge.)
Tsurugi.
(Swords.)
Hari.
(Needle.)
Yoroi.
(Armor.)
Kanazuchi.
(Hammer.)
Bita.
(Helm.)
Kanzashi.
(Hairpin.)
Nokogiri.
(Saw.)
Hakari.
(Scale.)
Mekki.
(Gilt.)
Juu.
(Pistols.)
The evil nature of those swords was said to exceed any other famous or enchanted blade.
Records show that the armies sent by the former shogun to collect the swords
were wiped out in their entirety by a single blade.
This is the first time I've heard of it.
And that's why I came to this island.
Master of the Kyotou style, Yasuri Shichika,
I wish you to undertake the task of collecting the remaining twelve swords forged by Shikizaki Kiki.
So that's what you meant by taking over the world.
Indeed.
Not that you're really going to be a conqueror or anything.
The current shogunate has been in power for a long time, hasn't it?
It's large enough to fend off a rebellion with brute force.
Yes, with brute force.
U-Uh, no!
The great rebellion was the problem, of course!
The Owari shogunate has been around for almost 150 years.
No one today knows the real horrors of the civil war era.
And nobody thinks of Shikizaki's swords as more than artifacts now.
But just think about the idea.
If the leader of the last rebellion was the owner of all twelve swords,
who knows what would have happened to the current shogunate.
The shogunate is afraid of another uprising.
So they're being extra careful.
So where are the swords now?
The ones we know of are in Inaba, Izumo, Satsuma, Ezo, and Tosa.
We're still looking for the rest.
So you only know where half of them are.
Give us some credit for locating half of them!
What is it?
If they're afraid of an uprising, shouldn't we refrain from attacking the people who have these swords?
The shogunate simply passed down orders to do it well.
And just how exactly do you do that?
That's why you have a strategist.
Someone who can move behind the scenes.
Um, just what is a strategist?
Specifically,
I am the War Campaign Overseer under the direct authority of Shogun Yanari of the Owari Shogunate,
Togame, the strategist!
Um...
Is that some sort of post created in the last twenty years?
No, that's just a name I made up myself.
Self-proclaimed?!
If you need tactics, you need a tactician.
If you need a clever strategy, you need a strategist!
Special orders require special people, and that's where I come in.
So, will you help me out?
If you claim to be a member of the shogunate,
you really don't need someone from the Kyotou style—
I know what you're going to say before you say it.
However, I can't hire someone motivated by wealth.
Huh?
A ninja sent to collect the swords... betrayed us.
A ninja betrayed you?
Your surprise is understandable.
Such an act only leads them to losing the trust they've gained after years and years of service.
However, they disappeared with the sword as soon as they retrieved it,
along with their entire clan and the village.
How awful.
The swords are masterpieces of art that are each worth an unfathomable amount of money.
I can't trust someone motivated by wealth.
I see.
Then how about honor?
My dad used to tell me that a swordsman fights for honor.
Honor, you say...
I can't ask a swordsman either.
The shogunate chose a swordsman who was the strongest and most loyal of them all.
He called himself Sabi Hakuhei.
We sent him to retrieve Hari, the Needle, which we thought would be the hardest to retrieve.
He was able to obtain it in record-breaking time.
Once he got it, he disappeared.
Hey...
The poison is too strong.
A swordsman motivated by honor could not resist the honor of owning one of Shikizaki's swords.
A ninja and a swordsman...
So now, the swords belong to people who are much stronger.
Your level of trust must be hitting rock bottom.
That's right!
What am I supposed to do?
I wouldn't know.
So that's why you seek the Kyotou style.
We're not tempted by wealth, and we don't use a sword.
That's right.
Yasuri Shichika, master of the Kyotou style,
will you use the techniques you've studied for the sake of a thousand years of Owari shogunate history?
I understand what you're saying.
But the fact is that you need the swords, and there's really nothing in it for me.
Are you afraid?
Of course I am.
But more than that, it's just a pain.
It's not worth crossing the sea, anyway.
Did you think I wasn't expecting that answer?
Do you think that a strategist, who's been betrayed repeatedly,
would come waltzing to this island without a compelling reason for you to help?
So you've already experienced the worst.
So then, what is this... reason?
Well, I can't trust someone driven by wealth.
I also can't trust someone driven by honor.
That leaves just one reason.
Love!
L-Love?!
I can trust someone driven by love.
Yasuri Shichika, I permit you to fall in love with me!
Shuriken?!
You've got to be kidding me!
This is the house my dad built!
Shichika.
Goodness. How hasty can he be?
No, he did the right thing.
It's best to act quickly when you're up against throwing weapons.
Well, he's just moving on instinct.
A ninja.
It's probably a Maniwa ninja.
Maniwa?
They're the ones who knew the value of Shikizaki's swords and betrayed us!
How many are there?
Only one, I think.
Maniwa ninjas hate working as a team.
I don't know why one is here, though.
I see no reason to be followed,
and I didn't tell anyone where I was going.
If there's really only one of them,
Shichika will probably lure him to that beach straight ahead.
You seem to be awfully confident.
He's going against a Maniwa ninja.
A ninja can't defeat the Kyotou style.
I'd really like to believe you,
but I'm more concerned about why a Maniwa ninja is here.
I suppose you're right.
Togame, are you quite positive that you were not followed?
Do you have to ask? I'm up against a ninja.
That's reason enough to be extra cautious.
That's also why I didn't tell anyone where I was going.
Really, how did he know?
Well, did you come here by yourself?
Why ask that now?
Well, how did you get here?
Only by boat.
Did you row the boat by yourself?
Don't be ridiculous.
My specialty is using my head.
Do I look like I have that kind of stren—
Was there a boatman?
W-Well... but...
Shoot!
That guy has one of Shikizaki's swords!
You don't really think you drove me to a corner, now do you?
Quite the opposite.
I was leading you here!
Hold on now.
We've had a lot of visitors here today, so my head's a bit muddled.
You should've picked some other day to come here!
Excuse me?! Do you think I'd give a damn about your plans?
I'm Maniwa Komori, one of the twelve heads of the Maniwa ninjas.
The Maniwa ninjas?
Oh, I heard about a ninja just a little while ago.
Hearing about us was when your luck ran out.
Otherwise, I could've just let you go.
My objective was to find out what that girl knows.
You were eavesdropping?
Quite a distasteful hobby.
You should say it's a good hobby!
So you followed Togame?
Oh, no. I wouldn't do something sneaky like that.
We came together.
I rowed the boat for her.
It was quite a bother.
She was being quite cocky, as if she were someone important.
She didn't even offer to help or anything.
Does everyone from the mainland talk this much?
Right? Don't you agree?
Sure.
You're a rather dull fellow.
Well, I suppose it's understandable, since you're a country bumpkin.
I have nothing against you, but I'm going to rip you to shreds.
Now that I think about it, this is my first fight.
Scared?
No.
You don't seem to have a sword, after all.
Oh, so you're one of those swordsmen who doesn't use swords, are you?
Kenjutsu assumes one's opponent is using a sword, after all.
So there are stupid styles of Kenjutsu as well!
Not really.
It's just that I don't really know much about fighting a ninja.
Don't worry.
I'm certainly not a swordsman.
But that doesn't mean I can't use a sword.
And to fulfill your request,
why don't I use the sword I brought along with me?
Wh-What is he doing?
Can a human actually do that?
Fear its name! Fear its sight!
This is one of the twelve altered blades perfected by Shikizaki Kiki.
Kanna, the Obstinate!
I'm surprised you can get a sword in your body.
My nickname is "Meido no Komori,"
which means that I'm quite generous about serving up a whole lot of hell!
Komori, the maid?
It sounds rather cute, in a strange sort of way.
Stop talking crap already!
Shouldn't you be worried about something?
This is one of those Shikizaki swords that girl told you about earlier.
Huh? Don't you have anything to say?!
I can't really take it when it's all covered in spit.
Huh?!
It's worth a lot, isn't it?
Should you really be walking around with it like that?
Quite the opposite.
There's no better way to keep something as valuable as this safe and close to you at all times.
Besides, this baby here's got a certain charm about it.
That girl dared to call it a poison, but it's far more like a fine sake.
Just having it makes me want to slice people up.
Cleave of Retribution!
Kyotou style, first stance: Lily of the Valley.
Then how about this?
Here! Cleave of Retribution!
Kyotou style: Chrysanthemum!
Huh?!
Y-You could see me?!
You make too much noise!
I should thank you, Kyotou style master.
It's been a long time since someone has surprised me like that.
You can use your hands and feet as swords.
Now that I know your secret, I guess I could say you're a swordsman.
I hardly compare to how surprising you are.
And on top of that...
I can't compare to that Kanna, either.
Did you notice something with that last attack?
That technique I used wasn't intended to disarm you.
Huh?
The Kyotou style: Chrysanthemum is a technique that breaks an opponent's sword in two.
That sword is definitely strange.
Now that I think about it, it is strange!
It would've been even more bizarre if it didn't seem strange!
This sword, Kanna the Obstinate, was created with toughness as its main characteristic.
Swords are expendable, so if you use them,
they eventually break or bend and lose their cutting ability.
But Kanna is different.
It will never break or bend.
Thus, it can cut someone down every time!
Oh?
Despite this sword being a straight sword, the blade will never become dull, no matter what.
It won't break even if an elephant stomps on it.
I can sell this for a fortune!
From what I've discovered, while that old geezer Shikizaki was a swordsmith,
he delved into the arts of sorcery and alchemy.
Who knows what other strange arts he used to forge this!
You're strange enough, pulling a sword out of your mouth.
At any rate, what this means is...
the Kyotou style is no match for a blade forged by Shikizaki.
After all, your technique to break the sword didn't break it!
So, the Kyotou style even goes to the length of breaking the opponent's sword?
Oh, my! That's just amazing!
But I would've much rather been surprised from seeing you actually break the sword!
Kyotou style, second stance: Daffodil!
This time, I'll break that sword of yours for sure!
You idiot!
What are you going to do if it breaks?!
If I give it to the shogunate like that, they'll make me commit suicide!
Do you even listen when people are talking to you?!
I never agreed to help you in the first place.
That's not the problem here!
Do you actually understand the value of things?
She's right.
Since I understand the value of things,
I'd never break something this valuable!
Let me just say this:
Long time no see, kitty cat.
Maniwa Komori.
Don't be so angry!
A ninja always betrays people.
We sell unfair and cowardly services, after all.
You bastard!
I'd be happy to hear your side of the story, Miss Strategist.
After I kill this guy, we can take all the time we need.
Shichika, kick his ass!
For the time being, that Kanna has really sparked my interest.
No. I told you, don't break it!
Fine, fine.
If you have any other requests, tell me now.
I'll do whatever you ask.
A-All right then.
Use as many flashy moves as you can!
What?
I've got to write a report about retrieving these swords and submit it later.
If you've got cool techniques that would gain the readers' interests,
then serve me up a couple!
I also want to remind you not to break the sword, no matter what.
If you do, the story will end at chapter one!
Chapter one? Are you planning to write a book?
That might be a nice plan for the future.
It would sell.
Then I'll show you some flashy moves.
Now let's do this, Komori.
Hey!
Nope, sorry for making you wait.
What are you doing?!
So you don't plan to fight anymore?
No. I'm not a swordsman, after all.
I don't want to lose to you just because I was too obsessed with using this sword all the time.
Oh, was that a bad pun?!
It doesn't matter to me. I'll beat you either way.
If I use my ninjutsu on you, you won't provide any challenge for me.
Your experience is different. Your battle experience, that is.
This was just an introduction.
Think of it as just a bad habit of mine.
I'll get serious from here on out.
Cut the crap!
That blade isn't something you can taint with your saliva!
Cough it up! Cough it up, right now!
My goodness... just shut up, kitty cat.
Fine then.
What? You're more obedient than I thou—
Ouch!
What?!
Geez, that was close. Too close.
That punk is really something else.
Well, I did figure you were up to something, kitty cat.
Wh-What's going on?
Oh, are you awake now?
Don't worry. My plan is just beginning.
Komori.
You look like you have a good head on your shoulders, but you're too naive.
He may be ready to fight, but he's not ready for battle.
You're just a coward who runs away.
Hey, hey, hey!
What are you babbling about?
When fighting a strong opponent, a smart person always has a plan, right, Miss Strategist?
You just toy with people who are weak.
My plans work to make weak people stronger.
They sharpen life and soul.
Don't put me on the same level as you, lowlife!
A strategist is good at working with reason too,
but I gotta say that line was just hilarious.
Huh?
"I permit you to fall in love with me." That one.
Wow, you really brought it on there!
You surprised me so much I unintentionally spat out my shuriken!
That attack was unintentional?
I'm not good at dealing with embarrassing stuff, after all.
It was a bittersweet feeling!
I wish you'd said that to me, too.
Well, now that I've heard what I needed to, everything's in order.
Just kill me now!
Don't act so tough, kitty cat.
You're just saying that, while deep down you're thinking of a way to get the jump on me, right?
Your insides are even more messed up than mine.
Relax, I don't want to kill you.
I missed on purpose with that shuriken attack earlier.
At least you know how to limit yourself.
I would've died if it even left a scratch on me!
You have no idea how weak I am!
Well, that's nothing to boast about!
When we get back, we'll torture you,
so be sure to hold out as best you can.
After all, you do have some information on where the other swords are, right?
I'll give you one final chance.
Why not betray the shogunate and join us?
I'll give you a cut of the profits.
I refuse.
I can't trust anyone driven by money.
You're still mad that I betrayed you?
It's just stupid to trust a ninja.
Now then...
I've been thinking.
You won't actually make a good hostage.
What if I do this?
What if I change my appearance?
What if I look like you?
I'm sure that Kyotou style guy won't expect this.
You weren't completely ignorant of my abilities.
You did order me to steal Kanna after all.
Once I've killed that Kyotou style guy,
I'll change into him and kill his sister.
Sorry, but you'll just have to stay here a while.
Wait!
I betrayed you for money.
Even if I hadn't, and had realized who you were from the start,
I wouldn't have agreed to join you.
I invited you to join us just now...
but it was merely to betray you again.
There isn't a man in this world who would ever love you.
That's odd.
Where could they have gone?
Me leaving the island...
at a time like this...
What a pain.
The Kyotou school is truly the worst match-up against Shikizaki's swords.
I'll have to make full use of this chance to kill you.
I can definitely kill him. What a shame...
Though your luck ran out the moment that girl set her eyes on you.
Should I go?
The plan is to act as if I'd been captured and barely escaped with my life,
then hug him before he can say anything,
and kill him.
Shichika!
Kyotou style: Peony!
Why?!
What went wrong?!
My disguise? No, it can't be my disguise.
The transformation was perfect!
Now that I take a look, aren't you Togame?
He attacked without looking to see who it was?!
Huh?
Does this mean you're actually Komori?
Y-You can't even tell who I look like?!
Well, before today, I'd never met anyone besides my sister.
It's hard for me to tell people apart.
What did you say?
The disguise was not the problem.
This guy can't tell people apart?!
That was close.
If it'd been her, she'd be dead.
This isn't the talk of some bumpkin.
Is he inhuman?
She asked me to use flashy moves, but that one was kinda plain.
Do you...
Do you really want to be useful to this girl?!
Huh?
I'm asking if you want her to use you!
Use?
You heard her story. Didn't you think it was strange?
Why would the shogunate start looking for Shikizaki's blades now?
I think she said because they were afraid of an uprising.
That'd be a sufficient reason, if it were true.
However, doesn't it sound a little too good to be true?
Don't you think so?
The current shogunate doesn't revere Shikizaki's swords.
They're more practical.
This sword collecting is just a way for her to get a promotion.
The strategist, Togame.
She'll do anything to achieve greater fame as the army's overseer.
I don't know about this promotion thing.
Isn't an overseer a pretty high rank already?
Not high enough to satisfy her.
She wants to get to the top.
Do you know what suspicion is?
You need to get your hands dirty in order to reach the top of an organization at her age.
Having the skills alone won't get you up that far.
I shivered the first time I met her,
when I saw the ambition in her eyes.
She seemed indifferent about who or what she'd have to sacrifice.
She was trying to use the Maniwa ninja clan as well.
We're talking about the Maniwa clan — a clan of ninjas feared for their skills in assassination.
She's going all out.
She's just using you too, Kyotou master.
Is this all going to end here?
Right here...
So you betrayed her before she betrayed you?
That's right.
You just can't go along with her plans.
What do you think is her ultimate goal?
To rule next to the future shogun.
Huh?
The current shogun is old.
It won't be long before he retires.
When that happens, who do you think will be the companion of the new, younger shogun?
See where I'm coming from?
Ruling the world...
I threw away my name, my home,
and now I'm going to die on this island?
Well, you can't really blame her for that, can you?
I mean, I'm sure it didn't feel great for you guys to be used, but...
We don't really care whether we're used or not.
Using and being used is a fact of life.
However, in this case the reason she used us is the problem!
I'm warning you now. I'm not all that bright, so that doesn't really tell me anything.
This girl is the daughter of the Hida Takahito, the leader of the last rebellion!
No one can really deny the rebels their way of thinking.
In better times, she was the princess of a country.
I could already see it.
It was just within my reach!
This girl is aiming for the top, no matter what it takes.
She wants to be the companion to the next shogun.
You know what that means, don't you?
Father's beliefs.
Father's regrets!
She was willing to ask her father's enemies to collect those swords?
What she's plotting is clear as day, isn't it?
She wants revenge!
Just when I could avenge my father's regrets!
She wants revenge for the eradication of her family.
Apparently she saw your family kill hers with her own eyes!
Even though I was out of cards to play,
I can't believe I'm asking help from the person who killed my father... or his son, even!
So I'm her enemy's son.
I knew I shouldn't have tried to rely on the Kyotou style school.
When she herself is like a tape worm in the shogunate from the rebel army,
who is she to tell me about betrayal and unfairness?!
This is a nice body.
I'll use it for reference.
Now our strength, muscle, and speed are all the same.
Oh, wait.
Your arm is hurting a bit from those shuriken before.
I guess that means I have a slight advantage, right?
You should know that the scratches you gave me don't even hurt or itch anymore.
I bet they don't!
Then we're evenly matched, rock to rock.
Now my rock is a little stronger.
Say...
Does anyone else know Togame's secret?
Huh?
I wouldn't blab such valuable information everywhere I go.
Then everything will be fine, once I beat you down.
How are you even that confident against me?
I am the seventh generation master of the Kyotou style, Yasuri Shichika.
Come and get me!
You think you're all that?!
Come!
I'll make you eat the flashiest move I've got!
My final technique!
Cleave of Retribution!
Wh-Why?!
The masters of the Kyotou style have been completely inept at using swords for generations!
It's not that we're swordsmen that don't use swords.
We're swordsmen who can't use swords!
Damn! I—
By the way, I mentioned that it was my final technique,
but that's only because I just thought of this finishing move last night!
This unblockable technique strikes seven times at once,
shattering the opponent in eight places instantly.
For the time being, I'll call it...
Kyotou style: Shichika Hachiretsu!
What a predicament.
Am I really the daughter of a military family?
Before I get into an even more embarrassing situation...
I refuse to believe that this rope won't come loose!
My strategies always cut through, and never break or bend!
This is hardly a challenge!
Oh, so this is where you were.
So that's what he meant by your eye.
I think it's rather glittery and pretty, actually.
At any rate, here's the first one!
What's going on?
Did he mean that he was just getting started?
Shichika, what about Komori?
Oh, I beat him up in a really cool way.
You missed it.
That's too bad.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I'm doing this all for you.
I don't really want money, and I'm not tempted by the poison of Shikizaki's swords.
And I really don't plan on doing squat for the shogunate.
I've just started to feel like I want to do this for you.
I've decided to fall in love with you.
Togame.
I just wanted you to know that I approve of this decision.
Oh, is that right?
I thought you'd be against it.
I suppose...
But to be honest, I don't really care one way or another about your story.
This boy has my approval, whatever his reasons for venturing into the world might be.
After all the training he's undergone in the twenty years since we came here,
I'd be deeply disappointed to think that it will never amount to anything.
I'll tell you this, Nanami.
It's not going to be an easy journey in any sense.
There's the Maniwa ninja clan, then Sabi Hakuhei,
and of course any other monsters lurking near the swords we haven't located yet.
They may even be ogres, or serpents.
That's the kind of battle I'm taking your brother into.
You're rather kind.
You seem to be genuinely worried about Shichika.
If my brother is in your hands, I'm not worried.
I-I'm...
I'm not that nice of a girl.
Yasuri Shichika. I have four orders to give you.
Four? Let's hear them.
I've told you the first one: Don't break any of the swords.
Very well. I'll protect the swords.
The second?
Protect me.
Even if we collect all of Shikizaki's swords, it will be meaningless if I'm dead.
Very well. I'll protect you.
The third?
Protect yourself.
This doesn't mean that I'm being considerate of you.
You're not allowed to die until we've collected all twelve swords.
Very well.
I'll protect myself.
The fourth?
Protect yourself.
This is me being considerate of you.
Don't die.
It will be a hard journey, but you mustn't die.
You can do that, right?
Don't tell me you can't.
Hurry up and say you'll do it.
Completely understood.
So what do we do now?
Let's not rush.
When we get to the city, I'll buy you some clothes.
Understood.
I love you.
Good. Love me as much as you like.
A man who knew no one, and a woman who'd lost her heart,
set forth on their journey together.
The journey to gather the swords would take them to unknown places.
Will they face ogres or serpents?
The story of Katanagatari for this month ends here.
But...
Will she be all right when Shichika's still so weak?
This is the strategist Togame, War Campaign Overseer under the direct authority of Shogun Yanari of the Owari shogunate.
It seems like everything is going according to my plan.
Are you doubting me?
As a matter of fact, your doubt is well within my calculations.
Now, it looks like my robust, action-packed, dramatic story is about to begin.
About that Kyotou guy, Yasuri Shichika...
I wonder how far he'll go to be my sword.
Next time, on Katanagatari: Namakura, the Slayer.
Cheerio!