A large Roman army has appeared on the border of Seize and Nomansland?!
Aisha!
What was that gunshot just now?
We've secured a Roman soldier.
Is the soldier dead?
No, she's still breathing.
Good work.
We shall now rendezvous with the 1st and 3rd Divisions deployed on the border.
What are you—?
Don't move.
If you move, I'll shoot.
Commander!
Colonel, please order your subordinates to fall back and vacate the fort.
Resound into the Azure Sky
What exactly is happening here?
Treason.
The girls of that fort took our commander hostage and barricaded themselves inside.
What the hell?!
Thankfully, it missed her internal organs.
She should be able to recover quickly.
Thank you, Yumina-san.
Good job.
That woman will be the sacrifice that triggers the battle.
If she had died, she'd be worthless.
What do you mean by that?!
For the past month, we've been carefully observing the Roman army from the rear.
In all likelihood, this incident is meant to force the peace talks along.
They're taking us for fools.
But the Archduke was weak and said not to attack them.
That's why we need something to force their hand.
For example, executing a weeping prisoner right in front of their eyes.
Don't tell me you guys—
The peace talks are a farce!
We must destroy Rome!
Isn't that right, Kannagi Noël?
No, my sworn ally, the Witch of Helvetia.
You thought I wouldn't notice?
Stop it.
Noël was just being used by you!
Noël-san... so you really did have something to do with the Invisible Reaper?
"The Invisible Reaper"...?
The greatest genius the Academy had seen in a hundred years,
the one who resurrected the Invisible Reaper — the biological weapons plant from the previous age...
...is that girl right there.
Your talent is invaluable.
Return to me.
Kureha-chan...
...throw that man into the underground distillery.
My comrades are already moving out to exterminate the Roman Army.
It won't take much to get the situation moving.
It's back to the battlefield again, huh?
And when we finally thought it was over.
We just have no luck.
The colonel has been detained in the distillery.
Good work, Kureha-chan.
Eat if you like.
Some baked sweets I found in Treize.
They're quite good.
Naomi-san, you're still here?
I'll leave if it gets really bad.
This is really messed up already.
They say the Flame Maidens protect the town.
But we're the ones dragging them into this conflict.
About that...
When we were hiding, I asked Aisha-san about the legend of the Flame Maidens.
She told me that they tell a completely different version in the Roman literature.
How so?
The Flame Maidens protect lives.
Wh-What?
It's time to change shifts.
It's fine.
If you're here, I'd worry.
Besides, could you even fire a gun at someone?
If I believed it was the right thing to do,
I might be able to.
Really?!
I mean, I'm a maiden of the fort too.
Just like the Flame Maidens before us.
What?
Do you really believe that made up Roman fairytale?
Yeah. It's something I can agree with.
The Flame Maidens protect lives.
I'm sure that's how it is.
What is it?
I can hear it…
What?
Kanata?
No matter how good her ears are, it'll never reach her from here.
A ceasefire signal?
Yes, I could hear it.
Is that the truth?
I'm not mistaken.
It's too soon to be happy!
She might have misheard it, and we don't really know if the peace talks have concluded.
In any case, we need to inform Colonel Hopkins—
We have a problem! When I went to bring him food, the Colonel wasn't there!
I'm relieved you're safe and sound.
We will launch the assault in 10 minutes.
Colonel.
Do you really believe the colonel will listen?
There's no harm in trying.
Roger that.
It's pointless.
The Colonel...
...was laughing.
When he used the Reaper I had revived, and watched as it killed so many people...
...he just laughed dreadfully.
He will...
...just kill.
He will fight, until no one remains.
But I helped him...
It's all my fault.
If that's what you believe, then protect more lives than you took, Noël-san.
Aisha.
Ceasefire you say?! Don't make me laugh.
But I trust her ears.
That's right!
We agree!
She may be careless, forgets things, is childish, and has no sex appeal, but...!
Onee-chan wouldn't lie!
Arrest this woman.
Do you really want to go to war that much?!
War will surely drive civilization and science forward.
I want to bring back the former glory of humanity.
What was that?!
The Roman Army plans to begin their assault tomorrow morning!
Then there's no way to avoid a battle.
Naomi-san was just arrested.
Let's go.
You're being absurd!
The enemy is the Demon of Vingt.
But I want to deliver it!
The sound that someone entrusted to me!
That's selfish!
It's selfishness.
How can you act based on your own judgement?
We're soldiers.
Someone had said that the world had already ended.
But I like this world.
I like this city.
I love everyone here.
I can't just...
...give up.
Kanata.
I'm begging you.
Please stop the war.
Aisha-san said that as well.
But I...
Me...
You...
The same…
"You've suffered enough."
"That's why... I'll..."
You'll... forgive me...?
Thank you, Aisha.
I've already said this, but we'll never be able to return after this.
Even then, are you sure?
Yeah.
Then I...
...have nothing else to say.
Do as you please.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
You've always opposed us for our own good, haven't you?
Even I had decided... that I didn't want to see...
a girl the same age as me... tortured.
But Rio-senpai isn't here!
And Noël and Kanata are so leisurely.
So I... had to work... so hard...
I'm sorry I'm such an unreliable commander.
Kureha-chan.
Let's go, everyone.
May the countless gods give their blessings to the Flame Maidens.
Main converter reactor power rising.
FAP, FAC, DMR, and ECP are normal.
Super-conducting circuit operating stably.
Firing control system is working fine.
Primary and auxiliary cannons operational.
Release all joint locks.
W-Weight reduction system operational.
Negative factor is around five.
Departure preparations, complete.
If we do it just like in training, we'll have no problems.
Let's go, my ladies!
Yes, ma'am!
Ready primary cannon.
Load armor-piercing round.
Armor-piercing round loaded.
Alignment completed.
Kana-chan, the signal.
Yes, ma'am.
Begin the attack?
Fire!
Do you want to see things developed by your voice?
Do you want to see a purer air, a world with the changed hearts of men?
But everything on the Earth is fragile.
Nothing is meaningless.
It's Kanata-neechan!
Takemikazuchi…
They've restored that much of that pinnacle of antediluvian technology?
Notify all tanks!
Do everything you can to prevent them from escaping!
Begin the attack!
We won't let you through here.
We don't want a war!
Don't get in their way!
When all is said and done, reality is not always mirrored in your eyes.
If you really want to go, you'll have to go through us.
Hell yeah!
So, what will you do?
Which to others, see horrid and demonic things.
Mr. Devil of Vingt?
No matter whose story you hear,
only your eyes can tell the difference.
We're going around!
We'll rendezvous with the rear forces!
We'll sing the world's colors
The Flame Maidens protect lives.
and not forget a single one.
The rest is up to you, Kanata-san.
Everything has a reason,
A very long time ago,
before the world became the way it is now,
like the stars in the symphony of life.
God sent an angel down to punish the world.
Injured, it stopped in a town in the far west to rest its wings.
Everyone makes a song of the skies.
The ones who saved the angel were the maidens who lived in the town's fortress.
Everything is taught and bound.
It had been sent to destroy them.
However, the maidens decided to cleanse its wounded and meek body.
When we see each other,
With the aid of a giant spider, they sheltered the angel at the bottom of the valley.
we'll become one with the stars.
In order to stem the overflowing blood, the maidens took turns embracing its head.
In gratitude, the angel bestowed upon them a golden horn.
However, the people of the town became aware of the existence of the angel.
Would you like to see the story of the world again?
They set fire to the valley.
Would you like to choose his colors to make your own painting?
The maidens were separated by the flames, released the angel's head, and its life drained away.
Given the good, the bad, and without sorting it, accept it.
Look up without covering your eyes.
At that moment, a host of angels appeared and covered the town's skies.
However, something amazing happened.
Happy things and sad things are only one.
Suddenly, a sonorous sound of the sky resounded, and the angels withdrew.
Everything is in our destiny
The sound that protected those people,
was played by the final remaining maiden as she sacrificed herself, just to sound the golden horn.
A sorrow is born from every laugh.
In every voice, in every tiny noise
Live the infinite
Hey, do you remember that girl?
The one you gave the caramels to?
She'll get dragged into all this.
Prepare to charge!
There's nothing we can do. We're soldiers.
Charge!
What was that?
What is that?
An allied tank.
It belongs to...
The 1121st platoon.
It's a ceasefire signal!
It's a Roman signal!
Commander?
We can't end it here.
Ready primary cannon.
No good. They won't stop.
Commander!
Kana-chan!
It's that girl...
Hey, what are you doing?
What about the assault?
Shoot! Shoot them!
Both sides, lay down your weapons.
I am the second heir to the Imperial Family of the Republic of Helvetia,
and betrothed of the Holy Roman Emperor,
Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
In the name of my father, the Archduke of Helvetia,
and on the authority of the Roman Emperor, I am here to inform you.
The peace talks have ended.
Fighting will not be allowed.
Both sides are to stand down immediately.
This is an imperial command!
Those opposed will be punished by the 1st Division of the Helvetian Royal Guard!
Impossible...
So we...
Don't have to fight?
Missy!
Sergeant!
Spring has come, hasn't it?
Oh yeah. Noël, what was written in that letter from Aisha?
Translate it!
She's doing well and is practicing the trumpet.
Really? Isn't that great?
We've gotten letters from Rome, but not from her, eh?
I'm sure she's busy.
Since she's a princess now.
But still, at that battlefield, she was surrounded by the Royal Guard right away, so we couldn't even talk to her.
It's the sound of Klaus-san's bike!
She's here!
I've been waiting for the new girl.
I'm going to be strict…
As of today, I have been assigned here, at the 1121st Platoon.
I am 2nd Lt. Rio Kazumiya Arkadia.
Commander Filicia Heideman,
may I have permission to take up my post?
I give my permission.
We don't use ranks here, Rio.
Well... about the Roman Emperor...
He's a rather down-to-earth guy.
He said he'd listen to any request in return for stopping the war...
So...
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Welcome back, Rio.