"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
It's summer! It's the beach!
And so, ma'am, we're counting on
you and Yui to guide
and drive us today!
Yeah!
In any case...
Both of you have quite a bit
of time on your hands.
"Fixtures of Summer"
I'm sorry that we brought you
out on your day off.
Oh no, don't worry about it.
Miss Narumi, you're a police officer
in the traffic safety division, right?
That's right. Leave all
the traffic laws to me!
Hey, he passed me...
Damn him...
Hey, traffic safety division?!
She goes out of control when
she's behind the wheel.
So we'll have Kagami and Tsukasa
be our human sacrifices.
Oh, I see... Unusual
for a police officer.
Oh, this is strange...
We've gotten separated
from the other car.
Oh, ma'am, you went
onto the wrong road!
No, that's a one-way street!
I should have known better!
Both of them were the wrong pick!
Ah yeah... Yo yo yo...
Gravity... Gravity...
Feel the power
That car is amazing!
Who's driving it?!
The braking drift on
the way down is perfect!
A FD car is losing in the plunge in!
It's got some serious pickup!
Wow, that's amazing!
It barely missed the guardrail!
The point of attack...
...is the five consecutive
hairpin curves up ahead!
I can't feel the difference
in love, go for a future
Open your eyes, open your mind,
feel the power
They're going in too fast!
Did the brakes die or something?!
"GRINNNND"
Passed him!
What is this _________-D-like
way of driving?
Miss Nanako... You're a good driver.
You think so?
Actually, I always get motion
sickness when I ride in a car.
So I brought some medicine
to prevent motion sickness...
But with your driving, Miss Nanako,
I didn't get sick at all!
Hey, I can't afford to comment
about that in this situation!
"Keep the beach clean"
"FIREWORKS ARE FORBIDDEN"
Now...
I guess we'll look for a place to stay?
It's so sunny out, it's the perfect day
to go swim in the sea!
Really... I wondered what
would happen to us yesterday.
I'm going to put my
bathing suit on before we leave.
What are you, a little girl...
Konata-san, are you
serious about that?
Or rather, I don't think I've
heard of anyone your age
wearing their school swimsuit...
Kagamin, there are needs
for such things as well.
"Sixth grade, class 3" "Izumi"
When is that bathing suit from?!
But you've got good
athletic skills to start with.
Why do you have one of
those inflatable tubes?
The fact that I can swim
doesn't mean that I'm going to
plunge through the waters
swimming freestyle, right?
The feeling I have is that of leisure.
L-E-l-S-U-R-E.
And, add to that the need for this,
visually speaking, I can't do without
the school swimsuit and tube.
But people with those needs don't
even come to the beach, right?
In manga and anime, splitting
watermelons is a standard,
but you don't see it that often
in real life, do you?
I've seen it before.
But maybe it's because
it feels like it's a waste?
That's true. When you destroy
a watermelon with a gun,
you end up with watermelon
all over your body.
You've been watching
too much anime.
Have you done it before, Miyuki-san,
since you're rich and stuff?
I'd have to say I haven't.
Come to think of it,
the image is such that
the rich are even less likely
to have done it.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
There!
I knew it all along, but things
just don't end up like in manga.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
meet your expectations.
But, you know, it's you-know-what.
Both of us loners really have it lonely,
having to come to the beach with
an all-girls group at our age
to chaperone, don't you think?
Oh no, you have it wron--
But, if you were to compromise
and tote something like him along,
don't you think you're just fine
with an all-girls group?
No, I'm telling you--
More and more people are
getting married later in life,
so we don't have to rush,
and can just go really slowly, right?
You have it wrong!
I have time only because my husband
and I have a commuter marriage.
I'm actually married!
The beach is a mecca
for picking up girls,
but we sure have nothing going for us.
But it's good, because
we're not being annoyed.
Besides, we have
someone like this with us,
so maybe they all think we're
just sisters on a family vacation?
"Ice"
There we go, Shouichi.
What's wrong?
You know, it's kinda gross to sit down
when you're still sopping wet.
Oh, I know that feeling.
Then, Tsukasa, you'll beat it
with the "air chair" pose?
That's kind of extreme.
What?
My neck's all tired.
I see.
Oh, just like what I expected!
Why are you so happy?
I mean, we've been served something
that's a picture-perfect model
of the beach house!
Look! Curry with no solid contents!
Nothing less from a beach house!
You're right. Even if you
wouldn't eat it normally,
it seems really tasty when
you eat it in a place like this.
Beer at the beach is the best after all!
But once in a while, you get
a really lukewarm one.
Though it's absurd that a hot dog
would cost 300 yen...
Right, right. And it's
practically raw, too.
But you don't mind,
and you still eat it.
Actually, I kinda like how
the chicken is oily and has
too much spice on it.
Very plain fried noodles like this
are rather tasty too.
But you know, on the other hand,
when you take it with you and
eat it back at home, it tastes awful!
--I guess that's what
makes it the beach house!
--Konata, thrilled!
You know...
Is it really tasty enough
to make that much fuss?
Not really.
Not as good as running along the
beach with nothing but a loincloth.
Is that another reference
to some anime?
"Ice"
Oh, I drank too much.
Can't help it...
Let's stay another night.
Yui, what about your work?
I'm still on paid vacation tomorrow,
so I'm fine, I'm fine!
It's really cold!
Oh, you're exaggerating, ma'am...
Lucky Star!
Why does your hair feel so creaky
after you swim in the sea?
Dunno. Maybe it has something
to do with the salt or something?
Right, Miyuki?
That's true. Most of it is caused
by the salt and ultraviolet light.
Then why is that a bad thing?
I mean, your hair is always
exposed to ultraviolet light.
Well, explaining in detail
will take a while...
Then...
Ahem.
The reason why your hair
gets damaged at the beach
is because your hair is exposed
to strong rays of ultraviolet light
after it loses moisture from the salt
that is in seawater,
as well as the ocean breeze.
Furthermore, if you bask in
strong ultraviolet rays outside,
the melanin pigments start to mutate,
and it causes your hair
to turn a bit brown.
If the salt, or other impurities
such as chlorine,
are allowed to remain in your hair,
this causes your hair to be
brittle or brown as well.
The reasons why your hair gets
damaged especially in the summer
are because of ultraviolet rays
and deposits of impurities.
These are caused by cuticles that
are damaged by such conditions.
When hit by strong ultraviolet light,
the cystine bonds
that preserve your hair's
natural strength get severed...
Look, look!
Timotei, Timotei, Timotei!
What is that?
I wonder how other people see us.
Who knows...
Our conversations don't last long...
It's safe to say we look like family,
or at least relatives.
Guess you're right.
You're not going to run with it?
Sis, Sis!
Timotei, Timotei, Timotei!
Oh, the memories! I used to do that!
This is it!
This is the reaction that I wanted!
How old are you?
Mandom.
Enough with the old man gags.
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
I've got a flag up right now!
What are you talking about?
This is where the event starts up!
For now, so that you can see both
choices in the end, save often!
Are you tossing a rock?
I've completed the image gallery!
It's perfect! Bring it on!
I can't keep up with you anymore.
In the first place,
you being like that is
exactly why, today...
Today?
I'm talking about guys hitting on us!
You brought it up originally anyway!
I hadn't thought of such a thing at all!
So you wanted someone
to hit on you, Kagami?
Th-That's not it...
Oh no, I missed seeing it!
What?
Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking about
what you do with unwanted hair.
I'm pretty smooth all around,
so I don't do anything.
What about you, Sis?
Me? I'm, well, normal, I guess.
Actually today was rather dangerous.
About what?
Well, I mean, it was almost time
for you-know-what...
Yeah, you-know-what.
I see, then that was good!
You were okay, Tsukasa?
Yeah, it totally missed me.
Since it ended last week,
I thought that I had perfect timing.
It's a problem when it
starts up at times like this.
I think so too.
It's sad when you're the only one
that can't go into the sea,
but on the other hand,
to use that thing...
Right, right, you get
hesitant or something.
I've never used one.
What a blunt conversation
you two are having.
Yeah, but what about you?
You don't suppose...
What's that look on your face?
Nothing...
I heard that this was something
that really happened...
Someone who works at a certain
video software wholesaler
finished work for that day,
and got on a bus late at night
like he usually does.
His house was towards
the end of the bus route.
And so, as he was riding the bus,
other passengers started
leaving one by one,
and he ended up as
the only passenger left.
The driver mistakenly thought that
there was nobody left on the bus...
And, can you believe it?
He started to sing, in a loud voice,
Danzen! Futari wa ______ Cure!
And that's the rumor that I heard.
So it really was nothing...
I'm so glad! I was really scared.
Actually, I was too...
I'm Sukekiyo.
Where did you bring that mask from?!
Well then, good night!
Yes, good night!
The Inugami Clan!
She sure is worth scaring...
Why don't you go to sleep already?
Hey, let's go!
Oh, okay!
I can't say something that funny.
I'm Tsukasa... I'm Tsukasa...
Sis!
What?
--It was so scary!
--It's the moment where a girl
took one more step towards
becoming an adult, Kagamin.
Huh?
The Comp-Fest seems
to be doing well.
Japanese people are suckers
for the words "limited edition."
If that one phrase makes
the difference in sales,
they should just do it every month.
If they did, then it wouldn't be
appreciated as much.
Both of you, make sure to clean
your rooms during vacation, okay?
Oh, these bring back memories!
These are textbooks
I used in junior high!
Sis, look! Look at this album!
Isn't Dad like totally
awful in this picture?
This thing of Dad was
really on my mind...
You seem to be having fun, but
how's the cleaning part coming?
Let's see...
Hey, do you want these clothes?
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
Then, I'll leave these here.
Thanks.
Here goes...
Hey, do you want this?
I guess I'll take it.
Then, what about this?
And this?
Wait, is she using me as her
trash bin or something?!
You can't help but to start flipping
through albums and stuff,
and that delays things.
Yeah, I know how that feels.
When you find an old magazine,
you can't help but read it.
That's exactly it.
By the way, where's Tsukasa?
She doesn't throw much stuff away,
so it always takes her longer.
She's still at it today.
Yeah, Tsukasa seems to be
the type that keeps everything.
On the other hand, Kagami,
you look like the type that
throws everything away.
You know, why is your image
of me so aggressive?
Oh, you had kept your
junior high textbooks?
You don't have things like that?
I left all that stuff behind at school,
with my memories.
No, take them home.
Don't cause trouble for the school.
I'm finally done cleaning up!
Though I think I'll never
use some things again,
I remembered the times
that I had used them,
and I can't bring myself
to throw them out.
Really, there are people that want
to keep anything and everything.
Tsukasa, you're the typical case
of someone like that.
You, on the other hand, might even
throw away something that you need.
I mean, you leave behind your
textbooks and stuff already.
Miyuki, you should get your teeth
treated before school starts.
I know that, but it's just not
something I deal with well.
Well, if you don't like it that much,
I feel sorry about making you
head over there.
If you can't go over there,
we'll have the dentist
come here as a house call!
Wait just a minute!
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Time passes so quickly
that Lucky Channel is
already on its sixth episode!
This is Akira Kogami, who has the
"I'd like to say people are getting
used to this segment too" syndrome!
Kyaru-n!
Not funny!
Did you say something?
--Oh, my assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi-kun,
--Scared... I'm so scared...
--is still not used to this
yet. He looks really nervous!
--It's like, he's fretting
over everyone looking at him?
--Tell me, what did I do?
--I went to the mountains because
Akira-sama told me to...
--I'd really like him to get
used to his job quickly!
--That's right, I also went to the beach.
--Especially how he should watch
his speech towards his superiors.
--I'm doing everything I can
to make this show funny too.
--How many times do I have to
tell him before he understands?
--That's right... The gum was really
tough... 54 pieces of gum...
--Honestly, it's getting irritating!
--Now today, we'd like to introduce
--I put 54 pieces of gum in my mouth...
--one of the key characters in
Lucky Star, Konata Izumi-san!
--That's how I'm doing my best, I tell you...
--What more do I need to do?
--Shut up already.
--I'm so troubled!
Let's see... Konata Izumi-san
is 17 years old.
Her hobbies are games, anime,
and reading books.
Well, according to
the source material,
she always checks out
the new shows and new books,
and spends all weekend storming
through 'net games until dawn...
In other words, an otaku?
Well, it seems that way.
Gotta think of something fast!
Otaku are, you know,
in their house all the time, right?
The people that cry watching
The Dog of Flanders and stuff, right?
Huh?
How dated can your image
of an otaku be?
Been doing your homework?
Don't go saying random stuff!
Well, um...
Well, it's true that both
The Dog of Flanders
and cute moe characters both
have a healing effect, you know?
But girls like me are
much better than dogs!
They're seeking really pretty
and cute maidens!
Don't you get it?
When I look to the right,
they look to the right!
When I look to left, they look left!
When they're in line
all night for a concert,
they can't take baths!
They end up with
horrible smell problems!
Even then, they want to see me!
Just that one thought drives them
into the damned heat,
burning in the infernal sun as
they wait for me to show up!
Even if the bandannas
they wrap around their heads
get so wet that you can
wring sweat out!
Well, they are customers, after all...
Even if they don't let me
finish a conversation quickly
during a handshake session,
or if they make some off-topic
comment during my MC,
you kinda get sympathetic, you know?
Like... "Oh, I'm here now
because of all these people."
"I have to do my best
for these people."
I guess that's what it's like?
You'll know in due time
just how hard it is to be an idol.
When you've seen both
the sweet and the sour side of life,
that's when the real taste comes out.
Even if a fan or a client
that you can't stand...
Oh, what a good time!
Everyone, did you get an idea
of Konata-san's character?
Then, I hope to see you again
in the next Lucky Channel!
Bye-nee!
Or rather, instead of
introducing Konata,
it was more of introducing otaku...
Akira-sama, are you all right?
Here, you do it.
Okay, got it!
Just then, the reporter saw...
That's not amusing.
Man, Kage is the best after all!
All right, all right.
So, Tsukasa, did you
put something in?
Yeah, I did.
Tsukasa-san's singing voice
will be fresh.
I wonder if I can sing it properly?
Hey, Miyuki, what are you
going to sing?
I really don't know that many songs,
so I'm a bit embarrassed.
Oh, so that's what you're going with.
Tsukasa-san, go for it!
♪ Tomorrow is special, a special day ♪
♪ The one chance you get a year ♪
♪ Oh darling ♪
L-O-V-E, lovely, Tsukasa!
♪ Oh darling, I love you ♪
L-O-V-E, lovely, Sayuri!
Who is Sayuri?
♪ Everyone is worked up in the carnival ♪
♪ Capture his heart to be yours ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
The name isn't Sayuri Kuninama.
♪ Oh, baby, love me do ♪
I'm asking you, who is Sayuri?
What was her membership number?
♪ A sweet, sweet chocolate of love ♪
♪ Even if I tried giving it to you ♪
♪ I won't stand out at all ♪
You're being too noisy!
♪ So I'm going to settle it
using my last resort ♪
♪ Valentine's Day kiss ♪
♪ Wrapped with a ribbon ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Kagami here.
There are times when you want
to get rid of that hangnail
and pull on it, only to have it peel off
much deeper than you expected,
leaving you in pain.
That, and the timing to
scratch off that scab...
When it gets itchy and you think
you want to get it off soon,
and you start peeling it off
slowly from the outside
and you think it's all right
and rip off the center part,
you end up bleeding after all...
That also gives
a pretty damaging blow.
Next episode: Image.
"Image"
Look forward to it!