We're at the beach for our drawing camp.
At night there are fireworks, hot springs and pillow fights.
So many fun things to do!
Right, Najimi-san?
We have no time!
The manga sale is in two days!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
The train isn't too bad once in a while.
I can tell where the public's interest lies.
Raw voices not heard in the numbers on a data table.
Boys, don't you want to know what happens in that manga you're reading?
I, as the editor, hold the bag which contains next month's manuscript. Here it...
Isn't?
Why?
Why isn't it in here?
Don't damage my car.
I know.
You got everything you need?
Yeah.
Well brother, I'm off.
It's inside the car!
I didn't have everything I needed!
And that's...
Pretty much how it went, so I chased you all the way out here.
Brother, you work at a publisher?
Hey!
Oh, didn't you know that?
I just assumed you were a club host or something.
With your hair, and all...
Hey, hey! Any way you look at it, I look good!
By the way, where's Najimi and Nidou-san?
I had them go to the store on foot.
Two ladies by themselves this late at night...
That worries me.
Najimi-san!
Look, a big fishy!
We're not buying that, put it back!
This rice is a great deal.
We definitely don't need ten kilograms.
Then, just get this badminton set?
No!
Najimi-san!
So-u-ve-nirs!
Uh, really...
Hey hey, where you girls from?
Thanks so much for the ride.
Like, we were totally bored, anyway.
Are you two, like, friendly sisters, or something?
Do we seem that way?
Eh?
Yeah!
Like, your T-shirts are totally matching.
Oh crap!
I chose these!
You came all the way out here for a swim?
Well, ummm...
We're here to train.
Training?
Like surfing, or something?
Well, ummm...
Training to draw!
Ah, like, an art college student?
Well, not exactly, but...
The male figure is very difficult.
Hey, now!
You draw stuff like that, too?
Want us to model for you?
Not really... Ummm...
Please do!
Erm... this is kinda gross.
Deal with it.
It's not like I'm enjoying it, either.
Can you put your faces closer together?
I wanna go home!
Like this?
Closer.
Ugh, this is ridiculous!
Quit breathing on me!
Don't move!
No!
Like, what kind of drawing is this for?
A beautiful form of love.
A beautiful...
Form of love?
How about you forget that, and...
Join us in a normal expression of love.
What's going to happen to us?
A will o' the wisp!
It's coming closer.
There's no will o' the wisps in this day and age.
Right?
Like, no way.
Totally unlikely.
W-what the?
It's just some dude.
Justice!
Justice?!
It seems my companions are troubling you.
Who the heck are you?
These girls are playing with us.
Playing with you, huh?
Well, then is there...
Any chance I can join you?!
H-how horrible!
So, this new artist that you've found...
What kind of person are they?
Najimi-san makes really good manga.
Wait a second!
Najimi-san?
She's a girl.
So it's a girl...
Ok...
Alright, continue.
First, read this.
Ah, Najimi's manga.
Hmm, nice paper, really.
What do you think, brother?
No, this is what you call awful, isn't it?
No way!
Can't you feel the emotion she put into that manga?
Emotion, you say?
It seems more like you're putting your feelings towards the girl who drew this.
How insightful.
That's not how it is.
You don't understand at all, brother.
That's enough, just leave!
This room belongs to Sora and I.
You're being hard-headed, brother!
I'm leaving!
That's...
The closet.
I should really stop following strangers...
Finally finished the story and panel layout!
I'm very thankful for what Justice-san did.
Shall we head off to bed?
Let's do that.
It feels like a school trip.
Hey hey, let's have a pillow fight.
I don't want to!
But it's fun...
Alright, how is it?
Just let me know what needs to be fixed!
Everything.
Narrow it down a little...
Every drawing.
Please tell me what I can fix.
Well, as a grown adult in societ-
The art could use some work.
Yep, I'll do my best!
I'm done!
It's finally complete, right?
Congratulations.
Well, It's copy paper, but it turned out alright.
You're amazing, Najimi-san.
I'm touched!
Seriously, though.
Huh, you're still here?
I packed my belongings, I'm about to leave.
It was a good harvest though.
I think I understand a little bit of what you were saying.
Ah, my book.
Who is that, anyway?
You haven't been introduced, have you?
It's Hoshi-kun's brother.
Nice to meet you, I'm Najimi Osana.
She held my hand!
Hi there, thanks for taking care of my brother all the time.
No, no.  He takes care of me all the time.
Sorry for the wait!
Alright.  Both of you are here now.
What's wrong, brother?
Najimi, was that her name?
She totally digs me...
She held my hand just now...
And we just met!
How troublesome.
Oh yeah?
Well, I was aggressively hugged when we first met.
How...
She definitely likes me more.
How easy can she be?
Najimi-san isn't that kind of person!
I'll set up over here.
Huh? Ok.
Little brother...
Big brother...
Stop it...
Nidou-san?
Yes?
Nosebleed...
Huh? It's not what you think!
This is my heart sweating.
Okay, I'm gonna sell like crazy!
Me too!
Huh?
I guess this sort of thing happens.
I figured something like this would happen.
But... all that effort's gone down the drain now.
Yeah, but it wasn't a waste at all.
I've never focused so much on drawing before.
Right?
Ummm..
How much is this?
A hundred yen!
Alright.
T-thank you very much!
Look at what I found for a hundred yen!
How awful.
I'll take one, too.
Yes!
Can I have that one?
Ah, yes!
Please line up.
Would anyone like something to drink?
Her feelings got through, huh.
I guess I should be heading home now.
Damn it!
The manuscript!
A manuscript dripping with beauty!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
So, it's the final spurt.
Let Najimi hear your cheers.
Let me hear your fetishes.