When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
It's spring all of a sudden.
It feels as if the time flew by.
And, I also feel a third person's intent at work, someone other than God's.
So, how's it going? Got used to living here?
Don't start talking when the episode's just started.
You'll surprise the NEETs who are just picking up the show with this episode.
"NEET": An acronym for "Not currently engaged in Employment, Education, or Training"
Screw them. Think about the kids.
Or what, you have a problem with me?
I have a B license in real estate and building management, and a license as a boiler worker, too.
Real estate and building management?
Ah, but don't tell anyone I can talk.
You see, if you see me in the world of Pocket *******,
which is now ten years old, I have a Pika***-like role.
So I must keep the correct image.
You're just one of the random characters,
and you're acting like a mascot character?
Don't tell me you think you have the potential of bringing in billions of economic wealth?
What? How dare you call me a random character?
In a certain magazine, I ranked twelfth in a popularity contest!
Also, in a autograph session in Nagoya,
I was the last one to get the final request!
Milady? This is rare, leaving the mansion grounds.
Hey, listen to me!
I will be back, so wait here for me.
Honestly, I don't want to go.
Where could our Lady be going?
Even the elderly are all over me!
This was the farewell between Hayate and Nagi.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Hey! Butler buried in debt! Stop ignoring me!
You bastard!
We have a problem.
Maria-san! I just saw Milady go outside somewhere!
Somewhere? She's gone to school.
What's the surprise? No matter how you look at her, she's right around that age.
But, ever since I've come here...
I had assumed she had home schooling.
Well, how do I say... She's in a rough state.
Is she a Hikikomori?
Hikikomori: A Japanese term referring to young adults who have chosen to withdraw from social life.
And it's already the middle of April, right?
So the school called in to tell her to come.
I see.
Out of curiosity, where does she go?
Hakuou Academy.
Hakuou?!
That's that super-famous school with lots of rich people,
going from grade one through twelve!
She is smart, after all.
But what a problem.
And that is?
It's Nagi's lunch.
She left it here.
I'll deliver it.
But...
It's part of my duties as a butler.
This is modern Tokyo, right?
It's probably bigger than Suginami Ward, isn't it?
Sign reads "Hakuou Academy"
Finding Milady in here will be really hard!
I must give it my all.
Hold it.
You're not a student of Hakuou, are you?
Who are you?
Identify yourself!
Are you a teacher here?
Um, I'm Lady Sanzein Nagi's-
Don't lie to me!
You can't possibly be Nagi-chan.
She's breastless, but she still is a girl!
There are limits to the lies you can say and to credit card use!
No, you see, I'm her butler.
Stop making things up!
What an amazing cosmo.
There is no butler out there with a cheap face like yours.
Well, maybe one if you search,
but I've never seen one.
And I don't believe anything I've never seen. You get it?
You got it, right?!
It's my duty to protect this school from suspicious people.
Why you ask? Because I can't have my salary cut any more.
So settle this matter as you being a stranger and get out of here!
I can't do that.
I have my duty to take this bento to Milady.
So this is now a fight between each other's duties.
So it seems.
Let's hear your name.
Ayasaki Hayate.
And you are?
I won't give you my name.
Why? Because it's personal information!
It's common sense to protect one's personal information nowadays!
So cruel of you.
You fell for it, Ayasaki Hayate.
The battle's already started.
I really don't get it, but you're cheating.
What's going on?
Watching Katsura-chan and thinking how she's doing things again.
Who's that poor-looking boy?
Now, give it up, Ayasaki-kun.
You won't be able to run past me.
The background is suddenly of another dimension!
I-Is this the legendary drunken boxing?
But I think something's wrong.
Anyway, I must walk by her to make my way into the building.
Into the building...
Hey look, I already walked past you.
Crap!
We switched place before I noticed!
You're pretty good.
I'm in a hurry, so bye.
W-Wait! No! That one doesn't count!
You can't find a fool that stops after being told to stop.
Nope.
You girls.
Dear audiences of all ages watching this anime.
Nice to meet you.
I am a student from this school, Hanabishi Miki.
I'm Segawa Izumi.
And I'm Minami Haruo.
Minami Haruo (1923 - 2001): A Japanese enka singer
Sorry, I'm Asakaze Risa.
Don't show up all of a sudden and speak through the CRT screen.
CRT: Cathode Ray Tube
Besides, don't you girls have class?
CRT screen...
Sorry, but I think there's something
we need to worry about more than class.
CRT screen...
Would you like us to help you, Katsura-chan?
Are we in the mid 1900's?
Oh no, I ran away due to the habit I developed from
the days I was getting chased by debt collectors, but...
Come to think of it, I'm not a suspicious person at all.
I should walk with more dignity.
After all, I am a butler of the Sanzenin family!
What? Where am I?
On a different note, that clock tower is amazing.
Since I've come all the way, I'd like to go up there.
You can't.
Only student council members are allowed in the deepest parts of the clock tower.
Wh-Who are you?
Where are you talking to me from?
Over here.
What could a Sanzenin family butler be doing here?
Um... And what are you doing up there?
You indeed are the butler of the Sanzenin family.
You cut right to the chase.
I see. Tree climbing is the craze in Hakuou Academy right now.
Do I look like I'm playing to you?
But it's dangerous.
I know that without having you tell me!
This is... You know!
Trees are actually rough on the surface and, with the aid of branches, are easy to climb,
but if you only look up, you forget about what's below you and...
Simply put, you're like a cat that climbed to a high place but can't get down?
Don't simplify it!
It makes it sound like I'm stupid!
Yes, stupid people and smoke like high places,
but I'm not stupid, you hear?!
I never said that.
Well, fine.
If you're a Sanzenin butler, you must be somewhat athletic.
Eh?
Come to think of, how does she know that I'm the Sanzenin's new butler?
In any case, I have a little favor to ask of you.
A favor?
So... Well... Um...
C...
Catch me, okay?
Sorry, are you all right?
Y-Yes, somehow.
It's dangerous if you don't catch me properly.
If you think it's dangerous,
then please don't jump in the first place.
I'm sorry.
But you don't have to yell at me like that.
I was really scared up there,
and I wanted to get down as soon as possible.
I'm scared of heights, too.
Well, okay.
But either way, it wasn't very graceful.
Girls shouldn't do that with a skirt on.
Oh, you don't have to worry about that.
I'm wearing sports pants underneath.
Wh-What are you doing?!
Girls should have more modesty.
What's with that innocent act?
Could the butlers in Sanzenin have
the minds of grade school children?
F-Fooling around with me like that...
Besides, if you'd waited, I would have gone up to help you without you having to jump.
Oh, so you'll help me if I call for you?
Ah, come to think of, why were you up there if you're scared of heights?
I had no choice. She fell from the nest and was crying.
You climbed a tree you couldn't get off for that reason?
What, are you going to make fun of me again?
No. I was thinking how kind you are.
I'm sorry for all the rude comments.
It's fine as long as you understand.
But now that chick can be at ease and-
Ahh, what is that crow doing?
You can't! You'll hit the chick with that!
Look!
It's the parents!
Beautiful parental love is about to save the chick!
What? You're going to abandon her?
A mother and father should never abandon their child!
Mr. Crow, can you back off now?
Or else, next time, I'll have to hit you.
So you tell me not to throw anything, but then you do?
I have a good control.
What do you mean by that?
You make it sound as if I have no control.
Besides you're-
It's Hayate.
My name is Ayasaki Hayate.
And you are?
I'm...
Why does youth make you hungry?
What is this cute girl's name?
With mystery and dubiety left, we'll move on to part B.
Nori.
Nori = Seaweed
Rinpa.
Rinpa = Lymph
Hayate is?
Yes, he should have gone there. Have you not met him yet?
Well this school is as big as Vana'****.
But I see. Hayate is here to bring my lunch filled with love...
Okay, don't worry. I will make sure to get ahold of his love.
Um, I'm the one who made it...
But, where and what could Hayate-kun be doing?
I see, so your name is Katsura Hinagiku.
That's a nice name.
You think so?
How about, as a token of my thanks,
would you like me to take you up there?
But I thought only student council members were allowed there.
Don't worry. I'm the student council president.
Really, what kind of an idiot placed
the student council room so high up?
I see.
But Katsura-san, you're scared of heights, right?
I'm fine. I'm happy enough to be able to see it so close.
But you said you wanted to go up it once.
Then you'll be even more satisfied if you do go up.
I suppose, but...
Then don't waste your chance.
It's my "thank you" gift.
Ayasaki-kun, if you don't become a little bit more selfish,
you won't catch your happiness.
But really, how stupid could one be to place the student council room so high up?
She reminds me of Lady Nagi.
Now let's go. I'm the student council president,
so it's not like I've never went up, so don't worry about me.
A-All right...
If you're a guy, be more articulate.
Yes!
Is that really an intruder?
Maybe it really was a Sanzenin family butler.
Don't talk like you know it all.
What would a boring single teacher who makes Gun**** at school understand?
Oh no, my parts!
Listen. It doesn't matter if he's really an intruder or not.
It's a fact that Hakuou allowed someone we don't know in!
Unless we catch him, our fame for security is down the drain!
She's copying off of us.
She's a teacher, and yet we need to keep an eye on her.
You do see the problem when that happens, right?
You do, right?
Especially my salary, since I let him in!
Who are you three talking to?
Okay, Segawa-san, you search though the inside the school building.
Hanabishi-san, you check around the gym.
Asakaze-san, you check...
Just look around somewhere.
Take Yasu with you!
Yasu? Who's that?
Roger.
So we are really going to do this?
I'll start off by getting a bird's eye view.
It's an amazing panorama!
Isn't it something?
The view from this clock tower is indescribable.
It's so wonderful you forget to blink, isn't it?
You can't see it if you're inside.
Don't worry about me. I'm seeing it through my mind's eye.
But from up here, you can see what goes on in the campus really well.
Of course. The reason why the student council room is so high up is for us to be able to observe the students.
You take a look at the students from here often?
I listen to people rather than look at them.
But this really is...
School looks like so much fun.
Oh, come to think of, it's the middle of the class now. Is it fine for you to be here?
Katsura-san?
Oh, be quiet.
Classes started while I was saving Cha-bou, so don't blame me!
Um, who's Cha-bou?
That chick we saved earlier.
It's a brown sparrow, so Cha-bou.
Cha-bou: Literally "brown child"
Wow, so simple.
Wh-What? In anime, it's important
to make things easy to understand!
I have to take the bento to Milady now.
Now I know where the cafeteria is, too.
Thank you very much. I was able to see a view I'll never forget.
You sound as though you'll never come here again.
I'll never be able to come here again, Katsura-san.
Call me Hinagiku.
There's another Katsura on campus who stands out more than me, so everyone calls me by my given name.
So call me Hinagiku.
Got it, Ayasaki Hayate-kun?
I found you, intruder!
Y-You're...
Onee-chan!
Onee-chan?
Yup, Yukiji Onee-chan.
Intruder, your life ends here!
But, of course, you're not really going to die.
Ah, yes, right, I probably won't.
Anyway, time to destroy you.
Hold on, he's not an intruder or anythi-
Shut up! I already explained to the people watching this show that that doesn't matter anymore!
Slay!
Evil!
Immediately!
Prepare yourself!
Hina.
There you go uttering nonsense again.
You've gotten better.
But you can't stop your sister's passion at your level yet!
Nor can you stop my salary from dropping!
Yeah right. I've never lost in a fight against you.
The only thing I lose to you is your wastefully spent life.
Even if you're my little sister, I won't forgive you for that, Hina!
Um, both of you...
When will the twenty thousand yen I lent you last month be coming back to me?
PLACEHOLDER
You coward! Taking Yukichi as a hostage?!
Yukichi: The person whose portrait appears on the ten-thousand yen bill.
I am not!
Um, I need to deliver this bento to Milady...
Yukichi's an important figure, you know?!
His "Talking Scholarly" sold over 3.4 million copies!
I could care less!
It's mine!
Onee-chan!
Hina, do you want this back?
But can you come all the way here when you're scared of heights?
If you can't come, then give that intruder to me and forget about the twenty thousand yen.
Hinagiku-san.
Don't mock me, Onee-chan.
I'm the student council president of
Hakuou Academy, Katsura Hinagiku.
I will not forgive you for treating my guest as an intruder!
You sure are my sister.
Then I'll-
Onee-chan!
Really, it's dangerous of you to get up on such a place.
The Sanzenin family's butlers are amazing.
So you finally believe me?
Well, yeah.
Thank you for saving my sister, Hayate-kun.
It was nothing. I'm glad the confusion got resolved.
I need to take the bento to Milady now, so...
Sorry, I threw it without thinking.
What should I do? I'll get fired.
Don't worry. I'll apologize to Nagi.
Okay?
Y-Yeah, I'll apologize, too, maybe.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Milady.
Nagi! There's a long story behind this.
I can guess.
I bet Sensei stole the bento,
and then stood on top of the railing with the bento in hand.
Then a gust of wind blew, and Hayate saved her as she was about to fall,
and instead, the bento became the sacrifice.
Am I right?
U-Unbelievable observation.
The result was a failure, but thank you for coming so far for me, Hayate.
Milady!
I'm hungry, so this is perfect. Let's go home, Hayate.
You can't, Milady. You have to attend afternoon classes, too.
But I'm hungry.
I'll deliver another one at light speed.
But that won't let me ditch class!
Studying is important.
You were crying until just a moment ago!
But this is my duty as your butler.
I need to have you study hard and become a wonderful lady.
Ayasaki Hayate, eh?
But-
Sneaking into Hakuou Academy is now over.
Next time, we'll fight against the comedy boom!
Intruder!
We're looking for him so hard.
What fast legs he has.
But thanks to him, we're able to skip class with a legitimate excuse.
Thanks to the intruder.
Such great weather again.
If the weather keeps up,
maybe it'll be summer by the time Golden Week ends.
As if, right?
Of course not, you fool!
Looks like you found a good comedian, Nagi.
He's a butler.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Unneeded Gags and Kindness Bring Misfortune.
I was told not to talk with people I don't know, yet I'm talking...
This one will be awesome!