Hellstorm
THE SISTERS WITH TOO MUCH GOING ON
THE FOLLOWING DAY
Unknown Heroes Snatch
yet Another Victory
Unknown Heroes Snatch Victory
From S - class Heroes
DEFEAT!
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
watashi wa senritsu no tatsumaki
I am the Tornado of Terror
do itsumo koitsu mo watashi
ga inai to dame ne!
Everyone is worthless without me!
watashi wa jigoku no fubuki...
I am the Hellish Blizzard...
to ieba wakaru kashira?
You know who I am, right?
burakku doresu de yoen ni
Dressing in pitch black, we look glamorous
tenchi mo yurugasu cho noryoku
Wielding psychic power,
we shake the world
kireigoto nante iranai no
No need to sugarcoat it,
sa keshite age mashou
it's time for you to disappear
mitame wa zuibun chigau kedo
We may look very different
futari wa shimai na no
But we are actually sisters
aa chisai okii chisai okii
Ah, little, big, little, big!
choppiri tanki na karisuma yo
We are charismatic but have short fuses
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
anata mo kono fubuki gumi
no ichiin ni naritai no?
Do you also want
to join the Blizzard Bunch?
dattara watashi ni sore soo
no tsuyosa o shomei shinasai
Then you better show me
how tough you are.
anta soredemo otoko na no!?
nasakenai wa ne!
You call yourself a man? Pathetic!
fuyukai, kiete!
You disgust me. Get lost!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March