There's nowhere to run.
The Blizzard Bunch from
the Hero Association has you surrounded!
Surrender quietly!
Going in for the kill!
Wait—!
Dammit, who told you to do that, Lily?
Never act on impulse.
We're the Blizzard "Bunch" for a reason.
Miss Fubuki!
Good work, everyone.
Miss Fubuki is here!
All right, we're behind you 100%!
They're all so lost without me.
Hellstorm
This is sure to get
the Blizzard Bunch's name out there.
THE SISTERS WITH TOO MUCH GOING ON
THE FOLLOWING DAY
What is this?
Not a single word about the Blizzard Bunch!
Well, Miss Fubuki,
I think in our own way, we did our duty…
That's true.
Unknown Heroes Snatch
yet Another Victory
Unknown Heroes Snatch Victory
From S - class Heroes
DEFEAT!
The big news this time was about
how the lower-ranked heroes
ganged up to beat a monster
that even Class S couldn't defeat.
Yeah, even Stinger only got a passing mention.
Miss Fubuki, where are you going?
Oh, don't worry.
This is nothing new.
But…
I understand her frustration.
Her little sister got a big write up,
even though she didn't do anything.
Don't you know?
Tatsumaki isn't Miss Fubuki's younger sister.
It's not fair.
They didn't even mention us!
And she did absolutely nothing.
I believe that is…
The top B-class hero, Blizzard from Hell.
Founder and leader of the Blizzard Bunch.
A hero rumored to partake in hazing newbies.
But why is she…?
Does she have allergies?
Crabs.
Crabs for my master.
Isn't this guy from Class S?
Yes, it is me.
What? A bomb?!
Yes, we just got word from Heavy Kong.
He apprehended an A-class criminal
called The Serial Bomber.
The miscreant said he'd planted a bomb
on a train headed for City Z.
City Z?
Do you know the exact train?
The limited express,
departed at 2:22 PM, bound for City Z.
He's tampered with the controls
so the bomb will go off in the terminal.
His plan is to kill everyone within range,
demolishing everything around the station.
We have already ordered nearby residents to evacuate,
but the most crucial part, the bomb, is…
Hey, Genos?
Everyone, evacuate immediately!
There is a bomb on this train.
Please exit as quickly as you—
Dammit.
There's nowhere to escape to.
Hey, what do you mean, a bomb?
Blizzard from Hell,
if I remember correctly,
you are an esper, correct?
What's going on?!
Let me off now!
Do something! I don't wanna die!
Stop this train!
Everyone stay calm.
I'll get you all off safely, one at a time.
You're amazing, Fubuki!
You want me to take care of the passengers?
Yes.
This express train makes
no stops until the station.
Our priority is rescuing the passengers.
I will stop the train.
What is it?
Can you handle it without your underlings?
Of course. I just don't appreciate
being ordered around.
What about the bomb?
There is not enough time to search for it.
Um…
I can look for it.
I'm a hero too…
though I'm just Class C.
Stop staring and find that bomb!
Yes, ma'am!
You're the last one.
That's odd, are we going faster?
What the hell is he doing?
The bomb!
I found it!
The bathroom showed as occupied,
but no one responded when I knocked,
so I broke in…
I know he froze the controls,
but it seems he also removed the engine's limiter!
Approximately 40 seconds to the terminal.
I must stop it before then!
What do we do?!
We're out of—
Shut up!
Whining won't change anything!
Prepare yourself.
If I can just contain the bomb,
I can minimize the damage.
The explosion will cause
a rapid expansion of gas.
If I can suppress it…
But, can I do that?
Am I strong enough?
All right!
Outta the way.
The only thing I know that could
move a mass like that is…
My sister!
Man…
Why didn't you just get out of there?
None of your business, is it?
She did it…
again…
Excuse me!
Thank you so much for saving me!
It's nothing.
You were just in the way.
Um… You're Blizzard from Hell,
the top hero in Class B, right?
Hmm?
So you know me.
Well, I'm a hero too, more or less.
Oh, right.
But I'm down at the very bottom of Class C.
It's getting tough to fulfill
the weekly quotas of heroic acts,
so I was thinking about quitting…
Today, I jumped on the train
to go look at the ocean,
just to take my mind off things.
But once again, I was useless.
I figured I'm not cut out
to be a hero, after all.
I see.
That's a wise decision.
But then I decided I'd try being a hero
for just a little longer.
I won't whine anymore.
So, one day, when I've moved up to Class B,
please let me join the Blizzard Bunch!
Is that a no…?
Isn't that a question you should ask
after you make it to Class B?
I'm sorry, Fubuki.
Miss Fubuki.
That's what members of
the Blizzard Bunch call me.
You'd better start getting used to it.
Right!
Sister…
I won't give up either!
Doctor Kuseno…
Power, speed, range…
I've found something else that I lack.
This is quite sudden.
What is it?
Psychic powers.
My technology cannot help you with that.
Must have been quite
a formidable opponent.
What happened?
I failed at shopping.
If only I had psychic powers,
the crabs would not have exploded…
He must be tired.
He sure is taking his time…
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
watashi wa senritsu no tatsumaki
I am the Tornado of Terror
do itsumo koitsu mo watashi
ga inai to dame ne!
Everyone is worthless without me!
watashi wa jigoku no fubuki...
I am the Blizzard from Hell...
to ieba wakaru kashira?
You know who I am, right?
burakku doresu de yoen ni
Dressing in pitch black, we look glamorous
tenchi mo yurugasu cho noryoku
Wielding psychic power,
we shake the world
kireigoto nante iranai no
No need to sugarcoat it,
sa keshite age mashou
it's time for you to disappear
mitame wa zuibun chigau kedo
We may look very different
futari wa shimai na no
But we are actually sisters
aa chisai okii chisai okii
Ah, little, big, little, big!
choppiri tanki na karisuma yo
We are charismatic but have short fuses
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
anata mo kono fubuki gumi
no ichiin ni naritai no?
Do you also want
to join the Blizzard Bunch?
dattara watashi ni sore soo
no tsuyosa o shomei shinasai
Then you better show me
how tough you are.
anta soredemo otoko na no!?
nasakenai wa ne!
You call yourself a man? Pathetic!
fuyukai, kiete!
You disgust me. Get lost!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March