Where should I go?
I don't even know where I came from.
I don't remember anything.
What should I do to be free?
What is... freedom reached by killing?
Smile...
Please smile...
Elen...
Just give it to the police.
I'm counting on you.
Ah! Wai-
I will die if I don't run away.
I can't run from those dark eyes.
If you do not wish to die,
come at me with everything you have.
You were born with a talent.
A talent to kill.
A talent to survive.
Talents needed for an assassin.
You'll need to be reborn if you want to keep living.
You have already become an existence that cannot live without killing.
What is our way of existence?
As a tool...
...or as mere equipment...
...we only have to perform our function.
Don't think about unimportant matters.
"Let us erase a green boy's memories and turn him into an assassin."
Scythe brought up such a foolhardy proposal,
and I agreed.
As it truly was necessary.
Phantom's ability, that is.
Phantom.
Inferno's ultimate assassin.
A title given to the organization's top sniper.
My ultimate masterpiece.
Ein...
...and Zwei.
Him too...
But...
In the end, she is just someone who is being used by the organization.
Phantom and I.
We can only live like slaves.
Indeed, we are giving you only one way of life.
But you're not slaves.
You have freedom.
It's your speed.
Speed?
Even in the pre-determined course,
as long as you have will and effort,
you can take off to wherever you want.
You might even be able to stand in the organization's court.
How you deal with any obstacles is up to you.
Say, Lizzie.
Will you follow any order?
I wouldn't stay long under someone I don't want to follow.
That's so like you.
Hey, Clau.
What?
I've always wanted to apologize to you.
Four years ago I joined Musho but I couldn't be of any use.
And then your gang was crushed by Wisemel.
Even Romero...
If only I could...
It's all in the past.
The weak will be devoured by the strong.
That's simply how it is.
And that's why I...
...became a member of Inferno.
Clau...
The things I lost...
The things that were taken from me...
...need to be retaken by me one day.
I need you to do one more operation in Las Vegas soon.
Make an unexpected contribution and have your superior indebted to you?
Yes.
That is the reason why we need to keep this between us.
I cannot bring myself to hate such a scheme.
This man is no longer necessary.
I will take Zwei.
Phantom...
Can't be...
That's right.
This is your passport.
The real you, your past, is here.
Try saying your name.
Azuma...
Reiji.
That's right.
I was...
...on a trip...
...and then...
Yes, Azuma speaking.
Hello?
There's no way I can...
...ever return.
What organization are they with?
Phantom?!
Scythe, that bastard!
You idiot! What're you doing shooting your own people?
I don't care if it's Scythe's order, stop being a puppet!
You won't have anywhere to run!
Think it through!
Ein!
I have to do it myself.
Ein. The only one to protect you now...
...is me.
I won't leave you behind.
I will never hand you over to the organization.
Let's run together.
From this town.
From Inferno.
Why?
Why are you so concerned about me?
You have nothing to gain.
I don't want you to die.
I don't want them to slaughter you.
It's not for anyone's sake.
This is my own will.
You need a new name.
A name?
Not like Phantom or a number.
A name for you to live your life by.
Elen.
It's Elen.
I'm going to call you Elen from now on.
Why "Elen"?
I don't need a reason.
That's my decision.
Not as an assassin or a puppet.
It's a name for you to keep on living as yourself.
Elen.
Elen...
It's a bit strange.
Elen, let's look for it.
The past you've lost.
Together.
How unlike you, Ein...
Overcome your pain with willpower.
Master...
Phantom has returned to Scythe's side.
That's a lie!
You're an idiot.
They branded you an accomplice.
People question your loyalty.
Your chance to return to Japan is gone.
However...
...there is one last option open to you.
A way to prove your innocence,
and take Ein back.
What... is it?
You should know...
...how to use this.
I will kill Scythe.
Scythe!
Rei...ji...
Such an interesting outcome.
What a perfect finale.
Within these three months, we have succeeded in taking over the primary organizations on the east coast.
The Renato Family in Boston as well as the Baldinis in Philadelphia.
Negotiations have commenced with each of their number twos regarding their induction.
Our laws will not change.
We will slap the wrist of anyone who bares their fangs at us.
And death to those who oppose us.
Destruction and renewal.
The entire country will advance...
...into our era, the era of Inferno.
Are you sure?
About entrusting everything to that woman.
She is magnificent.
As Inferno is now experiencing rapid expansion, her existence is crucial to coordinate every aspect.
Furthermore,
you have subordinates by the name of "Bloodies".
That strengthens my position.
As she has no such support,
she is not tied down to anyone in the organization.
She has Phantom, though.
Phantom is indeed unsurpassed.
But she won't defy the organization with Phantom alone.
That was just what Scythe Master tried three months ago.
No doubt about it.
He is a foolish man.
Now that he has lost Phantom,
he holds no value whatsoever.
Sorry for the wait,
Mr. Giuseppe.
And should Claudia become conceited and act the same,
it's only a matter of eliminating her.
Go play around for a bit.
Come back here in an hour.
You think I'm lying?
We just couldn't fathom it,
Miss McCunnen.
What profit could you make by proposing such favorable terms to us?
I want to be indebted to by the Godou clan.
I want a clan with strict principles, like you, to owe me.
Is that so?
You want someone to cover your back?
Correct.
I will give you 200 million dollars.
But I will be able to gain something more valuable than that.
Indeed, you can call that a proper deal.
Well then, we will send you a report of the profit margin.
We'll make a pretty huge profit.
In return, we owe you a rather big favor.
This is the true beginning.
Don't you agree?
Romero.
I can't believe he took down this many foes...
Who the hell is he?
Zwei.
We affirm thy devotion and supplement to the organization,
and bestow upon thee such title as befits thou.
We affirm thy succession.
Thou shalt stand atop hereafter and howl thy name...
...across the netherworld, with terror as thy herald.
Phantom.
Henceforth, thee art Inferno's Phantom.
I will hold all in the palm of my hand.
And for that I need you.
Reiji.
Mine and mine alone, Phantom.
Okay, Reiji.
We'll be partners from now on.