Himeji Mizuki is enthusiastic in everything.
Even today, she is reading up on something she doesn't know in a book on the subject.
How to deliver a love letter.
TL Note: Chapter 3 "How to deliver a love letter"
It is best to personally deliver it as it conveys your feelings better and raises the chance of a good res—
Himeji-san, are you studying?
Yoshii-kun?!
Yes, there was something I didn't understand.
That's right, if I give it to him now...
Yoshii-kun, actually, it's this!
Um...
Please don't laugh.
Sorry, I made a mistake!
"When should I laugh?"
When should I laugh?
"When shouldI laugh?"
"When should I laugh?"
For the second year Class F's Yoshii Akihisa, an ordinary morning arrives.
Please wake up, Aki-kun.
It's morning already.
I'm still sleepy.
I guess it can't be helped. I'll have to give you a morning kiss to wake you up.
I'm awake, I'm awake, I'm completely awake!
Is that so?
Then a good-bye kiss as advance payment—
You can't give an advance on that!
I guess I have to give up on family bonding.
Please get dressed quickly, your breakfast is ready.
Breakfast? Nee-san can't cook.
I knew it'd turn out like this.
It's a healthy, balanced breakfast.
I prepared a variety of liquids for mornings when you're on the run.
It's not exactly food, but at least it's nutritious.
Take in a lot of calories in the morning to start off the day
and eat light meals at night when you're inactive for your health.
That's good, right?
Considering that approximately twenty-five hundred calories are taken in per day,
it is appropriate to take in one thousand calories for breakfast and for lunch, and five hundred for dinner.
Since one of these is two hundred calories, you should drink five of these in the morning, coming out to one liter.
No, this is too much.
13 of these in a day adds up to 2.6 liters.
I can't drink that much.
Don't worry, I prepared a variety so you won't get sick of them.
The entrée is normal, the side dish is corn soup, the beverage is coffee, and you can pick between café au lait and cocoa for dessert.
That's not the problem.
You're right. I'm sorry, nee-san was wrong.
This isn't enough for Aki-kun since he's growing, is it?
Knock it off!
Don't give me more!
Akihisa's blissful mornings are a distant memory.
She could've at least given me something solid.
Huh? What're you doing, Ninja Pervert?
A period measurement.
Measurement?
Statistics for this academy's bust sizes.
It's an A-cup if the top to bottom measurement is 10 cm.
And with each 2.5 cm increase, it becomes a B-cup, C-cup, D-cup, etc.
B, C, A, A, B, D, B, B, C, B, A—no, D, A, B, A—
Wasn't that a C just now?
That's a fake.
I'm amazed you can tell.
This one's rather small.
Is that an A cup?
No, no.
For each 2.5 cm decrease from A-cup, it becomes an AA-cup, then AAA-cup...
I see, so a completely flat one like that—
There's nothing wrong with being completely flat!
Yuuji can't look.
Just a bit more, just a bit more...
Noisy as always.
Hideyoshi, what's with that outfit?
I got it; you're going to heal me, right?
Sign: Akihisa - Healing
Background - See Nurse
It's a costume from the drama club.
It's a male nurse's uniform, but when I put it on it looked like a woman's.
Not a female nurse, just a nurse.
What, I misread the script?
No wonder the front of the underwear didn't open, even though the front of the top did.
Sign: Collapse
Geez, what're you guys doing?
Sign: No regrets!
This is really embarrassing.
Sister!
Cut it out, Hideyoshi. People give me looks when you do stupid things, too.
I'm not doing anything that looks stupid.
Just believing that proves your idiocy.
Simply being in Class F is bad enough, but it's like a zoo for idiots in here.
Severely
ill
Stupid idiots
I'm ashamed to be a student of the same academy.
You don't have to say that much.
The truth is the truth.
Or have your grades gone up since then?
This is a school, so study if you have time to play.
Let's go, Rep.
At that time, Himeji Mizuki was perusing a technical book.
How to deliver a love letter.
If you don't have the courage to deliver it directly, you can ask a close friend.
Sign: Left - Target
Middle - Close Friend
A close friend?
Minami-chan.
What is it, Mizuki?
It's about Yoshii-kun, but...
Is that—Could it be that you also...
Eh, you mean... you too?
Sign: Super Bargain!!
You have one that I don't have?
I should've asked Yoshii-kun's close friend instead of mine.
Sakamoto-kun.
What's up, Himeji?
I have a request.
Actually, a love letter—
Wait, Shouko! I didn't do anything wrong!
This takes priority.
A marriage registration?!
Stop that! I'll never sign it!
Sign: Wheat flour sale
If it's too difficult to just hand over the love letter by itself, you can deliver it with a present.
Um, Yoshii-kun.
What is it, Himeji-san?
Actually, there's something I want Yoshii-kun to have.
I baked some cookies this morning.
Huh? Yoshii-kun?
Sign: Margarine Special Sale
Yoshii-kun! Where are you, Yoshii-kun?
I was here first.
If caught, both of our lives—
What're you fooling around for, Yoshii?
Iron Man!
Good timing. Help me carry some stuff.
You can also secretly leave it in the recipient's bag or shoe box.
It looks humble, and the recipient's impression of you will be better.
Sign: Impression
I should've just done this from the start.
What're you doing, Mizuki?
Um...
This is..
This is...
Yuuji, where are you?
If this gets into Shouko's hands, my life will end.
Sign: Marriage Registration
Sign: Marriage
It's finally completed. The complete statistics of bust sizes, impossible to replicate.
I couldn't leave it in his shoe box after all.
What should I do?
This envelope is...
In its own way, this is—
No, where's my love letter?!
Did I drop it back there?
Why do I always have to go through this?
What's this?
Sign: 2nd Year 1st Semester Mock Examination
Could this be... the questions for the next exam?
If I read this and know the questions before the test, then even I can get a full score!
As if.
That's the same as cheating.
I'll be suspected if I suddenly score a 100.
Huh? The box is ripped.
What should I do?
Should I use the classroom's orange boxes instead?
I'm done!
You'll see these again during the next mock exam.
Be sure to review until then.
Got it.
Found it!
I'm glad I—
A statement of delivery?
What's wrong, Himeji-san? You don't look so well.
Yoshii-kun? Um, well...
What is it? If I can help, then please tell me.
Yoshii-kun.
Actually...
It's gone!
Where'd it go?
Sign: What are you searching for?
My marriage registration form!
The list of bust sizes that I painstakingly compiled!
The fake photos I bought!
Where's my costume?
What does this mean? I left it in the safe and locked it up.
Lock
If you're talking about the orange boxes, Iron Man just took some.
What?!
And then...
Your important envelope?!
And do you have any clue about where it is?
Well, I found this around where I dropped it.
A delivery statement of this year's mock exam questions.
Then when I dropped the questions, it got mixed in with them.
The safe it's in is locked, and students can't get in on their own.
What shall we do?
We'll help out!
I'll assist.
Don't be so reserved, consult with us!
We need to help each other when we're in trouble.
Yuuji, everyone!
The things in that safe are also important to us!
They may not hold any value to others...
But they are the fruits of our labor!
We'll get it back, no matter what!
Everyone.
Everyone, thank you!
Everybody work together for Himeji!
Although this isn't just for Himeji.
So it's inside this safe.
It's a double lock with a key and a code.
Key
Pin
It won't open with just one of them.
It's really secure.
Why not break through the door with Aki's Summoned Being?
They'll punish me.
Sign: Eco-friendly
Hey! I have an idea!
What is it?
We put on a show about a master bank robber recently, and the robber had a trick he used to get inside the safe.
And what was it?
First, make a copy of the treasure.
Then show the fake to the owner and tell him you took it from the safe.
The panicking owner will run over and open the safe to confirm the contents,
and that's when you steal it.
Amazing!
You're smart!
Even a fool can understand that explanation!
Then let's do it!
Yeah!
Iron Man, look—the mock exam's questions!
Hand it over.
Eh?
Um, you're not going to open the safe and check?
Why would I check the safe? You have it with you.
But... what?
It was no good!
It went well on stage.
I wonder what went wrong?
The scenario.
We'll have to open it ourselves after all.
But how?
How are we going to get both the key and the pin code?
Key
Pin
Shall I help out, too?
You?
Nemoto Kyouji, Second-year Class B representative.
You just have to open the safe, right? Want me to help?
You can?
It'd be impossible to do it by myself.
If you can get the key, I'll get the code.
Really?!
Yeah, I promise.
We have to help each other when we get in trouble, right?
Thank you, Nemoto-kun!
Where is it?
There!
That's the key to the safe?
It's right behind Nishimura-sensei.
What should we do?
Seems impossible.
Okay, let's go with the decoy plan.
Decoy plan?
Somebody should seductively catch their attention while we steal the key from behind them.
Sign: Safe
Then Hideyoshi is perfect!
Why me?
Because we can't let Himeji-san do it, and Minami doesn't have any sex appeal, so it'd be weird if she does it...
Let me go!
TL Note: Name: Argentina Back-breaker
What?!
What're you doing!
There's a reason for this and there's nothing indecent about—
My skull is—
That was rough.
That's pretty deep.
But during that, I got the safe's key.
Good job, Ninja Pervert. Just as planned.
So I was the decoy?!
Okay, it's open.
Next is the code.
Don't touch it carelessly. The alarm will go off if you screw up.
You know a lot.
Then what are we going to do?
Look at this.
This is—
A good digital camera.
Iron Man just opened it.
It shows which buttons he's pressing!
That's right, this is today's code.
Found it.
I'm glad it was safe.
Mine was here too!
I have to secure it better next time.
Found it!
That's great, Himeji-san.
Yes, thank you very much.
Really, thank you!
Oh, my costume's here!
There's a bra too?
And it's a front hook.
So that's what those look like.
Mizuki, you don't know about front hooks?
There are none in my size.
Something about the clasp being too weak to hold them because of their size.
That's not true!
The clasps are durable, and who decided that front hooks are for flat-chested girls?
Sign: Front hook
Too large...
So this is it.
What're you doing, Nemoto?
Why, just some reviewing.
You can't, Nemoto-kun!
That's cheating!
What're you getting all worked up about? We're all the same here.
You entered the safe holding the questions without permission.
They'll punish you for cheating too if we get found out.
We just came here to get what we lost!
You think they'll buy that, Himeji?
Maybe you caught their stupidity during your time in Class F?
Results are everything.
Sign: Results
Simply put, the method doesn't matter.
But that's...
If you can solve these questions on your own by the exam date, it means you've improved.
It just so happens that the questions you reviewed were the ones on the test.
That's screwed up!
You're throwing this kind of chance away? That's why you're stupid.
Nobody gets hurt if I get a better score. Being naïvely honest won't get you anywhere.
You're in Class F because you don't get that.
It isn't your academic ability; your brain itself is bad.
That's why it's the worst class, filled with the scum of the academy.
That's not true!
Himeji-san?
Class F may have bad grades, but everyone is nice, kind, caring, and fun. It's a really good class!
Himeji-san.
Class F is not the worst.
Anyway, you'll all be suspended if we get caught. Maybe even expelled.
We're in this together.
Listen. I never saw you, and you never saw me.
Isn't that enough?
Let's live smarter, idiots.
Yuuji...
Are we idiots after all?
Why're you asking now? We're real idiots.
You're right.
Are you upset over being mocked?
I don't care about myself, but that he bad-mouthed Himeji-san, Minami, and the others...
Himeji-san could've been in Class A and used their setup, but she had bad luck and got dumped in Class F.
Why'd he insult her like that?!
If you're that upset, why don't we do it?
The three-month mark is coming up soon.
Our ban on declaring war will be lifted.
We led the class to a defeat last time because I didn't think it through.
I'm sorry.
Yuuji.
But we did do pretty well,
and we won't go through that again.
If you'd like to, would you want another go at it?
What're you talking about? Of course, Yuuji.
We'll win this time and prove that we're not idiots!
Let's start the Summoned Being Exam War!
Yeah, let's go and settle this.
Before that—
I'll go and grab Himeji-san's cookies.
Sounds great!
We shouldn't be the only ones who get to eat those.
Awaken!
Summoned being, summon!
What's this?
Looks like the mock exam questions.
Wait, if we study this, we can get a full score in the next exam!
They're complete idiots.
Questions that were made public won't appear on the exam.
Could it be that Aki did this?
Yoshii-kun.
Yoshii! Sakamoto! What're you doing?
We're sorry!
What do you think you're doing?!
We were just playing a prank!
We went overboard!
Don't lie! What're you plotting—
We're very sorry!
Is there a reason you can't tell me?
No, this is a prank.
Was there ever a time where you two honestly apologized?
Fine! Both of you will go through the Satanic Reviews!
Be ready! I'll give you more work than usual as punishment for your pranks!
Yes!
What's this?
A present from a girl?
I can't be underestimated.
I should eat these before Yuuka finds me.
The sound of the soul being taken away.
The eleventh question.
What was the tactic that the German military excelled with during World War II that used bombing raids and tank divisions?
Let's go intensely!
Let's treasure life.
Next week: Arch-Enemy, Love Letter, and Blitzkrieg Tactics.
This will be on the test.