So you really can make any wish come true?
Don't worry. I've heard your prayers.
So, are you sure?
Do it.
Go on and take it.
That's your destiny.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 5     There's no way I would regret this
Oh my, how embarrassing.
Please excuse me.
What's wrong with you, Hitomi? You didn't sleep well?
Indeed. I was at the hospital and the police station last night.
What? What happened?!
Perhaps I was sleepwalking. I displayed symptoms similar to that.
When I came to, everyone there had collapsed on the ground.
What are you talking about?
The doctor said that it was like a collective hallucination.
I have to go in for some more examinations today after school.
My, such a hassle.
Then why didn't you take the day off?
I can't!
That would make it seem as if I'm really sick
and my family would get even more worried.
You're a real honor student! So dedicated!
I haven't felt this good for some time.
I'm so refreshed!
Sayaka, aren't you scared?
Hmm, well, I'm kinda scared,
but I was able to defeat those guys yesterday easily.
I was thinking, "If I don't do something,
I might lose both Madoka and Hitomi, my two dear friends."
That would've been much scarier.
That's why.
I wonder what it was. Confidence? Sense of security?
I feel proud of myself.
Well, I'm excited!
Puella Magi Sayaka will do her best to keep the peace in the City of Mitakihara!
So you definitely won't regret it?
Right.
Well, I regret that I couldn't decide to do it until now.
I feel like I should've made my decision earlier.
Mami might've survived if I had fought that witch alongside her.
I...
Okay, what strange things are going through your mind?
I... I...
I can say that now that I've become a Puella Magi.
It's arrogant to say you're just doing it for Mami's sake.
Like others, I became a Puella Magi because I wanted to.
Sayaka...
Because I've found my wish.
It's something I'd risk my life to fight for.
I kinda regret that I found it too late.
So you shouldn't feel as if you're not as great as I am.
Madoka, you don't have to become a Puella Magi. That's it.
Well then, I need to leave.
Do you have to do something?
Well, kinda.
Ah, so you're still in the hospital.
I haven't finished rehab for my legs yet.
I can't leave the hospital until I can walk.
How did my hand suddenly heal? I don't understand it at all.
That's why they still need to do some more examinations.
Kyosuke, how does your body feel? Weird?
Nope. It feels like nothing happened, which scares me.
It's like the accident was just a bad dream.
Like, why am I even lying on this bed?
So this is the miracle you talked about, Sayaka.
Huh?
I said something really mean to you, Sayaka.
I can't believe how depressed I was.
Don't think about that stuff.
You deserve to feel happy right now. Don't make a sad face.
Right. I don't really feel that way though.
Well, you don't have to feel that way.
I've gotta go.
Kyosuke, come outside and get a breath of fresh air.
What are you going to do on the roof?
You'll see.
Guys!
The actual celebration will be after you leave the hospital,
but your hand recovered before your legs did.
T-That's...
You told me to help you get rid of it, but I just couldn't do it.
I...
Go ahead and try it. No need to be afraid.
Mami, my wish has come true.
There's no way I would regret this.
This is the happiest time of my life!
So that's the new Puella Magi in town, huh?
Are you really going to start something with her?
Can't you see how easy it is?
I could kill someone like her in a second!
Or is there anything else you wanna say?
You gotta problem with me?
Things won't go according to your calculations.
Since there's another Puella Magi in this town.
Hmm, what kind of person is she?
I don't know much about her either.
What? What do you mean!?
Didn't she make a contract with you like everybody else?
She did and she didn't.
She's extremely irregular.
Not even I can predict what she's going to do.
Hmm, that's just what I want.
This way, I won't feel bored.
There must be something interesting about her.
What do you want to talk about?
Well, about Sayaka...
She's such a stubborn girl and it's hard to change her mind.
So she gets into arguments with people easily.
But she's a really nice girl!
She's kind, brave, and works hard for other people.
A Puella Magi can lose her life due to those traits.
Really...
Being too kind can lead you to being naive.
Being recklessly brave can mean being careless.
Your safety's never guaranteed no matter how carefully you act.
If she doesn't understand that, she won't be able to fulfill the duty of a Puella Magi.
That's also why Mami Tomoe lost her life.
Don't put it that way!
Sayaka did say that she was fine,
but what if she's troubled like Mami was?
What can I do?
So you're worried about Sayaka Miki.
I can't help Sayaka at all.
So, please, Homura.
Please be nice to Sayaka.
Don't argue with her like you did with Mami!
I'm sure it would be safer if you two hunted witches together.
I don't want to lie. I can't promise something I can't do.
So please give up on Sayaka Miki.
Why...
She shouldn't have made the contract.
That's my fault.
I should've watched her too, not just you.
Then...
But, since I've declared my responsibility, allow me to put it this way.
This is a mistake that one can never compensate for.
It's the same as being unable to bring back the dead.
Once you've become a Puella Magi, you can never get rescued.
The contract means you have to give up everything for just one wish.
So that's why you've given up, Homura?
You've given up on yourself. You've given up on other people. Everything.
Right.
I won't say that I'm paying for my sin.
I have to keep fighting no matter how much sin I have.
It seems that I've wasted your time.
I apologize.
Nervous?
Kinda.
Because a single mistake means failure.
Madoka?
Sayaka... You're going to...
Right. I'm going patrolling to find evil witches.
You have to do this to protect justice.
Will you be okay by yourself?
I'll be fine.
Mami also did her job this way.
And being her protege, I can do it too.
Umm, I know that I can't do anything for you,
but...
Could you please take me with you?
I mean, assuming I can even access the place and that I won't be any trouble.
You're pushing yourself too hard.
S-Sorry. I guess it won't work out.
I knew I was going to be trouble for you.
Naw, I'm really happy.
You understand, right?
My hands kept trembling for a while.
I guess I'm being weak.
I'm already a Puella Magi, but I still feel helpless when I'm alone.
Sayaka...
You won't be any trouble for me. I'm really happy, actually.
It's really encouraging to hear that you want to be with me.
Just hearing that helps me tremendously.
I...
I'll be sure to protect you. Just relax and follow me.
Let's kill the witches like we did before!
Yes!
So you acknowledge the danger, right?
Yes.
Since I'm an idiot, I could go crazy when I'm by myself.
I'll probably be more careful if I know Madoka's by my side.
I see.
Then it shouldn't be a problem since you've given it some thought.
Kyubey...
Madoka, you have your own thoughts too, right?
I know that you want to protect Sayaka.
Actually, just by having you by her side,
we've gained one more weapon to combat the disasters.
I...
You don't have to say anything now.
Sayaka would be against it for sure.
On the other hand, I'll always be ready to do it.
Just tell me when you feel that you're ready to make the decision.
Here it is.
This magical barrier was probably created by a familiar, not a witch.
Doesn't mean it'll be easy.
I can't lose here. I just got started.
You have to be careful.
I know.
Is that it?
It's getting away!
Leave it to me!
Hey there, what are you two doing!?
She let it get away!
Can't you tell? That's not a witch, it's a familiar.
It doesn't have a Grief Seed.
But someone will die if you just let it go!
You just need to wait for it to eat a few people and turn into a witch.
That way, it'll actually have a Grief Seed.
What good is a little baby chicken that hasn't even started to lay eggs?
Witches attack people! Don't you care about their lives!?
Sounds like you've got the wrong idea about this.
You know what the food chain is? Didn't you learn about it in school?
Witches prey on weak humans and we prey on the witches.
Isn't that how nature works? It's a way to rank your strength.
How can that...
You...
I really hope you didn't make a contract with him just so you could brag
about something as stupid as protecting humans or justice.
So what if I did?!
Then why don't you quit?
Pisses me off to hear that you joined for some half-assed reason.
Sayaka!
Why don't you take a chill pill?
That's weird.
My bite should've left you hospitalized for at least three months.
Sayaka's okay?
Yes. The contract she formed to become a Puella Magi was a prayer of healing.
Thus, she recovers faster than other humans.
Like you could defeat me...
Mami wouldn't have died if people like you didn't exist!
Shut up.
Just shut up!
And what the hell was that?
Don't you know how to speak to your elders?
Shut up!!
Don't talk to me like that, you idiot!
Sayaka!
Don't get closer, Madoka! It's dangerous!
I've told you and hit you, but you still don't get it.
An idiot like you...
...only deserves death!
I won't lose!
How could I lose?!
Why?
Why is this happening?!
There's no witch here! Why does she have to fight a fellow Puella Magi?!
I can't do anything about it.
Neither of them wants to accept the other.
Please, Kyubey. Stop them.
I don't want this to happen!
There's nothing I can do.
However...
If there's a wish that you'd try your best to make come true,
there's a way to do it.
In order to join their fight, you have to be a Puella Magi.
But you have the right to do it. If you really wish to do it, that is.
That's right... I just need to make a contract!
Game over!
I...
That's unnecessary.
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Kamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate God Himself
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Yupon (nitro+)
Sayaka, you became a Puella Magi to hunt witches, right?
That's not a witch. She's a Puella Magi like you.
Episode 6     This is so weird