It's been a week since then.
My saving your dog was just a coincidence.
I'm pretty sure I'd've still turned out a loner, even if it hadn't happened.
If you were being nice to me out of guilt, then just drop it.
How did it end up this way?
Jerk.
Wait, Sablé!
hi no michiru kono heya
In this sunlight-filled room
sotto toki wo matsu yo
Quietly I'll wait for the time
kidzukeba fukan de nagameteru hako
Before I knew it, I was looking down into the box
onaji mesen wa naku
No one else saw it like me
itsu shika kokoro wa hakushoku futoumei
My heart had turned a cloudy white, completely opaque
yuki ni ochita hikari mo chiru
Even the light that fell on the snow scattered
kumo kara koboreru tsumetai ame
Cold raindrops keep falling from the clouds
me wo harasu no wa tooi harukaze dake
Only the distant spring winds can clear them from my eyes
azalea wo sakasete atatakai niwa made
To a warm garden filled with azaleas you made bloom
tsuredashite tsuredashite nante ne
Take me there, take me there, just kidding
shiawase dake kaita otogibanashi nante nai
There are no fairy tales that are filled with only happiness
wakatteru wakatteru sore demo ne
I know that, I know that, but still, you know
soko he ikitai no
I want to go there
It's so hot!
Hey.
H-Hi.
Okay, cool.
We're totally reset.
By resetting our relationship, I've regained my peace of mind,
and Yuigahama has been freed from the chains of guilt
and can now return to her original fulfilling life.
I didn't make the wrong decision.
My decision was as right as they come.
And so, that's the end of that.
We reset, and return to our separate lives.
You can't reset your life, but you can reset your relationships.
I'm the source on that.
Like how I haven't talked
to anyone from middle school—
That wasn't a reset, that was a delete.
Did you do something to Yuigahama-san?
Nope. Nothing.
I doubt that Yuigahama-san would stop coming unless something happened between you two.
Did you two have a fight?
No, we didn't.
At least, I think.
Besides, only people who
are somewhat close can have fights.
It's less of a fight and more of a...
An argument?
Not quite. You're warm, though.
A war, then?
No, now you're getting colder.
Total war, then.
Sorry, were you listening? Colder.
A difference of opinions?
Something like that.
I see. Then there isn't much else to say.
Oh, so Yuigahama didn't come today either?
Sensei, knock, please.
I was expecting great things out of her too.
Hey, Sensei.
Didn't you come here to do something?
Oh, right, Hikigaya!
About the contest—let's go with a battle royale.
A battle royale? With just two people?
If you need to, you can go recruit new members.
Doesn't look like Yuigahama's
coming back, after all.
Yuigahama-san hasn't quit the club—
If she isn't coming, she may as well have.
We only waste time with unmotivated students in compulsory education.
If you have not the will,
you can naught but leave.
Um...
I'm not motivated, and I don't have the will to be here. Can I leave?
Y-Yeah, thought so.
In any case,
thanks to Yuigahama, now we know that you guys are more active when you've got more members.
This is a good opportunity!
Get at least one more member by next Monday.
Find someone with the motivation and the will to replenish your human resources.
If you're so inclined,
you can start now.
This is tyranny.
Rude much?
I'm trying to be nice here.
Hiratsuka-sensei, just so we're on the same page,
we simply need to replenish our human resources, correct?
Precisely, Yukinoshita.
I wish you luck.
Replenish human resources?
How're we supposed to do that?
I have someone in mind who might join.
Who? Totsuka?
Totsuka, huh?
Totsuka, right?
Yuigahama-san.
Wait, but she's quitting, right?
Then we just need her to join again.
Hiratsuka-sensei said that we just had to replenish our human resources.
But you think she'd just come back?
Typically, once someone leaves, they're gone for good.
June 18.
Do you know what's on that day?
No.
It's Yuigahama-san's birthday.
I think.
Her e-mail address ends with 0618.
But you never asked her the actual date.
Yeah, great communication skills.
Anyway, I want to celebrate her birthday.
Even if she doesn't come back to the Service Club,
I want her to know that I'm grateful to her.
I see.
Hey, Hikigaya-kun.
U-Um...
Er...
Huh?
C-Could you go out with me?
Huh?!
Sorry for asking you out on a weekend.
Oh, don't mention it!
I wanna buy a present for Yui-san too!
And hanging out with you sounds like buckets of fun, Yukino-san!
All right. Let's go for maximum efficiency.
I'll take this side.
Then I'll take this side.
Okay, Komachi, you've got that part of—
Stop right there.
What was that for? That hurt like hell!
When'll we get another chance like this? Let's shop together!
And we can make suggestions and stuff! It's better!
But we won't be able to cover the whole mall.
Don't worry.
My senses tell me that we can find stuff Yui-san likes...
if we just cover this section here!
Komachi.
This is the section, right?
Huh?
Did you see where she went?
Hi, hi!
Hey, where'd you go?
Oh, there's a ton of stuff I wanna buy, so I totally forgot about you.
You were the one who wanted to shop together!
I never imagined my sister could be this much of an airhead.
I worry about you.
Yeah, guess you can't take a hint, Onii-chan.
What the hell are you trying to say?
Nothing! I'm gonna take another five hours or so, and I can find my own way home,
so good luck, you two!
Hey!
Why would I need luck to buy something?
Yukinoshita?
So where did Komachi-san go?
Oh, she said she had stuff to buy.
So we're stuck present-hunting by ourselves.
We asked her for her time on a weekend.
She has a right to complain. We don't.
We'll have to manage on our own.
Thank you very much!
Let's go.
Do I look that shady?
It seems people are wary of lone male shoppers in this part of the mall.
Not much I can do around here, then.
I'll wait for you over there—
Wait.
You want me to choose a present based on my judgment alone?
I don't mean to brag,
but I have a very different sense of worth from your typical high school girl.
So you knew?
So, um...
I'd like you to assist me.
I've messed up giving a presentation in front of girls before,
but I've never bought a present for one in my life.
But I can't exactly go into these stores.
I guess we have no choice.
Try not to put too much distance between us.
Huh? Distance?
Do I have to spell everything out for you?
If all you're good for is taking in air and blowing it back out,
a common air conditioner is far more skilled than you.
Yeah, it would be a lot easier if I could sense tension in it too.
Basically, I will permit you to act as though you were my boyfriend today and today alone.
Wow, that sounded really condescending.
Do you have a problem with that?
No, not really.
I-I see.
Nothing to be surprised about.
I wouldn't date her even if she were the last girl on Earth,
but Yukinoshita can't lie.
When she says "act," she really means act.
There's no room for misunderstanding.
I was convinced you would be hostile to the suggestion.
No. No reason for me to refuse it, anyway.
And aren't you hostile to it?
I have no reason to be.
Considering that everyone around us are complete strangers,
I have no reason to believe that my reputation could be damaged through a misunderstanding.
grooming
I can't let things sit the way they are.
I have to talk it through with him.
I couldn't give him the cookies in the end, either.
We're not shopping for office supplies here.
You'll never settle on a dress if all you're looking at is durability.
And I doubt Yuigahama's looking for a defense bonus in her clothes, either.
What am I supposed to do?
I can't judge them based on anything but material and manufacturing quality.
I don't know what Yuigahama-san likes, or what her hobbies are.
Do you really need to know?
If someone acted like they knew exactly what I wanted based on general tastes, I'd get pissed.
It's like giving someone from Chiba Prefecture peanuts from another prefecture.
That analogy was too Chiba for me to understand.
It's like sending a sommelier wine without being an expert yourself.
I see.
If that's the case...
What do you think?
I don't know what to say,
other than, "Wow, it looks great on you."
I see. Thank you.
But I wasn't asking about me.
I was asking how Yuigahama-san would like it.
Don't you think Yuigahama would like something more fancy and frilly
that someone with a lower IQ would wear?
That's a very rude way to put it,
but it's so accurate that I'm not sure how to respond.
I'll get this for her.
Hey, why not? Whatever rocks your socks.
You're buying that one too?
Huh? Yukino-chan?
Oh, I knew it! It is you!
Nee-san?
Huh?! "Nee-san"?!
Huh?!
I'm Yukino-chan's older sister, Haruno.
What's your name?
Uh... Hikigaya.
Hikigaya? Hm...
Hikigaya-kun, huh?
Okay, nice to meet you!
When'd you two start dating?
Come on, come on! Tell me!
We're just in the same grade.
I'm not her boyfriend.
Look at you, getting all flustered!
Make Yukino-chan cry, and I'll make sure you regret it!
Hey, that hurts!
And get off me! Get off me! Get off me!
Hey, she smells nice.
Nee-san, could you stop that, please?
Oh, sorry.
I may have gone a little overboard.
Yukino-chan's actually very delicate,
so you'd better be careful with her, 'kay?
Did I do something you didn't like?
Oh, no, uh...
My ears are sensitive.
Hikigaya-kun, I'd recommend against revealing your fetishes to women you've only just met.
You may find yourself receiving a summons.
Wow, Hikigaya-kun, you're so funny!
May we leave now?
If you have no business with us, we'd like to leave.
Hikigaya-kun, if you ever start dating Yukino-chan for real, we should have a drink!
Your sister's amazing.
Everyone who meets her says the same.
Indeed, you probably won't find another woman as perfect as her.
Everyone sings her praises.
Huh?
Sure, but we can say the same about you.
Use her to praise yourself?
Huh?
What I found amazing was... How should I put it?
That Fortified Armored Shell-like mask of hers.
Acting all sociable and always smiling, starting conversations like a nice girl.
Every man's ideal woman.
But ideals are ideals.
They aren't reality.
So it feels totally fake.
Despite your rotting eyes—
or perhaps you can see because they're rotten.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
It is.
I'm singing your praises.
A-A dog...
H-Hikigaya-kun...
Huh?
Hey, where's your owner?
Haven't they heard of a leash?
Whoa!
What's up with this dog?
It likes me way too much.
This dog...
I'm so sorry!
My little Sablé just ran off and...
Oh? Yuigahama-san?
Huh? Hikky and Yukinon?
Huh?
Why are you here together?
Why? No reason.
No, never mind! It's okay! Forget I asked!
I mean, like, you two going out together on a weekend? It's totally obvious!
I see! Why didn't I, like, notice?
Noticing things was the only thing I was good at too!
I think she might have the wrong idea.
W-Well, I'll be going now.
Yuigahama-san, I want to tell you something about us.
Would you mind coming to the clubroom on Monday?
Um...
I might not really want to hear it.
It's like, nothing'll change even if I do, right?
Or, like, there's nothing I can do about it.
Being the way I am, I didn't really know how to tell you before,
but I do want to tell you properly.
Okay...
What are you doing?
H-Hikky?!
W-Well, like... the air tasted great?
Come on, let's go.
Yuigahama-san.
Y-Yahallo, Yukinon...
U-Um...
You wanted to tell me something about you and Hikky, right?
Yes.
We wanted to tell you about our future—
H-Hey, you don't need to mind me at all!
I mean, like, yeah, I was surprised at first,
but it was more because, like, we need to celebrate!
H-How did you know?
I wanted to celebrate it.
Also, I'm very thankful to you.
H-Hey, I never did anything you need to thank me for!
I never did anything.
Regardless, I'm still thankful to you.
And celebrations like these don't happen because a celebrant asks.
I simply want to celebrate.
Okay...
It feels like they aren't talking about the same thing.
So... um...
I might not want to hear any more.
Yuigahama, I think
you're misunderstanding something here.
W-Wait a second!
So you guys weren't dating or anything?
Like hell that'd happen!
Yuigahama-san, my fuse isn't infinitely long.
In the first place, that man could never handle an interpersonal relationship,
let alone a relationship
with someone of the opposite sex.
Oh, shut up.
Like I'd ever want to be
in some stupid relationship.
If some broad called me in the night, crying,
I'd break up with her right then and there.
Sorry, sorry.
Huh?
It seems we're out of time.
I even baked a cake for you too.
A cake? Why a cake?
Why?
I asked you to come so we could celebrate your birthday.
You haven't been coming recently, but you've done a lot for the club.
And... I guess you could call it a token of our appreciation.
A present too?!
Wow! Yukinon!
I'm not the only one with a present for you.
Huh?
I never thought you'd get a present for me too, Hikky.
I mean, we've been kinda... awkward recently?
Sorry.
This isn't just for your birthday.
How should I put it...
I was thinking we could call it even.
My saving your dog and
your feeling guilty about it...
Just forget it.
I didn't do it to get any favors out of anyone in the first place,
so you don't need to return any favors to me.
So, uh... how to say it...
I want to pay you back
for whatever you did out of guilt.
Now any debts are paid and done.
You don't need to be concerned about me anymore.
So we can end all that now, right?
How can you think that?
I never thought of things in terms of pity or guilt.
It's just that...
It's so complicated that I don't know what to call it anymore.
It was a lot simpler in my head.
I don't think it's a particularly difficult issue.
Hikigaya-kun had no intention of helping Yuigahama-san.
And Yuigahama-san has no recollection of ever pitying Hikigaya-kun.
Everything was wrong from the start.
So I think Hikigaya-kun's decision to end it here is correct.
But I don't want anything to end here.
Silly.
Once it ends, you can begin all over again.
You're not the ones at fault, after all.
Huh?
While one of you saved and the other was saved,
both of you were victims.
That means that the one who caused all of this is the malefactor.
Neither of you was at fault, so there was no cause for argument in the first place.
And so...
The two of you can begin anew properly.
Oh, I need to report to Hiratsuka-sensei that we've replenished our human resources.
Hey, can I open that?
Be my guest.
Wow!
Hey, how does it look?
H-Hold on a second...
You know, that's...
a dog collar, right?
Huh?!
T-Tell me that before I put it on! You jerk!
Seriously! Geez!
I'm telling Hiratsuka-sensei on you!
Thanks, jerk.
Finally, His and Her Beginning Has Ended.
Shining in the big blue sky
An airplane, flying from one horizon to the other
air
plane
plane
Something I held in my heart
Started to boil over
I kept in the feelings I wanted to express
And turned them into words I couldn't say
Right until the end
I couldn't be true to myself
I took the string tying us together
I tangled it up
And I cut it off
The plane trails spreading in the wind
Before they completely disappear
If only I could say I wanted to see you
If only I could escape from this
Unending shell of sadness
I'd be alone again with you
Hello, Hello, Alone
hel
lo
a
lone
hel
lo
a
lone
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
over summer break.
Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now.
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
Hikigaya-kun, I have an urgent announcement regarding the Service Club's activities over summer break. Please contact me at your earliest convenience.
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
You've noticed them, haven't you?
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
You've noticed them, right?
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
You've noticed them, right?
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
You've noticed them, right?
Are you still asleep?
I've sent a few texts and called you quite a few times now. You've noticed them, haven't you?
You've noticed them, right?
Answer the phone.
I'm afraid. Very afraid.
I'm afraid.
Very afraid
Next time:
Regardless, Not Getting
a Break Over Summer Break Is Wrong.
Regardless, Not Getting a Break Over Summer Break Is Wrong.