I'll let you choose.
Mizushima Kiyoi.
Homura Suzuko.
Who wants to play me first?
I'll—
I'll go.
Suzuko...
Please, let me do it.
You're my opponent, Homura Suzuko?
Open!
Unlock. Coin bet!
Grow.
Homura Suzuko,
I've been waiting for my chance to fight you.
Unlock. Coin bet.
Coin bet. Joker.
Joker?
Suzu, be careful.
Right.
Direct!
That's the pain we LRIGs feel!
Suzu!
Suzuko!
I'm fine.
You've always endured this, Riru...
I can, too.
The fight's just getting started.
Let's go, Riru, Meru!
Right!
Let's go, Ruu!
I love...
this feeling!
Get Charge!
I won't lose if I'm with Ruu!
Tama...
Just like I thought...
I felt it the last time we battled.
You're just like me!
I've been waiting for someone like me...
Someone who feels joy when they
overwhelm and destroy an enemy,
just like I do!
My life is boring as hell.
"I want to battle."
"I want a battle that hurts,
where we both bet everything we have."
That's all I ever thought...
Wish.
Tell us your wish.
Do you want to do it?
Do you want to have a battle?
A Selector battle.
If you lose, you'll disappear.
Do you still want to fight?
Of course I do.
That's my wish...
That's my only wish!
I was chosen...
And I met you.
Now, let's have more fun!
We're both the same, so let's
fight with all we've got!
No! I'm not like that!
Just admit it! Come on!
You're wrong!
Ruu...
Tama and I won't fight battles
where we lose what we care about!
Ruuko...
We have to end these battles
that make everyone suffer!
That's why we fight!
Right, Tama?
Yeah!
I'm ending my battle with you now!
We're ending it!
So I was wrong...
Fine. Let's end it.
But it's you who'll be finished!
Doping!
She's coming, Ruuko!
Right!
Tactical Punish.
I can't defeat her with normal attacks.
She really is strong!
Are you underestimating me, Homura Suzuko?
If this is all you've got,
there's no point in me fighting.
Riru, Meru, let's do this!
Requiem?
Very well.
Now I can destroy the horrible
past where it defeated me!
Grow!
Level 5?
Shock.
It wasn't just an urban legend?
Carnival reached level 5?
The ultimate being,
who's gone beyond the limits...
That's what level 5 means!
Suzu, what do we do?
Let's do it. Requiem.
But she's level 5.
If it doesn't work...
Suzu, don't tell me...
Riru, Meru, lend me your strength!
Coin bet!
Requiem!
Fate Struggle.
What's this?
Requiem's power is being erased!
Riru! Meru!
Did you see that?
This is my power!
I'm the strongest!
It's about time for checkmate.
Coin bet. Joker. Requiem.
Astonishment...
This is a level 5 Requiem?
Suzuko!
Riru! Meru!
Thank you!
Suzuko... I can't believe you...
I'm sorry. I lost.
It's okay.
You can win, Kiyoi-chan.
Let's finish this.
Very well.
Open!
Come out, other king.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
Kiyoi-chan...
Lecture!
Suzuko-san, you didn't need to take such a
big risk to show Kiyoi-san how Carnival fights.
I was planning on winning.
But I didn't know there was
such a thing as level 5.
Still, I think I was a little helpful.
Understanding.
Now, let's entrust the rest to Kiyoi-san.
Come on!
You can't even hit me back?!
Tama! Coin bet!
Innocence!
Spell: Strategy Gale!
Tama, attack!
Right!
You really are just like me!
It's fun beating the hell out of people, isn't it?
I am not!
You are!
You and I are the same!
That was so fun...
I'd love to do it again...
Midoriko!
Hanayo-san!
Ruu, I won!
I was so worried.
Where were you?
I was taken to the room of white windows.
But Yuki let me out!
Yuki did?
But Yuki's still there...
Tama.
Yuki?
What's wrong, Tama?
I can hear Yuki's voice!
Tama, open the door.
The real door.
The real door?
Tell Ruu to find the room.
The room of the beginning of all things.
The room of the beginning...
Activate Joker.
Turn Merlin into Shiva.
Lancelot. Attack.
She's losing...
Why doesn't she use her coin skills?
Hypothesis.
Perhaps she's waiting for
some kind of opening?
The room of the beginning of all things?
The real door is there?
Yeah. Yuki said to find that room.
We have to tell the others!
Yeah...
Mizushima Kiyoi.
Are you sure you want to
end the Selector battles?
What do you mean?
I know you realize
that everyone wants the battles!
We LRIGs can't live without them.
Humans are the same, right?
They're all looking for a place to unleash
the rage, sadness, and hate in their hearts.
That's why the Selector battles never end.
And this is the perfect arena,
a place for them to do it!
That room is a holy ground for LRIGs.
It has to be protected.
Both LRIGs and humans want it.
No!
That's not what I want!
Agreement.
It's infuriating to hear you say
everyone shares your personal opinion!
Then why do the Selector battles still exist?
They don't end because you
humans don't want them to!
No...
The Selector battles don't end
because humans don't want them to.
If you call that darkness,
then the darkness will continue forever...
That's the truth!
Yes.
The darkness exists in everyone's heart.
In mine, as well.
But people overcome it to become stronger.
They can find the light beyond the darkness.
Friends I truly believe in,
comrades who believe in me...
Someone I loved, who believed
in a person like me.
Even if the darkness is too
big for me to carry alone,
I can overcome it with someone else's help.
That's what humans are.
That is our strength!
Kiyoi-chan!
Then use that strength to stop me!
Grow!
Coin bet!
Joker!
Doping!
An unending series of
perfectly arranged battles!
That is the new world I'm going to create!
I am a Selector!
I am the one who chooses!
No.
You've chosen nothing.
What?
You think you've chosen everything,
but you were only doing what
Eternal wanted you to do!
Eternal was also my choice.
Everything I did was by my own will...
It was my choice!
If your choice was to be Eternal's pawn,
then you can't beat us!
I'll prove it.
Coin bet!
Catharsis!
What is this?
What did you do?
I know level 5,
and I know that there's nothing beyond it.
So I raised your level again.
The power has gone beyond its limits
and is going out of control inside you.
I'm going to lose?
I didn't choose that!
We didn't choose to be Selectors.
That's why everyone keeps struggling.
But you accepted everything from the start.
Just like Eternal, the one
who chose you, wanted.
No... I'm a Selector...
I am the only...
Selector!
Kiyoi-chan, you did it!
You did it, Kiyoi-san!
It's thanks to you.
Thank you, Suzuko.
There they are! Kiyoi-chan!
Ruuko!
It looks like this is all of them.
Conclusion.
The only question left is who goes
to the room of white windows.
I think Kiyoi-chan should.
We only made it this far because of you.
And I believe that you'll
make the best choice.
Agreement.
Suzuko-san's wish, everyone else's hopes...
We'll entrust them all to you, Kiyoi-san.
There's something bothering me...
The room of the beginning of all things?
The real door is there, she said.
Maybe...
The Selector battles were created when Mayu
sought a connection with the outside world.
Keep Out
Everything was born in that room.
Maybe that's what Yuki was talking about.
I think I have to go there.
For Mayu's sake, as well.
Confirmation.
Let's go there.
Yeah.
I forfeit this battle!
Is that... the key?
Tama!
Ruu... I have to go to Yuki.
Go. Be careful.
Okay!
We'll be going, then.
I am Eternal.
Welcome, Selector.
You're...
Tama!
It's okay.
I'll save Yuki!
You found the key.
Open the door.
What is this place?
Choice / Battle and Battle
This room is yours.
You are the new law.
Why do you end it?
Why do you seek memories?
What waits when you end it?
Nothing but overwhelming force...
This is my battle.
Light
"Light."