Yo.
Nice going, Manabe-kun!
Huh?
Manabe
Kotoura
What are you guys thinking?!
It was missing the heart!
That's an important part! Don't you get it?!
S-Sorry!
Honestly... They just don't understand what a love umbrella means.
Um...
Please, just drop it...
TLC
Tobikage
Timer
Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo AFX : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Kaitou[Kid]
QC
Robo731   Floris257
Encoder
Floris257
So Happy, So Fun
What's with you?
Still mad about before?
I'm not mad.
Kotoura doesn't know about what happened then...
Because I like her! Got a problem with that?!
I'll have to keep quiet about that for a while,
or who knows what people will say to Kotoura...
He's worried about me...
I'm going to buy some bread from the cafeteria.
You go on ahead to the club room. I'll be there soon.
O-Okay.
Hey, Kotoura...
Wh-What?
Well, uh...
S-Sorry!
Well, see ya.
What am I doing?
H-Hello.
Hey.
This is kind of awkward.
I still don't know what kind of person Muroto-senpai is.
Manabe-kun isn't here yet?
Yuriko can't come,
so it's just the two of us.
No one to get in the way.
This room is tucked away in the old building, so not many people come by.
I guess...
this is my chance!
I've always wanted to dissect a psychic.
No!
'Sup?
Sorry I'm late.
Anyone up for lunch?
Hey. We've been waiting for you two.
We really couldn't wait any longer.
Was he teasing me?!
I'd like to know how I wound up in this situation.
You'd like to know, would you?
You know why!
Manabe-kun is the only one who's allowed to tease Kotoura.
And that's because Manabe-kun wants Kotoura-chan to be his girl—
Oh, that's right.
He doesn't know that you overheard his confession, does he?
Hey, Manabe-kun, know what? Yesterday, Kotoura-chan—
President! No!
Why not? It's not like you had a problem with it, right?
Th-That's not true!
All right, all right.
Now, hurry up and eat before our lunch break ends.
Um, was there any point in me not telling him?
Hey, did you make that lunch yourself, Kotoura-chan?
Yes.
Did you make yours, too?
Yeah.
My grandparents are getting on in years, after all.
I-I see...
Yuriko—
What? I'm still not letting you down.
No, I just thought I'd check to see how much you've improved.
That's big talk, given your current position.
Here.
65 points.
Jeez, you're always such a harsh marker.
I-Is this...
Um... President, are you and Muroto-senpai...
Well, you see, Muroto-kun is...
...A childhood friend.
You could say we're stuck with each other.
She's always made trouble and I've had to jump in to stop her.
It's really been tough.
So sue me!
Ma-a-ake...
it...
sto-o-op...!
Anyway, Manabe-kun, it seems like you're always eating bread or convenience store lunches.
Ma-a-ake...
it...
sto-o-op...!
Well, my mom's not a morning person...
Oh, really?
Ma-a-ake...
it...
sto-o-op...!
Then, Kotoura-chan, why don't you make his lunch?
You could even feed it to him while you're at it.
I-I'm not going that far!
But you will make lunch for him?
W-Well...
I'll think about it.
Oh yeah!
It'll be my first lunch made by a girl!
I haven't decided to make it yet!
All right.
I will now announce the details of today's ESP Society activities.
R-Right.
Today, after school,
the ESP Society will...
Let's singing!
Um... What exactly...
In order to complete the mission of the ESP Society,
there must be a strong bond between our members.
Yes, I suppose...
In other words, we must solidify our friendship!
That said, Kotoura-chan...
Yes?
Here, give it a try!
No... No way! I can't!
You've never sung karaoke before?
No!
At the very least, every high school girl should be skilled in karaoke.
Otherwise, you'll encounter problems on your dates with Manabe-kun.
Kotoura does have a cute voice.
I wonder what her singing sounds like?
O-Okay, I'm going to sing.
It's my first time, so it might not be very good.
Please don't laugh.
I've been waiting for this!
Yay, Kotoura-chan!
I'll enter the song.
You're too cute!
That's the Story Behind the Inside Story, Right?
You rock!
One morning, I suddenly realized
Sing louder!
all I thought about was you and only you.
My heart beats fast and I can't stand still... Strange, isn't it?
I feel like I'll lose my strength just by being close to you.
And yet you keep coming closer
to my heart without a care in the world.
Crazy! Crazy! Crazy! Crazy! For you~!
Don't rub so much on me!
Rub, rub...
Because your heart will also rub off on me…
But, but...
I actually want you to tell me that everything will be alright.
Hey, is this "love"?
She is...
But that's not the whole story, right?
Unexpectedly...
But that's not the whole story... is it?
Hopelessly...
Tone deaf!
Okay, Manabe-kun, make sure you see Kotoura-chan home.
Roger!
And no making a move on her once you get her home.
Hey! Aren't you going to respond?!
I'm not letting you inside!
It'll be just the two of you.
Why not confess your feelings to him?
What do you mean by that?!
K-Kotoura?
Uh... It's nothing!
Well, we're off.
See you tomorrow.
Are you trying to make amends for what you did to her before?
Not at all.
I need her to achieve my goal.
I'll play the role of the nice senpai as much as I need to for that.
Sorry, but you don't have the talent to be an actress.
Especially playing the role of a villain.
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, by the way, you should eat at my place tonight.
My mom keeps pestering me to bring you over now and then.
You'd better walk me home after.
Wow, today was really fun!
Yeah.
But I made Senpai worry about me again.
Kotoura, that was...
It's okay. I understand.
I know her kindness has nothing to do with my power.
Just like you.
I don't know much about the distance people should keep between each other.
There are people who are slowly becoming closer to me.
And this time, they're not slipping through my fingers.
That's why this is the happiest and most enjoyable time of my life.
Stupid.
You'll have a heap of happy and fun moments from now on.
Don't sell yourself short by saying that right now is the best.
M-Manabe-kun...
Why don't you just tell him how you feel?
No! Don't eat me, Mr. Wolf!
Didn't you let me in because you wanted me to eat you?!
Let's eat!
No!
I told you. I'm not letting you inside, pervert.
Wild sheep?
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Mori
tani
Style
Oh, you're here, Miss!
Mori!
You're full of spirit so early this morning, Miss.
I guess the future of the Moritani Style is secure now.
I just wanted to exercise a little to let off some steam.
If you don't mind, could we spar with you?
We'll do anything we can to be of use to you.
God, they're so suffocating.
This is why I hate living in a dojo.
You said you'd do anything, didn't you?
Of course, Miss!
Is that so?
We'll be going.
Oh, Kotoura-chan, come over here a second.
Yes?
What is the meaning of this?
Manabe-kun ate a convenience store lunch again today.
D-Did he?
Muroto-senpai, you seem to always be reading really complicated looking books.
What are you reading?
Books pertaining to psychic abilities, computers, and stuff.
They're not that complicated.
Y-You mean...
They're erotic books?
Are you stupid?
That's no good!
That idiot won't notice anything if you don't make a move yourself!
I tried my best!
I can't give him an embarrassing lunch like this!
And that's why...
Don't think about it so hard.
Any lunch you made for him would move that idiot to tears.
I guess you're right.
It really is girl-on-girl action this time, isn't it?!
You really are stupid.
Huh? What is it, Kotoura?
Uh, well...
I need to pick up some things. You can go on home.
Hey, don't be so cold.
I can at least carry your bags.
That's sort of a bad idea...
S-So...
Let's just say... you'll find out at lunch tomorrow.
Eating only bread and convenience store food for lunch can't be very nutritious.
And cooking for two won't take any more effort than cooking for one.
You... You'll really make my lunch for me?
Yahoo!
Manabe-kun?!
For real? I really get to eat your homemade lunches?
Man, I'm getting hyped!
Please, calm down!
Sorry. I was just so happy.
Really?
But if that's why, then I guess I understand.
See you tomorrow.
Y-Yeah.
How embarrassing...
Kotoura's homemade lunch, huh?
I'm so pumped!
I wonder if I bought too much...
Manabe-kun just seemed so ecstatic.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
No mistake. He's the guy.
Little bastard, looking down on us...
What the hell do you guys want?
He's been following me around everywhere.
If it keeps up, I don't know what he'll do to me.
I'm... scared.
We got it!
Just leave it to us, Miss!
Thanks.
Just rough him up a little.
Get up!
Don't think this is all we'll do to you!
I don't know what's going on...
But it's a good thing.
Miss!
Wh-What happened to you?
He put up more of a fight than we expected...
But please don't worry.
Most of the blood is from that stalker.
We're not hurt too badly.
I'm not worried about you!
What about him? Is he okay?
I don't think he's dead...
I told you to just rough him up a little!
I wonder how he'll look when he eats it.
Is he running late today?
Okay, everyone to your seats.
I have something important to tell you.
No...
Manabe was hurt, and has been hospitalized.
It appears he was in a bit of an accident.
It was no accident.
It's not...
It's not my fault.
I didn't tell them to go that far.
I'm... I'm not the one to blame.
What's the matter, Kotoura?
She's looking... She's looking... She's looking!
What do I do? She knows... everything!
No! They'll find out everything!
It wasn't like that! I didn't mean...
I-I'm sorry, Manabe...
I only wanted you to...
Please... forgive me!
I...
It's okay.
Manabe-kun will be okay.
Sensei, which hospital is he in?
Hold on, Kotoura. The hospital has doctors to—
Central Hospital, right?
I'm leaving early!
Hey, wait! Kotoura!
Why? Why didn't she say anything?
Why did she have that expression?
She never told me anything.
She kept it all bottled up inside of her.
I'm a fool.
Manabe was right about everything!
How much longer do I have to wait?
My wife won't even come visit me...
It was just a brawl between some hoodlums.
They deserved what they got.
Excuse me.
Manabe Yoshihisa
Manabe-kun!
Thank goodness.
These angels in white really are the best!
Miss Nurse!
I can't eat this by myself.
Please feed me.
You're just a big baby, aren't you?
But I can't. You have to eat it yourself.
Aw, man.
Still, I'm relieved. He doesn't seem to be hurt too badly.
If you want to be fed, ask your girlfriend.
Well, actually, my love is sort of unrequited...
It's really a good thing Kotoura wasn't with me yesterday.
She didn't get dragged into that mess and end up hurt.
Yeah. Kotoura doesn't need to get hurt anymore.
I'm really glad this only happened to me.
Manabe-kun, you're wrong.
The one responsible is...
I was happy to have you looking out for me.
I thought that things could change for me now.
But it doesn't work that way.
You'll just get hurt in my place.
I knew it...
I knew the people around me always end up unhappy.
But I pretended not to notice and took advantage of you.
Even Moritani-san felt so pressured because of me.
I swore to never get involved with anyone again...
And still...
I'm sorry, Manabe-kun.
I'm sorry, Moritani-san.
So please... forget about me.
I'll just...
Shortly after that, I was discharged.
But Kotoura wasn't there anymore.
Kotoura
She even moved out. Where did she go?
I still don't know.
There's a lot I don't understand,
but there is one thing I know.
And that is...
I couldn't protect her.
After I met you,
my faded world began to shine in brilliant colors.
But it was only a fleeting dream.
If I could have just one more chance...
Episode 4
Changing World
With you...