Thank goodness!
They've all grown back wonderfully!
They smell so nice!
They really do smell nice!
It's all thanks to our hard work!
Yeah, we've given this our all!
But...
I can't believe she'd stain these beautiful flowers with darkness like that.
Once I destroy you two, I'll become the real thing.
We have to defeat that impostor Precure this time!
Yes...
But there's no way we can defeat
Dark Precure in our current shape.
If we combine our strength, we'll make it happen somehow!
Right.
We have to do something.
Hee-ya!
What is it?
The second you put those two brothers together, they start doing silly things.
Hey, hold on a second!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
In spring, the dawn — when the slowly paling mountain rim is tinged with red,
and wisps of faintly crimson-purple cloud float in the sky.
All right, that'll do. Masato,
continue from where he left off.
Ah, um...
Page 20!
Okay!
Ow!
And just who were you responding to there?
I wasn't! I mean...
Masato, can you stand up for a second?
Huh?
Exactly when did our school's uniform replace its indoor shoes with kung fu shoes?
Oh, these?
I thought that by wearing these, I'd be ready no matter when the enemy chose to strike!
Yo, Kung Fu Master!
All right, settle down.
Your tastes are your own business, but make sure
you wear your indoor shoes when you're in school.
Now, let's continue the lesson.
Kung Fu Master?
Hee-ya!
Power up with Kung Fu!
Hanasaki, thank you for saving me earlier.
You're quite welcome!
So, you know kung fu, Sakai?
Yeah. I've pretty much mastered the style.
That's amazing!
I guess!
Tsubomi, there's no way that Sakai could actually know kung fu!
Even if he says he's mastered it, he's probably just imitating his kung fu movies.
That's not true! I've actually learned the style!
If I used my kung fu seriously...
then no other martial art could even compare!
Now I've gotten him started...
I-Is that really true?!
Please teach me kung fu as well!
Huh? Are you serious?
I'm serious!
Well then, I'm off to learn kung fu!
Huh?
Hee-ya!
Tsubomi... why are you so fired up about this?
First of all, you need to master the steps laid out by the markings.
O-Okay!
Hey, bro, what're you doing?
Yoshito! You're late!
Who's she?
She's Hanasaki Tsubomi from my class.
It seems she wants to learn kung fu too.
I'm Hanasaki Tsubomi—
Bro only needs one pupil, and that's me!
Huh?!
Yoshito!
Having another pupil means you'll have someone to practice against, see?
Yessir...
Nice to meet you, Yoshito!
That's wrong!
Huh?
I'm bro's first pupil!
And you're his second, so you should say "Nice to be working with you!"
Oh!
I was first, so show me some respect!
Got it! Nice to be working with you, Yoshito!
Nice to meet you too, Tsubomi.
All right then, let's begin practice.
O-Okay!
You should answer with "Yessir!"
Y-Yessir!
In combat, it's critical that you're not
fooled by your opponent's movements.
That's why you mustn't merely see your opponent, but feel with your heart how they're going to act.
Yessir!
Controlling nunchucks is very difficult.
Don't think. Feel!
Don't merely perceive with your eyes, but feel with your heart!
Yessir!
Y-Yessir!
All right, then continue with that.
Yessir!
That seems fun!
Feel it with your heart!
Y-Yessir...
Just what are you doing, Tsubomi...
She's working so hard to try
to get rid of her weaknesses.
That's right!
It's very important to have all the various forms at your disposal.
The crane! The tiger! The snake!
Tsubomi!
Erika!
Kung fu is seriously amazing!
You should try it too, Erika!
No, I'm fine, really!
What are you doing here, Kurumi?
I was worried about Tsubomi, so I...
And I wanted to apologize for
saying you couldn't do kung fu.
It's all right.
All right, then you can be his third pupil!
It's settled, then!
And remember to practice all that, you two!
Yessir!
That little brother of his has quite the attitude, doesn't he?
He really admires Sakai from the bottom of his heart.
I don't think I could ever bring
myself to idolize Momo like that.
Haa. Haa. Haa. Haa!
Hey, Tsubomi...
Why did you suddenly want to learn kung fu?
I've been kinda worried.
I want to learn something new and become stronger.
I'm not sure how this'll sound coming from me...
but Tsubomi, you're not as weak as you make yourself out to be.
Huh?
We're growing closer and closer together as the days go by.
That's why no matter what
happens, we'll make it work out!
Yeah...
There!
Don't let that get you down!
Keep fighting, Tsubomi!
Right...
Don't think. Feel!
Don't merely perceive with your eyes, but feel it with your heart!
All right...
Send the next one right.
It's coming!
That huuuuuurt!
Hanasaki, are you all right?
I really am useless...
Bow!
You said yer kung fu could beat any kind of martial art, didn't cha?
I-I didn't mean...
Go!
Point!
That's it?
Aren'tcha supposed to be strong?
I-It's because this is a Judo lesson...
Then try yer kung fu next time!
Yer just a kung fu nerd after all, ain'tcha?
Sakai...
See ya!
See you tomorrow.
Sakai, I'll be giving it my all again today!
I won't be teaching you kung fu anymore.
You saw from our P.E. lesson, didn't you?
In an actual match, I tense up, and I'm completely useless...
But that was just because—
I'm sorry!
Wait, Sakai!
Hmph!
There's no way I would actually lose, after all.
I don't know what this Dark Precure of his is up to, but I wish he'd entrust this to me.
Use that unyielding power of yours to crush the Precure!
Go now, Kumojacky.
Oh, how I have longed to hear those words!
Yoshito!
Hey, bro!
Practice is canceled. We're going home.
Why? Tsubomi's on her way, isn't she?
That's enough!
But...
Yo, Kung Fu Master!
Done playin' kung fu already?
Who the hell are you?!
So this is the guy ya flattened in Judo?
Don't make fun of my bro!
Stop.
But...
Hey, what're you doing?!
You're pretty cheeky for the little
brother of a kung fu nerd, ain'tcha?
Shut it!
Do you got any clue what my bro'll do to you if you piss him off?!
Please do tell.
Well, Kung Fu Master?
Please give back my brother's nunchucks.
If you want 'em back, then yer gonna have ta apologize and admit ya can't do kung fu!
My bro has nothing to apologize for!
He's the Kung Fu Mast—
I'm sorry!
I can't do kung fu...
That's why I can't match up to your martial arts!
Bro!
Well, if ya get it, then ya should stop runnin' yer mouth.
Give 'em back.
Hee-yaaaa!
'ere.
What a wimp!
Yeah!
Why didn't you just beat them up, bro?!
There's no way I could match up to them.
Then forget it!
Yoshito, wait!
Yoshito...
Sakai!
I still think we should train, despite what you said.
I want to bolster my confidence using kung fu!
"Haaaaa!" Like that!
Huh?
Is your little brother not here yet?
He's not coming.
He ran off somewhere.
Did you have a fight or something?
He just realized how weak I actually am, that's all!
What are you saying?!
You're Yoshito's hero, and nothing will ever change that!
I'm going to go look for Yoshito!
Hey, wait up, Tsubomi!
Bro wasn't himself back there!
That weapon of yours looks rather interesting.
Who are you people?!
But such a fine weapon...
is ill-suited to the hands of one whose Flower of the Heart is so weak!
Wha—?!
Give back those nunchucks! My bro gave me those!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
Hee-yaaaa!
We can't seem to find Yoshito anywhere.
Tsubomi, we'll be able to practice kung fu some other time, so—
That's no good!
It's not just about kung fu. Sakai and Yoshito are brothers, so we can't just let them fight like this!
Kibougahana Inari Shrine
All right then!
If that's how it is, Tsubomi, then I'll help you look!
Thank you, Erika!
Hee-yaaaa!
I hate you, bro!
It couldn't be...
It's a Desertrian!
Tsubomi, Erika, hurry and transform!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Stop that at once!
Give that crystal back right now!
So you're finally here.
I've been waiting for you, Precure.
Let's go, Blossom!
Right!
Marine Dynamite!
Hee-ya!
Hee-yaya!
I hate you, bro!
Hee-ya!
Marine Shoot!
Because of those nunchucks, I can't find an opening!
Looks like you're no match, Precure.
Merely watching this is boring me.
I don't want my bro to be so pathetic!
Is that... Yoshito?!
Blossom Impact!
Hey, over here, Desertrian!
Are you all right?!
Y-Yeah!
I hate you so much, bro!
I hate you, bro!
That monster is Yoshito...
That's not true!
The real Yoshito is over there!
Huh?!
Yoshito is trapped within that crystal!
The Precure are in trouble!
I have to save him.
I have to save him!
If bro had actually tried, he would've been able to beat them in a flash!
Your bro can't...
Hmph!
Even if that was true, a coward who can't act when it counts is already a loser before he's begun!
He's not a coward!
At times, everyone feels like things are beyond them!
But you're just using your underhanded ways to play with the bond that ties them together!
I've had it up to here with this!
Hee-yayayayaya!
You'll find no openings in those nunchucks.
Blossom?
Don't think. Feel!
Don't merely perceive with your eyes, but feel it with your heart!
I feel it!
Hee-yaaaa!
Blossom Double Impact!
Tch...
Now's your chance!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Yay! You did it!
Tch... All right, you lot! When we get back, you're redoing your training!
Now, hurry and restore Yoshito to normal!
Restore him!
Okay!
Yoshito... Yoshito!
Bro?
Yoshito, are you okay?
What happened to me?
There was this monster with nunchucks, and then you came and...
Yeah.
I think we might have been dreaming, but everything's all right now!
Is that...
Well, when I get serious, I end up hurting myself a bit!
Hee-yaaaa!
That's the bro I know! I mean... Master!
Of course it is!
Master, let's go train at the park!
Sure!
I think I finally understand.
Tsubomi?
Even if I do strengthen myself with kung fu,
if I don't have a heart strong enough to believe I can win, I won't be able to beat anyone.
Jeez, that's what I've been telling you!
Neither of us are weak!
No matter who's in our way, Dark Precure or otherwise, we'll get by somehow!
We can do it... right?
Of course we can!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born...
This will restore the Great Heart Tree a little more!
In the language of flowers, a digitalis means "burning passion."
Hee-ya!
Huh?
Finisher! Form of the Snake! Hiss, hiss, hiss!
Then I'll use the Form of the Tiger! Roar, roar!
Not bad at all, Erika!
You're not so bad yourself!
Those two sure are...
...way too easygoing.
Hee-yaaaaa!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
We're your love-love cupids!
For those of you too timid to make your move, here!
A bouquet of flowers to convey your feelings!
And for those of you too pessimistic about love, try this!
Fairy Drop's alluring fashion!
With our lovely cure-cure special items, we'll bring you young lovers closer together!
We'll make the flowers of love bloom!
HeartCatch Precure:
Hearts Aflutter!
The Great Proposal!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!