Nishimi...
Nishimi.
You're back at the head of the class.
I was worried with your grades dropping there for a while,
but it looks like you've straightened out your act.
Maybe it's because entrance exams are looming.
Or maybe it's thanks to the disappearance of that impediment to your studies.
Pass it here!
I never thought they'd agree to open up the roof, but they went right for it.
Yeah, I heard a third-year thug was monopolizing the key up 'til now.
Hey, Bon'taro-kun!
I'm playing volleyball with the girls.
How about joining in?
No. I'll pass.
Bontaro-kun!
I know you're lonely without Kawabuchi-kun,
but you've got to get over it.
You're right. Thanks.
Mukae-san!
I bet you're looking for Nishimi-kun.
No, that's not it.
Shirayuri
It's cold!
I love milkshakes when it starts getting cold outside!
Hey, Ritsuko-san? Are you awake?
Yeah.
Could it be you're worried about
Kawabuchi-kun after he disappeared?
Y-Yeah, there's that too.
I know! It's Nishimi-san, isn't it?
Like, you haven't been able to talk at all or go home together recently?
Ricchan, you can't just wait.
You need to make things happen yourself.
Hey, look!
Isn't that Nishimi-san?
Ricchan...
Were you eating sweets?
You've got whipped cream on your mouth.
Um, Kaoru-san...
You're not coming to the basement today either?
No. Sorry.
With entrance exams coming up, I've decided not to go for a while.
I see. Yeah, that makes sense.
Tell Pops that I'm sorry for not being able to come.
Well, see you.
Wait!
Kaoru-san, um...
Why not study at my place?
MUKAE
RECORDS
JAZZ
POP
CLASSI
The shop's closed today?
Where's your dad?
He's off buying up stock, so it's just me today.
Give me a second.
I'll clean up here.
That one's my favorite photos. I always have it out here.
Both of you look so happy in the picture.
Look at Sentaro's face.
Stop talking about him.
Shall we get started?
English and math, right?
So first of all, the word order is reversed.
This "so" comes first, and the subject and verb change places.
What?
Um... I'm sorry about before.
I wasn't thinking about how you felt when I showed you that photo.
Since Sentaro left, you're the one it's hit the hardest, isn't it?
I'm fine.
He may not be around, but I've still got you, Ricchan.
W-Wait, Kaoru-san!
Don't! Hey...
Kaoru-san, w-wait.
I'm glad he's gone.
Now I can be alone with you whenever I want.
Stop it!
How...
How could you say that?
You're happy that Sentaro is gone?
Even if you're joking, I don't want to hear such a thing!
I'm sorry about that.
Ricchan, I haven't been able to say this before,
but I'm going to a college in Tokyo.
I'll go home for today.
I'm scum!
The lowest of the low!
Dammit! Why did things turn out like this?!
They didn't call Kawabuchi-kun's name, huh?
What's the difference?
Everyone's going their own way.
We'll all forget being here in no time.
Nishimi-kun...
I won't ever forget your performance at the school festival last year!
Excuse me...
Maruo-san?
Could I have the second button on your jacket?
Sure, if you'd be satisfied with mine...
I'm thrilled!
I wasn't sure if I'd be able to ask you.
I was crying my eyes out.
I'm so happy!
Farewell and good riddance to this damned slope!
Don't go trudging up the thing tomorrow out of habit!
I see.
So you're going off to college in Tokyo too, Prince Bon?
Well, it'll probably get a little lonely around here.
Nah, we can't get gloomy about it.
It's great news, isn't it?
Oh, that's right.
Ritsuko was accepted at the college here.
Hey, Ritsuko! Come down!
Prince Bon got into college! Hey!
Ricchan! You can stay there, but just listen!
I'm sorry about the other day!
You may not want to hear anything from me, but just let me say this!
The reason I started coming here is because I wanted to see your smile!
Ricchan, your smile always encouraged me, even when things were rough.
I never knew that feeling before meeting you.
Thank you, Ricchan.
Meeting you was a blessing.
Call us as soon as you get there.
I will.
Kaoru-kun, write me, okay?
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you for everything.
The sleeper express train, Sakura, will depart for Tokyo on track one.
Its next stop will be Haiki.
All passengers, please board.
Hey!
I made it in time!
Here, a little going-away gift.
Thanks, Pops.
Um... Is Ricchan...
Nope. But there's a lunch in there that Ritsuko made for you.
Well, take care, Bon.
I will. You too, Pops!
See you again!
Ricchan!
EAST HIGH DIPLOMA
DOCTORATE DEGREE
It's okay.
When you're sick, you're apt to lose heart,
but sickness and health start with the mind.
Doctor, you have a good head on your shoulders for someone so young.
Oh, no. I'm still a rookie.
Dr. Nishimi, we've got an emergency.
Okay, I'll be right there!
Hey, there's a free bed in the nap room.
Why don't you get a little rest?
No, if I lie down now, it's all over.
I won't be able to come back.
Yeah, being a resident on the night shift is even harder than I heard it'd be.
It takes a lot of stamina.
Tell me about it.
Our guest is a popular star who both sings and acts.
Matsuoka Seiji-san joins us in the studio today!
Hello! I'm Matsuoka Seiji!
Guest: Matsuoka Seiji
I want to start right off with a question.
Which do you like better, singing or acting?
What's wrong?
Th-That's...
I like them both.
...a classmate from high school.
Huh? My little sister goes nuts over that guy!
And I like jazz too.
Hey! Get me an autograph!
Oh, jazz?!
I see.
So Matsuoka's dream came true.
Dream...
It can't be.
Kaoru-kun?!
Kaoru-kun, is that you?!
Yurika-san...
How wonderful! You've become a doctor!
Um...
Oh, I'm six months along.
Junichi-san wants a girl, but I wonder.
I think he'd spoil her rotten.
How are you? Have you been good?
Do you still play the piano?
No.
I'd heard that Sentaro-kun had taken off, but you've never seen him since then?
Oh, that's right.
This is no time to be catching up.
There's something I've been carrying around to show everyone.
A friend from back home sent me this photo,
but don't you think the person on the far left looks like someone we know?
U-Um...
Can I borrow this photo?
What the hell am I doing?
I've been trying to forget him all this time,
but my heart is beating fast.
There's no way I can stop this rhythm in my heart.
If you want the church, it's at the top of the slope.
Young priest? Dunno.
The priest here has been around for years and years.
Yeah, I think he helps raise the orphans from around the prefecture.
He raises children?
Yes, you mean the priest-in-training.
Though I hear he does nothing but cause trouble for the poor priest.
Th-Thank you!
Could it be...
Could it be him?
What the heck is this?
Lucky!
Pick me up too!
What's wrong?
I always thought this day might come sometime.
Looks like it's today.
Enough!
What do you two think you're doing?!
I told you that you can only play on special occasions, but again, you do as you please!
Uh-oh! Run, Bon!
Hey, wait! Sen!
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
It's been a long time. How are you? I'm writing now because there's something I want to tell you, Ritsuko-chan. A friend of mine from back home got married at a church, and in a photo of the ceremony that she sent me, there's a priest who resembles Sentaro-san. I'm not sure of it, but I thought it would be worth looking into. The church is on a small island, so it should be easy to find. I just wrote this postcard to let you know. If you find anything out, please write back.Yours truly,Yukari Fukahori
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.