Sign: Shonan Hospital
I'm healed! Let me out!
It'll take two more months before you're fully recovered!
Listen to me!
Good grief.
I've been looking after patients from Shonan for a long time,
but you're the first one who's wanted to get out early.
What, are you lonely?
Shut up.
Hey, Sakuragi.
Those boys were so worried that they even donated blood.
Take care of yourself, okay?
The six boys in 2-6 were moved to a small temporary cell.
Ishihara was placed under house arrest.
He was replaced as warden of Compound 2...
by Kumagai.
The six no longer had to fear Ishihara...
and could live quietly for the first time since their arrival.
How about that?
But it was only a brief respite.
Sign: Shonan Hospital
What, release him?!
You want to release Sakuragi?
Since he wants it so badly.
But...
Are you worried?
You've been paying such close attention to him.
Yo.
Bro!
Bro?
Why are you all so surprised?
We thought you'd be in there a whole 'nother month!
I'm not that much of a softie.
Weren't you just lonely without us?
No way!
One month after the fire,
Sakuragi returned to 2-6.
Hey, Sakuragi.
Don't overdo it.
Yeah, Bro. Get some rest.
Mr. Kumagai's right.
What are you talking about?
I haven't worked outside for a long time. I need exercise.
All right! Fifteen-minute break!
Man, it's peaceful.
Ishihara's gone, and Kumagai's a nice guy.
Bro...
you're getting released in a month, right?
Yeah.
Once you're out,
are you gonna start boxing again?
Yeah.
That's all I can do.
I don't want to give up boxing halfway.
I'm going straight for the women!
They must be so lonely out there without me.
There you go again.
And once I meet up with them outside...
How about you, Cabbage?
What are you going to do when you get out?
Eat lots of tasty things!
Just what I expected from you.
Aren't you listening to me?
Mario, how about you?
I haven't really thought about it.
Weren't you going to try boxing?
You've got the talent for it.
Me?
What about you, Soldier?
I'm joining the SDF.
Oh, right.
I'm gonna get rich.
I've got plenty of ideas in my noggin about making a killing.
How about Joe? You're gonna be a singer, right?
Yeah, I will!
You're all invited to my debut concert.
I'm looking forward to it!
Yeah!
Hey, everyone.
I'll be out there waiting, a step ahead of you.
You'd better all make it out.
Since we're all looking forward to it,
why don't we leave a memento here?
Sounds good.
Then...
Why don't we carve our dreams on this tree?
Then we'll all meet back here the summer after next.
That's great.
Good idea.
All right, it's settled. Let's carve!
I'll go first.
I see.
So you're back starting today.
Yes.
Now that I think of it, Sakuragi's out of the hospital and due for release in a month.
Don't worry.
I know just how to silence him.
However, you were involved in the fire.
You mustn't be too obvious.
Let's try to keep it legal.
Legal, huh?
Yes.
That's it.
There was a real cutie in last week's batch.
Take care of it, Ishihara.
You liked him too?
Hey, Cabbage, you wrote "lots" as "lost."
Huh, you're right.
How dumb are  you?
Turtle, your "h" is too big.
Hey, nothing wrong with big dreams!
You're the only one left, Mario.
Hey!
Break's over! Back to work!
You guys go ahead.
I'll write something and then catch up to you.
The boys were like caged canaries...
singing happily of when they'd be free.
What song pleases them the most?
Which melody, which rhythm?
Will their dreams come true?
Even as the storm howls...
Even as they starve...
They are preparing for it.
Afterwards, with guts, courage, and a little luck, their dreams will come true.
The seven canaries believed this.
Okay, now what?
Ishihara!
Sakuragi Rokurouta. Step out of the cell.
You're being moved.
Get out here, Sakuragi.
Bro, they're moving...
Don't worry. They're just moving me to the release holding cell.
Release holding cell?
It's where they go over everything pre-release.
Later.
Bro!
The release holding cell burned down in the recent fire.
It's simply an administrative issue.
Try to take it easy for your last month.
I hope you boys get along well.
Okay?
So there you are.
I've heard all about you.
Let's be bros, 'kay?
Happy to meet ya.
I see.
The boys in cell 8 will do just fine.
They know just what I want.
So there's no need to get our hands dirty.
Indeed.
All we have to do is sit back and wait.
Ishihara!
Why did you move Sakuragi to Compound 1?!
Ishihara, are you-
Fresh meat like you should mind its own business.
Just shut up and do what I tell you.
So you're going to do it.
I'm almost out of here.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
Try not to kill me.
What, you can't sleep?
Isn't there something funny about Ishihara coming here?
Bro, are you gonna be okay?
Sakuragi set himself the task of getting back outside without breaking.
However, Sasaki and Ishihara, afraid that their evil deeds would come to light,
had decided to silence Sakuragi by snuffing out his life.
The bell rang for that month-long final round.
This should be good enough for today.
Yeah.
We can have fun playing with you all month.
Don't let us down and croak halfway through.
How's it going?
That bastard Sakuragi isn't resisting at all.
He's like a human sandbag.
I see.
But... he smiles.
No matter how much we hurt him, he still grins.
It's a little creepy.
Then just kill him.
What are you doing, Mario?!
Hurry and sit down!
The guards will notice you!
Bro...
He's not here today again.
He's not reacting like I'd expect a boxer would.
Yeah. He's too tough.
Shut up. We've got three more weeks.
We still have time.
We'll have plenty of fun.
Do you know something?
If you know something about Sakuragi Rokurouta, tell me.
Where'd you come from?
Oh, that's it. You're from 2-6.
Hey, Mario!
You know something, don't you?!
Yeah, he's in 1-8.
So why isn't he coming here?
It's part of his pre-release training.
He's always on a different schedule.
What are you doing?!
Where'd you get those scratches?!
What did you do to Bro?!
We didn't do anything.
He's just so energetic that we have to put him down every night.
Nice and soft like.
What?
Funny to think the hero of 2-6 is a pansy that won't fight back.
Is he...
a boxer too?
Hey! What's going on?!
Hey, Minakami!
Let me go! I'm gonna kill him!
Let me go!
Dammit!
Knock it off, Minakami!
What were you thinking, Mario?
What does beating up someone from 1-8 solve?!
I...
Bro's the one who's going to suffer for it!
Think about what's going to happen before you do things!
Bro's going to...
Here ya go.
We brought your dinner.
Dig in, Sakuragi.
Not good enough for the hero of 2-6?
Hey...
He should be screaming by now!
Calm down, Yokoyama.
He's not gonna fight back at all.
We've got a toy for three more weeks.
Let's have fun.
I'd like to talk with you.
It's you!
You've got some balls coming over here alone.
This is how I'm going to apologize for punching you yesterday.
Punch me until you're satisfied.
But in exchange...
just leave Bro alone.
Oh? Sounds like fun.
I don't care what happens to me.
Just...
Just leave Bro-
You've picked up boxing, haven't you?
Your right hand is pretty important then.
Here we go.
Let's go, Mario.
Three.
Two.
One!
Zero!
Bro... Just make it through three more weeks.
Oh, man.
You're such a bore. You should look more pained.
Mario's more fun to pick on.
Mario?!
Yeah. He's a lot cuter than you.
He came crying, begging us not to touch you.
So we smashed his hand.
Nice and pulpy.
Mario's... hand?!
He'll never be a boxer now.
Never, huh?
It's an emergency!
Open up!
This boy's hand is terribly hurt!
I thought your half-assed beatings were better than Ishihara's dirty tricks.
That's why I put up with them.
But now you've gone too far.
He could endure anything they did to him,
but he couldn't forgive them for hurting his friends.
With three weeks until his release,
Sakuragi's rage boils over.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Insatiable bloodlust.
Hidden truth.
Sakuragi accepts his fate.