When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Where am I...
What happened...
What happened to me?
It's a very ugly robot.
Eight.
I'm going to get serious now.
I remember it all, now.
I...
I can't let it end here!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
That voice!
It's like a scream of suffering.
Fantasy-Science Thriller, start!
Butler uniforms aren't the best on you, after all.
Eh? What?
Are you going to...
Yes! Super-Moe pose.
No, we'll save that for another occasion.
"Another occasion"?
So I'm scheduled to cross-dress?
Wh-What was I imagining?
Yeah, at some point.
Depending on the ratings, it may come earlier than later.
But leaving that aside,
today, we're going to the amusement park,
so I was thinking that outfit isn't the best for it.
Amusement park?
Therefore, let's get him changed.
Help me, Maria!
Yes.
Wait! Please! I can get changed myself!
You look pretty good.
Geez, I can get changed myself.
In clothes like that, you look like the boy you should be.
Let's go now, Hayate.
Yes.
Nagi, your hat!
Eh?
But Milady, is it all right for you to go to the amusement park?
Fine how?
Well, you are a hikikomori after all.
Don't treat me as the epitome of a modern culture epidemic.
But you are not comfortable leaving the house, right?
Don't be a fool; what are you saying?
Who would leave the house just to go to the amusement park?
Eh?
It's on the grounds.
Is...
Is this Michael ****son's house?!
Pop!
See, we didn't have to leave the house, right?
Wow, the Sanzenins' quality is incomparable to others'.
But Isumi and Saku's houses have them, too.
Are you all Pres***, owning various things by yourselves...
But why come to an amusement park all of a sudden?
Well, that's because, at the beach class,
I couldn't play much with you because of all that happened.
And, I wanted to spend the remaining short break with you...
Ah, well... you know...
But, an empty amusement park is a little lonely.
Hey look, look, friends of the forest!
What?
A new friend has come today!
Milady, what's this?
It's an amusement park,
so of course there are mascot characters.
I'm this Nagi Nagi Land's fairy of the forest, Keru Naguru-chan!
Keru Naguru-chan = Kick Punch-chan.
I'd hate to be named like that.
But really, it's been forever since we last had a visitor here.
Seriously... Thank you for coming.
Thank you so much!
I think I just heard his true voice.
B-By the way, when was the last time you came here, Milady?
I think three years ago.
Three years?
Three years...
The person inside must have it tough.
There's no one inside!
But you're a costume...
I said there's no one inside!
We're the fairies of the forest!
Yes, we're fairies!
Everyone!
Nagi Nagi Stretch is starting!
But why did you build such
an amazing amusement park in the house?
The old man gave it to me a long time ago for my birthday.
Old man...
That person I met...
What's wrong, Hayate?
N-No, nothing.
But, a birthday present, huh?
I guess he's a good grandfather to you.
Do you really think so?
He isn't?
If you really think so, then take a good look around.
Good look?
The rides in this park turn out to have...
a minimum height restriction of 140cm.
A minimum of 140cm!
And another of 140cm!
So I can't ride most of the rides here.
It's a very expensive prank.
That old man would never do anything that would make me happy.
That's why I hate him.
She's still small and can't ride, but you can, right?
Everyone, come over here!
We have the first person to ride the rides!
Eh?
EH?!
Are you all right, Hayate?
Yes, but I'd prefer something a little more safe next time.
Then how about the Haunted House?
Haunted House?
That sounds good.
That doesn't have a height restriction.
No! W-W-W-What are you saying?
T-T-T-The Haunted House is scary!
Well, that's what Haunted Houses are made for.
No, I'm not scared.
I'm not scared, you hear?
But... it's dangerous if there's a hole in the floor.
This isn't good. At this rate, they'll skip the Haunted House.
Waste of all the practice.
But we might get fired if we make her cry.
That'd be a problem.
I'll go check if there's anything dangerous.
If you insist so much.
He's entering....
Alone?
All by himself?
Then we'll trip him up.
We are?
I'll be off then.
Take care, all right?
Wow, they made a really good one.
It really is amazing.
Milady might cry because of this.
What was that for?
It's my job to scare you.
I'd die before being surprised!
But don't worry, I'll use the flat of the blade.
I don't see a flat.
Hayate.
I might be allowed to use the move in this situation.
Please make sure to get permission.
Dra*** Shiryu ultimate move.
Roza-
Not happening, baby.
What is this about?
I feel threat from you while you're trying to fake an accident.
What am I doing this for?
That's because...
...I have a grudge against you, I guess.
Y-You're!
Who were you?
You don't remember me?!
I don't know who you are,
but what grudge do you hold against me?
I won't forgive you.
Click.
You can't see me in this dark, can you?
I'll be moving to your side now.
Damn it.
Can you handle the pressure?
We turned the light on so our Lady wouldn't be scared.
You're right; I won't be scared with this.
Hayate! You're safe!
Y-Yes.
What is that?
I don't know what that is, but it's a very ugly robot.
Y-You...
...little brat!
Die!
Milady! Watch out!
What do you think you're doing when you're new here?
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I've been waiting here for years!
Damn you!
Debt-ridden butler, you'd better remember this!
I'll definitely come get my revenge!
Wh-What was that?
No clue.
Milady.
Let us go on.
It's summer, after all.
Please enjoy the amusement park to your heart's content.
Hayate.
Yeah, let's go!
I'm so bored.
Not a single customer's coming...
It's the summer, so I was hoping I might get to see Hayate-kun if I worked here, but...
Hayate! Hurry!
Let's get on the Merry-Go-Round next!
Yes, Milady!
Love. It's about crossing paths.
Continuing to Part B.
Tou tou yonin gumi
Tou tou yonin gumi = We're finally a group of four.
Mimi no nagai doubutsu nanda?
Mimi no nagai doubutsu nanda = What animal has long ears?
We will now start the test of the new nursing robot, Nine.
Contact! Activate Nine!
Activating!
Deploy targets!
Fire Nursing Missiles!
All missiles hit!
Good. Fire Nursing Laser!
Okay, activate Nursing Rugio Hammer.
Note: This is a pun on "Kaigorudion" (Kai Goldion) vs. "Kaigo Rudion" (Nursing Rudion)
Approved!
We tried, at least.
The experiment is a success.
Now there will be no enemies against the elderly.
Chief! A high-speed unknown is approaching Nine!
"Unknown"?
It's too small to identify.
Nine, intercept it!
Boost, on!
M-My Nine...
All right, I got the controller chip.
Insert.
Spin spin spin spin.
Now that debt-ridden butler isn't my rival.
Hey!
You robot there!
What company's spy are you?
M-Makimura-san.
Even you forgot about me?
Wait!
That robot looks familiar.
Damn it... Makimura-san, please wait for me.
I'll... I'll definitely...
Maria, today was really, really fun!
Hayate would go wham and bam!
Yes, yes.
Hayate enjoyed it a lot, too.
Doing good things for other people makes you happy, too, doesn't it, Maria?
I understand you, so you should get your sleep.
I wonder if Hayate-kun's all right.
I did all the first aid I could.
I'm burned out.
I'm white ash.
It's my chance.
I'll do him in and...
Hold it!
Huh?
He's mine!
You're the robot from the afternoon!
You're the nursing robot that came out
in episode three and got defeated by Hayate,
Eight!
Oh!
You know me?
Tama, how do you alone remember him?
Hayate, unlike you,
who is sitting pretty on the main character's seat,
I'm watching this anime's opening every week to the point that I have it down solid.
Because it's the only section where I am sure to show up!
And this Eight is in a similar situation.
He doesn't have any show time in the show,
yet shows up in the opening.
That's why I noticed!
Eh? Was this robot in the opening?
I haven't seen the kind people recently, either.
So, time to get my revenge!
It's a really pounding background noise.
What's going on?
Let's leave it to Hayate.
He's in great condition today.
Whee...
Revenge? It's your own fault for losing control!
Shut up! Because I lost to you, I... I lost everything!
Eight, you have to become the world's best nursing robot.
I did tests after tests to meet the scientist's standard.
It was boring, but I did my best.
Because...
Are you doing okay over there, Eight?
Because she was there.
Eight!
You're amazing!
You're so cool, Eight!
Eight~
Beat the Vandel ******.
She was everything to me.
But that day!
What? Eight lost to a trash among humans?
Defeated in such a way, too?
My nursing missiles were ineffective?
Chief...
Then I guess we'll terminate development.
Beside, it's wrong to try and let robots do everything.
Plus the design and the functions were so lame.
Ch-Chief!
I lost everything as such
and got thrown away as noncombustible trash.
Chief has her own world and is forgetful, so she forgot about me...
...and was working on developing a new nursing robot.
But... But my heart won't be salvaged with that.
In order for me to get her smile back,
Hayate, I need to beat you and that twin-tailed brat!
Wh-What? You're only a pet.
Shut up, you scrap ****!
I don't care what you do to the miserable, stupid, human trash, debt-ridden butler,
but I won't forgive anyone who tries to hurt the Lady.
You're right; Our Lady is selfish, self-centered, and rude.
Her acts are based on whims, and she never admits mistakes.
She's tougher than others,
doesn't know the real world, is cheeky,
but can't sleep alone at night.
She proclaims to have high athleticism when she doesn't.
As such, she's a failure as a human,
but she's the one who saved my life.
What's wrong, Nagi?
I don't know, but I feel like someone just spoke badly of me.
So, I'll destroy everything that becomes Our Lady's enemy.
Wait!
Hayate! Y-You...
You're going to shield him when he tried to kill you?
I know the sadness of being abandoned and forsaken.
But, because there was a person who saved us...
...we are here today!
You understand that, too, Tama.
So you...
So you understand how I feel?
Since I've gone through a similar experience.
I see.
If you understand my feeling,
then be killed by me!
The sound's getting louder.
According to the report from Security, the nursing robot from sometime ago is here for revenge and is causing a rampage.
Are you sure you don't need to go save him?
Hayate won't lose against someone he fought once before.
But apparently he versioned up to 8.1 and powered up.
8.1? That's just adding a patch file.
Besides, Hayate is fighting for me.
Doesn't that turn you on a little?
I hope he hasn't turned into a ball of flame.
Take this, my new ultimate mode that came with the new version!
Mosquito Destroy Mode!
Japan's summer is filled with mosquitoes.
It's a necessary mode for providing the nursed one a pleasant sleep.
Um, how about we call it quits?
You won't win against us with that.
Shut up! I must have her-
Eight!
Th-That voice... It can't be...
C-Chief!
Eight, thank goodness, you were here.
I remembered about you.
S-So? What did you come here now for?
I'm already abandoned by you.
I'm sorry.
But you got it all wrong.
There was a slight mistake.
Chief...
I was thoughtless and threw you out as noncombustible...
I'm really sorry...
Chief...
I was wrong.
It's fine now.
Eight, you are not noncombustible trash.
It's so tear-jerking.
Yes.
You're oversized trash.
Hello, we're the ones you called for.
Please take care of it.
Is this it?
Yes, take it away, please.
Ch-Chief?
Do you know there's a law for recycling household appliances?
You're not supposed to throw
large electronic devices away on the street.
But don't worry, they'll take you apart and trash you properly.
Bye now.
We're lucky Milady was the one that picked us up.
Yeah.
Wait, this isn't the right way to end this at all!
We need to do something to save Eight!
But how?
Leave it to me.
Hey, this Makimura?
It's me, Sanzenin Nagi.
Listen, you mustn't break that rundown robot.
That's right.
Didn't I sound just like her?
I never knew you had such a trick!
Hayate! Hayate!
Did you use Kamehame** to defeat him last night?
No, I can't use that yet.
By the way, soon after leaving the mansion,
Makimura-san, please go out with me!
What? Sure.
Eight started a new life.
Next time, we'll fight against the lord of the lake to be the champion of the Slympics.
Nagi and...
Isumi's...
Butler Network!
Last week, Isumi couldn't say anything about the song, so today, I'm here to support her.
Thank you, Nagi.
So Isumi, this song is, you know, slow like you, and then thickened and has fat added and all cooked together.
I don't think that made any sense.
Anyway, it's a nice song.
Thank you, Nagi.
Bye bye.
This time, it's fishing.
We'll catch all we can!
First, it's fly fishing!
Fly fishing? Isn't that challenging?
In "I Love Fishing. Sanpei", Sanpei-kun was catching one fish after another using flies.
There isn't anything I can't do when Sanpei-kun can.
Milady, it's not good to mix manga and reality.
Hit, hit, hit!
DAAAHH!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Who Came Up With the Onomatopoeia "Kapo~n"? It's Amazing.
I didn't expect Hayate to come so close the moment we were alone.
The entertainment level will be in the red zone as usual.