Your call can not be connected at the moment.
Please leave a message after the beep.
U-Uh, Kushieda?
It's about tonight's party...
Ryuuji, you there?
I'll call you back later.
Hey, open your window, Ryuuji!
You have to come no matter what, okay?
It'll definitely be fun! Bye!
Hey, Ryuuji!
You're so slow!
What were you doing?
No, what are you do-
Catch this.
Why did you do that out of the blue?!
You're so viole-
Whatever. Just open it.
Huh?
You'll understand when you open it.
I have to get ready, so I'll come over in half an hour.
Later.
Hey!
What's going on? What's going on?
My silky love
nijuuyon jikan zutto
24時間ずっと
Every hour of the day
My silky love
kimi no koto omou tabi
キミのこと想うたび
whenever I think of you
My silky love
modokashii kono kimochi
もどかしいこの気持ち
these impatient feelings
My silky love
tada afurekaetteku
ただ溢れかえってく
simply overflow.
suki to ieba kantan na no ni
スキと言えば簡単なのに
Even though it's easy to say "I love you"
kimi ga mae ni kichau to
キミが前に来ちゃうと
when you stand in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
個性がそびえ　私のコトを邪魔してる
my personality stands up and gets in my way.
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
いつもならば強気でイケる
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku na no ni
そんな性格なのに
that's just how I am.
donna ganbatte mite mo kabe wa kuzusenai
どんな頑張ってみても　壁は崩せない
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us.
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
察して欲しい…　この気持ちを
I want you to realise… my feelings.
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
だから私は　いつもキミに
So I always send a gaze
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
大好きだよと送る視線
of "I really love you" your way
saidai no yuuki de
最大の勇気で!
with all of my courage!
yaburesou na shiruku no haato
破れそうなシルクノハート
My flimsy silky heart.
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
キミに逢って気づいた　やっと
After meeting you, I finally realised
ai ni wa bukiyou dattan datte
愛には不器用だったんだって
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love.
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
忘れかけた恋の傷跡
The scars from love that I'd almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashita no kyun to
急に疼きだしたの　キュンと
have started to ache all of a sudden.
itsuka wa watashi rashiku suki to
いつかは私らしくスキと
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
言わなきゃ…今より弱くなっちゃうよ
I must say "I love you", or else I'll become even weaker.
Holy Night Party
Coming!
Wow! You look so cute, Taiga-chan!
Ryuu-chan, come over here and check her out!
O-Okay...
Ryuu-chan, you look amazing!
That's good, it's the perfect size.
I-Is it okay for me to borrow these clothes from you?
You're not borrowing.
They're yours now.
Mine?!
The name "R. Aisaka" is sown inside!
Isn't this is your father's?
He just sort of left it because it didn't fit him, so it's okay.
Just take it.
Wearing his cast-offs? Are you messing with me?
If you don't want it, I'll just throw it away.
These small chores really suit you.
You were the one who told me to take it.
D-Destroy the evidence!
How can you say something like that when you can't even say your name?
All right!
Magical Girl Ya-chan will cast some magic on you two!
Magic?
Now don't go too wild.
Once the party starts,
this will smell really good mixed in with your scent.
And you, Ryuu-chan...
Here.
This is...
Is this my father's-
Nope.
A long time ago, when I ran away from home,
I took a few valuable things with me.
That means this is my grandfather's.
Correct!
S-Stolen goods?
Write down your name and class when you enter!
Hey, you'll a catch a cold like this.
Wow, there are a lot of people.
Just how many are here?
It doesn't matter. There's only one important thing...
There's something you have to do tonight, get it?
Y-Yeah...
Oh! Yuri-chan-sensei, you dressed up!
So the reason you're not coming to the party is because you have a date.
It's not a date.
I'm going to a course for single women about buying real estate.
Huh?
Real estate?
Yeah, I'm going to buy an apartment.
Why today, of all days?
Well, that's because women who date on
Christmas Eve are far from being prepared.
When you find something you want, you have to get it right away!
Um...
Anyway, I need to worry about buying an apartment.
I'll be leaving now.
Everyone, try to stay out of trouble!
Okay...
Oh, my.
Oh, hello.
Thank goodness the Christmas tree was fixed.
Your grades went up too, so I'm really happy.
Thank you, Sensei.
I knew you'd be rewarded for all the effort you put in.
Yeah, and you'll definitely get what you want as well!
A fantastic single life is waiting for you!
Right, thanks.
Hey, everyone!
I'd like to thank you all for coming out tonight for this party, planned by the God of Broken Hearts!
We went through a lot of trouble,
Hey, Kitamura's clothes...
but regardless, this Christmas party is about to begin.
Stop, we'll lose if you complain.
Everyone, I truly appreciate your cooperation.
I want you all to have a wonderful time tonight!
So...
...are you ready?
We're going to celebrate Christmas Eve, so...
...Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Oh! Drumsticks!
I know what this is!
It's called turkey, right?
No, it's just normal chicken.
Did you hear her?
It's good!
As expected of home-bred turkey!
Yeah...
Nanako, they have cake over there!
You're kidding! Where?
The corner over there.
Shall we?
Let's go!
Kihara in hot pants and Nanako-san in an innocent one piece are really hot.
Speaking of which, why is everyone all dressed up?
I look out of place... I mean, poor.
Hey, over there!
Keep focused while you're walking.
The floor will get sticky if syrup spills on it!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Scary...
Takasu.
I was wondering why I didn't see you.
What are you doing here?
Well, I couldn't stand how the drinks were being handled, so...
By the way, I'm surprised you have such an expensive suit!
Wow...
Isn't that chicken grease on your hands?!
Taka-chan, don't you know?
This is called turkey!
Moreover, it's home-bred turkey!
Kaoru, you're so slow!
Oh, sorry.
What were you looking at?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, right...
I haven't seen Ami-chan yet!
She's here, right?
Y-Yeah, probably.
I think I caught a glimpse of her.
Seriously?! Was she hot?
Was she really hot?!
Is she not here?
And Taiga too...
Taiga, huh?
Well, Taiga isn't bad,
He's right, where did she go?
but I'm all in for Ami-chan.
saa christmas ippai no egao
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of smiles
kimi ni todokenda party night
I've given you a party night
saa christmas ippai no negai
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
I promise you a Holy, Holy, Night
Ami-chan and Taiga?
Woah, amazing!
kotoshi no christmas chotto tokubetsu sa
This year's Christmas is a bit special
white christmas janaku datte
Even though it's not a white Christmas
hoshikuzu no illumination
The illumination of the stardust
When exactly did they practise for this?
hora furitsumoru yo
Look, it's snowing
kirakira kagayaite minna ga shiawase de
It's glittering and shining, everyone is happy
chikachika matataite minna ga yume wo mite
It's flickering and twinkling, everyone is dreaming
saa christmas ippai no egao
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of smiles
kimi ni todokenda party night
I've given you a party night
saa christmas ippai no negai
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
I promise you a Holy, Holy, Night
Santa Claus
Uh, Kushieda?
It's about tonight's party...
Ryuuji, you there?
Hey, open your window, Ryuuji!
I'll call you back later.
You have to come no matter what, okay?
Hey, Ryuuji!
It'll definitely be fun! Bye!
Wow, that was awesome.
Ami-chan and Taiga were both hot, but still cute as well!
Here.
Thank you.
Takasu!
How long are you planning to stay there?
It was like a dream come true!
Huh?
I'm sure it was different than your dreams.
Look, "hot, but still cute", and so on, are basically the same thing.
Oh? Then, am I...
...hot, but still cute?!
You're hot! You're really hot!
H-Hey!
You damn perverted exhibitionist.
Hey, Maruo, what are you doing?
Oh, Kihara!
Do you think I'm hot, but still cute?
Huh? Um...
Isn't that sexual harassment?
Revenge!
Give me some fruit punch please.
Oh, okay.
Kawashima!
So you're here.
Yeah, somehow it turned out like this.
Hey, how was my singing?
It was amazing!
When did you practise for it?
If it wasn't kept a secret, it wouldn't have been a surprise, right?
Were you surprised?
Yeah, I was totally caught off guard.
I see, that's good.
By the way, where's Taiga?
I could tell she tried her best,
so I wanted to give her some fruit punch as a reward.
Taiga left already.
You didn't know?
O-Oh...
Seriously?
You didn't notice?
She's going to Minori-chan's place.
She said she was going to get Minori to come here and then go home.
It was something about welcoming Santa, I think.
Why is she doing that?
Why is she going home?
I don't know, but maybe there's something she'd rather not see.
That's why I gave you some advice.
Advice?
"I think you should stop playing this childish game of house."
"Why do you have to pretend to be daddy?"
Whatever.
Kawashima!
What the heck?
He didn't even listen to me back then.
To give everyone a happy and joyful Christmas,
I'm prepared to take off one or two
pieces of clothing, or even take it all off.
Is that really all right?
I want to be good.
I want to be part of the happy, glittering scene on Christmas Eve,
while wearing a happy face.
Takasu, can you get me some fruit punch?
I burned too many calories.
Kitamura.
I'm going out for a bit.
Hey, Takasu!
As I thought,
something's wrong!
Is that it?
Kushieda
Really?
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
Ryuuji is waiting for you to come.
He said he won't leave until he sees you.
He's even prepared to live at school.
I'm sorry, Minorin,
but it's not that you don't like him, right?
I understand.
Because we're best friends,
there was no other choice.
Santa isn't here yet.
As I thought, it doesn't work if I'm only good around Christmas.
Actually, there's no Santa.
That's why I'll be alone this year.
I'll also be alone next year...
...and forever and ever...
I'll never have someone to rely on,
and I'll be all alone.
No one to rely on?
What's that?
It's coming from my bedroom.
S-Santa?
H-Hang in there!
You're heavy!
Are you really Santa?
What is this?!
Hey, come here!
Look, Santa!
That's my Christmas tree!
I knew you'd approve!
Yay!
I knew this would be the best!
Amazing! Amazing!
Santa praised my Christmas tree!
This is real, right?
Wow, my dream...
My dream came true!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Thank you...
...very much, Ryuuji.
D-Don't take it off, you idiot!
G-Give it back!
So tell me, where did you get this?
I borrowed it from a guy who was wearing it.
Oh, what did you do with your suit?
Well, I traded it with the guy who was wearing this.
Oh, I'll definitely get it back later.
I will.
You took it off when it was just about to begin.
You're honestly stupid.
Stupid! Stupid!
Even though I planned everything for you...
Even though you had the chance to meet Minorin!
What do you mean by stupid?
Didn't I tell you to believe in Angel Taiga?
Minorin is on her way to the party.
She's probably already there.
Come on, you can still make it if you hurry.
Huh? But...
I've already changed my clothes,
and I don't want to leave you by yourself.
What are you talking about?
I'm fine now.
A fake Santa and faking being good... It was a fun experience!
Oh, and of course, I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
If by some chance things go well with Minorin,
tomorrow's Christmas meal will be on me!
Chicken and rice bowl!
Beef and rice bowl!
No, we can't have chicken because of Inko-chan.
Then, it'll just be a beef and rice bowl.
Come on, hurry up! Get moving!
B-But...
If you're not there at that party, it'll mean I lied to Minorin, right?
Come on!
Hey, I said wai-
Santa came already, so I have to be good until the end of the year!
So...
...just let me be good.
Getting Minorin to go to the party is my real Christmas present for you.
So please...
...accept it.
Taiga-
Come on, indecisive dog!
Thanks!
He finally left.
I forgot to give this back to him.
This is so troublesome.
Huh?
Why...
Oh, I see.
I was always relying on Ryuuji.
On his kindness...
But those times have passed.
Minorin will definitely fall for Ryuuji,
and Ryuuji truly likes Minorin.
In other words, they both like each other.
Then, I won't be able to...
...stay by Ryuuji's side anymore.
I won't be able to walk by his side.
The one beside Ryuuji...
...won't be me.
I don't...
...want that.
Ryuuji...
Ryuuji!
Ryuuji... Ryuuji...
Ryuuji...
This sucks.
I didn't bring my cell phone,
and my present is still in the pocket of the suit.
What should I do?
It's a great bear, right?
Yo.
Oh, yeah...
K-Kushie-
Takasu-kun.
I'm sorry, but let me speak first.
Do you still remember,
when we were at Amin's villa during the summer,
we had a talk one night about weird things?
It was about UFOs and ghosts...
Y-Yeah.
You know, Takasu-kun.
About UFOs and ghosts.... I really think I shouldn't see them.
I think it'd be best not to see them.
I've been thinking about it a lot recently, and this is what I decided.
I wanted to tell you that.
That's why I'm here.
Kushieda...
I'm sorry for just saying what I wanted to say.
Kushieda will be leaving first.
Seriously?
Wait, what?
Was I...
...rejected?
saa christmas ippai no egao
さあ　クリスマス　いっぱいの笑顔
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of smiles
kimi ni todokenda party night
君に届けんだ　パーティー・ナイト
I've given you a party night
saa christmas ippai no negai
さあ　クリスマス　いっぱいの願い
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
君に誓うんだ　ホーリー・ホーリー・ナイト
I promise you a Holy, Holy, Night
kotoshi no christmas kitto tokubetsu sa
今年のクリスマス　きっと特別さ
This year's Christmas is surely special
lonely christmas ja tsumaranai
ロンリー・クリスマスじゃ　つまらない
A lonely Christmas is boring
egao wa illumination
笑顔はイルミネーション
A smile is an illumination
hora kazatteageru
ほら　飾ってあげる
Look, I'll decorate it
yurayura yurameite minnadete wo tsunagi
ユラユラ　揺らめいて　みんなで手をつなぎ
It's swaying and flickering, everyone is holding hands
pikapika kirameite minna de hoshi miage
ピカピカ　煌いて　みんなで星見上げ
It's sparkling and twinkling, everyone is looking up at the stars
saa christmas ippai no egao
さあ　クリスマス　いっぱいの笑顔
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of smiles
kimi ni todokenda party night
君に届けんだ パーティー・ナイト
I've given you a party night
saa christmas ippai no negai
さあ　クリスマス　いっぱいの願い
Now it's Christmas, there are lots of wishes
kimi ni chikaunda holy holy night
君に誓うんだ ホーリー・ホーリー・ナイト
I promise you a Holy, Holy, Night
Next Episode Preview
Always, like this
I was rejected by Kushieda.
Whenever I close my eyes, I-
Takasu-kun, you're dreaming!
I'm already hearing her usual cheerful voice.
All right, boom!