Marble Doughnuts are the best!
Somethin' wrong?
Dyspairvil!
Girls!
Huh?
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
You ended it already?
Oh, isn't that Kirara?
It's her!
Okay, let's get going.
There she goes...
Bon.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
The Shooting Star, Kirara!
To the Stage Sparkling with Dreams!
Boo-yah!
Nice shot!
Still, you don't play around with us too often.
I need a little fun sometimes!
A bit of exercise never hurt!
One more round!
I'm in!
Back then, I just wanted to protect Rinrin's dream myself.
I don't regret it.
Hey!
Kirara!
Well, uh... you know, your work...
How's that been going?
Don't worry!
I just had a bit too much of it until now.
Well, I can't say you haven't...
You have visitors.
At this hour?
They said it was urgent.
Kirara!
Pres? Rinrin?
Is it true you're on hiatus from modeling?!
Wha?!
Since when?
You want to own up to the Japan Collection incident.
I understand that,
but you know that this industry is too brutal to let young models back into the spotlight so easily.
Besides...
Bonsoir,
Mademoiselle Kirara.
Bauanne? But why?
I feel it'd be a pity to lose your luster so soon.
And so...
I have a proposition.
And it's about work, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Wha? Why?!
I'm grateful for the offer, but I can't do it now.
Kirara, Bauanne's thinking about your fu—
Very well.
Let us go.
Monsieur Bauanne!
Why?
Sorry.
Wait, Kirara!
Kirara!
Why?
Modeling is your dream!
That's why.
I thought I could juggle being a model and a Precure if I put in 200% effort.
But I was wrong.
Treating my work so lightly just pushes the burden onto the president and everyone I work with.
I can't call myself a pro like that.
You plan to sacrifice your dream to fulfill your duty as a Precure?
Yeah. I made up my mind.
I've spent so long chasing after her...
Nobody can light up a stage like her!
Kirara has every right to have her dream come true!
But now...
She didn't sound like she'd be easy to persuade.
I don't want Kirara to lose the radiance of her dream.
But...
how do we...
I know!
I've got a great idea!
I see.
This event sounds splendid.
Very well, I'll approve your request for the ballroom.
Thank you very much!
What?
We're running that at school?
Yeah. I want you all to help!
Of course!
We'd be glad to help!
Thanks!
Oh, the Drama Club might be able to build the set!
Really?
Okay, Prince Kanata. Take care!
I shall.
So it's Kirara...
The four castles may be under the influence of the Precures' hearts.
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
What's this?
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
Schooltime
Scarf Tech!
50-Tip Combo
Scarvelous!
An invitation?
You're invited!
Please come!
It's pitch black...
Welcome...
to Noble Academy's surprise event, the Dream Fashion Show!
M-Minamin?
Fashion show?
Today is an exhibition of dreams.
Let us begin!
It's showtime!
Haruharu!
For our first dream,
the Princess of Flowers blooming for tomorrow!
For our next dream,
a picture book author pouring her heart into her brush!
Come on...
Moving on, our next dream...
is a police officer to keep our city safe!
A doctor to keep us healthy!
Hitomin and Youtan are trying way too hard...
C-Cut it out!
I'm not doin' it!
It's not embarrassing if we're all up together!
Nope, nope, nope!
Next i—
The wait is over.
The most supreme idol under the sun,
Ichijou Ranko, is here!
Here comes my debut self-written single, Ranko Revo—
What're you goons—
Watch the merchandise!
Our next dream is...
a judge!
A pro baseball player!
A traditional dancer!
A flower coordinator!
And today's special guest!
Rinrin?!
Who's she?
She's so petite!
What do you think of our show?
It's a mess.
The stage is shoddy and the models are so amateurish that it hurts to watch.
Well, that's because you're not meant to be a spectator, Kirara.
The first time I saw your show, I was blown away.
You were so beautiful and majestic...
I wanted to be someone who could
chase her dreams as honestly as you.
Just like how you want to protect everyone else's dreams,
we want to support you in reaching yours!
So please, keep trying...
Keep chasing your dreams!
Kirara?
Where's the dressing room?
Took you long enough.
We've been waiting.
We all worked together to design this just for you.
Thank you...
Good grief...
I've got too many nosy friends.
Oh, but they're right...
This is too fun!
Now, what is your dream?
To be the brightest star in the sky...
the number one model in the world!
Haut de gamme, Star Princess.
That was le fantastic spectacle.
Bauanne!
Would you like to discuss my offer once more?
Yes.
Listen to my song!
The Castle of Stars?
So, it's begun...
You shall not revive the castle!
Dystroyvil!
Oh no!
Go forth.
Kirara!
Haruharu!
Something's coming!
I'll clean up here!
Thanks!
See ya.
Dystroy!
What's that?
Doesn't matter!
Because we're unbeatable!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Now...
do prepare yourself!
Dystroyviiiiil!
Flora!
Twinkle!
Shooting Star!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dystroyvil!
Dystroy!
Vil!
Thanks...
Dystroyvil!
Precure!
Scarlet Flame!
Sorry, lizard,
but I'm unstoppable!
Galaxy!
Sharanla, O Galaxy!
Precure!
Galaxy Chorus!
That's the core!
Let's finish it!
Right!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
What was that?
It seemed similar to what we saw in Hope Kingdom.
We've seen this before. It's a...
Royal Majesty!
Where are we?
Cure Twinkle, awaken the Castle of Stars!
Kanata? I got it.
Shimmer, O distant stars!
The sky has returned!
I was talking with Bauanne.
He's starting a new brand soon,
so he wants me to train in Paris to become its official model.
That's super amazing, Kirara!
It's the next step toward your dream! Thank goodness...
Wait, in Paris?
That means...
Yeah... he said to be there in spring.
What does this mean?
It means I won't stay in Noble Academy for much longer.
But...
You're... going, right?
Yeah.
It's already settled.
Then... we've just gotta become Grand Princesses and save Hope Kingdom before then!
Right?
Of course! I've got this, trust me!
You sure do!
Really?
It won't be so eas—
Yes, it will!
Who the heck do you think I am?
You're talking...
to Amanogawa Kirara!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Minami! Here, take an ornament!
Hm?
Oh, my apologies.
Might something be on your mind?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
That doesn't sound like nothing to me.
Minami, you can talk to us about anything!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Gushing Heart!
Minami's True Feelings!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Saitama Prefecture - Reina (Age 6)
Osaka Prefecture - Hanna (Age 6)