Sakuragi
Really?
I can perform in the Western Festival?
You want Joe to perform with your third-rate band?
...but unfortunately, we already have a band.
What do you think?
We're here to settle things.
Minakami Mario.
I need you to tell him about this.
Please, Shigeo.
Brother...
Take that!
Please, stop!
You've done enough!
Joe!
Look at your pretty face now.
Mario...
Minakami Mario...
Ow...
Aw, aren't you on soon?
What will you do?
How much do you want?
I'll pay as much as you want, so stop now!
You're dead wrong if you think money will settle everything.
I don't give a damn about Five Lemons anymore.
I just want to beat your cute Joe to a pulp.
Excuse me?!
This is for making a fool out of me!
You've already done enough!
Mr. Kawamata...
Joe used to be part of your band.
Why can't you just celebrate his success?
Aren't you also pursuing a career in music?
Mr. Kawamata!
Daddy...
Kid, is this note yours?
Yeah, give it back!
Give it back!
I need to go see Minakami Mario!
I need to save Daddy and Joe!
Hey, give it back!
Hey, isn't that note...
Yeah, it's the one I gave Joe.
Give it back!
Please give it back!
Please!
Joe sure sent us a cute carrier pigeon.
Kid, nice job.
I'm Minakami Mario, the man you're looking for.
Now, let's go save Joe and your daddy.
Yeah.
Let's go, Turtle, Cabbage.
Mr. Kawamata...
You asshole!
Mr. Tsubouchi, you shot someone!
You said you were just gonna stop Joe from going on stage.
Yeah, I did.
And I plan to.
I'll keep him off the stage forever.
Mr. Tsubouchi...
Now, playtime's over.
Observe, Miss Yamauchi.
Bye bye, Joe.
Mario...
Who the hell are you?
Turtle, take Joe.
Right.
Cabbage, let's clean up the trash.
Yeah.
Don't think you assholes can get out of this place alive!
Let's stop the chitchat and start the fight.
What are you doing? Do something!
You fucker!
You okay, Joe?
Yeah.
Look at that.
They're having a blast.
The phone...
Daddy!
Shigeo...
Daddy, you're bleeding.
I'm fine.
It's just a scratch.
Sorry I made you worry, Shigeo.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill every one of you.
He's next.
It's almost my brother's turn.
Mr. Arito, over here.
You cleaned them all up?
Okay, let's leave the rest to them and go.
Joe, can you stand?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Where are you planning to go?
Isn't that obvious?
Tell her, Joe.
To the Western Festival stadium...
It's too late.
You'll never get there in time.
Miss Manager,
unfortunately for you,
we disciplinary school grads suck at giving up.
Wait.
Take it.
Cabbage, faster!
I know!
I don't believe in miracles,
but if we can get there in time...
Please, Bro.
Please show Joe a miracle!
Mario and his friends took Joe to the car and rushed to the festival.
"We're always getting in messes like this,
but at disciplinary school,
we never learned how to give up."
Let's hurry.
Get on your knees or whatever and beg them for a chance.
Yeah.
Turtle, go with him.
He'll need the support.
Okay.
I'll definitely see him on stage.
I sure hope Joe gets his chance.
Misfortune was the only thing they attracted.
Joe had lost hope before,
but this time he was completely beat.
"Have I branded myself as a disciplinary school grad?"
"Or was it all God's doing?"
The man with blue eyes stood in silence in the empty hall.
Joe...
They said I was a hundred years too young to miss a performance when I'm not even famous.
Miss Yamauchi, I'm sorry!
I'll start again from scratch.
Please continue to show me the way.
I'll definitely meet your expectations next time.
There is no next time for you.
Performing in this festival was the first and last chance for an unknown piece of trash like you.
Yet you blew it.
I suggest you give up on making a living in this business.
Let's go.
Give me a break!
You're blaming Joe for everything?
This is why I hate disciplinary school kids.
What?!
I was an idiot to expect anything from you.
Mr. Arito...
Miss Yamauchi!
I beg you.
Please...
Please give me one last chance!
You're a really annoying kid.
I don't want to see your face ever again.
It's over...
all over.
Hey, Mario...
Tell me.
Is it pointless for people like us to try?
Cabbage, are we disciplinary school grads just the trash of humanity?
Aren't we...
even allowed to dream?!
What the hell are you crying about?
You can't dream 'cause you went to disciplinary school?
You serious about that, Joe?
Turtle...
It's not over yet.
Sing your song!
We're here to listen to you.
Sing?
This means I get to hear you sing your song.
Got a problem with that?
Hey, I want to hear it too!
Cabbage...
Yeah.
They don't have tickets, but give them a discount.
Turtle, I...
We're not good enough to be your audience?
This might be my final time on stage.
It's not so bad to have you guys as my last audience.
We're not the only ones.
Yeah, I'm sure Bro's here too.
Right.
When you can't sleep at night,
you begin to hear the rain making a melody.
Take a gentle ride on the clouds.
Let's sail towards the future.
On this starless night,
a bridge spans the dark sky.
They say that on rainy days,
you can glimpse the seven-colored illusion.
Something unthinkable may happen along the way...
What's wrong, Joe?
M-Meg?
You shouldn't stop in the middle.
Meg?
I want to hear the rest of the song too, Brother.
Hey, Turtle.
How'd you find Joe's sister?
Oh, you wanna hear about it?
I was arguing with the guards because I tried to come in after the show was over.
Then a woman asked me if I knew Yokosuka Jou.
She said he might be her brother.
I told her that I'd make Joe sing, no matter what,
so if she was sure it was her brother, she should come in.
Turtle, you're so cool!
Yeah?
Unlike your face.
You didn't need to add that.
It's like a miracle.
It's all thanks to Bro.
Bro?
Yeah.
I asked him to show Joe a miracle.
Whose grave is this?
This guy we call "Bro."
He's our older brother.
So...
what are you gonna do now, Joe?
What do you mean?
You wanted to be a singer so
you could find your sister, right?
What are you gonna do after you quit singing?
Who said I'm quitting?
I won't quit.
I have to start again from scratch,
but I'll never give up singing.
Thanks, Bro.
I'll definitely be a singer.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Cabbage dreams of a business where he can be a man.
Following his dream, he steps into an unknown world.