Growl!
One day, an asteroid in the far reaches of the universe called Kumaria went kaboom.
A bunch'a the little bits fell to Earth as a meteor shower.
Kumaria Meteor Shower
HISTORY
Then all of a sudden, every bear on the planet rose to its feet!
Everyone came together and started
attacking humans. Like, I was totally shocked!
The humans built the Severance Barrier to keep us bears out
and tried to chase us away from their world.
But you know what?
We don't listen to those silly human rules! Growl!
We are bears!
Bears eat people. That's just how we are.
And now...
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
Grind... scrape... grind... scrape...
Bears are eating a person!
Shock!
Bear shock!
Those are the transfer students...
I see now... those two were simply taking the form of humans. They're bears!
Lily bear!
Lily bear storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
An atrocious bear attack has brought Izumino Sumika-san's short life on this world to an end.
Hakonaka Yurika
LILY
Yurizono Mitsuko-san will now speak a few words on behalf of the student body
as a final farewell to our departed friend.
Tsubaki Kureha (absent)
LILY
Izumino Sumiko-san was a kind girl.
She cared for the weak and frail and was like a fountain of affection towards those around her.
Regardless of her circumstances,
Yurizono Mitsuko
LILY
she stayed true to herself and lived with a clear heart befitting her name—
Shock!
Is something the matter, Yurizono-san?
N-No, my apologies.
Izumino-san was like a white flower blooming in the fields of spring.
Yurikawa Konomi
LILY
Noble and lovely, with enough resilience to—
Tsubaki Kureha
LILY
It's a lie!
I won't believe that Sumika was eaten by bears.
It must be a lie! Nothing but a falsehood!
Please do not hold it against her that Kureha-chan was not able to attend your send-off.
The poor thing.
She has lost yet another precious person.
Beware
Kureha, did you play nicely with your friend today?
What happened? Why the long face?
Keep your chin up.
You must really care for her, Kureha.
Don't worry. I'm certain you'll see her again.
All you need to do is wish with all your heart.
Mom, I...
No matter how hard I wish, I'll never see Sumika again.
I wasn't able to protect my friend.
Just hearing the word bear
sends shivers down my spine.
And like, what's even the point of the Severance Barrier?
A bear waltzed right in!
Oh, and did you hear that there's
another missing girl in that class?
Seriously?
Then you think a bear got her too?
I'd think so. Nothing's official yet since they haven't found a body.
Why do they all have to look so yummy?
That girl... Tsubaki Kureha isn't here.
Oh, guess not. Can't really do much if she doesn't come to school.
Tsubaki Kureha has a deliciousmell. Growl.
Even though you act cool,
your happy trail's raging like a wild animal's!
Ah, I just want to lose myself in your scent!
I just had a light bulb moment!
I'm such a genius!
I'm not mistaken.
Yurishiro Ginko and Yurigasaki Lulu.
Those transfer students are bears.
How could this happen? What I witnessed in the garden is irrefutable proof.
Mitsuko.
Earth to Mitsuko.
Mitsuko!
Konomi...
What's got your head in the clouds?
You've been acting strange all day.
Nothing's wrong.
Is that girl all you can think about?!
I know all about Tsubaki Kureha,
and how you can hardly keep yourself away.
Tell me why.
If you become friends with her, then you'll be swept into the Invisible Storm as well.
Nothing good will come of it.
Now that Izumino Sumika is dead,
she's guaranteed to be next.
You're right. Tsubaki Kureha didn't back down on her love for Izumino Sumika.
Those who act outside the group
will become targets for elimination.
That is how it is set up.
Then why?
There's something I can't get off my mind.
What is it? You can tell me
anything you're worried about.
Perhaps I should.
Beware
To tell you the truth,
I saw something I shouldn't have.
Hello! It's the transfer students, Yurigasaki Lulu...
Yurigasaki Lulu
LILY
Yurishiro Ginko
...and Yurishiro Ginko.
So anyway, could you spare us a room?
What?
Growl! What an adorable home!
Hey, you could spare your attic, right?
Mind if we use it?
What are you saying?!
Me and Ginko have been sleeping
under the stars ever since we moved here.
We're bound to get fleas and be itchy where the sun don't shine like this!
Pretty please?
Won't you at least let us use your bathroom?
I-I suppose that's fine.
Yay! Negotiation success! I'm a genius!
Don't forget that this is a one-day offer!
Um... Yurigasaki-san!
Just call me Lulu.
I'm also fine with Ginko.
You taste of tears, growl.
Shower! Shower! Showers are so fun!
Bubble, bubble! Scrub, scrub!
Growl! Growl! Growl!
I won't allow you to stay.
This may be a bit rude, but please leave with Yurigasaki-san after you finish drinking.
You were crying, growl.
I wasn't crying!
Growl. Did you know?
Tears of sorrow and loneliness taste the best.
This is heaven!
We even managed to invade Kureha's house.
I really am a genius!
In any case, please leave once Yurigasaki-san is finished.
I don't mind if you want to shower first too.
There's no need, growl.
I see.
What is wrong with this girl? She keeps on staring at me.
Is she trying to bore a hole in me?
That weird "growl" thing is starting to worry me too.
Your love is true.
I could tell by the flavor of your tears, growl.
Flashback
I love you.
I'm in love with you.
What could you know?
I know, for my love is true as well.
You know nothing!
You don't know the first thing about me and Sumika, so don't speak like you do!
Growl.
Tsubaki Kureha, I've longed for you.
We came here to meet you alone.
What are... you talking about?
You reek of a deliciousmell, growl.
Accept my love.
Yurizono-san?
Yurizono-san?!
Step away from Kureha this instant!
Yurishiro Ginko and Yurigasaki Lulu.
I know your true identities!
I saw it all.
Everything you two did that day.
Now, back off!
I won't let you lay a finger on Kureha!
Reveal yourselves!
They're quick at escaping.
Yurizono-san, why...
There's no time to explain.
After them!
What just happened?
restricted number
Hello?
Is your love true?
This is a challenge from the Severance Barrier.
Tsubaki Kureha, if your love is true, then come to the rooftop at once.
The bears are awaiting you.
Who is this? Who are you?
Entrust your body to the bears,
and your love shall be approved.
What does that mean? Answer me!
My love...
call ended
Mitsuko loves her.
She loves Tsubaki Kureha.
I've never seen her act like tha—
I will never forgive that.
Mitsuko is mine alone!
I won't let you have her!
I'll take care of Tsubaki Kureha!
Shock!
I, Yurikawa Konomi, shall eat her!
Bear shock!
Scum!
Scum, scum!
Grind grind grind...
The time of judgement has come.
I shan't forgive the bears.
I will exterminate the bears!
Flashback
What flowers are you planting?
Lilies.
Lilies?
They're my mother's flowers.
Flashback
Wow, it really sprouted!
I always thought that you were supposed to eat lily roots with egg custard.
You're so silly.
I hope they flower soon.
Flashback
It won't be long now.
Yes.
Your love is about to blossom.
My love?
Yes, love.
My... love.
Scum!
I'll prove my love!
I shan't forgive the bears!
I will exterminate the bears!
Why can't I hit it?
Die, you beast!
Die! Die! Die!
I have to kill it... to take revenge for Sumika!
I want to eat!
I want to eat that girl right now!
Enter!
Welcome to the Severance Court.
Severance Court
LOCATION
The Lily Court is now in session.
Lily Court in Session
TRIAL
Growl.
Bearfendant
Yurigasaki Lulu
BEAR
Bearfendant
Yurishiro Ginko
BEAR
Growl growl.
Your Honor!
Less than a week has transpired since the bearfendants last partook of their prey.
This is clearly an act of overeating.
Prosecutor
Life Cool
JUDGEMENS
I declare them guilty!
Objection!
I believe that everyone has their own level of bearing their tummy rumbling!
Defense
Attorney
Life Beauty
JUDGEMENS
Shiny shine!
Objection sustained.
Huh?!
Bears must follow their instincts.
That is sexy!
Shabadadu.
I ask of you, bearfendants.
Will you become invisible?
Or will you eat humans?
We will eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I shall hand down my sentence.
Lily, approved!
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily
Approved!
Approved
Lily approved!
Kureha.
I am going to eat you.
Where is that which I desire?
I shall search for it from within the Invisible Storm.
What are you searching for?
Lick.
Where are you searching?
Bestow upon me the promised kiss!
Scum?!
Scum scum!
Yurizono-san?
I came not a moment too soon.
Are you alright, Kureha? Did it harm you?
I'm fine, but...
There were two bears.
One should still be around here.
Don't worry. Bears are cautious creatures.
It won't attack you today.
But still!
Kureha, you mustn't blame yourself.
Izumino-san's death was no fault of yours.
She was simply a bit unluckier than the other girls.
No... she's not...
I know. I understand.
Yurizono-san...
I...
It's alright to cry, Kureha.
You were a true friend of Izumino-san.
You have the right to shed tears.
This is Unit 105.
Location: Arashigaoka Academy service road.
One bear corpse discovered.
I repeat.
Sumi... ka...
Kureha.
With this, your love will be mine.
Deliciousmell!
My body is aching uncontrollably for you.
But the time is not yet ripe.
Chomp chomp grawl... Chomp chomp grawl...
How unsavory. There really is no taste to be found of an invisible girl.
I finally understand after stuffing myself this much.
Only the forbidden path
leads to true deliciousness.
Only the meat of girls who don't back down on love tastes of pomegranate and honey.
Only that will satisfy my hunger!
Izumino Sumika. You were quite delectable.
It won't be long...
The Invisible Storm will come before long!
I'm quivering with excitement!
Quickly... I want to eat her now!
Tsubaki Kureha!
Grawl grawl!
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger