01}
Welcome to the Velvet Room.
I'm afraid my master is away today.
Or did you perchance intentionally come while he's out?
I see you have obtained yet another Arcana: the Emperor.
I wonder just how far your unparalleled Persona abilities will evolve.
I daresay you have piqued my curiosity.
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
When it's hot out, you gotta match it with hot cup noodles!
It's nice and sultry.
Gotta fight fire with fire!
Doesn't this rock?
Yeah, it does.
Huh? What does?
Summer clothes rock!
You have a perverted look in your eye.
You sound like a creep.
Hey, wait up! He was looking too! Why are you guys only attacking me?
Okay, moving on...
Come on!
We should watch TV every night once the rainy season hits.
You mean the Midnight Channel?
We'll be getting tons of rain.
But I hope it's nice out this weekend.
Why's that?
The school camping trip!
Thursday, June 16th
Sunny
The Day Before
the School Camping Trip
The day before the school camping trip!
Isn't this your guys' first school camping trip?
Each team has to prepare their own meals, right?
I heard all about it!
What should we make?
I was debating between noodles and curry.
I prefer curry.
Then curry it is!
Hey, don't forget about my opinion!
Curry! We gotta do curry!
Camping equals curry!
Geez, we get it!
Uh...
Carrots, potatoes...
So, what do you do on the trip?
We just pick up trash in the afternoon.
What, seriously? No one told me that!
Well, the other stuff is kinda fun.
We get to cook outside and sleep in tents.
The four of us make one team, right?
So do we share a tent?
Guys and girls sleep separately!
That's a shame.
After we were dismissed, though, didn't we go play by the riverbank?
Oh yeah, we did!
You can swim in the river?
Yeah, I guess so. People did it in the past.
I just remembered something.
Sorry! I'll be right back!
Hey! What about the shopping?
What's gotten into him?
Persona!
At Junes, every day is Customer Appreciation Day!
Huh? Where'd they go?
They're still shopping.
Come see for yourself, and get in touch with our products!
Well, I bet we're in good hands with Amagi around.
Every day's great at your Junes!
After all, she's the future manager of a traditional inn.
Persona!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Big Bro!
Oh, Junes!
Every day's great at your Junes!
I'm so jealous! You were at Junes?
Yeah, I went shopping there.
I picked up dinner while I was there.
What did you get?
Ingredients to make curry for the school camping trip and stuff.
Curry? That sounds yummy.
I love curry!
I'll be out all day tomorrow.
That's okay.
I'll be fine.
I can watch the house by myself.
With a red rose in my right hand and a silk hat in my left,
my codename is Magical Experiment X!
Huh?
Wow!
How'd you do that? Again! Do it again!
Okay.
Friday, June 17th
Cloudy
School Camping Trip,
Day 1
School camping trip, day one!
Hanamura!
What happened?
Cu-Cu-Cu...
Culicid?
W-W-Wa...
Worms?
Mosquitoes and worms?
There weren't any in it.
Thank goodness! I was afraid some fell in.
Are you okay, Hanamura?
You know how cooking outside can attract insects!
I don't see what's so funny.
Was the curry too spicy?
I think it's mild.
Don't you, Chie?
Y-Yeah! If you're so worried, why don't you try some?
Good idea! Why don't you give it a try?
Uh...
Well, here I go.
Narukami!
Persona!
What the hell?!
What the hell did you—
I guess we should've taste-tested it.
I didn't have the courage to.
Curry's supposed to be really spicy or kinda mild!
But that thing just stinks!
It's really something.
It's somehow both gritty and slimy! And it's got squishy parts too!
It's so frickin' nasty I can't even swallow it!
Well, it just didn't mix too well.
But we put a lot of love into it.
What the hell kind of "love" did you put in?
Curry uses cornstarch, doesn't it?
W-Why not?
Otherwise, it wouldn't thicken up, right?
So I guess we'll need cornstarch and flour.
Should we use strong or weak flour?
Strong, of course. We're feeding boys.
Next up...
...is red peppers.
It's not curry if it isn't spicy hot.
This thing has spicy in the name! Oh, and pepper!
Pepper comes in black and white.
That's the manager's daughter for ya!
Now for something to bring out the flavor.
Oh yeah, I heard on TV to mix in coffee!
But I hate coffee, so let's use coffee milk instead!
How about sea cucumber? It'll give us a good broth.
Get anything that sounds about right!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Now what? Our team's gonna starve!
I mean, if it was even slightly edible...
But I'm not taking another bite of Mystery Food X.
That curry looks good.
Whoa! Ohtani?
Are those leftovers?
Y-Yeah...
Go ahead and help yourself.
It's got a new twist!
The Underclassman
So is it true Konishi doesn't have to do any homework?
First Aid
Say what? I'm so jealous!
It's no wonder, considering what happened.
The poor guy...
Excuse me.
Oh, uh, yeah?
Can I help out?
It's okay! Really!
But I'm part of the health association.
It's fine. We have everything covered.
Are you sure about participating in the camping trip?
Aren't you busy helping around home?
They'll manage.
First Aid
I'm gonna help pick up trash.
I'll join you!
Konishi, you can stay here.
Excuse me, but he needs an antacid.
My stomach's killing me.
Huh?!
I'm Konishi Naoki.
I hate Hanamura...
and you, too.
He's Konishi's little brother.
Is he now?
We talked a couple times when I was with her.
A friend told me he's been alone a lot since the murder.
Hey! You guys!
Over here!
Come over here!
Persona!
Thanks.
Leave the bowls here.
Thanks again, Aika!
I'm amazed you found us out here.
We might order dinner from you too.
Thanks again.
Oh, nice! You ordered delivery!
You guys are so thoughtful!
We just ordered whatever, though.
Let's eat up before King Moron finds us.
So, what exactly are you doing here?
My teachers threatened to hold me back a year if I skipped the trip.
But the freshmen tent is so quiet you'd think someone died there.
Well, I bet it is when you're around.
I prefer being with you guys, anyway.
Hey, Kanji.
Huh?
Do you know Konishi Naoki?
Naoki, huh? Sure, I know him.
We're childhood friends.
Huh?
What— For real?
So he's...
...Konishi's little brother, right?
We hung out a lot back in elementary school,
but we haven't talked much lately.
What's he like in class?
Is it true he's always being left out?
Dunno.
You "dunno"?! This is important!
I don't know! We're in different classes.
Man, you're no help.
What?! Dude, you're the annoying one.
Hey, what's up?
Done already?
Persona!
Here he is.
What's the big deal?!
If you want to learn more about him, just ask him directly.
But that wasn't the problem.
Uh, wh-what is it?
Uh, well...
Are you being left out in class?
Hey, that's too direct!
That's the first time someone's asked me that straight to my face.
It's actually refreshing for a change.
It's true. Honestly, I feel left out.
It's like everyone's staring at me from a distance.
They're always babying me.
Have you been skipping school a lot?
Yeah, I have to help my family fend off the press and all.
I know how you feel. I have to do the same thing.
Lately, the neighbors have been coming to take shifts.
They tell me to live my life to the fullest for my sister and then start crying.
It's suffocating.
It's yours if you want it.
Huh? A beef bowl from Aiya?
You sure? That's my favorite!
Hey! Those are my seconds!
Just deal with it, Kanji!
Be nice!
Punk, you owe me!
Hey, I'm sorry I said I hated you when I didn't even know you.
I kinda had fun today.
Let's hang out again sometime.
Sure.
Anytime.
Thanks.
Narukami?
Yeah.
We gotta catch the culprit.
Indeed.
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Informed
A
Courage
Fearless
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Generous
Expression
Eloquent
Knowledge
Informed
A
Deduction time!
Kanji's incident disproved our idea that all the victims would be women.
We might be overlooking something.
Not that I can think of any other connection...
Let's try to come up with something, anything!
Oh, yeah.
My mom told me that after Councilman Namatame got fired,
he came back here and inherited his family's business.
I heard that too. Isn't he a deliveryman now?
Didn't he have a fling with Ms. Yamano?
No wonder he got kicked off the council.
But didn't he have an alibi?
He doesn't seem like our guy.
Anything else?
Oh! Actually, I think I got something.
Remember how Ms. Yamano appeared on the news over her affair?
And Konishi was on the news as the one who found the body.
Hey, wait a sec.
Amagi, weren't you interviewed on TV, too?
Yep.
And wasn't Kanji on some special?
Yeah, I wish I could forget.
Then everyone appeared on TV before they vanished.
I doubt it's a coincidence.
It's related to the TV?
So our culprit's gonna go after the next person featured on TV?
Yeah, that's highly likely.
But who would do this, and why?
We have no idea as to what his motives are.
Huh?
Hey, punks! Quit yer yapping and pick up the damn trash!
Anyway, pay close attention to whoever's on TV!
We'll have to stay on our toes and check out a bunch of channels.
Persona!
School camping trip at night... night... night...
So do you really swing that way?
What way?
Considering our situation, I'd like you to be honest with us.
Uh-huh.
Is our chastity in danger?
What—
Wh-What the hell?! Huh?!
I'm not like that!
Then why the extreme reaction?!
It only makes you seem more suspicious.
Like hell it does!
I'm fine with women now!
I still don't fully trust you, you know?
Sleeping next to you takes courage.
Hey, didn't you accept me?!
Not at night.
Fine then!
In that case...
I'm going to the girls' tent!
I'll prove I'm a man!
Great! Go on.
Don't underestimate the great Tatsumi Kanji, dammit!
You'll get expelled if King Moron finds out!
What now?
Persona!
I can't sleep.
I've had it!
Will she stop snoring if we cover her nose and mouth?
Whoa! Don't do that!
Who's there?!
Bear-sona!
Hey there.
What are you doing here?
We can't go back to our tent!
You see, Kanji, uh...
H-He burst in and fell unconscious.
Right, Yukiko?
Yeah.
What happened?
We couldn’t sleep with him there.
He could go berserk when he wakes up!
I don't have my shit list on hand...
It's King Moron!
Hey, hide already!
but anyone caught doing anything inappropriate
Where?!
Under here for now!
is getting their asses kicked outta school.
Hey, you're too close, Hanamura!
Keep that in mind!
Keep quiet, stupid.
Hey, you asleep in there?
You two better answer if you're in there!
We're asleep!
No, you're not! Shut the hell up and go to sleep!
Shit, I drank too much.
Years were just shaved off my life.
So, what are you gonna do?
Aren't you going back?
We can't go out right now, anyway.
We'll leave before anyone wakes up, so can we please stay?
I don't see why not.
Stay out of our side, boys.
There's no way!
Don't do anything weird, Hanamura.
Come again?!
I'm okay with this arrangement.
Whatever then.
Yay!
Well, good night.
Good night.
I can't sleep.
That night was uncomfortable in more ways than one.
Persona!
School camping trip, day two!
Saturday, June 18th
Cloudy to Clear
School Camping Trip,
Day Two
It's finally over!
The trip was over before we knew it.
Isn't it great that no one got expelled?
Yeah.
All righty then!
Since we're all here, let's go swimming!
Huh?
What, you're going swimming?
I'll pass. I'm way too tired.
Hey, you okay?
Were you able to get any sleep?
I didn't sleep with anyone or anything!
Huh?
Oh, don't worry about me.
But it wouldn't be any fun if I swam alone.
Who are you looking at? Go swim by yourself!
You know, you two still owe us.
I mean, we do owe you, but...
Oh, yeah! We didn't bring our swimsuits!
Right, Yukiko?
That's right!
Y-Yeah, it really is unfortunate.
Ta-da!
They're Junes-brand originals! Just in for the summer season!
What?
Is that what you went to get?
Man, that's messed up.
Persona!
They're taking forever! How far out did they go to change?
Hey, those swim trunks are awesome!
Aren’t they hip?
They sure are!
Sorry for the wait.
Whoa!
Quit staring at us! It's embarrassing.
Don't just stand there! Say something!
You two look great.
Why'd you have to go and say that?!
Y-You're horrible.
Really, you're hotter than I imagined.
Those girls might be childish on the inside, but I bet they're gonna turn into some fine-looking women!
Right, Narukami?
Yeah.
You guys crossed the line.
Definitely.
Are you guys okay?
Hmph!
Hey! Kanji?!
Huh?
Gross!
You didn't have to push us in!
Who cares? You were going in, anyway.
It's freezing.
Did you hear that?
That voice...
King Moron?
I drank too much.
I feel terrible.
Yikes! Something's floating downstream!
Persona!
Do I stink?
Don't say another word.
We've lost something important again.
Good thing we found out before we got in.
Yep.
Huh?
Whoa!
What's this?
Is she going to...
...confess her feelings?
Yep.
What is it?
Well, I...
Guys like you...
aren't my type.
I'm sorry.
Just forget about last night.
What the hell?!
Let's leave him alone.
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
I'm back.
Welcome home, Big Bro!
I might get kidnapped, right?
Are you the killer?
What?! That ain't cool!
Jiraiya!
It could be the culprit's warning.
Here I go!