Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Episode 8
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
Episode 9
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean