I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
With a new encounter, our destinies
have been set in motion once again.
It's like we're both lost in a dark forest,
but I'm sure within both of our hearts lies a small light illuminating our feelings.
I've decided to believe in that small light...
and travel this path,
even if it ends in the darkest of skies.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
It appears the battle is underway at their location.
The core of the Lost Logia is rated A+ class.
Their actions are haphazard, and their attacks are erratic.
This emergency affects us on a dimensional level.
We have to secure it as soon as possible.
Enforcer Chrono Harlaown, can you make it out there?
The transfer coordinates are already set.
Given the order, I can go at any time.
Well then, Chrono,
I order you to go to the combat site,
cease all hostilities,
and retrieve the Lost Logia.
Have them explain the
circumstances, as well.
Understood, Captain.
You be careful out there, okay?
Yes... I'll be going now...
Episode 8
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Stop!
Engaging in combat here is too dangerous!
I'm an Enforcer from the
Time-Space Administrative Bureau,
Chrono Harlaown.
I'll need a detailed explanation from both of you.
The Time-Space Administrative Bureau?
First off, put away your weapons!
If you continue to fight here...
Fate! We have to retreat!
Get away from there!
Fate!
Don't!
Stop! Don't fire!
We're going to run for it, Fate! Hold on tight!
Combat has ceased.
One of the two combatants has escaped.
Can we trace her?
They fled using multiple teleports.
It doesn't look like we can follow her.
Is that so?
Well, he ended their battle in time,
and we also managed to secure a Lost Logia.
I think everything ended well.
And besides, it seems like we'll
find out what really happened.
Chrono, good job.
I'm sorry, I let one
of the parties get away.
Well... that's all right.
Oh, and I'd like to hear their story,
so I was wondering if you could
bring those two to the Arthra?
Understood, I will return momentarily.
Yuuno... Yuuno,
what is this place?
Looks like a dimensional patrol ship from
the Time-Space Administrative Bureau.
Um... to put it simply
we're inside a ship that travels
through the space between dimensions.
I... I don't think that's really simplifying it much...
Um, let's see... along with the world you live in,
there are hundreds of other worlds
similar to it, including the one I come from.
This ship and its crew travel between them,
and supervise the affairs of those worlds
when they interfere with dimensional space.
I see...
Oh, you must be uncomfortable in that.
You can release your Barrier Jacket and Device here.
Oh, that's right.
Y-You're right. Well then...
Also... shouldn't you return to your true form, too?
Oh, yeah! Now that you mention it, I guess I will.
I've been in this form for so
long that I completely forgot.
I guess it's been a while since you've
seen me in this form, huh, Nanoha?
N-Nanoha?
Yuuno, you're... Y-Yuuno, you're a...!
Ah, what the heck?!
B-But w-weren't you just a... no way!!!
Did your perceptions of
each other just change?
Um... N-Nanoha.
When we first met, I was in this form, wasn't I...?
No, no! Y-You were a ferret to begin with!
A-Ah! Th-That's right, isn't it?
Ah, sorry about that! Sorry!
I never did show you my true form.
Yeah! You never did!
You really surprised me.
Um... excuse me for a moment.
I don't know what's going on between you two, but...
the captain is waiting, and we'd like to
hear your story as soon as possible.
A-Ah... yes.
Excuse us.
Well then, this way, please.
Captain, I brought them.
Good job.
Well then, please come in.
Make yourselves at home.
Go ahead.
O-Okay.
I see. Is that so?
You're the one who excavated the
Lost Logia... the Jewel Seeds.
Yes... and I went there to retrieve them.
How noble.
But at the same time, it was reckless!
Um... just what are these Lost Logia?
Ah... they're relics of a lost world...
but you probably wouldn't
understand that...
So, let's see...
Countless worlds exist within dimensional space.
They all are born
and grow on their own.
Among them, some worlds evolve
too quickly for their own good.
Because their technology and science are too advanced for them,
they end up destroying their own world.
All that remains are the dangerous
technological relics of these lost worlds.
We call those relics "Lost Logia."
Their purpose can be unclear,
but depending on the user,
an entire world, or even all of dimensional space, could be destroyed by their power.
That technology is incredibly dangerous.
We must handle those items properly,
and keep them in a proper
place for safekeeping.
The Lost Logia you two have been
searching for... the Jewel Seeds,
are crystallized forms of energy
used for dimensional interference.
If several Seeds were to be activated together,
they would cause a
dimensional distortion.
In the worst case scenario, it could
even cause a dimensional dislocation.
When you fought that black mage,
the flash of light was an explosion which had a huge impact on space.
That was a dimensional distortion.
Even a tiny fraction of a Jewel Seed's
power can cause a disaster of that scale.
Activating several at once
would be unfathomable.
I've heard of that happening once before.
In 462 of the old calendar,
a dimensional dislocation occurred.
Yes, that was a terrible incident.
Many of the adjacent worlds
were completely annihilated.
That tragedy will always stain our history.
We can't let that happen again.
So, I'd like to inform you that the
Time-Space Administrative Bureau
will assume all authority regarding
the Lost Logia, the Jewel Seeds.
It'd be best if you two just forgot
about what happened here,
returned to your separate worlds,
and resumed your normal lives.
But, that's...
This incident involves dimensional interference!
We can't allow civilians to get involved with this matter.
But...
Well, we brought this up so suddenly,
so you probably can't think clearly.
So why don't you two think it over this evening,
and discuss it between yourselves?
We can talk about everything
again in the morning.
I'll take you back.
Is where I found you all right?
Yes...
For the time being, should we go home?
Yeah...
And um... I guess you're about my age?
Ah... yeah... probably.
Um... are you mad about this?
I really didn't mean for things
to turn out this way, but...
I guess it seemed like I was
keeping it a secret from you...
Oh... not at all. I was just a little surprised, but that's all.
Um... I'm sorry. And thank you.
F-For now...
It seems more convenient for
me to stay in this form, so...
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Let's go have dinner,
and then do some thinking...
about what to do from now on.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
They're amazing! Both of them are AAA class mages!
Yeah...
This girl in white seems like she'd be
your type, Chrono. She's pretty cute.
Amy! I don't care about stuff like that.
This girl's average mana
output... is 1.27 million!
And the girl in black's is... 1.43 million!
At their peak, those numbers triple!
They exceed you in mana
alone, huh, Chrono?
That's not all there is to magic!
You also have to apply it
to the situation at hand,
which requires sound problem-solving skills, you know!
Well, of course.
I believe you.
You are the Arthra's
trump card, Chrono.
Oh, Captain!
Ah, you're looking at their data.
Yes.
They're amazing, aren't they?
If that much mana flowed
into a Lost Logia,
it would definitely cause
a dimensional distortion.
Those kids...
we know why Nanoha and Yuuno
were gathering the Jewel Seeds, but...
I wonder why the girl in black
was gathering them as well?
She looked... pretty desperate.
She must have a very strong motive.
Motive, huh...
She's such a young girl...
Young enough to still be reliant on her mother's love...
if she's even being
raised like a normal girl.
Stay still.
With the Time-Space Administrative
Bureau here, we can't continue.
Let's run away... we'll go
somewhere where we can be alone...
I can't do that...
But even though we managed to
get away, he's a top class mage!
If he comes after us for real,
it won't be long until they find us here!
And that demon of a woman...
your mother keeps saying all those
things that don't make any sense!
And she's so cruel to you, too!
Don't speak badly of Mother...
I will speak badly of her!
Because I'm so worried about you!
Whenever you're sad,
my heart hurts so much it feels
like it's being ripped to pieces.
Whenever you're crying,
my eyes and nose get all blurry and drippy,
and I can't do anything about it!
I don't want you to be in pain or to cry anymore, Fate!
I guess that's because you and I
are linked in mind and spirit.
I'm sorry...
If you're ever hurting, I'll be sure to
stop myself from being sad, to stop crying.
I just want you to smile and be happy, Fate!
Why... Why can't you understand?!
Thank you, Arf...
But you see... I want to grant my mother's wish.
And it's not just for my mother.
I'm sure... it's for myself, as well.
So... just a little more...
We're almost finished,
so will you give me
your best until then?
Promise me...
that you're not doing this because
that woman's telling you to...
but you're doing your best for yourself, and yourself alone.
Then I will always protect you.
Yeah.
So... Nanoha and I would like to help you.
Help us, huh...
Even without me, I'm sure Nanoha's
magical powers will be worth having.
Both to collect the Jewel Seeds,
and to fight against that girl.
In either situation,
I'm pretty sure she'll be really helpful.
I see. You sure have thought things over.
In that case, I guess it'd be all right.
M-Mom– Captain!
Let's have them help us.
I'd like to save our trump card until the last minute, if possible.
Isn't that right, Enforcer Chrono?
Yes...
We have two conditions.
You will both be under the Time-Space Administrative Bureau's command,
and you will obey every
order given to you.
I trust that's all right?
I understand.
Nanoha, it's been decided.
Yeah... thanks, Yuuno.
Well then, Momoko, Nanoha,
we're going out back now.
Okay. Will you be
training again tonight?
Yeah.
Be careful!
Yep.
Now then, shall we go?
Yeah!
It's been a while,
so I'm going all out!
Ah! Wait, wait! Let me watch!
If you're gonna come, hurry up.
Yeah! Just wait a second!
Miyuki, you're still the same as ever!
Well then, that's that.
Yep.
So... what was that important thing
you wanted to talk to me about?
Well...
I told my mom about everything.
From the day I met Yuuno,
all the way up to today.
I couldn't really mention the stuff about magic and Yuuno's true form, but...
I told her all that I could.
And then I told her that because of everything, I had to leave for a little while...
It might be dangerous, but...
it's something I started with my friends, so I want to see it through to the end.
I see...
It might be enough to make you worry...
Well... you know that I'll always worry about you.
I'm your mother, after all.
Of course I'll be worried
about you, Nanoha.
But you know...
if you were still thinking about which path to take,
I think I'd probably say you can't
do anything dangerous like that.
But you've already decided
for yourself, haven't you?
You want to finish what you've
started with your friends.
And you still want to try talking things
over with that other girl you met.
Yeah...
Well... take care, and don't
regret anything you do.
I'll convince your father and brother, too.
Okay.
Thank you, Mom!
I can't turn back now.
This is the path I've chosen.
This is what I truly want to do!
Hurry... hurry, Fate...
The promised land...
Al-Hazard awaits us...
My... our utopia!
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
The Time-Space
Administrative Bureau ship,
the Arthra, is where I'll be staying, along with Yuuno.
We've never seen such a powerful reaction between Jewel Seeds before.
We'll also see the reunion
of Nanoha and Fate!
Just what does Fate's mother want?
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 9
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
Episode Nine:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean.
Lyrical Magical, I won't lose!