This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's twelve and dreams of becoming a singer.
She passed her audition,
and achieved her wish of
becoming a singer, but...
She refused her debut song
and came to be at odds with the producer Takasu-san.
In the end,
she wrote her own song!
But despite that...
...she's well on her way to debuting
as the artist Full Moon.
Well then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You look really happy Meroko!
Of course.
I haven't been able to keep my
skin smooth and clean lately.
Besides...
...you're quite happy too, aren't you?
Eh? I guess so.
I'm going to debut as Full Moon, huh?
I'm so excited about it... I just can't wait.
Ah!
It's from Ooshige-san!
H-Hello?
Ah. Mitsuki-chan?
Yes.
It's on short notice, but...
...there's a photo shoot I need you for.
A photo shoot?
That's right.
Well then, Miss Songwriter!
I'm counting on you.
What?!
It's tomorrow?!
The First Job
A photo shoot on the beach...
It's been so long since I've been to the beach.
Why is Meroko in such high spirits?
Ignoring that... did your manager
get in touch with you?
Yep.
If we're going to the beach...
...it'll be good for my health.
I'm really happy about it.
Is that so?
Yep!
Ah! That's right!
Hmm?
I wonder if I should bring my swimsuit.
Hey.
Don't forget about the Shinigami oath.
Geez... I know that already.
Are you sure?
Wow! The air feels so different.
Ooshige-san.
Is it okay if I take a little walk?
Come back soon, okay?
Okay!
Hey, hey! Where's she going,
leaving us behind like that?!
I want to go to the beach too!
Oh! Here it is!
This isn't the beach, you know!
It doesn't matter!
A trip...
Not even a fever could ruin this, right?
Yep!
Wow! This feels good!
Yo-re-i-ho!
It feels so good to be able to use my voice so loudly.
That girl's so simplistic.
Takuto!
Hmm? What is it?
Pay attention!
You do  remember what you told me last night, right?
Last night?
You told me that we can't allow her to meet
the person who will change her fate.
I know about that already.
Besides... you're the one who should be paying attention...
We didn't come here on a picnic.
I'm so  sorry!
Ow.
Didn't we say to wait for us?
What are you going to do if something happens?
What do you mean by "something"...?
By something, I mean...
...like...
If the fact that you're really twelve years old was revealed...
There's no way something like
that is going to happen.
Look.
As long as I'm like this, there's no way I'll be found out.
Mitsuki-chan!
It's about to begin, so...
...come back over here!
Okay!
So then, shall we begin?
Please do your best.
Those are some cute stuffed animals.
You're Full Moon-san, right?
Yes!
They're my very important friends!
I see.
I'm Takeda from Monthly SuperStar.
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
The Monthly SuperStar?
So many of the idols I dream about are featured in here!
Mitsuki-chan.
Mitsuki-chan!
Y-Yes!
Introduce yourself.
I-I'm Full Moon!
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
Please excuse her.
That's just how she is.
She's much more adorable than I thought she'd be.
Um...
You're a high school student, right?
Yes! I'm sixteen years old!
My blood type is A!
My hobby is reading!
My favorite color is blue!
Yep, yep, that's the way.
All that practicing is paying off.
You think so?
In my spare time...
...I enjoy sitting in my room daydreaming.
I guess you could say that...
...I'm the type of person who takes pride in being independent.
You're quite an interesting person, huh?
I suppose...
Ah.
Excuse me.
I have to leave for a bit, so...
...I'll leave everything to you.
Okay.
That's fine.
This is your first interview, right?
Good luck!
Ah. Okay.
Hmm... so then, Full Moon-san...
...how long have you wanted to be a singer?
Yes!
Since I was ten years old!
You're quite sure of yourself.
Did something occur that caused this to happen?
Eh?
It's to meet Eichi-kun, right?
But, that's...
Ah?
What's wrong?
Ah. It's nothing.
Um...
I want lots of people to listen to my songs!
I see.
Let's see...
Is there a singer you're trying to be like?
Eh?
Shoot!
We didn't practice this!
What's wrong?
Don't you have one?
W-Well...
I like everyone who sings.
My question was pretty insignificant, huh?
So then... what kind of foods do you like?
Taiyaki and our school's Shrimp Pilaf.
Ah?!
The school's...?!
Dummy...
School food?
Full Moon-san, you're a high school student, aren't you?
Your school provides meals?
T-That's not what I meant!
Um...
The Shrimp Pilaf from back in elementary school...
...I still can't forget how much I loved it!
Full Moon-san...
...you're really a grade school student, aren't you?
Ah!
Did he figure it out?!
I'm just kidding.
Please don't worry about it.
Ah. Okay.
It looks like we didn't practice hard enough.
The things you told her to say were totally irrelevant!
It'll be a problem if they get published.
What's that?!
I have to be more careful.
I have to act more like a sixteen year old!
Ah!
I wonder if I look like an adult?
Why don't you try walking around a little?
O-Okay.
Well, try posing by lifting your hand?
Eh?
Oh. Okay!
Look here...
Can't you make it look more natural?!
Eh?
I'm sorry.
Even if you say that... she's just an amateur, after all.
Can't you be a tad more considerate?
Look at the water this time, then.
Pretend that you're gazing into the distance at the scenery.
O-Okay.
I have to give the impression that I'm a sixteen year old.
Yep!
That's no good! No good!
I can't take a picture of you like that!
Break time!
Man...
Sorry.
Our boss likes to work himself into a trance,
so his clientèle have to fit his style.
Don't worry about it.
I should be apologizing because
she's so inexperienced.
Well, it's gotten cloudy...
...let's take a little break.
Mitsuki-chan.
I'm sorry.
Don't fret over it.
It's okay to just do things at your own pace.
But...
Do you want to take a walk?
Since we have some time now...
Come on.
You'll feel better.
Okay.
What is that dummy so down for?
You're wrong.
She just needs to get some fresh air after
the cameraman made her feel incompetent!
If it were me...
...I'd show him just how charming I could be!
I see.
That girl isn't showing her charm.
Huh?
That girl's charm?
Geez!
What do you mean by charm?!
I was talking about myself!
What does this have to do with you?
It doesn't matter! Geez.
I won't let you see her anymore!
Hey! You!
What'd you do?!
Hey Meroko, get this off!
Hmph!
Where am I?!
All right.
Back to work, back to work.
Hey! What is this?!
Let's see...
The keyword is...
I'm going to tear this apart!
Female high school students?
Where are you?!
What the...?
Do something about this, Meroko!
Can I find them in a place like this?
Ah! Ah!
I'm kinda tired...
If they find out that I'm really twelve years old...
...I wonder what would happen.
They might even cancel my debut.
If that were to happen...
...I wouldn't be able to meet Eichi-kun.
I have to do my best...
What is your reason for becoming a singer?
So that I can find Eichi-kun.
That's right!
That's why I want to become a singer!
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many thanks for you!
Ah!
Ah? Um...
Who are you?
Eh?
We heard a really, really beautiful voice, so...
...we thought we should come and check it out.
It was just someone singing and being carefree... we were surprised!
Ah. I'm sorry.
There's nothing to apologize for.
But you really do have a pretty voice.
Hey, why are you in a place like this?
In a place like this...?
Could it be that...
...you're one of those people who believes in the Sixteen Year Old Hill?
The Sixteen Year Old... Hill?
What? That's not it?
Man...
This hill...
It's rumored around these parts that if on your...
...sixteenth birthday, when you come here...
...there's a myth that you'll get a boyfriend.
And... today's A-chan's birthday.
Yep!
That's why we all came here today.
A boyfriend?
A boyfriend, huh?
I've become sixteen years old, too...
But I haven't had my sixteenth birthday yet.
Geez!
Just where did that girl run off to?
And I don't see any female high school students around here.
Ah! This cellphone is new, isn't it?
Eh? What?
You can play games on this, right?
Games?
You don't know about that?
Yeah.
Look.
Ah. You really can.
So there are, from time to time...
...high school students who don't know how to use cellphones.
Are you talking about... me?
It can't be that...
...you never receive any e-mail, right?
Huh? E-mail?
Just as I thought.
I was wondering if that was possible.
I guess that I'm still a twelve year old on the inside.
Ah, that's right!
Speaking of which, how old are you?
Twelve years old.
Eh?!
Ah!
No way!
I thought that you'd be around sixteen, like me.
Ah! That's right!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm actually sixteen!
That's right.
No matter how you look at it, she doesn't look twelve at all.
Man... she had me going there!
That's a relief.
They said that I look sixteen.
Hey, do you want me to teach you how to use your e-mail?
Okay!
Let's exchange addresses then.
Ah! She was in a place like this.
Aren't those female high school students?!
This is bad.
Hey! You girls!
Ah?
Get away from Mitsuki!
Meroko? What are you doing?
My job!
Eh?
What's going on?
Ah. Meroko.
What are you doing here?
Huh?
The keyword of danger  in there...
...it says female high school students!
It really does.
That's why...
I have to separate them!
Ah!
Meroko.
What?
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
This.
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
be stoned.
Space Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
toned.
e Shuttle
ce Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
toned.
Shuttle
ce Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
oned.
Shuttle
Ice Flow
Female High School Students
(Excluding those with loose socks)
ned.
Shuttle
Flow
(Excluding those with loose socks)
Female High School Students
Excluding those with loose socks?
Ugh. What was that wind just now?
It tingles...
No way...
Ah! It's already this late!
No Way!
Well, we have to go back now.
Eh?
Ah. Okay.
Later, then.
Later.
I hope we meet again.
Next time, we'll use e-mail.
Okay!
Thank you!
Huh?
You know...
...I'm going to be debuting as a singer soon!
Eh?!
That's great!
Good luck!
We'll cheer for you!
Thank you!
Geez...
Because of you, I had to fly all over the place.
Hey.
See... about me...
They told me that I look like I'm sixteen.
Oh really?!
That's good to know!
Hey, Takuto.
I really look like I'm sixteen years old now!
Well, of course.
That's why the truth hasn't been discovered.
I see.
That's how it is.
Ah.
Where did you go?
I was about to call you.
You know, um...
...the Sixteen Year Old Hill.
What's that?
It's just...
...what the local high school students around here call that hill.
If you go on that hill on your sixteenth birthday...
...they believe that you'll find a boyfriend.
That's what the local high school students said.
You're really quite interesting.
You explained it so well.
Hey!
We're starting!
O-Okay!
Then... do your best, Mitsuki-chan.
Good luck.
Okay!
It's fine if I don't act like I'm sixteen!
I am... myself, after all!
Ah.
That's a good pose.
You're growing into a woman, aren't you?
Thank you very much!
Mitsuki's so...beautiful...
Hmm...
Huh?
Takuto!
Hmm?
Why are you staring at her?
What's that?
You're the one who said she was "beautiful" in the first place, right?
And then...
I realized that it was unreasonable and that there was no need for me to try to be an adult.
That's right.
I think that you should stay just the way you are, too.
Yep!
But... there's still a lot I have to learn...
Since Eichi-kun doesn't know anything about this yet...
I'll amaze him.
I wonder where Eichi-kun is...
I want to meet him already...
Girls are so... mysterious.
Eh?
Just when you think they're being childish...
...they suddenly look so grown up.
Eh?!
I-I wonder if that's true?
I hit it right on the nose, didn't I?
What are you thinking about right now, Mitsuki-chan?
Nothing at all!
Geez...
I said nothing at all!
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Preview
Wah!
What's with that girl?
Where is she planning on taking me?
Geez...
Takuto, you oaf!
How could you let someone see you talk while you were a stuffed animal?!
I couldn't help it!
She kept going on and on so foolishly.
Because she kept saying "I can't record...", that's why!
You should have just run away!
That's true, but...
Wait a minute.
This girl is...
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The Long Day in the Studio.
The Long Day in the Studio
Look forward to it!