Those who don't work, don't eat.
Go find your own food.
Me? I'm okay. Women are grand by birth.
"Three million."
Well, I'll have the guys earn it for me.
Damn, blues harp music is good.
It's just as good as I thought.
I thought you were a fan of jazz music?
Don't be stupid.
I even warbled
when I was sucking on my mother's milk.
You were a pretty thoughtful kid.
No mistake... that's Giraffe.
All right, I'm going from the right.
You go from the left.
There's a fatso in the way.
That's... Fatty.
The ball's in your court.
Hey, Fatty!
Fatty River! Long time no see!
Oh, who'd have thought? It's Jet Black!
When the hell did you get here?
How about you? You look so easygoing!
Did you catch a big one?
I didn't know you were a fan
of blues music.
Are you kidding me?
I've lived only for the blues
since I was in my dad's sack!
Give him back!
Zebra!
Hey, you. Don't die. Hey.
Shit, are you going to wipe out my bounty?
D-- Don't be fooled by his appearance.
You idiot. Don't speak.
Him... Help... him.
This stone.
Hey!
I can't say for sure until I analyze it,
but it might be worth a hefty sum.
So, what are you gonna do?
Like I know.
He's the one who gave it to me
and he's the one who died.
I see no harm in keeping it.
There is no harm.
After all, it's not your duty
to help the kid.
This is gonna pay for our food.
There's none for you.
You have such a poor heart.
I'm not like that.
Here, have a gift.
Oh, what's this?
An invoice? What for?
All the expenses that you've racked up
on our ship.
Thanks for your business.
You're welcome.
So, why are you asking about
the dead bounty?
Well...
So, you were after Giraffe, too.
You got a good deal.
Go ahead, eat.
Oh, well, there's no bounty in it anyway.
Yeah. No gain at all.
No, no. There really is nothing.
Oh, well, you'll owe me one for today.
You know that kid on the blues harp
the other day?
Giraffe was after
that kid, Wenn's, father.
His old acquaintance, Zebra.
Acquaintance?
You didn't know that?
That they were the top
of the Volunteer Self Defense Squad
until ten years ago?
But... why is he after an old comrade?
Ten years ago, Zebra and Giraffe attempted
to reclaim a certain facility.
But, a few days later,
Zebra ends up missing
and Giraffe finds himself blindfolded
in a weird place he'd never seen before.
Giraffe was going after the top spot
in the group, but he was betrayed.
But... Zebra was still alive.
So, in the end, Giraffe was killed
by some form of betrayal?
Women easily betray others,
but men live for duty.
Duty, huh?
That's what I'd like to believe.
Who are you?
Someone suspicious.
What do you want?
Giraffe asked me to help you.
But Zebra shot Giraffe.
Yeah.
Then why did Giraffe tell him
to help the kid?
This kid's showing up here, too.
He must be pretty famous.
Yeah, the kid's a genius.
- This guy isn't Zebra!
- What?!
Look... the date.
What the--?
Why the hell is this kid in an article
from 30 years ago, with the same face?!
Come on. There's nothing to fear.
Come over here.
Little twerps should stay out of this.
If you stick your neck in too far,
you'll get burnt.
Don't give me that conceited crap, kid.
I ain't a kid.
All kids say that.
I may look like this,
but I've been alive since the days
when humans only crawled
on the face of the Earth.
It started on the day
of the accidental explosion
of the hyperspace gate.
My body has ceased to age.
I can't die.
The guys that took interest in me,
and experimented on me,
all died before me.
The end for this guy started
when he snuck into the lab.
I needed... a parent to use as a cover.
D-- Don't be fooled by his appearance.
Him...
Help... him.
I think this was the third guy.
Now, give me the ring.
Ring? What ring?
That's fine.
Even if you had it,
it's a pearl before swine.
Give me a break, you big klutz.
You're lucky you got away
with so little...
since we don't have the money
for a funeral.
Sorry.
Knock it off, Ein.
Shut up.
Jet, the alpha-catch.
Shit. This piece of junk.
All right.
Now, what are you seeing?
The hotel.
He's remembering the moment
that Giraffe died.
Give him back! Zebra!
Come over here!
Shit. And then what?
What did Giraffe say?
I have it now. I can do you in with this.
This is a stone
that will return time to you!
Now, hand Zebra over to me!
Zebra!
When the Gate exploded,
a vast amount of energy...
and an imaginary coordinate system
were created
from the resulting twists in hyperspace,
and got enclosed in the gem in this ring.
And that same energy
broke Wenn's circadian rhythm.
His pineal gland continually produces
a substance
similar to melatonin that inhibits aging.
That's how the theory goes, in a nutshell.
- You understand?
- Like I do.
I don't either.
So, in other words,
there's no way to do it for sure...
other than to stick that gem into Wenn.
I don't know what will happen.
It might explode
the moment you shoot it in.
This makes me excited.
What?
I thought this might be
the last time I see you,
so I thought I'd see you off.
- So, you're finally gonna leave us?
- No. You aren't coming back.
I don't like it.
I don't like it one bit.
Men are such idiots.
I see.
I can finally die now.
I feel so heavy.
But... I feel so at ease now.
Do you know?
Do you understand? Do you?
Like I do.
- Hey, do you know what heavy metal is?!
- What? I didn't catch that!
- Heavy metal! I said, heavy metal!
- What did you say?
Hey, can you do something
about this racket?!
This is in the background
during the entire next episode!
- Maybe I shouldn't appear then!
- I can't hear a thing you're saying!
Next episode: "Heavy Metal Queen!"
Are you sure they can really hear us?!