Rumi! Make sure you keep hold of Dad's hand, all right?
So you show yourself, monster!
Precure! Open My Heart!
It's the new issue of Precure!
Make sure you all buy it!
Wow, this does look good!
I'll take a copy too!
This one's really pretty!
Yeah, it is.
But this one's really good too!
It's a really great shot.
Huh? Nishihara, you did come after all!
I love you!
And I, you! Never again shall I let you go!
Nor shall I!
But little did they know the scale of what awaited them.
We'd better get a move on with our rehearsal.
Yeah.
That reminds me, where are Aya and Mayu?
Dunno.
Fashion Club now preparing
Non-members are
strictly prohibited
No entry!
Momoka's outfit is all ready!
What about Yuri's?
Erika's just shortening the skirt on it a little.
Erika!
I'm nearly done!
Naminami, how's the corsage repair coming along?
I'll be finished in a sec. What about Tsubomi?
I-I'm here!
Are you all right?!
I-I'm fine...
Oh no, the outfits!
Don't tell me...
Are you nervous?
I-I feel like if I stop moving, I'm just gonna faint.
We can't give up after coming this far!
Being nervous won't get you anywhere! Okay?
Sometimes I envy how laid back Erika can be.
She's just optimistic to a fault.
It's not a fault!
I know they say, "Do your best
and leave the rest to Providence."
But my heart won't stop racing!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Here are your teas and coffees!
Wait... what?! Dad?! Mom?!
What're you doing here?! What about the shops?!
We've taken the day off.
It's our daughters' big day, after all.
We're really looking forward to your fashion show.
Yeah.
But I must say...
I must say...
Those outfits look really cute on you!
Sir, please refrain from taking photos within the café!
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Tsubomi! Erika!
Oh, Itsuki!
They've finally confirmed this afternoon's schedule for the main stage.
Here's the stage program, and the...
Huh?!
Dad, Mom, big brother! Grandpa's here too?!
We're expecting good things from your fashion show.
Make sure you give it your all, okay?
I-I will!
Can I have a word with you two?
So the fashion show's after the
Light Music Club goes on, huh?
And then after us is...
What the hell?!
We're the headline show?!
Apparently.
We're the very last thing on the schedule.
Huh?
Whaaaaat?!
Everyone's a Star!
This is Our Stage!
Whoa!
What a huge stage!
Thish ish amazing!
This is where you're holding your fashion show?!
Yeah.
But it's kind of tradition for the Light Music Club to be the closing performance of the day.
Wh-What are we gonna do?!
Now I'm really fired up!
If this is how it's gotta be, we're just gonna have to roll with it and make the fashion show a huge success!
That's right!
As a member of the Fashion Club,
and as a member of the School Festival Committee,
I want to make this the most
amazing fashion show possible!
Yeah.
But hey, isn't the Light Music Club gonna be a bit annoyed with us for this?
I was worried about that too.
I'm gonna head over there now and talk to them.
I'll come with you!
I'll come too!
Okay!
You can't just back out now!
There's just no way we can do it!
It's just out of our league!
Damn it! I guess we're out of options.
Please stop!
Stop that this instant!
We're begging you!
We're so sorry!
Huh?
Aya! Mayu!
Damn it!
Damn, that was bad timing.
S-Sorry.
What on earth just happened?
It's our vocalists, Aya and Mayu.
They said they wanted to cancel today's concert!
Huh?!
Apparently we're having a fashion show this year, and Kurumi Momoka's gonna be in it.
Everyone's gonna be there to see her.
It seems they got cold feet.
Sorry. Truth is, I'm the president of the Fashion Club.
Huh?!
And we actually came here to tell you all
that this year, the Fashion Club's been put last in the schedule.
I'm really sorry about all this!
Don't. We should be thankin' you, if anything.
The bigger the audience, the better, right?
But what about Aya and Mayu?
We'll just have to find 'em and change their minds!
There's no point doin' this without 'em.
We've gotta let our spirits burn bright on stage together!
Right!
Um, do you mind if we help find them?!
Yeah! Let's do it!
We'll help look too!
That'sh right!
Okay!
Myoudou School Festival
The Myoudou School Festival?
"Our students will be showing off all the hard work they've put into their club activities, live on stage," is it?
I'm sure everyone would much rather see my beautiful visage upon their stage than that dross, non?
Please, just think it over!
Sorry!
We just can't sing today!
We'll be waiting for you on stage, all right?!
We'll wait as long as it takes!
We're sorry!
Aya!
Mayu...
Hey.
Are you really all right with this?
You won't regret it?
You can do it!
'Cause, ya know, you're not alone in this.
Aya, Mayu.
To be honest, I'm really frightened of going up on stage too.
But I have all these great friends who support and believe in me, so I know I can do it!
All your friends from the Light Music Club believe in you two as well.
We'll be waiting for you on stage!
Next up, we have a performance by the Light Music Club.
W-Wait!
You'll be fine, really!
Aya! Mayu!
Go for it! You can do it!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
We can't do this after all!
Well then, I guess this stage...
will have to be commandeered!
Kobraja!
Bow down before my beauty, my dear humans!
Get off the stage!
You philistine!
That shall do nicely!
I shall take the Flowers from both your Hearts!
Flowers of the Heart, your moment has come!
There we go!
And now, behold the power of the Dark Bracelet!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Sing a song!
Come on, you three!
Yuri!
Hurry and transhform into Precuresh!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
I'm just so scared people won't like our singing!
Blossom!
Maybe we don't have any talent after all.
That's what we're afraid of!
We want to sing,
but we just can't!
Aya, Mayu, your friends in the Light Music Club are there to support you, so please believe in them!
If your friends believe in you,
then you've gotta be able to believe in yourself too!
You two have what it takes to sing up on stage!
I suppose I should make my debut.
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
Rather than listen to these cowards sing, I shall treat you to one of my glorious rhapsodies!
Just stay still, will you?!
Curse you. Take this!
Get them!
Believing? Friends? How utterly ridiculous!
Cowards like them will always be cowardly!
They'll never accomplish anything!
No.
You're wrong!
Because people believe in us, we can give our all.
Because our friends are there for us, we get stronger!
And you dare to mock that?
I've had it up to here with this!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Precure Shining Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
I-I won't forget this!
Aya! Mayu!
Are you two all right?!
Yeah...
Would the members of the Fashion Club please report backstage?
All that chaos out there kinda took up our timeslot.
Looks like we're not gonna have our concert this year.
But hey, there's always next year, right?
I'm so sorry!
We didn't have the courage to perform, and now...
Don't sweat it.
Oh!
This is kinda sudden, but I think we
can change up our production a bit!
What?
Sorry about this!
Without further ado, the Fashion Club and the Light Music Club will now present their fashion show!
The feelings that got me here all seemed so half-hearted
But there's no turning back now
I just have to trust in all my hard work, and take the first step
Now's the time to take the plunge, ready, go!
So no matter how afraid we feel
We'll never give up, cause even though you can't see it
We've found a treasure more precious than any other
In the sunny skies of my heart
I soar into a higher octave
My heart goes on, and when it resounds with all of my friends
Those distant dreams can one day become reality
I think our limits are just an illusion we make because we're afraid
I've come to understand that now
You've always believed in me, been there to support me
You've given me such courage
You saw the way out of the dark
So I know your eyes will be able to see
The true light within that no one else can find
In the boundless skies of my heart
This melody takes flight
My heart goes on, and I won't let a moment go to waste
And though my tears fall, slowly the seed shall bloom into a beautiful flower
In the language of flowers, an
aster means "a trushting heart."
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
In the sunny skies of my heart
I soar into a higher octave
My heart goes on, and when it resounds with all of my friends
Those distant dreams can one day become reality
By love's gentle touch, and the light of the stars, we're all shining here together
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
The emissary of despair, the Desert Devil, appears!
It'll take all our courage to beat it!
But when we turn to the HeartCatch Mirage for
guidance, it shows us the weakness within our hearts!
It's a grand battle of Precure vs Precure!
O resilient hearts, never sinking into darkness!
Become the light of hope that shall cut down despair!
HeartCatch Precure:
We'll Become Stronger!
Our Trial is Precure vs. Precure!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!