IT WAS RAINING
THAT DAY, AS WELL.
AND SO YOU DIDN'T COME
BECAUSE OF THE RAIN?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO KILL YOU.
IT WAS ALL SET UP.
IF I HAD...
I WOULD'VE BEEN FREE.
SO WHY DIDN'T YOU?
YOU CHOSE TO BE HUNTED. WHY?
WHY DID YOU LOVE ME?
LET'S JUST GO AWAY SOMEWHERE.
ESCAPE. VANISH.
GO SOMEWHERE WHERE
THERE'S NO ONE ELSE.
JUST THE TWO OF US.
[FOOTSTEPS]
WAS THE TARGET TERMINATED?
HE GOT AWAY.
OUR AGENTS WERE CUT DOWN.
THEY RAN OUT OF FIREPOWER
AND WERE UNABLE TO TAKE OUT--
WHY DID YOU COME BACK?
WHERE'S JULIA?
I COULDN'T FIND HER.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[INAUDIBLE]
CHINN, DO NOT FOLLOW
IN YOUR BROTHER'S FOOTSTEPS.
KEEP GOING.
JUST DRIVE PAST IT.
WHAT?
SOMEBODY MIGHT'VE
GOTTEN THERE ALREADY.
WAIT HERE.
ANNIE?
[MOANING SOFTLY]
I TOLD THEM YOU WEREN'T HERE.
I SAID YOU WERE ALREADY DEAD.
TOLD THEM THEY WERE
WASTING THEIR TIME.
DON'T TALK.
VICIOUS ASSASSINATED
ALL OF THE ELDERS.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID.
EVERYONE. THEY'VE ALL LOST THEIR
SENSE OF PLACE IN THE WORLD,
LIKE KITES WITHOUT
STRINGS OR TAILS.
[GASPS]
OH, SO YOU FOUND JULIA.
THAT'S GOOD.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
ANNIE.
IT GOT A LITTLE CHILLY TODAY.
IT'S THOSE COLD WINDS.
[FOOTSTEPS]
YOU WON'T NEED
ALL THOSE WEAPONS
IF WE RUN AWAY TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU'RE STAYING.
THEN I'LL STAY, TOO.
I'LL BE WITH YOU UNTIL THE END.
[COCKS RIFLE]
I'M SORRY. I'M GONNA MAKE
A BIT OF A SCENE.
[METAL CLANKING]
YOU'RE A VERY LUCKY WOMAN.
YEAH, RIGHT.
MY TIMING WAS PERFECT
FOR GETTING SHOT AT
AND NEARLY KILLED.
I'M REALLY ON A ROLL.
THE RED TAIL WON'T BE
FUNCTIONAL FOR AWHILE.
YOU'RE HAVING SOME
PRETTY GOOD LUCK YOURSELF.
THAT SPIKE; HE WAS
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE.
HE'S PROBABLY NOT COMING BACK.
THEY MAY HAVE KILLED HIM
ALREADY, YOU KNOW.
IT'S POSSIBLE.
SO WHAT? YOU WANT ME
TO GO LOOKING FOR HIM?
FORGET IT. HE'S DEALING
WITH HIS OWN PAST.
IT'S HIS FIGHT.
YOU TOLD HIM TO GO AFTER HER.
MY LEG IS WRECKED,
MY SHIP IS BUSTED.
HELL, YES. HE WAS
NOTHING BUT TROUBLE,
AND I DON'T GIVE A DAMN.
SO, WHAT KIND OF WOMAN IS SHE?
WHAT'S JULIA LIKE?
ORDINARY.
THE KIND OF DANGEROUS,
BEAUTIFUL ORDINARY
THAT YOU JUST CAN'T LEAVE ALONE.
I SEE.
LIKE AN ANGEL
FROM THE UNDERWORLD.
OR MAYBE A DEVIL FROM PARADISE.
[GUNFIRE]
UGH!
AAH!
THIS WAY.
GET DOWN!
[CLICKS]
UGH!
[GASPING]
JULIA!
JULIA.
[SOFT MOAN]
[INAUDIBLE]
WHERE'S SPIKE?
CAN YOU HELP ME TRACK HIM DOWN?
ALL LIVING THINGS, EVERY
BEING THAT WALKS AND BREATHES,
EACH HAS ITS OWN STAR.
HUH?
WHEN A LIFE IS BORN,
A NEW STAR APPEARS.
THAT IS THE GUARDIAN STAR.
THE STAR THAT WARMS THIS PLANET
IS SOMEONE'S
GUARDIAN STAR, AS WELL.
THE RED STAR YOU SEE OVERHEAD;
THE BLUE STAR ON THE HORIZON.
AND WHEN A LIFE ENDS,
THE STAR FALLS AND DISAPPEARS.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU, RUNNING ROCK...
THAT'S NOT MY NAME.
DON'T CALL ME THAT.
HIS STAR IS ABOUT TO FALL.
I HAVE DREAMED IT.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
DO NOT FEAR DEATH.
DEATH IS ALWAYS AT OUR SIDE.
WHEN WE SHOW FEAR, IT JUMPS
AT US FASTER THAN LIGHT,
BUT IF WE DO NOT SHOW FEAR,
IT CASTS ITS EYE UPON US GENTLY
AND THEN GUIDES US
INTO INFINITY.
VICIOUS, HERE IT IS.
HER PASSPORT WAS STILL
INSIDE THE POCKET.
IT'LL BE IMPOSSIBLE FOR THEM
TO ESCAPE THE PLANET NOW.
A BEAST THAT HAS
LOST HIS PLACE.
HE HAS NOWHERE TO RETURN TO NOW.
HE WILL COME.
[GASPS]
SPIKE, YOU'RE... YOU'RE BACK.
YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO EAT?
HUH?
I'M REALLY STARVING.
THIS FOOD TASTES
TERRIBLE, AS USUAL.
FOR BEING SO BAD,
YOU SURE EAT A LOT OF IT.
THEY SAY HUNGER
IS THE BEST SPICE.
HA HA HA.
EVER HEARD THIS STORY?
HUH?
THERE ONCE WAS
A TIGER-STRIPED CAT.
THIS CAT DIED A MILLION DEATHS,
REVIVED, AND LIVED
A MILLION LIVES,
AND HE WAS OWNED
BY VARIOUS PEOPLE
WHO HE DIDN'T REALLY CARE FOR.
THE CAT WASN'T AFRAID TO DIE.
THEN ONE DAY, THE CAT
BECAME A STRAY CAT,
WHICH MEANT HE WAS FREE.
HE MET A WHITE FEMALE CAT,
AND THE TWO OF THEM SPENT
THEIR DAYS TOGETHER HAPPILY.
WELL, YEARS PASSED
AND THE WHITE CAT GREW WEAK
AND DIED OF OLD AGE.
THE TIGER-STRIPED CAT
CRIED A MILLION TIMES,
THEN HE DIED, TOO,
EXCEPT THIS TIME,
HE DIDN'T COME BACK TO LIFE.
YEAH. IT'S A GOOD STORY.
I HATE THAT STORY.
HUH?
I NEVER LIKED CATS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
OH, YEAH. THAT'S RIGHT.
HEH.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
HEY, SPIKE.
YEAH?
I JUST WANT TO
ASK YOU ONE THING.
WHAT'S THAT?
IS IT FOR THE GIRL?
SHE'S DEAD.
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO FOR HER NOW.
[CLICK]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHY ARE YOU GOING?
YOU TOLD ME ONCE
TO FORGET THE PAST
'CAUSE IT DOESN'T MATTER...
BUT YOU'RE THE ONE STILL
TIED TO THE PAST, SPIKE!
LOOK AT MY EYES, FAYE.
ONE OF THEM IS A FAKE 'CAUSE
I LOST IT IN AN ACCIDENT.
SINCE THEN, I'VE BEEN
SEEING THE PAST IN ONE EYE
AND THE PRESENT IN THE OTHER,
SO I THOUGHT I COULD ONLY SEE
PATCHES OF REALITY,
NEVER THE WHOLE PICTURE.
DON'T TELL ME
THINGS LIKE THAT.
YOU'VE NEVER TOLD ME
ANYTHING ABOUT YOURSELF,
SO DON'T TELL ME NOW.
I FELT LIKE I WAS WATCHING
A DREAM I'D NEVER WAKE UP FROM.
HMM. BEFORE I KNEW IT,
THE DREAM WAS ALL OVER.
MY MEMORY FINALLY CAME BACK,
BUT NOTHING GOOD CAME OF IT.
THERE WAS NO PLACE
FOR ME TO RETURN TO.
THIS WAS THE ONLY PLACE
I COULD GO.
AND NOW YOU'RE LEAVING,
JUST LIKE THAT!
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO GO?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
JUST THROW YOU LIFE AWAY
LIKE IT WAS NOTHING?
I'M NOT GOING THERE TO DIE.
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT
IF I'M REALLY ALIVE.
I HAVE TO DO IT, FAYE.
[FIRES GUN]
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
[GUNFIRE]
UGH!
UGH.
CHINN.
WHERE'S VICIOUS?
ON THE TOP FLOOR.
THIS WAY.
CHINN!
[MOANING]
VICIOUS... HAS GOT
TO BE STOPPED.
I... WAS WAITING FOR YOU
TO COME BACK AND TAKE OVER.
UGH.
SO, YOU'RE FINALLY AWAKE.
I TOLD YOU BEFORE, SPIKE,
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN
KILL YOU AND SET YOU FREE.
THOSE WORDS APPLY
TO YOU, AS WELL, VICIOUS.
EITHER WAY,
IT'S GOING TO END HERE.
[GRUNTING]
JULIA IS DEAD.
LET'S FINISH IT NOW.
AS YOU WISH.
IT'S ALL A... DREAM.
YEAH. JUST A DREAM.
BANG.
♪ NEVER SEEN A BLUER SKY ♪
♪ YEAH, I CAN FEEL IT
REACHING OUT AND MOVING CLOSER ♪
♪ THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT BLUE ♪
♪ ASKED MYSELF
WHAT IT'S ALL FOR ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THE FUNNY THING
ABOUT IT, I COULDN'T ANSWER ♪
♪ NO, I COULDN'T ANSWER ♪
♪ THINGS HAVE TURNED
A DEEPER SHADE OF BLUE ♪
♪ AND IMAGES THAT MIGHT BE REAL
MAY BE ILLUSION ♪
♪ KEEP FLASHING OFF AND ON ♪
♪ FREE... ♪
♪ WANNA BE FREE ♪
♪ GONNA BE FREE ♪
♪ AND MOVE AMONG THE STARS ♪
♪ YOU KNOW THEY
REALLY AREN'T SO FAR ♪
♪ FEELS SO FREE... ♪
♪ GOT TO KNOW FREE... ♪
♪ PLEASE... ♪
♪ DON'T WAKE ME FROM THE DREAM ♪
♪ IT'S REALLY
EVERYTHING IT SEEMED ♪
♪ I'M SO FREE... ♪
♪ NO BLACK AND WHITE
IN THE BLUE ♪
[SINGING IN JAPANESE]
♪ EVERYTHING IS CLEARER NOW ♪
♪ LIFE IS JUST A DREAM,
YOU KNOW ♪
♪ THAT'S NEVER ENDING ♪
♪ I'M ASCENDING ♪