No way!
Was that the trash can from the convenience store?
Anyway, don't go near Heiwajima Shizuo.
Jeez, when you get violent, no logic or reason reaches you, Shizu-chan.
Didn't I tell you never to come back to Ikebukuro?
Shizuo, it's not good to fight.
Shut up!
What? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Then it has to be that guy...
Heiwajima Shizuo!
They fired me without warning!
I've been kicked out of the dorm too.
They didn't even give me severance pay!
I don't have money for food or anything else.
And the state hasn't even done anything!
Yeah! It's all the state's fault!
Shut up already...
So you took out a loan to bang a prostitute?
It's love!
Mint-chan and I are truly in love.
What?
Shut up!
We can only meet here, and I don't know her cell phone number.
But our love is genuine!
That's it!
You can only meet here?
And you don't even know her cell phone number?
H-Hey! Shizuo!
Let me be clear from the start:
"True love"...
my...
ass!
I hate violence.
Did you hear?
That Heiwajima Shizuo guy has been
causing quite the uproar lately.
What?
Isn't Heiwajima Shizuo-san the guy
who dresses like a bartender?
Yeah.
People say he's pretty scary, but he's
been particularly aggressive lately.
They say Ikebukuro is like a battlefield!
I've seen him before...
Uh... I guess he's a pretty scary person.
I dunno.
You shouldn't pass judgment just because of some rumors.
Oh my, Setton-san, you know him?
Don't tell me you're from their world?
Scary! Help me, Mommy!
I am not!
Sheesh dude, how are we going to collect debts if you beat the crap out of everyone?
Sorry.
It stinks...
Apparently, he hasn't been home for a few days.
This has happened a lot recently.
Was he a victim of those rumored kidnappings?
Something stinks...
Hey, someone's been injured!
I heard it was the slasher.
This happened just a few minutes ago?!
I saw him!
He ran that way.
Oh boy. Ikebukuro has gotten pretty lively again.
Something stinks!
Something really stinks! The whole city stinks!
What is this smell?
This is so annoying!
Hi, Shizuo, Tom-san.
Hey, Simon.
Shizuo.
Sorry about him.
He's been in a terrible mood the past few days.
Oh... Did he hit puberty?
More like the rebellious phase.
Rebellious phase?
Hey, long time no see.
He's starring in another movie?
Hanejima Yuuhei is a real star, huh?
Or should I say, Heiwajima Kasuka-san?
Aren't you proud of him as his older brother,
Heiwajima Shizuo-san?
Ah, excuse me.
This is my card.
He's not just handsome, but a skilled actor as well.
What was the name of his debut film?
Ah, right.
"Vampire Ninja Carmilla Saizou."
Ever since I saw that movie, I knew he'd be a star.
He performed all his stunts himself, right?
Some speculate that you trained him.
I'd like to ask you more about this.
Shizuo!
I hate violence.
I'm not lying.
I wasn't like this before.
The first time it happened, I was having a fight with my brother Kasuka.
I lost my temper over something trivial and picked up the refrigerator all gung-ho to throw at him.
Picking it up wasn't a conscious decision on my part.
It's just that...
I couldn't help myself.
Ever since then...
Boo! Shizuo, you bedwetter!
Dumbass! Dumbass!
I couldn't stay calm.
My body moves on its own when I'm angry.
And then...
You know the brute strength you unleash in extreme situations?
I wonder if you can let it out whenever you want?
A person's brain usually keeps their strength in check so they don't
overexert themselves and break their bones or tear their muscles.
But your  brain lets your strength go wild!
That's a mystery of life!
It's just jaw-dropping!
Hey, can I take a peek—
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It hurts!
It hurts, Shizuo-kun!
I don't understand the details.
It's gonna break!
But the fact is, I can't control my anger.
My ulna... my ulna...
Thus, I end up destroying everything around me,
My right ulna...
including my own body.
I came to understand that much.
And so...
I didn't keep it bottled up anymore.
If I couldn't control it, then there was no point in trying to suppress it in the first place.
I'll break my bones?
The hell if I care!
I broke my bones a lot,
and every time I got back on my feet, I got stronger.
Shinra said...
Recalling it is such a pain!
Anyway, I kept getting stronger.
However...
Hey...
Are you all right? You're always injured.
Wait a minute.
Here.
You need to drink milk to build stronger bones.
And one for you too.
Thank you.
I did it...
How do I say it...
When I realized what I did...
Good morning!
What caused all this?
I was raised in a normal house.
I didn't have a traumatic childhood either.
So why?
Kasuka...
What?
Aren't you afraid of me?
Nope.
It was around then that I entered Raira Academy.
It's a grand-opening sale!
You'll receive a discount!
The shop is fresh. The fish is fresh!
It must be fate that we're attending the same school again.
Zip it.
Well, how's your body?
Oh, I can give you a checkup to celebrate our reunion.
No?
Then how about a blood sample?
Selty!
What happened last night?
I was worried sick when you didn't show up.
Were you searching for your head again?
Yeah, right! That's just an excuse. You were having fun with a man—
Selty...
Stop jabbing my solar plexus!
I had a strange feeling.
Let me introduce him.
He's my friend, Heiwajima Shizuo-kun.
I don't know how to put it...
Shizuo-kun, Selty is living with me.
Just...
And she's my future—
I just remembered something annoying.
Oh, right...
That was when that flea bastard showed up.
Him...
Orihara Izaya!
I hated that guy...
This is Orihara Izaya. We went to the same junior high.
...from the moment I saw him.
Well, he really isn't a good person.
He's more like a pretty bad person.
Ouch, Shinra.
No, I didn't mean it in a bad way.
I don't like you.
Huh?
What a pity.
I thought we'd be able to have some fun.
Shut up.
Don't be so cold, Shizuo-kun.
See?
Fun, ain't it?
The day we met, we had a death match.
There wasn't any reason for it.
I just didn't like him.
But...
Are you all right?
Don't worry, he's fine.
He's solidly built.
I-Is he really okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
Screw this.
I'm beat.
What a coincidence.
Izaya's here too.
Hey, why aren't you hurt?
I'll kill you!
Kill you! Kill you! Kill you! Kill you! Kill you!
And the next day, things got even more annoying.
I'll fucking kill you!
Some random punks started a fight with me.
I didn't do anything at all.
I just wanted to live in peace!
Damn! Damn!
Fuck!
He's pissing me off!
Annoying! Damn annoying!
So annoying! So annoying! So annoying! So annoying!
So damn annoying...
I know...
Die!
It was Izaya.
That bastard was pulling the strings.
When I found out...
Izaya!
I should have killed him on the spot!
Damn!
After we graduated from Raira Academy...
Well? Does it look good on me?
That idiot was like this.
And that flea was doing business with the Yakuza.
Anyway, things were quiet for a while.
As for me...
It was like this.
Welcome.
Hey, did you see him?
No way!
It's that famous actor!
Hanejima Yuuhei!
Hey, Kasuka.
What's up?
Bartender uniforms?
I think it'd be better if you didn't change jobs so often.
I bought enough to last you forever.
Thanks.
I'll do my best.
But...
Damn!
Izaya!
That fucking flea framed me.
He disappeared from Ikebukuro.
The police quickly discovered that I was innocent and released me.
But...
Sorry, I couldn't keep my promise.
Oh, Shizuo-chan.
Tom-san was my senior in junior high,
and asked me to help him to collect debts.
Well, I'm something like a bodyguard.
At first I wasn't really that impressed with the job.
But Tom-san...
You don't have to resort to force for everything.
No one in Ikebukuro will fight back after hearing the name "Heiwajima Shizuo."
Well, that's how he convinced me, but...
Kasuka had been pretty busy with his job,
and I hadn't seen him in a while.
I wondered if he was mad at me.
What's all this then?
Yuuhei!
Yuuhei-san, it's your turn.
I don't know why,
but I felt better.
And so...
I've been working with Tom-san all this time.
It's time to repay?
I don't understand all this complicated stuff.
We're NEETs.
Aye.
It's the fault of society, school, and everyone else.
The ugly side of the human heart!
Listen.
I told you I don't know anything.
Buzz off, geezer.
That "geezer" has a job to do.
Huh? What's with that look?
H-Hey!
What's up with those clothes?
He's a butler, you idiot!
You guys haven't heard about Shizuo?
Who's that?
A celebrity?
Are you, Mr. Butt-ler?
Crap!
Fill my glass please, okay, Mr. Butt-ler?
You really are NEETs if you're in Ikebukuro and you haven't heard about Shizuo.
My clothes...
The clothes I got from my brother...
I still dislike violence.
I want to become even stronger.
Strong enough to suppress my wrath.
I don't know why, but I feel much better after talking to you.
Glad to hear that.
Lately, I've been really pissed for some reason.
Yeah.
I came here because I heard a rumor about that.
I see.
Sorry about that.
Oh hush.
Bye.
I want to keep people at a distance,
but I can't be left alone.
That's why I try to stay in touch with other people,
like Tom-san and Kasuka.
The two of us are alike.
I'm sure...
Hey.
Shizuo.
Are you out of puberty?
Then eat some sushi.
It's good. It's yummy.
Next time.
Izaya!
I see...
I knew something stunk!
So it was you!
What's he up to?
What's he doing in the city this time?!
Damn!
Izaya!
I dream.
I have the same dream again and again.
I wonder if I'm asleep while my head is awake, and vice versa?
Next time: Transient Dream.