What?! Eichi is at Narita Airport?
Just before the Fantasia
Music Festival's rehearsal,
Mitsuki receives another
fake email from Izumi.
Mitsuki is waiting at the airport,
and Takuto decides to tell her the truth.
But Mitsuki isn't discouraged
by the news,
and she goes on to win
the Best New Singer Award!
You did great, Mitsuki!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Good morning.
Morning!
Congratulations on
the Best New Singer Award!
Thank you very much!
Thanks to the award, I get to go to America.
I'm so happy I can't stand it!
How nice! Share a little bit
of your happiness with me!
Well, Ms. Oda, why don't you come
to the Christmas party?
We're talking about doing it at
Ms. Oshige's house on Christmas Eve.
A Christmas party? It kind of sounds like
an elementary school kid's way of saying it.
What? Yeah, maybe.
But I have work
on Christmas Eve.
Aww, that's too bad!
Seems like she's super excited.
She's so close to finding out
where Eichi is.
She's so happy she
can't contain herself.
Well, shall we start
recording soon?
Sure!
Okay, this program is going to
be aired on Christmas Eve,
so let's do this
like it's the 24th.
Okay!
Hello, everyone! Merry Christmas!
Well, our guest tonight is...
Full Moon! Merry Christmas!
Ms. Oshige and me...
Wakana, Tomoe...
There they are!
Good morning!
Oh, morning!
Morning.
Hey Kumi, Emi, do you have
plans on Christmas Eve?
No, why?
I'm going to have a Christmas party
with everybody.
- A Christmas party?!
Yeah! Do you two
wanna come?
We'll decorate the door with a wreath,
exchange presents and stuff.
It'll definitely be fun!
Yeah, sounds good.
And it's our last Christmas as
elementary school students!
Yep! Let's all have fun together.
So look here, you do this...
Then this, then this...
You put a ribbon on it...
And the wreath is complete!
- The Forest Friends Play!
At Christmas, hanging a wreath on the door
or a wall is supposed to attract happiness.
Everyone in front of the TV,
hang a wreath on the door
for Christmas, and let's be happy!
We Death Spirits don't really have
anything to do with Christmas though.
No way! Death Spirits want to be
happy on Christmas too!
Mitsuki, you're so good.
Before I moved in with my grandma,
I made them every year.
Oh, you mean...
They bring back special memories
you made with Eichi?!
What?!
It's a beautiful wreath, Mitsuki.
If the wreath is made
by you, Mitsuki,
I feel like it's really going to
bring me happiness.
I hope that Eichi and me,
and everyone will find happiness.
You're so lucky, Mitsuki!
What?
Oh, I'm jealous!
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I know, how about if we invite boys
for Christmas? Okay, Kumi?
What?!
It'll be your chance!
Then, is that okay?
- Yeah!
Kumi, Wakana...
Emi, and then...
Yeah, yeah, it doesn't matter
how many people,
so invite everyone
and we'll party!
Okay.
But I wonder if it's okay
to invite classmates.
That's right, how will you
explain Ms. Oshige.
That's no problem.
You can tell them that I'm like a big sister.
"Big sister," really?
I don't think you'd pass.
What are you two saying!
That's why I said "like"
a big sister. Jeez!
My CD is finally done.
Mr. Takasu wanted to release
your CD within the year,
and he did everything possible
to make it happen.
The release date is towards
the very end of the year...December 24th.
December 24th?
Don't get spoiled by
your Christmas present.
It's a humble celebration for
the new Madoka Wakamatsu
who could finally get
her start as a singer.
Thank you so much.
I see. A Christmas party, huh?
Dr. Wakaoji, you should come too.
Sorry, I have to work that day.
What?!
But if I can go home early,
I'll swing by.
Okay!
So, you saw it, right?
Yes, the husband came
down from the second floor
and said that
he wanted coffee.
So I thought I'd make it, but the wife said
she would make it, which she rarely does.
Ms. Tanaka...
Yes?
Wow! Fuyuko Komaki's
Christmas Dinner Show?!
It's a little early,
but it's a Christmas present.
Th-Thank you very much!
I can't believe you were able to get a ticket.
I got it from Ms. Oshige.
But I can't go.
Oh, I see.
But it's such a nice thing!
It's too much! Oh, I know!
Here, this is a gift in return.
A radio?
I won it in a lottery when
I was out shopping.
I already have a radio.
This will be a secret from
your grandmother!
I am so happy,
I am so happy!
Oh, yes! I have to listen to all of
Fuyuko Komaki's CDs again.
Well then, the fax theme
for this evening is,
"Christmas is almost here!
What do you want for a present?!"
I'm giving my grandma a knit shawl.
A hand knit present, huh?
You put so much into it, Mitsuki.
Think of your body...
and don't overdo it.
Hey, are there Christmas presents
in the world of Death Spirits?
It's not that there aren't, but...
Well, why don't you knit
a present for Takuto too?
Oh, are you not good at knitting?
No, but...is it okay?
What?
No... Umm... You're right!
It's Christmas!
Yes, let's all be happy!
I want to be happy too.
On Christmas Eve, I'm going to give Takuto
a present and confess my love!
Yeah!
And now one song.
This song will be released
on December 24th,
and it is Madoka Wakamatsu's
debut single.
It's a cover of
a Route L song,
and it was a hot topic when
she competed with Full Moon.
It's a little bit late,
but it's finally on sale.
Her version is more rhythmic.
If you give this to the person you like
for Christmas, I'm sure things will go well!
Here is Madoka Wakamtsu's,
"Eternal Snow"!
How long has it been
since I fell in love with you?
- My feelings keep getting stronger...
- Madoka... That's great.
I wonder if you can notice them.
Even though I've
never mentioned it.
They're silent like the snow,
but they keep building up.
Hold me tight,
if loving someone
was going to feel like this
I wish I never found out
about love.
I love you.
My tears won't stop.
If this is how it's going to be...
It would have been better...
I wish I had never met you!
Hey, Meroko.
Hmm?
Let's keep this a secret from Takuto until
Christmas Eve and surprise him, okay?
Yeah!
I'm sure that Christmas
this year is going to be lovely.
Okay, I'll see you on the 24th!
At four o'clock in front of
the shopping mall, right?
Yeah!
Mitsuki, Kumi invited Machida too!
Really?!
Yeah.
Wow! That's great!
Okay, bye!
- Bye!
What's up with that Meroko lately?
What do you mean?
Both yesterday and today,
she said, "I'm sleepy"
and wouldn't even come with you.
I'm sure that she's doing something
in the middle of the night.
Girls have a lot of things to do.
Like what?
Just a lot of things...
Yep, I'm sure that Grandma will
be happy to receive this.
Oh, you're so lucky, Mitsuki.
I haven't even scratched
the surface of my scarf.
Well, if it's come to this,
I'll use my powers!
If you don't knit it all
with your own hands,
you won't be able to convey
your feelings to Takuto.
What are you talking about
in the middle of the night?
Whoa! Nothing!
Th-That's right.
It's nothing.
It's okay to be excited for Christmas,
but keep it in check.
- Okay!
Grandma?
You could at least answer!
Meroko!
Umm... Grandma...
I've made plans with my friends today.
I'll come home before it gets too late.
May I go—
Do as you like.
Th-Thank you!
Well, I'm off!
Oh, she's here!
Mitsuki!
Everyone!
Wow...
It's a beautiful tree, isn't it?
I'm sure it's even more
beautiful in the evening.
It's romantic.
I've decided to confess to
Takuto over there!
Oh, I think that will be lovely.
What are you whispering about?
Oh, nothing!
It's a secret.
Huh?
What is it with those two?
- Merry Christmas!
Hey, what happened to everyone?
Umm... Machida...
Umm...
- Please go out with me!
- Yay!
Come to think of it, where is Meroko?
Oh, Takuto.
You have something in your pocket.
Huh?
So I'm supposed to clean
this up by myself?
Yes?
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji...
Merry Christmas.
Huh? Is it all over?
No, no.
There's still some food left over,
so let's make a toast!
I'LL BE WAITING AT
THE TOP OF THE TREE
IN THE SHOPPING MALL PLAZA.
—MEROKO
Meroko.
What is this?
You could've just told me this.
But...
I wanted to give this to you
in front of this tree.
You... Is this what you've been
sneaking around to do lately?
It's Christmas! It's the first Christmas
since Green Onion Ramen was formed.
Mitsuki taught me,
and I knit it the best that I could.
What?
She taught you?
Takuto... I've been given the cold shoulder
many times, but I'll keep confessing.
Takuto, I really like you.
What?
Oh, I understand.
You just...
I've confessed 58 times,
and this is the first time you didn't let it
go in one ear and out the other.
W-Well, it's the first Christmas
since we've met.
So...
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
I don't especially like anyone...
I'm unsure of...my feelings.
That's okay.
Compared to the past,
this is major progress. I'm satisfied.
This is great.
H-Hey!
Wrap this around yourself too.
Aww, Takuto!
I know, I know.
Stop crying.
Yay!
- Yahoo! Jingle, jingle...
- Hmm, 58 times, huh?
I let it go in one ear and
out the other 83 times.
Who cares about that this evening?
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Okay, smile, smile!
Huh? I don't understand
how to work the flash!
What are you doing? C'mon!
Actually, I have a present for
the two of you as well.
Here you go.
It's cute!
Mitsuki, you made these for us?
Hey Takuto!
Yeah!
Okay!
Green Onion Ramen returns the favor!
It's snowing!
Yeah!
Wow, so pretty!
Hello, everyone! Merry Christmas!
Well, our guest tonight is...
Full Moon!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
- Thanks for joining us tonight.
- Thanks you for having me!
Well, why don't we start with the song?
Will you introduce it for us?
Sure!
From the bottom of my heart,
I hope you all have a wonderful Christmas.
This is Full Moon,
and here is my song, "Eternal Snow."
Oh no! This is bad!
I know!
We were so caught up in the excitement
over the Best New Singer Award
that we forgot to think about
her grandmother!
Isn't there some way to convince her
to let her go to America?
There's no way!
We have to keep it a secret that
it's the prize for winning the award!
Oh, more bad news!
She got in a fight with
her grandmother!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Grandma's Past"
- Look forward to it!