The Impossible
Murder Case
His guard may have been down,
but even so, there aren't many humans
who could take out a Class S hero.
Indeed. The killer is probably...
one of us here!
But who was it?
The Zombieman
Murder File
The Day Before
The story begins a day ago.
We were honored as persons of distinguished service
for saving the Earth from alien invasions
and preventing the largest disaster in history.
To show their appreciation,
the Hero Association took us on an overnight trip.
That feels good...
It was very generous of the Association to take us
on a hot springs trip to celebrate our victory.
Though some of us left the field without fighting...
You're right.
How come we're sharing this place with a pack of jerks
who didn't lift a finger?!
We had other tasks.
What's more important than fighting aliens?
It's none of your business.
They were taking down violent criminals and monsters
with bounties on their heads in other towns.
It's all been confirmed.
They left because they figured
the rest of us could handle things without them.
Yeah, well, it all worked out.
I left because I was hungry.
I just want to protect my own town.
I've always got a pile of requests to get rid of monsters.
I can't lie around all day like you.
What'd you say?!
I had to skip my little sister's piano recital!
Come on, guys. Let's try to get along today.
I could have handled it all by myself.
Hey! You're not supposed to wear swimsuits in a hot spring!
W-Who cares...?!
Jeez...
I doubt that the danger Shibabawa-sama prophesied has passed.
I've asked you all here today under the pretext
of discussing this matter.
But be that as it may,
I am deeply grateful for your heroic acts on the day of the attack.
I'd like you all to let loose and enjoy yourselves tonight.
All right!
Cheers!
This is “Dragon Killer”, no?
A truly great sake!
Yeah. Easy to drink, but strong.
Who is it? Who's number one?
Muscle... pose!
Do they ever resist putting on a muscle show?
Having fun, Child Emperor?
Oh yeah, kind of.
I see. That's good.
No one would have believed it at the time,
but our peaceful party was about to turn into
a gruesome crime scene...
Let's start with the weapon that was used.
Yeah, that's mine.
But I left my sword in the banquet hall.
Someone must've taken it.
You don't believe me?
To begin with,
we were drinking in there 'til just recently, right?
True.
What? You think we're all conspiring together?
Atomic Samurai is innocent.
What?
Sitch and I were there too.
You can ask him.
I suppose he can't be a suspect,
so his testimony would be credible.
Besides, we have no motive.
A motive, huh...
Speaking of motives, I just remembered, Prisoner...
You were staring at Zombieman rather suspiciously!
Yeah... I was thinking it'd be so great...
What would?
If Zombie-chan here were mine.
However, I restrict myself to violent criminals.
Even then, I never kill them! What a waste!
But you're the only “convict" amongst us.
Although you escape from prison like it's nothing.
So society would say the least trustworthy is—
That's discrimination!
I am reasoning via the process of elimination.
In that case, I have someone in mind too.
I overheard an ominous remark when you and Zombie-chan were talking.
You asked Zombie-chan
if he really wouldn't die even if you punched him.
Yeah, Genos told me
there's a rumor going round that he's immortal.
Don't tell me
Saitama-sensei is a suspect?
I'm just looking at different possibilities from a rational perspective.
We don't know much about Saitama.
He could be a spy from another organization—
Well, maybe not with that face.
Look, even if Saitama-sensei wanted to kill Zombieman,
He would not need weapons.
A single punch—
Wait.
If Sensei wanted to test Zombieman's immortality,
he might have used a weapon to go easy on him.
That would make sense!
Sensei, do not worry.
I will defend you right to the end.
I didn't do it!
Now, now. The others haven't been cleared yet either.
Flash-san has fallen silent as he stares at the dead body.
Pig God-san is eating breakfast.
Watchdog Man-san is still sleeping.
And as for Metal Bat-san...
I didn't do it.
Unlike the others, I'm underage, so I didn't drink.
So I couldn't have gotten drunk and made a mistake...
W-What?
You're unusually quiet today.
Lay off! I'm just not a morning person, that's all!
Now, now...
So who first discovered the body?
Wouldn't they be the prime suspect?
It was the waitress here, so that's a dead end.
Well... I just ran over because someone told me...
What? So someone else discovered the body first?
King-san!
You...
Why didn't you say anything?
No one asked me.
Please tell us how you found the body.
I was on my way to the vending machine to get a drink
when I saw a body on the ground.
I let the front desk know.
That's it.
King-san, what were you up to last night?
I soaked in the bath in my room, then went to sleep.
What? This inn is known for its large outdoor bath.
Why would you use the bath in your room?
Such decisions are mine to make.
There was always something sketchy about this King guy...
I'm not trying to hide anything.
That sound...
You call it the “King Engine", right?
Am I to assume you are ready to fight?
If my innocence is under suspicion,
I'm left with no choice.
Jeez!
You're still at it?
If you're all under suspicion,
then I'll just restrain all of you!
Just a moment, Tatsumaki!
Restrain? What's going on?
Could someone pull this out?
Who attacked you, Zombieman-san?
Well, I drank quite a bit last night,
so I don't really remember.
But, if I'm not mistaken,
that sword came flying through the air and impaled me.
Then, because I was drunk, I must have fallen asleep.
So you're saying my sword was floating in the air?
Yeah, surrounded by a green light.
Just like that.
W-What?
Tatsumaki-chan, what did you
do after dinner last night?
I don't remember!
Were you perhaps drinking?
I don't know. I said, I don't remember!
You think you're gonna get away
with a lame excuse like that?
What?!
Look, I know Zombieman doesn't die when he gets killed!
If I wanted him dead,
I wouldn't do something this half-assed!
Let's just forget it already.
As we can all see, Zombieman is fine.
Yeah, it doesn't bother me.
Stuff like this happens all the time when you drink.
Huh?
No. Not really.
Okay, let's break it up.
Let's hit the baths, Iai.
Oh... right!
Child Emperor-kun...
Do you have a minute?
T-This is...
So it really was Tatsumaki-chan who did it.
She looks pretty drunk.
But why on Earth would she do this?
I know Zombieman doesn't die when he gets killed!
Oh, I get it!
She knew about Zombieman's regenerative abilities
and was just enjoying herself...
Then again,
what would make Tatsumaki-chan
let herself get that drunk?
So the little brat caused all that trouble?
But why would she do something like that?
That is...
...most likely your fault, Sensei.
I'm done.
Here.
I still don't like drinking...
Don't like drinking?
Stop acting grown-up.
You're a kid. Of course you shouldn't be drinking!
Kids should be drinking orange juice or something!
Huh?! How dare you—
I'll go order one for you right now.
Tatsumaki's pride likely got hurt,
so she forced herself to drink more.
You know, that hot spring
sure felt great, huh, Genos?
Yes!
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Kateru katenai janaku
It's not about winning or losing
Koko de ore wa omae ni tachimukawa nakucha ikenai n da!
It's about me taking you on right here, right now!
Seigi no jitensha nori mumen raida sanjo!
Bicycle Rider of Justice, Mumen-Rider, shall be your opponent!
Sorezore kikkake aru keredo
Although we have different motivations,
Kokorozasu no wa onaji koto
our goals are the same.
Shimin no anzen mamoru tame warera hiro wa yuku
We heroes are the ones who protect the citizens.
Jisseki. noryoku. kokedo zara ni wa ninki made
Results, abilities, contributions, and popularities!
Aa S kyu A kyu B kyu C kyu!
Ah, S Class, A Class, B Class, C Class
S kyo nana i ore wa kingu!
7th in the S Class ranks, I am the King!
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
...kono onsoku no sonikku ga hiro to issho ni uta nado utaeru wake ga nai!
...There's no way I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic, is gonna sing with you heroes!
Tsubekobe ittenai de ma omae mo utae!
Don't be such a smart ass, just sing alright!
Fussorenara chijo saikyo no otoko, kingu ga soro de utatte yaruze!
Hmpf! Then I, the King, shall sing solo as the strongest man on earth!
Ikigomi wa yoshi! naka yoku minna de utao u!
Well said guys! Let's sing together!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
Wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch ah March