The Impossible
Murder Case
The Zombieman
Murder File
The Day Before
Aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
Aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
Aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Kateru katenai janaku
It's not about winning or losing
Koko de ore wa omae ni tachimukawa nakucha ikenai n da!
It's about me taking you on right here, right now!
Seigi no jitensha nori mumen raida sanjo!
Bicycle Rider of Justice, Mumen-Rider, shall be your opponent!
Sorezore kikkake aru keredo
Although we have different motivations,
Kokorozasu no wa onaji koto
our goals are the same.
Shimin no anzen mamoru tame warera hiro wa yuku
We heroes are the ones who protect the citizens.
Jisseki. noryoku. kokedo zara ni wa ninki made
Results, abilities, contributions, and popularities!
Aa S kyu A kyu B kyu C kyu!
Ah, S Class, A Class, B Class, C Class
S kyo nana i ore wa kingu!
7th in the S Class ranks, I am the King!
Wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
...kono onsoku no sonikku ga hiro to issho ni uta nado utaeru wake ga nai!
...There's no way I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic, is gonna sing with you heroes!
Tsubekobe ittenai de ma omae mo utae!
Don't be such a smart ass, just sing alright!
Fussorenara chijo saikyo no otoko, kingu ga soro de utatte yaruze!
Hmpf! Then I, the King, shall sing solo as the strongest man on earth!
Ikigomi wa yoshi! naka yoku minna de utao u!
Well said guys! Let's sing together!
Aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
Ichigeki hissatsu one punch
Killing blow one punch
One-Punch March
Wanpan ondo
Odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dancing, singing, and fighting
Wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch ah March