Transform!
Toh!
Ta-dah!
Time to be Mana's little helper!
Me too!
Thanks for the help, Charles.
And Rachel, I'm grateful for the consideration,
but having an elementary schooler in a middle school's kinda, well...
But I want to help you, Rikka!
Thump!
I'm jealous, Charles...
President, Rikka, I need help!
Oh... what's wrong, Yashima?
My Pom-Pom...
My Pom-Pom's gone missing...
Pom... poms?
He looks like he has two tails, right?
Oh, hence the name.
Yes.
But because of that, he doesn't have many rabbit friends.
So I've been supporting him every day.
But now this...
Oh, Pom-Pom!
There's no need to cry!
We'll help you find him!
Charles is on the case, too!
Thank you all so much!
All right, I'm doing this!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Pom-Pom!
Pom-Pom, where are you?
Come out wherever you are!
Found him?
Nope.
Where did he run off to?
I don't know what I'll do if I can't find him!
Hey!
I found him! I found Pom-Pom!
Rachel!
Pom-Pom!
I was so worried!
Where were you?
Thank goodness you found him.
Rachel, you saved the day!
Way to go!
Thank you so much!
Huh?
Rachel, was it?
Yeah!
Oh Rachel, you're my hero!
Hero?
Yeah!
Rachel's on Cloud Nine!
A Full Throttle First Love!
I can't get Yashima's smile out of my head!
Huh?
What's this?
My heart's racing for some reason!
Am I coming down with something?!
This is bad! I gotta sleep!
Keep it down, will ya...
Your heart won't stop racing?
No, it won't...
Oh yeah, your face's been pretty red, too.
Do you have a fever?
Does he?
It burns!
Perhaps it's a cold?
Fairies can catch colds?
I've never seen one that did.
What else could cause it?
My chest is also all knotted up...
It hurts!
Maybe it really is a cold?
Not quite.
It must be lovesickness.
Lovesickness?
Rachel fell in love with that pet caretaker!
Huh?
Love? You mean...
H-Huh?
What is it?
That's what we wanna ask!
Are you really in love?
With Yashima?
Yashimaaa...
Ehehe...
It seems...
there's little room for doubt.
Meaning there's room for grave concern.
A fairy is in love with a human!
That's right!
We need to nip this in the bud, and fast!
You mean...
You want us to break them up?!
That's too much for our hearts to bear!
Hey, listen,
it's not like they're going out already...
Rachel, I won't hear any excuses.
You must let—
What's the big idea?!
Love is love!
This is for Rachel's own good!
Calm down.
You're both acting like children.
Objection!
Makoto, whose side are you on?!
Get back here!
Forcing moral dilemmas on Makoto is not okay!
Calm down, everyone!
Look, Yashima isn't e—
Yashimaaaa...
Yesterday, she said she'd be on duty, so I could come over to hang out!
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Yashima!
I'll help you clean the cages.
Rachel, you really came.
Thank you.
Can he handle this?
Handle what?
Rachel's the honest, overthinking type.
If he's really in love with Yashima, I can't help but worry...
Indeed, it's worrying!
He'll be fine!
The one he really loves is Rikka, after all!
I feel the same.
Done!
It's all clean.
Rachel, thanks for cleani—
Yashima!
A bee?
Yeah, it was about to hit your head.
You saved me again.
Rachel, you really are my hero.
It's racing again...
Why does it beat so fast when Yashima smiles?
It must be lovesickness.
Something wrong?
N-Not a nothing!
Well, let's go home, then.
Huh?
But I don't want to leave yet...
Let's stay just a bit longer...
Yashima!
What is it?
I want to spend another hour, or even just a half,
with you...
Then I'll show you my favorite spot.
I see...
I get it now!
I really am...
in love with Yashima!
Ugh.
Nothing but lovebirds as far as the eye can see.
Hmph. Too much free time.
That's rich, coming from you.
Are you in any position to say that?
Ooh, I'm shakin'!
Oh, there's a thought.
Without me around, you two look like lovebirds yourselves!
Have fun!
Lovebirds?!
Okay, I'm done here.
I think I'll go make some Precure lives hell.
But still...
what relation does that Kyupirappa have with Egogy?
It's curious...
It's like we're on a date!
My heart's pounding!
Rachel, are you not feeling well?
No, I'm fine!
I'm thrilled to be on this boat!
Oh, that's good.
I love this lake, myself.
Isn't the water so clean and beautiful?
She sure is...
You know, this lake is cleaned by a lot of volunteers,
and now it's so clean that even birds flock here!
Wow!
I want to help!
Thanks, Rachel.
So, what do you normally do, Rachel?
Battle the forces of evil with my comrades!
Oh, like role-playing?
It's not role-playing!
I know, I know.
All kids take their games seriously.
That's not quite it, but oh well.
Where do you live? What do you like?
Umm... oh, the Hundred Poets!
Really? Wow!
What's your favorite poem?
Huh? Um...
Um...
This one!
For your precious sake, once my eager life itself was not dear to me.
But now it is my heart's desire that I live forever.
I know that one!
It's a poem of love.
I just happened to remember it!
It was a love poem?
There's no denying it anymore!
I'm in love with Yashima!
Something wrong?
N-Not a nothing!
So Yashima, what kind of music do you like?
You think you're all so happy with your dumb boats?
This lake could rot for all I care.
I'm just venting...
Why not let this lake rot?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Flush!
What's that?
A dark heartbeat!
I heard it from the park!
Rachel!
Potty shower!
That is so gross!
That potty's spraying something funky!
No way in hell!
Shower!
Just like that.
Tear those couples and their pretty lake apart!
Why is this happening?
It's polluting the lake!
How horrible!
Then I'll protect this lake for you!
Rachel?
Yashima, wait there! I'm going!
Wait, Rachel!
This isn't a game!
I know...
But I'm serious!
Girls! A Selfish appeared!
Yeah, we're on our way to the park!
Girls, hurry!
This way!
We've gotta fight for Yashima!
He's really into it.
The power of love, I suppose.
All right girls, let's go!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Didn't they save us during the cultural festival?
Oh poor duck who has lost its love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Oh no, this is no duck! It's a potty!
Hyper Potty Shower!
Beware!
That shower is poison!
Wait, wait!
Rachel?
Yashima loves this lake!
So I won't let that thing hurt it!
When you put it like that...
I'll fight shower with shower!
Darn right!
Precure Diamond Shower!
I only pretended to be a potty!
Duck Feather Shower!
Thank you!
Think nothing of it!
Hyper Shower Shower!
No, not again!
How dare you!
Diamond Swirk—
You stupid potty!
Don't pollute the lake!
Rachel!
We're ramming him head on!
No, wait, Rachel, calm do—
I'm gonna protect this lake!
I promised Yashima I would!
Rachel, for real, stop!
I am...
Yashima's hero!
Seeeeeelf!
Pssssssss...
I suppose... we should purify it.
We send our power to you, Cure Heart!
Precure Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
What was that?
Hmph!
Yashima!
The lake returned to normal!
Yeah!
Because you protected it, right?
This is that Rachel boy I was telling you about.
He said he wanted to volunteer too!
Who's this?
My boyfriend, Harada.
Nice to meet you, Rachel.
Bo... y.... frie... nd?
Um... Rachel?
We ought to get going...
Rikka!
Sorry for keeping Rachel from you for so long.
Don't worry.
He had fun, right?
Y-Yeah...
Well, see you later, Yashima.
Sure.
See you later too, Rachel!
S-See ya!
His face is really swollen.
Should we bring more ice?
I'm sure that it's not his face that's in pain, but his heart.
I-I'm fine.
I protected the lake.
Your fighting out there was magnificent!
You were heroic, Rachel.
Your bravery was remarkable.
And you were strong.
Love makes us stronger.
I've learned something today!
Cheer up.
You've got me with you.
Right?
You know you're my number one, Rikka!
Rikka!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Ai won't eat her carrots!
She can't become a healthy adult if she's a picky eater!
Hold on.
Aguri, you've left nothing but carrots on your plate.
I left them on purpose!
Wait, do you hate carrots?
All right!
I, Cure Heart, will end your dislike of carrots once more!
Dokidoki Precure:
No More Picky Eating!
Carrots vs. Aguri!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!