Let's make it a little more lively...
There we go!
Maybe I should raise the tempo a bit.
Oh, nice!
The drums drive the beat,
the melody pumps me up,
and the words flow out.
The moment when I find that
"oh, nice!" deep inside...
My heart leaps so high
that it pierces the sky!
It's past midnight.
Hang on, hang on, hang on!
What's wrong with me?!
I need to study, damnit!
Study, study, study!
I guess just stacking samples isn't going to cut it.
In that case, maybe I should
make this part a little more subdued...
Study!
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change if you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning, the footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes, it never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal, it may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands, see? See?
See? There it goes again, it's so stupid
Shine a light through the hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream, even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything, even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
Everything will change if you just reach out
Stupid Q&A
TL note: reference to a song by Eastern Youth https://youtu.be/NL5D6-7C9hg
Crap!
Sorry...
The pigeon was on the rhythm...
Get it together!
I haven't even covered two pages since yesterday.
I might as well have just been goofing off.
Oh, a guitar.
I think this is what
they call an acoustic guitar?
Hello?
Oh, Nina-chan! Come in!
Have you eaten?
N-No.
We have meat buns! M-e-a-t b-u-n-s!
You're such a savage!
And you're such a princess.
You put sauce on your meat buns?
It's better this way.
A girl at my school
works in Chinatown and got some leftovers.
Oh yeah?
How is it?
It tastes great, thanks.
Good, I'm glad.
- So about that song...
- Is it done?
I wish it were that easy.
Why'd you call us here then?
I live pretty far away, you know.
I figured we should talk about what sort of song we wanna do.
What best suits the three of us? I just can't see it.
As long as I can drum, that's enough for me.
What do you think, Nina-chan?
It tastes great, thanks!
It's only been a week since I taught you how to use that app, right?
You came up with this in such a short time? Wow!
Well, Momoka-san said
that even if I can't read sheet music, I could do it by feel.
And so...
Still, I wasn't expecting something this complete.
You must've spent, like, eight hours every day on this.
Where are you going?
Home.
I have to study! I have to study!
Called it.
It's all your fault for teaching me this!
You said it wouldn't impact my studies!
Don't take it out on me.
I know.
If you know, then don't blame me.
But...
Fine, I get it.
I shouldn't have taught you.
I'll delete the app, so you just focus on singing.
Don't delete it.
Make up your mind!
It's my own fault!
I should leave band stuff to you,
and switch gears when I need to, right?
Who are you talking to?
Myself!
I'll see you next week.
Geez, what's with her? She's loopy.
I'm going home too.
Wait, what about the rest of the meat buns?
You can have them! Bye!
Nina-chan!
Let's walk to the station together.
Um, okay.
Writing a song like that really is incredible.
I could never manage it.
That was just, you know, monkey see, monkey do...
But the lyrics are a totally different story.
I guess so.
Yeah.
Um, I'm going to drop by the convenience store...
I'll come with.
Uh, that's alright.
I was going to walk home anyway.
Alright.
Bye.
Subaru too?
Why don't you do it?
I've gotta go to work. Is that a no?
It's not, but...
Look, you can go once class is over.
Just take it to her.
Remember the meat buns!
This place is famous...
For real?
What a bumpkin.
Where is it?
Umm...
Uhh...
This way?
Guess not.
I found it!
Excuse me?
Can I help you?
Um, yes!
I'm looking for Awa-san...
Awa-san?
Oh, you mean Subaru-chan!
Subaru!
Yeah, we can adlib that.
Nina-chan!
What brings you here?
Did you manage to get here okay?
If you'd called the school, I could've come to get you.
Sorry it took so long.
Here.
Oh, thank you!
What, did you lose it?
Yeah.
Teehee, silly me.
Oh, they're calling for you.
- Okay.
- See you.
Enjoy your evening!
Are you free now? Let's get some dinner.
My treat.
I, uh, have to study...
How about on the weekend then?
Can you do Sunday?
Um, really, it was no trouble.
I was already in the neighborhood.
Now if you'll excuse me...
Should I quit?
The band. Should I quit the band?
I'm not stupid. I can tell you're avoiding me.
Uh, no, I...
I'm not trying to get in your way or anything.
There are other bands out there I could join.
Uh, really, it's not like that...
It's just...
I'm sorry!
Are you sure?
Yeah. I can study later.
It's all pretty flexible.
Not that. I mean me.
I only started playing in my club
when I was in middle school,
so I can't get too uppity about it, but...
Bands are all about different people making music together,
and it can get pretty crowded.
When there's a disagreement, you can't just leave it be.
If you try and pretend nothing's wrong,
things will inevitably break down.
So if you don't like me,
you should just say so.
It's not that I don't like you.
It's a me problem.
I'm tired of hearing that.
I know, I'm a bitch.
I mean, no, that's not right!
It's just, I tend to keep my distance.
I'm shy, and people have to act considerate of me.
And you don't like that?
It's not that I don't like it.
But like, I find myself thinking
"I won't fall for that! I'm not that naive!"
whenever someone tries to get along with me.
You're so high maintenance.
That must be why you dropped out of high school.
No, that was...
Wait, she told you?
Maybe.
Must be nice up there on your high horse.
Now see here!
You've got the wrong idea about me!
They call it an acting school,
but they don't award high school diplomas.
We're in the same boat.
But you're aiming to become an actress!
Doesn't that mean you're chasing your dream?!
You can tell people that with your head held high!
Like I said, you've got the wrong idea.
Do you recognize her?
I feel like I might.
Detective Granny's Case Files.
They air reruns during the day.
She's my grandmother.
Really?
She won't shut up about wanting me
to follow in her footsteps.
"I'll put in a good word for you,
so enrol in this acting school."
So are you going to become an actress?
I'm not really aiming to.
But you're still attending an acting school...
Right? It drives me crazy.
"This isn't what I want. What am I doing here?"
But no one else sees things the same way.
They all just think it's natural, given my family.
Then what about the band?
Just my own way of fighting back.
Back in middle school, I swore I'd never join the Theatre Club.
I like music, so I joined the Light Music Club instead.
It was more fun that I expected.
I even secretly started my own band at one point.
Your grandmother didn't know?
How could I tell her?
Oh, have you seen Hachiko?
Won't people think we're hicks?
Who cares? You are a hick.
In for a penny, in for a pound.
I'm going to start calling you Nina,
you little punk!
Girls Band Cry.
SUNDAY NOON
A public concert?
Yep. I figured that'd be
a good way to kick things off.
I've already booked a slot at an event on Saturday.
Weren't we going to record a song and post it online first?
We'll do that too,
but I just feel like the three of us
- are like a concert.
- A concert?
When I saw the photo you sent me the other day,
you two struck me
as having this inescapable sense of misfortune, or dissatisfaction.
- How rude.
- That's right.
But that's exactly why I reached out to you.
Both of you.
- What do you think, Nina?
- It kind of ticks me off.
I kind of get what she means, though.
Can we even perform without a bassist?
You can't play, can you Nina?
The event is in the city. We'll figure something out.
Plus, we have this.
What is it?
A looper pedal.
You record some music like this...
And presto.
Whoa...
Um, a public concert means...
I'd have to sing in front of people, right?
Obviously. You saw me do it, didn't you?
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Give it a rest.
Let go of me! This wasn't what we agreed!
Quit complaining! You sang in front of the station!
It's the exact same thing.
Easy for you to say!
I've never done this before!
Don't worry. If things go wrong, I'll cover for you.
Then why don't you sing?
You're way better than me.
You wanna play the guitar then?
You know I can't.
I keep telling you,
I want to hear you sing.
Why?
You'll get it once you do it. Trust me.
I'm going home.
Are you quitting the band then?
I am. It was nice knowing you.
Wait!
It's alright.
It's so unfair to take the band hostage like that!
Your argument's falling apart.
- But I...
- Relax.
Regardless of whether it goes well or not,
regardless of whether we flop or fly,
you're gonna regret it either way.
That's what you're like.
- That's...
- The truth.
You might as well bare it all
and sing with whatever you're feeling right now.
Am I wrong?
Nina got blown the fuck out.
You shut up!
Shove that rage into your singing!
That's who you really are.
Ooh, they've got some pretty nice gear!
Yep. They're the cheapest place in the area, too.
Let's give this a go.
Yep, not bad.
Nina, have you memorized the song
I sent you the other day?
I've worked in bits of the song you wrote.
Yeah.
Cool. Try singing, then.
Don't tell me you didn't see this coming.
It's all so sudden!
Like I said, just relax.
It's just practice. No one expects it to go perfectly.
So what if you screw up?
Here.
Slower.
One, two, three, four!
How was that?
I've got goosebumps!
Really crazy goosebumps!
Uh oh.
You've fallen for Momoka-san's trap.
Now that you know how it feels,
you'll never be able to quit.
But why...?
Homo sapiens, you see,
are genetically wired to dance to music.
It's our base instinct to sing and dance.
Right?
Yep.
What's the matter?
Nothing. You just reminded me of how nice your voice is.
Really?
Yeah. You gave me goosebumps, too.
Come on, let's keep going.
Okay!
A medium and a beer.
Medium, no onions.
Medium.
You sound hungover.
You both told me to sing as hard as I could.
Yeah, but nobody actually sings so hard their voice dies!
Oh, shut up.
"Thank yer very much."
I'm sure it'll mend by tomorrow,
but you gotta take care of your throat.
Are you three in a band?
You've got a guitar case.
You're welcome to come see us.
Thank you very much.
SHIN-KAWASAKI (TENTATIVE)
She invited us.
So?
We could invite them too.
Maybe after we see them first.
Thanks for the food.
Alright, I'm off.
Where to?
Work.
See ya.
She paid for us again today.
Both here and at karaoke.
What's she looking at?
Probably her former bandmates.
See?
The next band is making their debut performance today!
They're a three woman band, started in Kawasaki!
Their name is...
"Shin-Kawasaki"?
We're going to have to discuss our band name later.
Come on, it's just tentative.
Sorry I'm late.
Don't tell me...
You plan on going on stage dressed like that?
Should I not?
I did tell you to bare it all.
Go get changed.
Ahem. This is a business-related announcement.
I thought the outfit you hated the most would work best.
Don't overthink it.
Just cram in everything you think and feel.
Don't worry. Trust me.
You're weak, but so stubborn.
You're cowardly, but so confident.
You're a bundle of self-contradiction.
That's not a compliment!
Come on, Nina! It's time to go!
That's just how gloomy and pent up you are.
And that's...
Well and truly...
Rock.
Rock?
No one here knows you.
No one here cares.
But that's what makes things interesting.
You're so rock'n'roll, Nina.
If nothing changes
No matter how long I wait
Then there's nobody I can rely on
It's not as if the pain disappears
When you blame someone else
I pray to say goodbye
To cowering every day
Holding my knees to my chest
I don't even believe in God
Shut up
(Shut up)
Leave me alone
(Leave me alone)
A stranger sings
Until they lose their voice
Telling me that I'm not alone
I'm sure that to some people
Those words are enough
I don't know
I see
Was that right?
I forgot
It's all a pain
I want to break it
I don't have the courage
Someone hurry up and teach me
A reason to live
There are so many people to take my place
You can't just tell me to be myself
Take it back if it can be granted
I can dream all I want
There's still reality
Is anyone there?
That...was so...
rock.
AWA SUBARU
Sorry, I'm quitting the band!
Next episode:
"Thanks (Surprise)".
TL note: reference to a song by Fishmans https://youtu.be/d6mAmJskZIY