When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
One morning, the boy found
himself in the Twilight Zone.
What?
WHAT?!
That's...
It can't be!
Panning vertically!
A close-up horizontal pan!
I-It's Isumi!
But what's with her outfit?
Kid, you're digging it, aren't you?
What?! She's getting on
a bus with no hesitation!
Th-This can't be...
I'm getting on!
Go return the utility pole.
Oh, whoops!
Or Tokyo Electric Power Company
is going to yell at you.
You're right.
Ta-da!
I'm getting on...
I didn't make it on!
You brought that on yourself.
Isumi...
What the heck is going on here?! Tell me!
You don't come over often, but when you do,
you ask the most nonsensical
questions, you know that?
But I mean, a blazer!
The answer to that is simple.
You haven't seen Isumi lately, have you?
Oh, well, I've been busy
with finals and stuff.
What you saw was a hallucination!
A hallu...cination?
It's got to be a hallucination!
Right now, everyone in town
looks like Isumi to you!
There's no way that's true!
That was definitely Isumi!
Then how about this?!
She's probably fallen for
a guy at another school,
so she's sneaking in by
wearing their uniform.
Who the heck goes to such lengths?
Well, we like in a "Hana-Kimi" sort of world,
where girls disguise themselves as
guys to get into all-boys' schools
just to see a good-looking guy she adores.
But you're putting on an awfully nuanced
performance at a time like this.
I guess...
But I had no idea the world
had progressed that far.
That's right.
Technical High School
Whether there's a school gate there!
No vandalizing!!
Or a wall!
Or nurikabe wall monsters!
Climbing over them all is
what it means to be a girl!
Could it be...?
Could it be...
...that Isumi is...
Do Not Climb
...trying to climb over?!
Up we go.
Pardon me, we could not
help overhearing that.
No worries.
I wouldn't say it's entirely impossible,
but don't cases like the one you
outlined tend to be exceptional?
I don't see the need to be
so hard on a boy in distress.
It's fun to mess with him.
I mean, Isumi in a blazer getting on a bus!
Well, it's too bad it's not a
sailor suit and a machine gun.
That's way old.
It sounds interesting, so go
investigate it for me, Hayate.
I'll be counting on you.
Miss, just because it sounds interesting...
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
Isumi's found some guy she
likes?! Say it isn't so!
Young Sir, what is the matter?
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
His Name Is Magic Ball Pitcher Wataru!!!
Video Rental
V Tachibana
Duskin today, Duskin tomorrow.
Junki Takegami
Gaou Rangerman
Young Sir, I found "Ryukendo"
mixed in on the Toei sentai shelf!
Oh, yeah?
I'll put it away.
Go! Goodman
Young Sir, that is the shelf
for Toho's superhero SFX films.
Toho Superhero SFX
Right...
More Shochiku films other than "The
X" and "Goke, Body Snatcher"...
Superhero SFX is a genre you know well.
How could you make a mistake like that?
Did something happen?
Nah, not really.
But when you're so blatantly depressed...
What happened to the Young Sir?!
As his maid, I cannot just let this go!
A-Are you all right?
H-Hayate...
I was afraid he might be like that...
The Miss was feeding his
fears quite a bit, after all.
So that was the reason.
Huh? Is something wrong?
No, it's just that he won't come
to me for advice, and yet...
No, it's probably because
it's easier for him to talk
to Miss Nagi, who is his age,
or some other equally trivial reason.
So, as I suspected, being older is no good.
No, no, no, no!
I am past 20 already, so perhaps it
means I am past my expiration date.
Th-That is not the issue!
You're still at a luscious age! I
mean, even if you were married...
Wait. That's...!
Young Sir!
Is it all right to be doing this?
Ta-da!
No, it ain't.
Young Sir!
As I recall...
Okay, pan. Keep panning.
That uniform is...!
Shio
Even if what Nagi said was right...
Darn it! Thinking about it
isn't going to get me anywhere!
I did not imagine such
a turn of events, so...
This outfit stands out, doesn't it?
You always stand out...
But under normal circumstances, I
think he would've noticed us long ago.
Next stop, Shiomi Municipal
High School Main Gate.
Shiomi?!
I am burning to get off
at the next stoooooop!!
It has been a long time since I've
found myself coming to this school...
Isumi's... here...
Damn it! You can't keep Isumi and
me apart with something like this!
Young Sir...
Isumi must have been wearing their uniform.
Why does he have to go to
such lengths for Isumi?
But if only I could do something
for the Young Sir...
Um, if you'd like, shall I tell you
how to get inside the school grounds?
Is it normal for butlers to
know things like that, too?
Uh...
Rider Kick!
Darn it! Why won't the gate open?!
Since it's come to this,
I'll do a vertical suplex...
Young Sir.
Wh-What are you doing here?!
What about you?
That's none of your business, right?
That is part of my business.
I have heard what is going on from Hayate.
Did you think I could just
leave you to your own devices?!
Y-Yes, ma'am! Please do as you see fit!
Now, get into the school grounds
through the tear in this fence.
There's no tear.
What?!
This cannot be! According to
the map Hayate drew for me...
But there isn't.
Goodness! It has been completely repaired!
Wow, Wataru, what are you doing here?
Y-You...?!
Never mind. Could you just let us in?
Okay, sure.
Makariku Maharita! There!
Oh...
I'm always barely on time,
so don't underestimate me!
Are you bragging?
So, what are you doing here?
Yeah...
There are times when a man
just has to get going.
Young Sir, you can act
cool like Captain Okita,
but it is lame when you are
caught on the chain link fence.
Shut up!
At any rate, might we ask you
to show us around the school?
Sure, I don't mind, but it's
a really normal school.
I see...
Wait, whoa!
Wh-Wh-What is th-th-that?
Uh, uh, um...
They're delinquents.
You know, we're a normal high school,
so we have people like that, too.
What a good boy you are!
Puppies are so awesome! They're
so soothing for the soul!
What fortune is this?!
Shio
What about that?
No idea...
You've never seen a female gang leader?
You know, because we're a normal high school.
No, no, you don't see those these days.
That's so cool!
Th-That smelled nice.
This is the fragrance of lavender.
You know, because we're a normal high school,
we sometimes get a girl leaping through time.
That's not the anime version.
That is the Tomoyo Harada version.
You should be able to handle the rest, right?
I have to hurry back to the co-op,
or they'll be sold out. Later!
Having said that, the
girl cheerfully ran off.
Y-Yes.
My heart is pounding.
Spin, spin.
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
This does not seem... to be the place...
Isumi...
Is Isumi not here?
Here we go!
Y-Yes.
This also does not seem... to be the place.
This also does not seem... Ptewy.
Naturally, this is not a fan service episode
Swimming, swimming, swimming along...
made specially for the Isumi fans.
Isumi is searching for something here.
Where in the world could Isumi be?
Young Sir?
Why are you straining like that?
What?
Why is Isumi dressed like that?!
Young Sir? Whoa, whoa.
Not only that, but at the
end of her intent gaze is...
Senpai
What's with that guy with the face
that makes you want to touch it
and "senpai" written on his back?!
I imagine you do not watch
DVDs along those lines, but...
Wha?!
That is a standard move in youth dramas.
The "Senpai, please wipe your
sweat with this" attack!
What?!
So this is the move that's
considered an endangered species
in anime and TV shows,
and even in girls' manga.
The "Senpai, please wipe
your sweat with this"!
You fools!
For you young'uns out there,
try asking your Showa
Era mothers and fathers.
I may not look it, but I am
still just a bit past 20, so...
The white towel is an essential
item for a girl in love.
It is a symbol that says,
"I will be there for your sweat
and tears of youth, senpai."
I am well aware of that.
SHOCK!
Maybe I didn't really know who Isumi was.
That Isumi wanted that blue
set square sort of season
that the sun could give or withhold...
That she was looking for
that experience of youth...
It's true, the ardent passion of
youth isn't flowing in my veins.
Flowing in me is the murky blood of an otaku!
Will the Heavens forsake me?!
The sun... is blinding!
Young Sir, the sun is that way.
Right, right.
The sun...
Ruru-ruru-ru ru-ta-wa. What is it in reverse?
(Ruru-ruru-ru ru-ta-wa. Hantai kara yomu to?)
Tonto-ton-ton, favorite part? Roasted jowl butt.
(Toto-ton-ton, suki na bui wa? Tontoro rousu.)
This place brings back memories.
But I feel shy about seeing
my old friends again.
I need to be careful, so no one spots me.
Hayate!
It's only been 7 seconds and 3 frames!
Miss Nishizawa... Looks like you found me.
Why is Hayate here? Could it be
that maybe he's come to see me?
Since it's come to this, it
might be faster just to ask her.
Um...
Has anything strange happened today...
Want some bread? It's half-eaten, but...
What?
No, it's nothing.
Oh, really! What am I saying
at a time like this?!
Um...
Y-Yes?
Oh! I saw you!
No, I mean, other than me.
Not much else has happened.
We're a normal high school here,
so there aren't any celebrities
or IT industry CEOs here.
That's true.
Pardon me for interrupting your meal!
Oh, wait a minute!
If it's like the Seven Mysteries of
Shiomi High School, I could tell you.
Huh?
Ever since the manager of a certain
club suddenly passed away,
all kinds of strange things have
been happening after school.
Because of that, no one
wants to stay after school,
and all the managers quit.
Everyone says it's the
dead manager's curse now.
I feel like those are all horror
stories I've heard somewhere before.
Well, it's just a rumor, though.
Could it be...
...that Isumi was asked to banish
a spirit in relation to this?
Thank you very much!
See you around!
See you!
What the heck? So Hayate
wasn't here to see me...
This yakisoba sandwich is making me tear up!
Young Sir...
It's true, I don't have impressive pecs...
And sweat and tears aren't for me!
Young Sir!
So... this was the place...
No one... Not anyone else...
No one will be allowed to
wipe my senpai's sweat!
Um...
Go ahead.
You can use my body.
What?
Y-You can see me?
Yes, you could say that.
A hit! There's a hit!
All that aside, what did you
mean? Go ahead with what?
You may use my body as a medium
to make your wish come true.
What? C-Can I really?
Yes.
So I'm a loser!
Loser
Young Sir!
What?!
I don't care anymore!
It's just too blindingly brilliant!
I don't have a chance in...
You hit me! I've never
even been hit by my dad!
Please do not say that line!
Because this is not a
parody! This is your life!
Young Sir, are you really fine with this?
You even said it yourself earlier, remember?
That there are times when a
man just has to get going.
There are times when a man
has to face things head-on,
no matter how great an
obstacle stands in your way.
I understand.
Young Sir!
But how am I supposed to
face that great obstacle?
I may not look it, but I have more
life experience than you, so...
Once upon a time, when it
came to a man-to-man fight...
Soul
...it was always a baseball match,
putting heart and soul into one pitch!
Hitting and hitting, and
pitching and pitching!
Truly, fair and square!
No regrets in your youth!
All right, I understand.
Saki
Thank you.
Someday, the Young Sir may sprout wings...
And maybe leap out of a window...
And because I'm kind of sort of the
Bible that teaches him about freedom,
so it's fine. This is how it should be.
Even she doesn't really
know what she's saying,
so even if there were a song that
had similar-sounding lyrics,
it would merely be a coincidence.
Ah, a thesis, a thesis.
Saki, where did Wataru go?
The Young Sir...
...has gone to fight a man's battle!
Huh?
Senpai.
Here you are.
Hold it right there!
Who are you?
Yeah! What do you want?!
Soul
A baseball match!
Putting heart and soul into
one pitch for her white towel.
I request that you engage me
in an earnest duel between men.
The winner will get his sweat wiped
by the manager with her white towel!
Hey, you can't just do that!
Interesting. I accept!
Young Sir...
Watch me, Isumi!
I'm going to put everything I've experienced
in my life thus far into this one pitch!
How dare he get all fired up on his own?
Reach for me! My...!
Young Sir!
My...!
I'm completely burnt out.
Young Sir!
Saki, I've been defeated...
and I have no regrets.
Yes, sir.
I worked up a good sweat.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Now, you have no more
regrets holding you back.
Isumi!
That must have been tough for you.
A job well done.
I will escort you back to your residence.
I-I appreciate it, but...
I-Isumi, I... I mean, I myself...
Wataru, you helped me, didn't you?
Thank you for letting him
work up a good sweat.
I guess...
...Isumi appreciated what I did.
I don't quite understand,
but it seems to have gone well.
So in the end, it looks like I
was making a fuss over nothing...
Lame, huh?
You were a fine young man today, Young Sir.
What? Really?
Yes. You were cooler than
I have ever seen you.
I see.
Let's go home.
We left the shop unattended.
Yes, Young Sir.
What the heck?
So Isumi was just working
part-time as a manager?
Yes, apparently so.
After all, I can't tell her
that Isumi was working...
...to banish the spirit of a dead manager.
They say that reality is
stranger than fiction,
but nothing that strange ever happens.
True.
This doesn't leave anything
for Tamori to comment on.
Indeed, I agree, Miss Nagi.
No, no, what happened was
actually plenty strange.
Next time, it looks like a rival
will be appearing for Hayate.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Student Council Girl Trio
Lettering by Masumi Asano
The student council girl
trio's Butler Report!
Butler Report
Morning, it's Izumi Segawa.
I'm Risa Asakaze.
Explosion! I'm Miki Hanabishi.
Today will be the last of the
Student Council Girl Trio specials.
These 3 weeks have flown by.
But no matter how many times I listen to
this song, I still think it's a masterpiece.
Yes, a masterpiece!
It could even be featured on
that New Year's music show!
It might even be as good
as our national anthem!
No, it should be turned
into the show's theme song!
Okay, time for the fan service shot.
Actually, if you paste the 3 fan service
shots together, you get one single picture.
That's amazing!
Which means we have no choice but to
use it to create original merchandise!
Adios, amigo!
Preview
Hayate, you don't have to work anymore.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Is that to say that you're firing me?
No, no, that's not it.
It means you can take a break
from your butler duties
and focus on your studies
until exams are over.
I made arrangements just
for such an occasion!
For a new, temporary butler!
A pleasure to meet you.
I am Mecha Butler No. 13.
Next time, "Sure, Amuro May Have
Had a Place to Return to, But..."
I am superior to him, you know.
Sure, Amuro May Have
Had a Place to Return to, But..."
Change! Switch on, one, two, three, with
"Hayate the Combat Butler" next time!