[NARRATOR]
On the day before
the long-awaited Promised Day,
Alphonse Elric
hid in a train yard
outside the Eastern
training grounds.
However, the Homunculi
Gluttony and Pride
surprised him
with an ambush...
Defenseless against their
attack, Alphonse is captured.
[PRIDE]
Alphonse.
It's time to
wake up, Alphonse.
[AL GRUNTS]
[AL]
Who are you?
[PRIDE]
It's too soon for you to die.
We aren't done with you yet.
There's still so much work
we have in store for you.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[FAMERS GRUNTING]
[ED]
Excuse me... Is this
place called Kanama?
[FARMER]
Mr. Ho.
You've got some company.
[HOHENHEIM]
Edward... I didn't think--
Ahhh. That felt good.
Ahh... You could've
at least warned me
you were about
to slug me...!
And with your
metal hand, too.
Hmph...
[HOHENHEIM]
I see you've made
a new group of friends.
We're not--
It's more like we're all
in the same sinking ship.
That's right...
And I guess you could say
I'm the captain of that ship.
So you're
the one in charge?
Then I'd like to thank you
for looking after my son.
Sure... But you know he
can be a real pain in the ass.
Hey!
That's an interesting tattoo.
Yeaahhh... You noticed...
I guess there's no
point in hiding it.
But let's make this
honesty thing mutual, pops.
Look, we need to talk.
The Promised Day is tomorrow.
Fair enough...
I'll tell you everything.
[ED SHUDDERING]
[HOHENHEIM]
I was worried this might be
more difficult for you to accept
than it was for Alphonse.
Wait, you told
Al about this?
I did... I'm sure he has his
own thoughts on the matter...
...but he accepted
it none the less.
If you want to use me to get
your bodies back... you can.
Are you crazy...?!
Maybe you are a living
Philosopher's Stone...
...but I'm not gonna
sacrifice innocent souls...
It's our fault
we lost our bodies!
[HOHENHEIM SIGHS]
I'm proud my son
feels that way.
There will be
a solar eclipse tomorrow.
He plans on harnessing
it for his scheme.
An eclipse...?
So that's his plan?
Listen, Edward...
He has to be
stopped at all costs.
I need you to help me.
Help you...?
Now look here...
I'm gonna stop that
bearded bastard...
but I'm not doing it because
you want me to help you!
Our best chance at beating
this guy is to team up,
and that's the only reason I'm
even talking to you right now!
[ED SEETHES WITH ANGER]
That's fine with me.
It doesn't matter
what your reasons are
as long as you'll
still fight alongside me.
[ED]
Granny asked me...
...to give you
Mom's final words.
[ED BREATHES DEEPLY]
"Sorry I couldn't
keep my promise..."
"...but I'm dying first."
So there, I told you!
[ED GASPS]
[HEINKEL]
Y'know, Ed... Don't
ya think you should
maybe try to be a little
nicer to your old man?
[DARIUS]
Yeah, really... You could at
least refer to him as "Dad."
It sounds like you've had
a rocky past with him...
but he doesn't strike me as the
type who'd abandon his wife...
Y'know?
The guy must've had
his reasons... So...
Why don't you give him
the chance to explain?
[ED SCREAMS]
Shut up...! Did ya ever think
that I've got my reasons?!
Oh, yeah?
Let's hear 'em then.
You're just stubbornly
holding a grudge.
[GREED]
Heh. Such a whirlwind
of emotions...
I can see why...
The guy's a walking, talking
Philosopher's Stone...
And to make it worse... He
also happens to be your father.
[ED]
There's more
to it than that.
It's just... He's not
what I was expecting.
[TRISHA]
Someday...
I'm going to be a wrinkled
old monster myself...
So today... we're going
to take this picture,
and I'll be able to remember
us all together smiling...
No matter what,
we're always a family.
[HOHENHEIM]
Trisha... I'm going away.
Will you wait for me?
[HOHENHEIM GASPS]
[TRISHA]
Of course.
I'll be right here.
I'm sorry, Trisha...
I couldn't keep my promise.
You passed away so early.
You knew that I was unable to
grow old and die with you...
...but you always
believed that I'd come back.
I should've been
beside you, my love.
Tomorrow... Trisha.
[OLDER WOMAN]
And here you go.
[ED]
Thank you, ma'am.
[GREED]
And what exactly
is that for?
Whoa!
C'mon, what's wrong with
what you're wearing now?
That doesn't seem
flashy to you?
[ED]
There's a pretty good chance
this is gonna be the last
battle we ever fight.
I want to do it in style.
[ED]
Listen, guys...
you don't have to tag
along with me, y'know...
I'm thinking you'd be
better off going your own way
before things start
to get too serious.
Hey, hold on... That isn't
your call to make, pal,
I'm the one in charge.
I mean, if it's...
...just about trying to
get your old bodies back...
That's not it...
These bodies do
have their perks...
To be honest, I don't really
mind staying like this.
[GREED LAUGHS]
Yeah, now that's the spirit!
So why stick with me then?
Well, why wouldn't we...?
It's not like we have
anything better to do.
My animal instincts tell me
something good's comin'...
So I'll ride this
thing out with you.
[ED SIGHS]
And what's your
story, Greed...?
Are you hoping to settle the
score with the other Homunculi
for what they did
to your friends?
[GREED]
Are you asking me why I've
decided to return to Central?
I'm not telling ya, kid.
[ED STAMMERS]
Hmm...?
Hey, What's the holdup?
[ED GASPS]
[METAL CLANKING]
It's Al!
Oh, man, you
freaked me out there!
Feels like I haven't
seen you in years...!
How've you been, Al?
[AL]
I'm glad to see
you're okay, Brother.
Hey, wait...
I thought you were with Major
Miles over in the Eastern area.
Nothing bad happened, right?
That's actually why
I'm here... We need to talk.
Uh, sure.
Hey, uh... Are you sure
you're feeling alright, Al?
[GREED SHUDDERING]
What do you mean?
Well...
You seem a little...
[LING]
Ed!
Ling?
Get away from him!
That's not...
He's a...
[METAL CLANKING]
[DARIUS SHOUTS]
What...
What the hell was that?!
[PRIDE]
I see that you're working
with them now... Huh, Greed?
How pathetic that you'd share
your consciousness with a human.
Your soul couldn't
be any weaker!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[MILES]
The Fuhrer's remains
haven't turned up yet?
[GRUMMAN]
So far, they've only found
one of his subordinate's
bodies washed up downriver.
It would take some kind of
miracle to live through that.
I'd like the cooperation
of the Northern forces...
...but I intend to oversee
the rest of the search.
You're gonna
personally direct it?
I won't be able to
comfortably sleep at night
until I see his corpse
with my own eyes.
And what about
the plan, sir?
Aren't you going to
proceed to Central?
I don't seem to
have much choice.
I suppose I'll just have
to let Colonel Mustang
have the bigger slice
of Central pie.
[GRUMMAN THINKING]
Bradley's current
administration will still be
properly functioning
at this point in time.
If Colonel Mustang
or General Armstrong
try to make their move now,
every soldier in Central
will be ordered to retrieve
their treasonous heads.
And once they're captured...
I'll step in to restore order.
They'll take the fall
as enemies of the state...
while General Grumman
will heroically come
riding in on a white horse.
I'll let the youngsters
dive headfirst into danger
and do all the dirty work...
and then I'll take
my rightful place
as leader of this country
without any risk.
[MILES THINKING]
It wouldn't surprise me
if that's what the sly
old fox is plotting.
We may have joined forces to
prepare for the Promised Day...
But I'll withhold my
trust until it's passed.
[SOUNDS OF METAL WARPING]
That's not...
[GREED]
It's Pride.
You don't mean that--
[GREED]
Yeah...
That's my brother...
My oldest brother,
I guess you'd say.
[ED GASPS]
A Homunculus...?!
[PRIDE]
So, you've made up your mind to
betray us no matter what, Greed.
Which makes you nothing
more than an annoyance
to us at this point.
Damn it... How did you
even know I was here?
[PRIDE LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
How dare you disguise
yourself as my brother?!
[PRIDE]
Who said this
was a disguise?
[PRIDE]
This is, without a doubt,
your brother's actual body.
You bastard!
[PRIDE]
First things first,
I need to deal with Greed...
Now, Fullmetal Alchemist,
if you would be so kind
as to come with me.
Heinkel, you guys
should run for cover.
What the...?
You don't waste any time!
Our animal instincts are
telling us that we should
stay the hell away
from that thing.
[ED GRUNTS ANGRILY]
It'd probably be
smart for you to run too.
I'll be just fine...
They need me and Al
for their plans
so they aren't
gonna kill us.
But that doesn't mean I've
gotta go easy on them...
I've got no problem
taking them down!
[PRIDE]
You're right...
I must take you alive.
But if I slice off a few of your
limbs in the process, so be it.
I've gotta make sure to keep
him away from the slums.
[EXPLOSION]
A barrier's not
gonna work against him!
[GREED THINKING]
That was close.
[GREED YELLS IN PAIN]
[PRIDE]
Now then... I've captured
your friend, Fullmetal...
Ready to give up?
You're not going to make me
threaten the lives of the
slum dwellers too, are you?
True to form... He always goes
straight for the cheap shot
in order to
get what he wants.
I think it's about time
I start winning some of
these fights for a change.
[SMALL EXPLOSION]
[GREED GASPS]
[FARMER 2]
What happened?
[FARMER 3]
It's a blackout.
[FARMER 4]
Who shut off the lights?!
[ED]
I can't see a damn thing...
But then, neither can he...
[HEINKEL]
Greed.
Is that you, Heinkel?
It's me...
What happened to the power?
I don't know...
But it's saving our asses...
Pride can't cast any shadows
without a source of light
and he's just as blind in this
darkness as the rest of us.
So we got
rid of him then?
No... He's just
lying in wait...
He'll be back at it as soon
as the lights are on again--
Ow, Damn it.
[DARIUS]
So what do we do now?
Hey, Heinkel...
Did you notice the shadow
cast by Al's body?
Yeah... It's kind of hard to
miss those freaky tentacles.
No, not those.
[GREED]
He kept close to the edge of
the shadows from the forest.
His actual body's probably
just beyond those trees.
His body?
So he's not
inside the armor?
No... He's got a special
container that he uses
when he's
traveling around.
[DARIUS]
What kind of container?
[PRIDE THINKING]
The skies are
completely overcast.
The others won't be able to
see in this darkness either...
The slum's lights
will be on soon enough.
[HEINKEL YELLS]
You're not getting away!
You've got some pretty strong
nerves to attack a small child
without even flinching.
It'd be different if you
were an actual child...
but I know what you are!
And not only that...
But my animal instincts
are screaming at me!
They're tellin' me to
kill you before you kill me!
[DARIUS]
Ed!
Hey, Ed!
I'm over here.
Where's your brother?
Same spot as earlier...
His body clanks
whenever he moves.
Alright... Let's get out
of here for the time being.
I'm not gonna leave
Al behind like that.
I know how worried
you've gotta be...
but what if we get close to him
and it turns out to be a trap?
We've gotta stick
close to one another
until Heinkel's
done with Pride...
We don't want to accidentally
attack each other.
[LOUD THUDS]
[ED]
So those sounds...
That's the lion guy
fighting with Pride?
It's always
your best bet
to let the nocturnal animals
handle fighting in the dark.
[GREED THINKING]
Damned Pride... How was he
even capable of finding us?
Did Father give him
some new ability?
[DARIUS GASPS]
[GLUTTONY GROWLING]
Get down! Now!
[GLUTTONY YELLS]
[ED, DARIUS, AND GREED
THUD ONTO THE GROUND]
[TREE CRASHES
AGAINST THE GROUND]
[GLUTTONY]
I smell you Fullmetal
Alchemist... And I smell Greed.
Of course he'd
bring Gluttony!
That fat slob?!
That makes sense. Now I know how
Pride managed to track us down.
He used Gluttony's sense of
smell to follow our scent.
[GLUTTONY SNIFFS]
I also smell someone
I never smelled before...
...and they smell tasty!
It's all you...
Go for it...
Oh, and he's a
Homunculus by the way.
How do you expect me to
fight a monster like that?
He's relying on his sense of
smell to guide him in the dark.
So right now, I'd say you're
evenly matched for a fair fight.
My animal instincts
are calling me an idiot
for listening to you.
So I guess I'm an idiot...!
The first strike is mine!
[DARIUS GROWLING]
[GLUTTONY YELLS IN PAIN]
[DARIUS AND GLUTTONY
BOTH GRUNTING]
[GLUTTONY SCREAMS]
Now for the final blow!
Why, Mr. Gorilla...?
Weren't we sticking close to
avoid attacking each other?
Sorry.
[GREED THINKING]
So Gluttony's got the upper hand
on all of us in the dark...
And then we've got Pride to deal
with when the lights are on...
There's not much hope for us.
[LING]
Hey, Greed.
What, Ling?
Switch with me... I can detect
the presence of a Homunculus
when I'm the one in control.
I was the one who warned
us about Pride, right...?
I'll be able to maneuver
around through the darkness.
[GREED SIGHS FRUSTRATEDLY]
[GREED]
It's not like
I have a choice!
But don't go tryin'
to run off with this body!
Just drop it... It was
my body to begin with.
Time to eat you!
[LING]
Got ya!
[GLUTTONY CHOKING]
Heh...
[GREED]
Wow, nicely done...
I'm glad that you and
I are on the same team.
Thanks.
Ling?
That's right!
[GLUTTONY]
You're making me mad...!
All I wanna do is eat...!
But you won't let me eat you,
and I'm getting hungrier!
You're being mean!
So I'm just gonna have
to swallow everything!
I sense somethin' bad.
Bad, how bad?
It's coming this way.
What's coming
this way?!
[LING]
I've felt this
presence before.
[ED]
Will you freaks tell me what
the hell you're talking about?!
Hello?! Normal guy here!
I can't see in the dark!
[DARIUS GASPS]
What's the-?!
What happened?
[ED YELLS]
Stay down, kid!
Is there something
else out there?
I'm not sure.
But I think it might--
It is...!
[GLUTTONY]
I smell you.
[GLUTTONY SCREAMING]
I know... that smell.
[GLUTTONY CHOKING]
[ED GASPS]
I'm glad to see you're okay!
I was wondering when
you'd find me... Lan Fan.
[NARRATOR]
If you're terrified
of the realization
that you must know yourself
in order to know your enemy,
you should run while you can.
But if you choose to accept this
knowledge and stand your ground,
your newfound wisdom is sure
to be rewarded with victory.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode 48:
The Oath in the Tunnel.
Are you willing
to claim victory
from the blood of your
friends, or aren't you?