I thought I told you, Sam.
Melanie Square doesn't tolerate hard drugs.
P-Please wait, Tony. I didn't have a choice!
Ben told me to sell them at all costs.
I don't give a shit about why!
This is my turf... the Stone Family's turf.
I don't show mercy to delinquents.
Even if it's the President or the First Lady!
That's enough.
Ol' Gant...
I'll take him. You don't mind?
Suit yourself.
You're as old-fashioned as ever.
You're probably the only mafia family in LA that doesn't allow hard drugs today.
I just want Melanie Square to be a decent place to play.
We don't need to bend our morales as we have enough methods of making money.
Don't talk big, you inexperienced brat...
you've never lived by the fruit of your own labor.
You said it.
Hardheaded Tony, huh?
Moment
Papa!
Duke! Why're you here?
Sorry for intruding, Tony.
Eva.
We came to the Square to see a movie, so...
Daddy, do you remember?
We're going together to the amusement park the day after tomorrow.
Yeah, of course I remember.
How can I forget if I always look forward to being with you?
Yeah!
Tony, excuse me...
That guy again?
It's about time to settle this.
If he says no, teach him a lesson.
Yes.
Ms. McCunnen, this is Richard Harrington.
I'm hoping to get a favorable response from you today.
We're giving you the best deal we can offer.
I see, it's not a bad deal.
But my response is the same.
Why?
Don't make me repeat myself. Melanie square is our family's turf.
Everyone who lives here...Everyone who works here...They're all my family.
I will never betray them.
You heard him. So go back and tell your boss.
Or do you wanna eat bullets and go back in a body bag?
It seems that you still don't realize the true power of Inferno.
What?!
We'll give you three more days. This is your last chance.
I trust you'll change your mind...Tony Stone.
That asshole! What's with that cocky attitude?!
That bluff was so creepy.
Lutz, Rob. Do a thorough investigation on who's behind Inferno.
It's hard to think that they're just some new organization.
I understand.
Have you prepared?
Anytime.
It doesn't end after you block your opponent's weapon.
Yeah.
That was amazing.
Before you couldn't do anything, but now you can hold your own.
I have a good coach.
There're two missions that I'd like you to carry out. Will you accept?
Two?
I'll explain at my place. Come with me.
Your place?
So this is your house, Ms. McCunnen?
That's right. It's a little big for a single woman with no family.
Lizzie's been assigned to a different case today, too, so...
To get to the point, please tell me what those missions are.
First, I want you to keep me company by being my bodyguard for the night.
What?
I told you, right?...Lizzie isn't here.
Although the security here is perfect,
I want someone to be here even if just as a formality.
Why does a senior member like you have only one guard?
Do I need anyone else?
And, the second mission is...to observe a mother and her child.
Okay, if that's your order.
That's not good.
You're not a doll.
Why they need to be observed...Why is it important...
You need to ask those things. Okay?
You can't get a clear picture about Inferno?!
Ah, yes. We've asked information brokers and others all over the place,
but they all say something different.
One would say the Verrocchio Family is involved,
and another would say the Cervanted Family is.
And, of course, I heard the Bloodies' name as well. What can I say...
What the hell's your problem?!
Lutz, since when did you start letting people sell you a bill of goods?!
I-I'm sorry.
Stop it, Anton.
They did do their job.
What do you mean?
Extending their power in a short time. Doing things in various ways.
The mysterious senior members. And the information Lutz and Rob got...
If we put them all together, we have the answer.
Inferno is a special organization that is connected
to the mafia families of the West Coast.
What?!
That guy's confidence also comes from that.
The only way for us to survive is to kiss up to them.
He knew that.
Boss, then Melanie Square will be...
Hell no!
No matter who we're facing, I won't betray the people of the Square!
Anton, set up a meeting with Inferno immediately.
But give them a condition.
Tell them to bring their boss.
Tony...don't tell me...
I'll negotiate...at least...
The real boss probably won't show considering their organization system.
But that's okay. It'll be enough to pick a fight with them.
But once we do that, they'll certainly retaliate against us.
He's right. Not just the square, but your family will also be in danger!
I'll leave them to you. Protect them with your lives.
I'll teach them that we're too troublesome to swallow.
Then, depending on how they react, the mother and her child will have to be...?
That's right. Even if that's the case...
Can you do it?
Tell me...Don't just take order...
Tell me your answer.
Come on! Hurry up!
Okay!
Thank you.
No problem.
Looks like you got quite used to it.
In order to blend in with a flock of sheep, you have to wear sheepskin.
What were the characteristics of the fifth person from the last that we passed by?
A Caucasian male in his twenties.
He was wearing a Dodger cap and a black shirt.
Based on how he was talking to his cell,
he got separated from his friend and is trying to find where they're supposed to meet up.
Correct.
Even when wearing sheepskin, a wolf shouldn't forget his sense of smell.
That's also something you taught me.
Hey, hold on.
Okay, I see. Buy it for him.
Well then, Duke. See you later.
Okay, Papa.
Tony, be very careful.
Anton said that everything is ready.
Let's go.
What're you hardheaded guys doing all dressed up like that?
Old man Gant... It has nothing to with you, now does it?
Listen. Don't do anything that would hurt the citizens, okay?
If you do...
I know.
Your residence is thoroughly guarded by Abel and Bark.
That place is the safest place in LA tonight.
What about Inferno?
They'll be here soon.
So it's okay to have you handle it, Ms. McCunnen?
Yes. We have to think about the future, too. So I'll be the rep.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
My feelings are a bit mixed though, being the one in charge of this district.
We'd like to make Melanie Square ours without turning it into a battlefield.
I'm counting on you, Ms. McCunnen,
Please don't worry. With our two trump cards,
we'll win most of the games.
Rob just contacted me and said that the meeting is about to start.
I see.
Please don't worry. So far, things have been quiet around here.
So long as nothing happens tonight, the game is ours.
Yeah...
I didn't expect such a pretty woman to be a senior member of Inferno.
Many people are surprised.
I sure hope you aren't just a decoration.
I thought we told you to bring your boss.
I won't say that I'm the number one person in Inferno.
However, I've been given full authority regarding this case.
She's right. Please refrain from speaking rudely to her.
Back off from Melanie Square.
You think we'd just agree to that?
We'll pay the debt later on. That's the code of conduct among the mafia, right?
You won't have to. All we want...
is Melanie Square.
Those at the Square were all driven from other places and forced to live obscurely.
They are inept and the Square is the only place they can call home.
But they're our family.
I won't betray my family. That's against my principles.
Old-fashioned and stubborn. You're just like your nickname, Tony Stone.
Can you say the same even if your real family is in danger?
If you do that, you'll lose everything, too. Is that what you want?
I'll ask you one more time.
Will you give Melanie Square over to Inferno?
No.
You're late, Phantom.
Wh-what the hell?!
Duck! It's a sniper!
Shoot back! Shoot him dead!
We can't! It's too far!
Zwei, get to work.
What?! What about the Boss?! Is he okay?!
The negotiation was broken off. The Boss and Anton are all right,
Okay.
They're crazy...
Inferno!
Mama!
Duke, you haven't gone to bed yet?
You see, that guy I saw at the amusement park is...
What?
Eva! Eva!
Wonderful.
You're...wonderful.
Conflagration
Be an instrument. Be a tool.
All we need to do...is just function.