Good morning, Rachel.
Morning...
I wonder if Mana's awake?
She was up late last night doing student council paperwork,
so let's meet up with her early.
Rikka, you'd be a great wife for Mana!
Do you even know what that means?
Oh?
You, as my wife?
I know, what a hoot!
No, I can see it!
A wife is always by your side,
and you trust her more than anyone!
That's totally you!
I second that!
What are you two on about?
So, today,
our class will be welcoming a new student.
A transfer?
Boy or girl?
My heart's pounding!
Who could it be?
I'm sure you kids know her well.
Come on in.
Huuuuuh?!
Makopi?!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
The Transfer Student's
A Super Famous Idol!!
Makopi's here, in the flesh!
Didn't see that coming!
And get this, she sits next to me!
I never thought you'd transfer here!
But why the sudden move?
If I want to find my queen,
I need to learn more about this world.
But she really just wants to be around you all.
Davi!
Oh, my heart!
I'm so happy you wanted to be with us!
Welcome to Oogai First Middle School.
Does the student council know Makopi?
How long were they looking?
Everyone's staring at us!
Idols have it rough.
She looked at us!
She smiled!
So cute!
Well, she is an idol...
Not allowed go a whole day without smiling, huh?
You're the only ones who can make her smile.
I humbly ask that you take good care of Makoto.
I'll be fine.
I came to learn about this school of yours.
Class, don't forget to write your names on the test!
Names, huh?
Test
Name
Makopi!
Don't autograph it, just write it! Normally!
Huh?
Like this?
Wait, Makopi!
Huh?
Hey, Makopi!
Makopi's got a mop...
She's even cute while cleaning!
It's like a mic! I hope she sings!
Makopi, stand back!
Cutest cleaning accident ever!
That was cute?
I'm sorry. I'll clean it right away.
Huh?
When I did this in the Trump Kingdom,
someone would be called to clean it up...
Well, I already did it, so don't worry.
Good job, Rikka.
Makopi might need some time to get used to school,
so let's stay with her.
Sure.
Makoto, excellent work!
Excellent work!
Do you know them?
Those are Makoto's cheerleaders!
They're all polite, upstanding people!
I want an autograph!
You bozos!
This is Makoto's private life!
No autographs!
Right! Understood!
Now, we'll recite all 130 articles of our constitution!
Number one!
Protect Makopi's private life!
Number two!
They really are polite.
Never steal the spotlight!
Did they say 130?
Number three!
Never betray your comrades!
Hey, there's Makopi!
She really did transfer here!
Entertainment reporters.
Look over here!
Smile a bit!
Go on without me.
Huh?
I don't want to burden you two.
What? But we were just about to go home together...
I'll get their attention.
Rikka?
You two can escape while I distract them.
You've all clearly taken quite a few pictures,
but do you have the school's permission?
Well...
Having its students and uniforms photographed
is bad publicity for a school.
And above all,
when Kenzaki dons her uniform,
she is not an idol, but a student!
Now begone!
You heard the lady!
Stay outta Makopi's private life!
Now's your chance!
Let's go, Makopi!
Hey, Makopi!
Hey, listen to me!
We're fine here.
Yes, thanks.
But that was some quick thinking on Rikka's part!
Yeah, I always count on her!
She sounds pretty reliable.
Yeah, Rikka's reliable,
but she's more than that. She's my BFF!
Makopi?
Makoto's totally jealous!
Davi!
You're cute when you're honest!
Yeah, it makes my heart throb!
Good afternoon, Rikka.
Alice.
So, Makoto transferred into your school.
You already knew?
Yes, but I worry.
This is Makoto's first time attending school,
so she may get lost...
That's what you're worried about?
But it's rather nice.
Now we'll always be together.
Yeah.
Mana was happy about Makopi's transfer, too.
Shall we visit Mana's home?
Sure!
I want to know what happened after they left.
Oh, Rikka, Alice!
Huh? Makopi?
Good afternoon.
Guess what? Makopi has a day off today!
Now she can stay over here tonight!
My, what fun.
I know, right?
You two should stay over, too!
Well, my mom's coming home today...
What?
I'll certainly do so next time.
Aww...
I was hoping we'd get to eat dinner and do homework together like we always do.
But when we stay over, Rikka alway helps you with everything.
The way I see it, Rikka babysits you more than anything!
Sorry about that.
Don't worry.
So, next time, okay?
Huh?
Makopi's asleep.
She was up late working, so she must have been tired.
And she was still the center of attention at school.
I'll let her sleep until dinner.
Well, goodbye.
Rikka, we simply must stay over next time.
I'm certain Mana awaits it as well.
Yeah, you're right.
Rikka looked kinda down today.
Girls have moments like that.
Moments like what?
Moments when their hearts ache.
It's quite complicated.
Thanks for dinner.
I'm so happy!
About what, Mom?
I was just thinking about how blessed I am.
I can work as hard as I need to as a doctor,
and still come home to eat dinner and listen to my cute daughter.
Life's perfect!
So?
How was your day, Rikka?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Well, I guess our class got a transfer student today...
and now she's staying over at Mana's house...
Quite the day.
When you say nothing happened, I know something did.
So you knew...
Well, I am your mother.
Rikka, you can't sleep?
I keep wondering what Mana and Makopi are doing...
Knowing Mana,
they're probably up late chatting...
What is this feeling?
Dangit!
Stupid ball doesn't do what I tell it to!
Can't you just hit those stupid pins for once?!
Must you always act like a child?
Huh?!
It's essential that he does.
He wants everything to go his way.
That's a fundamental emotion.
Selfish as ever, I see.
Guess that's why you'll always be a big baby.
Cool bandages, pops.
Five more...
Oh no!
Mom, I've gotta go!
Would you like breakfast?
Sorry, no time!
I've gotta see Mana!
Oh, Mana called earlier.
She said she already left with a girl named Makoto...
Why?
Did something happen?
There they are!
Mana and Makopi!
They came to see Ai.
Makopi, feed her.
You think I can?
Yeah, totally!
Here's your milky, Ai.
Oh, good job!
Look, Ai!
It's your mommy, Mana, and your daddy, Makopi!
You really are like a mommy and daddy!
Mommy and daddy?
They're like newlyweds.
Alice!
Good morning.
I was simply strolling by,
but they seem happy.
Both Mana and Makoto.
Yeah.
Shall we join in?
Sure...
Huh?
What's this feeling?
My heart is aching...
I've felt strange since yesterday...
I'm so jealous!
I'm super jealous!
Who might that be?
The head of Makopi's cheerleaders.
Deep down,
I want to be that close to Makopi!
No, I can't!
This is Makopi's private life!
This is what I swore to uphold!
I-I apologize!
Is he okay?
Maybe, but I'm worried.
I can't!
It'd be impure for me alone to be close to her!
Number one!
Protect Makopi's private life!
Number two!
Never steal the spotlight!
Number three!
Never betray your comrades!
Aw, just get close to her.
Who's there?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Seeeelfiiiish!
L-O-V-E Lovely Makopi!
It's a Selfish!
The cheerleader!
A dark heartbeat!
It's over there!
Makopi is mine!
I won't let anyone else have her!
Is he red with jealousy?
I feel the same.
I'm jealous of how well Mana and Makopi get along.
So jealous...
But that's only natural.
You want to stay by a dear friend's side,
and be closer to her than anyone.
Everyone feels that way.
Even I do.
Even you do,
and even the cheerleader does.
Really?
It's true.
But I cannot permit one to abuse those feelings to create a Selfish.
Makopi is mine!
I only have eyes for her!
I see...
So that's it.
Let's go, Rachel!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
Stop!
I won't let you use that cheerleader any more!
Rachel!
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
I can't move!
Is your love that weak?
Melt the ice with the heat of your love!
L-O-V-E!
I love Makopi!
The ice!
Makopi!
Alice!
Are you okay?
There's trouble!
It's the head of Makoto's cheerleaders!
Love Makopi!
Let's go, everyone!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Everyone!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor cheerleader who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
I love Makopi!
I'm happy you feel that way,
but there's no joy in seeing you used like this!
Who are you?
You won't get between Makopi and I!
L-E-T-S Let's Go Makopi!
Davi!
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Love!
Lance!
Rigid Rosetta Wall!
Rachel!
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
Now's your chance, Cure Heart!
I've got it!
Charles!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
Love love looove!
Huh?
Talk about head over heels!
You and Heart really do work well together.
I'm jealous of you two.
I can feel how strongly you trust each other.
As a latecomer,
I never knew if I could be as close as you are.
But I want to be BFFs with you all!
Sword...
I feel the same way.
I want to be better friends with you all.
A friend from the heart.
Rosetta...
We all feel the same way...
Everyone felt the same heartache!
What're you talking about?
We're already friends, you know!
But I know how you feel.
Yeah!
Hey, wanna stay over this weekend?
A sleepover sounds wonderful!
I approve!
We could eat together and do homework!
Makoto's looking forward to it the most!
Davi!
I keep telling you to stop blurting out how I really feel before I can!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
That's strange.
There's a big game coming up,
but Mana isn't going!
She's the softball club's helper,
and given Mana's overwhelming sense of responsibility, it's unlike her to stand someone up!
Something has to have happened!
I'm sorry, everyone,
but there's something I have to do!
I'm coming to save you!
Just wait, Ai!
Dokidoki Precure:
Awaken!
The Precure's Newest Power!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!