Tora Dora! Episode 5 English Translation by KloneDesu
() Are notes/information for the timer/editor.
Today's the last day of the long vacation.
How's everyone enjoying their time?
I'm so bored that I might die.
Sheesh! It's because that mutt's so useless.
You know it wasn't my fault that you couldn't see Kitamura.
He said that he's going to be busy during the break with his softball and student council activities.
Isn't it a dog's job to do something about that?
Even if you see him, it's not like you can even have a normal conversation with him.
I'm going to drop you into hell!
It spilled on me!
What the hell are you doing?
Hurry! Get something to wipe it.
Sheesh...
It's because you were saying something ridiculous.
It's so noisy...
Oh, we woke her up.
Here, just wipe it with this for now.
You guys were going to eat omelet rice together while I was asleep?!
I have yours wrapped up and in the fridge.
You didn't forget to right my name right?
"Ya-su-ko" with the ketchup.
I'll write it, so stop crying.
"Sniffle"
Alright...
I'm gonna sleep a bit more.
Ugh. What should I do?
It's gonna stain.
If you deal with it properly, it'll come off.
I'll get it off for you, so in return—
Jonny's again?
Oh come on! Please!
I just can't go alone!
You should be helping with things between me and Kushieda, at least a little.
Oh, you are so annoying. I'm going to throw up!
Huh?! Throw up what?
They said... Kushieda's off...
The "laboring" girl has to take some days off too.
It was probably punishment for trying to be the only one that's happy.
Unlike you, whose already said you liked or has already been told—
My eyes! My eyes!
Stop saying embarrassing things, you dog in heat.
What do you think you're doing?!
This is so cute!
Let me see.
But for you to wear it, the heels have to be—
What I want is this purse! The purse!
Welcome.
Yeah, yeah. I'm short and stumpy anyways.
But I've never burdened someone else because of th—at.
What's wrong?
Ryuuji, this!
The purse right?
That's not what I'm talking about.
The model person!
Model?
See, that person!
It's this person right?
You're right.
Her name's Kawashima Ami.
She's the daughter of that actress, Kawashima Anna.
Why would someone like that be in a place like this?
Sorry, Ami. I made you wait.
Wha—?!
Ki-Ki-Ki-Kita-Kitamu!
Oh! If it isn't Takasu and Aisaka!
How unexpected!
Wh-Why?!
H-Hey! Come here a second!
Hey, even if you say that—
What are you two quarreling about?
You two sure do get along.
N-N—
That's not it!
What's wrong Yuusaku?
Oh, I was just thinking about introducing you.
Yuusaku?
She's Kawashima Ami.
She lived in my neighborhood a long time ago.
I suppose she's what you'd call a childhood friend.
And these two are Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga.
Childhood friend?
H-Hello.
Nice to meet you!
That's...
Oh, we were just looking at this... and we—
Oh no.
I've let you see something embarrassing.
I should have worn better clothes and put my make-up on properly.
I just let my guard down when I don't have work.
Oh no— Um— Th-There's nothing wrong at all.
Why don't the four of us talk together since we have this opportunity?
Huh?
Wha—?
You don't mind, do you Ami?
Of course not.
This restaurant is so nostalgic!
We used to come here a lot didn't we?
Yup, yup, with our whole family!
Here Takasu-kun, have some too.
Would you have preferred the diet-sugar?
N-No.
Oh, so you like your coffee black?
Sheesh, you're so hasty.
I'm so sorry!
When I saw Yuusaku putting it in, I just…
I-It's okay.
I did it again.
Everyone always says, I'm such a klutz and an airhead.
I'm so sorry.
No. It's not a problem at all!
I like sweet stuff anyway.
Thank you! You're so kind.
Oh my. What am I doing?
Oh, so-sorry.
No, why are you apologizing Takasu-kun?
Well, that's—
I suppose I'll go to the restroom for a bit.
Wha—hey...
I'm going to the restroom too.
I give up. I can't keep it going.
You left your seat, just as expected.
I-I thought you were going to the restroom?!
Wh-What is it?
I want you to answer this frankly.
What do you think of Ami, Takasu?
What do I think?
You suddenly brought such cute girl over so I got nervous and I was totally out of it.
I'll admit that she's cute.
Plus she seems like a really nice girl!
She seems a bit air headed but—
She's what you'd call pure or...
Well, just watch for a bit.
Ah man. I'm tired.
TL Note: Kawashima is talking in a more crude way compared to before.
Hey, my ice tea's all gone.
Go get me some more.
You're just gonna ignore me, huh?
Anyway, I think you have kind of a bad attitude.
I got it! I'll have your boyfriend bring it over.
He seemed like someone that would listen to anything I say.
Is it okay if I take him from you?
Not like I want him even one bit.
He's not my boyfriend.
Okay, whatever.
Not that I really care.
Indeed. That's Ami's true self.
She's childish, selfish and tyrannical.
A stereo-typical princess type.
I can only think that a demon's possessing her.
Well, in a nowhere town like this, I guess the only guy you can get is one at that level.
Hey-hey. How tall are you?
I just noticed, but isn't there something wrong with you?
Oh man! I didn't even know they sold clothes that are that small!
Anyway, what do you do when you want to buy—
I can't believe Taiga is able to just—
There was a mosquito. A mosquito.
Oh, it was a fly.
Hey you—!
Come on now Ami. It's time to go home.
Alright, alright.
Sorry Aisaka, I'll have to go for today.
Seconds!
There isn't anymore left.
You just ate two and half bowls.
Hmph... It's all her fault.
That wicked woman... Just thinking about her makes me hungry.
Don't you mean angry?
But Kitamura was pretty troubled.
Wh-What should I do?
I wonder if Kitamura-kun hates me after I did such a thing!
Well, I don't think that would be a problem.
Kitamura had all the details—
I don't like... that woman...
Don't cry...
What about you?!
You were drooling all over her!
I didn't really—
There's something wrong with someone that can just call themselves an air-head anyway!
Oh well. It's not like we'll ever see her again.
I'll be an adult and just swallow down this hatred!
Hey! That's mine!
Shut up!
I just transferred to this school today.
My name is Kawashima Ami.
Please call me Ami.
Could it be?!
The girl that's modeling for Lan Vi?
Oh my god! She's so cute!
An angel has fallen down!
Thank you god!
Everyone, please be kind to our new friend.
Um... Well, first we have to decide on your seat.
I'm a winner!
I'm so glad that I was in this class!
It's kind of embarrassing to stand out this way.
Why? It looks good on you!
Yeah, you're very stylish.
What?! I really hope I can hurry and get the same jersey as everyone else!
Ami-chan certainly is cute and extraordinarily stylish, but...
The "High-Speed Kushieda Cute-Girl Radar" isn't giving a signal.
Minorin?
Are you okay Ami-chan?!
Oh jeez! Why do I trip when there's nothing even here?
It's so uncool.
I guess you're quite a klutz Ami-chan.
You might be a little air-headed too!
No, that's not it at all!
But sometimes people say that I'm an airhead...
I thought so!
It's not true at all though!
Okay, okay. We get it.
Sheesh! I really mean it.
That's amazing.
Yeah. She has the ability to completely grasp public attention.
Why didn't you say that she's transferring over to our school?
If I did have, she wouldn't have showed her true self.
That's no good.
What's that supposed to mean.
To be honest, I don't mind Ami's true self.
That's why I want everyone else to learn her true self and like that part about her.
No... I don't think that would—
And if she gets hated after that, Ami would be able to acknowledge it.
I don't want her to have to lie anymore.
Me first!
I didn't know that a vending machine was in such a place.
Why did you—?
Because, the fourth block is about to start soon but you left the classroom.
I was curious so I followed you.
No, I shouldn't... in truth she's...
It's against the rules to buy drinks at anytime other than lunch break.
Then...
...I suppose we're accomplices.
I'll pay for it.
That's okay.
That's to make amends for yesterday.
A-Amends?
Sheesh. I was really surprised.
I didn't know you were from the same school Takasu-kun.
Aisaka-san too...
Yuusaku didn't say anything about it.
Did you hear anything about yesterday form Aisaka-san?
About yesterday?
Everything about yesterday was my fault.
I think the air headed part of me annoyed Aisaka-san.
I was just talking to her normally and she suddenly said I was conceited and cocky.
But I—
It's not Aisaka-san's fault!
If I was more of a proper girl…
That wouldn't have happened.
It just happens sometimes.
Girls just don't like me sometimes.
That's why I'm not bothered by it and I can still go on.
I see.
That's why I don't want you to tell anyone about yesterday.
I—
I get what you want to say Kawashima.
So let's go back for now.
Thank you!
Let's hurry!
This here means that the sun had risen high above and—
Why?
Sheesh.
Takasu-kun. I'm mad at you!
It seems there's something suspicious going on between you and transfer student-chan!
Is it an affair? Are you cheating on her?!
If you throw away Taiga— I'll punish you~!
D-Damn it!
Why do I have to go through this?!
From Takasu to Kushieda.
Sorry for talking about something unrelated, but what do you think of someone that calls themselves an air head?
Alright. Is there anything you guys haven't understood so far?
What's wrong you guys?
Hey Takasu, Haruta said that he'll introduce us to three first-year girls.
You'll definitely be going right?
Even if I go, I'll just scare them.
Of course not!
We're just trying to get three people to match the other three anyway.
Plus...
Palm-top tiger...
That's how it is.
What on earth would you have to do to get this?
It wasn't on purpose!
I fell, it couldn't be helped!
I'll go get a rag.
You can go home first.
That's okay. I'll wait in the classroom.
Ryu—
Eww. Why are you here?
You are like such an eyesore.
Stay away from me you brat.
You're so scary~!
As expected from the Aisaka-san that even teachers fear.
I went to the faculty room earlier and all they're saying is how cute I am.
They said that they're worried that you might pick on me.
They must really hate you.
I'll have quite a fun time—
seeing how long your two-faced personality can last.
It's easy for me to reveal your true self to everyone.
But that would be boring right?
I'll just keep watching you.
Even when the class changes, even after we graduate.
Like a stalker.
You are such an annoying squirt.
That's probably why you have no friends.
Oh wait. You do have one... Takasu Ryuuji.
Even though he has that delinquent look, he's totally into me.
What a creep!
But I guess now you're really all alone.
I really feel sorry for you.
Even that Yuusaku with that monk philosophy hates you.
What did you just say?
I told him everything you did to me at that family restaurant.
He probably hates you a lot now.
It's totally over for you.
Kawashima?
Come on. Move it.
Wow, pork-cutlets made by Ryu-chan.
Sheesh.
It tastes the best when it's just been fried.
If you're worried—
Go pick her up.
Aww, it went dumb.
Taiga, I'm coming in.
What's going on?
I knew you were here.
You didn't even turn the lights on.
Hey Tai—
What do you want?
What? It's time—to eat!
Ta-Taiga?
Are you okay?!
Kitamura-kun... thinks I'm...
He hates me...
That woman said she told him everything...
I... I...
It's okay.
What's okay?
Kitamura already knows everything.
Kawashima's personality—
why that happened at the family restaurant—
her lies—
All of it.
Really?
Really.
Not to mention, Kitamura isn't the type of person who would hate someone for such a thing.
You should know that the most.
Then why am I so small?
Huh?
Why do I have a weird name?
Wha—?
Well, that's—
Why is it?!
Just because she's 165 cm tall!
Just because she has a bishoujo name!
TL Note: Bishoujo is a Japanese term used to refer to young and pretty girls.
Just because she's Kitamura's childhood friend?
Sorry. Are you alright?
Sheesh, you're worried about such trivial—
Unlike you, I'm DELICATE!
You—
Ryuu-chan!
Even though it's pork-culets there's no sauce!
What should I do?!
Pork-cutlets?
Sauce!
It's a black pig too.
What about pudding?
We're only here for sauce!
Huh?
Hey, we're going home.
Yasuko's gonna be late.
Ryuuji, look at this.
This is…
That means they're taking a vacation right?
Is our school worth enough to want to take your job off and come?
Isn't that—
That woman...
So it is Kawashima Ami, right?
Why is she dressed like that?
And her bags, they're full of sweets.
Is she going to have a party at home?
No, that's not it.
That's...
Oh? I just saw something that's interesting.
Oh my god! You are so annoying.
If you keep following me around so persistently...
Ami-chan will just have to give you a stab.
You effeminate stupid Chihuahua!