Kaleido Star is about to begin.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Yes, Miss!
Well now! Cathy here!
Are you burning with youth, everybody?!
Let yourself go and get more
revved up, push yourself higher!
Everybody here is running
head-on at his or her own dream!
This Kaleido Stage is looking pretty good!
All right! I've started to get revved up!
I'm gonna stick with you all like crazy,
with this stage you've tried to protect!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
I've changed my mind.
We'll start the special training again.
Yes, sir!
Hurry up and get on your feet.
You're wasting time.
Right...
She's got so many weights on...
She's been at it nonstop
since early this morning.
Want to take a break?
No.
Sora...
Why does she have to keep
going until she collapses like that?
I can... keep going...
"Our Amazing Futures."
Simon Park accepted the
job of writing the press copy.
Mmm-hmm.
Now, about Layla...
I have no intention of stopping Layla.
You're a real piece of work.
For the Angel's Maneuver
you need innate instinct.
Even Layla may not be able
to bring it off just by trying hard.
And people are sure to pass judgment
on someone who leaves the stage and
then comes back to make a second attempt.
She made a brilliant exit,
but this could sully it.
Do you mean to make her give up on this?
If I can.
But if I can't...
I'll just have to sully my own
reputation along with her, that's all.
What do you think?
During the actual performance, I plan to use
lasers in those places where I've put film here.
Um, I think it's pretty good,
but something's missing...
Just say flat-out that it's no good.
Oh, no, I wouldn't call it "no good"...
So you're saying it's good?
No...
So it's no good then, is it?
Yes, ma'am.
I see.
I'm sorry.
There's no need for you to apologize, Mia.
No, Mia's the one at fault here.
Yes, I know.
It's my fault, because I haven't completely
worked out how we'll stage the climax.
What are you going to do?
At this rate we can't even build the set.
I'll just have to give it my best.
All right! Well said! Give it your best then!
Go at it like there's no tomorrow!
Go at it until you collapse, like Sora!
Yes! I'll go at it until I collapse, like Sora!
I know you want to move on this right away,
Yes, that's right... At this rate...
but please give Mia a little more time.
I'll just have to give it a try...
Okay, got it.
Thanks.
The seal loved it!
So... was it was a success, then?
It's hard to say.
Odile can't express her love in
any other way but hating Odette...
Then that means if she destroys Odette,
she won't be able to express love anymore.
That's like I was when I couldn't get pumped
up anymore because Sora had left the stage.
Odile is me...
What the prince is to Odile
is what the stage is to me.
Odile can't win the prince's love as
long as she keeps trying to defeat Odette.
The difference between Odette and Odile...
It's that Odile's love is the
most important thing to her,
but on the other hand Odette values
the prince more than she does herself.
Sora values the stage
more than she does herself.
As long as I keep trying
to defeat Sora, I can't win.
Pose number nine.
Right!
The stage more than yourself, huh?
Sora, don't tell me you're...
The training seems to involve
more difficult things every day.
Yes?
Good afternoon.
Oh, please wait one moment.
Miss, it's Mr. Yuri.
Let him in.
Yes, Miss!
I apologize for the wait. I'll be right there.
Thank you for waiting! Please come in.
Miss Layla is in the
practice room in the basement.
Thanks.
Stubborn, aren't you?
If you've got no intention of
becoming my partner, then go home.
I don't get it.
To any outside observer,
you making a comeback on the
Kaleido Stage doesn't look too good.
On the contrary, they could even
get the impression you couldn't let go.
And if you fail you'll be a laughingstock.
I don't care what anyone thinks.
I have to do this. No matter what.
To think you're too wiped
out to even take a bath.
Oh? What's that? Are you
trying to say something?
Do you want me to change your clothes?
Will you... give me... a massage?
How's this? Is this about right?
It's not helping...
Never mind. Thanks though.
For some reason this rankles.
Like this?
Oh, there's a bar at the bottom.
Stand on that.
Okay.
Sora, we're going to start.
R-Right!
It looks like this training
is going to be pretty harsh.
Maintain your pose on the bar,
no matter what happens.
Right!
Rosetta!
What?
I'm thinking of making my move
during the climax a two-person move.
I see.
I've already cleared it with Cathy.
Uh-huh...
What are you doing zoning out?
If you get what I'm saying,
then let's start practicing!
Hey, wait!
Didn't I tell you I wasn't
going to be in the show?
Are you really okay with that?
I'm telling you, I am.
Sora's got no hesitation about this.
I imagine she'll go through with it,
even if it means she'll never
be able to perform onstage again.
When I came to the Kaleido Stage,
Miss Layla wasn't here anymore.
I can't even tell you how
bitterly disappointing that was.
The move that I'm thinking of
right now can't be done by one person.
That's why I'm asking you to do it.
But if you refuse, I'll look for someone else.
What will you do?
If you seriously want to
do this thing, I'll train you.
But...
It'll be hard.
May...
I'll do it. I want to give it a shot!
All right, then.
Her balance has improved, even if only a little.
But she doesn't own the pose
and her facial expression is strained.
She's still not at a level
where she can take this onstage.
Physically, I don't know if
Sora will last out this training...
Okay!
How about a little change of scene?
Huh?
Um, where are we going at this time of night?
You'll find out when we get there!
The seal seemed to like it.
Uh-huh...
That's probably better than nobody liking it.
Look, Mia.
Okay.
Real swans!
Yep. Mother Nature is the best stage director.
It's good for us to sit back
and be her audience sometimes.
Right.
You can't get a firm image of an angel?
An angel who doesn't fight.
An angel who loves even her hating heart...
I thought that suited Sora perfectly, but...
It's too easy and perfect?
Yeah.
Though that probably sounds
funny coming from me, since I wrote it.
You see, I'm the same type as May.
Charging headlong is more my style.
I always made fun of
people who said things like
"Let's all get along and
do this together as friends."
I'd say, "You're just cowards
who're afraid of getting hurt!"
But Sora's different from them, isn't she?
When I tried to make her
battle May, Sora refused.
May said she was just running away,
but those weren't the eyes of
someone who was running away.
Some of our regular players also
say they can't sympathize with Sora
when she says she won't fight.
They say "Come on, battle
May and show her a thing or two."
Although those people
always turn out to be the ones
who don't have the courage to fight themselves.
Well, but that's about 80% of the
people in this world, so it's a lost cause.
Um, okay...
Leon pulled Sora onto the stage, right?
She gave a lively performance,
undaunted when May came after her.
There was something
really thrilling about Sora then.
I didn't sense even a hint of the
weakness of someone who was running.
It's like Sora's battling something, isn't it?
Maybe even inside Sora there's a
fear that the fighting may never stop,
and she's battling that fear.
How beautiful...
I see...
If Sora hadn't made a
stage with no battles her goal,
maybe she couldn't have come
back to the Kaleido Stage when she did.
The force of the waves, the force
of the wind, the force of the boat...
A lot of different forces are mixing together.
It's more complicated
than the trapeze could ever be.
Sense the flow of all of
the different forces at work.
Don't think. Feel with your body.
With my body?
Yes.
If you do that, you'll always be able to
return to your original position after you jump.
Right.
Be careful not to break the pose.
That's Sora for you.
She's already on the right track.
The lengths of the trapezes and the distances
between them are different than at Noir Circus,
so you can't use the same timing you did then.
Right!
You can't let your body relax!
That's happening because
you're not picturing your next move!
Your role is that of a fairy who guides me out
of the dark path of hatred I've wandered down.
What I have to express isn't hatred;
it's Odile trying to defeat her own hatred.
Even if she has to get help from someone
who will guide her with strong power.
May...
And if my guide is that
timid it ain't gonna happen!
We're going to get this
basic stuff over with fast
and move on to the special
training for the Eternal Illusion!
"Eternal Illusion"?
So close...
I see, so my timing was too fast that time.
I'm surprised you got to this level on your own.
It's no good if I'm still thinking about it.
I have to sense it directly with my body.
Try changing the way you
channel your strength each time.
Do it like this is the real thing.
Okay.
Oh, this warms me up! Thanks, Miss Sarah!
I gave Japanese pork miso
soup a try. I'm glad you like it!
It's a shame I'm so tired
that I can't really taste it.
Oh, that's too bad! And I felt
pretty confident about it too!
I tried adding a bunch of fresh cream.
Is it nice? Is it nice?
Maybe it's a good thing I can't really taste it.
Oh, good!
Say, Leon, do you want some too?
No.
Mother Nature... Swans...
The Angel's Maneuver...
Not right.
Ugh, this is too hard!
What if I ran like this?
Do you think the seal would like that?
Okay, the seal doesn't have to like it.
Oh, right!
This is agony.
I've started wanting to run away.
Looks like she's about at her limit.
I wanted to run away when I was
training for the legendary great maneuver too,
because it hurt so bad.
The reason I could give it my all back then
was because Miss Layla led me on.
But Miss Layla gave it her all right
through to the end just on her own power.
Without help from anyone.
What?!
She did it!
Amazing!
Layla really is an amazing performer.
It should get better and better...
Huh?
This show is gonna be amazing!
Be sure to come see it, okay?
I wonder if I could meet the lead, Sora Naegino.
Are you a fan of Sora's?
I suppose so.
Sora's been training at sea for days.
Look.
Wh-What is that maneuver?
Is that the true Angel's Manuever?
It's so pretty...
Amazing...
She's like an angel... no, she is an angel!
I just got an amazing idea.
What should I do?
The only way to beat Sora
is to play the very best Odile.
I'm going to make this show the very best show.
I want to make my dream
come true on this stage.
Everyone's hearts are starting to become one.
Leon, that's the stage of a true star.
Sophie, it looks like I'm finally going
to be able to keep my promise to you.
I'll practice more and more
right up until opening day,
and I'll make the true
Kaleido Star a reality no matter what!
Hold on.
There's another candidate
for the role of Odette.
What?
Tomorrow, we'll be holding an
audition for the role of Odette.
Audition?
Who is this "other candidate"?
May?
What's this about?
Miss Layla!
The contest is on, Sora.
If you don't like it, step down from your role.
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation, I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
Back then, I never dreamed
a day like this would come.
I'm here because of my admiration for you.
Your kindness, and your harshness...
The warmth we felt that day...
I won't forget those things.
Look at how much I've grown!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"A Most Amazing and Inescapable Showdown."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...