Yuriko!
Muroto-kun?!
Hold it!
Oh, no!
Moritani-san!
What's going on?
What happened?
TLC:
Tobikage
Timer:
Floris257
Editor:
Chippo
K-time:
Floris257
Karaoke:
Naruto-kun
Logo : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter:
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC:
Robo731
Floris257
Hritham
Encoder:
Floris257
Stand By Me
Moritani-san, are you hurt?
I'm okay. It's just a little bump.
This is all my fault.
Kotoura-san?
You being arrested, the president being attacked,
Muroto-senpai getting hurt...
It's all... It's all my...
Because I have this power...
Because I have this power that hurts everyone...
No. It's not my psychic ability.
I shouldn't even exist.
What are you talking about?
What exactly do you think you did?
All of this is the criminal's fault!
Even Manabe told you...
That's right, Manabe!
What is he doing at a time like this?
No! Don't call Manabe-kun!
Are you still dwelling on that fight you guys had?
That's not it.
Even while we were fighting, he still...
Kotoura is a klutz.
I hope she doesn't do anything reckless.
It's no use.
When I worry about something happening to her, I can't even eat.
Stupid criminal, just get caught already!
Then Kotoura won't have to do anything dangerous.
He's constantly worrying about me!
Even though I've been so selfish...
Still...
I can't just rely on him in times like these.
Kotoura-san...
I'm sorry, President... Muroto-senpai... Moritani-san...
I'm sorry, Manabe-kun...
For God's sake, why are you always so—
Oh, who is it now?
Crap! It's my parents!
Hello?
Yeah... What? Yeah...
I know that. I'm not a child anymore.
What? Pick up miso and soy sauce on my way home?
Don't call me about running stupid little errands like that right now!
Honestly...
Sorry, Kotoura-san—
Seriously, you all need to stop screwing with me!
That's it. I can't take it anymore.
This is the park I visited with Tsukino-san...
Huh? Kotoura-san?
Huh?
We've been running into each other a lot lately, huh?
Tsukino-san...
What's wrong?
Wait! You're hurt!
Hey, what's wrong?
Checking for new messages...
No new messages available.
Damn it!
How long is this going to drag on for?!
You won't understand no matter what I say, and I hate you for it!
She hates me, she says...
I never thought Kotoura would volunteer to use her own ability.
But that could put her in danger.
What should I have done?
Jeez, who is it at this time of night?
Shut up! Nobody's home now!
Keep it down! What time do you think—
Hi.
Demon!
Sorry it's such a mess, but come on in.
First, we need to take care of that leg.
Oh... Yeah...
Okay, that should do it.
Thank you very much.
No police officer would turn a blind eye to an injured girl crying outside alone at night.
Okay, shall we have some dinner?
Sit tight, and I'll whip something up.
Oh, I should text Moritani-san.
I'm sure she's worried.
I'm at Tsukino-san's apartment. Everything's okay.
And I'm sorry for just taking off.
Send.
Wh-What was that?!
Sorry...
To tell you the truth, I'm a terrible cook...
Um... Shall I make something?
You can cook? Seriously?!
U-Um, just where are you planning on beating me?
This is so nostalgic...
Even though it's only been three years since we graduated from this grade school.
Y-You're going to beat me here?
The attacker assaulted the club president.
What?!
Don't worry. She's okay.
Muroto-senpai protected her, but he didn't suffer any serious injuries either.
Oh... That's a relief...
Wait! What about Kotoura? And are you okay?
Huh? Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
So is Kotoura-san.
You should've told me that first!
But Kotoura-san has disappeared again.
Me getting arrested,
the president being attacked,
and Muroto-senpai getting hurt, she felt responsible for them all.
Damn, she's talking like that again?
How much responsibility does that idiot have to force on herself before she's satisfied?
That's right...
You were the one who told me that she was that kind of person.
She never told me anything.
She kept it all bottled up inside of her.
And now...
Why the hell are you moping around alone?!
Ow! What are you doing?!
That's my line!
Why weren't you by Kotoura-san's side?!
Why did you leave her over a little argument?!
It's true that she can be a lot of trouble.
But that's exactly why you should have just stayed with her, regardless of what happened.
That would have been enough for her!
I'll stay with you.
No matter what happens, I won't leave.
What the hell...
How could I have forgotten something so obvious until now?
Hey, Manabe, can I tell you something?
What?
I love you, Manabe.
Cut it out. This is no time to be joking ar—
I've always, always loved you.
Sorry. I love Kotoura.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
I see.
Aww, I got rejected.
This might sound weird after I confessed to you,
but I love you and Kotoura-san being together.
I love watching you two.
Moritani...
Even when you two were fighting,
instead of seeing it as my chance, I was just worried.
I'm not sure why...
But it bothers me when you two aren't together.
So...
Go after her right now!
Wait, where exactly is Kotoura?
Huh? I don't know!
Why don't you find her yourself?
Wh-What?!
Kotoura!
Moritani.
Wh-What?
When you were bullying Kotoura...
Your mind is so disgusting, it made Kotoura puke.
I shouldn't have said that.
I've felt bad about it ever since.
Why are you bringing that up now?
You've said far worse things since then.
Like that time you called me a bug.
I'm sorry!
Well, enough being mean.
I guess I'll forward Kotoura-san's text to him.
So your family owns a dojo?
Y-Yeah...
Wow! That's so cool!
Manabe Yoshihisa
Huh? Why...
I knew from the start that it...
that it would turn out this way...
Muroto-kun?
Huh, have you been crying?
Shut up!
Good. Looks like you're okay.
Good, nothing! Why did you have to go and...
Sorry. It was my fault.
And not just you...
If anything had gone wrong,
Kotoura-chan and Moritani-san
might have become victims of my selfish quest for revenge, too.
I was scared...
I thought you would never open your eyes again.
I thought you would leave me like my mother did...
Don't do that again!
I never want to see you get hurt because of me again!
My mom said a liar's kid will also be a liar!
Don't come to school again!
Stop it!
You again?!
You're a real pain, you know!
H-Hey, let's go.
Let's go home, Mifune-san.
Please...
Telling me that only makes things harder.
If I was in that situation again,
I'd probably do the same thing.
You've always been like that!
Why do you stay by my side,
even when you end up like this?
Because I'm Mifune Chizuru's daughter?
It's true that I respect Mifune-sensei.
But if I had to choose between you and her, I'd choose you.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm saying you're more important to me than Mifune-sensei.
I won't tell you to forget about your anger, or your revenge.
But I don't want you to sacrifice the time you have now for that.
Now...?
Yeah.
You look so happy when you're with Kotoura-kun and the others.
Like you've forgotten about all the things burdening you.
But... I've always wanted to avenge my mother...
I'm on this boat now.
I'll stay with you until the end.
Even through your selfishness and your lousy bad-guy act.
What do you mean, lousy act?
I'll do whatever it takes to accomplish my goals...
That's the kind of person I am...
Ah, Kotoura-san, please marry me!
I'll have to pass on that...
Aww, too bad.
Well, now that we've finished eating.
Is it true that the criminal knew your club president's name?
Yes...
Do you have any ideas?
All right. I'll talk to Yama-san tomorrow.
You can stay here tonight.
But wouldn't that be an inconvenience for you?
What did I tell you?
No police officer would turn a blind eye to this.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Sorry for the mess.
I rarely have anyone over.
Despite my large stature, I've always been pretty timid.
Growing up, I was often the subject of bullying.
I got so tired of it, I began training, and became really strong...
But that just scared people off, so I remained alone.
Then, the next thing I knew, I was using my physique to forge myself a career as a detective.
She sounds a little like me...
But you're lucky, Kotoura-san.
Even with that power of yours, you've got some great friends.
Okay, I'll take care of the cleaning up.
You just make yourself at home.
Okay, thank you.
She's a little ditzy, but she's not a bad person.
Still... I feel a little bad for her...
Something seems off.
Off?
The area where we encountered the attacker.
The detective had warned us not to go there.
What's so strange about that?
When you're told not to go somewhere, you naturally become compelled to go there.
Well, sorry...
And one other thing.
The criminal knew you,
and knew we would go to that location.
The only person that could be...
The daughter of Mifune Chizuru.
I see... The clairvoyant's daughter...
What did the detective want?
She said the 2nd Street alley is dangerous, so we should stay away.
The text that Moritani-san forwarded to me earlier said Kotoura-chan is at that detective's place...
Yuriko!
Oh, my phone...
Huh? It's gone...
When did it get there?
Darn, I missed.
Tsukino-san...
No... Who are you?
Come on, don't give me that look.
You've been looking for me all this time, haven't you?
You mean, you're...
That's right! I'm the attacker!
Looking at you makes me sick.
That mind reading is a real nuisance.
I'll crush you!
Hey!
You think you can get away?!
Hey, wait up!
I don't know what's going on anymore...
I bet people call you a klutz, huh?
What kind of an idiot tries to escape by going up?!
President! Muroto-senpai! Moritani-san!
Manabe-kun!
Kotoura?!
Did something happen, Manabe-kun?
No, nothing.
More importantly, haven't you found that detective's address yet?!
The police said they won't tell us because it's too dangerous, so Muroto-kun is looking for it now.
Hang tight!
Damn it!
What are you gonna do if we're too late?!
Where are you, Kotoura?!
Why?
Why did you attack those people?
Why would you want to hurt anyone?
To relieve stress.
When you were talking to that woman earlier,
didn't you wonder why she was laughing all the time?
She's always been a spineless coward.
She crammed all her negative thoughts deep inside her heart.
And that's how I came to be.
Jealous of their happiness,
spiteful because they have friends...
She wants to ruin the lives of people who have what she doesn't.
Especially those people who remind her of her most painful days, back when she was a student.
Tsukino-san was that...
So all this time, I've been burning off the stress that she didn't even know she'd built up over all these years.
It was going well until today.
I never thought I'd be backed into a corner by a monster like you.
Oh, did that hurt?
But someone who reads the minds of others can only be described as a monster.
No! Stop it!
That's right.
She envied you, even as she wore a smile on her face.
Guess I can't blame her.
A monster who has everything that she doesn't?
Well, I honestly couldn't care less about her.
I'm just here to have a good time.
But I'd rather not get caught, so...
Bye-bye.
Until recently,
I thought the world would be better off if I'd never been born.
Sometimes I even felt like I should die.
But...
Kotoura!
I don't want to die! I don't want to die!
I want to live! I want to live!
Manabe-kun!
Y-You?!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Kotoura.
Manabe-kun!
Damn you!
Sorry. I promised, didn't I?
That I'd always stay with you.
Manabe-kun...
Oh, to hell with this!
If this is how it's gonna be, then you can both...
Tsukino-san, stop this!
Maybe I am a monster.
But I met people who reached out to me.
So what?!
No one ever did that for her, and no one ever will!
That's what I thought too.
But I was wrong.
I'm sure there are people who'll stay with you.
So don't give up.
Kotoura!
Hey! What are you waiting for?
She's just a kid playing around!
I can hear your voice, Tsukino-san.
It's okay. Even I was able to change.
If you leave it at this, you'll just be a criminal!
I'll keep helping you!
So stop! Stop!
Stop!
Sorry to scare you like that.
Tsukino-san?
Kotoura-san!
Kotoura-chan!
You guys...
You okay?
Yeah, somehow.
Wait, Tsukino-san!
I have to pay for my crimes.
Tsukino-san...
So there you have it.
Let's go. Get in the car.
Yama-san...
When you get out, stop by anytime.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Extra large, right?!
Idiot! You know you're only getting regular!
Kotoura, let's head home.
Come on, hurry!
Yeah!
Everyone gather!
Yes!
We've made it to the last episode,
so let's do the last one together!
One, two...
Kotoura-san will live on in perversion forever!
Nooooo!
Episode 12
The Things I Want to Tell You