I'm done. I'm leaving now.
Huh? O-Okay.
Hibari's Room
Hibari, it's me. Are you awake?
I'm sorry for leaving ahead of you before.
Hibari?
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
Serpentine Academy for Girls
Intruders? That's impossible!
No signs of any disturbance.
But just to be sure...
It's safe.
Oh no... sleeping gas...
The top secret ninja art scroll...
...has been stolen?
Ever since that raid earlier,
our security has been tightened.
The only ones who could sneak into the school building, and then open up the depository,
are those of us who are here, myself included.
There's no way we would do something like that!
I know that, but the fact remains that it was taken.
Th-Then, who took it?
In any case, I have to contact headquarters.
Today, you are all to wait in your rooms.
What should I do if I have to wait in my room? Study, I guess?
What's that?
Yang
Top-secret ninja art scroll.
Huh? What does this mean? Why is it here?
Nicely done. Good job.
I-It's you!
Just as you promised, you were my friend, weren't you?
Your friend?
Please! Let Yagyu go!
All right.
In light of your own adorable bravery, I will spare her for you.
In return, you'll be my friend.
Y-Your friend?
Yes. This will be a token of our friendship.
No way!
You make an adorable puppet.
Give it back!
Now you have betrayed Hanzo Academy—
all ninjas, in fact.
But who cares? They see you as a burden to them.
I'm not like that, though.
I can see your true potential.
P-Potential?
I was aware of it from the moment I first saw you.
The wariness and sharpness of instinct that comes from being weak.
Those are ideal abilities for spying.
There's more to being a ninja than just being strong.
Your potential will be truly appreciated on our side.
A-Are you telling me to switch sides?!
If that's what you feel like.
We'll be expecting you.
Wh-What is this?
What am I thinking?!
Yagyu, something terrible happened!
It's Hibari!
I came to return a book that I had borrowed, and that letter was lying here.
I can't believe Hibari was the culprit.
Don't call her the culprit.
: Hibari
: Everyone
It says she was being controlled by a Serpentine ninja, right?
But how exactly did they do it?
With this?
What is it?
I knew it!
It's a psychic transmitter.
A psychic transmitter:
used to impose the will of a ninja who has undergone specialized training.
It also amplifies the ninja's will, allowing the subject to be controlled with no restraint.
It's a trick that puppeteers often use.
When did she manage to plant it?
"I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
What I have done cannot be forgiven, no matter how much I apologize.
But I swear I will get back the ninja art scroll myself.
Even if it costs me my life."
Hibari...
Yagyu!
Hold it, Yagyu!
Ninja morph!
Asuka!
Right!
Ninja morph!
Yagyu!
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to find Hibari.
Even though we don't know where she went?
Doesn't matter. I'll find her regardless.
That's crazy, Yagyu!
Out of my way!
Theater
Did you see her?
No. She's not at the academy.
Theater
She always gets so reckless when it comes to Hibari.
Move!
She got behind me?!
Calm down, Yagyu!
Let me go!
Leave me alone, would you?!
Yagyu!
There she is.
This is my responsibility.
I knew that Hibari wasn't in her room last night.
You what?
When I heard about the intruder, I remembered that.
But I couldn't bring myself to suspect Hibari.
That's only natural, right?
If I had been in the same position, I wouldn't have either.
Yeah. Nobody realized that Hibari was being controlled.
It's not just that.
I left Hibari behind during our extra training.
If I had stayed with her the whole time, this wouldn't have happened.
It's because of me that Hibari...
You're wrong, Yagyu.
It definitely isn't your fault.
You're not the one to blame.
It's those Serpentine girls who
manipulated Hibari into doing this.
We should all bear the responsibility together.
Yagyu, have you forgotten?
We are all friends.
Friends?
That's right! We're all concerned
.about Hibari. Not just you, Yagyu.
It should be just ahead.
So this is Serpentine Academy.
Who goes there?
U-Um, I'm not...
You little miscreant!
I'll bet you're a Hanzo spy!
Y-You're wrong! Let me see Haruka!
What?
Did you say Miss Haruka?
Miss Haruka...
What is it?
We caught a suspicious looking girl coming to the academy.
Girl?
She says she wants to see you, Miss Haruka.
Oh, that was sooner than I expected.
Please bring her to my room.
But the rules say that when we catch an intruder, we are to first report them to the academy.
And I told you to bring her to me.
B-Begging your pardon! Right away!
Senran Kagura
Welcome.
What a barbaric way of tying you up.
No sex appeal at all.
I'm sorry. It's troubling how many rough girls we have here.
You poor thing. Look how dirty you've gotten.
U-Um...
Don't worry. I was going to take my bath anyway.
Right...
You understood everything I told you, huh? I'm so glad.
I... have no place at Hanzo Academy any longer.
But can someone from Hanzo Academy like me
really transfer to Serpentine Academy?
It's all right. We will do you no wrong.
So just relax and entrust yourself to me.
The Owner's secret orders don't mean anything.
All I wanted was this girl.
I-I'll get the ninja art scroll back, no matter what!
This is our training ground.
With its vast dark ninja resources, Serpentine
.scours Japan for potentially talented students.
We do get a lot of dropouts, though.
Well, we have a rare visitor.
A Hanzo Academy ninja, of all people.
Security's going to need some disciplining.
As of today, she is a student of Serpentine.
I personally scouted her.
There you go again with your bad habits, Haruka.
Are you serious?
Y-Yes, I am! I can't go back to Hanzo Academy, after all.
I see. Well then, from now on, you are our friend.
What's the matter?
You say that, but don't you suspect me?
Suspect you? Of what?
You've been our enemy up until now, so we're accepting you too easily.
That's what you're thinking, right?
The forces of light have always been narrow-minded and discriminatory.
Darkness is much more tolerant than light.
That's the major difference between us.
But if I were to betray you, what would you do?
Well, if someone betrays their friends once,
it doesn't necessarily mean they won't do it again.
Go ahead and try it, if you think you can.
Darkness doesn't turn anyone away.
However, you'll be responsible for your actions.
In any case, if you ignore me, I'll kill you!
I-I won't ignore you!
As long as you don't ignore me,
I'll hang with you like everyone else.
Middle class, I'd say.
You'll do us neither harm nor good.
By the way, do you like sprouts?
Huh?
Sprouts! Sprouts!
Well, I don't dislike them.
Really? In that case, what do you think of the spike in the cost of sprouts lately?
I think it is utterly abhorrent!
Sprouts are supposed to be the food of the common people, but...
That's a relief.
Someone else has come along to talk to her about sprouts.
Well, it's just about time for training. Let's go.
The word "ninja" is written with a "heart" and "blade".
One must always carry a blade within one's heart!
What's wrong?
Nothing, just that there are so many students.
At Hanzo Academy, we only had five students.
We dark ninjas do not have the same consideration for bloodlines that the others do.
For money's sake, or simply to escape the world... there are many reasons why our students enroll.
Homura comes from a family of virtuous ninjas like you.
Normally, she would've been one of your classmates.
Then, why did she become a dark ninja?
I'm sure you're aware of this, but Hanzo Academy, being a school for virtuous ninjas,
requires that one have no prior criminal behavior to be admitted.
Criminal behavior?
I heard she stabbed someone.
She didn't have any other option but to become a dark ninja.
Mirai was supposedly bullied a lot when she was younger.
She became a dark ninja to bully the rest of the world back.
Hikage was raised on the battlefield since she was a child,
which forced her to become a fighting machine.
Yomi, who lost her parents and grew up in a poverty-striken ghetto, hates society as we know it.
Here at Serpentine, the five of us have been recognized for advancing on our own strengths.
We work on a whole different premise than you did.
Yagyu... and everyone else...
Sorry to keep you.
This is our adviser, Ms. Suzune.
I-I'm Hibari.
I find it hard to believe that a student from Hanzo Academy would defect.
It isn't as though this is without precedent.
It's possible that by changing sides,
she can become an even greater ninja.
Right?
I leave her to you then, Haruka.
Understood.
Hibari, was it?
Y-Yes!
The transition to being a dark ninja requires significant resolve.
Resolve to forsake yourself, body and soul.
Body and soul...
Ms. Suzune was once a virtuous ninja.
Huh?
This is top secret.
I'm just telling you this because I want you to know that there are others like you too.
That woman... What is this I'm feeling?
Huh? Did something just...
A transfer student? At a time like this?
On the recommendation of one of the students.
Her abilities as a ninja are appreciable.
However, this student is...
No matter. The administration of the students is your job.
Understood.
Are you upset that I took it upon myself to acquire the scroll without speaking to you first?
It is not that.
As I said before, simply acquiring it means nothing.
It is no more than an act of folly.
Do not get the wrong idea, Suzune.
Who do you think it is that made it possible for you to be here?
Having failed your mission, on the brink of death,
I am the one who took you in and supported you for this long.
I am mindful of that.
You are also the one who used me to get to where you are now, no?
I cannot afford to delay any longer.
The time has come for what lies in this moonlight to be stained with blood.
There seems to be a lot of Serpentine students.
As for staying unnoticed,
it's hard to think it's hidden in the city the way Hanzo Academy is, isn't it?
If that's so, it's either on a desert island or deep in the mountains.
The direction is another question, huh?
It's a ninja facility, so you'll need to take into account chi flow and feng shui.
This is so complicated I can't keep up.
You seem to have calmed down.
I'm sorry.
It's not me you should be apologizing to, right?
If Asuka hadn't located you...
At the time, I was so preoccupied I couldn't hold myself back.
Asuka still managed to avoid my unbridled thrust.
The same thrust that even the
.Serpentine ninjas couldn't avoid.
Asuka's skills are improving dramatically.
Is that what you're saying?
I believe that's the gist of it.
That girl has great potential.
She still hasn't realized it, though.
Latent strength is unconscious strength.
As such, she is a double-edged sword.
If she takes the wrong path...
A double-edged sword, huh?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I remembered something I need to do. Wait here until I return.
Understood.
That's strange, huh?
What is, Katsu?
Usually, he disappears in a burst of smoke.
The sound came from around here.
Who are you?!
Serpentine Academy for Girls, Ninja Instructor Suzune.
Suzune?
Hanzo Academy Ninja School Teacher Kiriya...
I challenge you.
Did you come to show me your swordsmanship...
Rin?!
Seeing your face kinda made me want to test you.
Imagine, exposing me after just one exchange.
That's my master for you.
As though I'd forget my student's swordsmanship.
Ah yes, speaking of students, one of your own is now with Serpentine Academy.
Hibari really did go there?
Right now, we are both in positions of responsibility.
I came here to inform you of that.
Why, Rin? Why did you become a dark ninja?
If you want to know...
Come and find out!
A map of Serpentine Academy?
I'll be expecting you, Mr. Kiriya.
Rin!
When the love you devoted to others vanishes, girl,
your heart will turn to ice
When the wishes you believed in have rotted away, girl,
you will come to know only strife
Once I was deemed innocent,
but now those days are gone forever,
and I wander aimlessly and all alone
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
The fragrant flower                           in your heart
blooms undaunted                               under this sky
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
There is a red flower in your heart
Let it bloom and scatter its petals before it is picked
Next Episode Preview
Haruka, it really annoys me when someone ignores me!
There's a skill that keeps anyone from taking their eyes off of you.
Really?
You wear an ugly mask, carry a torch, and hula dance in the nude.
You'll be the center of attention.
I wish I hadn't asked.
Yin and Yang
Next time, "Yin and Yang."
Come get it as though your life depended on it.