Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
"All things small are beautiful."
So cold...
Hey.
It sure is cold today, Yuzu-chan.
Haruka, did you not check the forecast?
Snow?!
"A Snowy Day, Memories, and an Impact"
We hardly ever get snow around here!
How rare! I wonder if it'll stick!
Probably not, I'm sure it'll stop soon.
I wonder if Yuu-chan's asleep again.
Yuu-chan, it's snowing!
She's awake! That makes two rare events!
Or not! I got her right before she passed out.
West Misato High School
Yuu-chan, it's lunchtime! There's snow too!
Look outside!
poke
You're sleeping your life away! Come back to us!
She bit it!
What's all this yelling about?
You're so childish, Haruka.
Yuu-chan, it's snowing.
I don't care about snow at all!
Oh? How grown-up of you.
Now we can't have gym outside!
I take that back.
I really love snow.
I like it too! It's so magical and romantic.
Isn't it? I knew you'd understand.
That's it!
We should take this chance to eat lunch outside.
Are you crazy, Harupoppo?
Not a chance.
Yeah.
I-I'm in!
Shizuku-chan!
See? Now what?
No, too cold.
Don't wanna!
No.
That only leaves...
glance
Kaede-chan, take a stance!
We're deciding on next year's student council so I'll pass.
Oh yeah, forgot that was today.
No way...
That's three against two. Stay-insiders win.
Exactly!
Fine then, let's just go alone, Shizuku-chan.
R-Right.
You two are nuts.
Hold it, you turncoats.
It may be freezing, but I just love it out here!
Me too.
Are you okay? I don't want you getting sick.
I-I'm fine.
I have a hand warmer here.
Let's share it.
So warm!
Yeah.
W-We can't eat with our hands like this.
T-True.
H-Haruka-chan, I think we might be better off giving up on this.
B-But still...
Let's go inside.
But there's a real possibility that a day like this won't come again in the next two years.
West Misato High School
We might never get to see something like this together again,
so I want to etch it in my memories.
This is seriously a bad idea!
What you just said sounds like
a line Kotone would say.
Huh? What I just said?
Yeah, she's really serious about it.
She said, "These three years will fly by, so enjoy every second you've got."
She told me something like that too.
"If you let this chance slip by, Yuu-chan will never get to be a cheerleader."
I get it now. I think I can see why she cares about it so much.
I almost forgot. Kotone-chan is already engaged.
It's because her days with Shizuku-chan are limited
that she's living with her despite all the opposition.
Wait here.
She ran off.
The only reason Kotone made a fuss about living with me
is because she'll have to go away once we graduate.
But I... I don't want our time together to end.
Even after we graduate and leave this school...
I want to be with her forever...
Shizuku-chan, let's play.
Let's make memories.
And then when we're older, we can
reminisce about all the things we did.
Yeah.
It's freezing!
I told you I didn't wanna!
You'll get used to it.
Why are you talking like I'm a kid? We're all in high school here.
Haha, what a stupidhead!
Yuu-chan!
MAD
Yuzu-chan, there was no reason to throw so hard!
She's the one who called me a stupidhead!
Shizuku-chan and Kotone-chan, gotcha good!
Gosh, Yuu-chan...
You got my scrunchy wet!
I've never heard Shizuku-chan shout before.
Your attacks have no effect.
Let's get this started for real now!
Here I go!
Yuu-chan!
Kotone-chan, you're terrible!
Look who the stupidhead is no—
It's my turn now!
So strong!
Yuzu-chan, get ready!
It's so much fun to play with everyone like this!
It sure is.
Please don't forget about Kaede.
Student Council Office
That is all.
Next year's student council positions have all been filled.
There may only be two grades starting next year, but please do your best.
Sumi-chan, it's up to you from now on.
Got it!
You just leave everything to me!
All right then, thank you all for the past year.
Big Sister
Thank you very much.
President Mitsuki!
Kaede-san, good work this year.
I guess you're not really "President" Mitsuki anymore...
Ex-President Mitsuki.
Just stick with the usual.
Anyway...
I've been wondering for a while now, but are you okay with that kind of stuff?
Well, I understand how hard it can be to come out about something like that,
but I personally wouldn't mind if they just told me.
As for Yuzu... she might be surprised at first,
but I think she'd accept it pretty quickly.
Um, I'm not following you here.
I'm talking about how Haruka and Yuu are going out.
"A Snowy Day, Memories, and an Impact"
The end
West Misato High School
Oh no, I'm getting a bit too "healthy" around here.
I wonder what we'll do in gym class today.
No idea.
Pretty sure I heard that we're jumping rope.
Aw man, I wanted to play volleyball!
Yuu-chan, aren't you cold in those shorts?
Not a bit!
They do say that children need to bear it and grow.
I'm not herring roe!
Herring roe...
Kaede-chan, let's get moving.
Sorry, I'm coming.
Kaede, your skirt!
That was close. I almost got my skirt wrinkled.
Come on, we're running late.
Huh?
Did you actually forget to take it off?
Yeah.
But knowing you, you would have done it intentionally
so that someone could say something clever about it.
Then let's leave it at that.
"Usual Shenanigans in the Gym Storage Room"
What's wrong with you today? You've been out of it since morning.
There's just something on my mind.
Huh? Was Kaede-chan acting weird today?
I didn't realize.
She seemed pretty normal.
Did you notice anything, Kotone?
You've known her since middle school.
Shizuku-chan filled up my whole world.
Wh-What do you mean?
Oh, you.
Shizuku-chan's so cute!
Isn't she?
Stop that, you're messing my hair up.
Yuu-chan, do something.
Shizuku-chan!
It's hard to tell when something's
wrong with Kaede-chan.
She always has a poker face.
I wonder if something's troubling her.
There's always something wrong with her. No normal person walks around with a mouse toy.
I'm sure her troubles are just about who she's going to play pranks on for the day.
It's pointless to think about it.
smack
Oh, my bad. I accidentally tossed my personal spider there.
I'm trying to be concerned for you!
No, pretty sure that was just Shizuku-chan.
Where do they even sell these things? And anyway, don't buy them!
But Haruka, it's just a stuffed toy.
Yuu-chan, don't let it touch you!
Spit it out, quick!
Did it get in her mouth?
Smirk.
I'm going to absolutely trounce her at jump rope.
You need to learn some tolerance, Haruka.
Kaede-chan's just been taking
advantage of my tolerance!
And that's exactly why you'll never lose your SBJK title.
How was that in any way jealousy?
Spiteful Bully Jerk Kid!
Spiteful
Bully
Jerk
Kid
SBJK for short.
Spiteful
Bully
Jerk
Kid
No! Another weird title!
Everyone got their ropes ready?
Yes.
Today is a consecutive-jump group competition.
Last place will be penalized, so do your best.
This sucks.
I'm so bad at this.
I will not lose to Kaede-chan.
Grrr...
Ready, and... start.
Here we go.
One and—
Come on, Haruka!
Four, five...
One more time. One and—
Ah, sorry.
From the top. One and—
Ow!
Don't worry about it. One—
Haruka!
Just jump, Haruka!
I am!
This calls for another SBJK title.
But that wasn't jealous or spiteful!
Seriously Bad at Jumping Kid.
Seriously
Bad at
Jumping
Kid
Seriously
Bad at
Jumping
Kid
Seriously
Bad at
Jumping
Kid
Are you trying to provoke me?
It's so spot on I can't complain.
Harpoppo has a tendency to jump when we first move the rope,
so all she has to do is wait
until it comes around to jump.
I'm sure you can do it this time.
Okay.
Ready? One and...
I did it! I jumped!
Ah, sorry, that was me.
Shizuku-chan, I'll forgive.
Yuu-chan!
998, 999... 1000!
Everybody stop.
Your group was fantastic, Ikeno.
On the other hand, last place needs to clean up.
Sigh...
Puu
It's all because you kept tripping!
I know, I know. I'll clean up by myself, so let me off the hook.
Thanks a bunch, Harupoppo!
Are you sure?
I am! All we did was jump rope today, so it shouldn't take long.
Wow, there're a lot.
O-On second thought...
quiet
I-I was too late...
Yuu-chan.
What's up?
Huh? Nothing at all.
Wanna wait here for Haruka-chan?
Yeah!
Such a bright smile.
She's an open book.
They already finished cleaning up? That was fast.
And... done.
Great, they're all put away.
BANG!
I got locked in!
Wait, don't go!
I'm still in here! Someone, open the door!
My phone... is in my uniform pocket.
Yuu-chan, I got locked inside...
This isn't the first time this has happened.
When we snuck into that unused classroom...
Yuu-chan was with me back then, so I wasn't scared at all.
Yuu-chan!
Haruka's sure taking her time.
Maybe we really should've offered to help.
What're you all doing here?
We've been waiting for you in the classroom.
Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan—
You girls really cleaned up in a jiffy. Thanks for that.
Sensei?
Huh?! Haruka's still not back!
Don't tell me she got locked in the storage room...
S-Sensei, wait!
I'm gonna go check it from outside!
You should try the door inside.
Okay.
Figures her girlfriend would run off first.
Girlfriend?
Oh?
But which one of them is the girlfriend?
Hey, Haruka!
You in there?
I guess she must be somewhere else.
We might've just missed her.
Haruka!
A hand!
So she responded to Yuu's voice.
Looks like she really is trapped in there.
I hope Haruka's not hurt...
What if she got trapped under something?
She seems pretty excited, so I think she's fine.
That's true.
But I'm still worried!
Why don't you go take a look?
Yuzu-chan, let's do this!
I didn't hear her say anything about using me as a human ladder.
Here, I found a real ladder.
Kaede-chan, you're the best!
Haruka!
Yuu-chan!
You okay?
Yuu-chan, I can't get out.
pull!
Thank you!
Haruka, I'm going to fall!
I was thinking of you the entire time I was in here.
And I got in the mood.
But...
Yuzu-chan and Kaede-chan are right below me...
Yeah, that's right.
We shouldn't do this.
M-Maybe just a little.
They don't know what we're doing, right?
Don't you worry.
Is Yuu trying to pull Haruka out?
There's no way.
Ah! Stop, it's dangerous!
Haruka-chan!
That hurt...
Yuu-chan?
I was seriously worried back there.
You're such a klutz.
You sure know how to make a girl worry.
Sorry we left you hanging.
You're not hurt?
I'm totally fine.
Seeing this, I can't really imagine them not going out.
I can't believe you.
Even though President Mitsuki denied it.
What do you mean they're going out?
Well...
Do Mikan-san and the rest know about this?!
It's got to be on purpose at this point.
No, it's not like I asked them directly, but I got the feeling they were.
O-Oh, so it's not like it's official or anything.
Besides, they're both girls. Don't worry me like that.
That's true.
There's nothing to be concerned about.
Haruka-san is a regular girl who just likes being intimate with her friends.
Big Sister
Yeah
Haruka-san always gives her all and supports Yuu whenever she can.
Sorry I made you all worried.
Come to think of it, President Mitsuki was awfully fixated on Haruka.
"Usual Shenanigans in the Gym Storage Room"
The end
Smile!
Rina-chan
Vice President Rina!
G'morning!
Do you have a minute?
Thanks a bunch.
Up next is an announcement from Vice President Sakai Rina.
What a wonderful speech!
Hey Kaede, what's the deal?!
All Vice President Rina did was smi—
Yuzu!
Just let it go.
But, Kaede...
Ah, er, uh...
Never mind.
Extra
Smile! Rina-chan
The End
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
Where did these mikans come from?
Mom bought them for us!
They seem delicious.
They were kind of sour.
But sweeter than a lemon, right?
Speaking of, I became friends with a girl named Yuzu-chan.
Mmphmm?
Onee-chan! Stop hogging all the mikans!
Oh, it's fine.
So, what kind of girl is Mikan-san?
Mikan-chan really loves her yakisoba.
Next time, Trick 10:
"The President is SumiSumi!"
"Sakura-colored Truth"
and "Sakura-colored Truth".
Look forward to it.
Huh?