What kind of job do you think I can do?
Are there any other good places to work?
It appears to be blood...
Jumbo Gyouza
If you eat in 30 minutes
Prize 5,000 Yen!!
Come again soon...!
Oh, Yamaji.
Are you making sure Youko-chan's doors are secure?
Ah, good morning.
How has your back been lately?
Youko-sama!
Morning!
Hayama-san, Futaba-san.
Good morning!
The weather's great again.
Yes, it is.
I heard there's a typhoon coming, though.
What is... this... bad feeling...
A Taste of Maid
Last week's typhoon was pretty bad, huh.
It is delightful to eat outdoors again.
Futaba-san?
You don't eat? What's happened?
How rare.
Futaba-san, you brought your lunch today?
I used up all my lunch allowance for the month...
Oh? For what?
Man, I shouldn't have gotten hooked on them...
Grilled sea urchin.
Sea—
Most people don't get hooked on them.
Aw, I'm broke...
Maybe I should get a job...
B-By "job" you mean a "part-time job"?!
Y-Yeah... usually...
I wonder if there are any nice jobs out there,
like a cake shop, or a bakery, or a boxed lunch shop...
Are you working for money or...
I'll make the most of it.
A part-time job...
I have been thinking of getting one myself.
What kind of job do you think I can do?
Youko-sama... working?
I have brought your menu.
Huh?!
Who do you think you are, ordering me around?
You can get your own coffee refill!
Like a...
...a themed restaurant?
Oh, I know!
Yamaji would know about part-time jobs.
Hm?
He usually comes out on his own...
Saying, "My poor—
Futaba-san?
What's this?
Now Hiring
Let's work together
No experience required!!
Wow, we're super lucky.
This shop opened recently, and I've been wanting to go.
It's a small and cute cake shop.
I can make money and eat all the cake I want.
That's not how it works.
I-I wonder if I can work properly.
You wanted to try working, right?
And I'll be with you, too.
Hello!
They look delicious.
Cakes!
It has been a while since I have even seen them.
Hello!
Excuse me!
What's this?
It appears to be blood...
Don't say anymore!
It leads inside.
Is anyone here?
Let's stop...
It leads behind this door.
What is this?!
A murder?!
Is that...?
Did the hand just move?
Nooooo...!
How careless of me.
I thought to recover by eating some sweets,
so I ate jam made from seasonal fruits,
but ended up falling asleep.
Sleeping?
Your eyes were open, though...
Sonobe, it is you!
Ah, Youko-sama.
Long time no see.
Wait, you know her?
Yes, she used to work for my family.
My name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
A maid?!
I enjoy making sweets—no, it's the only thing I can do.
So when I could not work as a maid,
I took the chance to start over and learn
a new trade, and now I'm able to open this store.
I see now.
I didn't know there were maids in Japan.
So that means this is the cake shop of a former maid?
I believe we haven't been introduced.
They are my friends!
I'm Hayama.
I'm Odagiri Futaba.
Sonobe?
Wh-What's wrong?!
Oh my. That was surprising.
All people associated with Youko-sama give a strong reaction.
Wait, so that was surprise?
Isn't it more reassuring to work at
a place owned by someone you know?
That is true.
Youko-sama? Work at my shop?!
Yes, if it is something I am capable of.
But of course.
I'm counting on you, Miss Youko!
She is counting on me?
...counting on me?
Oh, yes!
Me, too!
Of course!
A school mate of Youko-sama's
would be most amusin—
I mean, dependable.
You should join, too!
No, I...
What?!
Milk
Milk bottle caps?!
What is the meaning of this, Sonobe-san?
Yamaji!
Yamaji-san!
Oh, it's the milkman.
The fresh cream goes in the refrigerator.
You have not answered my question.
Making Youko-sama work?
I'm getting stomach pains just thinking about it.
Yamaji...
I would be worrying, too.
To make matters worse, I've had
to change shifts for other jobs,
and it's been hard finding people to cover me!
Thanks for helping me find this property, Mitsugu.
What? You found this place for her?
Indeed.
I happened to be working at a real-estate agency—
Anyway, please do not make Youko-sama work!
Sonobe is counting on me, though!
No! For you to work at a place owned by a shady character...
Wh-What is the meaning of this, Sonobe-san?
I was just swatting at a fly.
I see.
Oh, there's a fly there, too!
Stop this at once, Sonobe, Yamaji!
Get on your knees, both of youuuu!
Man, that scared me.
I wouldn't want to work there...
I apologize that you had to see that.
Are there any other good places to work?
There might be other places more suited for you...
Oh!
Jumbo Gyouza
If you eat in 30 minutes
Prize 5,000 Yen!!
Stuffed Hut
Jumbo Gyouza
If you eat in 30 minutes
Prize 5,000 Yen!!
Come again soon...!
Ah, that was delicious.
Stuffed Hut
I ate gyouza and got five thousand yen.
That's the best!
Maybe I'll make it through this month.
I thought you could do it, but you did it so easily...
I am jealous.
As for me, there is nothing I am good at.
That's not true.
Yeah, you have things you're good at.
You think so?
What are they?
Huh?
Er, um...
Oh, a themed restaurant!
A tsundere cafe!
What?
Central Shopping Arcade
But for Youko-sama, she wouldn't show her "dere" to strangers, even if it was for work.
A "tsun cafe" for masochists?
One that targets gentler customers.
"Dere"? "Tsun"?
Man, that was delicious...
Stuffed Hut
Come again soon...!
She's at it again.
Oh, Hayama-chan.
Being a glutton on the weekends, too?
I got the prize money again!
Money Envelope
Now, I'll use this to buy something yummy.
You're going to eat more?!
Oh, let's go to the maid's castle.
You mean Sonobe-san's shop.
The cakes she gave us were pretty good.
They were, right?
They were like...
...a taste of maid!
There is no such taste.
Hello!
Welcome!
Oh my, what are you two doing here?
Wh—
Why aren't you wearing a maid outfit?!
That's the first thing you ask?!
Wearing this is just my hobby.
It really is more comfortable working at a friend's place,
and Yamaji is working here with me,
so I decided to take the job.
Yamaji...
Is his stomach okay?
But, it's true that working at a friend's place is more comfortable.
Sonobe-san is still young, but she's
reliable enough to have her own shop.
She's in her teens?
Oh my, she may not look like it, but Sonobe is a proper adult.
I think she is in her early thirties.
Christmas cake?!
Excuse me.
I will be eating my lunch soon, too.
E-Er...
Sonobe-san, are you in your thirties—
I-Is Youko-sama doing okay?
Yes.
It is a small shop with a small
selection, so I am managing.
Also, most of the customers are women.
Okay, I will return now.
Thank you.
Youko-sama is amazing.
She's doing a good job.
For me to hire someone who once hired me.
It's really quite thrilling.
I wonder what the other two think
of me when they see me working.
Well, we should get going...
Please, take your time.
You can stay as I eat lunch.
I also have some sweets fresh from the oven.
Oh, okay.
Yay, I'll have some!
I can eat much more when I'm with two young girls.
Your young essence soaks into me.
Oh, really?
Wh-What to do?
I can't tell if she's joking or being serious...
Oh, you two are here?
Yamaji!
You're working here, too, right?
Where have you been this whole time?
Oh, I only help make the cakes in the morning.
Oh, I see.
I had some free time, so I came
to see how things are going.
Youko-sama, can I be of assistance to you?
Yeah, he does have other part-time jobs.
He came briefly in the morning and
easily finished after a little explanation.
Expected as much, I guess....
He's always been a repulsive man
who finished jobs flawlessly.
But, how nice to be in high school.
You must have fun every day.
I go to school looking forward to lunch.
We do work hard in our studies, too.
I see.
Youko-sama.
It's a little early, but it's okay if you leave now.
I can?
Mitsugu is here, too.
Didn't I say I only work here in the mornings?
Let's go home together then!
Okay!
It gets tiring standing all day.
Talking to customers also takes up energy.
Isn't it hard for you to bow to people?
W-Well, they are customers.
I manage somehow!
Your livelihood depends on it, huh, Miss Youko?
Are you striving to escape living on a bread crust diet?
Bread crusts has nothing do to with this!
They are so cheap and there is so much of them!
Youko-sama...
Please come again!
I'm so hungry.
Just one more class until lunch.
Futaba-saaan!
Hayama-saaan!
Hm? Is someone calling?
This voice...
Hayama-saaan!
It can't be...
Here, over here.
I'm over here.
Do you have a minute?
Wh-Wh-Wh—
What are you doing?!
Did I surprise you?
It doesn't matter.
Th-That uniform...
Oh, this?
I quickly made this after you all left yesterday.
I made it myself, pattern and all.
That really doesn't matter right now!
What are you doing here?!
That's right! You should be wearing a maid outfit!
That's not it!
I wanted see what it's like.
That's it?!
That's not the problem here.
What will you do if you're found out?
It's my heart of service.
You mean fan service?!
Fan service should be with the maid outfit!
Stop talking about that!
Ah, yes.
I had something for Youko-sama.
For Youko-sama?
I made too much food, so I packed
some for Youko-sama to eat.
Oh, lunch?
It might seem like an excuse, but it's true.
No matter the reason, there's nothing
that would explain this situation...
Oh, class is starting.
Sonobe-san, what will you do—
She disappeared!
Y-Yokai...
I won't be able to give Miss Youko
her lunch until lunch time.
Linoleum-floored hallway.
Oh, the fragrance of youth!
My, what a lovely view.
It feels good to be up so high.
It's a view that really stirs up my love for school uniforms.
You use a subject after "if."
After the subject, you use a verb—
Huh?
What's that voice that sounds
like it would come out of a jungle?
A yokai...
C'mon, hurry up and get into pairs!
Start stretching!
C'mon, get a move on!
This is just...
Where did Sonobe-sa— ah.
She's here!
So you're not classmates with Youko-sama.
What?
What are you doing here, Sonobe?
I wanted to eat lunch with you.
Wait, but...
You're not surprised, Youko-sama?
Things just happen when you work with Sonobe.
Youko-sama...
There is plenty, so please have some.
Thank you!
It's potato salad, with a generous amount of mayonnaise.
You know what I like, Sonobe.
I knew it, she was planning on coming here all along.
Thanks, Sonobe.
Youko-sama, it's from your father.
Wow, did you draw this?
Indeed.
I thought it would brighten up
a letter that only had words.
Thanks, Sonobe!
You shouldn't.
You need to have balanced meals.
I don't want to hear that from you.
I eat plenty of bread, rice, meat, and vegetables!
You eat too much.
I don't eat that much.
Youko-sama.
I will take my leave soon.
You're going already?
Hayama-san, Futaba-san, please take care of Youko-sama.
Sonobe...
I've found you, Sonobe-san!
Yamaji!
What are you doing, walking around in that uniform?
Sonobe-san!
Maybe she was just worried about Youko-sama?
Yeah.
She's a little weird, but she seems like a good person.
Sonobe...
Here you go. Here you go.
Today's Recommendations and New Cakes!
Here you go.
Please take one, here.
It's a yummy cake shop.
Yes, here you go.
Sonobe.
Ah, Youko-sama.
What are you doing, first thing in the morning?!
You can have one, too.
That is not what I was talking about.
Hey, now...
Youko-sama, calm down.
You think this is okay?
It's okay.
I'm confident nobody can tell.
Can tell what?
That you're passing out fliers?
That you're not a student here?!
Although I made this myself, I made it carefully.
I am not talking about that right now!
Oh, wait!
So-no-be!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
"This is
Maid Angel
Super Shino!"
I'm so happy
you enjoyed
this!
"This is
Maid Angel
Super Shino!"
I'm so happy
you enjoyed
this!
"This is Maid Angel Super Shino!"
I'm so happy you enjoyed this!
From this week on, I'll be here
to put a smile on your faces!
From
this week on,
I'll be here to
put a smile on
your faces!
From
this week on,
I'll be here to
put a smile on
your faces!
Please
support
meee!
Please
support
meee!
Please support meee!
...You will, right?
...You
will,
right?
...You
will,
right?
Arrogantly
I will fight with what I have!
I will
fight with
what I
have!
I will
fight with
what I
have!
Perish! Unpaid overtime! Illegal uploading!
Perish!
Unpaid
overtime!
Illegal
uploading!
Perish!
Unpaid
overtime!
Illegal
uploading!
What year are you in?
What
year are
you in?
What
year are
you in?
Next time:       Actually,
.             It's My Purpose in Life
2016,
why?
2016, why?
I feel like
someone's
watching
me.