THE SHADOW THAT SNUCK UP TOO CLOSE
Soy
Sauce
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore no na ha saitama
My name is Saitama
kono yo ni habikoru aku o taosu tame
I'm here to defeat the evil
that's infested this world,
shumi de hero o yatteiru mono da
just a guy who's a hero for fun.
mainichi kakasazu hibi tanren
Never miss a day of training
aircon kinshi ha kotaeta ga
and make sure to shut off the A/C
tsui ni te ni ireta kono kobushi
Finally, I've obtained at last
attouteki chikara
overwhelming power!
wasurecha naranu ha gomi dashi hi
Never forget about garbage day
super no tokubaibi
and bargain day at the supermarket
aa, yasui yasui yasui yasui
Ah, savings, savings, savings, savings!
konbu no kouka de kami hero
Come on, kelp, make my hair grow
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
hanashi ga nagai no ha nigate da
I hate listening to long speeches,
nijyu-moji inai ni kanketsu
ni matomete de naoshite koi!
shorten it to 20 words
or less and try again!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
One-Punch March
wanpan ah ondo