THE SHADOW THAT SNUCK UP TOO CLOSE
Could she have checked
my call history without asking?!
Dammit. We've lost the alien's location.
There it is, standing in front of the spacecraft!
This is trouble!
Your mom got a call from someone
saying she was your fiancée!
No, it can't be!
And the alien's been taken out.
She contacted me too!
"Everyone in my way has been eliminated.
I can't wait for our date tomorrow."
I never agreed to any dates!
The woman's more dangerous than the aliens!
Man… Stalkers really are scary.
Soy
Sauce
Come to think of it,
I've been feeling eyes on me lately, too.
I've defeated a lot of bad guys in the past.
Maybe someone's got a grudge against me.
It's no big deal if it's just someone with a grudge.
But, if that grudge or anger
turned into some kind of warped love, like that movie,
would I be able to handle it?
This place is getting pretty messy.
It has been three days since I started
investigating the secret of Master Saitama's power.
I have yet to gain any information,
and time is ticking away…
Is he purposely being cautious
so no one can find out?
I hope I come up with something soon.
As I suspected, he is on guard.
I must hurry.
Investigation, day 4.
He is eating out for the first time.
I see.
Perhaps the secret to his power lies in his food.
Right now, we have specials on steak.
They're all very good!
Uh… I guess… just give me…
whatever's cheapest.
The 150 gram steak?
Uh, no…
This.
So, one side order of French fries…
Oh, that's all.
Looks like it's time for a job again.
Man…
Enjoy.
Seriously? The portion's so small.
This is 300 yen?
And there's only one of the long, soft ones I like.
The rest are all short and crispy.
It sure isn't my day today…
Is that it?
Huh?
The nice long one is…
…gone!
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm…
missing a fry.
Huh?
Yeah, my fries.
The long one…
There was one that was on the longer side,
and while I was in the bathroom…
Uh…
You didn't eat it, did you?
What?
I mean, did anyone eat it?
Would you like me to call the manager?
Oh, no… it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
He makes a special trip to a family restaurant,
and orders only French fries.
No normal person would dream of such behavior.
And in that case…
There is…
a strong possibility that this is a special foodstuff,
and that it holds the key to Master Saitama's power.
Its appearance seems normal.
Could there be a secret ingredient?
No…
No matter how I look at it,
all I see is a regular French fry.
Perhaps there is no secret to his diet?
I will send the data and have it analyzed.
Who the hell ate my fry?
And why did it have to be the only long one?
Wait…
Don't tell me I really do have…
a stalker?
Thieving bastard!
I'm so gonna kick your ass!
I'll hide right here until he comes past.
The area around here is deserted,
so I should be the only one around.
In other words,
if someone shows up at my house,
that person has got to be my stalker,
no, my French fry thief, for sure!
No one's coming.
Master, what are you up to?
He's been in the same position
for two hours now.
Is he engaging in some kind of visualization exercise?
Is the analysis complete?
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll head back now.
Damn!
No one came.
What's going on?
My face…!
I'll make you all dry as dead leaves!
Better be careful.
It's been a bad day,
and I'm in a bad mood.
That head…
I finally meet it again!
Huh?
You don't remember me?
Six months ago, you beat me with a single punch.
I am the wanted B-class criminal,
Men's Esthetician Man!
The shock of being defeated by you
made my luscious skin completely dry out!
Ever since, I've kept to a strict skincare regimen,
all the while searching for you!
So you're—
That's right,
you remember now?
As I wandered about looking for you,
I turned into a much more powerful monster!
So that's what happened.
I knew that if I kept causing random incidents,
you'd turn up again.
Everything adds up now.
It was you.
I doubt you can keep up with this smoother, softer me!
I don't remember you at all.
But it was you, wasn't it?
You're the one who stole my French fry.
You're the stalker!
Main ingredient: potato.
24 kilocalories.
Sugar: 1.8 grams.
Carbohydrates: 4.2 grams.
Sodium: 0.035 grams.
Protein: 0.32 grams.
Damn!
It is just a French fry!
He has a normal diet.
It is no different from an average person's.
I have not discovered a single thing.
Could Master be a cyborg like me?
I am left with only one course of action.
I don't care how many times
you come back to challenge me.
But let me just say this…
Don't you ever go around stealing people's French fries again!
If you're gonna come at me, face me head on.
If I continue being a hero,
this won't be the last time someone's out for revenge against me.
That's just my fate.
Nothing I can do about it.
I just need to change my mindset.
Right! I need to think positively.
I just have to believe there'll be people in this world
who appreciate all the things that I do.
I became a hero three years ago.
I'm not saying I need fans,
but it would be nice if someone noticed what I've been doing…
Oh yeah, there was that guy who wanted to be my apprentice.
Investigation, day 5.
I have prepared myself for the worst.
Master!
You actually showed up.
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore no na ha saitama
My name is Saitama
kono yo ni habikoru aku o taosu tame
I'm here to defeat the evil
that's infested this world,
shumi de hero o yatteiru mono da
just a guy who's a hero for fun.
mainichi kakasazu hibi tanren
Never miss a day of training
aircon kinshi ha kotaeta ga
and make sure to shut off the A/C
tsui ni te ni ireta kono kobushi
Finally, I've obtained at last
attouteki chikara
overwhelming power!
wasurecha naranu ha gomi dashi hi
Never forget about garbage day
super no tokubaibi
and bargain day at the supermarket
aa, yasui yasui yasui yasui
Ah, savings, savings, savings, savings!
konbu no kouka de kami hero
Come on, kelp, make my hair grow
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
hanashi ga nagai no ha nigate da
I hate listening to long speeches,
nijyu-moji inai ni kanketsu
ni matomete de naoshite koi!
shorten it to 20 words
or less and try again!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
One-Punch March
wanpan ah ondo