Welcome to the Velvet Room.
We did well in utilizing your power of the wild card.
Most impressive.
My faith in you was not misplaced, after all.
In due time, I'm certain you'll master the power of your newly formed bond:
The Chariot Arcana.
I wonder how this power will shape your future.
I shall enjoy following your journey in the meantime.
Glaciers of ideas, importing
To my friends, then exporting
To the next, keeping it open
We want no closing
Even without those, our thoughts can be duped
This mind trade no one can stop
An act of thinking is terrible to stop
We just wanna change it up, not drop
And my crew can rock it like uprock
Life is tedious if it ain't flowing
Copy and paste? Constant defaulting?
Put my courage to it
Begin showing off
That's the way we wanna live
Keep going, yeah!
What was so much of transparency
Turned into bright expectation
Instinct tells me to keep going together, going together
It's breathtaking moments in life
Addicted to it, minds craving more and more
I'm believing you and I can do anything
We can change the world
The sky's the limit, we can spread wings
to roadless travel, together we go
Persona!
Go!
Sweet! Moving on!
Chie's on fire, isn't she?
Hey, Satonaka!
I know you're feeling better, but don't overdo it!
Yukiko! Where are you, Yukiko?!
She blew me off!
Satonaka, take it easy!
I'm fine! This is nothing.
Being ignored makes my poor heart ache.
Yukiko!
W-What was that?
It's darker than black!
You mean "pitch black."
Oh, my, my, my!
Yukiko!
No, that's—
What's this? Surprise guests?
Now this is a party!
It's time to jump into our next segment!
It's not scripted!
Hunt for Her Prince Charming
Princess Yukiko's
What's with that?
Was that a title screen?
Y-Yeah...
Who are you?!
Whatever do you mean?
I am Yukiko, and Yukiko is me.
No way!
You're... Where's the real Yukiko?!
Well, I'm off to resume my hunt!
You'd better be waiting with bells on, my dear prince!
Wait!
Dammit!
Outta my way!
So why not?
We just wanna have some good, clean fun.
We'll sing karaoke and go shopping and stuff.
I can't go. I'm too busy.
Well, when are you free?
Hey!
Pestering someone isn't cool!
Sheesh! We just wanted hang out with her!
Forget it.
Come on. Let's go.
Man, I was hoping she'd come.
Satonaka's extra scary today.
Thank you, Chie.
Oh, it was nothing!
I simply cleared the way, Milady.
You what? I think you used the wrong idiom.
That's so you!
What's that supposed to mean? Really, now!
Thank you so much, Chie.
Huh? Isn't that a little random?
Nuh-uh, it's for everything you've done.
You always come to my rescue...
Every time, without fail...
Chie is so kind.
Chie can do anything.
Chie will always be by my side.
Chie will always protect me.
Chie will always save me.
Who's there?
That's...
Seriously?! You're getting a job?
You know how I burn through money when I go out.
Why don't we work together?
Sure! We'll just ditch work if we get sick of it!
Yeah, right!
Oh, and then...
Yeah?
I got a call yesterday.
From who?
It's a secret.
Oh, come on!
Nope!
Don't you worry.
What...
Poor thing...
This is from back then.
So, do you think that was...
Definitely! It was her other self.
I knew it!
I thought something seemed off when I saw her on the Midnight Channel.
Amagi would never say something like "scoring with a hot stud."
"Scoring with a hot stud"? Hey, what's that mean?
Save it for later!
Yukiko, where are you?
You're just like me.
We can't live anywhere but here.
Or so I thought...
Did you forget to lock it?
Yuki, with the way you cared for it, you must be heartbroken.
So we can't?
I was hoping we could go eat together today.
I'm so sorry.
I keep having to turn you down.
Don't sweat it!
It's the busiest season for the inn, right?
It's not your fault!
I'm sorry.
Enough with the apologizing!
It makes me feel like I'm bothering you.
Oh, say, did something happen? You seem kinda down.
It's nothing.
You know, Yukiko, uh...
Yes?
I know you're set to inherit the inn, and that's just how it is,
but don't push yourself too hard.
Let me know if you need any help. I'll come running!
Yukiko?
It's okay. Thanks, Chie.
That's just how it is, huh?
That's when you realized,
"Chie won't free me from this wretched place."
You gave up all hope.
Who... Who's there?
Show yourself!
Wanna see me? See who I am?
Curious who I am?
I am...
...you!
Courage
Reliable
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Basic
Expression
Rough
Knowledge
Average
A
Courage
Reliable
Diligence
Persistent
Understanding
Basic
Expression
Rough
Knowledge
Average
A
Wanna see me? See who I am?
Curious who I am?
I am you!
Yukiko!
Chie!
Oh, my, my!
Three princes came!
There are two Amagis.
Whatever shall I do?
What's with the tense mood in here?
Hey, I want to go somewhere.
Somewhere far away, where no one knows who I am.
Won't my Prince Charming take me away?
Let's go already!
Three princes? Does that include me?
Obviously, I'm the third prince!
Keep dreaming.
Chie...
That's right. You're my prince!
You always lead the way.
Chie, you're a strong and magnificent prince!
Or you were.
I was?
But I'm through with you.
Dear guest, thanks to your newly formed bond, you have awakened to the Chariot Arcana.
Its Personas are characterized by their strength.
Ara Mitama!
Narukami!
Chie fell through on me.
Chie won't take me away.
She won't save me!
Stop it! That's enough!
Have him withdraw.
He's too far away!
Izanagi!
Narukami! Hanamura!
How horrible.
Historic inn? Manager training?
I'm sick of all these things chaining me down!
Dammit!
Grizzly!
Chie!
I never asked to be born here.
Everything's decided for me: From how I live, to where I die.
I've had enough. To hell with it all.
We gotta help her!
Enough!
Ouch! What's this crap?
Dammit! At this rate...
That's not true.
I just want to go somewhere far away.
Anywhere but here...
Someone, please take me away.
I can't leave here on my own.
Stop it. Please stop.
I have no hope if I stay, and no courage to leave.
So I sit on my ass hoping that, someday, my prince will come!
I don't care where we go! Anywhere but here is fine!
Please, don't...
Historical tradition?
Pride of the town?
What a bunch of bullshit!
How dare you?
That's how I really feel.
Isn't that right, "me"?
N-No...
You're not...
Yukiko!
Don't say it!
You're not me!
It's building more and more.
If this keeps up, I'll...
I am a Shadow... The true self...
Yukiko!
Chie!
Dammit, lemme go!
Just hang in there, Yukiko. We can handle everything she throws at us!
Oh, really?
Then I'll make sure to give you plenty to deal with!
Ouch! That burns!
Take it easy, will ya?!
Hot, hot!
Come on, Hanamura!
Go get her, Jiraiya!
It's tough!
Pain in the ass!
Yukiko, I'm on my way!
Chie!
I thought Chie could save me, but...
That's the way it is.
But she can't! Chie isn't my prince!
I've been waiting...
Oh, crap! Satonaka!
...for so...
Come!
...very...
...very long!
Yukiko!
Satonaka may not be your prince,
but so what?!
What was that?
Satonaka came all this way to save Amagi.
Don't you think it's enough that someone truly cares for her?
Narukami...
I...
We can't get near her!
Yukiko...
Chie, run!
I won't run away.
I have to tell you something.
You see, I've always been jealous of you.
Amagi
Yukiko
You had everything that I didn't.
That's why I loved how you depended on me.
Thank you so much, Chie.
I wanted to believe that I had to be there to protect you.
Exactly! I can't do anything on my own!
I'm helpless!
But that's not true!
Yukiko...
Yukiko is truly strong.
You wanna escape?
You can break free of that cage on your own and go anywhere you want!
Yukiko, you can because you're you!
That's not true.
I'm not strong!
Just like back then...
How heartbreaking.
No, I wasn't heartbroken.
I was mortified.
The bird I considered trapped like myself was able to fly away on its own.
I may have forgotten to lock the cage door.
But in the end, the bird mustered its courage and opened the door.
I didn't want to acknowledge that...
I'm not strong!
I'm horrible!
I'm just a coward who wants someone else to set me free!
So what if...
you're horrible?
Chie!
I'm not who you think I am either.
There are a bunch of horrible things about me too.
But even so...
I want to be with you!
You're dear to me!
You're my friend!
Chie...
Stop it!
What was I so afraid of?
There's nothing to fear.
Because I have...
Chie!
Yukiko!
Thank you!
Don't mention it.
No way!
The Shadow's getting weaker!
Let's go, partner!
Yeah, let's do it!
Pyro Jack!
What?! What are you?!
Get away from me, you pest!
H-Hey! Stop it!
Satonaka!
Let her have it!
Beat it!
Chie...
I'm sorry, Yukiko.
I was so focused on myself that I didn't notice your problems,
even though we're friends.
I never saw the real you either.
I was too busy trying to find an easy way out.
That's why I created you.
I'm sorry I didn't acknowledge you before.
"I want to run away."
"I want someone to save me."
You're right. Those feelings are a part of me too.
You're me, aren't you?
Yes...
So that's Amagi's Persona?
Yukiko!
Amagi!
Are you okay?
I'm just a little tired.
You all came to rescue me?
Of course!
Thank you.
So, who threw you in here?
Huh? Who are you?
Rather, what are you?
I'm Teddie!
I'm sorry, but I don't know.
You're the very essence of annoying, so just shut up!
Hmph! Your discrimination's unbearable!
I wanna know who did this too, but let's hurry back home.
Yukiko looks exhausted.
You're right. Let's go.
Wait! You're leaving me here?
Leaving you? What are you talking about?
You live here.
Well, yeah, but...
I'm sorry, Teddie.
I promise to come again,
so be a good boy and wait here until then.
R-Rawr!
Yukiko's so nice!
I have a special present for you!
Huh?
Whoa, Yukiko?!
I see. They're just like what you guys are wearing.
They're great. They even have a nose guard.
Not another word.
That won't protect you. Don't underestimate the Shadows!
Well?
Huh? Uh, well...
I made them in my free time.
Here. Try them on.
I'm actually bear-y good with my paws.
You certainly don't look it.
It's true! Check it out!
Why'd this have to happen?
What am I even looking at?!
It's one of her laughing fits.
And here I thought she only did that in front of me.
Yukiko, that's a bit much...
Oh, boy!
No time to waste
but make you pace
It's okay to remove, copy, and paste
I'm doing my way
You do it your way
Don't just follow your left, find the right way
Stereotypes
Too many hypes,
But I'm the epitome of new types
Having the fear is power to my soul
'Cause I overcome them
That's how I roll
Expose your thoughts
Don't be afraid of making mistakes
Rules prevailing in
That may be your greatest rival
Believe in faith and your heart
Your true soul stop being in the shades
Come on, out in the open sun
Beauty of the child of destiny
Delightful days
are with rich density of love
Thorny path
There's no easy way for real bliss
So I keep on fighting for
Beauty of destiny
Is this the soccer club?
You know how it's been, don'tcha?
I have to find out who did it.
Life's hard for a girl in love.
I totally don't get you!
Please love me.