When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Oh no!
What's the matter?
I forgot to return this DVD to Wataru.
Then I'll go return it.
How long have you been renting it?
Two years.
Or it could be three.
There's not much point in rushing, but it should still be returned.
Why did a potted plant fall?
I think I'm out of luck today.
I really am out of luck.
But it's not like I'm experiencing any misfortune.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Sir doesn't understand the minds of girls.
You jerk.
Heh.
I'm back.
I'm sorry, Hayate! That DVD was actually-
I'm sorry, Wataru-kun's store was closed, so I dropped it in the drop box.
Um, about that...
Welcome.
Hello.
Drats! I was making myself too comfortable and forgot to prep a gag.
What brings you here today?
What else! I heard Nagi isn't showing up to school at all,
so we came to check up on her!
Now that I think about it...
Forget about it.
The tea will go cold otherwise.
It's iced tea.
Since it is still hot out.
You're right.
If it's this hot in September,
I wonder how hot it'll be in October and November.
What the hell?!
But that was good. Keep it up.
That said, it is already autumn, isn't it?
Autumn equals food.
Yes, it is the season when you tend to forget stuff.
Season of fooey.
No good?
You lose the moment you ask!
You've got to have conviction in your words!
Y-Yes.
Come to think of...
Is that a lead-in into a new topic?
Lead-in?
Or are you trying to act dumb, as well?
No, my stole...
Stole?
Yes, it's a new stole of mine,
but I seem to have misplaced it somewhere.
You left it somewhere?
Oh, then I'll go look for it.
It is all right; I do not mind losing it.
It was only ¥50,000,000.
Note: Around $450,000
I'll go look for it right away!
Hayate-sama is such a kind person.
Of course! My Hayate is the kindest
and most reliable man in the world.
If I'm right, Isumi-san was taking a rest in the guest room.
Today was a mess.
The best thing to do on a day like this is sleep.
And look, here's a stole that's perfect for a blanket.
Let me grab it with these claws that tear fabrics apart.
Stop it, Tama! That stole costs ¥50,000,000!
Keep your hands off of Isumi's stole!
You've got guts to try to touch Isumi's stuff when you're a pet!
Seriously!
Wataru-kun? When did he come?
Even I don't get many chances to touch Isumi's belongings.
Her belongings...
Wataru-kun?
What are you doing?
D-Debt-ridden butler!
Since when have you been here?
I've been here all along.
Did you see me just...
Then?
Well, when I...
You mean an adolescent's illness-like act of taking a whiff of the attire of a girl he likes.
It's a normal thing for thirteen year olds to do.
Are you going to tell on me?
Are you going to tell what you just saw to Nagi and Isumi?!
Don't worry.
Butlers of the Sanzenins won't do anything to embarrass our guests.
But the Sanzenins' pet will do things to embarrass guests.
Damn you, tiger!
Tama!
I thought you weren't going to speak in front of others since it destroys other people's dreams?
What I don't want to destroy are the dreams of girls.
I'd rather destroy the dreams of boys!
This anime is targeted towards boys, mind you.
Therefore I'll report his actions to everyone with a dying message equal to that of Co**an's.
Wait, if Isumi finds out!
I never knew Wataru-kun was like that.
How filthy.
He's lower than bugs.
Please don't worry and leave the rest to me.
Th-Thanks, and sorry, debt-ridden butler.
I leave the rest to you.
Yes.
By the way, why are you here, Wataru-kun?
Oh, that's because that idiot returned the DVD I gave her.
So I came to give it back to her.
Oh, that's good.
Off I go now!
All right, first, I'll spread the rumor over the internet and make it so that the Lady will notice it.
I've started so many other rumors before.
It's fine! I can do this!
I'll use I.T. to keep my ranking high!
Tama. That's enough out of you making our guests uncomfortable.
Otherwise, even if you are Milady's pet, I won't forgive you.
Y-
Yes, Sir!!!
Tama's reflecting upon his actions.
But still, I don't know how I can face Isumi, so you give it to her.
Okay.
And ah...
Thank you for saving me.
It's my pleasure to be of aid.
Excuse me now.
Ayasaki Hayate.
I hope I can become a man like him.
Wataru-chan stares at Hayate's back.
Here's your stole, Isumi-san.
Glad you got it back, eh, Isumi?
Yes, thank you, Hayate-sama.
Oh, where's Sakuya-san?
She went home.
Saying that there isn't anyone to nail a jab on.
Then I'll make my way home, as well.
Please be careful on your way home.
Hayate-sama, you look happy.
Yes. A certain person said "thank you" to me.
My!
Things haven't been going too well recently.
I got run over by a truck this morning.
People glared at me, too.
So I was a little depressed.
But looks like I was just thinking too much.
It's nothing new for me to experience misery,
so it must have been just coincidence.
Hayate-sama.
Yes?
I-Isumi-san?
Um...
That was for finding my stole.
I think things will be a little better now.
Have a good evening.
And I really like you, Hayate-sama.
A love-comedy situation!
Continuing to Part B.
Riaru Rabu = Real Love.
Riaru Rabu.
Brajya Conpurekkusu
Brajya Conpurekkusu = Brassiere Complex
I-Isumi-san.
I really like you, Hayate-sama.
A dream...
I see! I must be easily liked by children!
Our main character has a pure mind that leaves children out of his target zone.
Have you been up all night?
Yeah.
Yesterday, it looked like they were hugging to me.
What was that?
If it bothers you that much, how about asking them?
But, if I did and it turns out Isumi really does love him...
Since Hayate loves me, I'll end up hurting Isumi.
Ah... I see.
But it could have been some kind of mistake.
There is a high possibility of Isumi holding affection for Hayate.
After all, Hayate's the most handsome man in the universe.
Wow...
Then it'll be trouble if that most handsome man in the universe is sweet-talking Isumi-san.
That can't possibly be happening!
Hayate would never do that to anyone other than me!
Not to Isumi! He'd never fall in love with any other girls!
He'd never...
I'm going to see Hayate!
Okay.
Hayate!
Y-Y-Y-Yes, what is it, Milady?
I have something I want to ask you.
Yes.
Do you, um, care for Isumi?
I do care for Isumi-san.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Do you seriously love Isumi?
Answer me! I saw you take action yesterday!
Um, I probably wouldn't say that I love her.
Then are you treating her as a game?
Was yesterday just part of your fun?
Rather than Isumi-san,
it's usually Sakuya-san that I have fun with.
Oh, but it's true that I'd like to have more fun with Isumi-san.
M-Milady?
You... You...
You jerk!
That hurt.
I shouldn't try to crack eggs with my head.
I've lost faith in you, Hayate!
Are you all right?
Um, did I do something?
Ah, I-I'm not sure.
Could Isumi-san saying she likes me be the problem?
Isumi-san did?
Yes, she's cute, isn't she?
I tend to be liked by young children,
so I might do well as a teacher at a nursery school.
Eh?
I guess...
This is...
I have to do something.
Really...
Why are men interested in watching something like this?
But then again, you've watched about thirty of them yourself.
Sir is still a child, so he probably isn't interested in girls yet,
but I wonder if he'd want to watch one of these, too.
No, this must be limited to a small fraction of men.
I'm sure Sir will not!
But he hasn't left the house since last night.
What could he be doing?
I-I-I'm sorry, the store's not open yet.
Lady Nagi!
Sorry to interrupt.
No, it can't be...
Isumi can't possibly love the debt-ridden butler...
What are you sleeping around for?!
N-Nagi! What are you doing here?
I ran away from home!
Huh?
The girl ran from her home due to
a broken heart and the feeling of being abandoned.
Oh, you guys can return now.
But don't let Maria know, all right?
Yes!
Wh-What do we do?
We have to find her, obviously.
Okay!
H-Hayate-kun!
I'll check Isumi-san's house first!
Wait!
E-Excuse me! What do you mean Lady Nagi ran away from home?
She'll be in your care here for a while.
By the way, Kijima Saki-dono.
Yes?
The one and only granddaughter of
the Sanzenins will be living here for a while.
If anything should happen...
You know the consequences, right?
You won't be able to get off the hook!
Anyway, we're not going to get anywhere even if we fight like this.
You're right.
Let's go to Isumi's house...
...And hear her feelings.
My, Nagi ran away from home?
Yes. Do you have any ideas?
Let's see, she's probably at-
What's wrong?
Dust got in my eye.
Are you all right?
Hey, couldn't it have been a mistake?
Right, them hugging each other could have been from-
It's not coming out.
Hayate!
Milady!
You're here!
You came to meet Isumi the moment I disappeared?!
Huh? Yes, I did.
I sell you to Isumi for ¥150,000,000!
Milady!
Milady! Why?!
I will, then.
Shall I buy Hayate-sama from you?
For ¥150,000,000?
Milady!
Lady Nagi!
And thus the love-comedy turns out to become a full-scale yucky, icky conflict.
Meanwhile, Maria was-
I have to do something but...
Wait, I'm all alone here?
What do you plan on doing, borrowing a boring DVD like this?
Huh?
You're borrowing a bunch of trash movies
that were only popular due to people's voices.
That's none of your business.
Shut up! Keep your mouth shut!
Listen to me!
Time is finite!
There are countless masterpieces
that must be watched in this world.
You are lacking Gund*m knowledge!!!
G-Gund*m?
Yes, Gund*m.
Therefore, I'll lend you from season 1 all the way to Double *.
All the way?
Listen! Don't sleep!
You must not sleep and watch it like you life's about to end!
Especially Counterattack and Turn A are-
You idiot!
Don't rent my DVDs out randomly!
I'm not renting them out randomly!
I'm picking out masterpieces!
Besides, why are you here?!
Because I ran away from home. What else?
And the reason why you didn't want to be at home was because the debt-ridden butler was there, wasn't it?
Then go home already!
He's no longer at your place!
Not at my place...
Hayate isn't...
...at my place...
SIR!!!!!!!!!
What are you doing picking on her?!
I wasn't really picking on her...
If you're like that, even Isumi-san will hate you!
SFX: DONG
Eh?
I'll burn down this shop!
Burn away!
And Saki-san was being toyed with by two children.
You can't, Sir!
Next week, we'll fight against robots.
I am a cat.
I do not have a name yet.
The sky's up high as always.
Look at that! It's so cute!
Wow, it's a kitty.
It's so soothing!
Yeah, whatever. If you're going to pity me, then feed me.
Wait, you're seriously going? You heartless people!
You hypocrites!
Damn, the rain in the city's so cold.
Man, I'm hungry.
It's milk!
Damn you!
Weren't you going to give that to me?
What? Mouth-to-mouth?
Bro...
Hey, are you okay?
Did you catch cold?
Oh, Wataru-kun. So this is where you were.
Ah, you found the kitty.
I'm happy for you.
You were worried about him and searched for him every time it rained.
You were looking for me, Bro?
Good kitty, good kitty.
What's your name, Bro?
'taru.
Oh, so this kitty's called Tatu Taru?
Heh?
Yup!
That's such a cute name.
I-It's a little lame, but I'll live with it.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Thanks for tuning in. This is Sanzenin Nagi.
This is Ayasaki Hayate.
It's Sakuya.
Hey, I think this show limits my screentime too much.
There are people who show up
every week without real purpose.
That's because anytime you show up,
other characters fade away.
I won't be fooled by that, debt-ridden butler.
It's because Saku's a character who gets forgotten.
What'd'ou say?!
Oh, forget it.
Here's my borderline sexy shot.
How was it? Did you burn it in to your eyes?
Bye bye!
It's natural for me to be discarded by Milady.
It was like a dream to be able to work at a mansion like that to begin with.
Hayate probably hates me now.
In that case, why not test the love?
Test the love?
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Shake the Heart
Fake a kidnapping?!
You can't do that!
The galaxy is calling for me.