Everything okay?
I heard you moaning.
Yeah, I had another nightmare.
What manner of monster is this Saitama?
You kept repeating
"Saitama, Saitama" in your sleep.
THE OVERLY-COMPLICATED NINJA
This has never happened to me before.
Losing a fight is one thing,
but for some reason,
I no longer "feel the wind."
This is unprecedented.
It was just one fight.
And I only lost because of bad luck.
There should be no difference
in ability between us.
So… why?
No matter what strategy I use…
I can't picture myself winning!
Why…?
Well, that's how it is.
That's how psychological trauma works.
You've been so good to me, Hunter.
Don't mention it.
We're birds of a feather.
My work puts my life at risk, too.
Up in the mountains,
I occasionally come across
horrible monsters on my hunts.
Just like you…
I've got my own enemy to defeat.
Is he tough?
Yeah, he's the master of this mountain.
He's the one who gave me these scars.
A bear?
Yeah.
Fortunately, my life was spared
when I ran straight towards a cliff,
but only because I fell off.
It hurt like hell.
Ever since,
the hand I hold my gun with trembles…
…from fear.
What if my gun fails me again,
just like it did that time?
The thought makes my hand shake,
and I can't make a good shot.
But if I can defeat him,
I'm sure my hand will tremble no more.
If you want to overcome your own fear,
the only way to do it is to defeat your enemy.
Huh? He's gone…
Who says I'm afraid of him?
Ridiculous! There's no way…
Sure, why not?
It'll be good training.
Damn it!
Wind Blade Kick!
I see. So that's how it is.
I'll admit it, Saitama…
You make me feel afraid!
I owe you one, little boar.
Thanks to you, I might get my strength back.
What a treat tonight!
Snake meat isn't all that bad, you know.
Looks like this uribo has taken a liking to you.
Uribo?
Yeah, boars found in the wild
rarely take to humans—
Why'd you call him "uribo"?
Huh?
No reason.
That's the word for wild boar piglets.
Isn't that normal?
He'll have a name, and I'll decide it.
O-Okay.
Ino.
From "inoshishi," the word for wild boar.
How's that?
"How's that?" Well…
Sounds pretty normal, but…
then again…
From that day forward, I devoted my days
to training for defeating Saitama.
And, by the time I finished,
I'd come to a conclusion.
I decided I would not
run away from fear,
and instead face my fears head-on.
By doing so, it becomes possible
to prevail over and control fear.
And if I can do that…
Wind Blade Kick!
Moving on?
Yeah, thanks for everything, Hunter.
Call me Frank.
Frank Hunter, huh?
Good name.
Huh?
It's a fine name for a man who hunts.
I won't forget it.
No, I'm no Hunter…
You're not a hunter?
Well yeah, I am a hunter,
but that's not my name…
It's, you know, my job.
Let's see…
maybe you'd understand it better
if I say it's more like "Frank the Hunter."
Ah, I get it.
So "Hunter" is the same
as "Speed-o'-Sound" in my name.
Anyway, you plan on staying here?
Yeah.
I see.
Listen, Hunter.
Yeah?
If you're defeated even before you fight,
the outcome will be the same,
no matter how often you try.
Any idea what he meant, Ino?
Ino? What's wrong? You miss him?
I'm sure he'll be back
when he loses… again.
Just as I thought…
It's you.
Allow me to repay you for my scars.
Listen, Hunter…
If you're defeated even before you fight,
the outcome will be the same,
no matter how often you try.
I get it. That's what he meant.
Sonic, what you were saying is…
I win!
Run, Ino…
Oh. A bear.
Well, bear's not bad, but…
I could go for wild boar too…
Hey…
Whatever. Bear will do.
So this is a bear hot pot, Master?
Yeah.
You heard those rumors about the giant bear
causing all that damage, right?
You can eat bear?
Yeah, you can eat most animals.
I see!
Oh, and I hear wild boar's pretty good, too.
I have so much to learn from you, Master!
Just you wait, Saitama.
The next time we meet
will be your demise.
Oh…
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore wa ansatsu kara yojinbo made
Whether it's assassination or bodyguarding
nani demo ukeou saikyo no ninja,
I accept any contract,
for I'm the strongest ninja
onsoku no sonikku
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic
ninja no sato ni nama o ukete
I was born in a ninja village
osanai koro kara mi ni tsuketa
I trained myself from when I was young
supido ninjutsu tekunikku
Speed, skills, techniques
mukau toko teki nashi
I know not defeat
zenaku nanka do demo ii
I care not about good or evil
onore o tameshitai
All that matters is my potential
a motto motto motto
Ah, more, more, more!
kansetsu panikku shite nai zo
Don't call me Jack-o'-Lantern Panic!
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
saitama! tsugini atta
toki ga omae no saigo da!
Saitama! The next time we
meet will be your demise!
kyukyoku no ninjutsu de
kakujitsu ni shitomeru!
You are no match for
my ultimate ninja skills!
kono onsoku no sonikku ga na!
For I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March