THE OVERLY-COMPLICATED NINJA
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ore wa ansatsu kara yojinbo made
Whether it's assassination or bodyguarding
nani demo ukeou saikyo no ninja,
I accept any contract,
for I'm the strongest ninja
onsoku no sonikku
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic
ninja no sato ni nama o ukete
I was born in a ninja village
osanai koro kara mi ni tsuketa
I trained myself from when I was young
supido ninjutsu tekunikku
Speed, skills, techniques
mukau toko teki nashi
I know not defeat
zenaku nanka do demo ii
I care not about good or evil
onore o tameshitai
All that matters is my potential
a motto motto motto
Ah, more, more, more!
kansetsu panikku shite nai zo
Don't call me Jack-o'-Lantern Panic!
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
saitama! tsugini atta
toki ga omae no saigo da!
Saitama! The next time we
meet will be your demise!
kyukyoku no ninjutsu de
kakujitsu ni shitomeru!
You are no match for
my ultimate ninja skills!
kono onsoku no sonikku ga na!
For I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March