We don't have a choice.
We live in a cruel world.
I'm going... to drive them out...!
No...
Kill them!
Humanity was suddenly reminded that day.
Of the terror of being at their mercy...
Of the humiliation of being
trapped inside a cage...
Eren!
Eren...
I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"Wall"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 3"
Let us pray.
For the solidity of the three
goddesses, Maria, Rose, and Sina.
For our own welfare.
We must not misdoubt the sacred walls.
These walls of light born
from the hands of the divine
are made ever more stalwart
through the offering of our faith.
For it is only the
innocence of faithful devotion
that protects us from the Titans.
It, alone, keeps the Titans away from--
A Titan?! Here?!
N-No...
Stay away from the wall...
Stay away...!
Looks like he's in control
of himself this time around.
Yes.
But Eren has yet to win against
the Female Titan even once.
If he's transformed, it means
he's gotta be ready for the worst.
--He won't lose so eas--
--Spirit alone can't win a fight.
You know that first-hand.
Surpassing Annie...
...will require more!
Level ground!
She's heading for level ground!
We can't use ODM there!
Split into two teams and go around!
Understood!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
This is crazy! What are Titans doing here?!
Annie...
You always acted like everything
around you was stupid and pointless...
You never seemed interested in anything.
But, there are times when you're full of life...
Whenever you show off
those combat skills of yours.
You talked about how there was no point to it...
...but it didn't seem
like you believed that at all.
If anything, you struck me as a bad liar.
Tell me, Annie...
What are you fighting for?
For what cause did you murder people?!
Oh, man...
Section Commander.
Even if we do catch the Female Titan,
the city's going to end up in ruins!
That's not our concern.
This is Erwin's decision.
Ready the capture nets.
Right!
Eren...
No one said anything about this...
Why are there Titans fighting here?
What in the world is happening?
Titans are fighting each other?!
Yes. The damage done to
the city is unimaginable...
Scores of civilians and soldiers
have been killed or wounded.
Erwin! Is this the result of your doing?!
It is.
I acted entirely on my own authority.
I offer no excuses.
You had to have known what this plan of yours
would've caused in the middle of a city!
Why?! Why did you do it?!
For humankind's...
...victory.
Don't give me that!
You're a traitor!
None of the higher-ups will
complain if I execute you right now!
If you wish.
But...
You'll be in charge afterward.
Do not let the Female Titan escape.
Peer is in charge of troop deployment.
Beirer is in charge of provisions.
--Work with them and do whatever it takes--
--W-Wait! Stop!
Do you really think...
...this is for humanity's sake?
I have faith it will serve as a step forward.
Everyone, lower your guns!
Cuff him!
Yes, Sir!
Deploy all troops
and focus on aiding and evacuating the citizens!
Yes, Sir!
Erwin. I'll let a court of law
decide how to execute you.
I'll gladly accept that,
once everything is over.
Levi. Stay put. You don't like pointless death.
You're right. I'm not fond of
causing it or experiencing it.
Those who can't abandon anything...
...can't change anything.
The ability to give up your humanity...
...when forced to rise above monsters...
I think that's something Annie can do!
Annie...
Annie!
Your dad is always on your side...
I... will kill...
...the Titans...
Every last one...
Eren!
Is he...?!
--Eren!
--Stop!
I'm not sure Eren would recognize you right now!
Whoa...
--She's on the wall!
--She intends to climb over!
Oh, no!
She's getting away!
I won't let her!
Annie.
Fall.
Annie...
It was wrong of me...
I won't ask for your forgiveness now.
But... all I ask of you...
...is one thing...
Even if you turn the whole
world against you, it's okay.
I will...
...destroy... the entire world...!
Even if the entire world ends up hating you...
...just know that your
dad is always on your side...
Oh, no! He's going to eat the person inside!
Stop, Eren!
Eren!
I'm...
...free...!
So promise me...
...that you'll come back...
Huh? What's he doing?
What the...?!
They're merging?!
Eren!
Don't go eatin' our key evidence, you idiot...
Eren...
Mikasa...
Where's Annie?
Damn it!
What the hell?! After all this,
we get the silent treatment?!
Annie!
Get out here!
Get out here and pay for what you've done!
Come on! Don't be a coward!
Annie! Annie!
Stop.
It's pointless.
Make a wire net!
Let's get this thing underground!
Understood!
If we end up not getting
any info out of Annie...
...what'll be left?
Nothing but countless casualties,
ruined lives, and unanswered questions...
...all for what?
Seems the plan wasn't much of a success.
No, I'd say the Scout
Regiment's in the clear now.
Just barely.
Let's hope so...
Erwin. We have a number of
questions concerning this latest operation.
If you believe you knew the target's identity,
why did you not ask for the
Military Police's assistance?
Sir.
Given the likelihood that the
Female Titan has inside accomplices,
it was necessary to involve
only those above suspicion.
But how do you justify the damage
caused to Stohess as a result of that?!
Our ineptitude is to blame.
I offer my sincerest apologies.
Apologies won't fix this!
Had we left her unchecked, the wall
would've been destroyed eventually.
The ensuing destruction would've been far worse.
I see.
So, do you have any proof that
this devastating operation of yours
has helped to prevent the downfall of humankind?
I find it unlikely you'll get anything
out of Annie Leonhart now...
Indeed, I doubt we will.
In other words... it was all for naught?
Eren.
Do you feel all right?
Yeah...
It's weird how normal I feel.
I guess Annie's still stuck in there?
Yeah.
Damn...
That big of an operation, all for nothin'.
Annie went that far to
keep her information safe...
Yeah. She slipped right through our fingers.
Eren let her get away.
Isn't that right, Eren?
If it hadn't been for that brief moment...
Yeah.
It's true.
I screwed up.
I froze as soon as I saw her...
Armin Arlelt.
Jean Kirschtein.
You're wanted for debriefing.
Right.
Guess we're up first.
See you later, then.
Yeah...
It actually felt nice...
Having my body come apart
somehow felt... refreshing.
So much so that I felt like I wanted to die.
Eren!
I don't want to now.
I'm glad... that you came back...
It's too much for me to understand.
Abandoning your humanity
to rise above monsters...
That's the only way to win, huh?
It's one hope humankind has
for prevailing over the Titans.
I think Eren can do it.
I wonder...
Getting rid of the Titans by
becoming that kind of monster...
Would that really be a victory for humankind?
Eat.
It won't be easy.
However...
I believe humankind has
gained great potential for survival.
There was a time when we never
even imagined humans becoming Titans.
Compared to then, capturing a member
of the enemy is an enormous step forward.
Yes. There are more out there.
And we will go after every last one.
This time, it is our turn to launch
an attack on the Titans within our walls!
The Scout Regiment and Eren Jaeger's
recall to the capital was rescinded,
and the Scouts were placed in charge of
supervising Annie Leonhart deep underground.
However...
It would take much more time and many more lives
for humanity to learn
what was holding it prisoner.
...changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map