Hey, Minami—
What?
Question 10
Me, Romance, and the Art of Love
Um...
Sorry about earlier.
Whatever.
Just go have fun with Mizuki.
Don't say that. Cheer up.
Let's think of another plan together.
If we end up fighting a battle with Class B and lose,
Himeji might have to transf—
What was that?
Idiot!
You just go on and on about Mizuki.
Why do you always treat her like a princess?
Minami...
So what about me?
Why do you treat me like that?
Do you think of me as a guy?
I didn't mean—
If it looks like Mizuki will have to transfer, I'll go talk to her parents.
Minami!
Don't talk to me.
I don't want to see you.
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Review of last episode.
Last Week's Recap
Yay.
Class B's rep, Nemoto Kyouji, saw the state of the boys, who were weakened by their suspension,
Stairs
Toilet
Connecting Corridor
Stairs
Culture Room
Connecting Corridor
Class E
Stairs
Connecting Corridor
Culture Room
Class E
Class F
Old School Building
Toilet
Stairs
Connecting Corridor
Culture Room
Class E
Class F
Old School Building
Toilet
Stairs
Culture Room
Toilet
Stairs
Culture Room
Connecting Corridor
Suspension
Toilet
Stairs
Connecting Corridor
Culture Room
Class E
Class F
Old School Building
Suspension
Stairs
Connecting Corridor
Old School Building
Toilet
Culture Room
Old School Building
ESB Declaration
Toilet
Class E
Class F
Old School Building
Suspension
ESB Declaration
as an opportunity to challenge Class F to an ESB.
Toilet
Culture Room
Old School Building
Suspension
ESB Declaration
Toilet
Culture Room
Old School Building
Suspension
ESB Declaration
So Akihisa's Class F was attempting to provoke Class D into starting an ESB.
Provoke
ESB Declaration
If they were to fight Class D, they would get the chance to take makeup exams after the battle.
If they could rebuild their strength in that time, Class B would hesitate to engage them.
Scores
In order to do that, Akihisa and Shimada would pretend to go out,
Guys
Girls
(2 person)
Current strength of Class F
Buying time by
having an ESB with Class D
Previously weakest
Rep
Me
Haven't rebuilt their points
since the training camp
Block
Strength
Rage
Acting as a couple
Akihisa
Shimada
Make them declare ESB first
Current strength of Class D
Shimizu Miharu
Provoke
Rep
Nemoto Kyouji
Independent
Shore up his position
Back
Hiraga
Directing all the rage
Unable to declare ESB immediately
and incite Shimizu Miharu's rage.
Or rather, that was our plan.
How'd you manage to screw it up so bad? Ya idiot!
Who's gonna think you're going out after the show you put on?
Sorry.
Perhaps I should've worked more on his acting.
Shimada and Himeji did a great job.
Oh, well...
I guess.
Why do you treat me like that?
Voyeur.
How're things looking with Class B?
At this time, they have recovered about 70 percent of their strength.
Some are making preparations for the battle.
That was quicker than I expected.
That means they're serious about this.
We need to buy some time.
First off, Voyeur,
disseminate false information among Class B.
Details?
Say Class D has begun preparing for an ESB,
and that they're after Class B.
Roger.
Will that really work?
Nemoto's goal is to win the battle and maintain his position.
He'll want to avoid multiple battles that will only wear them down.
ESB Declaration
If they learn Class D is after them,
he'll hesitate to challenge us to a battle.
ESB Declaration
I see!
After all, they're not after our facilities.
Next, Hideyoshi!
Bring Class D's Shimizu Miharu to the negotiating table.
We'll provoke her, to arouse her hostility.
Rage
ESB Declaration
If she declares war against us, we've succeeded.
Why me, though?
We need someone to go with Shimada to bring out Shimizu.
That means I can't ask Akihisa or Himeji to do it.
I see.
Understood.
And also, Akihisa!
Hm? What is it?
Are you hungry?
Well, I guess so.
That's no good.
You're the linchpin of this plan.
You need to eat well and build up your strength.
Right, Himeji?
Eh?
That's right.
He can't do anything on an empty stomach!
That's where you come in, Himeji.
Get Akihisa something to—
Oh, now I remember, I ate my box lunch earlier. I'm completely full! I couldn't eat a bite more.
Box lunch? What, that one?
Hm?
It's good.
Damn Tasty
Why?
There you have it.
Himeji, can you cook something for Akihisa?
Of course, I'd be glad to!
Yuuji, I give in!
Akihisa, what would you like to eat?
You're asking—
A smart choice here could lower the lethality.
Hurry up, Akihisa.
A dish with very specific ingredients that won't leave room for anything abnormal.
That's it, boiled eggs!
Mizuki's Homemade
Food
Today's Meal
Boiled Egg
Ingredients: just egg
Akihisa...
says he wants jelly.
Jelly
Ingredients: Innumerable
Today's Meal
I'll never know what she's put in that!
He might want it during the mission,
Today's Meal
Do not look
Drink Pouch
Ingredients: Innumerable
Do not look
so make it a jelly drink and put it in a drink pouch.
Today's Container
Drink Pouch
Do not look
Today's Container
Drink Pouch
Do not look
Today's Container
Drink Pouch
Do not look
Today's Container
Drink Pouch
Do not look
I won't even be able to see the color!
Got it!
Today's Container
Do not look
Drink Pouch
Today's Container
I'll do my best!
Wait, let's at least decide what kind of jelly!
Calm down, Akihisa.
I won't make you eat it.
I just needed a weapon for the mission.
Oh, then you should've just told me earlier!
Though Himeji is bound to try and make you eat it now.
You're so evil!
Home Economics Room
Jelly
Prepare gelatin and sugar...
Oh, it's actuallly pretty normal.
Thank God.
First, mix cocoa powder with corn soup.
What on earth is she making?
Be quiet, she'll spot us!
Oranges or scallions... I wonder which Akihisa would prefer?
Don't waver! The answer should be obvious, Himeji!
She's deciding based on what has the best nutritional value for you.
Taste is irrelevant.
I have scallions, so how about natto?
No, no!
Actually, I've heard that natto doesn't really cleanse your blood.
Safe!
Even so, it's still healthy!
3rd Inning
And blue-backed fish will cleanse the blood!
A double play.
Why vinegared mackerel? Why would vinegared mackerel go into jelly?
She's worried about your idiot brain, so she's putting in some DHA.
That's not good, is it?
Great! She noticed it!
Natto goes with mustard.
Not that!
Vinegared mackerel goes with ginger.
Not that, either!
And a secret ingredient to bring out the flavor.
No secret ingredients, just use the normal ones!
Oh, that's right! For a more mature flavor, some taba—
Let's go. Any more and you won't be able to eat it.
Wait! Just let me confirm whether it's Tabasco or tobacco!
It's already too late.
Here, eat up!
I need to clean up the home-ec room!
So what do we do with these?
I bet Nemoto will send a messenger to Class D.
That'll be to confirm whether they really do intend to battle.
If they do that, they'll find out it wasn't true!
So we'll assassinate the messenger!
Messenger
If we take out the messenger, Nemoto will grow suspicious of Class D.
Pissed off
Then our false information will be more credible.
What a fearful plan!
Merciless
Battles are fought heartlessly.
Voyeur!
Get on it.
Roger.
What is that?
D-Damn you!
Rest in peace.
M-Mom...
Assassination complete.
Good job, Voyeur.
That's some impressive skill you have there.
That was nothing.
How did you attract everyone's attention?
You don't need to know.
Nemoto should take the assassination as a warning from Class D.
This will buy us some time.
Hideyoshi, how are negotiations with Class D?
They've promised to meet us in an empty classroom.
Shimada's agreed to come.
And we'll provoke Class D into declaring an ESB.
Will they take the bait?
I've got a plan up my sleeve.
Leave it to me.
There's something bothering me.
What's wrong, Voyeur?
I saw Nemoto talking to someone in Class A.
In Class A?
That is strange.
Why would he—
Yuuji!
Shouko?
Wh-Why are you here?
You too, why are you still at school?
Huh? What do you mean?
Yuuji, I heard your mom collapsed.
Huh? That mom of mine?
She's so healthy she wouldn't even catch a cold!
Anyway, you need to hurry back home.
Wait! I've got an important operation to carry out—
This isn't the time for that.
Hold on! Why are you the one—
Just come with me.
Shouko! Calm down!
That was...
strange.
What do you mean, Voyeur?
You'd think they'd have contacted Yuuji first.
Maybe they couldn't get through.
His phone is dead, after all.
They could've used the P.A. system.
Then what Nemoto was saying must be—
Yes, it was misinformation.
What?
Crap. Yuuji was supposed to manage the plan to provoke Shimizu.
Did he say anything about it?
Nope, not a thing.
Hostility
Lies
Why did Nemoto do that?
He couldn't have found out about our plans, could he?
Hostility
No, they must be trying to buy some time as well.
Lies
Most likely, he wanted to stall us until he could decipher Class D's plans.
Sly indeed, Nemoto.
It's about time, right?
M-Minami...
I only came for the negotiations.
What are you gonna do, Akihisa?
Isn't it obvious?
Without Yuuji, we'll just have to improvise!
Question 10
Visualize the situation below and
answer the question that follows.
You are walking alone on a path in a
dark forest and are lost. As you walk
further into the forest, you find a small
hut by a lake. "How fortunate," you
think, as you enter it. Inside the hut, you
find a chair, a bed, and a portrait.
The question is: what are the
characteristics of the person
in the portrait?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
1. A cheerful expression
2. Gentle eyes
3. Makes you feel happy
Teacher's Comment
This is a psychological test to describe the
person you like. The dark forest symbolizes
your uncertainties, and the portrait inside the
hut symbolizes the person who is your
emotional support. It seems that the person
you like is a gentle, bright, and fun person.
Shimizu Miharu's Answer
1. Fiery eyes
2. Manly chest
3. Pony-tailed
Teacher's Comment
The last one feels wrong.
Shimada Minami's Answer
1. Broken fingers
2. Knees twisted the wrong way
3. Dislocated wrists
Teacher's Comment
All of that feels wrong.
Darling, I missed you so much!
Get off me, Miharu!
Your chest reminds me of the gentle rolling waves of the sea! It's the best!
Flat Chest
You're saying she's as flat as the sea, aren't you?
Get off me!
I think of you 360 days a year!
So you don't think about her during Obon or the New Year Holidays.
Shimizu! Stop right there!
Shimada is Akihisa's girlfriend.
Don't touch her like she's yours!
Finally!
The signal to begin the operation!
What are you going on about?
There's nothing between my darling and that pig over there! I can see it in her eyes!
Anyway, he's completely undeserving of my darling's affections!
W-Well, I'm not very cool, and I'm no good at studying either,
but—
Not cool? Studying?
It has nothing to do with such trivial flaws.
It's more basic than that.
I've been watching you two for a while now,
and I find your behavior to be absolutely horrendous.
The way you treat Himeji
and the way you treat my darling are worlds apart!
You treat Himeji kindly and gently,
as if she were a princess.
But you handle my darling without even a shred of gallantry.
To be blunt, not only are you completely oblivious to her charms,
you just treat her like one of the guys!
The problem is far deeper than your looks or academics
when it comes to deserving my darling's affection!
Furthermore,
even if it was just an act,
to actually dump her and chase after Himeji is just unthinkable!
You just think of Shimada as a guy, don't you?
Minami!
What are you going to do now?
Assault her with that coarse speech of yours?
Are you going to hurt her more?
I'll go.
You'd just make things worse right now.
Well, I don't really get it,
but I'd better get out of here.
I don't know what you were trying to achieve here,
but I'm no longer going to treat you as a romantic rival.
It's a waste of my time to be jealous of a pig who doesn't even notice her charms.
The only one who understands her
is me, Miharu.
Shimizu...
Still have something to say?
I have to tell you this.
We're proclaiming an ESB with Class F!
EHH!?
What do you mean?
Didn't the operation fail?
So what do we do now?
It'll be hard for us to win with our current strength.
I've taken care of that already.
Yuuji?
I was right. It was misinformation from Nemoto.
That sneaky bastard's been a busy little bee!
Glad to hear that's cleared up.
Well done, Akihisa.
It didn't go quite as I'd planned,
but you still succeeded in enraging Shimizu.
So how are we going to fight them?
We'll lose in an all-out war.
That's why it'll be a battle between the reps!
I'm surprised you didn't run away.
That's my line.
I don't want to battle my darling.
I'm fine with just beating the crap out of that pig.
You heard her, Akihisa.
This is your battle.
Good luck.
Thanks, Yuuji.
I won't forgive you.
Prepare yourself!
Permission to engage in battle.
Engage!
Summon!
Answer me this.
What?
Those things you said,
were they just lies to incite this battle?
Were they?
She was crying...
It was my words that made her cry.
But that's because—
it's because—
scum like you exist!
Why is scum like you so close to her?
Why does scum like you, who toy with her feelings, even get to talk to her every day?
Why? Why?
Why do you, who manipulated her with lies,
get to stay by her side as a friend?
I...
never lied to her!
I may be dumb,
but I know when not to lie.
Those weren't lies!
I don't believe you! I don't want to believe!
Those are my true feelings, without a shred of dishonesty!
I refuse to believe that!
That's enough!
Yuuji! What are you—
We'll take it from here.
That's really low! Isn't that grossly unfair?
I'm fine with that!
All's fair in war!
Yuuji!
Do it.
Yuuji! Stop—
Ow! Why me?
The pain! The pain!
The stabbing and the blunt impacts are combining to send me to a new world of pain!
Shimizu.
I've dealt with the root of the problem.
Can we bury the hatchet?
I suppose so.
Though since my anger has yet to subside,
I'll imprison this pig with an eon of supplementary lessons.
Was this... the real plan all along?
Sorry 'bout that, pal.
We couldn't beat Class D with our current strength.
It was only natural to negotiate a truce.
It was all your fault to begin with for hurting my darling's feelings!
I repent!
I'm sorry, from the bottom of my heart!
If I felt you'd been lying, I wouldn't have let you off so easily.
AGHHHHH!
But this time, I'll let it go with just this.
Negotiations are complete.
Guys, we're pulling back!
Welcome.
And so the battle ends.
How's the situation, Voyeur?
Seems like Nemoto's given up on the idea.
Well, that's to be expected.
There's nothing in it for him now.
I also managed to obtain this.
What's that?
I don't know what you were trying to achieve here,
Isn't that—
but I'm no longer going to treat you as a romantic rival.
It's a record of yesterday's conversation.
W-Wait right there! Why are you playing it back?
Hold him down.
Got it!
Let me go, Hideyoshi!
No can do!
You're so damn noisy.
Shut up, will ya?
I have to tell you this.
I'd like to clear things up.
I know that you going out with my darling was just an act.
No, that's not it.
Um...
You're not the only one who's aware of her charm.
What are you talking about?
You always talk to her with such crude language!
You don't even appreciate her as a girl!
You're right, I don't treat her like a princess.
And I might be treating her casually, just like one of the guys.
But...
But?
What is it?
Minami is someone I can always talk to freely and openly,
and I always have fun fooling around with her.
The things she does are really cute sometimes.
She's a really charming...
yes, a charming girl.
That...
That was totally unexpected.
Yeah...
I thought you'd beat around the bush, but...
...you just said it straight out.
They heard it...
Of all people, these three...
I didn't know you could be so bold when the moment called for it.
For some reason, my heart's really pouding...
That's so manly...
I'm so dead...
So dead...
Wee! Up you go!
Welcome home, sis!
I-I'm back.
What's wrong? Your face is beet red!
Hazuki, what should I do?
About what? Did something happen at school?
Well, Hazuki...
Yes?
Your sis...
might have fallen really hard for someone...
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
shinten shinai yo
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
This sucks.
How should I apologize to Minami when I see her?
Yo.
What's with the long face, Aki?
Eh?
M-Minami?
What?
No, um...
you know...
I'm sorry about yesterday!
For what? Did you go and do something wrong again?
N-No! That's not it—
I'm not gonna let you off easy if you make a mess again!
Eh?
Idiot!
Question 11
Answer the following question.
What do you call a person who
has been close to you since your
childhood?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
A childhood friend
Teacher's Comment
Correct as always, Himeji.
Do you have a childhood friend?
There are many people whose
childhood companions developed into
lifelong friends. You rarely come across
someone so precious in adulthood.
Please use this time to make as many
friends as you can.
Sakamoto Yuuji's Answer
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
Next Episode
Question 11: What do you call a person who has been close to you since your childhood?
A childhood f—
A childhood f- AARGHHHHHH
A fiancé.
Next episode: Yuuji, Shouko, and their Childhood Memories.
Yuuji, Shouko, and their Childhood Memories
This will be on the test.