What's wrong?
So, you're heading to Mistral?
That sucks.
But they do say the food and
women are good there.
It's been six months
since the ceasefire.
Glad we both made
it through alive!
Grand ouvert!
Read 'em and weep!
- You've gotta be kidding me!
- Damn!     - Seriously?
Miss! You up?
Your share of the spoils of war.
Caramel?
I-I'm honored to receive
such a treasure!
Um, Sergeant!
Don't worry.
If you're nice to the trumpeter,
you can hear them sound the retreat better.
Odd to see a new recruit,
now that the draft's over.
You volunteered?
Yes! I wanted to learn
how to play music.
I mean...
An honest girl... I like that!
Good luck, kiddo!
Private, what's your name?
Kanata! Kanata Sorami!
So Ra No Wo To
The Sound that Fills the Air -
The City of Dawn
Seize is having a festival today.
A festival?
So I can't take you further.
Look.
That's where you've been assigned.
Locals call it Clocktower Fortress.
Set a course for it.
Right!
Orders for Private Kanata Sorami.
You are ordered to report to the
1121 Platoon in Seize City, Trois.
Helvetia Republic Army HQ.
As of 1320, this mission is complete!
Thank you very much!
The town of lakes
and glass, Seize.
Wait! Wait!
I'm supposed to report at 1500.
I can finally let you sing.
Direction confirmed!
Time confirmed!
Equipment confirmed!
Advance!
Step right up!
G-flat... A wonderful sound!
Fishies!
Ten yen, twenty-five sen.
What a beautiful doll-
I-I'm sorry!
What's wrong, Rio?
A kitten had too much fun at the fair,
and it ran off in the wrong direction.
Can't be helped...
Cats always take their
time getting places.
That's why they're
cute, you know.
If it were a stray, it'd be OK.
But it's a domesticated cat.
Wow, that scared me...
But I found another
wonderful thing.
What's wrong?
Thanks!
Hey! A soldier!
A girl from the fort?
Great!
To the Flame Maidens!
Thank you!
OK!
I'll get you for that!
Ready... Fire!
Thanks!
Hey!
Are you stupid or something?
You shouldn't have joined them!
Your uniform's all messy now!
Umm... A-Ah...
God bless you.
Thank...
Geez... Come with me!
How's the bath?
It's great!
That's good.
Looks like you made quite the target...
Couldn't you have dodged a little?
Don't worry.
Once it dries, this dye fades.
That's a festival, right?
It comes from a Seize legend.
A legend?
What kind of legend?
The legend of the Flame Maidens
who protect the city...
Sorry for the trouble.
I'll add it to your tab.
I'm done with the repairs, too.
And... This, too.
Filicia...
That nosy brat!
Late.
Late! Late!
She's late!
And we came to welcome her, too!
Calm down.
Let's relax and wait for her.
It's a present from
your father, right?
It's nice.
D-flat.
Thank you for the bath!
Um... I get lost a lot.
But thanks to that, I met
someone this wonderful!
You're welcome.
But don't get lost here.
Wow!
You can tell the pitch?
It's a clear... somehow
nostalgic sound.
That's not what I meant!
Thief!
You idiot!
Thank you very much.
Geez...
You'd die over something
like that?
But that bell...
It's fine.
I'm sure this is for the best.
She's late.
Happiness.
Um...
I've got something
to do, so I'm off.
Don't get lost again.
That bell... I'm sure it was
really important to her.
What should I do?
Oh, no!
That way?
Advance!
The Flame Maidens?
A long time ago, before the world
became the way it is now,
a winged demon came to live
at the bottom of this valley.
The demon breathed fire, shook the ground,
and caused people to suffer.
Finally, he kidnapped the maidens
who lived in the fort,
locking them in an
underground labyrinth.
The girls, however,
refused to give up,
and called to each other with golden horns
given to them by the Lord of Heaven.
Upon escaping the labyrinth,
they gained the help of an enormous spider
and defeated the demon, taking its head.
Once they'd done so, it began
spewing flame everywhere.
If nothing had been done, it would have
burned the town above to ash.
To keep the flames at bay, the maidens embraced
the demon's head, each in turn.
Every day, the villagers would throw water
on the maiden with the flaming head.
A year passed, and the flames
disappeared at last.
Thus, every year, the town celebrates
the water-throwing festival
to commemorate the maidens
who saved it.
The new girl never came.
Who cares?
Captain, look at Rio-sempai!
You're right. She looks great.
We were right to leave it to her.
But we drew straws-
I got lost again.
I'm a failure...
Sometimes, getting lost means
that something fun happens.
But that's only when you
meet someone new.
It's no fun being alone.
Are you lost?
Yeah.
I want my mommy!
Don't worry.
If you long for her, she'll know.
Really?
A sound will always fill the air.
Fill the air.
Fill the air...
And then, it reaches
people's ears.
Here sleep the Flame Maidens.
Awaken now, and embrace the
demon to quell its curse.
What?
The golden horns?
Has the demon awakened?
Kureha!
Please, someone... Hear my sound!
It reached them.
Sound fills the air, and then...
Get out of bed!
Private Kanata Sorami!
Huh? Where am I?
Snap out of it, already.
This is Clocktower Fortress,
base camp of the 1121 Platoon!
Um... I-I'm very sorry
about yesterday!
Damn right, you are.
I-I'm sorry!
But...
I'm kidding.
But from now on,
don't do stuff like that.
Not for something as
stupid as this bell.
Let me show you something.
A trumpet!
This is why we're called
Clocktower Fortress.
It's the sound of the sky!
Rio Kazumiya.
That's my name.
I'll teach you how to
play the trumpet.
Thank you, Sergeant Rio-dono!
Rio's fine.
Huh?
Filicia.
The captain's policy is
not to use ranks here.
Uh... So, Rio-sempai!
Then let's get started.
Play a wake-up reveille!
The girl they've got playing this
morning isn't very good.
Next time: First Battle - A Chair Story!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.