This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
She went to Hiiragi-en to
perform a mini-concert,
but she encountered
a mischevious boy.
He was acting out because he was
going to be separated from the girl he liked
once the concert was over.
Having similar experiences,
Full Moon sings them a heartfelt song.
That song touched
my heart a little too.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Ms. Oshige is late...
and Takuto and others
won't be around today either.
Sorry!
I was summoned by Director Shinigami
and there's no way I can go today.
If something happens,
call me with the whistle.
All right? All right?
What are you doing?
We're going, Takuto.
I-I know.
So that's the story.
See you later.
Well, I guess nothing
can be done
because Takuto and others seem
to have lots of things to do too.
But still, where is Ms. Oshige?
Hello, is this Ms. Oshige?
Huh? What do you mean?
What?! You're in the hospital?!
Yeah, well...
That's why today, a replacement
manager named Akiba will go.
Oh...okay, I understand.
Yes, yes... Then please
take care of yourself.
It seems like it's going to
be a difficult day.
Oh yeah, Mr. Akiba who is
going to be the replacement...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Full Moon!
Ah, you have the wrong person.
What?!
Excuse me...
Are you Mr. Akiba?
Yes, that's me?
Nice to meet you,
I am Full Moon.
P-Pardon me!
I am Akiba Kotaro who will be
working with you today.
It was difficult finding you
because you were in disguise,
but I feel lucky that I was
somehow able to meet you!
Oh yes, I'm being told
by Ms. Oshige to be
"in disguise at places where
there are many people."
That's Ms. Oshige as expected!
It would not be good if
you're noticed by the fans.
But today I, Akiba Kotaro,
will work hard to support you
and offer you management that
would not be inferior to Ms. Oshige,
so please leave
the matters to me.
Full Moon!
Hey, it's Full Moon.
It's true.
Wow, give me your autograph!
Darn! I've already made a mistake.
But it's okay.
Here!
Now's the chance.
Let's go!
It seems they've lost us.
Now then!
Let's go to our first assignment today,
an autograph session!
Yes. But where is
this place, actually?
I don't know!
Ah... What do you mean
you don't know?
But it's okay!
We can figure it out with this.
Huh?!
I-I brought the wrong map.
Ah, you know.
Shouldn't we just ask somebody?
That's it! There was that move.
Let's immediately go find somebody!
Wha—? Mr. Akiba!
Here you go.
Please keep on supporting me!
Hello. Oh, it's City FM.
Yes, we'll be done here in
about 15 minutes, so it'll be fine.
Yes, we'll be on
our way there soon.
All right...take care.
Ah...Mr. Akiba...
I can't possibly do it in 15 minutes.
We'll be fine!
What's left is only 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
38, 39...40...41...42
387...389...390...
1421...1422...1423...
We're in trouble!
The number of fans in line
is more than I expected.
It'll take longer than an hour!
All right!
Please keep on supporting me.
How's this?
No...we won't be on time.
What?! I can't write
any faster than this.
Everybody!
The autographs after this will be
changed to handprints from Full Moon.
- What?
B-But that's not good.
The fans who took
the trouble to come here...
Oh no! Is this really bad?
That's so cool.
I'm envious.
I wanted that one instead.
It's valuable and cuter
than a regular autograph.
Here.
Here... Here... Here... Here... Here...
Everybody, please keep on
supporting me.
- Of course!
We were somehow able to
make up for the lost time.
I'm glad everybody
was happy about it too.
Hey, hey.
Today's guest is Miss Full Moon,
but it's almost time to say good bye.
Now, can you tell us about
your ambition from this point on?
Yes, I want to do even better on
the songs and release more CDs.
So it seems that you have plans for
live concert performances as well?
Yes.
Concerts?! Oh no!
I forgot to give her this!
Yeah, I really do want to
directly meet the fans?!
Full Moon! Full Moon!
Mr. Akiba.
Hey, what are you thinking?
We're on air!
Oh, I apologize...then.
Hey you!
Full Moon, here's the schedule
for the concerts!
I'm so sorry!
Well...I make that kind of mistake
a lot too, so please don't mind.
Thank you very much!
I'll work hard not to make
a mistake next time.
What is next?
Yes. It's a mini concert
at a department store.
I'm so sorry, Full Moon.
Mr. Akiba, this is...
Special concert hall will
be from next week.
Hey, it's Miss Full Moon.
I sincerely apologize!
Well, the baby was cute,
so I don't mind.
I'm glad that you would
say it in that way.
Aren't you hungry?
The weather is nice,
so let's have lunch here.
Here?
I used to be an adventurer.
I once climbed Chomoranma too.
Huh, that's incredible.
Maybe it's ready now?
Wow, let's eat.
It's so good.
That's great. There is plenty,
so please eat a lot.
Yeah. But why did you
become a manager?
It's my dream!
When you're in an adventure,
you often face tough situations.
In those kinds of time,
music gives me great power.
It's my dream to foster a person who can
sing songs that can give courage like that.
Full Moon.
Isn't it Miss Full Moon's dream
to become a first-rate singer?
Dream...
That's not the only thing.
It's such nice weather.
That's true...feels great.
W-What's wrong, Mr. Akiba?
We're about to be late
for our next job.
Oh no! What is it next?!
A meeting with Mr. Takasu.
Are we in trouble?!
This is bad! Really bad.
We have to go quickly.
All right!
Only thing we can do is...
Let's dash, Full Moon!
Full Moon, turn to the right
at the next corner.
Yes!
To reduce the time, we fly over
three white lines on the crosswalk!
Okay!
We fly over three tiles here too!
Let's go by flying
over five of them!
All right!
Great, Full Moon.
Let's keep on going this way!
Okay.
Now, we'll take a shortcut here!
We fly over three steps here!
Okay!
We're almost there, Full Moon.
Okay! Here, we'll go.
- Last spurt!
Well, we tried our best.
I've run...this much...
for the first time in my life.
Mr. Takasu.
Late! You're tardy by an hour.
- We apologize.
We are late,
it is my fault.
No, it was because of me too.
I'm sorry.
No, no!
It's my responsibility.
No, mine too!
- No! Mine too!
- It doesn't matter whose it is!
We're going to hurry up
and do the meeting!
- Yes.
And...so, I think it's about time
to release the first album.
Yay, an album.
I have about 30 demo songs,
but would you like to listen to them?
Yes.
What? Come on, come on.
Damn it.
Something's wrong, I wonder why
the sound doesn't come out?
It has been in a bad shape lately.
Sorry, but it might not
be possible today.
What?! That's horrible.
No good.
Wait here for a moment.
I wonder if it'll be fixed.
I'd like to listen to...the songs.
All right, I'll fix it.
What? Ah, Mr. Akiba,
shouldn't we leave it alone?
Mr. Takasu will yell at us.
It'll be fine.
I'm good at video games.
Mr. Akiba, I think it's different
from a video game.
What?
Something's wrong.
What the?
Hey, what are you doing?!
Ah, well...I mean.
All of the data for
the songs are erased.
- What?!
What have you done?!
That was the data
for the first album.
I-I'm so sorry!
Sorry, Mr. Takasu.
Mr. Akiba did not do it on purpose!
How can he do
such a thing on purpose!
First of all, how can an incompetent guy
like you work as a manager!
If a piece of garbage like you is around,
it brings trouble to everybody else,
so isn't it best to quit
as soon as possible?
Hurry up and leave,
you good for nothing!
Like Mr. Takasu said,
I might not be suited...as a manager.
That's not true at all.
No.
In fact, that is the case.
What?
I'm always like this.
When I'm entrusted with
somebody's management,
I jump the gun...and in the end,
it's mostly blunders.
This time,
I was determined to get a fresh start
in working with Miss Full Moon,
but it ends up being like this.
It might be time to quit.
What are you saying?!
Mr. Akiba, you're working
with all of your effort!
Even just now,
you did that because I was saying
how I wanted to listen to the songs.
In addition, I had many new experiences
today by being with Mr. Akiba.
What?
I haven't had that many opportunities
to play outside until now.
But today,
it was really fun because
I ate a meal like at a camp and
ran more than I've ever had.
Full Moon...
So stop saying that kind of stuff
and why don't we try our best?
Okay? Mr. Akiba...
Thank you very much.
Huh?! What is that?
No matter what you say,
that replacement manager is too clumsy!
He's like Ms. So-and-so.
W-What do you mean?!
I'm also trying my best in
doing this Shinigami work.
That person probably also fails
despite doing his best.
Yes!
I understand, I understand.
Hello...
Oh! Mr. Akiba?
Thank you very much.
Sorry about all those
things yesterday.
Ah...I thought a lot about it...
but I've decided to quit my job
and go home to the countryside.
What are you saying?!
Please don't say that you're quitting.
We can both go and
apologize to Mr. Takasu.
No...like Mr. Takasu was saying,
I should quit being a manager.
I just bring trouble to everybody
if I am around.
If I don't head towards the station,
I'll be late for the bullet train.
Full Moon,
thank you for everything.
Hey! Mr. Akiba?
Mr. Akiba!
Hello, hello, Mr. Akiba!
What's wrong?
Mr. Akiba is going to quit!
If I don't get to the station soon,
I'm going to be late for the bullet train,
and Mr. Takasu is going to be angry.
Oh, what should I do?
Takuto!
All right! I got it, so calm down!
Mr. Akiba...
I have to hurry.
Oh yeah, in this kind of situation...
To reduce the time, we fly over
three white lines on the crosswalk!
Okay!
We fly over three tiles here too!
Now, we'll take a shortcut here!
We fly over three steps here!
Okay!
Mr. Akiba!
Mr. Akiba...
Mr. Akiba.
F-Full Moon!
Mr. Akiba, please don't quit.
You came all the way here,
just to tell me that?!
Yes. You can't quit, Mr. Akiba.
No, if I'm around,
I'll just cause everyone trouble.
I've already decided.
But have you given up
your dream of nurturing a singer?!
Mr. Akiba.
The train for Akita is
about to depart from track.
Well, I'll be going now.
Mr. Akiba, please don't give up.
You might have sad moments
until your dream comes true,
but nothing will remain
if you give up!
Mr. Akiba!
Don't give up. Mr. Akiba!
There he goes.
It seems like many things happened
while I was away, Mitsuki.
Mr. Takasu had lots
of trouble as well,
but it was lucky because the songs
remained on a different computer.
What? Then you're saying
the songs are not erased?
No, by and large.
Thank goodness.
What?
Then Mr. Akiba doesn't
need to quit the company.
Hey, Mitsuki. Can you come
along with me today?
Huh?
Okay, we're here.
Ms. Oshige, what is this?
The store that sells
Full Moon merchandise.
What? Mine?!
Manager, about
the wiring over here...
I actually want to place
the display at this spot,
so please have the power source
go around on the opposite side
and also increase
the number of switches.
Yeah, got that.
Mr. Akiba...
Full Moon! Ms. Oshige!
Welcome! You two are
the first customers.
Mr. Akiba, I thought you went
back to the countryside.
And you're a store manager?
What Full Moon said was right.
I shouldn't give up.
That's why I'll start again from
the beginning as a store manager here.
My best regards, Full Moon.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Please allow me to
continue supporting you.
Thank you...I'll work hard too.
Isn't this great, Tact?!
Huh? What is?
I'm talking about that girl.
She's about to experience
some summer love.
I'm rooting for her!
You idiot!
That'll never happen!
She'd never fall for
some suspicious guy like that!
You're jealous, Tact!
That's terrible!
You already have me!
Shut up!
It's not like that!
Next time on Full Moon:
"First Kiss!"
- Don't miss it!