Good morning, Nagi.
Good morning.
It got cold all of a sudden.
Well, October is going to be over soon.
Halloween.
That's right, Halloween decorations have started to show.
True.
It feels like this has established itself in Japan out of the blue.
Right.
Aren't you scared?
What?
Nagi?
Halloween means ghosts.
Wouldn't you be scared?
Not really. It's not like they're real ghosts.
You see, I'm just slightly  bothered by scary things.
Slightly bothered?
Just slightly.
Well, Nagi, you have something that bothers you too, right?
No, nothing of the sort.
Good morning!
Get your spirits up!
G-Good morning.
Good morning!
Good morning...
Wasn't there nothing that bothered you?
Bad with hot-blooded people
Let's be energetic and do our best!
Well, I can't take that either.
Good morning!
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Present
Ah, Nagi-chan, Yuuko-chan, good morning!
Good morning...
You two look really exhausted. What happened?
Hot-blooded... In the morning...
Nagi-chan?
Everyone has something that bothers them.
What's up with this?
What is it?
There's some strange stuffed animal on my desk.
What's this? It's creepy!
For real.
Maybe this is some Halloween thing? Like "trick or treat"?
A prank? More like harassment. It really feels like it.
Shouldn't you throw it away?
But wouldn't doing that get you cursed even more?
What do I do? I can't tell them that I made it.
What? You made that stuffed animal, Run?
S-Sorry for bashing it so much.
Never mind. I heard that you liked this and I wanted to show it to you.
Animals are hard to make. It doesn't look like one at all.
No, it's really well-made!
Yeah, it is.
Especially the look of these... ears... or horns?
Or how the eyes are goggly-I mean endearing...
And the way the mouth is open is really characteristic!
It is, it is.
But what is this thing...
...that I'm supposed to like?
Doesn't it look similar?
Sure.
A Halloween party? Why, all of a sudden?
There was a lot going on this morning, and we ended up talking about it.
I've been interested in Halloween for a while.
Tomorrow's Saturday. Let's all get together, make snacks and eat them!
I can hardly wait.
What kind of snacks? Cookies? Or cake, perhaps?
I'll pass.
Nagi-chan, don't you enjoy baking snacks?
Baking has all kinds of precise measurements, and that doesn't suit me.
Besides, I'm on a diet.
It'll be fine. I'll calculate the calories for you.
Really?
Sure.
Well, I'll join the eating part.
Done.
What about you?
I think I'll be late.
I see.
I'll come over to eat around the time you finish.
I don't mind.
Then I'll come later too, together with her.
All right!
I guess the two of us will be baking, Yuuko-chan.
Yeah, is there something I should bring?
My mum is the one who usually does the baking, so I guess we have everything.
I see. I'm really looking forward to it.
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Yeah!
Run, what are you drawing?
This? It's for the diary exchange with Tooru.
We're playing picture-drawing shiritori!
What does it look like?
Another one of the stuffed animal incidents!
Is this even an animal?
It sort of looks like a bug...
I guess it's a little hard to see.
I'll give you a hint.
They're eaten a lot.
It's food?
That's almost giving it away.
It's a zebra, right?
That's right, Tooru!
A zebra?
That's Tooru for you.
T-That's a zebra?
Is my brain too inflexible?
Nagi, you're over-thinking it.
It's nice that she gave it to me, but this kinda freaks me out.
You're not going home yet, Nagi?
No, I'm going.
Speaking of which, do you want to meet up before we go to Run-chan's place tomorrow?
That'd make things easier, I guess.
Let's meet up at the north gate of the station then. The one near the shopping district.
Got it.
T-Tooru, what's that?
This? Run-chan gave it to me.
I know that.
Then what about it?
What kind of animal is it supposed to be?
Hmm, Nagi, you don't know?
This really gets to me. I wonder why.
To tell the truth, I got one too.
It's big!
This is unfair.
Please give it to me!
No way, this is mine.
Don't be like that.
Not gonna happen.
You're being unfair!
I'm not being unfair.
Sorry for the wait!
Let's all go home.
We'll be ready in a bit, so please wait.
Sure. Hurry up though.
Speaking of which, what's your favourite animal, Nagi?
You're not going to use this for the picture-drawing shiritori with Run, are you?
No, I was just curious.
Well, small animals are cute, so I like them.
Squirrels for example.
Squirrels sure are cute.
That said, I haven't told you what this is yet.
I'm done.
Tell me, tell me! I beg of you, tell me!
Squirrels sure are cute.
Hey, Tooru.
They're small animals.
What are they talking about?
Tell me.
Who knows?
I'm home.
This is creepy after all.
This way?
Trick or treat!
There you go.
Thank you.
These shops are all in the mood for Halloween.
We were supposed to meet somewhere around here...
I told you, "Trick or treat!"
Ah, Nagi...
Give us...
...sweets!
I told them I wasn't from the store, but these midgets...
I have no sweets.
Tooru, are those your casual clothes?
Eh?
Do we have to go through this shopping district to get to Run's place?
You've never gone this way?
I get the feeling we took a different route the last time I went.
Correct. This is a little bit of a detour.
Look.
Run-chan said they're going to make snacks, so I'm getting spares.
So you're buying them here? And you already know she failed...
Hey, Tooru-chan.
Hello.
Seems like you're in a good mood.
Look here, take these.
Thank you.
Tooru-chan, look here, these are delicious.
Take them.
Thank you, grandma.
That's right, she did mention she got a lot of stuff from the people in the shopping district.
Tooru-chan, there you go.
Nice of you to show up.
Use this as a bag.
She's not buying anything at all!
What's up all of a sudden?
I'm going into the book store since we still have time.
I see. There's a book I want to buy too. Good timing.
Hey, Tooru, look at-
Nagi?
One hour later
The girl on this manga looks like Yuuko.
Isn't that an adult manga?
Hey, you're right. They totally look alike.
Look, it's a collection of short stories, but the heroine looks almost the same every time.
The person who drew this would probably pay a lot of money for a picture of Yuuko.
Let's buy the thing.
Let's bake!
Yuuko-chan, do you want to wear an apron?
Will you lend it to me?
Your mum really has everything you need for baking.
There are lots of cute cookie cutters, too!
So we can just go ahead and use everything we have here?
Yeah, she said we could.
Really? I can't wait.
So what do we start with?
Wait a second.
These: pancakes!
Even though it's Halloween?
Yeah, I'm in the mood for pancakes right now!
I-I see.
Oh yeah! The other day, I split an egg with just one hand.
Watch this.
The other day... with one hand!
Run, let's move on!
I guess that's about it.
This should be fine.
Then I'll put it in the oven.
You do that.
Run!
Thank...
...goodness!
That hurt...
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry. I'll make them again!
It's all right, no need to rush!
Even though I screwed up, why are you the one victimised?
Oh, I don't mind.
That's right, I should be the victim!
There!
What now?
Wanna take a bath?
Yeah.
Yuuko-chan, you have a nice figure.
Not really.
It's because you have a pet, right?
What was it? It's something like a surname...
Tapeworms!
Again?
It's the power of the tapeworm!
I keep telling you they're not pets and I don't have them!
Running around like this in other people's homes...
I'll put your clothes in the living room.
I should've taken them with me into the bathroom.
"Dynamite!"
You were here already?
"What are you doing in other people's homes?"
"I don't remember raising you to be this dirty!"
What? What are you talking about?
"What's with these lewd breasts?"
What? Nagi, what is going on?
She's been practising all this time for you. Listen to her.
Practising what?
What kind of manga is that?
We found an adult manga with the heroine looking exactly like you.
Eh? No, an adult manga?
There, read it.
No, stop it!
I don't like adult stuff.
What is this?
No way...
So she says, but she's really reading it.
Unbelievable...
Yuuko-chan, what happened?
What is it, Tooru?
Run-chan, you can't.
She seems to have taken a liking to it.
Hey, you brought lots of snacks!
Tooru got all of them for free in the shopping district.
You're quite something, Tooru.
You saved me, though. I wanted to make pancakes for everybody.
Pancakes from Run-chan...
I failed.
Don't worry about it.
But I really wanted to eat pancakes with all of you.
Just make them next time.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's get this party started, then.
Let's have a toast!
Should we toast to the ghosts, since it's Halloween?
You're right... Wait, we can't do that!
Wait a second.
Let's make some now.
Make them again? We don't have ready-made pancakes anymore.
Not a problem.
Found it.
We can make them with this.
Crazy love cake!
Everyone ready?
Yeah.
totteoki no jikan ga yatte kimashita Are U Ready?
This very special time has arrived! Are you ready?
Eggs!
There I go...
tokimeku yo Cook Girl jouzu ni tsukutte egao sakasemashou
Get excited, Cook Girl. Cook it well and make people smile.
Is the pan ready?
nanoni danzen taberu ha sengen toka
Even though you claim to be more on the eating side.
saboccha dame (*_*) Let's make!
No slacking off, let's make something!
watashitachi dake no supesharu
Our very own speciality.
reigai nante aru wake ga nai!? joshi wa rawa suuiitsu
There's no way this is an exception. Girls love sweets.
ichi nichi kurai karori keisan wasureta furishichae!
It's just today; pretend you forgot to calculate the calories.
It's ready!
We're done!
chotto kurai misuttatte Good shippai wa seikou no mama
Even a small mistake is all right. Failure can still be success.
Looks delicious.
We all made it together. Now let's eat it!
kimochi ga daiji sou deshou? okoge mo aiseru kibun yo
It's the thought that counts, right? I'm in the mood to love even the burnt parts.
Let's eat!!
It looks delicious!
Crazy love cake!
It is!
Very good.
Lady chomp cake!
I'm glad.
Crazy love cake!
You've got something stuck to your cheek.
Yuuko, there you go, say "Ah".
Stop that.
I'm full.
Nagi, what about dieting?
Haven't you calculated the calories?
Don't worry, I kept the sugar to a minimum.
Don't scare me like that.
Tooru, let's all clean up together.
Tooru's getup looks like cosplay. It's cute.
She got into trouble with some kids because of it.
Isn't that nice, Tooru?
They pulled on her clothes and stuff.
You should've just handed out sweets like last year.
Tooru really likes children, so she-
I told you not to talk about that!
What's wrong, Tooru?
How unexpected of you.
You're mistaken!
Tooru really likes children!
No!
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
What's up with this subtitle?
Um... A beverage?
Isn't it sad to act like you don't know even though you do?
Shut up. This is a promise!
Yutaka, I wonder if it's about time we put your name in the subtitle?
I think we'd be finished talking in no time, if so.
Next time on A Channel: Carbonic Acid.
Next Time!
Carbonic Acid
Okay then, how about "Yutaka and Toorun"-
Hey, I'm here, so let's make it the three of us!