-OP-
-ED-
I will not tolerate any evil!
I'll make sure you end up in prison!
Would the prosecutor indict him or not?
Only ten days remained until the end of Mario's detention period.
Listen, guys.
We don't have time.
I'll need you guys to work in two groups.
Joe and Cabbage.
Soldier and Turtle.
To make an impression on the prosecutor,
we need a written statement, no matter what.
We need one of the groups to succeed.
We absolutely must have a statement.
Soldier and Turtle approached Kogure Yoshitaka,
the man Mario beat up.
On the other hand, Cabbage and Joe...
made their ways to Shonan Women's University.
Yokohama District Public Prosecutors Office
In July, 1955,
you violently assaulted your homeroom teacher, who didn't fight back,
inflicting injuries that took three months to heal.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Your reason?
Why did you beat him?
Or are you a piece of trash who beats people without cause?
No.
Stop!
Minakami.
Minakami Mario!
Well, are you?
I...
didn't have a motive.
I heard that Mario beat up his teacher to save a girl named Yoshida Junko.
Tell her what's happening to Mario,
and get her to write a statement in his defense.
Minakami is in detention?
Please, we want you to save him.
Me?
Please write down what happened that day and sign it.
That day?
Mario used violence to save you from your teacher...
who was about to violate you.
Is that what Minakami said?
No.
He'd never tell anyone about that.
One of our buddies dug up the secret.
I'm sorry.
But...
Why didn't Mario tell anyone about it?
He saved someone, right?
He could've said what happened without going into details.
Cabbage.
Cabbage!
I haven't even told my parents.
Stop.
Stop!
Minakami...
Please, stop.
Nothing... happened.
Nothing...
happened to me!
I...
wasn't about to be violated.
I already had been.
I'm sorry.
I can't give a statement.
She'd already been raped.
No wonder Mario kept quiet and went to disciplinary school.
Man, what an idiot.
He's too noble for his own good.
But...
that's why we've gotta do something.
Yeah.
I'm going to go ask her again.
Cabbage?
I'll do whatever I can!
I hate that teacher.
That asshole teacher.
And I hate myself for not being able to save her.
I can't talk about...
what happened that day.
If that's what's needed to get out of here,
I'd rather spend seven years in prison and tell no one.
Sign: Toni's Bar
I see.
So that's what happened.
But we haven't given up yet.
Cabbage is going to try and convince her.
Good.
Now, we're just waiting on Soldier and Turtle.
God dammit!
I'm never coming to this stupid place again!
Kogure Yoshitaka, I presume?
We'd like a few words with you.
Who the hell are you?
What?!
You want me to save that kid?
Mario's remorseful about his actions.
Remorseful?
Like hell I'd write a dumb statement.
Can you say you were completely blameless?
Are you shitting me?!
I'm the one with the broken bones!
What broken bones?!
You look perfectly fine!
Say that again?!
We beg you.
At this rate, he'll end up in prison for seven years.
Please!
Show him some mercy.
So basically...
I just need to sign this?
Yes!
Are you kidding me?
I'm not signing anything.
You asshole-
Stop, Turtle.
I heard Mario let you hit him twice at the beginning.
What are you trying to say?
If Mario took two hits,
I'll take three.
Sign: Shonan Women's University
What's wrong, Kogure?
You think you can beat me with those lousy punches?
Let me tell you, I'm not a softy like Mario.
If you can't knock me down,
maybe you'll end up somewhere else than the hospital.
You...
Now, then...
You've got one more shot!
You've made a fool out of me!
Now I'm serious.
Hey, that's not fair!
I see.
Can't beat me without a weapon, right?
Right, Kogure?
Give it to me, you coward!
Soldier!
How's that?
Got you good, right, shithead?
You asshole-
Wait, Turtle.
Hey, Kogure...
If I report this case to the police,
what'll happen to you?
And let me point out that I haven't laid a finger on you.
It's not just a fight now, is it?
Even without your prior record, you'll spend two years in jail.
You know...
jail is like hell.
Now, sign this.
I'll save Mario no matter what.
If my body isn't enough,
I'll even use a bazooka or a carbine.
I didn't become a soldier just for show.
Soldier...
Don't worry.
I won't let this report go to waste.
Take care of Soldier.
Yeah.
I heard you're a friend of Minakami Mario?
Yes, I'm Nomoto Ryuji.
Nomoto?
I brought a statement in his defense.
Take a seat.
What the hell is this?
Did you threaten the victim to get this?
No, that's an actual-
Figures.
Takes scum to know scum.
That written report is an-
Do you seriously think a coerced statement will help you?
Get lost!
We didn't lose blood in the war to save scum like you!
It's true.
In the public's mind, we may be scum.
However, we didn't choose to become this way.
My father was KIA in Manchuria.
My mother did things that can never be mentioned to feed me and my siblings.
Because...
you people started the war!
Can't you...
Can't you at least listen to us?
No matter what you say, a crime is an injustice.
I will not tolerate any evil!
Mario doesn't go around beating people up for no reason!
Even though he broke out of disciplinary school because he couldn't do his time?
Do you know why he broke out?
Of course you wouldn't.
You wouldn't know the true face of that school...
or those hellish days.
The guards hit us like we were sandbags,
and the doctor paid them to make us into his playthings.
When our best friend learned that,
they tried to kill him.
They tried to kill Bro...
a man who risked his life for his friends and gave us the courage and hope to live!
They tried to kill him!
That's why Mario broke out of the school with Bro on his back!
What justice?!
In the end, your stupid definition of justice killed Bro!
I won't believe such a ridiculous story.
You have the power to see for yourself if it's ridiculous or not!
Excuse me.
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
I'll call the guards!
Please!
Please, save him!
His heart is like stone, I must soften it!
I'll do anything to make him see things our way.
Adult society isn't the only thing the war ruined.
We also have hearts!
We have feelings!
Please...
Please listen to my words!
Mario went into the disciplinary school for a very good reason!
What reason?
That's...
That's!
I'll tell you the reason.
You've suffered quite a lot.
Back then, Minakami didn't tell anyone about me,
and sacrificed himself by going to that school.
I see what happened very clearly now.
May I ask you one question?
Yes?
What made you tell me about this?
I don't know.
I was just envious, I think.
Envious?
I don't have any friends who would go this far for me.
But...
Minakami has five of them.
Five wonderful friends.
Is that a good enough reason?
I also had an irreplaceable friend.
A friend I spent just three months with, in Manchuria.
Yoshida Junko, thank you for coming in.
Nomoto.
I met your son today.
The son you were so proud of.
But guess what?
My son's a genius.
He'll do something revolutionary one day.
He's called Ryuji.
Nomoto Ryuji.
Better not forget it.
Indictment Date
Under normal circumstances, this case would be reckoned a serious crime.
However, taking into account a statement by the victim concerning this case,
and the defendant's visible remorse for his actions,
we will consider this a summary offense.
A summary offense?
You'll be fined 800 yen.
You can go home once you pay the fine downstairs.
That's all.
Wait a minute!
What do you mean, exactly?
If you pay the fine, you're free.
Now, hurry on home.
Excuse me.
Minakami.
You've chosen your friends well.
Minakami Mario Summary Order: The defendant is fined 800 yen.
Short on change, mister?
Turtle.
If you need a loan, maybe I can help.
An exclusive service for today only.
You can pay back 1% a day.
What are you doing?!
Go pay up and become a free man.
We're all waiting.
All of you?
Hey!
He's back!
Man, I wish I was there.
I heard you got on your knees.
Shut up!
Oh, Mario.
The bar master asked if you could return to work tomorrow.
Mario?
You idiots...
What am I supposed to do?
Tell me, Uncovered.
How in the world...
do I pay you all back for this?
You dumbass.
We're friends, aren't we?
Okay! Let's party!
Let's go, guys.
Bro...
"If it's a huge debt, spend a lifetime paying it back."
"Your bonds will last forever."
In his heart, Mario heard Bro telling him those words.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Young passion.
Emotions burst.
They each walk their own roads.