Yeah!
You're the one that I like...
You don't have to give me an answer right away.
I just wanted to let you know that there's somebody here
who's in love with you.
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Richie, you're stoppin' again...
Be quiet.
I'm going to come back in here with a cool improv riff.
It don't mean a thing if you don't actually play.
Looks like you're havin' a good time, Sen-boy.
Mind if I sit in?
Brother Jun!
Oh, you're early!
Actually, I already mentioned this to Ritsu's dad,
but I've got some good news.
Would you cats be up for playin' jazz in front of an audience?
The bar I worked at nearby asked us to do a Christmas performance for 'em.
It's a bar for foreigners and the U.S. troops stationed here, so if we're gonna do this,
we'd better put some spunk into it.
Well? Wanna give it a shot?
Yes!
Good!
We got just a month before Christmas, so that doesn't give us much time!
What'll we play?!
That reminds me, Sen.
Isn't your birthday on Christmas?
Yeah. I'm almost sixteen!
We'd better do a decent performance.
It's been a while. So for starters, let's play some together.
Outta sight!
This'll be our first session as a quartet since summer vacation!
One, two, a one-two-three!
Come on, Richie, ain't you gonna play?
What's wrong, Kaoru?
Once in a while, this guy just freezes up.
Kaoru's got a classical background,
so maybe he's shootin' for perfection.
Don't be thinkin' you need to do anything complicated at first.
All you really have to do is hit the keys.
That's plenty lively for some improv.
Try rememberin' how it felt last summer when you jumped in and went wild.
You said it, Brother Jun! Right on!
Go for broke, Bill Evans!
Oh, he looks like 'im!
Never thought I'd meet Bill Evans in a place like this!
Now I think we can expect you to play great!
By the way, what were you doing the other day with Yurika?
Huh?
In the back of the art room.
Y-You saw that?
So are you two already having that kind of relationship?
What do ya mean?
Don't play dumb.
You can't tell me nothing happened when you were dressed like that!
Don't be a dope!
She just asked me to model for her painting.
No! Tilt your head more!
Gaze at that twig lovingly!
I didn't get what it was about,
but it was over before I knew it.
Oh, is that all?
Huh? Why am I so relieved?
Oh. That must be it...
Come to think of it, she told me to be her model every week from now on.
Huh. Sounds like there's hope for you yet.
What will you do next time
if she does something like that to you?
Why, you!
What the hell d'you think you're doin'?!
Get back here, Richie!
Hey, who is that Nishimi guy, really?
Maybe the "secret boss?"
I heard your nephew got the top score on the final exam.
How wonderful.
And he's not just a prodigy, he can play the piano, too!
Yes, though I'm not fond of his new habit of coming home late every day.
Oh, you worry too much!
After all, he's the only male heir left in the Nishimi family.
I have to make sure he maintains his grades
so he can become a doctor or a lawyer.
Dad... Hurry home, would you?
Even though I'm surrounded by people here,
I'm always so alone.
Furuya Musical Shop
That reminds me, Sen.
Isn't your birthday on Christmas?
I don't see him buying a new pair for himself.
Maybe I'll get them for him, from one jazz musician to another...
K-Kaoru?!
Ritsu...
O-Oh my gosh! It looks like we both had the same idea.
Oh, no, this is...
Sentaro is a lucky guy.
Oh, I know!
We'll each buy one stick and give them to him as a pair.
Let's do that, okay?
This is a strange development...
Maybe it's okay if things just stay this way?
I wonder what Ritsu thinks of me...
You okay? Do you have a cold?
No. Winter in Kyushu is pretty cold.
I wouldn't be surprised if it started to snow.
Oh, it's not that cold!
It rarely snows here in December.
Look!
Kaoru, how did you know?!
This is amazing! Like in a movie!
It's beautiful!
Oh. It melts right away.
This won't stick.
Look, Kaoru!
It's—
M-Merry Christmas...
Cut it out, Kota!
You're gonna pay for that!
Ri'ko!
Who are you?!
How dare you make Ri'ko cry?!
It's Richie, from when we had watermelon!
Oh, what're you doin' here?
N-Nothing really...
Bro! He just made Ri'ko—
What about Ri'ko?
I-It's a misunderstanding.
He's the last person I wanted to see right now.
Bro, I have to pee...
All right, how 'bout we all race home?
The winner gets to have the biggest piece of cake!
Ready? Go!
Wait!
Look at 'em go.
You wanna join us for cake too, Richie?
Of course not.
Oh yeah, your family is rich.
Bet you have a fancy cake waitin' for you at home.
Oh, shut up.
Somebody who takes being surrounded with a loving family for granted
will never understand that there are people who can live in a big house
and still have no place in it!
Am I jealous of him?
Because he has one the thing I wish for more than anything,
but can never have?
Go home!
Your family's waiting for you, aren't they?!
When I'm around you, it only makes me feel more miserable!
Hey! Max Roach!
These are some really nice sticks.
Thank Ritsu.
I just laid out half the money for them.
Oh, so one's from Ri'ko and one's from you, huh?
That's pretty clever.
Wha—
Come with me!
What?!
Just do it!
No! Let go of me!
Ow!
What're you doing?!
Hurry up!
Ow!
Damn it...
W-What?
Ritsu...
Why is that kid next to her in all these pictures?
It's easy to tell when you see me as a little kid, right?
That I got mixed blood...
Richie, I'm one of those that ain't got a place in the house, too.
Ever since I was born...
Hey, America!
Can't you speak English?!
Don't look!
Sentaro!
Mother! Aren't Yasuko's things in that box?!
I don't care, she's no daughter of mine!
Seducing an enemy soldier, bearing his child, and then
abandoning her shame here before taking off!
I don't remember giving birth to a daughter like that!
What's wrong, Sentaro? Where's Grandma?
So you didn't see anything either, huh, kid?
Sentaro, we believe this is a memento
that your mother left behind when she left.
Sentaro, the rosary isn't a necklace.
Take it off.
You're always wearin' this thing.
Let me borrow it a minute.
Don't touch it!
Hey, that's him.
The Kawabuchi kid who went nuts yesterday...
Sentaro!
You won't have any friends left if you keep getting into fights!
I didn't have any to begin with.
My dad lost his job around then,
stayin' home and gettin' trashed every day.
Couldn't even look me in the eye no more.
Eventually, though, he found a job in another prefecture.
He said he was gonna live an' work there a while.
I thought it was my fault.
He's still workin' there now, hasn't come back home in all these years.
It's fun at home, never a dull moment.
But once in a while, I start to wonder
if it's really okay for me to be there.
I said too much...
I feel terrible.
I was so convinced this guy had it all...
Those things I said to him...
It's like we're kids playing around on an organ...
Sentaro!
Yeah?
What's up, Kaoru?
Let's practice some more.
Maybe even every day, 'til our gig...
Dummy! That goes without sayin'!
We gotta knock the socks off them Americans!
I get it.
This is the guy that Ritsu's in love with.
My love feels so cheap in comparison.
Since then, we put our all into every day's session.
Time flew and before we knew it, the day had come...
Our first time on stage.
Excuse me...
Foreign soldiers gather to drink here.
It's no place for a young lady like you.
I've come to listen to jazz. I was invited by a friend.
Oh, pardon me.
You're a respectable customer.
After you, young lady...
Stop calling me "young lady."
It feels like you're mocking me.
Yurika...
Ritsuko, long time no see.
All right, just play like we practiced at first,
but feel free to go crazy with it once you get in the groove.
Let's hang loose and have fun.
One, two, one-two-three-four...
What's wrong with him?
He's stiff...
Is it because Yurika's watching?
Wake up!
Pipe down already!
What's he sayin', Richie?
He says he doesn't like black jazz.
That we should play white jazz.
Huh?
What kinda segregation is that?!
What are you tryin' to say, old man?!
Don't do it, Sen-boy! Suck it up!
You can't get through to a drunk like that.
Just ignore him.
Hmph. I can't play like this!
Kaoru...
Can you play that one song?
"But Not for Me."
Oh... I think so.
At this rate, the party's gonna end on a sour note.
But maybe we can at least lighten up the mood.
Just the two of us?
Don't worry.
It'll just be like we're playing for fun.
Brother Jun is amazing...
I can understand why Sentaro gets so excited every time he's back to town.
It's only natural to admire him...
Anyway, Brother Jun really surprised me!
You're the hero of the night, Brother Jun!
Oh, look at you, pretending you dunno what I'm talking about!
Damn it!
So frustrating!
Thanks to that jerk cuttin' in,
I didn't get to play even half of what we practiced!
But it was a good experience.
The unexpected is what makes jazz fun, isn't it?
Listen to you, soundin' off like an expert!
Cut it out!
Am I buggin' you?!
Um, young la—
I mean...
Yurika.
Yurika, huh?
And what shall I call you?
That's right. Sometimes life is like jazz,
and goes in an unexpected direction...
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change