My name is Mami Tomoe.
I'm a third year student who attends
Mitakihara Middle School just like you.
And I'm a Puella Magi who made a contract with Kyubey.
Another weird dream.
Morning, Madoka!
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 2     It would be really nice
Madoka, why did you come home late last night?
I was invited over to a friend's house.
Well, it's not like you have a curfew or anything,
but you should've come home before dinner.
Sorry.
So other people really can't see him.
What a pretty room!
Make yourselves at home. No one else lives here.
I wasn't really ready to have guests, though.
This is really good, Mami!
It's delicious!
Thank you.
Being chosen by Kyubey means you're involved in this.
I think we need to get some explanations out of the way.
Sure! What should I explain?
Sayaka, you have it backwards.
It's beautiful!
This is a Soul Gem.
They're created when a girl chosen by Kyubey forms a contract.
It's the source of your magic power and the emblem of the Puella Magi.
What kind of contract?
I can grant any single wish of yours.
Really?
Any wish?
The sky is the limit.
I'll make any miracle come true!
Hmm... fabulous riches... eternal youth... Chinese delicacies...
I don't know about the last one...
But the price is the Soul Gem.
If you have one, you have to fight against the witches.
Witches?
Say, Mom...
What if... Just what if...
If you could magically have any wish granted,
what would you--
I'd fire all but two of the staff.
Stupid president...
He should be retiring soon 'cause he sure isn't getting any younger,
but he's acting like he's not going anywhere.
What if you could be the president?
...that might work.
If I play my cards with Sales right,
Planning and Business will be mine,
and then I'll just have to deal with the baldy in Accounting...
I wonder...
Mom, you're scaring me...
So what's a witch?
How are they different from Puella Magi?
Well, you could say Puella Magi are made from wishes
whereas witches are made from curses.
The way Puella Magi shower hope around them, witches spread despair.
And they're very dangerous because normal people can't see them.
Worry and doubt.
Strong anger and hatred.
They bring those seeds of disaster into the world.
It's quite possible that most motiveless murder and suicide cases
were caused by witches' curses.
They turn into a formless malice and infect humans from within.
So how come no one notices these dangerous things running around?
Witches hide inside magical barriers
and don't show themselves to humans.
The maze-like place you wandered into before was one of those.
That was quite dangerous.
Normal people who enter don't usually come out.
Do you fight those scary things, Mami?
Yes. With my life.
I think you two should choose carefully.
Being chosen by Kyubey means
you can have any single wish granted,
but taking that is flirting with death.
Man, this is hard...
How about this.
Would you like to go on a witch hunt with me?
You can see what fighting a witch is like for yourself.
Then you can decide if you have a wish that's worth the risk.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Morni--
Morning, Sayaka!
Is something wrong, Sayaka?
Other people can't see him?
It seems like it.
Um...?
Nope, nothings up! Come on!
We can talk to each other just by thinking!
You mean we already have magical powers?!
Naw, I'm acting as a relay right now.
It sure helps keep this a secret, though!
This feels weird.
Did something happen to you two?
You've been giving each other strange looks...
No, we're just...
I mean...
Are you... letting your feelings be known by gazing at each other...?
Gosh! How could you become so intimate in just one day?
What happened yesterday?
No, that's not really...
Well, I guess a lot of things did happen...
But it's wrong!
You're both girls!
This is what they call the love that dare not speak its name!
You forgot your bag!
Hitomi's acting like you today.
What's that supposed to mean?
Is it okay for you to be here?
What do you mean?
Didn't we tell you? The girl from yesterday is in this class.
Isn't she going to try to kill you again?
I'll be safe at school. Mami's here too.
But Mami is a third year. Her class is over there.
That's all right. I can hear you just fine.
She's within telepathy range.
Um... Good morning.
I can take care of myself.
She won't attack with other students around anyway.
I guess it's okay, but...
Hmph. Speak of the devil...
So that transfer student's also a, whatchamacallit, Puella Magi?
I mean, like you.
Yes. That's clear.
She's quite powerful, too.
But isn't she supposed to be a good guy who fights witches?
Why did she start attacking Madoka?
She was actually trying to get me.
She wants to stop me from making more Puella Magi.
But why?
If we're all fighting witches, we're on the same team, right?
Not exactly.
With you around, there'd be more competition.
What? Why?
There are rewards for defeating a Witch.
So while Puella Magi can certainly work together,
they can also be in conflict.
So she's been picking a fight with Madoka
because she knew that Kyubey would talk to her?
So it seems.
Don't worry, Madoka.
If she tries to do anything to you, I'll smack her!
Mami will be there, so...
Indeed. I'll be there just in case.
Don't worry.
Just in case what?
So, as you've been studying,
when you write the person or thing doing
the action as the subject of the sentence,
it's called the "active voice".
The opposite, the "passive voice",
is when we say that something was done to B by A,
thus making the subject affected by the action.
Passive voice is identifiable by a to be verb and a past participle.
For example, if you write "he likes me..."
Hey, Madoka.
Did you think about your wish?
Not really. You?
No idea.
I figured I'd think of lots of stuff.
There's all kinds of things I want to have and do,
but I wouldn't bet my life on them.
They're not that important.
That's unusual.
Most people would consider themselves lucky.
I think we're just ignorant.
We are?
We're ignorant in bliss.
I don't think it's that unusual.
A wish you'd give your life for?
There are lots of people in the world with those.
We don't have wishes because we don't really know misfortune.
We're ignorant because we're spoiled.
Why us?
Don't you think it's unfair?
There are other people out there who want this.
Sayaka...
It's all right.
Back to finish us off?
That isn't why I came.
I tried to kill him before he contacted Madoka Kaname,
but now it's too late.
So? What will you do?
Are you going to become a Puella Magi?
I...
We don't have anything to say to you!
Do you remember what I told you yesterday?
Yeah...
Good.
I didn't want my warning to be wasted.
Homura!
Uhm... What did you wish for when you became a Puella Magi?
Sorry, Hitomi. We have something to do tonight.
Oh my. It's a secret, isn't it?
Um...
I'm so jealous...
You don't want me getting in your way, do you?
No, that's not...
Hey Akemi! Wanna stop by the cafe on the way home?
I'm sorry, but I have something to do.
Excuse me.
Now, this is your first hands-on Puella Magi lesson.
Let's be enthusiastic!
Are you ready?
I'm not sure what you mean by "ready",
but I brought this!
I figured it was better than nothing.
I'm glad you're prepared for battle.
Madoka, did you bring anything?
I-I brought...
I had some ideas for costumes...
Your enthusiasm is enough.
You win this one...
It's picking up the trail of the Witch from yesterday.
It'll lead us to the witch.
I just have to hold it like this and follow it.
That's really simple.
It's not changing at all.
Well, that witch got away.
The trail is a day old so it's not very strong.
So... If you had chased it yesterday...
I might've been able to take it out,
but saving you came first.
I'm sorry...
Don't be.
That's how you know Mami's a good guy!
Unlike that creepy transfer student!
She makes me sick!
Is she really evil?
Mami, do you have any idea where the witch would be?
The witch's curse is strongest with traffic accidents and injuries.
So I check at intersections and places
where a fight is likely to break out.
Otherwise, unpopular places that lend themselves to suicide.
And the worst place is the hospital.
The most vulnerable people are all gathered there.
Lives to be drained and minds to be influenced.
The pulse is getting brighter.
It must be close.
It's definitely here.
Mami, look!
A witch's kiss.
I knew it.
Is she...
Don't worry. She's just unconscious.
Come on.
I'll get you today.
Amazing!
It's not much, but at least it'll help protect you.
Don't stray too far away from me.
Okay!
Get away!
Are you afraid?
I'm just fine, thanks!
I'm scared, but... but...
Keep going! We're almost to the deepest part of the barrier!
Look. That's a witch.
It feels wrong...
You're going to fight that thing?
Don't worry. I won't lose.
Get back!
Mami!
I'm fine.
I can't make myself look too bad in front of my future allies!
Time to finish up.
Yellow Finale!
Did she win?
Amazing!
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch egg.
A-An egg?
If you're lucky, a witch might drop one for you.
Don't worry. It's perfectly safe like that.
It can actually be pretty useful.
You see how my Soul Gem is dimmer compared to yesterday?
Now that you mention it...
But if I use the Grief Seed...
See?
It got brighter!
And now my magic is renewed.
This is the reward I mentioned that you get for destroying a witch.
It has one more use in it.
You can have it.
Homura Akemi.
How did she...
What? You don't like sharing?
It was your prey.
Keep it to yourself.
I see. So that's your answer, huh?
Hmph! She really creeps me out!
I wish we could get along...
If only she thought so too.
I... where am I?
No... I... why did... how could...
It'll be all right.
You just had a bad dream, that's all.
Looks like love at first sight, eh?
It's too difficult for me to pick a wish I want granted.
I won't be able to decide anytime soon.
But Mami looks so cool when she's helping people.
I thought it would be really nice
if little old me could help others
in the same way.
Artist Hekiru Hikawa
Acting cool, but doing nothing.
Being sad and afraid,
but unable to tell anyone.
Just crying by yourself...
Being a Puella Magi is a hard job.
Episode 3     Nothing scares me anymore!
Nothing scares me anymore!