I know it!
All of these classes mean nothing.
It's all made up!
What are you saying?
I died without achieving anything!
I already know that!
What's the point of doing any of this?!
Do I go to Heaven if I get a good grade or something?
Someone tell me!
Answer me!
Crap. It's the Student Council President.
What timing to show up.
He's going to get killed.
Then stop whining and do something about it.
You have something you want to do, right?
What do you need to accomplish that?
What do you need right now?
Answer me!
One person needed courage to face the past.
Another person needed effort to make a dream come true.
Yet another person needed time and friends.
What about you?
Right now...
...it's the courage to stand up to you!
Okay. Look. You can do it.
You know the way from here.
If you feel more anger at the unfairness of it all or lose your way, come to the Student Council room.
I'll be there, waiting.
He's so cool!
He's way out of this world!
He's called Otonashi-san, right?
Does he have a girlfriend?
I heard he's waiting for someone.
He is?
Hey, quiet down!
Focus on your tests!
You, too! Take your seat already!