February 28, clear skies.
Today, I shall confess something that has been on my mind for some time now.
Kagami?
What is it? I am quite busy.
Um, well, like, you see, Kagami...
please be my friend!
Don't sleep on me!
I'm being serious here!
This sounds offensively annoying, so I want no part in it.
Listen!
I transferred smack dab in the middle of the semester!
What's more, everyone knows about the homeroom teacher's sister
because my stupid brother said,
"Poor Sasami here has been a shut-in all her life,"
giving me this pathetic backstory,
and now everyone stays away!
I used to be surrounded by loads of guards,
and I was always treated gently,
and the only conversations I had were short and stiff.
They were super polite, too.
That is certainly true.
My sincerest apologies, I had not considered it.
And you're even stiffer than they were!
All I want is a normal student life!
Plain and simple!
But there's not even a month left of my freshman year!
That is why your request for friendship puzzles me.
Well, if I can start by getting along with you or something, I'll be...
a cheerful,
happy-go-lucky girl!
Or I'll act like one at least,
and then hopefully everyone will finally come and talk to me!
If I may digress, I take slight issue with how "or something" was appended.
Please!
I've never had a single friend before.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Um, well, that's why.
So I want to do a friendship rehearsal with you!
I'm sure you know a lot about etiquette,
so I thought we could practice so I don't get overexcited and ruin it.
You'd be like a stand-in friend!
Do you realize that the things you say make others doubt your humanity?
Please, Kagami!
Understood. Let us start small.
Really?
Your first lesson will be to sympathize with your friend and allow her to sleep.
Yeah, 'cause we're friends! Loud and clear! Good night!
Silence is golden, so please be quiet.
Okay!
And so, I made my first friend.
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 5
I Just Haven't Tried Yet
Kagami, Kagami!
It's lunchtime!
Class is over, so wake up!
What is it now?
Let's eat lunch together.
Why should we?
Why, you ask?
Because we're friends!
My body can function without eating food.
And since sleep is allowed during
our lunch break, I do exactly that.
But you sleep even when it's not allowed!
It's not natural for two friends to spend lunch apart.
Then I shall move our desks together,
and you can eat your lunch or whatever you wish.
I shall sleep.
But that's even sadder!
And I didn't bring a lunch, so let's go to the cafeteria!
What a drag.
I mean, I will accompany you.
We are friends, after all.
Cafeteria #1
Go, Tsukuyomi!
You're our only hope!
Don't...
Don't lose!
Chef, more!
Right away!
Do not fail! You cannot fail!
Ms. Midget's a demon!
What are they doing?
My sister, too?
Whoops, he's dead.
Ah, now that's a lunch.
What are you doing, Sister?
An eat-off, what's it look like?
If ya win, everyone else'll foot your bills!
And what did you wager?
A peck on the cheek.
Men are, for the most part, complete and utter fools.
Kagami!
I'm so very sorry!
Are you all right?
Your apology is enough.
It was an accident.
I apologize, Sasami.
I must go to change my clothes,
so please eat lunch on your own.
Kagami...
Hey, Kagami.
What is it this time?
We're friends now,
so let's do something instead of sleeping all day.
Understood.
You may deepen our bonds of friendship however you choose.
I shall take a nap while you do.
What are you telling me to do?
Kagami, let's go to the bathroom!
Huh?
Are you not old enough to go to the bathroom yourself?
I don't mean that!
It's just that I've always wanted to walk to the bathroom hand in hand!
With a fellow female friend, of course.
Robots like myself have no need to go there.
Don't be like that!
You can just wait outside!
Then we won't be entering together.
Kagami...
We are friends... right?
I have no idea where we are going or why we are going there.
Don't worry!
If we just walk around, we'll show that I, indeed, do have friends!
Have I truly been reduced to your training wheels?
Oh?
What's wrong?
I stepped on something.
That explains the stimulation from my feet sensors.
It doesn't hurt?
I am fine.
I am not a human, so something like this—
Kagami!
would not cause me pain.
It seems that today is not my day.
Please expel your fluids on your own.
Sushi-Go-Round
Kurari Sushi
Sushi-Go-Round Kurari Sushi
And so, I started by making Kagami my friend.
Tea Boiling Instructions
Please be gentle, courteous, and quiet while boiling tea.
Please insert used plates here.
Inserting multiple plates at once will damage the machine, so cut that out.
Oh, salmon next.
Right away.
You know, Kagami gets pretty good grades given how much she sleeps.
Cut the rice in half.
Right away.
I hear she can memorize a textbook in one look.
She can even do seven-digit math in her head.
I hate wasabi.
Oh, right.
She's got some high specs.
I should study with her!
You're dead if that touches soy sauce.
Oh, right.
Mm, delicioso.
I heard she was just an emotionless robot at first.
Tea.
Right away.
She was created by an evil organization from a part of Tsurugi.
But Tsurugi took her back,
and emotions started growing inside her while they lived together.
Blow on it.
Sometimes she looks a bit cold,
so maybe her emotions haven't finished growing.
Or maybe...
Sasami.
What?
Why are you only talking about Kagami?
Why haven't you spoken a comment's or even a tweet's worth about me?
Huh?
Sasami,
please... please... please...
Please eat me!
I can be your favorite thing in the world!
Wha... wha... wha...
Don't put sushi on your nipples!
Sushi-Go-Round
Kurari Sushi
Sushi-Go-Round Kurari Sushi
Don't do such embarrassing stuff in public!
Right.
I'll do it at home next time.
Don't do it at home, either!
I'd die if you ever did it again!
Brother, you really—
What is it, Sasami?
Kagami!
Are you okay, Kagami?
What happened?
Oh, it is you two.
Are you on your way home?
Don't you have bigger problems?
I'll call an am—
Do not worry.
I am built sturdier than you are,
so I can heal such wounds immediately.
What happened?
I... was only taking a nap.
Talk to me!
We're friends!
It does not concern you.
Our friendship as you requested it only exists inside school, correct?
I was never more than a stand-in until you could acquire real friends.
I do not know what you have misunderstood,
but your clingy nature is quite bothersome.
Kagami...
Kagami!
March 13
Six days until closing ceremony
Um, Kagami?
Kagami?
What business do you have?
Well, I've got these movie tickets...
We could go, if you want...
I am sorry, but I have cleaning duty today.
Six days until closing ceremony
What would be a good day for you?
Maybe we could hang out?
We don't have to see a movie.
I am sorry.
May I decline for the time being?
Six days until closing ceremony
Um, am I annoying?
No.
Neither my lifestyle nor my existence
are impacted in the slightest by your presence.
Six days until closing ceremony
Now then, see you tomorrow.
Forget it...
Just forget it!
Six days until closing ceremony
Dear Sasami,
I'll be late due to
a staff meeting.
Kamiomi
Really, Yagami?
I wanted to talk to you.
Ask whatever you like.
We are friends.
That's great!
So what do you do for fun?
Stop it...
Just stop it!
No surprise.
There's no way I could be normal.
I could never fit in.
I shouldn't have bothered leaving home.
Listen baddie, over here!
The clapping means you're near!
Gotcha!
You smell like Sacchin!
Dinnertime!
Don't hog her, Satou!
Eat me too!
Don't tickle me there!
I'm defeated!
But I'm the weakest of the baddies!
If you beat me, the other baddie generals will...
Huh?
I smell Mamarin.
Mamarin!
Guess what? I'm playing Blind-and-Seek!
'Cause I'm too good normally!
Huh? You're Mamarin, right?
Why are you so quiet?
Did I make an oopsie?
I wonder... hmm...
You taste like Mamarin!
Huh? Mamarin, are you crying?
Play with me, Mamarin!
It's super dangerous to be sad!
All the gods will be sad too, and then the world will, too!
And when you get sad, my heart gets all funny.
I'm not that smart, so I don't know what to say,
but I like you when you're smiling, Mamarin.
Play with me!
Sure.
See ya tomorrow!
I'm too old for this...
That was fun, Mamarin!
Let's do that again!
If I feel like it, sure.
Yay!
Hey, Tama...
how do you make friends?
What are you asking for?
Because... I don't have any.
But Kagami's your friend, right?
Huh?
Kagami was super happy 'cause she made a friend!
She talked about how you practiced for PE together,
or how you paired up in English class,
and her face never shows it, but I know she's happy!
We're gods, so we have a lot to worry about.
The world will Transform if we wish for something,
so we could have all the friends we want.
That's why it's scary.
We might play together,
and they might say they love me,
but I could just be forcing them.
Tama...
But you and Kagami are both gods!
It has to be the real thing, not a Transformation, so I'm jealous!
Mamarin, I hope you and Kagami stay friends.
It'll all end soon, after the closing ceremony.
Huh?
Kagami said it was something she had to do herself.
So wait for her.
Chain Gun Talisman, downloaded.
Inputting Spiritual Missiles.
Assigning Level B to Flame Lord Kagatsuchi protection.
Activating Eight Span Mirror.
Uninstalling all vulnerable or damaged functions.
Setting soul and emotions to sleep mode.
I should have known.
The gods of the Yaoyorozu will always do what they think pleases the Supreme God.
And the current Supreme God has to be an idiot like me!
I wished for a friend, of all things.
And I chose Kagami.
That made the surrounding gods jealous,
Safety    First     Safety    First     Safety    First     Safety    First     Safety
so they started attacking Kagami!
I used to be an emotionless doll.
A machine that efficiently achieved desired results.
But then, I found a family.
And perhaps a friend.
When Kagami became my friend,
the entire world turned on her!
It matters not what comes to pass.
If my friend desires it,
I will shed as much blood as necessary to grant her normality.
She only said that our friendship meant nothing outside of school
because it took all she had just to keep the peace there!
I do not wish for gratitude, per se.
Because I enjoyed it.
So I will keep my friend from knowing too much,
and settle this matter while it is still secret.
Those in my way shall be palverised!
Friends...
no, for you are pals!
Kagami...
I suggest you don't anger me!
First Year Right Class
Kagami...
What is it?
You are a tad early for class.
So are you!
This is pretty late for an overtime shift!
I dozed off, so I lost track of time.
You were with some classmates earlier.
Were they... friends?
I have no such things.
They were possessed by evil gods, so I exorcised them.
They snuck into those humans in an attempt to get closer to you.
You are something of a VIP,
so I was overjoyed that you did not notice.
For had a fool like you been provoked by those gods,
the world very well may have Transformed.
You were worried about me...
Are you not listening to me?
Are you perhaps an idiot?
Thank you, Kagami.
Sorry... I'm so sorry...
You need not worry.
I have finished cleaning the school.
There is no longer any risk of a Transformation should you make friends.
By your own efforts.
As such, you may take heart and enjoy your fun, cheerful student life.
Kagami!
I'm sorry, Kagami!
I was so stupid!
What are you saying?
You are spraying me in snot!
It is yucky!
I told those gods off,
so they won't do anything bad to you!
So please, please!
Kindly cram it, you wuss!
I'm sorry!
I really like you!
You are disgusting, you pig!
Kagami!
Please be my friend!
Please, Kagami.
Not as a stand-in, either.
As a real friend!
Sasami...
I used to be a doll.
My heart was a shell.
I had no function to congeal tears or let them flow.
And yet I have always yearned to fit in and be normal.
To laugh and cry.
To be a girl one could find anywhere.
If God could have granted me one wish,
I would have liked to be human.
To be foolish and weak.
Yet warm all the same.
I wanted to be human.
You're already warm, Kagami.
Do you think I could become human?
Do you think we could become friends?
We can!
No, from now on, we already are,
Kagami!
Good night, Kagami.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
I deeply apologize for the Sasami impostor last episode.
She has been strictly punished,
and the staff gladly helped themselves to her.
They ate her? Did they eat her?
They may have, but the faker only hijacked this program due to your laziness.
Please apply some effort.
I can help in a small capacity.
Then let's sing together, Kagami!
Two people can handle what one person can't!
Do I look like your mother?
I am already encouraging you,
so sing along to the song already.
Aw, it won't kill you!
I'm stunned by your laugh
Hey, let's walk home together
I can hear your voice
everywhere like a resounding symphony
The light shines a deep color
Let's hold hands forever
I want to feel the osmosis grow
That was actually kinda fun!
That was tiring.
I am never doing this again.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Just Quit
Quiz
Time for Just Quit Quiz.
Question 1.
What kind of problem will I get myself into next?
Hint:
It's an extremely difficult problem that nobody in the world has solved.
Tick, tick tick,
bzzzt.
Answer:
It's fine as long as you were thinking.
Question 2.
What's the answer to the problem you were thinking of?
Next time, on Episode 6.
Next Time, on Episode 6
My Parents Are The Real Burdens.
My Parents Are The Real Burdens