The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
This is amazing...
This is even cooler than Kamisakuramachi-ginza...
Well, I was talking as if I knew everything
about it, but I don't really know the details.
There are plenty of other dangerous guys lurking around, so I'd watch my back if I were you.
By the way, I saw that black motorcycle everyone's been talking about today.
Haven't had a good deal like this in a while.
A teenager.
Kudos to the informant.
And at that moment, I felt my body shaking...
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Is the "reality" you see actually real?
The scenery you're so used to has never changed.
Congratulations on your admittance, everyone.
You hear a lot of dark issues about Japan like the birthrate declining and such,
but when I see you all lined up like this, it really makes me
feel as though the country is headed toward a bright future.
It really cheers me up.
Today must be a bright day for you all,
-
but at the same time...
Don't you believe that you're also experiencing a reality that isn't anything out of the ordinary?
M-
My name is Mikado Ryugamine.
A timid boy who just arrived in Tokyo...
My name is Anri Sonohara.
Nice to meet you all.
And a girl who seems to be somewhat free from worldliness.
I'm Masaomi Kida!
I may look a little too mature, but on the inside...
...I'm just a fragile, sensitive fifteen year old like the rest of you!
A boy off in his own little world who appears so jovial...
I'm Rio Kamichika.
Nice to meet you.
A girl with a seemingly mysterious past.
They're all people who you'd see around you.
Umm... Harima?
Is Mika Harima present?
I guess not.
A run-of-the-mill scene you've definitely seen before.
Late on the first day?
We were all introducing ourselves just now. Please take the time now to do so.
I'm Seiji Yagiri. Nice to meet you.
But there are occasions where something
triggers reality to show a glimpse of its other self.
Okay, Yagiri, please have a seat.
No thanks.
I don't think I'll be able to attend school for a while.
Actually, I don't think I'll ever be coming back.
I came here today just to say that.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm afraid I'm a bit confused, Yagiri...
It's exactly as I said.
I've got something to take care of that means more than my entire life.
I don't have time for you all.
Well, then.
Hey, Yagiri. Wait.
Wait a second...
A sudden event that disrupts peace begins to stir restlessness in the hearts of all.
And there's also a girl here who has avoided one of those disruptions.
In reality, she should have died two days ago.
Highly
Unpredictable
The girl was born in an ordinary household.
She lived a life without any problems or poverty.
But when she entered middle school, an envelope was sent to her, almost like a surprise attack.
Nakura
Nickname
Everything's such a pain. I just want to
disappear without anyone knowing!
Nickname
Nakura
Everything's such a pain. I just want to
disappear without anyone knowing!
Nickname
Nakura
Everything's such a pain. I just want to
disappear without anyone knowing!
Nakura
Everything's such a pain. I just want to
disappear without anyone knowing!
Region: Tokyo
What was in it?
A picture of my father and another woman. Apparently, he was cheating on my mother.
And there was also a letter included in it.
It said something like, "Can something like this really be forgiven?"
I believe the person who sent it has some kind of a connection with the woman.
Your father is definitely at fault here, but so is that woman.
I just didn't know what to do.
So for the time being, I decided to hide the evidence.
Ever since then, the familiar scenery started to look disgusting to me.
It must have been hard on you.
Is something wrong, Rio?
I was only able to put up with it for about half a year.
I figured everything would be so
much easier if I were to reveal it.
If it's something you'd rather not talk
about, you don't have to force yourself.
I too have some things I can't bring myself to tell others about.
It's fine. I want you to know.
I can't believe I took the TV remote, thinking it was my cellphone!
But nothing changed.
-
It was a disaster!
I wasn't sure whether my mother chose not to say anything to him, or if they discussed it when I wasn't around.
Hasn't that ever happened to you, Rio?
My father's lame jokes and my mother's cooking that always tastes so sweet...
...not one thing had changed.
So I decided to disappear, to see
if that would change anything.
I've been thinking about stuff like that a lot recently.
I'm in a similar situation as well.
Although it's not as serious as yours.
What happened?
I was dating someone, but she got together with my father instead.
That's horrible...
But the person I really couldn't forgive was my mother.
What did she say to you?
She told me it's nothing special, and also insisted for me not to make a big deal out of it so we wouldn't look bad.
She didn't say a word on how she felt about the situation.
And I interpreted that as her considering her
reputation to be of higher importance than myself.
Or perhaps, she was taking my future into consideration.
I don't think that's it.
Really?
She probably doesn't even care about how you feel! She only cares about herself!
Dinner's ready, dear.
Coming.
Miss Magenta,
would you like to disappear with me?
If we were to die together, I think they'd pretty much be forced to realize...
...what they should have really treasured.
Thinking back on it now, it was a really foolish decision.
But she was quite determined when she left the house.
Because she felt as though Nakura's words gave her strength.
She wanted to see the face of a person who was having the same thoughts as herself.
Even if that happened to be a lie,
she wouldn't have anything to lose.
That's how it was supposed to be.
Yes?
Are you Miss Magenta?
I am.
Oh, are you Mr. Nakura?
Great! So I wasn't mistaken.
As soon as she saw his face, she had a feeling that the man wasn't Nakura.
Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
But she still followed him because she wouldn't have been able to forgive herself had she ran away at that point.
Well then, shall we get going?
Okay.
So when this happened...
Hi!
Hi.
Is anyone watching us?
Not a single soul.
Well then...
Sorry we tricked you!
...many emotions such as bewilderment,
resistance and regret passed through her mind...
But at the moment before she passed out,
she accepted the event as her destiny.
Why should she have to worry about her own safety after all this time?
She was just going to disappear from society without anyone else knowing about it...
However...
Yeah there is.
Even while the girl was passed out, things were still happening.
Well, it shouldn't really be a tough job, but be careful nonetheless.
Things such as emotions and feelings were irrelevant to her.
I can't.
I just haven't been able to get much cash.
I'm not saying I won't return the money, of course.
But if something were to happen to me, Mr. Shiki of the Awakusu group wouldn't be too happy...
Old man.
I don't have much time.
It's not that I'm busy,
but I'm only willing to give you about
two and half more minutes of my life!
Another guy you shouldn't make an enemy out of is...
Yo.
This isn't something I should have to say to an excellent deliverer such as yourself,
but you really don't have to do
anything more than I asked you to do.
You can just deal with them lightly.
Well then, I'm counting on you.
The world is revolving.
While it steers toward a direction so different from the destiny she believed to be true...
Hey.
What... the fuck are you?!
You okay?
The text on the phone read, "I've been
asked to deliver you to a certain location."
The motorcycle raced without a sound, and occasionally neighed like a horse.
It was as though she was dreaming.
But the body she felt in her arms
confirmed that it was indeed reality.
The girl wondered what was beyond the warmth she felt.
What the person was thinking, what they knew, and how they've been living their life.
She also wondered how she looked in the person's eyes.
There's someone waiting
for you up on the rooftop.
I understand.
My job ends here.
Miss Magenta.
Hi, I'm Nakura.
Are you really Mr. Nakura?
I'm the guy who wants to disappear without a trace.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Are you also the person who arranged to save me?
Yes, that was also me.
Thank you so much.
Were you afraid?
Yes.
It must have been a terrible experience.
Yeah...
But how did you know I was kidnapped?
Because I'm the one who told them to kidnap you.
And I'm also the one who told the biker to rescue you.
What do you mean?
You were thinking about dying, but you got kidnapped.
And you were a little mad at yourself for being frightened.
But if you happened to resist, that would mean that you'd be going against your earlier intentions to die,
so you were also thinking about accepting it as destiny.
But now that you've been saved, you're very much relieved.
I just wanted to see your face which holds all of those thoughts and emotions.
Basically, I wanted to see your face when you're at a loss for words after you realized that I saw right through you.
Why...?
"Why"?
Well... I think the answer to that may sound very philosophical to you.
And if I were to still explain my actions, it would be because I like humans.
Humans are so appealing and interesting. I just can't help myself.
Oh, and just because I like humans,
it doesn't mean that I like you personally.
That's important to note.
Were they... all lies?
Have you finally come to understand the situation you're in right now?
Come with me.
A few people have leaped from here before.
I wouldn't call it a popular location for suicide, but I heard you'll die for sure if you jump off from here.
Take a look at that stain down there.
Hey... do you think of yourself as someone special?
That's not true, by the way. We're all the same.
There's not a single person on earth who can live an honest life.
You've got a few secrets too, don't you?
Ever thought about why your parents are so good-for-nothing compared to you?
That's...
If you'll allow me to give you a conclusion to your situation...
I feel as though everyone else who has had an affair or found out about one...
...kept living their lives as they laughed at lame
jokes and ate food that was a seasoning too sweet.
Take a look.
No matter what worries they had, they're all just bloodstains on concrete now.
No matter who they were,
everyone went back to their divine creator as equals.
Want me to let you go?
See?
Well, I'm glad...
...I was able to see your unsightly feelings today.
What I'm really interested in is the ecology of your worrying,
not your actual worries.
And if I may add, you were awfully boring because all your actions were according to my plan.
And I knew you didn't want to die either.
Well, later!
It's been fun, Miss Magenta!
She actually hesitated a bit at that moment.
Would she be able to hurt him by killing herself now?
But then, she realized that she may just have been waiting for an opportunity.
And it just happened to be those words from a man like that.
But something was happening that the girl was unaware of...
Hey...
Why did you...
Because the world isn't as
cruel as you take it to be.
There you go, doing something unnecessary again...
And at that moment, the girl thought about her parents.
Her father, and his mistress...
And her father, and her mother.
And she also thought about the times she didn't know about.
It may perhaps be that things weren't as malicious, selfish, and detestable as she used to think of them.
They may not have been hidden by her own weakness and compromises.
As she made her way home, she decided to forgive them.
Ever since that day, the world has appeared differently in her eyes.
There are as many dreams as there are people, and the same goes for secrets.
She finally realized that it's nothing out of the ordinary.
Where do you wanna go?
I'll take you anywhere, so you'd better treat me!
Let's see... how about the bookstore then?
Well, there are quite a few bookstores...
Even those two, who look like people you'd see anywhere on an ordinary day, have secrets.
They also have dreams they can't tell anyone else.
Please, wait!
Yagiri, are you sure something's not bothering you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
B-But skipping school on the first day?
I told you, I don't know what you mean!
Wait!
Umm...
Is something wrong?
I wonder what that was about?
I'm such a sinner.
That girl with the glasses must have fallen for me.
She looked like she was feeling anxious about the dangerous, risky days that await her!
Sorry, do you mind speaking in a language I'm familiar with?
For him...
And also, for her...
What they both see may not be reality.
And the girl wondered if she'd someday be able to tell someone those same words...
"The world isn't as cruel as you take it to be."
I wasn't aware you joined the Justice League.
I thought the person I asked for help was an excellent deliverer instead...
Are you also responsible for the person
who leaped off there in the past?
No way!
Izaya Orihara, the informant, isn't that bad of a guy.
But I'm also not kind enough to stop someone who wants to die.
It's been fun, you excellent deliverer.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Rampant
We're in Ikebukuro.
Him, her, me, you...
...all came to this city to look for something,
to seek for something,
and to change something.
Next time: Rampant.
Want to eat sushi? It's good.
It's been forever, lad!