Year 845:
The Colossus Titan that suddenly
appeared along with the Armored Titan
destroyed everything as
easily as it did the wall.
Wall Maria was abandoned.
And with a fifth of its population
and a third of its land lost,
mankind had its territory reduced to Wall Rose.
Then, in the year 850, at Trost District,
mankind allowed the Titans to invade further.
Shortly after, Eren Jaeger,
who was devoured by a Titan,
emerged from within a mysterious Titan.
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Response
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑥
I'll ask you once again!
Just what are you?!
I'm human!
I see.
Don't think ill of me.
Marco, I've had enough.
I can't fight the Titans anymore!
What's wrong?
My comrades were devoured
right in front of me!
I didn't feel even feel sad or
angry seeing them die like that.
I was just thankful from the bottom
of my heart that it wasn't me!
But it must be my turn next.
I finally realized.
Our job is to keep fighting until
the Titans devour us, isn't it?!
If that's all I have to live for, I'd rather—
Calm down and get ahold of yourself!
You're not alone in this!
Everyone is battling with fear!
Look at Sasha!
Even after everything that's happened,
she's still a noble soldier.
Um, my stomach is hurting, so can I
be marked down as a casualty?
That's it!
Stop!
Stop it!
Keeping it confidential really was necessary.
With things as they are now,
if word about Eren spread...
Cannon fire?
But why only one shot?
Look, there's smoke!
It's from within the wall!
What's that?
What's happening?
Was the floodgate broken through?
It's the strongest part of the wall.
There's no way!
A high-explosive shell must've
accidentally been dropped.
But then why's there so much smoke?
Could it be steam from a Titan?
Hey!
What the hell's going on here?
It's alive!
Captain Felman!
W-We're on standby!
It's too dangerous to approach!
All units are to stand by on full alert!
Stand by!
Have the cannoneers ready another round!
What is this?
I remember up to the cannon fire.
Then there was a tremendous
crash, impact, and heat.
We're inside a Titan's skeleton right—
Eren protected us.
That's all that matters now.
Flowers, inside here?
Hey,
you guys okay?
Eren, what is this?
No idea.
But it's evaporating already.
Just like a Titan's corpse.
Let's back away a bit.
Whether they're figuring out
what to do or just distracted,
the Garrison can't see what we're doing now.
But in the end, they'll probably continue attacking.
I don't have the confidence to talk
them down after showing this.
It reminded me of something though.
The basement.
The basement of my house.
Dad said I'd understand
everything if I went there.
He's also the one that turned me into this.
If I get to that basement, I'll probably
learn the truth about the Titans.
Damn it!
Why did he keep it all a secret?!
The Survey Corps searched for that information
at the cost of thousands of lives.
It's mankind's only hope!
And you're telling me it was
locked away in my basement?
Just what was going through his mind?
Come to think of it, where did
he disappear to for five years—
Eren, we have other things to worry about now.
Right.
The smoke is clearing.
We'll attack on sight!
Let's finish this quickly!
Remain on standby!
I'm... leaving this place.
Where to?
How?
Anywhere will do for now.
I'll climb the wall from there
and head to my basement.
But I'll turn into a Titan first.
You can do that?
I'm not too sure how I do it myself,
but I think I can.
Just like how a person can't explain
how they move their arms.
Earlier, I unconsciously focused
on blocking the cannon.
That's why the body had no other
function and easily fell apart.
This time, I'll go for something stronger.
The 15-meter-class that I kicked around
all those Titans with should suffice!
Eren, your nose is bleeding.
You're looking pale, and your
breathing's heavy too.
It's clearly taking a toll on your body!
I couldn't care less for my well-being.
I've got two ideas in mind.
If you guys don't try to cover for me,
you'll be spared at the least.
I've already gotten you two in a real mess,
so I'll be moving solo from here on out.
No, I—
Eren,
I'm coming too.
You can't.
If I can't keep up, you can just abandon me.
But I don't have to listen to what you say.
I'm telling you to cut it out already!
I'm neither your little brother nor a kid!
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Yeast Part ①
A special yeast produced only within Wall Sina.
It's known that the presence of this yeast in storehouses or tents
full of fodder, wheat, or soybeans significantly reduces rate of decay.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
Yeast Part ②
Building storage plants filled with this yeast in order
to stock up on supplies necessary for the recapture
of Wall Maria has been mankind's strategy thus far.
Captain, the high-explosive
shell is almost loaded.
How shall we proceed?
Await my signal!
Sir.
There's no sign of the Garrison planning
to launch a close-quarters attack just yet.
If there was, Mikasa would've picked
up on it faster than a stray cat.
Even if they loaded the cannon as fast as possible,
it should take at least another 20 seconds.
Eren will probably act within
that time and depart from here.
Why am I remembering that now?
Is it because this is the end for us?
So even up to the very end...
I was nothing more than a coward, after all.
They've saved me countless times already.
But I've yet to return the favor even once.
How could I consider myself a friend
who's on equal terms with them?
How could I say, "I'm coming too?"
I don't even have the confidence to keep up.
After... all this...
the three of us will never be together again.
Eren, I—
Wait, Mikasa.
I said I had two ideas in mind, didn't I?
Armin, I'll leave everything for you to decide.
I'm well aware of just how unrealistic my plan is.
It would be the most effective to use this Titan
power systematically under the army's command.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but if you think you can convince
the Garrison that I'm not a threat,
I'll put my trust in you and stay.
That's my second idea.
If you think you can't, I'll have
to resort to the first idea.
You have fifteen seconds to decide.
Whether you can do it or not,
I'll respect any opinion you have.
Eren, why would you entrust
me with such a decision?
The worse a situation is, the better
your decisions are, you know?
I'm willing to bet on that.
When did I ever...
Lots of times.
Five years ago, if you didn't call Hannes-san,
Mikasa and I would've been devoured by a Titan.
It was just me convincing myself.
Convincing myself that I was
powerless and a burden.
That thought didn't cross their minds at all!
Armin, we're out of time.
The cannon's been loaded.
Ready to fire at any time.
The two entrusting their lives to me now
are the people I trust most in this world.
How could I possibly doubt myself now?
I'll convince them no matter what.
Do anything you guys can
to show you're not a threat.
Something's been on my mind
since I saw Eren fighting as a Titan.
I still haven't figured it out, but I'll pull this off.
I'll think while talking if I have to!
Halt!
So you've finally revealed
your true colors, monster!
I'll signal...
I'll signal the cannon!
He is not the enemy of mankind!
We're willing to share any and
all information that we have!
I have no intention of hearing your pleas!
We've seen everything we need to know.
There's no room for discussion!
If you claim he's not our enemy, then prove it!
If you can't, we'll simply eliminate the threat!
There's no need for proof!
That's right.
It's unnecessary!
Besides, how we see him is not an issue!
What?!
I've heard that many have seen him in action!
If that's true, they must've also
seen him fighting the Titans!
And that includes the sight of the
surrounding Titans swarming him!
In other words, the Titans saw him as a target
of predation, just like the rest of mankind!
No matter how we go about it,
that fact cannot be denied!
He has a point.
A Titan as an ally.
That's ridiculous.
Prepare to attack!
Don't be fooled by his clever tricks!
Their actions have always been
beyond our comprehension.
It must be possible for them to imitate
our form and speech to delude us!
We cannot allow them do
as they please any longer!
It's no good.
He's abandoned all reason.
He's too scared to think.
Eren, Mikasa!
I am a soldier that has long since offered
his life for the revival of mankind!
To perish while obeying that conviction
would be my life's greatest glory!
If we were to utilize his Titan powers
in addition to our remaining forces,
recapturing this town would
no longer be impossible!
Praying for the glory of mankind,
I shall elaborate on his strategic
worth with all the time I have left!
Captain Felman, perhaps we should consider his—
Silence!
No matter how they plea, they're still rebels!
Those who transgress must be eliminated!
That's the duty of a soldier!
That's enough.
As always, despite having a large
body, you're as feeble as a fawn.
Commander Pixis?
Are you blind to the brilliance of that salute?
I just arrived, but a messenger filled me in earlier.
Go take command of the reinforcements.
I think it'd be best to hear
what they have to say.
According to the Survey Corps' reports,
the Titans were predicted
to approach from the south.
Specifically, Shiganshina, the southernmost
district of Wall Maria, was attacked.
Therefore, the town that was the
most likely to be attacked next was
the southernmost district of Wall Rose, Trost.
Trost District  Inner Gate
Dott Pixis.
The chief executive in charge of all the southern
territories including Trost District,
and the man given full authority over the defense
of mankind's most important districts.
I guess I won't find one, after all.
I wouldn't mind being devoured, if it's
by an exquisitely beautiful female.
And he's also known as a natural eccentric.
What's the Commander thinking?!
How could he accompany such
suspicious people up there?
Well, the Commander's thoughts are beyond
the comprehension of average people.
Captain, the soldiers are in formation.
Right. Good work.
I see.
So you say that all the answers
lie within that basement.
Yes.
Do you believe me?
As long as you yourself aren't certain,
I'd say I can only keep it in mind at best.
However, I believe myself capable
of seeing the truth of things.
I shall guarantee your safety.
Recruit Arlert, was it?
Sir!
Earlier, you said that if we
utilize this "Titan power,"
it'd be possible to recapture
this town, did you not?
Did you truly believe that, or was
it a vain act of desperation?
It was...
both!
What I was trying to say back then
was that Eren could carry the large boulder
to seal the destroyed gate in his Titan form.
It's an idea that I came up with on the spot,
but I hoped the possibility to break out of this
deadlock could be seen in Eren's power.
Of course, it was all a genuine attempt to survive.
A genuine attempt to survive...
The most trustworthy words I'll ever hear.
Well, Recruit Jaeger?
Sir?
Can you seal that gate?
I...
Well...
I don't know.
I'm just as clueless as
the rest of us present here.
So, regardless of whether I can do it
or not, I can't answer half-heartedly.
Oh, that's true, I apologize.
That was the wrong question.
Will you do it or not—which is it?
I'll do it.
I'll do it!
I'm not sure whether I can or not, but I'll do it!
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba
Though they once ran in fear,
they're soldiers that inevitably
decided to remain on the battlefield.
Eren makes his decision.
To become the hope of mankind.
Idol
————— Battle for Trost District Part    —————
⑦