This is Mitsuki Koyama,
a 12-year-old girl.
She went to the beach and
met a wonderful boy there.
Mitsuki got a boyfriend and
I went on a date with Takuto at the beach!
But that guy was actually
a serial womanizer!
His girlfriend found out about it and
Mitsuki was saved just in time.
The beach really is a dangerous place
during the summer.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you.
Is model work busy for you?
Yes.
But it's a lot of fun!
I see...
But don't be overdoing it
just because it's summer vacation.
I won't!
What did Dr. Wakaoji say?
He said not to overdo it
just because it's summer vacation.
I see.
Like this?
Yes, great.
Looks pretty good.
But why did I get a shampoo job?
Would makeup have been better?
I-It's still too soon for makeup.
Your song is selling well
and you have some fans.
And you're wanted for commercials.
That's the next step.
Really? I wonder...
Your face will appear like crazy
in magazines and on TV
if you're in commercials.
That's a little...embarrassing.
But I think it's a short cut
for Eichi to notice you.
I see... Eichi...
Okay! I'll do my best!
Right. That's the spirit.
So, Miss Ooshige, when's the filming?
Oh, about that.
It hasn't been formally decided, yet.
There's an audition.
It's tomorrow.
Hm?
Please say that sooner!
I-I'm sorry!
Say, like this?
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Aww, split ends.
Jeez, Meroko. You have to
be sure to take care of your hair.
Hair is vital for a girl.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Just kidding.
I just teased you a little.
Oh, jeez, Meroko.
Say, Takuto.
What do you think?
Huh?
Are you opposed to this girl
being in a commercial?
Huh? Really?
N-Not particularly.
Oh, what's with the attitude?
How obnoxious.
Why do I have to be happy
about her commercial, too?
I'm going for a walk.
Oh.
Takuto...
Jeez, how unenthusiastic.
Usually, he's the first to be happy.
Really... I wonder why.
Come to think of it, didn't he say
he used to be a musician?
I wonder if he means don't get carried
away over something other than singing.
Right? You'd think that,
wouldn't you?
Huh?
Don't you think Takuto's
been acting strange lately?
He seems strange somehow
ever since the event the other day.
Event...
Oh.
Don't, don't tell me...
You don't know something
about it, do you?
Uh, no. Nothing at all.
I-I think I'll go to sleep now.
You're both acting strange.
D-Don't tell me...
...you two are doing something
behind my back!
What?! You're coming
with me to the audition?
Takuto doesn't really seem into it.
And I want to go out once in a while.
B-But...
Meroko concerns me.
It should be fine every once in awhile.
Umm...
Yes! I'm happy! Okay Takuto, you
take care of things here, all right?
Uh-huh.
I get a peculiarly suspicious feeling.
This time I won't let them be alone.
La, la, la.
Going out, going out.
- Going out, going out.
- I wonder what's wrong with Takuto.
It should be fine every once in a while.
I don't get it.
What's the matter?
N-Nothing.
Really?
Really.
Anyway, I'll just think
about the audition now.
Let me see, where is it?
What? You don't know
where the place is?
Then leave it to me!
Let's see, this way...
We passed through here, before.
Then how about this way?
It's the same place again...
Then, here!
That way!
This way!
We're totally lost, aren't we?
Maybe I'll have Miss Ooshige
come pick me up.
Are you lost?
What?
Y-You!
We met at the Seed Records
audition, right?
That's right.
Thank you for
talking to me then,
when I was so lonely not having
anyone I knew there.
Was that so?
Oh yeah,
congratulations on passing.
Thank you!
By the way,
where were you trying to go?
Oh, uh...
Here.
Oh. It'll be fast if you take the train to
the next station and then walk from there.
Wait.
I'll draw a map for you.
Yay...
But you didn't say a thing about that.
Okay, it's here.
Oh, okay.
Yay.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
All right, then! I'll be going.
- Good luck.
- Right!
Full Moon's easy game.
The audition will start if we don't hurry!
I know!
There she is!
Miss Ooshige!
You're late. What happened?
I'm sorry. I got lost.
I would've picked you up
if you'd called me.
Actually, there was someone along
the way who kindly told me the way.
From Shinbashi...
Shinbashi? You came from Shinbashi?
It said Yuurakucho, didn't it? See?
What?
No way!
Why?
- That woman!
- Huh?
Oh?!
It seems you've arrived safely.
Th-That's mean!
I'm sorry.
I teased you a little.
Huh?
I never thought you'd believe me.
Well, it's payback for before.
Payback?
Even though you said
you had no connections,
you actually did,
didn't you?
Without knowing that, I said such a thing
because I was convinced I'd pass.
No way...
I really didn't have any connections!
Is that so? I wonder if that's true.
If so, then let's leave things as they stand.
Let's fight fair and square
in the audition, okay?
What's with that woman?
It's Real Music's Madoka Wakamatsu.
According to the information I got,
she's your biggest rival in this audition.
What? Really?
You intend on continuing to
pretend not to know, eh.
I must have looked funny
in your eyes at the time.
But you watch, Full Moon.
I'll smash you to bits.
Are there other rivals?
Huh?
They're all rivals.
It's nothing but people I've seen
on TV and in magazines.
No way.
That's Madoka Wakamatsu?
I didn't notice until I was told.
Right? She had a plain image
when she was a child actor.
- Yeah.
She's like a different person.
Could it be that she had plastic surgery?
I don't know about that.
But I bet she worked really hard.
I could never do that.
So Madoka was an actress
from when she was little.
She's an amazing person.
I wonder if I can win.
- Hey, hey.
- Oh.
What're you getting nervous for?
Huh?
I guess it can't be helped.
I'll teach you what to look out for
so that you won't get stage fright.
Uh, okay...
Listen up. Be sure to reply carefully!
Okay.
Anyway, relax.
Keep your back straight.
Okay.
Answer promptly and clearly!
When talking, be sure to look at
the person you're talking with in the eye.
Understood!
Very well. Then, let's go.
Okay.
What?
What's the matter?
The door won't open!
What?!
I wonder if it broke!
No!
Is anybody there?
I was sure that it was here.
Where the heck did that Mitsuki go off to?
Jeez!
The audition is going to start.
Ms. Oshige!
Mitsuki!
Where were you?
I'm sorry.
The bathroom door wouldn't open.
Anyway, thank goodness
you made it in time.
This is the concept of the new product
that was handed out. Take a look at it.
Okay.
That woman.
I bet that woman did it.
Don't assume like that.
Also, the interview will be
in a group of two people.
It seems the results will be determined
by the repartee with the judges.
And as for the person you'll be with...
It seems she's oddly concerned with you.
But don't let her get the best of you.
I won't. I'll do my best!
It's almost time.
What am I doing getting worried?!
When the people ahead of you come out,
go in and take their place.
Okay.
The time has come.
I think the bathroom thing earlier
was definitely that woman's fault.
That again?
You did well to get out.
See?! I told you!
I knew it was this woman's doing.
Do you have someone special
in your life?
What?!
Relax! It's a strategy to try to
upset you before the interview.
Uh, uh-huh...
What would happen
if I did have someone?
The thing that's hated the most among
commercial personalities is scandal.
The product image would be
damaged in one shot, right?
So in the case of a scandal being
exposed during the contract period,
as well as the commercial being pulled,
there are instances of the office having
to pay damages for breach of contract.
I-Is that so?
What? Then what should you do?
She's shaken up.
I wonder if it'll be okay
with Meroko there.
Well, I guess it makes no difference.
Of course I regularly use
Mermaid Tear shampoo.
I've been using it all along ever since
a person in a beauty parlor
recommended it to me.
I see. I came without knowing
anything about the product.
How should I answer
if I'm asked?
That pure feeling of yours
is good, Mitsuki.
So just come right out
and say what you think.
Come right out and
say what I think, huh.
Hey, hey.
Don't look so anxious.
I'll make it all go well.
Meroko, actually...
So, how about you, Miss Full Moon?
Huh?!
What's your image regarding shampoo?
Oh, I...
Umm, I've been yearning
for dry hair since I was a kid.
Huh?
Okay. Dry, eh!
Fire.
That's too strong!
Meroko, turn it off!
I know.
Umm, I'm sorry.
This is nothing at all.
Uhh... Umm...
Jeez!
Oh, I should've just turned it off.
Oh... Umm...
Tadah. Is it dry?
You're funny.
Huh?
Yes...
It's not funny at all.
Just kidding.
Something like that goes over well?
At this rate...
Okay, this is it for the interview.
Oh, okay.
- Thank you.
Oh, come to think of it, Full Moon.
Was it okay not to talk about that?
Huh?
You have someone
special in your life, right?
Huh?
What's this woman doing
saying that at a time like this?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I went and said it.
Was that bad?
What? No.
What's the meaning of this?
Did you hear that?
Uh, well...
Say, "no!" Keep it a secret!
Keep it a secret.
What?
But the moon is hidden
and I can't see it.
Even if you can't see it,
the coming and going of the tide
is because of the moon's power.
So on nights like this, close your eyes
and try listening to the sound of the waves.
You can feel that there is a moon
in the sky even now, right?
Did you feel it?
Hmm...
But...
What?
Then I can't play hide and seek
with the moon.
That's right.
It's just for the promise with Eichi.
Why do I need to hide that?
If I were to hide it, it seems like
it'd be a bad thing. It's true, after all.
What's the matter?
Yes.
There is someone special in my life.
Oh no.
Now this kid's finished.
What?
You went and said it?!
Yes.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
That's the kind of girl you are.
I see.
It doesn't look good, huh.
Well, there's no need to be worried
about just failing one interview.
Yeah... Bye.
I see...
Sure enough, it was no good
with Meroko there, huh.
Oh, Meroko.
Where were you?
I had a phone call from Takuto.
What did he say?
He said not to worry about it.
I see...
But I didn't tell him that you talked
about Eichi during the interview.
Good job today with
the interviews.
I will now announce
the results of the audition.
Umm, the results of the judging.
The image character
for Mermaid Tear is...
...Real Music's
Miss Madoka Wakamatsu!
Thank you.
We look forward to
working with you.
Thank you.
I've paid you back for before.
Oh, and there's more.
Village Pro's Miss Full Moon.
Yes?
You're perfect for the image of
the commercial. So you, also.
M-Me?!
Yes.
You did it, Mitsuki!
Thank you!
That's all.
We'll be changing this commercial's plan
and go ahead with a pair.
W-What's up with that?!
Madoka.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's do our best together.
Huh?!
Please decide on
which one person!
What?
I don't want to work with her!
Huh?!
W-Why?
Takuto, you idiot!
Why did you tell Mitsuki that you
were a singer when you were alive?
Shut up!
This is my business!
Your business?
Takuto, do you know what
happens to Death Spirits
when they completely
remember their former life?
I already know that!
It's all right.
Just leave me alone!
Wait, Tack!
Come back here!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Conflicting Personalities"
- Look forward to it!