I will kill.
To keep on living,
Elen.
Let's go.
It has begun, Mr. Shiga.
This has been my goal.
This plot you've written will betray you in the end.
Your curtain call will be ugly, I would say... Scythe Master.
That would be simply fun as well.
Now...
You may sing and dance,
soldiers of my creation.
Spilling your blood...
...and killing each other in a world gone mad.
These girls...
There could only be one person with such warped taste.
We're the same.
There are still at least two enemies.
The odds don't look good.
Not necessarily.
I don't think Inferno brought more than these girls.
How do you know?
He wouldn't let useless extras be lifted onto the stage.
He wants to close the curtain himself?
This is the final battle.
Neun and Fünf have left the stage, I see.
You fought fairly well.
The scenario is better than anticipated.
Yes.
It's the perfect adornment for the epilogue.
Let's go.
I'll be the decoy.
Use the distraction to look for Scythe.
If we get to their commander, we will have the advantage.
You are the only one who can read his moves.
Be careful.
You too.
Two versus one.
I see.
You're there, aren't you?
Ein.
Welcome to my stage.
I won't perform on your stage.
Only two of them are coming at me?
Are the others after Ein?
Surely you're not surrendering, are you?
No. I've come to kill you, Master.
Kill?
Me?
That's interesting.
In a situation as ridden with despair as this,
how do you intend to kill me?
I can't be killed here in your storyboard.
You would never allow such a childish ending.
I never thought you would gain such insight.
It's just as you have said.
I returned to this Island Country...
...because I want to enjoy my little girls' performance with my own eyes.
Let me introduce you.
Sechs and Sieben.
They deserve no less as your little sisters.
Ein.
That's Ein, the sample you are based on.
Go play with her for a little while,
and when she reaches her limit,
cut her into tiny pieces.
What's wrong, Ein? You're up against a dead end.
You present me with this childish end even though I went easy on you?
You are a disappointment.
Their execution, movement, and breathing...
...are the same as mine were.
Yes, ever since you created me,
nothing has changed.
I'm sorry I had to rely on you to the very end, Cal.
My, my...
I'm astonished.
I never thought you would still be able to show me such fighting strength.
I told you.
I've come here to kill you.
I doubt that will happen.
Why is that?
Because I surrender.
Why?
You see, I'm no longer a threat to you.
How about it? Can you kill me now, Ein?
This is the difference between you and Zwei.
Unlike Zwei who fights of his own will,
you can only kill when you are under orders.
If you were to abandon that tenet,
your soul would shatter.
A murderer's fear and guilt would haunt you.
The mind you have, bereft of force of will...
...is weaker than that of an ordinary man.
You cannot shoot me.
In fact, you never could.
It's because...
...you need me.
I was truly entertained tonight, Ein.
Elen.
You really are a foolish man.
You honestly think you can cold-read people's minds...
Of course.
I will kill you.
Because I... despise you.
And also... because I can't forgive you for hurting him.
What will happen to you after you have killed me?
You will keep on running away...
...without your memories ever coming back.
All you enter is an endless spiral.
That may be true, but...
...I will kill you, Scythe Master.
Amazing.
This is amazing, Ein.
Don't call me Ein.
My name is Elen.
By that I hope...
...and by that I live.
Elen.
The muse's twisted prank...
Leave for hell ahead of me.
I'll follow you later.
He will be with me.
Let's go,
Elen.
I see.
Scythe Master and Phantom.
How will you proceed?
The young will destroy the old system and erect a new one in its place.
The transient flower withers.
A ghost that never existed.
Even if the dream is fleeting,
there are things we must do.
What is this? What happened?
Apparently there was an incident at the chapel and the old schoolhouse.
Oh my, that's scary.
See you again,
Reiji-san.
Helmut von Giuseppe.
Born in Berlin.
He acquired a Ph.D. in neuroscience and psychology and researched a new treatment at his university.
He was widely known as an expert on interrogation and brainwashing.
At that time, he came in contact with the underworld while wandering from place to place,
and became the freelance middleman for assassins.
The alias he used in the underworld...
...was Scythe Master.
In order to find Elen's past,
we had to trace this man's career.
Her and Scythe's first meeting five years ago...
...marked the beginning of the life of "Ein".
Their encounter...
...was in Hong Kong.
Is that true?
He came to this institution?
Yes, about five years ago.
He told me he wanted to adopt a girl from Ulan Bator.
Adopt her?
Her skin was so pale...
...and she'd probably be your age now if she's still alive.
Is it just my imagination or...
...did she look just like her?
Ulan Bator.
We've come as far as Mongolia.
Elen's trail goes cold here.
Look at the sky from the grassy vastness.
That will give you certainty.
You'll know when you look up at the sky.
We're here.
If you are a Mongolian,
you could never forget its sky.
The sky and the clouds are always inside your blood and bones.
You'll know when you look up at the sky.
We don't need to search any further.
Are you sure?
This is enough.
I can remember this sky.
I dreamed about it from time to time.
I'm satisfied.
Even though I've made lots of mistakes...
...and failed to keep many promises in my life,
there is one promise I must keep no matter what.
Nothing is necessary any longer.
Even if I couldn't find anything,
I have a name you gave me.
I will make you smile.
I have memories of the time we spent together.
I will give you back your true smile.
Someday...
I'm sure...
That's all I need...
That's all I need to keep on living.
It's all I need.