Hi, everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Hi, everyone. It's me, Rosetta.
I've decided to attempt
the trapeze this time.
I just can't forget how moved I was
when I saw Sora and Miss
Layla's legendary great maneuver.
Sora is the person I admire,
who taught me what was important.
I want to try flying through the sky
together with her, over the same stage.
Otherwise, my joining
Kaleido Stage has no meaning.
I'm able to do anything if I'm
with Sora. Anything! Anything!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
It's precisely because we have the past
that we also have the present and the future.
It seems a cute lamb has started
walking toward the future now.
Aries girl, Rosetta Passel.
Sora! I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
It's an emergency situation!
Hey, Sora!
Did you flood the washing machine again?
No! No! No!
Please give me special training, Sora.
No... Master Sora!
What?
I'm going to do a trapeze act
on the stage three days from now!
If I'm not capable of doing that,
I'm going to withdraw from Kaleido Stage.
"Amazing Rosetta of Sweat and Tears."
Hello...
Boss?!
I'm sorry for calling you so early.
But we decided to let you
appear in the show next week.
The show? You mean... diabolo?
Of course!
The way your diabolo is now,
I'm sure the audience will enjoy it a lot.
I want to do the trapeze.
Rosetta, you're not ready
for the trapeze yet.
You still haven't finished basic training.
First of all, Rosetta,
have you ever appeared in a trapeze show?
I've already gone through
enough basic training.
Rosetta, you're going
to do a diabolo show first.
If I knew I was just going to do diabolo,
I wouldn't have joined Kaleido Stage.
What's so hard about the trapeze?
I've got three days. That's more than enough.
No matter what you say,
three days are too short to learn...
If I can't learn, I'll
withdraw from Kaleido Stage!
Hello. Rosetta!
Good grief.
So that's the story.
Three days? Are you serious?
Sora, you were able to master
skating in three days, weren't you?
So please give me special
training, Master Sora.
"Master Sora"?
Is something wrong?
No. I'm moved!
I can't believe that such a proud
girl as Rosetta would call me Master.
I was born in Belgium and studied in France.
You're supposed to be my guide, but
you don't know anything about me, do you?
I demand a satisfactory explanation
from you in the dressing room!
Back then, you used to call me a guide.
Sorry. I was young.
Um, you're still young...
Anyway, my first goal is
to do the Golden Phoenix.
Well...
Anyway, why don't we give it a try?
What?! Really?!
Thank you, Sora.
No, Master Sora.
I'll go change my clothes too, then!
I wonder if this is okay...
Oh, Boss.
I need to talk to you about Rosetta.
I will let you handle her.
Once she sets out to do something,
nobody can stop her. So, do something.
What?!
You too. Listen, just get off of there.
"Something," he says...
Tadaaa!
Look, Sora.
Please give me special training, Master Sora!
Let's work hard for three days, Rosetta!
Long ago, it was Rosetta who was
giving me special training in the diabolo.
This... this... this is really tough!
Only one more day left until the time limit.
We don't have time to goof off!
The trapeze?
That's too much for Rosetta to do yet, Sora!
That's why she is going
to give me special training.
That's right. Special training.
What? What?
Rosetta is going to do the trapeze?
And Sora will be your teacher?
Both of those things might be hopeless...
If a beginner has to be able
to perform in three days,
I'm sure it will be super-special training.
Last time, I was your ruthless coach.
But you can be my ruthless coach this time.
Ruthless?
I'm not sure if I can be...
Please train me rigorously, Master Sora!
Rigorous special training, huh?
In that case, we'll get Sora to give us
special training in how to be gag characters.
Right, Ken?
What?!
I already told you I'm
not gonna pair with you!
And what makes you think I should give you
special training to be good gag characters?
Even without trying,
you still make everyone laugh!
That's what makes a gag character!
There's no doubt that Sora has
that talent, but I think Ken has it too!
So if Ken and I pair up and get Sora's special
training, we will be the best gag characters ever!
I don't think they need you, Anna.
So I'm the obstacle?
Oh, I've not seen that look for a while.
You look so cool.
Okay, let's start, Rosetta.
Rosetta, what are you doing?
Special training.
Well...
I want to hurry and be like Miss Layla.
What?
And then I'm going to do the
legendary great maneuver with Sora.
What?!
Roller Great Jump!
May!
Then I, the top star,
will give you special training.
You're the top star?
It's natural that I am the top
star because I am Leon's partner.
Sora's era is finished.
Who cares about Leon?
If I become Sora's partner,
Sora will be the top star.
Rosetta, for the time being,
let's practice, practice.
You're just holding the swing like a little
monkey, swinging your legs back and forth.
I'll help you swing, then.
Here!
Wait, May!
May, don't! Rosetta's still a beginner!
Here we go!
Excellent Top Star Swing!
May, stop!
Sora!
Sora, pull this rope and stop it.
Okay.
How is it, Rosetta?
Not yet. Not yet.
Now!
Go, Jonathan!
It stopped.
Are you okay?
I don't feel so good.
As I thought, you can't just jump into it.
Be strong, Rosetta.
Why don't you just do
diabolo like you're supposed to?
Sorry, Sora.
Rosetta, I think you should
start by strengthening your body.
I could say the same thing to you, Sora.
What?
I've been thinking about this for a while.
But you just kept challenging
Miss Layla with only big maneuvers.
So your body became unbalanced.
That's your weakness.
Why don't you do the
basic training with Rosetta?
Sora...
Okay.
Let's build the bodies we
need for the trapeze together.
Maybe you should start with your abs.
Weak abs can easily cause you
to lose your balance in the air.
Ready, go.
One, two...
Let me join you.
Only three days.
I really think that might be impossible...
Nine, ten...
Eleven, twelve...
Thirteen...
Fourteen...
Not good!
I spent all day just trying
to strengthen her body.
Why'd she promise to quit if she
can't use the trapeze in three days?
--Well, Aries do have a tendency
--There are only two days left.
--of not being able to apply the brakes.
--What are we gonna do?! What?! What?!
When that type falls in love
they're amazing, you know.
She's sure to be all smooch-smooch.
And this is Rosetta's special bear.
Naturally, she'll smooch
this bear too. Smooch, smooch.
So, if I smooch this bear, it will be
same as smooching Rosetta indirectly.
Sorry. Please forgive me.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred!
Next!
I smell something burning.
That's Rosetta's...
Rosetta!
I'm sorry.
You almost started a fire.
You put in too much detergent.
And you have to shut the door properly too!
Milk cartons go to the recycle bin.
Milk cartons?
Please separate trash properly
when you throw things away.
Rosetta, are you okay?
What's wrong?
What's all this milk for?
Are you trying to be a cow?
I'm trying to build muscles.
You need to have well-balanced meals.
You mustn't have an unbalanced diet.
And, Sora. I need to talk
to you for a second.
Yes.
You have to be responsible, Sora.
Didn't Kalos ask you to look after Rosetta?
Yes. I...
You're the older sister
in this relationship, okay?
Promises are important, but you
shouldn't let her get carried away.
In any case, you're going to
quit after two days, aren't you?
Hey, Sora.
I'm thinking about creating Rosetta's section
next time I update Kaleido Stage's home page.
Do you think it's okay?
Of course! Make one, definitely!
I'm glad. I feel better hearing that.
Sora...
What?! Why are you dressed like that?
For training. I'm going to run.
You shouldn't push yourself
too much, Rosetta.
We only have two days left.
I came into this prepared
to do this much hard work.
Only two days left...
Rosetta, look, look!
Here I go!
Amazing...
Unlike yesterday, today
will be real training,
so I'll attach a lifeline to you.
Please tell me if the belt is too tight.
No, it's fine.
Oh, here she is.
I created your page, Rosetta.
I think here you should
write "Rosetta Could Be Betta."
Let me see, let me see.
What is this?! It looks great!
See? See?
How about "Rosetta Set-ta The Bar Too High"?
That is very pretty.
How about if we put something
like "Rosetta Fell Into the Net-ta"?
You look tired.
No...
Have you been practicing
all the time ever since then?
Yes.
Or how about "Rosetta Is..."
Hey, Rosetta!
Rosetta?
Oh, no!
Shush.
She's all right. Just sleeping.
Sleeping?
"Rosetta Went to Bed-da"!
She's been building up fatigue even before
this, adjusting to a dorm life she's not used to.
Maybe it's better if we just let
her take a rest like this today.
Okay.
And, I just heard this from Rosetta,
but she says she's never even
been on a park swing before.
What?
What time is it now?
Oh, no! I overslept!
Sora?
"I have the show today,
so we'll do the rest tomorrow.
We'll go to a secret special training place,
so rest well until then. Sora."
Sora is in the middle of the show right now.
I can't just keep sleeping.
There is only one day left until
I have to make good on my promise.
Sora, where's this
secret special training place?
It's the elementary school
that Marion attends.
You're not saying we're
practicing on kiddie swings?
I already got the teacher's permission.
Are you looking down on me, Sora?
I'm serious about this.
They said I was a good pick because I was
ready to appear on the stage immediately,
but all I'm doing is
causing everybody trouble.
As it is now,
my coming to Kaleido Stage despite the
opposition from Mom is meaningless.
Marion, it's a little early,
but why don't we have lunch?
Okay.
You too, Rosetta. Okay?
Okay, Jonathan!
Rosetta, I hear you've never been on a swing?
Yes. I've never played in the park.
Since I was little, I've been
practicing diabolo the whole time.
I spent day and night on the stage every day.
As for me, I first rode a swing
by myself when I was three.
Of course, I never thought about
wanting to appear on stage,
I was just playing.
Playing?
At first, you can take your time.
So, let's think of this as playing.
But, I made a promise to the Boss.
Here.
It's herbal tea. It makes you relax.
Oh, thank you.
Hey! No fair! Me too!
--Leaving the Boss aside,
--Give me some.
I want to see what our trapeze
performance might look like together.
I want to see what our diabolo
Me too.
Okay.
Thank you, Sora.
Now, let's get going!
Okay.
We're going!
The one we can see over
there is Marion's school?
Yep. Isn't it big?
They are small.
What?! These are great swings!
That's right.
Let's play, Jonathan.
Here!
Why don't we also get on a swing?
What? Okay.
First of all, you have to
be able to rock the swing.
Okay.
Now, have a seat.
Rosetta!
Sorry, are you okay?
Sora, are you tired of me?
You're not sick of this?
Not, at all.
You've stopped liking me, huh?
Oh, it's true!
Master Rosetta!
What? Me?
Wow, she's the real thing!
She is younger than I thought.
Let me introduce my friends.
I'm Maria.
I'm Ben. Nice to meet you.
--They say they want you
to teach them juggling.
--I'm Andy.
What?
I'm Maggie.
We're thinking about doing a juggling
show for our friend's birthday party.
But we can't do it well.
We watched a magician's video and practiced.
You're also a specialist at
juggling, aren't you Rosetta?
Oh, yes.
The party is tomorrow.
Please teach us.
Please on my behalf too.
Okay.
First, please show me your juggling.
Yay!
The one we're going to do is bouncing balls.
We're going to bounce balls
on the ground and juggle them.
We will use three balls.
Ready, go!
Sheesh...
Good, good.
All you guys are much better than I am.
What? Really?
We can't perform like this!
When I started, I had a hard
time handling even two balls well.
So, all you guys have the
makings of good jugglers.
Wow. You guys were praised by a genius girl.
Everyone, do your best!
Sora, you too. Let's practice together.
What?
Okay, then I'll start
teaching you one at a time.
If you stay calm and patient,
I'm sure all of you will improve.
Do this rhythm, one, two, three.
Now, one, two, three.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
I think I'm getting better.
The most important thing is rhythm.
Oh, Sora. You're worse than Jonathan.
Everyone, you got a lot better.
I practiced every day
and I still can't do it.
Master!
Move your hands the way I move mine.
Don't be impatient. Relax your shoulders.
Okay.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
One, two, three. One...
Wow! I can do it.
I can do it!
You can't be impatient.
When you try too hard, it's hard
to get into the rhythm, isn't it?
One, two, three. One, two, three.
- -I see.
--One, two, three. One, two, three.
I was also being impatient with myself
for only being able to do the diabolo.
That's all I can teach you.
The thing you need to do is to
practice by yourself until tomorrow.
Thank you!
Excuse me, Master, but is it true
that you can't swing on the swings?
Hey, it's rude to ask
her something like that!
It's true.
And if I cannot learn how to get on a
swing by today, I have to quit Kaleido Stage.
What?!
Are you serious?
It's not true, is it?
I'll teach you.
Put your butt down like this,
and rock your body back and forth.
Then you will be perfect.
Thank you, Andy.
Then, let's have you try it!
Here, Rosetta, have a seat right here.
It's your turn this time, Rosetta.
Rosetta, don't be impatient.
Relax your shoulders.
Your body's rhythm is the important thing!
I know what to do.
Yeah!
Please teach me.
Here, sit down, sit down.
Let me take charge of your body.
Okay, here I go.
Now!
Wait, Sora!
I saw Kaleido Stage.
Where, where?
Behind us.
I can't see it.
I saw it a second ago.
I think I didn't swing enough.
Then, let's swing more!
Go! Go way up!
Look!
It's true.
Rosetta...
What, Sora?
You're the one rocking
the swing now, you know.
No way.
I'm not doing anything.
Amazing. I was able to rock the swing.
But, I know this is not
good enough for Kalos.
Don't worry. I'll go
apologize to him with you.
Thank you, Sora.
We'll be together all the time, Sora.
I couldn't keep the promise.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I don't remember any promise.
I promised that I was going to withdraw
if I couldn't learn the trapeze in three days.
Oh, that.
So, I need to withdraw?
Rosetta...
Three years!
--What?
--Excuse me?
Rosetta, I expect you to be the top
star of the trapeze three years from now.
Then...
The things you were talking about on the
phone, I don't remember agreeing with you.
Sora... I'm...
Isn't this great?
We're able to appear on stage together.
I'm so happy!
Don't relax your efforts, you two.
Don't skip a practice.
Three years will fly by before you know it.
Of course, I intend to
practice the trapeze very hard.
So, I won't be able to do my diabolo
show more than three times a week.
Are you serious?
I am serious, Boss.
Let's go, Sora.
Oh, then. Excuse us.
Three years from now,
I'll do the legendary great
maneuver with Sora for sure!
Rosetta's already started
walking with her own feet.
In order to be a real Kaleido Star,
I also have to start walking
forward! Forward! Forward!
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
Miss Layla...
Sora!
And so, I'm going to
co-star with that Miss Layla?!
Wait for a second!
I'll be the one to pair with Miss Layla!
Oh, May, please don't get in my way.
I wanted to see you, Miss Layla.
Layla! Layla!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Ever Amazing Miss Layla."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...