Wow!
Makopi's going to star in a movie!
Snow White
Kenzaki Makoto
And she's playing the leading role in Snow White!
I'm excited!
Snow White
Kenzaki Makoto
Are you playing the wicked queen, Davi?
I sure am... NOT!
tori Tamaki
The queen's being played by Ootori Tamaki!
Ootori Tamaki...
They call her the young queen of the film industry!
Yeah, the queen!
That's why Makoto has her hopes up!
She thought it might be the princess!
Snow White
Director
Toudou Izumi
Queen / Old Woman
Ootori Tamaki
Snow White
Kenzaki Makoto
But when we met her for real...
I'm Kenzaki Makoto.
I look forward to working with you.
Just don't be dead weight.
She was more like a wicked queen!
Really...
I'm sure she was just in character.
Huh?
Makopi's asleep.
She looks tired.
She's so busy with filming during the day,
but she still spends every night searching for the princess.
Makopi...
You were pushing yourself so much, and we didn't even know...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Super Busy!
Makoto's Idol Life!
My oh my,
Solitaire
you seem quite busy.
But I've gotta keep going!
Thanks to you all,
we've found two Royal Crystals,
so the princess must be close.
Hey Makopi, can we go with you to work today?
We can't let you work so hard alone!
If we're with you, we might find a way to help out.
I second this proposal!
You girls...
Yotsuba Studios
Morning!
Good morning!
Why the "Good mornings?"
No matter what time it is at a studio,
the greeting for when you start your work day is "Good morning."
Because people start working at all hours of the day!
You know a lot, Alice!
Her dad owns the place,
so Alice knows this stuff!
So your dad owns a studio...
It's Takakura Yuujirou!
Oh, it is.
Good morning!
Hey, Mana?
Oh, morning.
So cool!
I wish Mom could be here too!
It's over.
Mana's getting caught up in everything but helping Makopi.
But I'm kind of relieved.
I might catch some of Mana's energy.
If you catch anyone's, it'll be Mana's!
You say something?
All right!
Whether it's work or searching for the princess, I can do it!
All right, we're starting the rehearsal!
Break a leg.
You too.
My heart's pounding!
Yeah!
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all?
It would be my queen, of course.
But nay, it is Snow White!
What? Snow White?
We're doing the next scene!
The queen disguises herself as an old woman to give Snow White the apple.
Now, Ootori, come over here...
Princess, where might you be?
And Makoto will be...
Makoto?
Right!
You good to go?
I'm sorry!
Makoto...
All right, back to rehearsing!
Excuse me, young lady...
might you like a juicy apple?
Oh no, my line!
Cut!
Makoto, you gotta relax!
I'm sorry.
I've been having my doubts,
but are you even paying attention?
Are you letting your mind wander?
Well...
Honestly, you disappoint me.
She's scary!
Getting scolded that harshly will put her on edge!
Even so, it's unfitting for an actress.
The moment she steps on stage,
she ceases to be Makoto, and is instead Snow White!
I see...
It's a strict line of work.
We're restarting the rehearsal!
Keep it together!
You need to focus on acting!
You can do it!
Oh Prince, wherever might you be?
I wish to see you right this moment!
You sure don't look like you do.
Wait, what happened?
Ootori Tamaki won't continue the performance.
You didn't practice much, did you?
Your script is still crisp.
A lot of viewers are looking forward to this movie's completion.
If you don't care, then go home.
Ouch...
Kenzaki Makoto
What the heck, Ootori Tamaki?!
She's more wicked than the wicked queen!
Yeah, what Davi said!
Hey Makopi, do you want to go eat dinner at my place?
Grandpa and the others would love to see you!
Thank you,
but shooting starts early tomorrow.
I see...
Well, maybe next time!
Call me if you don't get around to doing your homework.
I would be pleased to help you as well.
Yotsuba Studios
Will Makopi be all right?
I hope she gets a good night's sleep,
but she'll probably be practicing her lines.
Makoto is quite the hard worker.
Makopi looks pretty worn out today.
Looks like she's been filming since morning.
Actually, she went out searching for the princess last night after practice.
She just can't stay still.
Neither can I!
With Makoto working so hard on her own,
I just can't sit back and watch!
Hey, Makoto?
If it's too much, you can always quit.
No, I'm fine.
Just like Tamaki said,
there are people looking forward to this movie.
I can't just throw this away.
But still...
you've already done plenty.
No.
I haven't done enough.
My script is still so crisp,
but Tamaki's is worn down from being read so many times.
I have to push myself more and more!
You've changed, Makoto.
You're not just about the princess.
You care about the people who support you, too.
In that case, how about leaving the search for the princess to us?
We want to help you, Makopi!
We're your allies!
You girls...
Can I really ask you to do that?
Of course.
I'm touched that you'd ask us!
You don't have to push yourself alone.
Thank you.
Then, take these with you.
The Crystals glowed the last time they were brought together, so that may happen again.
Also, if you get close to the princess,
these Crystals might let you know.
Okay, I've got it!
So Makopi, relax and focus on your work!
Yeah!
All right.
Now, I'm going to focus on my acting!
I won't let Tamaki outdo me!
For the staff that support us from behind the scenes,
and for my friends that are working hard for my sake...
We'll start the actual filming now!
Now, action!
Oh Prince, wherever might you be?
I wish to see you right this moment.
Makoto's doin' good today.
She's really into it.
Not good enough.
More...
I know you're capable of more.
I'm sorry!
I'd like to try that one more time!
Oh Prince, wherever might you be?
I wish to see you right this moment!
Prince!
What's this supposed to be?
It's the corn you requested...
What's it look like?
That's why I'm asking why you got me a corn cob!
Huh?
You were the one saying you wanted to eat corn!
The corn I want to eat isn't on a cob,
it's rich, luxuriously buttered corn!
You kiddin' me?!
If you want your corn buttered, you should specify...
What's the difference, anyway?
You meanies!
I'm done with you.
Oh, wherever might you be,
my good ol', rich, luxuriously buttered corn-esque girl?
That's a thing?!
We couldn't find the princess today.
The Royal Crystals didn't respond, either.
Makoto's doing all she can,
so we should find something in her stead!
Yeah!
Phone call from Davi!
Girls, here's a message from Makoto!
We finished most of the shoot today, so tomorrow will be the last one.
Feel free to come watch!
Tomorrow's her last day.
We've gotta go see her!
Yeah!
Yotsuba Studios
Hm?
Oh, the guy from Solitaire!
Oh, what perfect timing!
I came to deliver some props to Makoto's movie set,
but I don't know which studio to go to.
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all?
It would be my queen, of course.
But nay, it is Snow White!
Snow White?!
Indeed...
How could this be?
The fairest one in all the lands...
should be none other than I!
Loathsome!
Oh, how I loathe thee, Snow White!
Amazing...
Tamaki really is amazing!
Found ya!
My good ol' buttered corn!
Or should I say,
a selfish girl!
It's you!
Why are you here?
Well ya see,
I smelled someone selfish,
so I made my way here.
Right?
You're selfish, aren't you?
Who are you, child?
Tamaki, get back!
The heck?
Who's she?
It'd be my pleasure!
For me to become your master, that is!
Shut your mouth.
Now stop interfering with our performance.
Leave this place at once!
Pooey!
Don't order me around!
My orders are absolute, though.
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
Mirror Selfish!
What's that?!
Why?
Tamaki isn't selfish in the least!
Really? But what human isn't selfish?
Well, with my magic, I can turn anyone into a Selfish.
Selfish!
Shiiiiiiine!
I felt a dark heartbeat!
It came from the studio!
Makopi!
Everyone and everything...
burn from my reflecting!
She's burning everything!
Makopi!
Girls!
Are you okay?
Take Tamaki somewhere safe!
Allow me.
Now everyone, this way.
Let's go, girls!
Right!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor mirror who has lost her love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
If you wanna try, be my guests.
Reflection Ray!
Reflect!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Sparkle Swo—
Cut!
Get her, Selfish!
Now, shine!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Rosetta!
Don't worry. Let's fight together!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Now, Cure Heart!
Right!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Nullifying Mirror!
How's my Selfish?
Great, isn't it?
No...
The Heart Shoot had no effect!
Does that mean we can't purify the Selfish?
What should we do?
Let's try with the four of us!
If we can't do it alone,
we can just combine our strengths, I'm certain!
You girls taught me that.
Sword...
Now!
We can do anything together!
Yeah!
Ai!
Kyupirappa!
This is...
A new Lovies!
Everyone, let's go!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooooove!
Thank goodness.
Yeah!
We did it!
Wow, you guys beat up my Selfish!
Haven't we seen you before?
Who might you be?
I am Regina.
King Selfish's daughter.
Huh?!
King Selfish's... daughter?
Welp, see ya!
Snow White
Sneak Preview
Kenzaki Makoto
Ootori Tamaki
Everyone, we humbly thank you for attending.
Thanks to you all, we were able to complete a wonderful film.
I'd like to thank the fans and staff for supporting us, and...
a certain hard working, irreplaceable partner.
Huh?
Tamaki's compliment made me so happy.
Let's exchange scripts.
To remember this for life.
A Royal Crystal!
It's as though they called for each other!
Princess...
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Mana, I'll let you be my friend!
Huh? Regina?!
She seems to have taken a liking to Mana.
Let's play, Mana!
I can't! I'm in class!
Aw, just skip it.
I can't just...
Regina's an enemy, so how could she be our friend?
I don't know what Mana's thinking...
Dokidoki Precure:
Regina's Fierce Attack!
Mana Belongs to Me!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!