Seconds!
Coming!
This isn't how it's supposed to be!
Why have you been eating breakfast at my place?
Rather,
How come you're accepting her just like that?
No reason.
Taiga-chan is small, so she doesn't use much space.
Besides, the more the merrier.
Give me more already.
Wha-
I cooked 3 gou...
How much do you eat!?
I'm sorry.
What?
Are you making your own pet bald from stress?
Don't make it any more disgusting.
Don't call it disgusting!
They say that pets resemble their masters, but...
Damn you...
So ungrateful!
How could you be like that to me, when I make breakfast, supper and even a packed lunch for you?
Shut up, useless dog.
You're calling me that again!?
Give back the lunch!
Along with my kind feelings!
Shut up. And rot.
W-Wait Aisaka!
Since that midnight attack, Aisaka Taiga started eating with us.
I said wait!
And...
Besides that,
act properly when you get to school, okay?
About me with Kitamura-kun... to properly, um...
help get us together, okay?
Since you did promise to work for me like a dog!
...that's how it is.
If it doesn't turn out well...
Minorin!
You're late, Taiga!
Right! You're fine today as well!
Good morning, Minorin!
No way! What!?
I'm sorry, I didn't know!
That you and Takasu-kun were having a relationship where you walk to school side by side, in a two-shot style.
You're wrong!
Nobody would use such an expression these days.
That isn't the point.
So then, nowadays it's...
I'm so out of my mind, that I don't know how to say it in modern terms!
Oh yeah, I got it, it's avec!
That's not what I'm trying to say!
Aisaka and I only met there.
Right, Aisa-
Oh, it's just a coincidence.
It seems like he lives close by.
Um...
So then, see you later, Takasu-kun!
On TV yesterday...
I get it.
If I want to get together with Kushieda, I have to get Aisaka and Kitamura together first.
Then so be it!
All right, we're done with the streching!
And now, pair up to pass the ball.
Hey, Aisaka, let's team up!
Yes, we shall, Takasu-kun!
Yeah!
Now practice!
What's up, Takasu and Aisaka? You seem to be really eager.
Taiga?
Oh, it must be that...
The plan is simple.
I gently hit the person who's teaming up with Kitamura.
And...
I overreact and send him to the nurse's office.
Then Aisaka and Kitamura will be left behind to pair up.
Maruo!
Let's do it together.
Anyone want to pair with me?
Sure, I'm all up for it.
But stop calling me that.
But you're just like him!
Huh?
Kitamura-kun with some strange woman!?
What is this?
Right in my stomach.
Kushieda, why not do it with me?
Okay, let's do it.
Even Kushieda!?
Someone want to do it with me?
Oh well, start the plan.
But you...
It doesn't matter if it's a boy or a girl.
And the swelling of the arm muscle...
What's the matter, Haruta?
Throw without using the thumb!
It's not getting through, Kushieda.
The hard road to the satoru ball is surely steep.
Oh, it's nothing.
Only for people who can follow it.
That damn Noto.
Hey, pass!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Pass!
Pass, pass!
Here it goes, Maruo!
Okay!
Nice throwing.
What are you saying, Maruo?
Hey, pass!
Pass...?
I can't hit girls.
Pass!
Sorry, Kihara.
I shall repent my sins later.
Alter ego!
Huh?
Sorry, Maruo!
Huh? What happened!?
Takasu-kun finished off the Tenori Taiga!
Ah, shit.
Tenori Taiga is the kind of girl who would bite anyone without distinction.
But it's obvious that she is working so hard; to the point that it looks bad.
And it's not that I don't feel like helping her.
Alright,
give it to him naturally, okay?
Don't do it too formally, okay?
I-I got it.
Naturally, okay.
Thoughtlessly, effortlessly, and with a light ass.
Let's go.
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Kitamura went to the "B" building saying he had something to do, I think.
Takasu-kun!
He just left, so he should still be around.
There he is!
Let's follow him!
Y-Yes!
What?
Out of my way!
It's Takasu!
She's fast!
Well, she should catch up.
Ryuji!
How are the cookies?
Huh?
That hurt.
It's a bump.
Found it?
Were they okay?
I see.
Hey.
Could I be... a klutz?
And you just realize that?
If I try to give a love letter, I get the wrong bag.
If I try to make an assault, then I faint from starvation.
If I play basketball, it's only to be hit in the face by the ball.
If I try to catch someone to give him some cookies...
I fall.
And let them fall.
Well, well, you still have more.
Like forgetting to put the letter inside the envelope.
That's right.
Let me have one of those.
They're all broken.
And it's...
It's great!
You did it properly.
Too bad for you.
Let's work hard next time.
I surely saw it.
They were buying leeks and radishes in the supermarket together.
Like if they were a married couple!
They came out of the same apartment in the morning.
I feel lots of erotic stuff coming.
And they were eating handmade cookies together.
Going "Here, open up."
Oh, really?
No way.
Hey, Minori?
How's your best friend?
What the heck?
Hurry up and get in, will you?
Can I ask you something?
The sun is dry.
What's up with Kushieda-san?
I don't know.
Takasu-kun.
Yes!
Huh, me?
I entrust Taiga's well-being to you!
What?
Taiga is my beloved best friend.
Please, I beg you to make her happy!
Wait, Kushieda.
Could that mean...?
Happy?
So that's how it is.
Congratulations to you two.
Kitamura?
Why are you there?
I thought you two were often together, but...
Come to think of it, you two do match well.
Aisaka!
Keep it together!
You there, stop laughing!
Takasu-kun,
if you make Taiga cry
I will never forgive you.
Kushieda...
I'm horrible, aren't I?
Just because I barged into your house
you've been misunderstood by Minorin.
No, that's...
It felt nice there,
your house, that is.
I am...
...not on good terms with my parents.
I said, "I want to get out of this house."
Then I was given that apartment.
Although I knew that's how my parents were.
Weren't those cookies salty?
I was upset to see them all broken and ate some.
What was that? The worst?
But you still ate it all.
And even lied.
You're supposed to be a useless dog, but you try to be so caring.
You'll become bald.
That's none of your business.
Hey, do you also worry about Minorin?
Yeah, I do.
Of course you do...
Aisaka?
Why does no one understand?
When we have so many worries...
Why does no one know?
Really, everyone...
Everyone...
Everyone, everyone...
I'm pissed off!
Pissed off, pissed off, pissed off!
What's with "Tenori Taiga"!?
I'm not fine with that at all!
Stupid Minorin! Stupid Kitamura-kun.
Why won't any of them listen to me?
My mother and father too!
Nobody does!
They don't understand me!
Let's team up.
What's wrong with being small!?
Don't simply call me "yankee"!
What's wrong with this name!?
Sorry for having such a bad look!
Hey, are you okay?
Ryuji, isn't it a bit slanted?
No, it can't be-
It's slanted!?
Ain't it?
Woohoo!
I won!
Alright, then it's decided.
Tomorrow I will confess my love to Kitamura-kun.
And I will make it the end.
The end?
No more doggy work.
From tomorrow on, we are classmates with our houses right next to each other.
That's it.
Bye-bye, Takasu-kun.
Yeah...
Ryu-chan,
isn't today breakfast a bit weird?
I do like boiled canned mackerel, but...
I wonder if Taiga-chan is still asleep.
Who knows?
Did you two have a fight?
Not at all.
It's boring.
Right?
Uh huh...
H-Hi.
This is...?
T-Takasu.
We've been so bad to you.
Making strange rumors.
We were scolded by Aisaka-san.
"There's nothing between me and Ryuji..."
and "Ryuji is not a yankee," she swore to us.
Tenori Taiga is scary after all.
But I also said Takasu wasn't scary, right?
When?
Rather, shouldn't we clean this up, or we'll be in trouble?
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun, I'm sorry.
F-For what?
Taiga said,
"I would never go out with Takasu-kun."
So it's all a misunderstanding.
Taiga said she wanted me to understand.
She had, how should I say, a serious... a dead serious face.
But that means...
That means...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Takasu-kun!?
That girl...
What is she doing?
Isn't she going to confess to Kitamura today?
Is it time for her to be worrying about others?
From tomorrow on, we are classmates with our houses right next to each other.
That's it.
"That's it," she says.
Kitamura-kun!
I... Kitamura-kun.
About Kitamura-kun.
Um...
Well...
Hey, man.
Right after getting to school?
If it doesn't turn out well, the whole day will be miserable.
Wait a sec.
I seem to understand where you're going.
But before that, let me confirm one thing.
Aren't you going out with Takasu?
That was Minorin's misunderstanding.
There was nothing between me and Takasu-kun.
Don't you like Takasu?
It's not like that.
It's just that our homes are close by.
It's not that I like him or anything.
Then do you hate him?
I don't hate him.
But that's different.
It's not like that.
Um, Takasu-kun is...
Well...
Yes, fried rice.
Yes, he made me delicious fried rice!
He encouraged me.
He even lied to cheer me up.
And spent time with me.
Because he was there...
Because he was there for me.
So,
now I can have courage like this.
I love Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka,
you're amazing.
I see.
It's okay.
I think your feelings are being properly conveyed.
Kitamura-kun?
Do you remember, Aisaka?
It was a year ago.
Yes...
You began to show
more interesting faces back then.
Interesting faces?
Yeah.
While you were with Takasu, you showed very interesting faces.
Takasu is a really good guy.
And
to be able to think of him in that way, you really are a nice girl.
In that way?
What did I say?
Anyways, I'm relieved you are getting along with Takasu.
W-W-Wait a sec.
It has nothing to do with Ryuji.
Um, is my face interesting?
That's not my point.
What was I talking about? Oh, what did I say?
Did I properly say I love you?
It's alright, Aisaka.
It's alright.
Alright? What is?
Even though I don't know what I said.
It's alright.
We will become really good friends.
As I'm saying, not friends but a confession.
Friends?
Yes, friends.
We will be late for homeroom.
You hurry too.
I thought you'd cry.
W-W-What are you doing?
Were you watching?
Not on purpose.
Not on purpose but yo-
Rather, what are you going to do?
I'm going home.
I see.
Then I will make a meal for you.
You haven't had breakfast have you?
Rather, did you have a proper dinner last night?
You had another convenience store me-
Stop it!
If you do something like that, you'll be misunderstood again!
You don't have to do that stuff anymore!
I don't understand it,
but...
I can't leave you like that.
I said you don't have to!
You aren't my dog anymore!
I see.
Yes, I am not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
So,
I can be beside you! Ai-
Taiga!
You called me Taiga?
From ancient times, it has been decided...
...that the one who stands beside the Tiger has to be a Dragon.
I will become the dragon.
And...
...stand beside you as a Dragon.
How cheeky can you be!? Know your place!
Why you!
Wha, hey!
Hurry up! I'm hungry.
And we're making the next plan okay?
I won't give up on Kitamura-kun just like that.
Does that mean...?
I don't care if it's a dog or a Dragon.
You said you would stay beside me,
so work hard for me, got it?
Ryuji...
That was too rash of me.
Now hurry up!
Alright, alright.
He said Taiga...
Club activity girl Kushieda.
Working girl Kushieda.
You are Kushieda.
Always, anywhere, you glitter brightly.
Go and give them a shot.