Kiss, kiss, kiss!
kiss
mo
u
mu
I can't take my eyes off you.
Sakura
do
ki
Just being by your side
makes my heart throb.
My racing heartbeat
refuses to stop.
Even though we're just friends,
I feel like we should be more.
I don't know what I'll do
if things stay this way.
I've got this burning curiosity in my heart.
So why don't we do something
You're kidding!
nai
ko
to
ga
nobody else would do?
kiss
Won't you kiss me?
kiss
It'll be our special little secret.
I'm always here for you,
so won't you accept every bit of me?
kiss
Can I kiss you?
kiss
It'll be an unforgettable memory.
Picturing a heated kiss between us
makes my lips tremble with anticipation.
kiss
kiss
ha
na
re
I can't take my eyes off you.
West Misato High School
Look who's awake.
You slept through homeroom.
When did I...
Where's Haruka?
Oh, Haruka-chan left already.
Wait, hear me out. It's not like she left left.
She just went with Yuzu-chan
and the others to get some tea.
Pout
She left me?
W-Well...
Man, I'm out...
Where have you been, Kotone?
I got asked to clean up the library.
Talk about exhausting!
Sob
What are you two up to?
Shizuku-chan, did you make her cry?
It wasn't me!
At least, I don't think it was!
Let's Have Tea with the Sister!
They probably went to the café nearby.
We could go meet up with them.
Besides, their green tea cakes are delicious!
Green tea?!
I've been dying to have some cheesecake,
or maybe some strawberry chiffon cake!
An apple pie would be delicious, too!
Blueberry tarts have a lot going for them,
but lemon cake is the perfect combination of sweet and sour!
Tiramisu has that slightly bitter flavor...
We'll figure it out once we get there.
Sakura
Misato
Urban Area
Why'd Haruka have to go without me?
She could have woken me up...
I'll tease her by clinging to
Kotone-chan in front of her!
Oh my!
You know, it kinda feels like we're a family.
Maybe it does.
If we're a family,
I'm totally the mother.
Sorry about inviting you on such short notice.
Did you want to discuss something?
We'll talk about that over some drinks.
It's on us.
I see...
We're here!
Look at that.
This place is really crowded today.
And we rushed over here after class, too...
Guess everyone else had the same idea.
Great minds think alike.
Hey!
A table just opened up.
I'll go grab it.
Sounds good!
We'll order some drinks then.
Let's go.
Sure!
Big
Sister
On second thought, you two go get us a table.
We'll go order instead.
Slipped right through!
Um... I'd like to know why you girls asked me to come here.
Well...
Hey!
What?!
You look a lot like your sister, don't you?
Like... your eyes, mouth, and nose.
S-So we're the same?
No, there are plenty of differences!
For instance, Yuu-chan's cheeks are much softer!
F-Fine! I get it!
She's really staring me down.
Stare . . .
So what did you want to talk about?
Your hairpin!
Huh?
Big
Sister
Let me fix it!
It's okay! I can fix it myself!
Please! I insist!
Her face turned red...
You know, whenever I get close to Yuu-chan, she blushes a bit, too.
There's a lot you two have in common!
"Whenever you get close to Yuu-chan"?
Exactly how close do you mean?
Ah!
Sakura
You also share some similarities with Yuu.
I do?
She's been trying to not bring you up in our conversations,
but as soon as she slips up, it's all about you.
And you're the same.
You're always talking about her...
Even when we're apart, Yuu-chan thinks about me...
Feels...
I find it a bit unfair.
Huh?
President Mitsuki just said it was unfair.
Does that mean...
she doesn't like her sister talking about me?
Big
Sister
Little
I won't give you my sister!
I won't
give you my sister !
Does she secretly hate me?!
She didn't respond to my text, so I kinda just guessed.
Here's hoping she likes it.
Don't worry about it.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Clunk
President Mitsuki, here's a green tea latte.
It's like you read my mind or something!
Nailed it!
Why'd you invite me, anyway?
You had something to discuss, did you not?
There are a bunch of events planned for the cultural festival, right?
Correct.
We're wondering if you wanna help out with ours!
Huh?
It's a rendition of Snow White.
That's your project, isn't it?
Besides, why do I have to be the Huntsman?!
Getting a bit ahead of yourself there.
President Mitsuki...
Yuu-chan told me something.
It's the last cultural festival I'll have with my sister.
Flash
Back
I wanna do something special!
You see?
For us, it'll be the only festival
with all three years participating.
Still, to ask for an answer on such a short notice is...
C'mon! We totally had your back, remember?
Help a girl out!
Sec!
Huddle up!
What should we do?
The bribe-her-with-food-and-drinks plan didn't work out as expected.
Guess we just have to ask nicely.
There's no other option, is there?
Thanks, Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan.
Let's head back.
Huh?
Guess who!
You guys came?
We were planning to meet you back at school.
I wanted to surprise Yuu-chan, but...
What, is us coming against the law?
Not exactly, but...
Anyway, Haruka, fetch me another.
What?! Did you drink all of mine?!
You drank it all...
Wipe that grin off your face!
Haruka, buy me a green tea latte.
Ka-ching
I wonder if I have enough money...
Actually, I might not.
I'm sorry!
Yuu... Can't you see you're causing her trouble?
Give me a sec.
Do you want more to drink, Yuu?
Come over here. You can finish mine.
It's green tea flavored!
Green tea!
Drink
Coupon
I have a coupon!
Huh?
This green tea tastes great!
Pat
No way!
Are you declaring war, President Mitsuki?
I won't rest until... I get you to accept me!
I'll never stop trying!
I wonder why she's so worked up.
I was simply doing what a sister should...
Today's probably a lost cause.
Yep. Let's try again some other day.
President Mitsuki!
Huh?
We'll be heading off now.
L-Let me join you!
President Mitsuki didn't say she'd help us...
Green Tea Baumkuchen
She's trying to lure me in!
What is it?!
What's up?
Don't leave me behind!
I like being with you,
so don't just go off by yourself!
Yuu-chan!
Aw...
R
ub
You're so selfish.
R
ub
Let me be selfish today.
You know,
if you don't tell me what you
want, I can't give it to you.
You meanie.
Just kidding.
I'll kiss you as much as you want.
Let's Have Tea with the Sister!
The End
Good morning, Yuu-chan!
Morning, Haruka!
You know how we're doing Snow White for the upcoming cultural festival?
What part do you want to play?
The Witch.
Pierce
The Witch, huh?
Don't think I didn't see that! What are you chewing?!
Witches, Apples, and the Sister
President Mitsuki!
Ah
Big
Sister
What are you doing?
That's where the first-years are, you know.
Y-You're right!
I have something I need to do.
Apparently Yuu-chan wants to be the Witch!
Hold on!
The Witch is also the Queen, right?
I wanted to be the Queen!
Well, the Witch is certainly popular.
Why are you two fighting?
Wow, Yuu, you're passionate
about the strangest things.
It's not strange! The Witch is cool!
I'm surprised Shizuku wanted
to be the Witch, though.
Well, considering what the Witch went through...
Maybe she relates to her somehow...
Fu
You've just gotta laugh! I mean, talking to a mirror? Seriously?
That's your rationale?
Okay, how about this?
Snow White
Let's do a little read through,
and then we'll pick who should be the Witch.
Fair maiden! Dost thou wish for an apple?
I'll totally take one!
Calm down, Haruka.
Snow White
Fair maiden...
Dost thou wish for an apple?
Too much realism!
I'm scared!
Ye
ah!
Shizuku-chan, that's so cute!
You call that cute?!
Now, which one of us witches...
...will you call true?
Yuu-chan!
Shizuku-chan!
This is gonna be tough.
Hit
Someone's staring at me...
Hey, Kaede...
President Mitsuki's kinda staring at us.
Seems that way.
Don't tell me she's here to spy on Haruka and Yuu...
Oh, I know!
She totally wants in on this Snow White thing!
Her mind says yes, but her body says no...
I highly doubt that.
And get this!
They looked this way!
Did they see me?!
I'll retreat for now!
Hold it!
The student council president is the last
person who should be running in the halls.
Uh, well...
Onee-chan?
This just had to happen!
I was simply taking long strides.
That ain't gonna fly.
Sakura
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Nothing's wrong!
I was merely passing by!
I interrupted you, didn't I?
My apologies. See you later, Yuu.
Smells fishy.
Hm
mm
I know your secret.
You were interested in the Snow White thing,
but you couldn't bring yourself to say it,
so you were just lurking around!
Snow White
You're wrong! I was honestly just passing by!
C'mon now...
All because Haruka-san caught my eye!
You know, I've been seeing
President Mitsuki around a lot more.
Really? Like when?
During our lunch breaks, she's been staring from outside the door.
Seriously? Does she really do that?
Maybe she just watches from afar,
unable to say anything.
You think?
That has to be it.
Why don't you call out to her, huh?
I'm sure she's just shy!
Hold on, why are you crying?
Wait!
Does this mean that you'll join us, President Mitsuki?
Stop putting words in my mouth!
Really?!
Awesome!
They're kidding!
I'm not joining you.
Onee-chan, this is the last cultural festival we'll go to together!
Please! For Yuu-chan's sake!
UHHHH
HHHHH
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
C'mon, Onee-chan!
C'mon!
Well, Prez? How 'bout it?
You know, this would be a great opportunity to observe those two without drawing suspicion.
That's true.
If I joined, I'd have more
opportunities to talk to Haruka-san...
No!
Pull it together!
I'll do it so I can keep an eye on those two!
Well, that works for me!
Everyone!
President Mitsuki said she'll
play the role of Snow White!
Really?!
Snow White
Thank you, Onee-chan!
Hold on a second!
I did agree to participate,
but I didn't agree to play Snow White!
Well, you got any other part in mind?
Snow White
There's only one part for me.
Bam
The Huntsman!
At least you're consistent.
Why don't you read the script first?
Thank you.
Truth be told, I forget what Snow White's even about.
Snow White
A quick primer!
What? There's a kissing scene at the end!
Hold on. It's not like Haruka-san is going to be Snow White.
I guess she could pull off a decent Prince, though.
Wait!
Big
Sister
Wait
I'm getting off track!
What's the matter, Onee-chan?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
What character are you playing, Haruka-san?
Me?
Well, if Yuu-chan's going to be the Witch...
Maybe I'll be the Queen's Handmaid.
Or maybe even the Huntsman or the Prince!
I want to be the Huntsman, though.
Perhaps you should find another role.
Huh?
Wait...
Grrr
Is she trying to prevent me from... acting with Yuu?
P-President Mitsuki!
I really think that Snow White fits you best!
I-If anything, it suits you better!
I'm not cut out for that kind of role.
That's not true!
Well, you won't know unless you try!
Hey, that sounds like a good idea.
What?
Let's start with the scene where the
Witch's apple brings down Snow White.
Wait! Hold on!
About the Witch...
Yeah, we've still got two.
Let's try a different scene.
w
White
How about the scene where the Prince wakes up Snow White?
Wait! I would think the first one...
ow White
Haruka, you be the Prince, okay?
Got it!
Snow White
She fell!
What a diva!
Why is it always Haruka-san?
Snow White
Acting or not, kissing her is just...
No. I suggested the idea.
Snow White
I can't back down now.
Big
Sister
Have at me!
Snow White
Having fun down there?
Huh?
President Mitsuki isn't waking up...
Snow White
Maybe she doesn't know that we're just doing a read through!
To be fair, none of us have told her that part...
Snow White
What do I do?
U-Um...
Just get it over with!
Snow White
O-Okay!
Well, I'll just play along for now.
We'll explain things to her later.
Snow White
Ow!
Yuu-chan, what was that for?!
Onee-chan!
Snow White
Wake up, Onee-chan!
What are you lying down for?
Snow White
Huh? What's wrong?
All we're doing is reading! Now stand up!
What?
Wait, there's no...
You should've said that earlier!
After
School
Sakura
West Misato High School
Eyes on me, Haruka.
I'm gonna bewitch you.
I'm so glad President Mitsuki's
going to join us for Snow White!
Yuu-chan seems happy, too.
Did you see that?
Totally witchy, wasn't it?
See what?
Why weren't you watching?!
I'm gonna have to do this!
That's your punishment for not watching!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'll watch properly!
Take it off! Please!
H-Hold on!
Uh... Fair maiden! Dost thou wish for an apple?!
Just do it normally!
I'll take one of your fruits.
Go ahead...
Witches, Apples, and the Sister
The End
Big
Sister
A day in the life of Shizuku-chan!
A day in the life of Shizuku-chan
Obligatory fanservice.
Bonus
A day in the life of Shizuku-chan
The End
Love!
love
Won't you kiss?
won chu kiss
Kiss and love!
kiss and love
We've spent so much time together.
futari dake no jikan ga
We have secrets that no-one else knows,
futari dake no himitsu ga
and promises made between the two of us,
futari dake no yakusoku
just for us.
aru kara ne
We'll share in our joys.
yorokobi wakachiaete
We'll split our sorrows,
kanashimi wakeaetara
and we'll eventually find the happiness that comes
hitori yori shiawase ni
from being together.
nareru youni
Today was filled with great memories.
ashita mo omoide wo
So let's make tomorrow even greater.
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichauyo ne
Love you!
love you
It's a miracle that we could meet in this wide world of ours.
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
You're the thing that matters most in my life right now.
tokubetsu nano anata janai to dame dakara
There's something that I can't do with anyone but you.
futari janai to dekinai koto dayo
So hold me dear, with your kiss and love!
imasugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love!
love
Next Time
Shizuku-chan, why do you tie your hair up like that?
Well, I get to use some cute scrunchies...
Really? I think you'd be cuter if you let your hair down.
Y-You think?
I don't think! I know!
So start letting your hair down, okay?
Yuu-chan, are you trying to
monopolize the pigtail market?
Th-That's not it!
Don't look away!
Next time, on Trick 6!
It's the Cultural FestivalOSleepover Edition
It's the Cultural FestivalOFor Real!
B
"It's the Cultural Festival O Sleepover Edition,"
and "It's the Cultural Festival O For Real!"
Get hype!
She avoided the question!