Mario...
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we can drop
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where rules and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10
xXxTrIsTxXx
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find out fast we’re not alone
Thanks to you guys, Mario is a free man.
So it's on the house today! Drink up!
All Right!!!
Man, that was a real pain.
But at least it's all over now.
It isn't over yet.
Haven't you forgotten something Turtle?
Huh?
Women! Women!
Introduce me to women!
O-Okay, okay! Just calm down!
"Bar"
No problem! Don't you worry!
Okay, lady! Hook him up with a cute girl!
Sure thing!
See you later! Good luck Scam!
W-Wait, this place is...!
You need to learn about women, before all else!
You need to train here and gain experience!
Got it!
Kiddo!
Come right this way!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
N-No problem...
What do you say we get started, kiddo!
Turtle!
"Noodle Shop"
Gimme some more noodles, Pops!
Coming right up!
What brings you here so suddenly, Mario?
Oh, I know!
You want to ask me to another movie?
No, I guess not.
I forgot you don't like movies.
Say...
Joe's told you, hasn't he?
I'm... getting married.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you, but...
He's actually a very nice person
and he thinks dearly of me.
I think things can work out with him.
I can be happy--
Mario was unable to contain
his passion as the rain began to fall.
"I love you! I don't want to let you go!
I don't want to give you to anyone!"
His young heart screamed out.
It's been a year and a half,
but I still can't stop thinking about him...
But I'm still getting married anyway...
I'm no good, Mario...
You shouldn't choose a girl like me.
I don't care. I love you.
That's all I can think about.
Setsuko wept because she knew that the dazzling love they had shared was
a spectacular firework that would never rise into the night sky again.
Thanks for the food!
Whoa, it’s really coming down.
Hey Turtle!
S-Scam…
I’m sorry!  Don’t be so mad!
The hell with you! I almost wound up having sex with that hag!
Okay, okay!
I’ll take you to a real place next---
What are you doing?!
Oh, you two are sopping wet.
Why don’t we have some fun instead?
Turtle… Money…
Huh?
Money! Money!
It’s time for me to become a man!
Umm… I’m sorry.
You really are young.
Setsuko?
Where are you, Setsuko?
Setsuko…?
Are you sure about this, Mario?
Today’s the day she’s…
Yeah. I’m just going to drop by to see how she looks.
Is that all?
Is that really all you want?!
Mario…
--What a beautiful bride!
--You can say that again!
Her parents look very happy!
Well, this is a proud moment for their cherished daughter.
You’re in love with Anchan, aren't you, Setsuko?
It’s obvious enough to tell that.
I was hoping you could be there to see him, Setsuko?
Anchan is… dead…
I love you.
That’s all I can think about.
Goodbye, Setsuko…
"Closed"
Cheers!
Okay! Let’s pray for Setsuko’s happiness by drinking like crazy!
Yeah!
--Is he all right?
--Beats me!
In that case, let’s celebrate my becoming a bonafide man too!
That’s worthy of celebration all right! Cheers!
It was with a professional though!
Shut up! Professionals and amateurs do the exact same thing!
See you later, Mario!
Yeah!
Whew, I drank too much…
Man, its cold…
“To Rokurote Sakuragi and Mario Minakami…
Thank you. Farewell. – Setsuko Koike”
Huh? Tokyo?!
And you’ve decided to go?
--Yeah…
--What?!
A friend of mine is opening a place in Shibuya
and asked if I knew any nice bartenders.
But…
Oh, don’t worry about me.
You're still young. Why not try polishing your skills in Tokyo?
Tokyo…
Plus Turtle and Joe work in Tokyo too.
Oh… You're leaving too?
What, are you lonely without anyone to have fun with?
Yeah…
Then you should just come to Tokyo too.
It's not like you have a steady job at that.
That's it! Why didn't I think of that?!
Huh?
Thank you!
Hey Yokosuka! Bring us some drinks!
Right!
Man, you're useless.
We're dead tired from our concert.
You could at least have some booze ready for us!
Yes, I'm very sorry.
Don't be like that, Charlie.
Yokosuka. Re-string my guitar, will ya?
R-Right!
Bring me some smokes, too!
Right!
"I don't care how much they order me around; I will become a singer!"
Joe knew that just as caterpillars become butterflies, this is the only industry
in which a blue-eyed ex-reformatory inmate can make it big.
Great work today! Good Night!
All right! I still have time!
Sorry...!
Turtle!
Oww… what're you in such a rush for, Joe?
I'm on my way to a jazz club in Akasaka. Want to come?
What the hell, Joe?!
We're not here to drink?!
I won't learn anything just by being those guys' band assistant.
I need to watch lots of other bands and concerts too
if I want to catapult to the top of this industry.
Our vocalist ain't here?!
I’m sorry! I haven’t been able to contact him!
Screw that! We’re up next, you know!
How are we supposed to play without a vocalist?!
Go find us one!
---Umm, if you’d like…
--Huh?!
…you can borrow my vocalist.
Huh?!
I can sing for you, if you wouldn’t mind.
I’m a band assistant for the Five Lemons. My name’s Joe Yokosuka.
I can cover a couple songs for you until your vocalist arrives.
--Who’s he?
--Who’s the boy?
Joe…
This is it… This is my chance…
Someday you’re going to let us hear
that song on a big stage, right?
You can do it, Joe!
Let’s start this party
Come on, everyone join in
It’s a euphoric morning
Lose that bored look on your face
Tap your feet
H-he’s really good!
Is he really just an assistant!
This is crazy! He’s captivated this many people in no time flat!
Raise your voices
“I did it! The audience is watching me! They’re listening to me!
"Big chances almost never come to ex-reformatory inmates like us.
So I’m going to wager everything on this chance.”
Joe sang, to take his first step to stardom.
Good morning!
U-Umm, is something wrong…?
What’s the matter, Yokosuka?!
It’s not your bedtime yet!
It’s still way too soon for a shitty band
assistant like you to take to the stage!
That band’s our business competition, too!
I-I’m sorry.
Asshole.
Hey. Let’s go.
Go on ahead.
Sure. Suit yourself, Mickey.
Here. Clean yourself up.
So, how was the concert yesterday?
It was your first time taking the stage too.
I heard you were a big hit with the crowd.
Having everyone’s eyes all on you…
Having everyone listening to you…
I love that moment…
It’s the greatest feeling I’ve ever had.
That’s why I’m a vocalist.
It was a real thrill for you too, wasn’t it?
Yes…
Tell me. Yokosuka.
You’ve never swallowed mercury, have you?
Huh?
They say that people who swallow mercury
lose their voices for the rest of their life…
I hate it. I hate it when people steal the spotlight from me.
I’m begging you, Yokosuka…
Don’t get in my way.
The vocalist spot is where I belong.
But if you insist on putting me aside…
I’ll be forced to take away your singing voice.
I-I won’t sing anymore…
Looks like you’ve been through the wringer.
A man like you shouldn’t be wasting
your time with a second-rate band like them.
Joe. I can make you a superstar.
Three months.
In three months you can be a star.
All you have to do is do what I say.
Trust me.
Alright?
Meg…
Letting others use us is the only way we can survive.
You’re right Meg.
Our parents abandoned us; this is
the only way we can survive now…
I’m prepared for it.
Joe?
Yes.
“If it means stardom, I don’t care if it takes three months or half a year. The
only way for us siblings to be happy is to endure this perverted hell.”
What could I keep watching over
same ta manazashi
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on running
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it now
a far off distance
An opportunity arises. Turtle is delighted.
Joe distances himself from his friends.