Sakuraba-senpai...
I need you.
S-Satomi-kun?
I want you to...
I...
Would you...
...enter this with me?!
Huh?
Club Obstacle Course
Marathon
A marathon?
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
Club Obstacle Course
Marathon
The Interclub Obstacle Course Marathon...
Friends and Promises
Yes, two people per club form a team.
I don't know if I'd be
much use to you in this...
I know you have a weak constitution,
but there's nothing to worry about.
Here, look!
"The best score from the pair will be used."
You can retire right after
the race begins, if you want.
I'm sorry for getting you involved,
but I need to do this!
I want to win this!
I'm asking you...
I understand. I'll enter with you.
Really?! Thank you!
Oh, sorry.
I want to finish the race if I enter.
That's fine, right?
Yes, of course,
but don't push yourself, okay?
Thank you,
but don't worry about me.
I'll try my best to finish.
Cosplay Society
Stop...
I just said I wanted to
enter the obstacle race...
so why are you taking off my clothes?!
Why else?
I need to measure you for your racing outfit.
So, you're going to start
training with her today?
Yeah, I'd like to get
in better shape for the race.
Oh, yeah. Sanae, what are
you going to do for it?
Huh?
Hm...
We can have Sanae pick
someone at the beginning,
and then have her place the same as them.
How about it?
Hm...
I guess if I had to pick someone...
It'd be you.
Huh? You're okay with me?
You seem like you're good
at this sort of thing.
Also, we have a truce right now.
I'm not going to let you down, Sanae.
I'm sure you'll do well,
but make sure you watch out
for Kiriha and Theia, okay?
I know.
They've gotten themselves
into their clubs, too.
She's getting good times,
and she's intelligent.
I think we should have
her enter the marathon.
Yeah, I think she'd make
a good pair with you.
Seems like I'll be able to get myself
onto the track and field team.
Karama, Korama.
Right here!
I want you to find anyone
within the school who
possesses greater athletic
prowess than I do.
Also, I want you to prepare some funds.
Leave it to us!
Now, say my name. Who is your ruler?
Princess Theiamillis!
I can't hear you...
Hail to the princess!
What is it, Ruth?
We've detected two flying objects
hiding themselves with
thermo-electromagnetic camouflage
above the school grounds.
They seem to be running reconnaissance.
Who are they?
Blue Knight has determined
with a 63% probability
that they are Kiriha's
Japanese haniwa dolls.
I see.
Blue Knight, intercept the two flying
objects with an unmanned fighter.
Y-Your Highness!
The Corona Treaty prohibits any
hostilities with Kiriha-sama!
There's only a 63%
probability it's them, right?
It could be some outsider
trying to take a look at us.
Do it, Blue Knight.
As you command, my princess.
What's going on?!
Are you okay, Brother?!
Karama! Thank goodness!
We're mounting a counter attack!
We're not losing to some soulless machine!
We're going to show you what we're made of!
I think we can do better here.
I'm going to push you forward a little bit.
But...
I promise it won't hurt. You'll be fine!
Who's that girl?
The president of Koutarou's club.
Harumi Sakuraba.
Harumi Sakuraba...
I guess she's his princess, and
he's her knight in shining armor.
What?! He's sworn his loyalty to her?!
Yeah, something like that, I guess.
That fool...
Just how is she superior to me?!
That's because it's not based on logic.
What was that?!
Speaking of logic...
What was the logic behind
attacking me earlier?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I did however attack some voyeuristic,
unidentified objects
flying around the school.
W-We did it, Brother!
We proved souls win again...
Today's finally the day for the
Interclub Obstacle Course Marathon!
Interclub Obstacle Course Marathon
We'll be starting the race soon!
We've got everyone from our athletes
to those crazy liberal arts people.
All the clubs are here for the marathon!
We've got ten obstacles for you all.
Some of the obstacles will
require you to think,
so athletics alone won't
get you through this!
How are you feeling, Koutarou?
Pretty good.
I don't think I'll lose today.
What a coincidence.
I was just thinking the same thing.
You can bark all you want,
but I'll be the one biting.
I think we're forgetting about someone...
Stop...
She's...
Win!
You can do it,
Softball Team!
Let's sumo it up!
We can win,
Football Team!
You can do it!
I don't want people to see
people dressed like this.
What do you mean? You look great!
Don't be afraid, Nijino-san!
Sakuraba-senpai.
Satomi-kun!
How are you feeling?
Thanks for asking.
I'm fine.
Just watch.
I'm definitely going to finish the race!
I'm going to win this for us!
On your marks...
Let's do this, Kiri-chan.
Right, Takahashi-senpai.
Hmph.
Bang
There's the start!
The pair from track and
field has sprung into first!
Watch out!
We've got ourselves a crash!
What's going on?
Okay, let's do this according to plan.
Kiriha...
You bought some of these
guys off, didn't you?!
Go!
Hail to the princess!
Damn it...
That's our path.
Sakuraba-senpai,
let's go.
Huh?
Excuse me!
Knock on!
Uchi mata throw!
We're going to try to make up some time.
Um... Satomi-kun...
Damn, Kou got ahead of us!
This race isn't over yet!
Kisshouharukaze High School
Children's Park
Corona House
Vacant Lot
Ocean Park
The trouble at the start has calmed down!
Everyone's started on the course now!
Oh? We have someone here who hasn't left yet.
I wish someone had seen me before
my clothes got all messed up, at least...
Write the answer to the problem:
Answer:
Want me to just tell you?
No, it'd be cheating.
That's right.
Go ahead.
Sakuraba-senpai, go ahead!
But I...
You're going to finish the race, right?
Hurry up!
R-Right.
Got it.
First Obstacle
Math Problem
Kisshouharukaze High School
Children's Park
Corona House
Vacant Lot
Ocean Park
Hey, Tulip.
You're already here, Neanderthal?!
I bet the third obstacle took you some time.
Third Obstacle
That was pretty difficult.
Especially for someone as
short-tempered as you!
And you're only good at
sports, you dumb servant!
Yeah, sure, comfort yourself with that.
Fourth Obstacle
Red bean paste bun
Speed Eating Contest
Red bean paste bread speed eating
I got this!
The fourth obstacle is a red bean
paste bread speed eating contest.
What an indecent way of eating!
Shut up!
Hm?
Sakuraba-senpai!
Are you okay?
Yes, but I eat slow.
Satomi-kun, don't worry
about me, keep going!
But...
You want to place high, right?
Go ahead.
Got it.
See you later, then!
That neanderthal...
Kisshouharukaze High School
Children's Park
Corona House
Vacant Lot
Ocean Park
"Sousai"
Huh?
Uh...
"Aisatsu?"
Obstacle Seven
Kanji reading
"Gyokuro"
"Sousai"
"Senryuu"
Buzz.
"Nousatsu?"
Buzz!
See you later, muscle for brains!
Good luck!
Damn it!
Halfway Point
I knew this would happen...
But I'm halfway through...
Let's do this!
I can't come back from this...
I should just give up, shouldn't I?
I tried my best, didn't I?
Are you okay?
You're that nice person...
Don't give up.
We're already halfway through.
But, I can't win anymore.
No one's watching me.
No one's going to say I did well.
If you give up here, you'll lose to yourself.
That always happens.
Even so, I still don't
think you should give up.
Let's do this.
I believe in you.
R-Right!
Oh, yeah. I never introduced myself, did I?
My name is Harumi Sakuraba.
What about you?
Yurika.
Yurika Nijino.
Let's make it to the goal,
Nijino-san,
even if we're last.
Okay, Sakuraba-senpai!
You're still first!
You can do it!
Obstacle Eight
Shocking Scary Shaky
Balance Beam
This is next, huh?
This one is wider and
should be easier to cross.
This one is shorter, so you should
be able to cross it faster.
I don't have time to think about it.
Neanderthal, you're my
servant, so let me go first!
Yeah, right!
You've got a small heart and small
boobs to match, you crazy princess!
My boobs have nothing to do with this!
Sorry about that.
I was only talking about your heart, then!
You make me so mad...
You know, it'd be a lot easier if
you two didn't talk while you ran.
What should we do, Koutarou?
Isn't that obvious?
The shortest one!
Balance Beam
What took you so long?!
You seem to be taking it pretty
easy over there, Tulip.
A princess doesn't rush herself.
What's up with her?
She might be planning something.
Koutarou, look!
What the hell?!
Obstacle Eight
Shocking Scary
We're caught up with the leaders!
Where's the guy who stepped on us?!
Sumo!
Crap, they're...
Who was it...
He was with a girl...
Sumo! Sumo!
There he is!
You in the tuxedo!
Now you're gonna get it.
Sumo!
I got lucky...
You...
Tuxedo!
Osotogari throw!
Sumo!
Sumo...
Tulip, did you do something?!
I'm not quite sure what you mean...
They're quite similar to my
country's shock bombs, however.
Shock bombs?
Bombs? They're mines?
I knew she'd put up traps...
Fear me, Neanderthals.
Look at the guys in the back!
They're not having a problem!
So that's the only safe route?
Let's go, baby!
What?
You dummies! Stay away!
I told you not to put any
bombs under this beam!
Huh?
Baby!
Hail to the princess!
I'm sure someone made it
to the finish line already.
Nijino-san, let's finish the race.
Fight, fight!
Sakuraba-senpai, what
drives you to work so hard?
Me?
I told my friend I'd do the best I could.
A friend, huh?
Yes! He...
Sakuraba-senpai.
Senpai, um...
Medic!
Senpai! Sakuraba-senpai!
Senpai...
What should I do?
What should I do...
Come to me, Angel Halo!
Costume change!
Modifier, quick and permanent!
Remove disease!
Modifier maximize!
Magic, make Sakuraba-senpai better.
It's not working...
Why?
Yeah, but I think it's bad to give up.
No, I have to do what I can.
Work. Heal her.
Huh? What's going on?
It's not just my magic.
No, it doesn't matter.
If I have this much magic...
First place is just coming in now!
Just a little bit longer, Koutarou.
Satomi-sama, you can do it!
Interclub Obstacle Course Marathon
Tenth Obstacle
Borrowed Items Race
Welcome back, Master!
It'll be over as soon as you finish that!
Huh?
Over?
I did it!
No way!
He went down!
And now second and third have caught up!
Wonderful, Princess!
Want to give up, neanderthal?
I knew it'd be me and you.
Tenth Obstacle
Borrowed Items Race
Welcome back, Young Miss!
A bra sized
A-cup or lower
D-cup or larger
I assume I won't be able to just ask you...
Naturally.
You'll have to take it by force.
It's kind of strange.
I feel lighter than before I collapsed.
That's because of magic. Magic, you know?
Huh?
You know, I'm actually a magical
girl of love and courage,
hopes and dreams!
Okay. So it's magic, then!
That's right, magic.
Interclub Obstacle Course Marathon
A member of your club
Please keep going.
I'm going to give up.
Why?
A friend
I can't do this.
It'll be fine, Yurika-san.
You have what you're looking for right here.
Huh?
In exchange...
Could you do me a little favor?
Huh?
We finally have the finish line
being broken by our runners!
We have two teams coming in first!
The Knitting Society and the Cosplay Society!
What a surprise!
I never would have thought
those two would win.
Yeah, that's a surprise.
But, thanks to Harumi Sakuraba,
you technically won, too.
Yeah.
That means Yurika-chan,
Sanae-chan, and Koutarou all won!
Sis and Theia-chan lost...
I should have done better.
I can't agree to this.
Well, that's the way the cookie crumbles.
I guess all's well that ends well.
It didn't end well at all.
Who put the mines in on obstacle eight?!
Rage Rage Rage
It was you?!
Kiriha bought off those—
Shut up!
Well, that's what you get.
Kou, these senpai here would
like to have a word with you.
I'll talk to you later!
Wait!
Sumo!
That's what you get.
Hey, Neanderthal.
Get her away from me!
I could tell you the same!
One...
Two...
Ger her away from me!
Hell no!
What's this black thing?
It's Koutarou and Theia.
I guess things ended poorly for them.
Stop it...
The dark magic is getting me...
Next Episode: Swimming and Plots?!