Expect a v2.
Romero.
If you had been raised in another country, would you...
...have still had that firm expression?
Lizzie, you're still here?
Don't you need to be in Mexico by tomorrow?
When I'm gone, be good and don't be nit picky about everything.
Who's that person?
Don't you think he's very handsome?
Asians all look the same to me.
I can only see a difference when they relax.
Do you think he'd kill people?
You're joking! He wouldn't hurt a fly!
Yeah...
So you think so too...
Practice
Good, that's how you do it.
The knife is both a weapon and a shield.
So,
when fighting with knives, as long as you
can block the enemy's knife, you will win.
That was mercy...
You have a knife, so why do you still use an arm lock?
This afternoon in Mexico City, the corpse
of an F.B.I. officer, named Bruce, was discovered.
Read this carefully.
An investigation is currently underway.
Authorities suspect that terrorists were involved,
It's nothing.
as Bruce was investigating a Latin American terrorist group.
The Noche de Sangre are most likely the ones responsible.
Killing again?
How is Zwei coming along?
His combat skills are excellent.
The timing is perfect.
Ein, undress.
Yes.
Nobody would believe that this white and
pure skin would cover such a killing machine.
Raise your arm.
Ein.
You are perfect.
You were cultivated by me into the absolute masterpiece.
I want this perfection to be eternal.
Finish Zwei.
With your hands,
turn him into something as perfect as you.
Yes.
This is the final step to your completion.
Ein,
you must pass your perfection to the next generation.
Yes,
Master.
Ein.
You're late.
Come here.
We need to prepare.
How long do I have to wait?
Do you understand exactly how important I am to your organization?
Do you understand?
You only have your weapons because I sold them to you while I risked my life, for a year, in the army.
We are deeply thankful,
Captain Wallace.
But because it was so sudden, we'll need time.
Then what do I do?
I was on vacation when I became involved in this murder.
That is a shame.
The victim appears to be an F.B.I. agent.
Do you know him?
Don't be ridiculous.
I don't even understand how I'm a suspect.
I understand.
If I'm investigated, you'll be in trouble too.
Inferno has an obligation to help me.
That's a given.
Within hours, you'll be able to watch the sunset on the Caribbean.
I hope so too.
Choose the gun you've used best till now.
More training?
No, tonight is a test.
Test...
Follow me.
Aren't we heading to the airport?
What's going on!
What are you guys up to?!
Mr. McGwire,
he is an American Navy Seal, Captain Wallace.
Another member of Inferno?
That's a wide-barreled automatic.
A bodyguard.
What do you think you're doing?
This person...
Your hands reach too many places.
If you had only traded with us, this wouldn't have happened.
But you sold weapons to terrorists.
And now you're wanted by the F.B.I.
Preserving Inferno's secrecy is an informal law.
You're having me...
Scythe.
Captain Wallace,
Inferno will give you one chance for survival.
Run away please.
Huh?
Starting now, you have 10 minutes.
Then, we'll send someone after you. If you escape, you win.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
There is an armory in this building.
You may choose whatever you want.
What are you planning?
We're providing you with a chance to win your life back.
This is very merciful.
You guys repay me like this?!
You guys are t-
You're running out of time.
Fuck!
The situation is as you heard.
Zwei,
this is your first mission.
That man, kill him.
I don't care how.
As long as he's dead.
W-Wait,
I still haven't-
Your training is over.
You've done very well.
Actually, outstanding.
That's why I'm letting you participate in actual combat.
Go, you have the Inferno's Phantom's blessing.
Bring out some confidence.
Confidence?
Confidence in murder?
Hurry up, Zwei.
I can't do it.
I really can't do it!
I'll give you one more chance.
Accept your new life,
or reject it and die.
Will he be okay?
The enemy is a member of the Navy Seals.
There won't be a problem.
Mr. McGwire, we specifically invited
you to have you witness his power.
What weapon did he pick?
When hunting, think like the hunted;
their position is inverse.
The enemy will also consider this, so...
Phantom, what do you think?
Mr. Wallace is a well-trained, accomplished professional.
He also has more experience than Zwei.
Oh?
But when he's not distracted,
in terms of speed and concentration,
Zwei is better.
Your conclusion?
This'll be a 50/50 chance.
We'll be able to see his true potential.
What's Zwei chance of winning?
I don't know Mr. Wallace's skill.
Wait! Don't shoot!
I'm unarmed.
Listen to me.
I don't know why a child like you is doing this type of thing.
Think about it!
There's no reason for us to massacre each other.
How's your family?
I have a younger brother around your age.
I want to give him a good life.
Behind every mouse are thirty more.
Those who can lie, do not hesitate when lying.
I've always lived on the edge.
But now he's finally in college. I want to see him graduate.
The craftsman has more than one tool.
An assassin is the same.
Both you and me are just being used by Inferno.
It's that organization's fault.
And I thought those two shots decided it.
What do we do if the kid loses?
Luck can't be described.
How about we wait in the car? Just in case he loses.
Yeah.
Game's over.
I've seen too many people like you,
too scared to even cock a gun.
Here, let me teach you, how to kill.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Murder isn't something that can be done by just anyone.
Pay attention,
the lesson's just begun.
Zwei.
It wasn't bad for your first time.
Why?
This is...just a dream.
I told you already.
This'll be a very long dream.
And this is just a continuation.
Until you die or go insane, you'll never wake up from this dream.
To end it
is your choice.
Throw away your sight.
Throw away your hearing.
Throw away your heart.
And you will be pure.
By doing that and seeing everything through Zwei.
Hearing everything through Zwei.
You'll no longer be sad or scared.
And, you'll be free.
I'm...
I'm nothing...like Zwei.
Yes, you're right about that.
How do you want me to do it?
Let everything...end...
You are no longer yourself.
Stand up, Zwei.
Zwei.
Where did you find that boy again?
The country of Japan recommended him to me.
I see.
Even in a hopeless situation, he still found power.
Yes.
You've passed the test.
From today onward, you're a member of Inferno.
Assassination
You are what I was.
I understand the pain you're going through.