I done did it! Master kobe!
Good work Yao Ming, very honoraburr to famiry
I ain't lettin' you pass, sista!
Oh!
I not losin' to you either!
Everyone's wrecking shit out there
It'd be cash mone if we could get all 10
Still missing them 3, amirite?
Hey, ya know...
Since you two niggas lost,  just join the team at LeBron's Ballin' Academy
Fuck you!
I remember the last time I trusted a whitey!
Do I look like Dred Scott?
How else are you gonna get food and shelter?
Sh-shut up!
You're all too weak.
Even if you got your freedom from white-folk, you'd be sub-human
Later.
These fucking confederates...
We'll get our revenge, definitely!
Yeah.
A new menu for the Juneteenth Party
Yep.
We've decided to enter scene with hip new flavors
Like Fried Chicken-flavored popsicles!
Sounds fun!
Oh!
I'm hood too!
I'm sure we'll make a delicious menu when we pool our ideas together!
Yep!
Okay! Let's meet up at the halfway house, then.
Oh!
They should all be getting here...
Why aren't you coming to practice?
That's for me to decide.
I only play basketball to beat you, Chris
But you can't play basketball all by yourself, ohohoho
Saki: 1
Masami: -5
Subaru~n: 10,000
Oh screw you!
We're only one year apart!
Stop acting like an older sister, it's Creepy!
Oh baby when you talk that way...
I won't lose next time!
In basketball or in anything else!
At the Juneteenth festival either!
I'll be helping out at Chick-fil-A this year.
Chick-fil-A vs KFC
A duel between the best of the chikkens!
Can allah you help me out?
The 6th graders are helping out at KFC
This is a great chance to get our revenge!
But we want to get revenge on that bitch first, rather than Dirk
That girl?
The one with the apple-bottom jeans.
Boots with the fur?
Yeah, that's the one! The whole crowd was lookin at her
Got it!
Thank you!
That means...
I'm sorry, nigga. I can't fight with mah sista n-emore
I ain't betrayin' mah mastah
Yo!
You skanky bitches, who you think you are?
Let's decide with a vote!
Who wants to help out her?
Here!
That's it!
Emmit Till all over again!
Tyranny of the white folk!
Will you help us out, Anne?
Of course.
But before that...
If it's about going to LeBron's Ballin' Academy, then no deal
We did join the club, but we get to decide whether we want to practice together with them.
I see. That's just how it is, eh?
Putting that aside...
We've been thinking.
You're only in high school, but those are glorious
Hell yeah they are!
I just want to rub my face on them!
S-Stop it!
Eh? It's harder than I thought.
Isn't that because of her booby-erection?
Booby-erection?
My sister's gonna get hers soon...
Stop it! If you keep on rubbing them...
I'm home!
Is there an orgy I'm missing out on
Oh, Big Brotha!
We're molesting Anne and erecting her booby-penises!
I'm fine, carry on
Hey! Are you idiots?!
Stop doing weird things!
Don't you dare come in!
Oh! Big Brotha! Join in!
Nigga-kun?! Nigga-kun?!
We've got the chikken and the watermelum!
Chikken!
Oh!
Kool! Kool! Kool-Aid!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Cut that out, LeBron!
Got it, everyone?
KFCs going down! Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Hey!
Good.
Thanks Pops.
Pops, how come you always make the best chikken?
Hey, remember when you said you pulled out?
Well I think there's gonna be a new addition to the family...
Please respond...
Dad, it was a joke, I was kidding...
Dad...?
Listen, I know you don't joke about stuff like that but I
I...
It's k, I'm on the pill, Father.
I didn't expect us to be right next to each other.
We'll see who sells the most, Chris!
It's a duel! A duel!
Jeez, you're all so friggin stupid.
I'm sorry, they just won't listen to me.
Don't worry about it.
We do our thing, they do theirs. It's all good.
We just want our customers to be satisfied, right?
Right.
Thanks, everyone.
Please wait here to enter!
H-How is it?
It's good! It's perfect!
I knew it! We were gonna make something awesome!
Hmph! Ours is better!
Look!
Oh! So ca-yute!
Yeah! That looks nice!
How's our Twice-Paroled Hoodrat doing?
The fried chikken and the cornbread were all made by my Pops!
Wow!
This'll be popular to both illegal aliens and people in jail!
Now's your only chance to relax.
We'll lure all of the customers with sex appeal
While you guys get busted by the cracka ass police!
Jeez.
She just yaps on and on about her nigger shit
The Juneteenth Welfare Festival S-Grade Gourmet Fair will now begin!
AW shit here we go
Yeah, I want to sell at least one at least
Eh? I found a pair of twins who I recognize!
It's you!
From back then...
"You?"
Kinda cocky for a pair of losers.
But I guess I never told you my name.
You two were just too weak, so I never got the chance to.
Don't make those scary faces.
My name is Slim Shady
I'm a 5th grader at Eminem's Girls' Academy.
Nice to meet you.
M&M?
Hey, is she the one?
The one that sold us the bad weed?
Bad weed?
I'd never!
You two got so baked that day
Order something already.
We're busy now.
Hey! Stop lecturing me already!
I don't like it.
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Losers!
Hey, hey, hey!
And then...
I'm sorry.
Hey! What are you doing?
You made me drop my weed-flavored loli pop!
Wow, my bad.
That shot was sick, though
Stop fooling around!
All my hopes and dreams...SHATTERED!
Hey, Hey! Calm down!
That was an accident!
Yes, yes, an accident.
It can't be helped.
Oh, shut up!
Apologize to her!
Even if it was an accident, you should still take responsibility!
Can't you see that she's PMS'ing?
Oh, what's this?
What a pain.
I don't know anything! It wasn't my fault!
Later!
Wait!
We can't serve this anymore.
My daddy spent so many hours on that...
We thought about this together...
Stand up, be strong!
........
What do you want?
I know how you feel, but this isn't the time to feel down.
We need to make food for our customers.
You are the poster girl for Chick-Fil-A, right?
But the fried chikken...
You still have the watermelums, right? Then everything's fine.
Watermelum is the best! Of course it'll sell.
And who knows that the best?
But we only have that...
You're right.
Hey, can all of you come over here?
What is it?
Need our help?
Yep, we need your ideas.
How can we use this watermelum to make an S-Grade gourmet?
Oh!
Food again? I'll think hard!
We can only use what we have, then.
We have kool-aid, corn muffins, and weed...
Hey, wait! That's for your store, right?
Stop this! Don't do this!
We aren't doing this for your sake.
Then why?
We're doing this for the customers of Chick-Fil-A!
We can't make fried chikken anymore, but let's all think about something else.
Something new, something fresh, something with pop
But what about your other stuff?
We've already learned a lot by thinking about it together.
It's ain't important whether we sell a lot or not.
Right, everyone?
Yep!
Oh!
We can make it anytime!
We need to use the watermelum in an authentic way...
It's easier to eat if we wrap it up like a McWrap
I'm thinkin Arby's
But that may not look authentic anymore.
Isn't there a nice idea somewhere?
Using rice!
Stop being an idiot and think properly.
Rice? Baka?
Rice baka?
Rice burger?
Fried Chicken Burger! LeBron, that may work!
That looks great.
I'm done!
KFC and Chick-Fil-A's special collaboration menu will be on sale soon!
Please try us out!
Please!
Welcome!
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
Do your best.
Thank you very much!
Please have a looksie!
Seems like they're alright
Yeah.
Oh! The scrubbing feels so nice!
Rub a dub dub
Go!
Back at ya!
Chris..
Um... today...
Thanks.
Anytime, bby
I guess I'll cede my territory on 5th ave...for a kiss on the cheek...
What really?
Nope.
(Saki just played you)
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven, potato
Two, no wait, shit
We finally got all ten, I think
But it'll take some time for them to be a team.
Well, just getting them to come to stop bitching is a huge step forward.
What's with you all of a sudden?
What are you saying?
I even brought you this super important letter.
Super important?
Yo, this is...
Gather around the campfire, everyone!
Um, Charles Barkley?
LeBron's Ballin' Academy Bitch's Basketball Club has now officially entered the regional tournament.
So that means...
We can take part in the tournament?
Yes.
And our first round opponent will be...
Eminem's Girls Academy!
Emimen...Slim Shady...hmmmm
This is a wonderful chance.
We can get our revenge.
Alright, you two, get over here
And let's start practicing!
Let's do it, everyone!
Oh!
That Slim Shady really pisses me off!
We'll beat her to a pulp!
We must win our match against Eminem's Girls Academy!
We need to have the 6th graders teach us a lot.
I'll steal my master's skill!
Let's do our best, everynigga!