Wow, they're so pretty!
Thank you very much.
I'm certain the flowers are pleased as well.
Alice, haven't you always been part of the school's Gardening club?
Yes.
Do you like raising flowers?
My childhood dream was to become a florist.
What about now?
Well, I'll have to succeed my father's company,
so I won't be able to pursue that dream.
Oh...
Then we'll make it come true for you!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
We're done!
Alice's Floral Arrangements
"Alice's Floral Arrangements"! Sounds nice, huh?
It's wonderful!
Opening a flower shop in a flea market was a great idea!
Yeah!
I'm overjoyed to finally realize my childhood dream!
Good luck, manager!
Thanks!
I'm a manager too!
Do you know what a manager does?
I dunno!
Cosmos, geranium, cyclamen...
Why not showcase more extravagant flowers?
Because I like these.
There's a certain beauty to flowers blooming in their season.
Oh?
I thought I saw a pack of stray orangutans at first,
but I see it's just Alice's friends.
Look who's here.
Who might you be?
From the family that forever one-ups the Yotsubas,
I am the rose of the Itsutsuboshis,
Itsutsuboshi Reina!
Are you participating in the flea market as well, Reina?
But of course!
Your little flower stall might win you some publicity,
but one-upping you at every turn is my sworn duty as Itsutsuboshi Reina!
I've raised exquisite, luxurious flowers from the four seasons over in an enormous greenhouse,
and today, they will prove to be your match!
Round 1, fight!
Take a look over there!
Reina's
Flowers
Premium
Noblesse
Reina's Premium Flowers, Noblesse.
How wonderful!
We can be florists together!
Alice's Dream!
A Friendship Through Flowers
Would you like some flowers?
Come on, take a look!
Um...
Yes?
Well, I need to get some flowers for my girlfriend's birthday...
In that case,
perhaps this geranium would suit your needs?
Just a moment!
If you want a gift for a lover, what could be better then red roses?
We sell premium quality roses, and you get 30 for the price of 1!
Well, don't mind if I do...
Come again!
It's as though the match is already settled, wouldn't you agree?
You're selling luxury flowers for next to nothing!
That's a cheap trick!
Your tactics are underhanded!
I'd expect nothing less...
than such beautiful flowers from you, Reina.
Seems you know your place.
Indeed, you should expect nothing less.
Now, continue praising me!
Would you like some flowers?
We're not getting any customers...
And then there's our competition...
Now now, don't push!
Single file, people!
Don't be down. Just keep trying!
Hello.
Would you like some flowers?
Flowers, huh?
I'll... take a look.
Please do. They're all in season.
Those are cosmos.
They send my heart aflutter whenever I see them.
I'll have these, then.
Certainly!
Here you are!
I feel a bit better now. Thanks.
Thank you very much!
We did it!
Alice, you were like a real florist!
Really? Why, thank you!
A real florist gives love along with each flower.
I'd like to give a flower like that to Regina.
I don't need no flowers.
Regina!
But doesn't looking at flowers make you happy?
I told you before.
I have no mercy...
for things more beautiful than I.
I can't fly my RC plane with this flea market here!
Those flowers could die for all I care.
Well, my mom would probably like flowers for Mother's Day...
Just those flowers die.
Wh-Who said that?
I'll turn you into a splendid Selfish!
But how?!
What the?
Is it a Selfish?
But I didn't hear a dark heartbeat!
Oh, my poor flowers...
Reina, as long as they still have but one green leaf,
they can still come back to life!
Let's treat them immediately!
Clean the roots in water.
Leave only the unwithered roots to lighten the plant's burden.
Plant it in new soil...
And give it water.
All that's left is to wait and hope for their recovery.
Perhaps, but why?
Why help me after how mean I've been to you?
You're the one who taught me how to treat plants in emergencies.
And I know how much love you pour into your flowers.
Ever since we first met, in fact.
Itsutsuboshi Rose Garden
Those roses are pretty.
Not as pretty as me.
Do you like flowers?
Flowers make me look even more beautiful.
That's why I raise them with care.
Um...
What?
My gazanias...
Oh no, they're wilting!
But I don't know what to do...
Really...
Amateurs are always such a bother!
I'll show you how to treat them in emergencies, so listen up!
And you've been a dear friend to me ever since.
Friend?
Yes!
But in truth, I want friends too...
D-Don't be a fool!
Why's she crying?
Sometimes, people cry when they're happy.
Madam.
I've learned what's causing the flowers to wilt.
The Yotsuba satellite has been commandeered.
This is a video of the stratosphere above the city.
This Selfish is spreading Egogy seeds to make the flowers wilt!
Regina!
She was too far away for us to feel a dark heartbeat!
We need to stop her, and fast!
But how do we get above the stratosphere?
We have only one way!
Your flowers will certainly return to life as well.
Alice...
Condition, normal. Systems, all green.
So, Alice can fly an aircraft, too?
Alice!
Is there no way we can come with you?
This shuttle only supports one person.
Liftoff!
Target sighted!
It's a Selfish!
Wilt!
Autopilot, on!
Lance, I'm ready!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
What, just Yellow?
Regina, please stop making the flowers wilt!
When pigs fly.
Looking at flowers makes humans happy, right?
Have you ever wondered why?
Huh?
Like I care!
Because flowers contain life!
Even if a flower wilts down to its final leaf...
it will still struggle to live against all odds!
Don't you find that as beautiful as any flower in full bloom?
I know your heart can accept beauty for what it is!
I believe in you!
What's your point?
Please, accept this love!
Love?
That junk again?
Wilt...
Fall...
If love means so much to you, then burn to a crisp along with it!
Reina, I'm sorry...
My love wasn't strong enough...
But at least let this cosmos...
That's it.
As long as I have my life,
I cannot give up!
What's this?
Cure Rosetta!
Girls!
How did you get here?
Reina!
Alice...
or, should I say, Cure Rosetta.
I, Itsutsuboshi Reina, will fly to the ends of the earth for a friend in need!
Besides, the Itsutsuboshi Conglomerate's solar plane allows everyone to ride with me!
Thank you.
I should be the one thanking you.
I was only so mean to you before because I wanted to be your friend...
And to think you considered me your friend this whole time!
Yes, ever since we first met!
Girls!
This may be all I can do for you,
but please, take good care of my friend!
Gotcha!
'Scuse me, Mana.
Could we talk for a bit?
Sure, as long as you want!
I wanna talk a bunch with you, too!
You know, this whole "playing friends" thing...
really ticks me off!
Wilt!
Rosetta Reflection!
Are you all right?
Thanks, Cure Rosetta!
I'll blow you all away!
Thanks!
Cure Ace!
Wilt!
I did it!
Now, make a giant seed that'll wilt every flower on Earth...
and those stupid Precures along with them!
It wilt be done!
Wilt 'em all!
It's futile.
But how far will you go?
You can't!
If you use any more power...
you'll lose all that remains of your life force, Cure Rosetta!
I will not lose.
You moron!
You can't do squat just by protecting!
It doesn't matter!
Say what?
Just having flowers will bring people smiles.
Mana, Reina, and the rest of the girls are like flowers to me.
So what I can do is protect them as much as I can!
And also...
you're another flower I must protect, Regina!
Shut up!
Go away!
Alice!
Cosmos has a meaning in the language of flowers...
It stands for a maiden's purity.
I know that deep down, your heart is pure.
And I know that it's brimming with love!
Not again...
My chest is tingling with warmth...
Sadface...
Girls, let's go!
Precure Royal Lovely Straight Flush!
Love love looooove!
Regina's heart really is brimming with love.
I'm super duper mad!
Take this as a symbol of our friendship.
Thank you very much.
Please, have this.
Isn't that nice?
But I'm Alice's bestest friend!
It was fun being a florist!
Indeed!
And I think I've made a new dream.
A new dream?
Yes.
Until now, I've only had a vague desire to protect people's smiles,
but I did know that it could only be done with the power of love.
Only with...
The power of love?
Flowers, despite their frailty, bring smiles with their mere presence...
I want to protect things like them with the power of love.
That's why I'll raise the Yotsuba Conglomerate to grow ever bigger!
Madam...
I'd like to give Regina the power of love, too...
Yes, and I'd like to help you in any way I can.
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
I've longed to savor the taste of a birthday cake for an eternity!
Dokidoki Precure:
A Celebration With Everyone!
Her First Birthday!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!