Romeo and Juliet
Our class will be performing Romeo and Juliet for the upcoming school play.
Furuya nominated me to write the script...
That's a great idea!
Thank you!
I'd like to nominate my fellow Drama Club member,
Hirano, for the role of Romeo.
I-I'd be honored!
Romeo and Juliet
Good call, I'd say!
You got this, drama club!
Thanks...
Romeo and Juliet
And as Nanase suggested, I'd like to nominate Haruno for the role of Juliet.
You want me to play Juliet?!
Why?! I think Furuya would be way better!
She's in the Drama club!
I get stage fright, so my knees shake when I'm in front of an audience.
Romeo and Juliet
Besides, I want to try my hand at production!
I can work on the set.
Then I'll do lighting!
You can leave!
The costumes!
To us!
Yeah!
You all have roles you want to fill...
Haruno.
We should do this.
I might not live up to your hopes, though.
Haruka!
Romeo and Juliet
How about it?
I think you're a perfect fit!
Why not?
I agree!
Guess I'll give it a shot!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Haruka, I finished the script...
Whoah! Yui, keep it together!
Don't worry, it's stapled!
Romeo and Juliet
Not what I meant!
Yui wrote it?
That's great!
A play at the academy?
Yes.
My class is doing Romeo and Juliet!
It tells the tale of a man and a woman born between two rivaling families!
I'll be playing Juliet!
She's the girl who falls in love with Romeo.
My class is doing Cinderella!
I'm the fairy godmother and Towie's Cinderella!
That's great!
I'll do my best!
Come watch, Brother.
And Minamin?
We're doing The Tale of the Bamboo Cutter.
I'll be playing Princess Kaguya!
You're perfect for it!
Am I?
We'll start rehearsing tomorrow!
Okay!
I'm nervous about being the lead, but I'll do everything I can!
Haruka's the Star?!
The Slapstick Romantic Play!
Like this?
Yeah!
Over here?
Now then... action!
What light through yonder window breaks?
It is the east, and Juliet is the sun!
O R-Romeo!
W-Wherefore art thou... Romeo?
Cut, cut!
Huh?
You're too quiet!
You look as stiff as a board and your lines have zero emotion!
Could you not read the script verbatim?!
Furuya, got a minute?
Coming!
Has Furuya always had that side to her?
Haruka, are you all right?
Uh, yeah...
Sorry, Furuya gets a little heated when it comes to acting.
No, I'm sorry for not doing better! I'll keep trying.
Good!
Sorry about that! Let's continue.
Okay!
O Romeo.
It's monotone!
O Romeo!
It lacks feeling!
Whyfore art thou—
It's "wherefore," not "whyfore"!
O, Romeo!
From the heart!
O Romeo!
Stronger!
Romeo Romeo Romeoooooo!
Absolutely atrocious!
You must become Juliet!
Okay...
Haruno, let's think about Juliet's emotions together.
S-Sure!
We'll start here.
This might be harder than I thought...
Hmm, Juliet...
Their families are bitter enemies...
yet she falls into the dreamiest of romances...
Haruno, got a second?
Oh, sure!
We'll continue the scene.
Stay but a little, Romeo—
All wrong!
Act more wistfully! You're in love!
I'm a girl in love?
From the top.
Ah, Romeo!
Wrong!
Romeo!
Roooomeo!
Dead wrong!
Haruka, are you okay?
Sorry, Furuya, I'll get right—
Haruno...
Huh?
You need to understand Juliet.
If you act without it...
the audience won't connect.
Haruka?
Kanata!
Why are you here?
I had an errand around here.
What's wrong?
May I have a read?
Huh? Sure.
It's a tragic tale.
Yeah...
And yet, I feel it has beauty.
Such as how the couple stays true to each other.
What kind of girl is Juliet?
I need... to connect...
I'm just confusing myself!
That's what you've been worried over?
Why not give someone else the role?
Huh? I can't do that!
Everyone already has their job.
Besides...
Hm?
I chose to go through with this.
I'll never get anywhere if I quit so soon.
You're like her.
Hm?
You're like Juliet.
Huh? How?
Your optimism and honesty reminds me of her.
I don't know about me,
but Juliet's definitely honest.
All right, let's be honest!
Honestly!
Kanata, can you help me rehearse?
Huh?
Sure.
Thanks!
Then I'll start.
But, soft! what light through yonder window breaks?
It is the east, and Juliet is the sun!
O Romeo! wherefore art thou Romeo?
That which we call a rose,
by any other name would smell as sweet...
So Romeo would, were he not Romeo call'd.
I take thee at thy word.
Call me but love, and henceforth I never will be Romeo.
O Romeo!
Furuya! Hirano! Good morning!
Take this last week to whip me into shape!
Sure!
We'll pull this off!
Yeah!
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
School Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Noble
Academy
School
Play
Haruno, are you all right?
Eh, ehehe...
You must be nervous.
Sorry about my stage fright...
I-I'm gonna rehearse a bit outside!
Don't be late for the show!
All classes, gather in the hall to prepare...
He's not here!
Where could he have gone?
What's wrong?
Hirano hasn't come back!
What?
He's not in the dorm!
Let's split up and search.
Okay!
Hiranooo!
Hiran—
You too have something...
That you shouldn't.
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to direct the best play ever!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Furuya!
She's not alone.
Dyspairvil!
Hirano!
Furuya!
Give them back!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Those dreams trapped in their cold cages...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Can you win against...
Two foes at once?
Ugh, we do not have time for this!
Then we'll end this fight in 70 seconds.
Why 70 seconds?
And start.
Dyspair.
Wha?
Is that really...
a time bomb?!
What?!
Dyspaaaaairvil!
Oh yeah, the other one!
Wha?!
Dyspairvil.
Vilvilvilvil!
They're fast!
We can't get close!
But complaining...
won't get us anywhere!
We do not...
have time to delay!
Now!
If I just press the stop bu—
Dyspair!
Our time!
Stopwatches are mechanical!
If I douse it with my liquid attacks...
It'll short-circuit and stop!
Intriguing idea.
But can you succeed?
Dyspaaaairvil! Vil! Vil!
Dyspairvil.
It's the end, Precures.
Dyspairvil!
Viiil!
Mermaid!
Dyspair?
Viiiil!
Today is a big day for us!
Furuya, Hirano, and every student at this school...
have been breaking their backs preparing for this day!
I won't let their work go to waste!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
That's the end of that.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Furuya! Hirano!
Kenta!
There you are!
What was I...
From before...
Oh no!
I'm fine, it's no—
Hirano!
Sorry...
Can anyone replace him?
Does anyone know Romeo's lines?
Nobody knows them all...
I can...
Huh?
No, sorry, I can't!
I think...
I can handle Romeo.
Brother?
Who are you?
Oh, he's Towie's brother.
Akagi's?
I've rehearsed plenty with her, so I know his lines.
Can we do that?
We might be able to save the play, but...
We can't get a prize if we have an outsider.
But compared to not performing at all...
All students, please gather in the gym.
We worked so hard...
to get this far...
Let him... play Romeo...
Then let's do it!
But what if...
If we tell a teacher, I'm sure they'll understand!
I've gotta respect Kenta's choice!
Akagi's brother,
we'd like you to play Rom—
Hold on!
Even if the play doesn't go well,
I still feel like we should do it ourselves.
I can't explain why, and I know it might be crazy, but...
I don't care if we fail...
I want to perform this play with my class!
Me too...
I still want to act!
I'm sorry...
Hirano, let's do it.
But switch with me if it hurts too much. Got it?
Furuya...
Let's do it!
If we back Kenta up, we can make it happen!
Yeah, we've come this far!
I don't want to leave anyone out!
Haruharu!
Girls!
We've gotta hurry.
Let us lend a hand.
No time to lose.
Yeah!
Kanata!
Thank you!
Princess Kaguya, please do not go!
Father, I must return to the moon!
Oh, Minami!
It's a race against time, guys!
Right!
Got a compress!
Thanks!
The magic will vanish at the stroke of midnight!
Very well! I promise I'll return!
How splendid!
You're next! Hurry!
Costume's okay!
Do this part first.
That was First Year Star Class with Cinderella.
Hurry and switch over!
Ready, everyone?
Next is the First Year Flower Class performing Romeo and Juliet.
We're 20 seconds behind! Hurry!
Juliet, I'll make sure your honesty connects to the audience!
Can I go forward when my heart is here?
What light through yonder window breaks?
It is the east, and Juliet is the s—!
Ay me! Who goes before this orchard?
By Jove! art thou not Romeo?
O, how my heart doth pain to see you wounded!
O Romeo! wherefore art thou Romeo?
Nice!
Music!
Not bad, Haruharu!
Haruno...
That which we call a rose,
by any other name would smell as sweet...
So Romeo would, were he not Romeo call'd.
I take thee at thy word.
Call me but love, and henceforth I never will be Romeo.
Wow...
Thanks, Kanata.
We somehow pulled the show off ourselves.
You really are honest. Just like Juliet.
O Romeo! wherefore art thou Romeo?
I take thee at thy word.
Call me but love, and henceforth I never will be Romeo.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Oh, you seem quite spirited today.
I found a boy who's rooting for my dream!
Someone supported my dream as well.
Could he be the same boy?
Some kid I didn't know told me to follow my dreams, I guess...
Wow, a bunch of people are cheering us on!
Simply splendid!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Suspicious Trap...
The Lonely Princess!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!