Note: Chaham is the fried rice that she ate before, which was prepared by Takasu.
Seconds!
Okay!
Wait, that's not it!
Huh?
How did you end up having breakfast at our house?
Moreover, why aren't you saying anything?
Nothing much. Taiga's so small, she won't take up much space...
And meals taste better when you eat with more people.
Hurry up and get the rice for me.
I've already cooked three cups of rice.
How much are you going to eat?
So.....sorry
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I’m not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I’ll grasp you like a flea although I’m small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it’s a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono tanjun de katte ni kakedasu shiromono
Love is sweet and bitter, an amazing thing that’s simple and bolts out
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it’s like that
otoko to issho no ECCENTRIC na anata
You are together with an eccentric guy
tsuyogari soburi wo zenshin matomete tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PRE PARADE
A naive pre-parade
atama no naka wa junjou PRE PARADE
In my mind, I’m always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Ryuuji and Taiga
Geez.
Are you going to let your pet become bald from stress?
Don't let it become any uglier.
Who said it's ugly?
Well, they do say a pet's similar to its master.
You're such an... ingrate!
To me, the one who made not only breakfast and dinner, but also your lunch box.
You're noisy, you mongrel.
Mon-... Say it again!
Return the lunch box to me!
Return it along with my kindness!
Shut up, and then go rot.
W-Wait, Aisaka!
Ever since that late night raid,
Aisaka Taiga began to show up at our dining table.
I said wait up.
After that...
As compared to that...
Act properly when we get to school.
About the matter with Kitamura...
You have to properly... Um... Bring us together...
Since you did promise me that you'll work like a dog for me!
...It ended up like this.
If things don't go well for me...
Minori!
Ah, you're slow, Taiga.
Good, you're energetic today too.
Good morning, Minori.
Eh? It must be a lie! What's this?!
Sorry, I didn't know.
TL Note: Two-shot refers to any camera shot that is framed for two people to cover a conversation between them.
So Taiga and Takasu-kun have already progressed onto the stage of going to school in a two-shot together?!
You got it wrong.
No one would say “two-shot” these days.
It's not about that!
Is that so? Then nowadays...
I'm so shocked that I don't know how to put it across in today's words!
Ah, I got it. It's avec, right?
Like I've said, it's not that.
Aisaka and I just bumped into each other by coincidence. Right, Aisa-
Oh, that? So it's a coincidence?
My house is near his.
Um...
Well then, see you later, Takasu-kun!
On yesterday's television show...
I see.
If I want to get on good terms with Kushieda,
I have to bring Aisaka and Kitamura together first.
That's fine, I'll take you on!
Okay! Warming up exercise complete!
Next, in pairs, you'll be passing ball...
Hey, Aisaka. Let's pair up?
Okay, okay! Let's train together, Takasu-kun!
Yeah.
For ball practice...
What? Takasu and Aisaka, aren't you guys fired up?
Taiga?
This is how youth should be after all!
What, what? Today's that day?
The plan is simple.
I'll lightly hit the one pairing with Kitamura with the ball,
And then...
You'll make a huge ruckus,
and bring that person to the infirmary.
By doing so, Aisaka and Kitamura will become a pair naturally.
Maruo, pair up with me.
I don’t mind, but don’t call me that.
But it suits your image.
Huh?
Hey, hey, Kitamura and that weird woman... What is this about?
You hit my stomach.
Kushieda, pair up with me.
Oh, okay! Let's train together.
What... Even Kushieda...
Well, forget it. Begin the battle plan.
Eh? But you...
Don’t discriminate based on gender.
Well then, who wants to see a glorious bicep?
Oh, Haruta, what's wrong?
Not using the thumbs... Throw it out!
It’s not reaching me, Kushieda.
Mastering the path of the Satoru Ball is full of tribulations.
Huh?
It's okay, it's okay. It's normal for others to not understand me.
Damn... That Noto...
Hey, pass!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Pass! Pass, pass, pass!
It’s coming, Maruo.
Yeah.
Hm, not a bad passing technique.
What are you saying, Maruo?
Hey, pass!
You say pass but...
I can't do it to girls after all...
Pass!
Sorry, Kihara. I'll make up for it.
I'm so sorry, Maruo.
What? What happened?
Takasu finished off the palm-sized tiger!
Crap.
The palm-sized tiger that will bite anyone no matter who it is.
However, she works really hard to the extent that people see her as uncool.
No wonder I came up with the idea of supporting her.
You have to give it to him nonchalantly.
Don’t do it seriously all of a sudden.
I... I got it.
I have to relax, right?
Yeah. Light-mindedly... Conveniently... in a fickle manner...
Let's go.
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Ah, if it's Kitamura,
he said he has something on just now, and went to B Tower.
Takasu-kun!
He just went off, so he should still be in the vicinity.
Over there!
Let's give chase!
Y-Yeah.
What?
Move aside, move aside, move aside!
She's fast.
Well, with that speed, she'll be able to catch up...
Ryuuji.
Where are the cookies?
Huh?
Ouch... It swelled up after all.
Have you found it?
Was it alright?
I-I see.
Hey...
I wonder if... I'm too clumsy?
She didn't realise it at all?
When I wrote a love letter, I put it into the wrong bag.
When I went in to raid your house, I collapsed from hunger.
When I played basketball, I get hit in the face by a ball.
When I tried giving him cookies, I slip, fall, and drop the cookies.
Look here, look here, you still have more right?
Like forgetting to put the love letter into the envelope.
That's right...
That... Give me one.
Don't... It’s crumbled to pieces already
Moreover...
Delicious.
It's pretty well made, isn't it?
It's unfortunate but, you just have to work harder next time.
It's true that I witnessed it.
The two of them were buying mass onions and radish at the supermarket.
Witness 1         2nd Year Class C      H-da K-ji
They're pretty much like husband-wife already?
Witness 2      2nd Year Class C    K-hara M-ka
Those two came out from the condominium together in the morning.
There’s a rather mysterious smell to it~
Moreover, they also ate the handmade cookies together.
Witness 3     2nd Year Class C    N-nori H-kou
And were also playing "Here, Ah~"!
Witness 4       2nd Year Class C    K-tsuchi N-nako
Eh~ Is that so, is that so? No way...
Hey, Minori.
What happened to your best friend?
Yeah...
What happened?
Hey, hurry up and go in already.
Ah.
Kya.
Kya?
Can I have some of your time?
The sun... is dry.
What happened to Kushieda-san?
I don't know.
Takasu-kun.
Yes! Eh... Me?
HEY!
Please take good care of Taiga!
Eh?
Taiga is my most important best friend.
Please, please make her happy!
Wait, wait a minute, Kushieda.
Could this be...
Happiness?
So that's how it is.
It's something to celebrate, you two.
Kitamura? Why are you in that kind of a place?
I was thinking that you guys are always together but
now that you mention it, you two are compatible indeed.
Aisaka, pull yourself together!
You over there, stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you make Taiga cry,
I'll definitely not forgive you.
Kushieda...
Sorry for that.
It's all my fault for running into your house uninvited.
Making Minori misunderstand.
No, that is...
Actually...
Your house felt comfortable.
The relationship between between me and my parents is bad.
After mentioning that I wanted to leave the house,
they allowed me to move into that condominium.
Although I knew they were those kind of parents.
Those cookies were salty, right?
Eh?
Seeing that it crumbled into pieces, I felt upset
So I ate some.
What was that? It was awful.
But you ate it all anyway,
and lied too.
Obviously you’re only a mongrel but you worry so much about me.
You’ll go bald.
It’s none of your business.
Hey, do you get troubled when you think of Minori?
Of course I do.
That's right too.
Aisaka?
Why doesn't anyone understand us?
Although we’re pondering about this and that already.
Why doesn't anyone understand?
Really, everyone...
Everyone... Everyone... Everyone...
It irritates me!
It irritates me! It irritates me! It irritates me!
What "palm-sized tiger"?
Don't treat it like I don't care about it at all!
Minori, you idiot! Kitamura, you idiot!
Why didn't you listen to our explanations?
Daddy too, Mummy too.
No one...
Is willing to... understand me...
I'll lend you a hand.
Is it wrong to be small in size?
Don't call me a yankee just because of my appearance!
Is it wrong to be a little fierce?
Sorry for having an unfriendly expression!
Take this!
Hey, are you alright?
Ryuuji, is this crooked already?
Huh? How is it possible... It's really crooked.
Isn't it? We did it!
We won, we won!
Good, I've decided.
Tomorrow, I will confess to Kitamura-kun.
And then I’ll end it.
End?
Serving as a dog will end here.
Starting from tomorrow,
we're just classmates living as neighbors.
That's all.
Bye, bye, Takasu-kun.
Yea-
To
ra
do
!
www.aerosubs.net
Yeah...
Ryuu-chan... Isn't the breakfast today a little weird?
Although I like canned mackerel...
I wonder if Taiga-chan is still sleeping...
Who knows.
Ryuu-chan, did you guys fight?
No.
Somehow... It's boring, right?
Y-Yo.
This is...
Ta-Takasu...
Sorry for spreading weird rumors.
Aisaka got angry.
Eh?
Saying "there's nothing between Ryuuji and me".
"Ryuuji isn't a yankee", and making a fuss.
The palm-sized tiger is frightening after all.
However, didn't I say that Takasu isn’t scary at all.
Eh? When did you say that?
As compared to this, we've to clear up the mess first, right?
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun, sorry.
W-What's wrong?
Taiga... told me.
Eh?
She said she’d definitely never date you.
Therefore, it's just a misunderstanding, and hopes that at least I would understand.
That child... I don't know if I should say she's serious,
but she always has a desperate expression.
But, that is... That is...
Hey, Takasu-
Takasu-kun?
That girl...
What is she doing?
Isn't she confessing to Kitamura today?
It’s not the time to be worrying about others.
Starting from tomorrow,
we're just classmates living as neighbours.
That's all.
That's all, huh?
Kitamura-kun!
I... Kitamura-kun... Kitamura-kun...
Um... This...
Hey, hey. Taking action right after arriving at school.
If it fails, it’ll be awkward for the rest of the day.
Wait a minute.
Although it's just my assumption,
I can roughly know what you're going to say next.
But before that,
please allow me to confirm something.
Aren't you going out with Takasu?
That was Minori's misunderstanding.
There's nothing between Takasu and I...
Don't you like Takasu?
It's not like that.
It's just that Takasu's house is near mine.
There's totally nothing about liking or something.
Then, do you hate him?
I don't hate him...
But don't misunderstand! I didn't mean it like that.
Um... Takasu-kun... well...
That's right, Chaham!
Ryuuji cooked delicious Chaham for me,
and encouraged me...
Even lying to make me feel better.
And accompanying me.
Because there's Ryuuji...
Because Ryuuji's accompanying me...
Therefore...
I'm able to muster up courage like this right now.
I... like Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, you're really amazing.
Is that so?
It's alright. I've understood your feelings properly.
Kitamura-kun...
Do you still remember, Aisaka?
The incident a year ago...
Yeah.
Compared to how you were back then, you...
became more interesting.
I-Interesting?
Yeah.
The time when you were with Takasu, you had a really interesting expression.
Takasu is an amazing guy...
and the Aisaka who can think of him in that way just now...
...is a really great girl in my opinion.
Just now...
What have I said?
Anyway, knowing that you really patched it up with Takasu, I'm relieved.
W-W-W-Wait a moment!
This has nothing to do with Ryuuji...
Eh? My expression was interesting?
N-N-N-Not that... Relieved? Relieved about what?
Eh? No way, what am I saying?  Was I able to confess properly just now?
It's alright, Aisaka.
It's alright.
What do you mean by "it's alright"?
I don’t even remember what I said at all!
It's alright.
We'll definitely become really good friends from now onwards.
Didn't I say it's not just friends already, it's a confession...
Friends...
That's right. Friends.
We're going to be late for homeroom.
You should hurry up too, Aisaka.
I thought you would cry.
Y-Y-You... Why... H-H-Have you seen it?
It wasn't on purpose.
On purpose... You...
Apart from that, what do you plan to do?
I'm going home.
I see.
Well then, I'll whip up a meal for you.
You definitely didn't have breakfast, right?
Speaking of which, did you have a proper meal last night?
You probably had food from convenience store again...
Stop it.
Why? Doing things like this will bring about misunderstandings again.
Didn't I say to forget it? That kind of thing.
I don't understand either.
But, I can't leave you alone!
Like I've said, I don't need that!
You are not my dog anymore.
Is that so?
That's right, I'm not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
Therefore, I can stay by your side, Ai-
Taiga!
You called me Taiga?
The one able to stand by a tiger...
was decided to be a dragon in the past.
I'm going to become a dragon.
After which, as a dragon, I'll always stay by Taiga's side.
There's a limit to being thick-skinned.
Know your place!
You...!
Hey!
Hurry, I'm hungry.
Also, we're going to plan the next battle.
That won't make me give up on Kitamura-kun yet.
That means...
I don't care whether you are a dragon or a dog.
Since you said you're staying by my side,
you'll just have to work hard for my sake, right Ryuuji?
I made the decision too quickly.
Come on, hurry up!
Okay, okay.
Calling me Taiga, huh?
VANIRA SORUTO de VANIRA
Vanilla Salt, Vanilla
amai dakenara
If there's sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
Though understanding me more than anyone else
shintte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
But still wanting to find me
demo dekinaino
But it cannot be done
genke NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Experience nothing, too much gluttony
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But it's an ordinary love
watashi ga moto meteiru monotoha chigau
A little different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If you say I'm white
kuro datteiichau
I will say it's black
sunamo ninare baii amanochaku
It will be good if you are a little more honest, but you are always rebellious
SWEET iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say I'm sweet, I will say I hate it most
ureshii noni nani ite iunara
Being happy obviously, what am I saying
amai VANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding the sweet vanilla salt
Your Song
Club activities girl, Kushieda.
Friendly girl, Kushieda.
Ah, you're Kushieda.
Beaming with such radiance anytime, anywhere.
She's all yours now~