Starting tomorrow, I’ll be in high school, huh?
I wonder if I’ll make any friends…
Contact List
Search
So
Sonoda Yuu
Maybe I’ll ask Yuu for advice…
No! I can’t just always rely on her, I’m in high school now!
I need sleep!
Sonoda Yuu
Cell Phone
Yuu?
Hello?
Hello, Haruka?
Are you all packed for tomorrow?
Yuu?
Of course I did.
Good.
She hung up…
It’s Yuu again…
Hello?
Haruka, don’t forget that we’re checking our classes at the front gate tomorrow, okay?
Okay, I won’t forget…
Oh, really?
Yes, really!
You’re one to talk! I’d better not see you coming to school with rice on your face again!
I won’t!
I’m not like you, y’know?
I wouldn’t do that!
Alright, I’m hanging up. Don’t come with rice on your face tomorrow.
You’re  the one who did that!
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Ending the call...
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Ending the call...
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Ending the call...
Haruka
Mute
Speaker
to home screen
Ending the call...
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Call Ended
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Mute
Speaker
She hung up again…
What the heck?! Now I’m wide awake!
Stupid Yuu…
She was checking up on me.
Yuu’s always so nice to me.
She’ll probably show up with her usual hairstyle.
She’s pretty small, so I bet her uniform will look big on her.
I hope we’re in the same class…
It’d be great if I got to sit right behind her like I did in middle school.
Cherry blossom petals would be fluttering around, amidst a perfect sunset.
And then…
kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
i find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
being at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
i just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
we may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings go deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
at this rate
dou ka shichau
i might go crazy
gaman de wa
nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
if you just hold back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
i want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
won’t you kiss me? it’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
can I kiss you? it’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
with our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
West
Misato
High
School
62nd
Annual
Entrance
Ceremony
I’m sorry, Yuu!
You’re late, Haruka!
It’s because you called me so late last night!
That’s no excuse.
You have to plan ahead to manage your time properly.
You’re right.
I should follow your example!
A Cherry Blossom-Colored Start
My name is Takayama Haruka.
My last name starts with “Ta.”
And my friend’s last name, Sonoda Yuu, starts with “So.”
If we’re going by sitting arrangements I would be sitting at her back.
Class A
Iizuka Yuzu
Sonoda Yuu
Ikeno Kaede
Takayama Haruka
Osaki Akiko
Tsutsui Tomo
Hey, Haruka!
We’re in the same class!
Yes!
So
“So.”
Ta
“Ta.”
This is awful, I can’t tutor Yuu if she’s not sitting in front of me...
Haruka, I don’t understand this question...
Which one?
Wh-What is this...
Oh, that’s really quite simple...
Math 1
Thanks!
No problem.
No, stop imagining!
I don’t have much to talk about without Yuu here...
What if my neighbor’s really insensitive or something?
Nice to meet you. I’m Iizuka Yuzu, I’ll be sitting next to you.
I’m Ikeno Kaede.
Nice to meet you.
She’s here!
Ah, I made a weird sound!
So embarrassing!
Oh no, she’s actually...
not insensitive at all!
... I shouldn’t think that!
Entrance Ceremony
Alright, the opening ceremony will begin soon.
Everyone, please meet in the gymnasium.
Haruka!
Yuu!
Let’s go to the gym!
Let’s go!
Yeah!
Let’s go, let’s go!
Would you like to link arms as well?
N-No thanks!
You don’t like linking arms?
It’s not really normal, y’know?
Now that we’re in high school and all.
You’re just afraid of what people will think because Kaede is also a girl!
So you just pretend you’re a boy?
Your name’s Yuu, right?
Yup.
I’m Sonoda Yuu.
I’m Haruka’s friend.
Nice to meet you.
You too!
Hey Yuzu, we’re in the same class.
Kotone.
Her name’s Noda Kotone.
Her, Kaede and I all went to the same middle school.
Howdy, nice to meet you.
Howdy, nice to meet you!
You’re all great at it!
Boys
Okubo Satoshi
Oshima Tarou
Onoda Yuusuke
Katou Akishi
Kawasaki Hiroshi
Girls
Iizuka Yuzu
Ikeno Kaede
Osaki Akiko
Kawatou Ai
Sonoda Yuu
By the way…
The class list?
What about it?
Aramura Akane
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Look at this name.
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Murayama Yasuna
Moriuchi Ako
Minami Shizuku?
Interesting, right? It sounds like a name out of a comic.
She’s probably gorgeous!
I wonder what she’s like?
She’s raising the bar too high.
Otani Yuka
Let’s see.
Iizuka Yuzu
Ikeno Kaede
Osaki Akiko
Kawatou Ai
Sonoda Yuu
Takayama Haruka
Tsutsui Tomo
Aramura Akane
Noda Kotone
Minami Shizuku
Wouldn’t that be her?
Are you Minami Shizuku?
Ah, er, yes.
She’s so cute!
Just like her name.
Nice to meet you!
You too...
Don’t the people in our class seem fun?
Our school will be combined with the east school and will be effectively dissolved in three years.
We’re already in high school.
I’m sure the three years will go by in a flash.
She’s sleeping?
I still want to be with you through these coming years.
Yuu.
I still remember it.
The day we first met.
I was all alone until I met her.
That’s why it’s my turn to return the favor.
Clubs, culture festivals, and school trips…
So much for us to experience together.
They’re sleeping in plain view.
Yuu!
Let’s go home together.
Sonoda!
I got you!
That’s my  treasured spot!
What’s wrong, Haruka?
Eh? Um…
Tr-…
“Tr”?
T-Treasured spot!
N-Nothing!
Trouble?
Trip?
Truffle?
Transit?
I decided to just run away.
This is… an unused classroom?
Will Yuu and I grow distant? Will my heart become empty, just like this classroom?
Can we only be together in the past?
Haruka…
Yuu.
Haruka!
I let them do that even though I knew, I’m sorry!
Knew what?
That you’re an incredibly clingy and persistently jealous girl!
Jealousy
Y-You know…
I don’t want you to feel like you have to ignore everyone else just to make me happy.
I’ve just been selfishly thinking that I’m special to you.
Well then...
Let’s do something we’d never do with anyone else but each other.
Then it’ll be special, right?
R-Really?!
Yeah!
Then let’s try flower fortune telling!
She loves me!
She loves me not!
Go ahead.
Go.
A.
Head.
Geez, I’m trying to be serious here.
E-Er… What should we do?
Above all, it should be something the two of us won’t easily forget.
How about…
a k-kiss?
“K-Kiss”?! What are you saying?!
School is a place for studying, not a place for kissing!
Oh, my!
Oh my!
Studying, you say? Coming from the one always sleeping in class?
If you can’t even stay awake, how can you possibly kiss well?
A-Alright!
Let’s do it! Let’s kiss!
Really?!
Stand up!
Okay!
Yuu just let out a sound.
She’s adorable.
I made a sound.
What should I do if she heard me?
Make more sounds, Yuu.
One more.
Control yourself.
Control yourself!
Just one more.
Can’t breathe…
A Cherry Blossom-Colored Start
End
They made another new Pokitz.
No matter how many new flavors they make, I’ll always prefer salad flavor.
Oh, the unused classroom.
It’s closed.
The teacher said not to go in.
That door’s open!
Alright.
Yuu
Haruka
Your back is wide open!
Hey, say something.
Yuu gets so embarrassed when I don’t react to her jokes, how cute!
Yakisoba and Balconies and Girls
I wonder if they’ll move things around.
Like the desks?
I want it to stay exactly the same...
...because this place is a precious memory to us.
Nipa?
Nipa
Does she really not remember what happened or is she just a complete ditz?
Yuu, did you forget what happened here?!
Can I please have my math notebook back?
Eh? I didn’t borrow it.
What? I gave it to you this morning!
Now that I think about it, she is pretty forgetful.
Let’s do something we’d never do with anyone else but each other.
Did the kiss we shared mean nothing to her?
I’ll remind her!
Haruka, we need to hurry up!
This mission’s objective is to secure yakisoba for Yuzu.
Oh no! Two teachers are coming!
We have to hide!
But where?
The locker might be nice...
What if they find us?
Don’t worry.
No, no. The teacher’s desk is better.
S-Sorry.
Let’s run to the balcony!
Yuu!
dorori
What are you having for lunch, Yuzu?
I asked Haruka and Yuu to buy me something at the convenience store.
They left? Weird, those two always bring lunch boxes.
I’m just really craving for yakisoba.
I asked them to grab some for you, too.
Great. Yakisoba again.
Even though you were thinking of “this,” they might screw up and get “that.”
This
That
You don’t have faith in your own friends, Kaede?
I always believe in my friends!
What I don’t have faith in is your poor choice of words.
You only said “yakisoba,” right?
Yes, but obviously girls don’t eat yakisoba from a cup.
Eating them with bread is more refined.
Refined...
Empty
You just don’t get it.
Oh?
Where’s your lunch, Shizuku?
I’m not hungry.
gruuumble
I have hot water!
That’s not food...
Yuu, we ma-
Whoa, she’s close!
This might be my chance to kiss her again!
That’s odd, wasn’t this door closed?
Did someone open it?
They came in!
I’m glad we hid ourselves in time.
Now we just have to be absolutely silent.
What do you think you’re doing?!
This isn’t the time to be doing that!
But… But Yuu...
I-It’s because you forgot our kiss from before!
I thought you would remember if I kissed you again...
I’m sorry!
I should have realized you actually hated it and just left it alone!
That’s not it.
You’re too loud!
Don’t hate me!
You’re the only thing I have left!
Haruka, stop and listen to me!
Marry me, Yuu!
I really hope that was a joke!
No!
Don’t hate me!
Haruka!
Haruka, stop!
You finally shut up.
If you don’t do it again, I’ll start yelling.
Are you kidding me?!
No?
Think of what would happen if we got caught!
Don’t worry.
Just for one second.
Uh oh, this feels too good to stop.
I’m sorry, Yuu.
bonk
You said just one second!
Sorry, I’m sorry!
They sure are running late.
I’m starting to get really hungry.
I’m going to the cafeteria, any requests?
Nah, I’ll just wait for them.
Hey, Shizuku. Come to the cafeteria with me?
I think I’ll pass.
Oh, then shall I bring back some hot water?
I’ll come.
I hope the teachers left already.
What did they even come here for?
Let’s get going.
clatter
They came to lock the doors!
We’re locked in!
Geez! If you hadn’t wasted so much time making us kiss…
You shouldn’t have even come in here to begin with!
It’s all my fault…
No, it’s not!
Ah! It’s Yuzu’s fault!
If she hadn’t gotten a craving for yakisoba…
...we never would have entered this room!
What do we do now?
Stupid Yuzu!
I’m so sorry, Yuzu.
Don’t worry. If we use the balconies, we should be able to get next door.
Balcony?
Nice one, Haruka!
Daunting
What the...
Whooooosh
No choice but to jump.
I’ll go on ahead!
What? You’re going first?
Wait up! Don’t leave me behind!
Take me with you!
Yuu, what’re you trying to do?!
Pervert!
You’re such a pervert!
I bet you did it on purpose!
Who goes straight for the chest?!
I’m not a pervert!
I’m so sorry!
I kissed you so much, after all!
I’m way more perverted!
Please forgive me!
So
hungry
Okay, we’ve gotta do this.
Give it your best, Haruka.
Hey, Haruka…
You’re a C-cup, right?
Must be nice.
You sure know your stuff…
Though I’m more of a D…
Haruka, watch out!
Haruka… I will protect you!
Are you okay?!
Hey, c’mon!
I don’t think she’s breathing!
What’ll I do?
Mouth-to-mouth would be standard, wouldn’t it?
But we just locked lips so much…
She’ll probably get mad at me again!
No, this is an emergency.
Okay! Let’s do th-
Ouch… I hit my head…
What’s going on?
Yuzu! Kaede!
This is our classroom’s balcony!
What happened out here?
Um, well...
I can’t tell them! I need to create a diversion, fast!
Haruka’s a C-cup, ya know!
Um, what?
So, where’s my yakisoba bun?
Cup! Cup! Cup!
Stop chanting right now.
I have it right here.
It was the last one, too.
Yakisoba Flavor
Limited Spring Edition
Here you go!
Yakisoba Flavor
Limited Spring Edition
Even I couldn’t have predicted this...
Yakisoba and Balconies and Girls
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
the time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we share
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have them all
yorokobi wakachi aete
if we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
if we split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
memories of the future… let’s make them
ippai ni shichaou ne
we’ll make lots and lots
love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
the miracle of us meeting in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
it had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
it’s something we can’t do unless we’re together
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Minami Shizuku here.
Noda Kotone too!
Hey, why’d you raise those hurdles for me anyway?
Peek
Aren’t you the cutie?
Why?
Expulsion
Aren’t you just a cutie…
You really are a cutie!
Stop it!
You’re just so cute!
Next time, Trick 2.
One More Cherry Blossom-Color
After School with Mr. Hedgey
“One More Cherry Blossom-Color” and “After School with Mr. Hedgey”
I can’t wait!