Finally, I've started drawing doujinshi!
Well, it's not like there's a barrier to entry.
If I sell well, I'll be on the road to becoming a celebrity in no time!
You should be careful around Otome Road, though.
Otome Road, the nickname for a street in Ikebukuro often likened to an Akihabara for women.
I'll do well - just you watch!
Please, keep an eye out for her sake.
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
I've got a little something to ask you...
How do I make a book that'll sell well?
That's rather straightforward.
There's no reason to learn bit by bit, is there?
I thought it'd be faster to just learn from you, since you're already doing well...
You know, techniques and stuff.
Techniques...
What're you thinking?
So?  What kind of book should I make?
It'd be well-drawn
...Erotic...
And with an interesting story.
There's no way I could write something like that!
Are you making fun of me?
Finally, the most important element...
It would be love, wouldn't it?
Love is what moves the hearts of your readers.
Well, it's not like I don't understand what you mean, but...
I see... Love, huh.
If that's the case, I can't possibly lose to anyone.
Because, I give a lot of love to Father and Mother!
Najimi isn't here?
She hasn't been here for three days.
Besides that though, I'm more surprised that you go to the same university as us.
I'm not a teacher, though.
I'm a student.
More surprises.
It's Najimi.
I've finally done it...
I've given birth to something...
Najimi!
Did you really make one?
Yeah.
Then... it'll be here soon, won't it?
It may be painful, but do your best.
No way!
I've already struggled enough.
I've had more than enough of pain, making it.
Huh? It's already here?
That's why I'm this tired!
I didn't notice at all...
I was gone for a little while, though.
You didn't come for a while.
You became worried.
And then it was finally confirmed, wasn't it?
What do you mean, confirmed?
You must've been so scared, all alone...
I asked Justice to help me.
Didn't I, Justi-
What?
Justice, calm down.
Yeah.
And the name? Have you decided?
Yeah, Love Typhoon!
That's an original name.
I'm glad the registry let you choose it.
Osana Love Typhoon.
What are you muttering about?
So? What about your partner?
Partner?
What does your partner think?
Oh, you mean the customer?
CUS...TOMER?!
Najimi!
That hurt! What are you doing?
I totally misjudged you.
Pimping yourself out... stop it, now!
Eh?
Love Typhoon...
Now, see here! I was talking about my manga!
Yes, I know.
Huh?
Ahh, that was funny.
It wasn't funny at all.
Justice totally misunderstood.
And whose fault was that?
So, show me Love Typhoon.
Huh?
What do you think?
Give it to me straight.
Okay,  um...
Good paper...
This is good paper, definitely.
Yeah.
For a first printing to have paper this good, you're quite fortunate.
It feels good to the touch, and there's nothing wrong with the finish.
Tsuyuri, what are you...?
Oh, that's right.
The art's not much to speak of, but it feels like you put effort into it.
The readers will be able to see that.
Heh, really?
That's a little embarassing.
I'm having to think fast...
Nothing.
Najimi, what is this?
That's my pen name!
Beauty Love.
Um, yeah.
That fits you, Najimi, definitely.
Yeah.
Especially adding a ten-ten to "U" instead of using "Fu", I can really feel your attention to detail.
In other words-
Sorry, I just can't do this.
Finally, this day has arrived!
Come to me, my ten million yen!
With thirty copies, you'll never be able to make ten million.
Geez!  Don't bring me back down to earth like that!
I see.  So you brought thirty books, Najimi?
That's right, one thousandth as many as you.
Stop that!
No, Sora. It's all right.
To Najimi, this is a special piece of work.
Those thirty books clearly surpass the value of my thirty thousand.
Her concentrated love and tears.
He still hasn't gotten it yet, has he?
Najimi...
I'll help you.
After all, your body's not just yours now.
Really, you sent it off to the printers just like I taught you.
Let's see...
First, this is good paper.
Good paper, definitely.
Ah, for a first printing to have paper this good...
Oh?
And for you to have named it after your child...
What a wonderful child, Najimi!
You shouldn't look at that! It's for adults, you know.
Uh, I'm sorry!
What's with this kid?
Let's go, Sora.
Yeah...
This...
This is worse than I ever imagined.
What's with that smug look?
Oh!  It's you, from back then!
My, my, my.
What is it?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
We're so busy, there's not even any time to rest.
Despite that, it's fun.
Two people moving and moving, without time to rest.
A crowd of customers watching attentively.
You feel it, don't you?
As if this is a ballroom for only the two of us.
Justice!
Sora!
Sounds like Justice sold everything.
"How's Najimi doing?" he asks.
This is bad.
If this continues, I won't sell anything...
And that'll end my dream before it's even begun!
Huh?
It's you, from the other day.
You remembered me?
Well, it's more like I didn't want to remember that.
This, did you draw this?
Having some porn that you drew yourself shown to other people is...
That's right.
It's certainly embarassing.
It's like stripping yourself naked in public.
Even though you're absolutely right, that's a pretty icky example.
Eventually, you'll feel good about it.
Nah, no way!
Perverted, isn't it?
The book?
I'm not like that!
I just wrote down what I imagined!
I'm totally not into things like this in real life!
What am I doing, explaining myself?
It's going to have the opposite effect!
It's not like I'm narrow-minded...
Right?
Also, it's not like I drew porn because I was frustrated or anything.
It's not like that at all, so...
I understand.
Besides, I like girls who draw this kind of manga...
Are you sexually harassing me!?
Sexual harassment?
A sexual harasser?
Please form a line.
It's being read!
Lots of guys are reading!
My perverted pictures!
My perverted lines! They're being read!
It really feels like you went all-out with this.
One copy, please.
Here, one copy of this book, please.
Huh, really?
Really.
That'll be five hundred yen.
Uh, sure.
I love you!
Wait!
Don't!
So suddenly...
So, how much is this?
Me too, please!
There's no guarantee she'll hug you if you buy it.
Sorry! I mean, finally!
Thank you!
Oh, don't worry about it.
Um, if it's okay, after this why don't the two of us go somewhere and-
Wai- what is it?
He's going to kill me!
I see, so it was you?
Acknowledge your child, you bastard!
What're you talking about?!
But...I'm glad...
Look this way, please!
Be careful! There are things that are okay to sell, and things that aren't!
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
Next time,
You'll get 30 percent more service.
30 percent more...
Heh...