How much longer will this rain continue?
Our one day off and we get rained in!
Oh, I messed up again...
Tch, tch, tch!
That song is still far too difficult for you!
Hey, you're still learning it.
Everyone makes mistakes at first.
But I still love how splendid this song is.
Princesse Haruka, vous must be calm when playing.
Calm ta nerves and take la song one note at a time.
One note at a time!
Je once taught this song to le Prince Kanata.
As well as to his younger sister...
Wha?!
Kanata has a sister?!
Oui!
A sister...
That is to say, Hope Kingdom's princess.
His sister practiced violin day and night.
She became quite skilled in spite of her youth.
It's been too long, la petite princesse...
Hope Kingdom's princess...
Princess...
That's the princess I want to be!
Definitely...
I'll definitely become a princess!
Quoi?
Uh, I mean, I should work a bit harder...
You're working plenty.
You've learned violin, ballet,
and that thé de l'après-midi, right?
We've gotten nine Keys now, so we've come a long way!
Sometimes I wonder...
I feel like I haven't grown a bit since I moved here.
It's difficult to notice one's own growth.
Is that so?
Oh, I haven't been able to jog at all thanks to this rain!
I can at least master this!
Oh, there you all are!
Overcast got you downcast?
Seira...
Well, don't be blue!
The scavenger hunt's about to begin!
Scavenger hunt?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Found It!
The Treasure Inside the Dorm!
Princess Twilight, I shall crush the Princess Precures and avenge your defeat.
Defeat, you say?
You think the Precures truly bested me?!
N-No, I'd never even imagine...
W-Where are you going?
Princess Twilight!
Curse you, Princess Precures!
Glad you all made it!
Welcome, young treasure-seeking adventurers!
Seira loves holding events.
Sure do!
Now, it's time to start our in-dorm scavenger hunt!
Now, who here wants some treasure?
I can't hear you!
Who here wants some treasure?
Me!
Okay! First, let's split into teams!
Okay, that's everyone.
Now, find your teammates!
Let's do our best.
Sure!
Let's work together and find that treasure!
Sure.
Good luck, Haruno.
K-Kano, I'll try to stay on your good side!
Uh, okay...
This is my first time on a scavenger hunt!
Same here. I'm kind of excited.
That treasure...
is so gonna be ours!
Sure!
Seira, you're participating?
Of course!
Nobody wants to do this scavenger hunt more than me!
I figured that was the case.
Now, to disperse our clues to the treasure, we have...
Mrs. Shirogane, dorm mother.
Each letter has a challenge. Every team gets one.
"What kind of cave has one entrance but splits into five directions inside?"
"What's the most active kind of nut?"
Like, a nut that gives you energy?
Let me take a look.
The hint says that it's the nut itself that's active.
A nut that does things...
The nut... does...
Oh, maybe it's a doughnut!
'Cause it's a "Do-Nut"!
Or not...
Wow! Way to go, Hitomin!
H-Hitomin?
Our "Do-Nut" is a doughnut!
That's gotta be the answer!
Here, your treat is these handmade doughnuts.
They look yummy!
Doughnuts. Correct.
Great going!
What's wrong?
We always thought you were a bit harder to approach, Amanogawa.
Huh?
You know...
You'd always head straight to work after school.
But now...
There's a different air about you.
Different? Me?
Kirara!
Did you get the answer?!
Of course!
What?! We've gotta hurry!
Oh yeah, you can just call me Kirara.
Amanogawa's kinda long.
"What snickers by the entrance?"
To a restaurant? Customers, I suppose?
Maybe it means the entrance to the dorm.
Snickers by the entrance... Snickers by the entrance...
I've got it!
Wait, Minami!
Shoes?
Can't you imagine these sneakers "sneakering" by the entrance?
Correct.
I knew it!
I feel like you've learned to snicker more, Minami.
Remember how you used to be as strict as a teacher?
You were all, "put your back into it!"
But there's a different air about you now.
Is there?
Hey!
Minami! Yui! Good luck!
Same to you, Haruka!
See? You just snickered.
This isn't it...
I don't know!
Oops!
That was close!
Seems you've learned to walk in the halls.
Perf!
She's simply too cute!
Perf! Perf!
Uh, I mean, she's just so lovable, you know?
Since you always play with her, I'm sure Perf likes you the most.
D-Does she?
Perf!
I was never great with dogs,
but even I have no trouble petting her.
It's thanks to you, Haruno.
You're the first person to change this dorm's policies.
Where do you get your power from?
Yeah, and remember the field day?
You actually kept up with Aihara at tennis!
What motivates you so much?
N-Nothing!
Really, I'm nothing special...
"Something that's outside, yet still at home..."
Shall we go for a stroll?
Side ponytail!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
This light...
Have the Precures obtained a new Key?
The Princess Precures are doing what they can.
Until the day my kingdom is freed...
I also must not falter!
Let us ride, Wish.
What...
am I doing here?
Is that not...
How pretty!
They finally bloomed!
And I just pulled them...
Wait, have you been the one tending to this garden?
Yes!
I love flowers, after all.
There's one!
"Something that's outside, yet still at home" would be...
A snail!
Correct.
Yay!
We did it!
I never thought this garden could blossom so splendidly.
Admiring these flowers has become part of my daily routine.
Maybe my work's finally bearing fruit...
Now to give you your next challenge.
Next?
What appears different to all who gaze at it while changing day by day?
To restore Princess Twilight's smile,
there is naught but to defeat the Princess Precures!
This rain isn't letting up.
I may as well give the students a good meal.
The scent of cuisine carries with it the scent of dreams.
Now, show me your dream.
I hope my food gives our students
the nourishment they need to grow!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
"It appears different to all who gaze at it..."
"It changes day by day..."
The answer...
is my reflection in the mirror!
Correct.
Yay!
I see you've all found the real treasure.
People all grow in way in ways they don't even notice.
What do you all think of what you see in the mirror?
Dyspairvil!
What was that?
Everyone, stay calm.
I'll check outside.
Haruka, Kirara, can you come help?
Sure!
Okay!
Seira, look after the students.
Got it.
There you are, Precures.
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
It's fast!
Dyspair!
How fitting!
Kneel upon the rain-soaked soil!
Dyspair! Dyspair!
Stop it!
The dorm won't hold!
Dyspair?
Dyspair!
This dorm is dear to us!
It's really strong!
Dyspairvil!
Excellent!
Blow the Precures and their dormitory away!
Dyspairvil!
We'll stop you!
We'll protect our dorm!
It's our home that lets us grow day by day...
so we won't let you hurt it!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Dys... Dyspairvil!
Now's your chance!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Lily!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Curse you, Princess Precures!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Thanks for all the great meals.
I'm fine.
Little by little, I'm growing closer to becoming a princess.
How curious...
It's as though someone called me here.
Is that...
the Precure's...
Why is it here?
With this Perfume, I can match the Precures...
Nay, far surpass them!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Oh? What's this? The Keys are shining.
Are we in... Hope Kingdom?
It seems there's some kind of emergency.
They Keys are leading us... into a castle?
Could that man be... Kanata?!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Reunion With Kanata?!
Onward, To Hope Kingdom!
Go say bonjour to your dream!