This is... my favorite place...
No one comes around this side...
I see... Do you always
do battle here, Hitoe-san?
Ah? N-No. I just got my cards recently too.
The match against Akira-san was...
my very first battle...
I was imagining training myself
while Midoriko gave me tips,
to think of different battle situations.
Like this...
Wow!
P-Please don't look at it so closely!
I was still unprepared...
The real battle was much different.
I don't think I was ready for it yet...
Huh? Then why do you want to battle me?
Ah, well...
You seemed weak,
so I thought it would be okay...
That's... pretty straightforward.
I-I'm sorry! B-But, I really want to win...
She's really trying her best.
If she wins the battle,
and gets closer to her wish, then...
Let's battle.
Open!
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
Yay! Battling with Yuzu-pon!
Battling with Yuzu-pon!
I go first!
Draw! Energy Charge! Summon, Amethyst!
"Battle Stone" "Amethyst"
If she uses that Peeping-something move,
I'm gonna be in trouble.
With Amethyst's power,
I'll banish R.F.R and attack Sapphire!
I'll lay it on now before she
Grows enough to use that move!
Attack, Hanayo-san!
Ouch-y! You should be ashamed
for being so aggressive-y.
It's my turn now. Piruluk-tan, Grow.
And now for a spell! It's card bye-bye time!
Too Bad.
Here it comes...
Time to toss your card away! Mmm... that!
"Battle Stone" "Makuri" "Iron"
Aw... a level 1 card? So weak.
You're the type who wants to
overwhelm by going in numbers, right?
It's my choice how I fight!
I was just giving you some advice.
Even if you have a red deck, it doesn't mean
you should be super straightforward, you know?
Your style of battle is
too straightforward, Yuzuki.
What's so wrong with being straightforward?
Open!
The field feels a lot warmer compared
to when I battled Akira-san...
You're right. It does feel different
from when I was battling Yuzuki-san.
The wind feels good.
The field is a manifestation of
the affinity between the Selectors.
Affinity?
Hitoe, you're green, and Ruko is white...
a pretty rare color.
With both together, warm light is born.
I see...
I feel I can battle a lot more
calmly now, Midoriko!
Yeah. Let's do our best.
Hitoe-san and Midoriko-san are both really nice.
Ruko-san, please go first.
Um, okay. Um, draw...
Ener Charge. Tama, Grow.
I don't have any level 1 cards... Turn end.
I won't lose! Draw 2, Energy Charge!
Summon, Mi-Ke and Mi-Ke!
Mi-Ke, attack!
This is so different compared to when
I was playing at home with Grandma.
My ears feel hot... I can feel the pain...
But...
...I feel excited too!
Tama, Grow to level 2! Round, and Square!
Attack Mi-Ke with Round, banish!
Attack with Square!
Here she comes, Midoriko-san!
Tama, attack!
A-Again?! Midoriko!
Midoriko-san!
I'm fine! Use Grow!
Yes! Midoriko-san, level 2! Summon Shiro!
Midoriko Arts, Giant! Shiro's power
gains +5000 in the next turn!
Shiro attack!
I shouldn't win...
Ruko-san?
She seems to have lost heat all of a sudden.
Now's your chance, Hitoe! Attack!
Y-Yes!
...because...
Tama!
Piruluk-tan, Grow!
My Ener isn't ready...
Arts, Peeping Analyze.
It's finally going to come...
The move... It doesn't only discard my card...
...let me guess why Hitoe
wants to be an Eternal Girl...
She's going to see... Find out...
There's nothing wrong with it being known.
Hanayo-san...
If your wish comes true,
everyone will find out anyways.
Just brace yourself.
Knowing her, she's going to say
horrible things to you using it, but...
...your wish is nothing to be ashamed of!
Okay!
Let's toss out your level 1 cards!
And now... I'll take a peek into
your wish. Piruluk-tan, look into her!
Immoral...
Loves... her younger brother...
Whaaat?! No way! That was her younger
brother?! The pipsqueak with the same face?!
Calm down.
I know... I know...
You've got to be kidding?!
That's super erotic! That's super pervy!
--Super immoral!
--Sh-Shut... shut up!
I know a word that describes this.
Do you want to know the word?
I-N-C-E...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Yuzuki!
Dominating Fury!
Don't do it! If you use such
a burdening Arts now...!
Stop! Yuzuki!
...if I win, Hitoe-san's wish won't come true.
No...
No... I want to win...
Tama? You... just spoke?!
No lose on purpose...
No... I want to win. Tama wants to win!
Tama...
On purpose? Were you planning
to lose on purpose, Ruko-san?!
If you did that, even if I win, I won't
be happy. There's no meaning to it!
Hitoe-san...?
There's no use for me to hide it already...
I have no friends.
I moved from Aomori to Tokyo.
I had an accent and was slow,
so I couldn't make any friends...
"Uemura"
But then I got a letter from my friend in Aomori.
I read it over and over again, and... it saved me.
"you'll be fine wherever you go, Hitoe-chan"
"we'll always be friends" "let's play a lot again."
To me, a friend is a very beautiful thing!
Hitoe-san...
That's why I don't want to
tarnish my wish with cheating!
I want to do my best,
and attain my wish the right way!
You're so neat, Hitoe-san.
I'm sorry...
I don't have any wish,
but I want to battle with all I've got...
That's right... I'll battle with all I've got!
Ruko-san!
Good! Let's give it all we've got too!
Yes!
This is... fun!
I feel the excitement swelling
inside... I just want to shout!
Spell, Oversize! Power-up all the SIGNIs...
I won't let that spell get past me!
Anti-Spell!
This is the first time I've felt this good!
Midoriko!
I'm fine.
Hitoe...
You did well.
I...
...won?
Having a serious battle is... so amazing.
Huh? The battle ended, but why
aren't we being sent back to our world?
I wonder what's going on, Tama?
Tama?
Tama?!
Tama...
She evolved.
Evolved? Is this different from "Grow"?
Yeah. The closer a Selector is to being an
Eternal Girl, the more we LRIGs gain power
and become stronger.
Wow, Tama! You're beautiful!
Ru, thank you!
Tama! You're speaking...
Tama?
She's in her stronger form
even when she's in her card.
You're right... It looks like
the words here are different too.
Um, Ruko-san? Tama? I'm sorry
to have said that you looked weak.
You were both very strong.
Hitoe-san.
If I lose one more time, my wish
won't come true. But, I won't regret it!
But wait, I may regret it...
Um...
Yes?
I was thinking maybe we can be friends,
with all this Eternal Girl stuff aside.
Wh-What?!
I actually just moved here, and
I couldn't make any friends either.
But, when I finally made a friend, it felt good.
So, I... no, you may not like it,
but if you'd like...
Not like?! No! I...
Excuse me...
Can you be a bit more quiet?
--I'm sorry!
I-I'll think about it!
Hitoe-san...
She's already asleep.
Wow, it's so dark already.
Grandma's going to be worried.
"Pedestrians and vehicles only"
My, a book about a card game?
"WIXOSS Card Encyclopedia" "Bookstore"
This is quite something.
"Sephirum" "Square" "Riot" "God Eater"
Each card is carefully explained in detail.
There're a lot of cards I don't know here...
This one looks pretty good.
What are you doing?
Well, I met a girl today, and she was taking
notes on the decks and battle flow simulations.
Do you think you can be friends?
Well, I'm waiting for her answer.
Let me get that. Once dinner is ready,
let Grandma take a look too, okay?
And we can battle after too!
With how Tama is now, I can add more red
cards and work them with the Search effect.
This might work.
But, if I take out some cards, it'll become
weaker compared to Yuzuki-san's pure red deck.
I'll battle because it's fun. That's enough
for now. But, if that's okay, then...
"Receiving"
I'll get it.
Hello? Huh? Kazuki-kun?
What's the matter? What?
Yuzuki-san?!
Yuzuki-san hasn't come home yet?
Did you get in touch with her?
She hasn't phoned or emailed me back.
I thought she would be at your house.
Maybe...
Akira-san?
What's the matter?
Like, did you overdo yourself or something?
Stop being a try-hard.
Oh well, it's about time
I turn the tables. Here I come!
If I had the Adamasphere that Kazuki
was talking about, I could have retaliated...
Now, Piruluk-tan! Finish them! Boom!
Hanayo-san!
I'm sorry, Hanayo-san.
Yuzuki!
Yuzuki-san!
Did you battle Akira?!
Wait! Why'd you battle her?!
Let me go!
I told you that you can't beat her
with what you got now! Why did you...
--Shut up!
--Yuzuki...
You'd never understand, Kazuki...
You'd never understand how I feel!
Yuzuki...
That's...
I asked Momoka-san, and got this.
Is that why you met Momoka-san today?
How did you know?
She said that there was another
customer who was willing to trade it,
so Momoka-san worked it out for us.
"Shining Battle Stone" "Adamasphere"
Why...
Why didn't you just tell me?
If the trade didn't go well, I would've
just kept your hopes up for nothing.
I'm sorry I was so harsh on you, Yuzuki.
I mean, you just started after all, right?
Kazuki...
You'll be stronger if you have that card,
Yuzuki. You've only just begun.
I'll help too, so let's
get better together, okay?
Yuzuki...
I'll be fine!
Can you leave me alone for a bit...
I'm sorry!
Yuzuki...
Kazuki-kun... Yuzuki-san must
be really important to you.
Yeah...
When I was a kid, I was really weak and shy.
Yuzuki was always there to help me.
But now it's my turn.
I want to do my best to help
Yuzuki make her wish come true...
And when Yuzuki's wish comes true...
I can finally say that I was able to help Yuzuki.
Stupid Kazuki... Why is he so kind to me?
His kindness is making things more painful...
Good morning!
Akira, you're late! Hurry and get ready.
I'm sorry!
Looking good, Iona!
Yeah, cute!
Excuse me.
Damn... it...!
I've beaten Hitoe, and I've beaten Yuzuki...
So why isn't anything changing?!
If you lose three WIXOSS battles,
you lose rights to enter in battle...
So, how many times do you have
to win to become an Eternal Girl?!
Just winning isn't enough to be an Eternal Girl.
There are certain conditions
that need to be met for each wish.
So spill it then.
Say it, or else I'll rip you...
You better say it now before it's too late.
Here it comes...
Tear me.
The hell! You're pissing me off!
Talking all high n' mighty!
The way you say things... reminds me of her...
Iona... Enjoy the limelight while you still can...
Just you wait...
Say, Iona? I just sensed Akira's battle.
It looks like she won.
She seemed pretty upset though.
Say, Iona? Let's just get rid of Akira.
I'm sure it'll feel good seeing
her cry. It'll be a spectacle.
Stop saying such brutish things...
or else I'll burn you.
So scary...
Nodding to the clockwork shadow
opens the door to the end,
bringing in the darkness
There we catch glimpses of the perilous answer
Today's prayer becomes taboo tomorrow
The upside-down maze reflects
the heavens and the earth
The gear begins to turn
Listen carefully among the masses
and that bell resounding in
the skies beckons the soul...
I must move forward even beyond eternity
Because it is the future I chose
The unreachable summer clouds
and flickering heat haze
One day I'll get back my place of smiles
It doesn't bother me a bit.
Orichalcum, attack!
I wonder how it feels to be in love.
That feels so weird!
WIXOSS is so... wonderful.
"That Wish Is Blasphemy."