What is a physical body?
The body is merely an object.
It is an existence all too impure
to store the gods within us called souls.
Now, you will remember.
The bloodstained history.
Material desire. Hunger. Sexual drive.
Desire to dominate. Desire for fame.
As long as there is a body,
desires will be born.
As long as there is desire,
human ego will not disappear.
Humans will continue to fight
to fulfill their bodies' desires,
and it will never end.
At this rate, there is no future!
Now, awaken your soul!
Now, be rid of that filthy body.
We are SCRATCH,
an electronic transcendence group.
We are disciples of God,
sent here to free your soul from your body
and lead you to the infinite sea
of electrons.
Good evening. This is CBC News.
First, news about the electronic
transcendence group SCRATCH.
Last week, the ISSP and all
Sol Solar System Police Departments
received the wanted poster
for the leader, Londes,
and began searching the homes
of high-ranking members...
Here at the scene.
Enticing people with "easy entry"
and "salvation of the soul,"
SCRATCH has been able
to constantly grow in numbers.
However, another suicide...
The members of SCRATCH use
the brain-wave control device
on this new game console
to scan their own brain waves
and use a program
created by their leader, Londes...
which is said to copy the spirit
from brain waves as digital data
and upload that spirit data
into the universal network.
They believe that doing this will make
them exist as a soul without a body.
Now, Professor, they say that Londes,
the leader, was once a doctor.
Is such a thing possible?
This is ridiculous. Completely
in the realm of science fiction.
It may be theoretically possible to do so,
but a theory is only a theory, in the end.
Yes, and he hasn't returned for two weeks!
Lady, you have to talk it out
with your husband.
It's about your son.
But he isn't the type that
would just run away from home.
Could he have been kidnapped?!
Lady, are you listening
to what I'm saying?
That's gotta be it!
That religion that's popular now,
-that whatchamacallit--
- We're gonna take a break.
Hi! Today, I'm introducing Power CDJ,
an item for DJ's who don't exercise much!
You adjust the BPM using this lever
and it allows you to be a DJ
while you exercise!
Then, the reason
you decided to join is...?
Yes...
I got tired of my debt-filled life...
and that was when I found this.
Yes... if I rid myself of a body,
I'll no longer need money
- Hey, Jet.
- Hold on. It's almost done.
I don't care. Just get over here.
By releasing the spirit from the body,
we are able to discard all desire.
- So, you're going to forget your debt?
- I thought we hadn't seen her in a while.
What kind of joke is this?
Brain Dream!
The new game console, Brain Dream,
can read your mind!
Control your games
the way that you want to!
Are you always fighting
with your controls?
Do the cords get tangled?
If that's the case,
then let's dream together!
And so, at our station, we have
the strictest policies in the world
against programs such as this.
Oh, there it is.
I'm gonna eat now!
Dr. Londes. Wanted for murder.
The bounty is an amazing 38 million.
I see.
That's enough for her to flake out on us.
This guy was apparently
a neurobiology researcher 50 years ago.
However, one day he suddenly
had a vision from God...
and immersed himself in research
to store the human spirit,
the functions of the brain itself,
as digital data.
Since then, he's been missing.
Then, two years ago, he reappeared
to form the electronic transcendence group SCRATCH.
What the hell is that?
In other words, a new religious cult.
Anyway, according to him,
the human brain function itself
is a weak stream of electronic pulses,
so if you are able to copy that as data,
and replay it over
the universal network as a program,
you can exist only as a soul.
Are you listening to me?
Well, it's up to you to believe it or not.
There are already 20,000 believers,
of which approximately 100
have committed suicide
or ended up missing.
And so, the cops have started
moving their lazy asses.
His face ain't appetizing.
Seconds!
That's all.
We're gonna go after him, too.
We are SCRATCH,
an electronic transcendence group.
We are disciples of God,
sent here to free your soul from your body
and lead you
to the infinite sea of electrons.
Searching, searching. Where are you?
Oh, so, you want to be a member as well?
Yeah, I guess.
For that,
we need to cleanse your soul first.
As the first step--
Before that,
I want to meet this Mr. Londes.
- Do you know where he is?
- Oh, of course.
Really?
He's in heaven.
Londes?
Hum, did such a guy exist?
You gotta help me, old man.
You're the only colleague of his
that is still alive.
Can't you remember something? Anything?
Maybe he existed, maybe he didn't.
Which is it?
Oh, then you want
to be a member as well?
Yeah, I guess.
For that,
we need to cleanse your soul first.
- As the first step--
- Oh, can I ask something before that?
I want to see Mr. Londes.
Well, his soul or whatever will do, anything.
But how can I meet him?
Do you really want to become a member?
And so, Dr. Londes is the center
of everyone's attention.
The first big-name guy in a while!
Unfortunately,
we have absolutely no new information!
Oh, my.
Everyone is doing their best to find him,
but there just isn't any information.
We're seeing his face, virtually,
every day from SCRATCH's TV programs,
but we know nothing important about him.
Is he really a soul without a body?
Now, I have one other bit
of important news for you.
Oh, what is it?
- Actually--
- Hurry up and tell me!
We've been on the air for a long time now,
and I know it's sudden,
but this is our final episode!
You're kidding?!
They're canning us because of low ratings, unfortunately.
Unfortunately?!
How come I didn't hear about this?!
- No good?
- No good.
I got nothing, either.
Nope, nope!
I went after his colleagues
from his research days,
but it was all for nothing.
And I got nothing out of the members.
It's Faye-Faye.
I'm in... a little... trouble.
Are you listening?
I think I really can...
get rid of my debt.
Anyway, I'm trusting you with Faye.
I'm gonna be having a hard time
if you're gonna be baby-sitting forever.
As I said...
Brain Dream is pretty rare.
I have to line up here if I want one.
Are you really going
to hack into his home page?
That's the only lead we got left.
Beyond that, Faye seems to have
dug something up, so we can use that.
It's about that time.
- All right, go for it.
- Okay.
Welcome to SCRATCH,
an electronic transcendence group.
Head straight if you wish to join us.
Head over that way to request
more detailed information about SCRATCH.
So, I guess I can't copy
my spirit immediately.
Guess I have no choice.
Joining us?
Please, input your personal data.
Data, data. Fake data!
Blood, muscle, and bone...
when those are lost, humans face death.
What lies beyond that?
Heaven? Hell? Reincarnation?
Such things cannot possibly exist.
Those are mere excuses.
What's wrong?
What is this?
None of the previous paths to salvation
had such a clear vision as this.
Awaken your spirit!
Now, be rid of that filthy body!
High frequency?
Yeah. I'm not exactly sure,
but it has some contraption
that paralyzes the sympathetic nerves.
In seconds, everything before my eyes
went blank and I passed out.
If Ein didn't realize it and bite me,
I would have been...
A member of SCRATCH.
Anyway, we need to devise
a countermeasure to--
- Well, I'll try becoming a member now.
- Hey, Spike!
Hey!
I'm sure dogs have brain waves, too.
Ed wanna wear it, too!
If you become a member,
who's going to look Londes up?
Do it.
Welcome to SCRATCH,
an electronic transcendence gr--
Good going, Ed!
This is...
Can this really be?
A guy named Londes never existed.
His past, all the records,
they were all counterfeit.
And all the controls lead back to here...
Alles Valley Hospice.
Ed, help me.
Papa.
- Not yet!
- Papa!
Nobody here would want visitors.
And you need an appointment
to see someone.
Or did you come here for an inheritance?
Nothing of the sort!
Actually,
this girl's twin brother is here.
Papa!
Girl? Is she really a girl?
Actually... it's a long story.
I'm just having her sleep.
Of course, the other bounty hunters
all slept to death.
We finally tracked the long-lost brother
to be here.
Papa!
It was a shock to my daughter.
She has been insane ever since.
I thought about having
her meet her brother just once.
- You can go.
- I can't thank you enough.
Why do you kill off your members?
What's your purpose?
I am not forcing anything.
They are merely practicing a faith
that they've decided to believe in.
Why do you think people believe in God?
It's because they want to.
It's not easy living in this rotten world.
There is nothing certain
while living on in this world.
Do you get it?
God didn't create humans.
Humans created God.
He's it?
I'm sick of this little act.
What's wrong? Come on out.
An illusion isn't enough for me.
That is correct.
A man named Londes
does not exist in this world.
He is merely an imaginary character
I created.
A mere illusion created by scanning lines.
Is this a brain wave controller
like Brain Dream?
Hey, Ed.
Can you cut the connection between
the controller and the network?
Yeah.
But don't turn off
the life-support system.
Do you know what the greatest and worst
invention that humans ever made was?
Television.
Television controls people
using information
and steals their sense of reality.
Yes, now television itself is a religion.
TV has created people
that are easily fooled
by such an idiotic fantasy.
Just like a little kid.
What?
You are the one who can't tell...
fantasy from reality, Londes.
If you want to dream, dream alone.
W--? What do you know?!
What do you think you know about me?
What--? What are you doing?!
Stop!
Help! You can't do that!
Stop! Shit.
Stop it!
Stop it!!
Don't turn it off!
What--? What did I do?!
No. This is unfair.
Why am I the only one?
Shit.
Everyone... should have had...
the same... body... as me.
No. I...
I don't want to disappear!
I don't want to disappear.
Ronny Spangen. Previously a hacker.
A boy who became a vegetable two years ago
from a medical accident.
No, you are no longer a boy.
You're a damn good con-artist.
Oh, long time no see.
Where am I?
It was all a kid's dream.
Yeah, all he could do was dream.
This time, have sweet dreams.
Our souls that God has given us,
our spirit.
Is not our body an existence
all too small and weak for our spirits...
which found a way to swim through
the vast network
and live in the infinity of space?
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
Next episode: "Hard Luck Woman."