A sudden incident has befallen me,
Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
New introductions guided by magic...
Are they coincidence, or destiny?
Right now, I'm not sure which.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
The Lost Logia are in this area?
The form is a blue gem.
Normally called a Jewel Seed.
Right.
I'll have them in my hands in no time.
Episode 4:
A Rival?! Another Magical Girll
Here, Yuuno, over here!
Good job! Yuuno, you're so smart!
Still not ready, Nanoha?
Sorry! Just a bit longer...
Going out somewhere today?
Yeah, to the Tsukimuras' house.
Apparently, Nanoha got
an invitation from Suzuka.
Oh, I see.
And you, Kyo, are going
to go see Shinobu.
Well, my main purpose
is to chaperone Nanoha.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Then let's go.
We're barely going to
catch the bus as it is.
Okay.
Yuuno, over here!
Okay, see you later!
We're on our way!
Today, we're planning a tea party
at Suzuka's house.
I'm going to spend my day off
with Arisa and Suzuka.
And my brother is going to go see
Suzuka's older sister Shinobu.
No, it's nothing...
I see.
Welcome, Mr. Kyouya, Miss Nanoha.
Yeah. Thanks for the invitation.
Hello!
This is Noel, the head maid
of the Tsukimura family.
She doesn't talk much, but
she's so beautiful and so cool!
Please, this way.
Nanoha, Kyouya!
Suzuka!
Nanoha, welcome!
This is Falin.
She's Suzuka's personal maid.
She's a very bright and kind lady!
Welcome, Kyouya.
Yeah.
My brother and Shinobu have been
classmates since high school,
and they really get along nowadays.
Shall I go prepare the tea?
What would you like?
I'll leave it up to you.
And for you, Miss Nanoha?
I'll leave it up to you too.
As you wish. Falin?
Yes, roger, sister.
Then Kyouya and I
will be in my room.
Right, I will bring it over there.
Morning!
Yeah! Morning!
Suzuka's sister and Nanoha's brother
are as lovey-dovey as ever!
Yes.
My sister has seemed very happy
ever since she got to know Kyouya.
I wonder if it's the same
for my brother?
But compared to the past,
I think he's gotten a bit nicer.
I think he laughs a lot more now.
Oh, yeah, thanks for
inviting me today.
Not at all. Thank you
for coming today.
You seem to be
cheerful enough today.
Nanoha, you haven't been
too cheerful lately.
If there is something
that is worrying you,
we'd like you to tell us.
At least, that's what the
two of us were saying.
Suzuka... Arisa...
Yuuno!
Ein, stop that!
Here, sorry to keep you waiting!
Strawberry milk tea and
cream cheese cookies!
Falin, look out!
Safe!
Suzuka, Nanoha, I'm so sorry!
There she goes again.
That girl is so troublesome.
Your house is cat heaven,
just like always, Suzuka.
But the kittens are really cute!
Yes...
There are a couple of them
that found new parents,
so I have to say goodbye to them.
I see. That's a bit lonely.
But I'm happy that
the kittens will grow up.
I guess so.
Nanoha!
Yeah. It's really close by!
What should we do?
Well...
I gotit!
Yuuno?!
Oh, my... Is something
wrong with Yuuno?
Yeah, I think he found something.
I'll go look for him!
Would you like us to help?
I'm fine. I'll be right back,
so wait here!
It's been executed?!
People will see us here.
I have to create a barrier!
A barrier?
A space like when we first met!
It slightly shifts the flow of time
between the space where the magic
takes effect and normal space.
I'm pretty good at that magic.
I can't cut out too large of a space,
but if it's this house
and its surroundings,
I can manage.
That's...
Most likely, that kitten's wish to
grow has been properly granted.
I see...
But we have to turn it back
to what it was before,
or it will be dangerous.
Right.
After all, Suzuka would be
troubled if it stayed that size.
It doesn't seem like
it's going to attack us,
so I guess I should hurry and seal it.
Then, Raging Heart!
Bardiche, attack with
the Photon Lancer.
Photon Lancer, Full Auto Fire.
Magical light?!
No way...
Raging Heart, please!
Stand by ready. Set up.
Flier Fin.
Wide Area Protection.
A magic-user?
She's not surprised by much now.
Maybe there's nothing more
that I can teach Nanoha.
A similar type of magic-user.
One that searches for the Lost Logia...
No doubt about it.
She's from the same world as me.
And she knows the truth
about the Jewel Seeds!
The same type of intelligent
device as Bardiche...
Bardiche?
Lost Logia, Jewel Seeds.
Scythe Form, set up.
I apologize, but I'm taking it with me.
Evasion.
Flier Fin.
Arc Saber.
Protection.
Nanoha!
Why?
Why, so suddenly...
Even if I answered, it would
likely be meaningless.
Device Mode.
Shooting Mode.
Divine Buster, stand by.
Photon Lancer, get set.
I'm sure she's my age.
Pretty eyes, and pretty hair...
But this girl...
I'm sorry.
Fire.
Nanoha!
Sealing Form, set up.
Capture.
Order?
Lost Logia, Jewel Seed, Serial 14...
Seal.
Yes, sir.
Sealing.
Captured.
When I woke up again, the sky
had changed color to that of dusk.
Yuuno had called for my brother
and everyone else.
And I told a small lie,
that I tripped and passed out
while searching for Yuuno.
I made everyone worry so much.
My heart was full of apologies.
That staff, that armor,
how she used magic...
Most likely...
No, I'm positive that she lives
in the same world as I do.
Yeah.
If I'm going to collect
more Jewel Seeds...
I wonder if I'm going
to run into her again?
For some strange reason,
I wasn't scared at all.
But it made me feel kind of sad.
I had very complicated feelings.
There was a bit of interference,
but I was all right.
Jewel Seed, Serial 14.
I wonder if she has a few of them?
It's all right. I won't lose my way.
Wait for me, Mother.
I'll be home soon.
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of
cellophane and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying
inside a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining on
the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something I
can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Students and working people alike,
at times they just need
a break to relax.
And so we're here at the local
resort, Uminari Hot Springs!
Just when we're relaxing,
who's getting in our way?!
And what is the
objective and intentions
of that mysterious
magical girl in black?!
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 5: This is a Town of Hot Water,
Uminari Hot Springs!
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 5: This is a Town of Hot Water,
Uminari Hot Springs!
Episode 5: This is a Town of Hot
Water, Uminari Hot Springs!
Lyrical, magical, I'll do my best!