The two of us are decidedly incompatible.
Because we are the light and the shadow born from Princess Ann!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Ace and Regina!
The Truth Behind Their Births!
Cure Ace and Regina are light and shadow?
And they were born from the princess?
How could this be?
Sorry, you won't win by making me die of laughter.
You know,
every look I get of you makes my stomach turn!
Because you look upon yourself.
Myself?
If you have the courage to learn the truth,
I shall reveal to you our destiny!
The Eternal Golden Crown...
Well?
Y-You just want me to see it?
Then hand it over!
Regina!
What happened?
She is witnessing the memories of the kingdom recorded within the Golden Crown.
Memories of the kingdom?
And within that lies...
the truth behind you two!
Cure Ace!
Show us too!
I ask as well.
Very well.
Close your eyes and connect your hearts with mine.
We shall begin.
We're in...
Trump Kingdom when it was at peace.
Hey, he's...
Trump Kingdom's king!
Then that means...
the baby he's holding is...
Princess Ann.
Princess...
On the very day Princess Ann came into this world,
her mother left it.
Doctor...
Marie Ange, my daughter,
live in your mother's stead.
You are as radiant as the very sun that bestows upon us hopes and dreams.
Ann, wrapped in the King's deep love, was quick to mature.
Ann, your skills have improved yet again.
I've still much to learn, Father!
But you'll need to put that effort into more ladylike pursuits soon enough, no?
But Father,
a proper lady never neglects her swordsmanship!
She lived her days in happiness.
However...
Princess Ann suddenly collapsed due to a mysterious illness.
There must be something that can be done!
This is all modern medicine can do...
Am I to simply watch as the flame of Ann's life extinguishes?!
Dear God,
did claiming my wife not satisfy you?!
Must you steal my daughter as well?!
I shall not allow it!
There is... one way.
What?
The Eternal Golden Crown.
The circlet of gold imbued with boundless wisdom!
If we had its power...
I understand.
However...
That circlet of gold seals away the darkness that the legendary Precure warriors defeated.
Should we use it,
that darkness may be unleashed!
It pains me to say this, my king,
but if nothing is done, the princess...
If I use this,
Ann will be saved...
But still...
if that darkness were to be unleashed once more, what would become of the people?
Every peaceful citizen of Trump Kingdom...
But... But I must!
There is no other way!
Raise her...
into a woman as radiant as the very sun that bestows upon us hopes and dreams...
A deal with a devil to save her life would bring Ann no joy!
But if nothing is done...
What must I do?
I... I...
I see.
Ann's death would mean no less than the end of the world as I know it.
If I can at least save Ann,
then it matters not what becomes of everything else!
Don't cry, Makopi.
Anyone would struggle to choose between their family and the world.
Mana's right.
It's a question with no easy answer.
With the wisdom gained from the Golden Crown, Ann was cured.
But the true tragedy had yet to begin...
Oh, Ann! You've awoken!
Father...
I heard...
the dark heartbeat.
That selfish, wicked desire...
Who goes there?
You committed taboo to save your beloved daughter,
leading the world to destruction!
Truly the ultimate in selfishness!
You shall make for a fitting vessel!
Father!
My king!
My goodness!
No way!
The king...
Yes.
The king's soul was overtaken with Egogy...
transforming him into King Selfish.
You've awakened at last, King Selfish.
Finally our time to shine.
Now, what are your orders?
Paint this world black with Egogy!
Every Precure defending the kingdom was defeated by the Selfish Army's ferocious attack save for Cure Sword.
Why, Father?
This country is brimming with love!
Why would you destroy it?
This world needs no love.
The cancer known as love brings only pain!
That is not true!
It was your love that saved my life, Father!
My name... is King Selfish!
I shall destroy everything in the world!
Father...
Please, Miracle Dragon Glaive...
The battle ended with Princess Ann turning King Selfish to stone and fleeing into the mirror.
But...
Escape, Cure Sword!
Alone, if you must!
Princess!
That's enough hide-and-seek,
Princess.
A question, though.
Why did you leave King Selfish alive?
With the power of one of the Three Sacred Treasures, the Miracle Dragon Glaive,
you could have blown him to smithereens.
So, why didn't you?
I see. You let him live 'cause he's your dear old dad.
Well, aren't you selfish!
The royal family's supposed to protect its citizens,
yet you threw them under the bus to save your flesh and blood.
Thicker than water, as they say...
You're the most sickeningly, stupendously selfish one of all!
No!
If I do nothing, I'll become a Selfish...
I'll make it painless.
Wha?!
What?!
The love my father gave me...
The love to protect the smiles of my people...
Selfishness and love are two sides of the same coin.
I cannot say which is more important...
I entrust that answer and the fate of the world...
to the battle between those who will be born from these two psyches.
And so I leave you to bear a cruel fate.
Forgive my cowardice...
Fool!
Princess!
Those were...
The two halves of the princess's psyche!
One made its way to King Selfish to become Regina.
The other gave birth to me, Madoka Aguri.
And without her psyche, the princess's body became an egg and entered the human world.
And that egg was...
Ai?
So, you girls saw the truth behind Ann and the kingdom.
I can't believe it...
Regina and Aguri used to be the same person!
To think that Princess Ann met such an unfortunate fate...
But everything makes sense now.
It explains why Regina wanted the Royal Crystals...
And why Regina doesn't have any memories of her dad.
And most importantly...
her use of the Golden Crown proves she's of Princess Ann's flesh and blood.
Does this mean we can't bring the princess back?
Wait!
If we can merge her light and her shadow, we could bring the princess back!
There's no way for the princess to return to her previous form...
It's a decision she came to through the strength of her heart.
Thank you, Aguri.
You told us the truth,
so now we finally understand how you feel and why you wanted to end this.
Mana...
But knowing the truth means even more that violence isn't the answer!
There has to be a way to resolve this!
We can all find it together!
Regina, you can help us, too!
Regina?
Mana, I'm happy...
My daddy tried to save me even if the entire world paid the price...
Regina's eyes changed!
Regina!
Have any of you ever been loved so much?
Have you been loved more than the world or the universe itself?
Only I have...
I can't turn my back on Daddy after that!
I'll fight for Daddy until the bitter end!
You can't, Regina!
Daddy?
He's finally awakened!
I'm coming, Daddy!
Regina!
It seems we've no choice left but to defeat Regina and King Selfish.
Aguri...
I bear the cross of the royal family.
And as long as Regina and King Selfish yet live,
Trump Kingdom will never recover.
You're sure you won't regret it?
I understand your desire to fulfill the princess's goal all too well.
But...
won't you be hurt in the end?
Makoto...
Look out!
Stop it, Regina!
I won't, Mana!
My kingdom needs only Regina and me!
Begone!
Now, let's eliminate humanity and create a world for just the two of us.
Okay!
I'll make all your wishes come true, Daddy!
Girls, are you all right?
Yeah...
Somehow!
King Selfish...
Entered the human world!
For now, we have to stop those two.
I don't have all the answers now,
so all we can do is hit 'em with all the love we've got!
That's Mana's kind of plan.
Though I don't think it's a bad one.
Aguri.
Understood.
Let us go!
What's that?
We'll protect this world!
Girls, let's go!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Regina, King Selfish,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Hey, King Selfish!
Could you listen to us for a bit?
Dokidoki Precure:
Cure Heart's Determination!
A Promise to Protect!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!