What?
So sleepy...
Sheesh.
You tossed your skirt in the laundry basket with a tissue still in its pocket, didn't you?
It was a disaster.
Also, make sure that you separate your clothes based on their colors. The dark colored ones go in the orange basket-
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop nitpicking on every little thing!
Guys are supposed to go out with a ba-
We want a home run!
Yay, yay, yay!
Hit one now! Yay!
We want a home run!
Yay, yay, yay!
Don't worry about it!
All right!
And now... it's Minori-time.
Fight, captain!
My, my, thanks for cheering me on!
Kushieda...
Give me your best shot!
That refreshing smile...
Kushieda... That sparkling sweat...
First base! Yay!
Second base! Yay!
Turning at the third base, and we have a home run!
That off-pitch singing...
Home in!
Oh, Kushieda... You're wonderful again today...
Stop it with that lewd look, you disgusting dog.
Kushieda, about the weekend's co-ed practice...
Oh hey, Kitamura-kun. I was about to-
Hey, are you listening to me, you stupid dog?!
Stop doing that-
Wait!
Even the Go Home Club is getting their morning run good and proper.
Taiga, stop-!
Take that!
Your health comes first, after all.
pure purepara-to tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre-Preparation. Even though I'm not strong at all.
pure purepare-do itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre-Pre parade. Some day I will catch you.
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
If you let your guard down, there'll be a tickling attack. Prepare yourself.
chiisai kedo hasamuno mijinnko mitai na anata
You're small, but fit in, you who are as small as a water flea.
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to   (purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
What we wanted was a plastic heart.   (Plus! Plus! But then, minus!)
demo sore ja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono kachi
But there were those that noticed it was too boring!
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing.
tanjunmeikai fukuzatsukaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, complicated and mysterious.
do- de mo ii koto bakkari ki ni shitari suruno
If you keep worrying about useless things,
donna kanji? sonna kanji!
how will it feel? It'll feel like that!
onkoutokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You who are gentle and sincere, yet eccentric,
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
put up a fight by pretending like you're tough with your whole being.
sunao na dokidoki shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
The impact from being honestly excited will send you dizzy spells.
kizuichauno   (kizuikechauno)
You hurt someone   (You've been hurt)
junjou purepara-to
A naive preparation.
atama no naka wa   (itsumo hitori no)
In your head   (Always on your own)
junjou purepare-do
A naive pre-parade.
Your Song
A cellphone decoration? You're really dexterous with your fingers.
You could say that. I might not look it, but I'm rather crafty with my hands.
What's Kushieda doing?
All right, one down!
Next up is...
What's up with that smothered voice?
Um, y-you see...
Hey, why don't I decorate yours too, Takasu-kun?
You see, I'm a part-time cellphone decorator.
D-Decorator?
I'll spell out "Ryuuji" with purple Swarovski stones on yours.
Ryuuji
She'd do that for me...?
No, I-I'm all rig...
Kushieda.
Please decorate ours, too.
I see, more orders!
On this paper, write down your name, the color you want, and a small drawing.
To give it a lovely feeling, I'll go with a large heart and the color pink.
That's lovely!
So she's a part-time cellphone decorator...
The sparkling Kushieda and her sparkling
decorations. What a wonderful combination.
Hey, Yacchan's not eating here since she's at the hostess club, right? Then can I have her side dish...
And she said "Ryuuji." She remembered my first name...
That's because I address you like that all the time.
But anyway, about Yacchan's side dish...
Oh man, I talked with her so much...
Taiga, was I able to talk normally with...
...her?
Listen when people are talking to you!
And no, you sounded really shady!
What about dinner, is it ready yet?
That hurt, you know! It's almost done.
Today, we're having a rice bowl dish, so as long as we have rice we'll be ok-
What the?!
What's wrong?
The rice cooker's broken.
Welcome and good evening!
What should I get?
Going all the way out to a family restaurant...
We didn't have any rice, but there was bread.
Bay while you can, mongrel.
Soon, you'll be kneeling your head in gratitude.
And here you go, two servings!
Huh? But we haven't ordered anyth-
What?!
Keep this a secret. An extra large serving of ice cream, the Taiga Special!
Hide it from the other customers while you eat it, okay?
Thanks for making it every time, Minorin.
"Every time"?
Takasu-kun doesn't like sweet things?
Then how about some french fries?
I'll give you a huge serving! A huge  serving!
No, I'm-
Minorin also works part time at places like
convenience stores and karaoke clubs, right?
Yeah! And last week, I added a shabu-shabu place to the list!
That many?!
And I'm still saving time for other things!
Being the girls' softball club's captain, I can't possibly skip club activities, after all.
Are you working so hard because you want something in particular?
Nah, I've just got the time so I gotta labor.
"Labor"?
Yes, the "Mysterious Files of Labor"!
The kind of labor that revives you!
But, wow, you two sure are close now.
Waitress, some cold water, please.
Well, enjoy your time here.
I'm pretty sure I've lost some eyesight because you've been poking my eyes all day.
You pitiful mongrel, drooling while checking out Minorin's uniform...
I was just thinking...
...that her smile was so bright...
Sp-Spare my eyes!
If I continue, my fingers will be contaminated.
Damnit...
But why is she juggling all those jobs?
She called it the "Mysterious Files of Labor", didn't she?
Could it be possible that she has a reason for earning all that money?
Something related to her home? Maybe she's helping her sick mom?
She called it laboring.
But even so...
You should stop assuming things.
Huh?
"I'm the only one who truly understands her!"
It'll only add on to your filth level.
Ew, how gross! Keep your distance from me, you're so disgusting!
Hey, Taiga! What's with your tone, you're so cold!
Stay away from me! Since when have I not  been cold towards you?
Now that you mention it...
Hello, Inko-chan! Sorry to make you wait, it's dinner time!
I'll give you a huge serving! A huge  serving!
-nko.
Oh, today you'll be able to say it?!
-nko, -oop!
Poop!
Man, the mornings during holidays are really refreshing!
We've gone out for breakfast.
There's sandwiches in the fridge.
Ryuu
Right, Taiga?
I shouldn't have told you...
Did you say something?
Not bothering to prepare breakfast in order to see Minorin at the family restaurant...
It can't be helped, the rice cooker is still broken.
Then why don't we go to an electrical appliance store first?
You even said you hate bread.
I don't mind eating bread for breakfast.
Why are you so cheerful? Those clothes don't look good on you.
I forgot something at home-
What an annoying idiot.
I beg you, let go of me!
What you wear won't make a difference!
Hey, you there!
Aren't you Mirano-chan's son?
Oh, old man Inage?
"Mirano"?
Yeah, Yasuko's hostess name.
Mirano-chan
Vaisravana's
Heaven
Hi! Go out the station's north exit, it's 200 meters straight ahead!
I'm Vaisravana's Heaven's Mirano-chan!
How old do I look? Twenty-three?
Bingo!
This is a fortunate morning!
And now to grab a feel of Mirano-chan's DNA!
Nice and firm, being young must be nice!
Let's go.
Somehow, this old guy's pissing me off.
Hold it right there, you two! If you haven't eaten breakfast yet,
I recommend the docosahexaenoic acid and the calcium-filled taste of this Gyonisa!
Okay.
Huh?
Kushieda?
Minorin?
INAGE LIQUOR STORE
Here, carry this!
W-Why?
Another!
And some more!
It would be better if I-
No, it's okay. Sit down and relax with some tea. You're Mirano-chan's son, after all.
Why do I have to do this?
I ask her for some help, but only during holidays.
Kushieda, you better work hard!
Understood!
We've run out of workers these days, now that we're so busy.
You ran out of workers...?
Oh yeah, do you want to work here too, young lady? Being friends with Kushieda and all...
I'll pay you well!
Yes!
I'll work!
Along with her.
I can't keep this up!
Hey, don't cause a ruckus. It'll give Kushieda trouble.
Then help out a little!
Little girl, I need you to go do the deliveries!
Three of those beer cases.
With pleasure!
And that's it!
Be careful.
What's wrong, Taiga?
You...
You can't ride a bike?
Shut up!
So what if I can't ride a bike?! I'll just have to transport it like this!
That's wrong! You're doing it wrong!
You're on fire, Taiga!
She's ridiculous.
Well, if she just pushes the bike, she'll be all right.
Oh, right, I was going to restock the shochu.
I'll-
I'll help, too.
I'd feel bad if I wasn't doing anything.
Then I'll be counting on you.
Y-Yeah!
Where's the potato shochu?
It's really hard to see in this darkness.
This place isn't used that often.
They don't open up this place more than once a week or so.
If we got locked in here, it'd be horrible.
It would feel almost like we were stranded or something!
That little runt, leaving it open like that.
Hey! There are still people inside!
S.O.S.! S.O.S.!
Calm down, Takasu-kun!
Kushieda?
It's for these times that we have school songs!
Huh?
School songs?
This is dumb.
There's no reason for me to make an effort.
I really can't keep this up.
Keep what up?
K-Kitamura-kun! W-Why are you h-h-here?
Self-training.
By the way, is that your bike?
Um, yeah... something like that.
You're capable of riding a bike now?
That's remarkable progress.
Um, putting aside whether I can ride a bike or not...
How did you know that I didn't know how to ride a bike?
That's because I was closely observing you last year.
Bikes are great. The world opens up before you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
He was observing me last year...?
Damnit!
Opening up a world in which
Kitamura-kun's not watching me...
...is meaningless!
Two, thr-
Aren't you lat- What happened, you look awful.
Nothing much. Where are the others?
Oh, right, where has that Kushieda run off to?
Not minding Ryuuji-kun...
That mongrel, slacking off in comfort while I'm out working!
What're you saying?
Anyway, the next delivery's three blocks away-
Ryuuji, what the hell are you up to?!
♪ The bridge that leads to the future ♫
♫ That bridge is a chopstick, a chopstick ♪
My throat's all dry.
Nobody noticed us even though we raised our voices...
At around this time, the old guy's obsessing over horse racing.
Right...
It's gotten a bit cold.
I'll lend you my coat, the-
Okay, let's warm up!
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
Who's scared? Aren't you the pitcher?
He's scared! Hey!
The pitcher is scared! Hey, hey, hey!
Wait, you're actually scared?
Your hand's trembling.
You've got it all wrong, I'm trembling from excitement!
Here I go, you'd better be ready!
Strike!
Changeover.
We swap places now.
Oh, okay.
You see, there's no point being afraid.
That's why...
I only need to beat up my weakness!
Kushieda...
Could it be...
Could it be possible?
Hey, Takasu-kun. Can't we get out through that window?
Where is he?! Where is he?! Where is he?! Where is he?! Where is he?! Where is he?!
WHERE IS HE?!
Look, Takasu-kun.
So you're in there...!
There might be more to Kushieda's cheerfulness than her simply being bright and energetic.
Watch out!
I'm sorry, Kushieda! Are you oka-
Whoa, your nose is bleeding!
Oh, it'll be okay somewhy!
Somewhy?
A nosebleed is the perspiration of your heart.
That aside, we're almost there!
Keep stacking them boxes, Takasu!
Y-Yes, sir!
I see, she was beating up her weakness, wasn't she?
We're going to get out of here!
Yeah, of course! Fight!
Huh?
When I say fight, you say...?
C-Chug one?
Yeah yeah, that's it!
Fight!
C-Chug one!
Now that I think about it,
she's always been gleaming with cheerfulness.
Even when I had just met her too.
Fight!
Even now...
Chug one!
She's gleaming with joy!
FOUND YOU!
Taiga, how did you get in here?!
How? I used the ladder.
Yay! We can get outside now, Takasu-kun!
But...
Thanks, Taiga!
This is truly the ladder to the future!
Um, Minorin...
You get up too, Takasu-kun!
O-Okay.
Like I've been trying to say!
The ladder fell down when I landed on Ryuuji's face...
vanilla salt de vanilla...
A salty vanilla... Vanilla...
amai dakenara salt kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet.
dame yo ima motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
No! I expose myself since I want you to understand me more and more.
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience.
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a bit different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for.
shiro to iwaretara kuro datte icchau
When you tell me white I reply with black.
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself.
suki to iwaretara daikirai datte
When you tell me that you love me, I shout I hate you!
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, yet what am I saying?
amai vanilla ni salt kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla.
Next Episode Preview
The Face Back Then
Sealed deep within my heart.
Our precious memory that we couldn't tell anyone about.
Nope, I've told Takasu.
Ki-ta-mu-!