I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
VT, your shift over?
Yeah, finally. How about you?
Just on my way to Europa.
That'll make you some bucks.
Nothing like what you've been pulling in.
I heard you did a round trip from
here to Venus in four days or so.
- It was three days.
- See what I mean?
Anyway, take it easy now.
You too.
Oh, I almost forgot...
Hey, VT!
So you're still trying, huh?
Yeah, of course! And I'm gonna keep
on trying till I get my money back!
Hey, knock yourself out.
Okay. You've only got one shot,
and you get no clues.
All right. VT, I say your name is...
Val Tomiana.
- Nice try.
- Oh no!
This is a bad sign...
You be careful now, Otto.
You know that cross-eyed guy they put
an 8 million reward on the other day?
Guess who got him. Me!
The other day...
That was ten years ago,
you old coot! Jeez.
What do you know, you young turks.
Why, I taught Terpsichore
everything he ever knew.
- The Terpsichore, the bounty hunter?
- That's right.
Those with a price on their heads
quivered in fear at the sound of his name.
You're blowing smoke, old man.
Oh hi, Zeros. Hey, VT.
- What's it gonna be? The usual?
- Yeah.
What's with all the muscle boys?
This place is usually empty.
There's something coming down.
A bounty head named Decker is supposed
to show up here later, and word got out.
These guys are all bounty hunters.
No wonder it's such a circus.
Looks like punks on parade in here.
You said exclusive information.
No, the place is crawling
with bounty hunters.
They all know about Decker.
And I've got a hangover
the size of Neptune.
We don't even know
what the guy looks like.
All we know is he's got
a tattoo shaped like a dragon.
And Faye?
Yeah, right, like she's gonna
find him in that place.
Welcome to Woody's,
the family fun place!
If you're celebrating
a birthday today,
you can have your picture taken free
with Mackey and Mannie Muskrat!
That's right, moms and dads!
Just ask your server.
Hi.
What do you want, babe?
You looking for some action?
Well, you might say that.
A certain kind of action.
I'm all yours.
Put your hands up,
Decker my friend.
Don't be so rough!
Just get the hell over here.
I'm working right now, please!
- We just wanna be friends, sweetie.
- Good friends.
- P-Please, stop it!
- I'll show you how to have some fun.
- That's the way!
- Come here!
Stop, please! Someone, help!
Who the hell are you?
VT!
Since when is it a
bounty hunter's job
to chase after a woman's butt
instead of chasing after money?
Sorry, it's not personal.
This is my job.
- What'd I do wrong?
- It's no use playing innocent.
I can see the edge
of your dragon tattoo.
You got the wrong guy!
Hey, you, with the glasses.
Put a call in to the police.
Let them know I caught Decker.
No, wait, stop, don't!
What the hell is that?
I got a thing for eels...
Next time, keep it covered!
You're dead!
Cut him up, boys.
VT!
I'm tired of you, blondie!
W-Where'd you come from?!
You spilled my egg.
I needed that egg.
Aw, shit! Come on, boys,
let's get this guy too!
There you are!
Shit, I'll make you pay for that.
Just kidding.
Just forget about us.
My 12 million... all gone...
Talk about the bottom
of the food chain...
Bounty hunters must be
the lowest form of life there is.
- You think so?
- I know so.
Human beings are just
a price tag to them.
They live by gambling
on other people's lives.
Yeah, well, that may be.
So have a seat.
The drinks are on me.
Don't whine.
Bean sprouts are very healthy.
They're good for you.
Anyway, that's all there is.
Gimme a break here,
would you, please?
That must be him!
Oh, Faye, it's you. That was quick.
What?!
Oh, man, that's gross.
It's called a prairie oyster.
Good for hangovers.
You're the second person I've known
who actually drinks those awful things.
And who's the first?
It was my husband.
VT!
- We're bound to get it now.
- All cash.
One try for all three of you guys?
- That's right.
- All right, suit yourself.
Here it is! Let's go!
VT, I think your name is--
Adrienne. That's just gotta be it, right?
But Adrienne doesn't start with a V.
Ah, you see, we should've
stuck with Lutetia!
Yeah...
So tell me, do I get that little mountain
of cash if I can guess your name?
Yeah. I don't remember who
started it, but it just kept piling up.
And here I am now sitting
on a fat stack, you know?
Well, I'll give it a try.
Spike, it's me.
Faye just missed Decker.
Go after him, quick.
Spike!
- Get lost.
- Eh?
Lying, lowlife bounty hunter.
I'm not paying for your drink.
Aww... Wait, Spike!
Oh my...
Gah! My ship!
Yeah, they wrecked it,
those guys you beat up.
They're called the something brothers.
You were watching?
Uh-huh.
So Muriel, why didn't
you tell me about it?
But I did tell you.
I told you just now.
What do you want?
You headed for home now, VT?
That's right. Zeros, come on!
What are you still doing here?
Hitchhiking.
Those stooges smashed up my starship.
You're just a messed-up loser, Spike.
And a lowlife bounty hunter scumbag.
Don't forget that.
Don't push your luck!
Come on, let's go.
Mind if I take another
friend of mine along?
How many times do I have to
tell you the same thing?!
Short, bald, with glasses,
and Sarasvati--
Huh? What are you saying?
I just said it!
Ooh! Can you please turn
down that repulsive music?
I don't think so.
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Huh?
And it's not repulsive,
it's very soothing.
It's called heavy metal, by the way.
I can't believe they wrecked
both ships on the same day.
And who do they think's
gonna repair these things?
Now what the hell am I supposed to do
with those little scraps of information?
How many bald guys with glasses
do you think there are in this galaxy?
I said bald, short, with glasses,
and driving a tacky truck with
Sarasvati painted on the side!
- Yeah?
- VT, is that you?
Hey, Otto, what's up?
- I got into a hit-and-run.
- Huh?
Guy cuts into line at the gate,
rams me, and then jets off!
Shit, I gotta make him
pay for repairs at least!
So tell me if you see the weasel.
So how do I spot him?
Let me think...
Yeah, there was this giant Asian
goddess painted on his ship.
Wait a minute,
it wasn't Sarasvati, was it?
Yeah, yeah, that's what it said.
How'd you know, anyway?
Zeros?
Breaker 1-9, Breaker 1-9,
to all truckers on the asteroids.
This is Heavy Metal Queen.
Hey, guys, if you see a truck
with Sarasvati painted on it,
gimme a ring. Thanks, guys.
Hey, VT, Love Machine
over here at sector 12.
What's up with this call,
did some dude skip out on you?
Something like that.
I haven't seen the guy, but you
know I'll be out looking for him.
Thanks for the help.
Yeah, this is Sneaky Snake.
- Did you say a painting of a clown?
- No.
This is Spider Mike,
Black Panther of Jupiter, VT.
I've never met you, but I hear a lotta
wild stories about the Heavy Metal Queen.
I guess that's a compliment.
So what do you know?
Got a positive ID on your
target about ten minutes ago.
It wasn't too far from
the old Linus Mines.
Hope that helps.
Thanks a bunch.
I owe you one, guy.
Great. One more part to be replaced.
He's mine!
Trying to outmaneuver me, pal?
Nice try, scumbag!
This is VT calling. Let me talk to
that lowlife scum bounty hunter.
The Linus Mines? That's crazy!
- Stay away!
- Huh? What'd you say?
Just stay away from Decker!
He's hauling high explosives!
Hello?
Hey, hold on!
I have first dibs on Decker! Wait!
It's so ugly...
and parts of it are still broken!
Too bad it wasn't your
mouth that was broken.
I heard that.
Hey, Jet, I'm going out!
Hold on, I didn't even get
the artillery working yet!
That was a big mistake!
What's all this?
Isn't this a little risky?
Watch your back!
There goes my 12 million.
VT, you there?
If you're alive, say something!
I'm okay. Takes more than
that to get rid of me.
We gotta get outta here!
Decker was selling enhanced nitro,
and it's all destabilized now.
His ship is packed with it.
The whole thing? That's enough nitro
to blow this place to shreds!
It gets worse. This place
is an old mining satellite,
and the reactors are breaking up!
We've gotta find a way outta this mess.
How much further to the exit chutes?
Not far. Angle 20 degrees left.
There, it's up ahead.
It's blocked... Behind you, Faye!
In front!
You shooting a pop gun?
You'll never blast through like that.
Well, excuse me! I have no artillery!
All I have are these pincers!
All right, come on!
There must be a way to get out!
'Course there is.
And it's just waiting for us,
packed inside that freighter.
I don't like this.
It's a delicate operation,
and I'm not really the delicate type.
All right, then don't be so delicate.
Let's just go for it!
All right, now grab one.
Easy for you to say, Mr. Perfect.
Uh, there's gas coming out...
- Probably stabilizers.
- Which means?
- It's touch-sensitive.
- What?!
Come on, girl,
what's the worst that can happen?
- Screw up, and we all die.
- That's very comforting.
Okay, I've got one.
Now, what do I do with it?
I'm programming this pod to shoot toward
the exit and self-explode in 40 seconds.
So get that nitro in here ASAP.
You don't have a lot of time, Faye.
What are you gonna do?
My floating act.
Zeros, get outta the way!
We've gotta let him in!
Bingo!
It's all clear!
I need a new gig.
Zeros...
Thanks for the help...
Victoria Terpsichore.
And give your husband my thanks, too.
I figured out who you
were because of this.
Of course, everyone's heard about him.
The legendary bounty hunter, Terpsichore.
And wife.
I won't be able to give him
your thanks for a while.
I'm afraid he's doing all his bounty
hunting up in heaven these days.
I see.
The rest is for your husband.
I'm sure that he's got
a hangover up there.
Treat him to a prairie oyster on me.
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
Once in a while,
I do the preview myself.
I'm Jet Black, 36 years old.
I'm often told I don't look 36.
But you shouldn't judge people
based on appearances.
Or how much hair they have.
Things are never
what they seem to be.
That's how the next episode is, too.
It's a story that seems
very unlike Bebop.
Next episode:
"Waltz for Venus."
Stuff like this is good
once in a while, huh?