[IZUMI] To think that you saw it
and managed to survive...
I doubt you even know
how impressive that is.
I... no.
[IZUMI]
Regardless...
I can't accept the
decision you made.
You're expelled.
[AL] But, teacher!
- [ED] Al.
- [AL] But, teacher!
[IZUMI] The trains are
still running... get on one.
Thank you... for everything.
[TRAIN WHISTLE AND
CLANGING OF BELL]
[SIG] Feel free to drop
by if you're ever in town.
[AL] I'm not so
sure about that.
You idiots!
You're so busy pouting
you can't see what your
expulsion means...
You aren't her students anymore,
so now you're finally
free to speak to
Izumi as equals!
Unless, of course,
you're too chicken to try it.
Awwww, damn!
Al... we haven't
done what we
came here to do in
the first place!
[AL GASPS]
Thank you...
We're heading back
there right now!
Don't let her kill you.
Teacher!
[ED SCREAMS]
What the hell are you
doing coming back here?!
[IZUMI] And you
called me teacher...?!
I do not teach scum like you...!
Get out of my home!
[ED]
Teacher!
[AL] We came to you
because we're trying to
find a way to get
our bodies back.
And we won't leave
without your help!
Get out now!
We're staying!
You idiots.
[IZUMI] Al, you didn't see
"the Truth," did you?
[AL] No... I don't really
even know what that means.
You must've lost your
memory from the shock...
We need to get
Al's memory back...
His entire body
was taken from him.
[IZUMI] Just think what
he must've seen.
Oh, yeah...!
We only exchanged parts
of our bodies for
what we saw...
but Al paid the "toll" with
his entire physical being...
He must've seen more
of "the Truth"
than either of us did!
[AL] So... if I can
remember what I saw,
then we'll know how
to get our bodies back?
But the memory
of that thing...
[ED]
That thing...
[AL] What, is it
something bad?
No, it's more like awful.
[ED] Yeah...
and horrifying.
It could drive
you insane.
Or even leave
you brain dead.
[AL] That doesn't matter...
if there's a chance
that it can help us...
Then I wanna do it.
Alright... I have an
acquaintance that might
know a way to retrieve
your memory for you.
[ED AND AL GASP]
But...!
Let's eat dinner first...
Gimme a hand.
Okay!
[BIDO] The
rumors are true...
He's able to
transmute human souls...
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
There's only one week left
until the big transfer, huh?
Yessir.
[GENERAL GRUMMAN] It just
won't be the same without you...
You brought a little color
to this dreary desert.
[ROY CHUCKLES]
[ROY] I'm boring
compared to some
of the stories I've
heard about you.
[GENERAL GRUMMAN]
Well all of your hard work
has made my life easier...
Finally got to relax.
[ROY] And I feel like I've grown
as an officer thanks to the
variety of work you've
allowed me to take on.
[ROY]
Checkmate.
[GENERAL GRUMMAN]
Agh!
It took me long
enough to beat you.
You can consider
that my going-away gift.
Well, then.
If you're in a
gift-giving mood,
there's something else I'd like.
[ROY] Master Sergeant
Kain Fuery...
Warrant Officer Vato Falman...
Second Lieutenant
Heymans Breda...
Jean Havoc...
First Lieutenant
Riza Hawkeye.
Gather up your things...
All five of you
are transferring
to Central with me...
And no objections...
Understood?
I've got a
problem, sir...
See, I just started dating
this girl and I really like her.
Dump her.
[RICK] Come on,
not again...!
Your wounds are
never gonna heal
if you don't give it a rest.
[SCAR]
Master!
[MASTER] I'm glad
that you're well.
I was informed
that you've been
targeting State Alchemists
for execution.
[MASTER] I know the
animosity you feel...
A State Alchemist is
responsible for the burning
of our village and the
death of our loved ones...
But, your vengeance will
only sow the seeds
of further violence.
What you're doing
is senseless revenge...
and it's feeding a
fruitless, cycle of death...
You must end this cycle,
once and for all.
[MAN 1]
Anybody home...?
Wouldja look at that!
He really is here...!
[MAN 1] He's got the
scar and everything.
Looks like you've
got yourself a deal.
We'll split the bounty
three ways with you...
What the--?
[MAN 2] Guess he
didn't want the reward.
Yoki!
How could you do
something like this?
We took you in and
treated you like family
when you had
nowhere else to go--
Just shut up...!
I never even wanted anything
to do with you Ishvalans!
You lost your war,
but I'll rise again...!
I'll rise up...! I will rise...!
And I'll use my power...
to annihilate Edward Elric!
[YOKI]
Now then...
Capture him please so
we can fetch our money.
It's obvious that I'll only
bring more trouble
if I stay here.
Well, thanks for
making this easy, pal.
[ENERGY BURST]
[MAN 2 SCREAMS IN AGONY]
The hell?! What'd
you do to him?!
I'll give you a
moment to pray to god.
You should be
the one praying...!
You freak!
[MAN 2 SCREAMS]
[YOKI]
No... no, wait...!
Please! I'm sorry!
Please don't
kill me!
Please, I'm begging you
to spare my life...!
I'll do anything!
[MASTER]
So you're leaving then.
Your brother
would be sad.
Still, it's... too late...
to turn back now.
[AL]
Hmm?
[BIDO LAUGHS]
He's here.
[DOLCETTO] There
you are... 'bout time.
[AL] "We know
your secret...
Meet us at the Devil's Nest
if you want to talk"...
I'm guessing you're the
people that wrote this note?
[DOLCETTO]
That's right.
And we know
a lot about you.
[AL]
Well that's good...
'cuz there's a lot
about me that I don't know.
Then I'm the guy
you wanna talk to...
Why don't you come with us?
[AL] But my teacher
always said
I'm not supposed
to go with strangers.
How old are you?
[AL]
Fourteen.
Well come on then...
I'd say fourteen is old enough
to think for yourself, kid...
You gotta act like an adult
and start taking some risks.
[AL]
You think so...?
I should think for myself?
Yes...! And you can
start by coming wit--
[AL] So I thought it
over for myself...
And I decided that I should
just make you tell me
what I want to know.
So you wanna
do this by force?
[AL REACTS SHOCKED]
Sorry to drop in!
[AL]
You're inside me...?
Hey! Be a good boy
and hold still!
[MARTEL] So what's it
like having someone
control you from inside?
[AL] You can't stop
me from moving...!
And you're not strong enough
to hold this up forever!
You're right... but...
All I'm trying to do
is slow you down a little.
[ROA]
For my turn.
You all right in there?
Oh, I'm wonderful.
You're makin' this
way too hard, kid.
[AL] You people aren't
human, are you?
[GREED] Good guess!
They're Chimeras...
And they happen to work for me.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Cool... You're actually hollow.
The name's Greed...
And... I wanna
be your friend.
[AL] Then why don't you tell me
what you people really are?
[AL] You're not Chimeras.
It's impossible...
No one's made a
Chimera that can talk.
You can't believe everything
the government tells you, kid.
[GREED] You got all the proof
you need right inside you...
The girl in there is part snake.
And this big
guy here...
Roa, what were
you made with...? Cow?
Yeah.
We've also got a
lizard and a crocodile...
And the little runt that you
took down earlier tends
to lift his leg when he pees.
Only once!
[AL]
You're part dog?
Yep... It's really
not so bad.
[AL] I don't
believe it...
It's not possible...!
Who would even be
capable of creating one?!
[GREED]
The military.
[AL] Are
you saying...
You got it...
There's a shadow world
beneath yours that's jam
packed with the impossible...
Hell, I'm more
uncommon they are.
[GREED]
I'm a Homunculus.
[AL] A Homunculus?!
[GREED] You know
what that means, right?
[GREED] I'm an artificially
created human.
Really... no joke.
Homunculus?
It's a person made
from alchemy.
But doesn't that book
say you're not supposed
to try and make people?
[AL]
You're lying...!
A Homunculus is just a theory,
nobody's made one!
Oh, man...
Guess I've gotta prove it.
[AL] Why'd you
do that to him?!
[STRETCHES AND THEN POPS NECK]
That's one time I've died.
[AL]
No way.
[GREED]
You get it yet...?
Nothing is
impossible, alright...?
I'm a little surprised
you would have
such a hard time
accepting that...
Considering you're just
a soul in a suit of armor.
[AL]
Who told you that?!
People like to talk
in the shadow world
and I've got plenty of friends.
[GREED CHUCKLES]
Well... Let's skip this
casual chit-chat...
I'm more interested
in hearing what
it's like to have a body
that'll never die.
An individual soul
transmuted...?
And bound to an object?
It sounds like that's the
perfect recipe
for immortality to me.
[GREED]
Let me explain.
See, I'm Greed...
I want everything
you can think of...
Money and women...
Power and sex.
Status, glory...
I demand the finer things...
And of course...
I crave eternal life.
[AL] Aren't you
already immortal?
[GREED] Well,
I guess I was put
together a little
sturdier than most...
I am nearly two
hundred years old...
but I wouldn't exactly
say that I'm immortal.
So... I've spilled
my guts all over...
Told you my darkest secret...
Now it's your turn...
How'd you get your body?
[MARTEL] Just make
this easy and tell him.
Unless you'd rather
be examined...
which means he'll
have to take you apart.
[AL] I wish
I could tell you...
that would mean I actually
remember how I got it...
but even if I could,
I'm not the one who
did the transmutation.
That's not a problem.
In that case...
I'll just ask the
person who did.
[AL STAMMERS IN FEAR]
Now where'd a seven-foot
tall suit of armor run off to?
[BIDO] I'd be happy to tell you
where you could find him.
[BIDO] But first you tell me...
what his secret is.
[DOOR CRASHES OPEN
AND BIDO BELLOWS]
[AL]
Brother!
Never really crossed my mind
that you could get kidnapped.
[AL] Brother! This
guy's a Homunculus!
Are you serious?!
Hey...! Way to ruin it.
[AL] You might be able
to get some leads from
him on how to get
our original bodies back!
An Uroboros tattoo.
Aren't you
observant...?
I was hoping
that I'd
only have to deal with
the little armored giant.
Why don't you just
ask your partners
whatever you
want to know?
Partners?
[ED] Yeah, the rest of the
Uroboros gang
from the fifth lab...
They had a couple of
armor-bonded souls
with them as well.
Y'don't say...
Well, it's kind
of a long story...
but we don't
talk much anymore.
[GREED] I've got a
little proposal for you...
You guys are pretty desperate
to get your bodies back, right?
Because I could teach
you how to fabricate your
own Homunculus
in no time at all.
[GREED] In return...
all I ask is you
teach me how
to transmute a soul.
Classic equivalent exchange.
But I really don't understand
why you would want
your other body back.
[GREED] Seems like you've got
one that's perfect already.
[AL] No, I don't!
[GREED] You're
joking, right...?
You don't need to eat...
You don't need to sleep...
You don't even
need to use the toilet!
Sounds great to me!
That's enough--
Shut your... damned... mouth...
[ED SCREAMS OUT]
Sounds GREAT to you...?!
It SEEMS PERFECT...?!
[ED] You don't know anything
about the hell he's had
to go through stuck
with that body!!!
[ED] And you wanna know
how to transmute a soul?!
[ED] YOU KIDNAP MY
BROTHER AND YOU WANNA
TRADE SECRETS WITH ME?!
[ED] I'm gonna
crush you creeps...!
I'LL, SMASH YOU... END YOU!
And I won't give you slime...
ANYTHING!
In other words,
There won't be an exchange...
with you...
SCUUUMMM!!!
I guess we're doing
this by force again.
[GREED]
Don't kill him, alright?
Yeah, yeah.
[ED] You're a lot slower
than a prisoner I know.
Next?
Roa. Get the armored
kid outta here...
Guess we'll dismantle him.
[ROA]
Right!
[AL] Hey! Hold on!
- [ED] Drop him!
- [AL] Hey! Hold on!
Nope. Sorry...
That little hand-sword of
yours is kinda neat,
but it can't even
scratch my Ultimate Shield!
Guard your head next time.
Awww, that hurt...
That move would've
hospitalized most people.
[ED] But you're not
like most people, huh?
Well... My body is.
All that sets me apart
are my Ultimate Shield and
my advanced healing powers.
[GREED]
Nothin' special.
But you're never
gonna beat me.
So I'd suggest
making a deal.
[GREED] Oh.
You're one of those guys...
You don't care if somebody
beats the crap out of you...
But if someone lays a
finger on a family member,
you completely freak out.
What a waste...
You lose your temper like this
and you're gonna lose my
information and your brother.
My brother's fine.
He's just waiting for
me to kick your ass...
You've already told us
you're not immortal,
remember...?
And your Ultimate Shield
doesn't cover much.
[GREED LAUGHS]
[GREED] Sorry to let you down,
but I've been holding back.
[GREED] This obscures
my handsome face...
so I try not to
wear it that much.
[GREED]
I wasn't kidding, kid...
Try all ya like,
but you're not gonna beat me.
[SIG] I found this
lying in the alley.
[IZUMI] Then you're saying...
they're both missing?
Those idiots...!
They can't even
sweep the street
without getting into trouble!
They're lucky I expelled them,
otherwise I'd kill them!
[MASON]
I think I can help.
Here, catch. A friend of mine
noticed a short
blonde haired kid
heading into a bar
called the Devil's Nest.
[ED SUFFERING IN PAIN]
You dead yet?
There ya go...!
You're chock full
of piss and vinegar!
[IMPACT AND METAL CLANKING]
[GREED] I appreciate the effort,
but you just can't win!
[ED IN PAIN]
Sooo, are you ready to
tell me your secret now?
Huh?
[ED] Thanks for
toying with me.
What?
You gave me just
enough time to cool off
and start thinking clearly.
[ED] Is my mechanic
amazing or what...?
Even after all this,
it's still working.
[HANDS CLAP FOLLOWED BY
ELECTRICAL ENERGY]
[GREED] How long you
wanna drag this out, kid?
It'd be so much
easier if you'd just...
...stay down!
Well. That was bizarre...
Good as new.
What was that for?!
Come on. Again...?
Try a new one!
[GREED YELPS IN PAIN]
[GREED] What the hell
did you do to my shield?
It's actually pretty simple
once you think about it...
You may be a homunculus,
but you really shouldn't have
told me that your body is human,
considering that means
a third of it is made of carbon.
[ED] The hardness of carbon
varies depending on
how the atoms are
arranged so it's obvious
that's what your
shield is made of.
Once I've got that figured out,
the rest is simple alchemy.
[ED CHUCKLES]
I'm glad to hear it...!
It's no fun if it's
not a challenge!
And there's one other
important thing I noticed!
[ED] You can't harden
your shield and
heal at the same time!
I think that it is safe to
say that I underestimated you...
But how much longer
can you keep this
up in your condition?
[DOOR BLASTS OPEN]
[IZUMI] Sorry to
barge in like this.
[ED]
Teacher?!
You damn imbecile!
[IZUMI] You think it's funny
not put the broom away...?!
I asked you a question!
No... I'm so sorry!
Thanks for your hospitality...
He definitely
needed the exercise.
[ED] Teacher...!
Careful!
[ED] He's a--
[IZUMI]
Yes, I know...
I could hear the two
of you all the way
down the hall.
Oh gimme a break,
don't tell me you're
gonna try and
start anything, lady...
It's no fun fighting a woman.
[GREED LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
Well now...!
Just what the hell are you?
[IZUMI] You
asked what I am?
A housewife!!
[NARRATOR] Even the
mighty have no choice
but to answer to a
greater power...
No matter how
strong one is,
there is always
another above them...
But as long as one's
spirit retains its pride,
it will also remain indomitable...
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode Fourteen...
Those Who Lurk Underground.
There is much more
to our existence...
than what we can see.