I was just supposed to be an ordinary third grader,
but then a small incident happened.
What I believed in was my courageous heart.
What I gained were magical powers.
I made a decision with adamant feelings...
...because I can somewhat understand
why you'd want to run away from this.
That's why we're having our first and last true match.
I'll bet everything on my magic!
And I'll tell you anything, because
I want you to show me your smile.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
I was always so uneasy that I was shaking
Hugging my knees in the corner of my room.
I was afraid of knowing the "truth"
and closed the door to it.
Through a kind lie, I discovered where I should be.
I fled and took refuge in my dreams.
No one knows of the lonely sea
being dyed a deep blue color
that hides my loneliness.
With wholehearted feelings, I wounded your heart.
The secret within your eyes makes me want to soak it up.
I'll bring the truth behind
your smile with a warm love.
If I touch it, the warmth that seems so breakable will
break away from its past and overflow.
Because you're always by my side
I will no longer be puzzled over the shadow of loneliness.
Mother...yes, my mother...
She was always so tender... that was my mother...
The mother who'd call my name so gently...
Look! Isn't this really pretty, Alicia?
Alicia? No, Mother... I'm Fate...
Come closer, Alicia.
There. You're so cute, my lovely Alicia...
Well... I guess it's all right...
Because I love my oh so gentle Mother, I will...
Memories That Lie Beyond Time.
Looks like a battle's broken out...
Yeah
But it certainly is unusual for you to allow
that kind of gamble, Chrono-kun.
Well... it'd be for the best if Nanoha wins...
...but either way, it won't really matter in the
grand scheme of things who falls first.
While Nanoha-chan is buying
us time during her match...
...I was thinking I'd prepare the tracking system so
I can see where that girl has been returning to.
I'm counting on you. Don't let her get away this time.
Of course! Just leave it to me!
Huh?
But... is it really okay not to tell Nanoha-chan?
About Precia Testarossa's family... and that accident.
It'd be best if she wins on her own...
I don't want her to hesitate in the slightest right now.
Photon Lancer.
Divine Shooter.
Fire!
Shoot!
Scythe Form.
Round Shield.
Flash Move.
Take this!
Scythe Slash.
Fire.
When we first met, she was just a beginner
with strong magical powers, but now...
She's so different from before...
so fast... and so strong.
If I hesitate now, I'll be beaten!
Phalanx Shift.
Lightning Bind!
This is bad! Fate's gotten really serious!
Nanoha! I'm going to support you!
NO!
Arf-san, Yuuno-kun, please don't interfere.
This is a one-on-one fight to our limits.
This is our match!
But it'll be bad if Fate's truly serious!
I'll be fine!
Arukas, Krutas, Eygias...
Heavenly gods who shine over all,
descend upon us now as I guide you.
Baruel, Zaluel, Browzel...
Photon Lancer... Phalanx Shift!
Strike her down! Fire!
Nanoha!
Fate!
Of course the bind would wear off
after you finished your attack.
Now it's my...
Divine...
...turn!
...Buster.
A direct hit...!
But... I can endure it.
After all, that girl withstood my attack!
Fate...
See if you can take this variation on my Divine Buster...
Starlight Breaker.
A bind...!
This is my ultimate strength... it's everything I've got!
Starlight... BREAKER!
W-What an insane amount of magical power!
Woah... I wonder if Fate-chan can survive that?!
Fate-chan!
Are you all right, Fate-chan?
I'm sorry... are you all right?
Yeah...
I guess... I won, right?
It... looks that way...
Put Out.
Can you still fly?
All right, Nanoha. Secure the
Jewel Seeds, and bring her...
No... she's here!
Fate-chan!
Bingo! I've got her!
All right! We might be fatally unprepared for
what lies beyond, but get those coordinates.
I've already calculated them!
Sending them over right away!
Armed Enforcers, start mobilizing
at the transport point!
Your mission is to take Precia Testarossa into custody!
Yes, ma'am!
As I thought... my body will no longer
last with just support magic...
And... my capture is imminent...
Fate... it appears that girl was a waste after all.
It might finally be time to set things in motion...
Second Platoon, transport complete.
First Platoon, infiltration successful.
Good job.
And... Fate-san, it's a pleasure to finally meet you.
It'd be unbearable for her to watch
her mother get captured.
Nanoha-san, please take her to a different room.
Y-Yes.
Fate-chan, if you'd like, why don't
you come to my room with-
All hands have successfully infiltrated the throne room.
We've located the target.
Precia Testarossa! You have violated the laws
of the Time-Space Administration Bureau.
You will be arrested for attacking the Bureau's warship.
Drop any weapons you may have and step over here.
Fortify yourself over here!
Hey, there's something over here!
Th-This is...!
Don't you dare come near my Alicia!
F-Fire!
You're quite irritating...
You're in danger! Pull back!
This is bad! Transport the Enforcers back at once!
U-Understood!
Ali... cia...?
Fixed coordinates: 0120 503!
Affirmative! Stand by at Precia's location for transport!
It looks like everything might have
been in vain... we are out of time.
With only nine Lost Logia, we may not
be able to reach Alhazred, but...
But it's all right now. I'll put an end to everything.
To all the time this girl was
deprived after I lost her...
...and also to the doll I created to play as my daughter.
Are you listening? I'm talking about you, Fate.
Even after I went to the trouble of giving you Alicia's
memories, only your appearance is the same.
You were such useless, unusable scum... my little doll.
You see... during her first accident,
Precia lost her... true daughter, Alicia Testarossa.
She wasn't just researching the creation of familiars...
...but something surpassing them...
the creation of artificial beings.
And also... the secret art of reincarnation.
The name "Fate" came from the name of the
research project she was involved with.
You've certainly learned quite a bit...
You're right. It's just as you said.
But in the end, it was all worthless.
It didn't go even slightly as planned.
In the end, the life of an artificial product is
just as it sounds... nothing but a product.
It couldn't possibly replace something I lost.
Alicia smiled much more sweetly than you.
She'd speak out of selfishness every now and then,
but she always listened to what I had to say.
Stop it...
Alicia was always so good to me...
Fate, in the end, you were really nothing
but an imitation of Alicia.
Even after I gave you her precious
memories, you were no good.
Stop it... stop it!
You were nothing but a doll made for my consolation
while I was working on bringing Alicia back to life.
And that's why I no longer need you.
Vanish from the face of this world!
Please, stop it already!
I'll tell you something good, Fate.
Ever since I created you, I've always...
...hated you!
Fate-chan!
Fate...
The Enforcers have all been retrieved.
B-Big trouble! Take a look over here!
There's a large number of magical reactions
occurring throughout her residence!
What is it?! What's happening over there?!
The reactions in the Garden of Time are all rated A+!
Total number of reactions... sixty...
no, eighty... and rising!
Precia Testarossa! What are you planning?!
I don't want anyone to interrupt us on our journey.
We are leaving this place!
To the forgotten capital... to Alhazred!
She couldn't possibly be...?!
With their power... we will partake
in this journey, and reclaim it...
We'll reclaim it all!
Dimensional disturbance detected...
it's huge, well beyond our limits!
Turn on our impact defense, the Distortion Shield!
All nine Jewel Seeds have activated!
The dimensional disturbance is getting stronger!
Maintain transfer distance, but maneuver
evasively if you detect any feedback!
U-Understood!
I confirm many more outbreaks of power!
At this rate, it's going to turn into
a dimensional dislocation!
Alhazred...
Such a stupid thing to do...!
Chrono-kun?!
I'm going to stop her! Open a gate!
The forgotten capital... Alhazred...
The land where the forbidden technology was sealed...
What do you plan to do there?!
Do you really think you can recover your lost past?!
No matter what kind of magic you use,
you can never... bring back the past!
At Alhazred, Alicia and I... will reclaim the past we lost!
Make a little wish. I was stumbling
and losing my way on my journey
but since you were there
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy
Ah, the silver wind came looking for
two who were lacking something
beyond the cellophane sea and forest.
Ah, I was just crying in our city that's
nothing more than a diorama.
Looking for your warm hand
you held out to me that day.
In the ever-swaying years,
I felt you looking at me.
And then I had finally, finally found the secret key.
Make a little wish. Gather the lemon-colored
drops of the moon.
I want to gently light the path you're walking down.
Make a little wish, even if it's a small one.
If you say you can't do anything
then remember that because you were there,
I was able to keep smiling and stay happy.
The dimensional disturbance
we couldn't stop...
In order to stop Precia, we all
head towards the Garden of Time!
Nanoha's world... our world...
in order to stop the destruction of worlds like them...
And also, at the
same time, Fate has...!
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Twelve:
The Time of the Sealing of Our Fates
Lyrical Magical!
Surely, until the very end...