What's wrong?
Really? So, you're going to Mistral?
Of all the places...
But they got good food there. And the girls are lookers too.
It's been half a year since the last war, eh?
Glad we both survived it in one piece.
There, full house!
Tough luck!
That sucks!
Dammit.
Hey missy, you up?
Spoils from the war.
Caramel?
I-I don't think I deserve this expensive food!
Um...
...Sergeant!
No sweat. They say if you treat your trumpeter right, she'll play the call to retreat louder.
Without conscription going on, a new recruit's pretty rare.
You volunteer?
Yes! I wanted to learn to play music.
What?
No, I mean...
Honesty is great!
Good luck, missy.
Private, your name?
Kanata.
I'm Sorami Kanata!
SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
That someone sung for you is happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Even if you shed tears, you cannot stop here
We're seperated a long way from tomorrow in the lights that rain without end
RESOUNDING NOTE
THE CITY AT DAWN
There's a festival in Seize today.
A festival?
So I'll stop here.
Look!
Your assigned post is the Timekeeping Fortress.
Just head in that direction.
Roger!
Notice of appointment, Private Sorami Konata.
You are hereby assigned to Platoon 1121 in Trois, Seize.
Helvetia Republic Army Headquarters.
Here.
1320 hours, mission complete.
Thank you very much.
The town of lakes and glass, Seize.
Wait, wait!
I must report to my post at 1500 hours.
Finally, I can let you sing.
Bearing, check!
Current time, check!
Equipment, check!
Forward, march!
Welcome!
G-flat.
What a wonderful note.
Wow, they're fish!
10.25 yen.
What a pretty doll-
I-I'm sorry!
Something wrong, Rio?
A kitten was swept up in the festival,
and suddenly sped off in a random direction.
That's just how it is.
Kittens like to loiter on the street.
Isn't that what makes them cute?
Only if it's a stray.
Unfortunately, this one has an owner.
Hey, hey, wait a minute.
Hey, hey, bring that thing over here.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
That surprised me.
But I found another wonderful thing.
What's wrong?
Thank you!
Miss soldier!
A girl from the fortress?
How thankful of them!
For the sake of the flame, thank you!
Alright...
How dare you!
Take this!
Fire!
Thank you!
Hey!
Are you stupid?!
You made a mess of yourself.
What're you gonna do with these clothes?!
Um, well...
Bless you.
Thank yo-
Jeez! Come on!
How's the water?
Yes, it's perfect.
That's good.
Looks like she must've been an easy target.
Couldn't you at least dodge it?
Don't worry, this dye is made to disappear once it dries.
No problems at all.
That was a festival, wasn't it?
It's related to the legend of Seize.
A legend?
What kind of legend?
Of the fire maidens who protected this town.
Sorry to trouble you.
Don't worry about it.
I also took care of the other thing.
And...
this, too.
It's Felicia, huh?
It's none of her business.
She's late.
She's late! She's late! She's so late!
I came all this way to welcome her, you know?
Okay.
Let's wait patiently.
It's a present from your father, isn't it?
It's a nice bell.
D-flat.
Thank you for the bath.
Um, I got myself lost along the way,
but thanks to that, I had a wonderful encounter!
You're flattering.
But please don't get lost here, okay?
Do you know this sound?
It's very soothing, and somehow nostalgic.
That's not what I-
You thief!
Idiot!
Thank you very much...
Jeez.
Do you want to die for that thing?!
But, the bell...
It's fine.
I'm sure... this is for the best.
Late.
I'm happy.
Um...
I have something to do, so I'm leaving first.
Don't get lost again.
That bell must have been important to her.
What do I do?
Oh no!
That way?
Forward, march!
The fire maidens?
Long ago, when the world was much like the world today,
a winged demon settled in the valley below this town.
This demon rained fire, shook the land, and caused great suffering.
And then, it took maidens living in the fortress, trapping them in a labyrinth below the earth.
However, these maidens never yielded to their fate.
Using a golden horn entrusted by Heaven, they called out to each other and escaped the labyrinth.
And with the help of a giant spider, they defeated the demon,
cutting its head to the ground.
But suddenly, from the head came a great inferno.
Untended, the entire town would have burnt to ash.
To stop the fire from spreading, the maidens embraced the demon's head in turns.
And so, the burning demon's head was embraced by the maidens,
as the villagers poured water on them every day.
Finally, after a year, the flames died.
From those days hence, the water festival was held to impart some solace on these savior maidens.
The new girl didn't come, did she?
I couldn't care less about her!
Look at that, Captain! It's Rio!
It looks really good on her.
It was right to have her do it.
But didn't we draw lots?
I'm lost again.
I'm... so useless.
There are times when getting lost is fun,
but that must be because I get to meet someone new.
Being alone... isn't fun at all.
Are you lost?
Yes...
I want to see my mom.
Don't worry.
If you truly wish for it, your feelings will reach her.
Really?
Yes. That note will surely resound.
It will surely resound.
It will surely resound...
...and reach out.
The fire maidens will not rest here.
You embraced the demon, and suppressed the curse.
This is the time to awaken before the people, your pain will-
This sound...
It's the golden horn!
Does it mean the demon has...
...awoken?
Kureha!
Please reach!
Someone, please receive my note!
It reached.
The note resounded,
and...
Get up already!
Private Sorami Kanata!
Huh?
Where am I?
How long do you plan on dreaming?
We're in the Timekeeping Fortress, the post of Platoon 1121.
Ah!
About yesterday, um...
I-I'm sorry for all the trouble I caused.
You'd better be.
I-I'm sorry!
But...
I'm just joking.
But, don't be so reckless.
Can't believe it was all for this bell...
Let me tell you a story.
A trumpet!
A tale of why this fortress is called the "Timekeeping Fortress".
The notes of the sky!
Kazumiya Rio.
That's my name.
I'm going to guide you as a trumpeter.
I'm in your care, Sergeant Major Rio.
"Rio" is fine.
It's Felicia's... I mean, our Captain's policy.
We don't use ranks here.
Um...
Well then, Rio.
Alright, let's start right away.
Try a morning bugle call for me.
What?!
The girl this time is pretty bad...
Pile up the feelings of love and friendship
Performing is also important
I cried happily
I laughed eagerly
But all of them make me alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me why we dance
you just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I want them to echo forever
Speaking endless words touched by love
Our harmony
I can hear our harmony
Next episode: First Campaign - A Story of the Chair
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.