Go, Charles!
Thanks for joining our club, Gregg Popobitch
We made a damn good team during that middle school tournament
Just like how Shizuno Middle School's Suga.
Yeah, but we got beat by Suga in the end.
Me, too, for my last match...
But we're a lot stronger now with you as our teammate.
Um, are you sure you got my name right?
My last name is not Popobitch. It's Popovich
Sorry! I really thought...
Popovich...
Yeah.
Gregg Popovich
Yo, we meetin' at the station monday?
Yep.
We're goinna the court Charles Barkley used
Dirk! You's all soaked!
Hey!
I wonder what kind of place it is?
Oh! I'm looking forward to it!
What's with dat towel, Kareem?
It's mah brotha's
Did you make up with your brother?
No... I think my mom messed up.
I see.
Um...
Y'see, I ain't been talking to my brother.
Ya gotta make it up with 'im
I do want to take the initiative, but I get scared.
And I think he's avoiding me.
You don't need to hurry things up. Just don't give up and everything will be fine.
Yep.
I didn't know you were Kareem's brother
I's surprised, too, that you two know Kareem
So that means...
You know her pedo coach, too?
Pedo coach?
The coach of the LeBron's Ballin' Girls' Basketball Team is some retarted nigga, right?
And this coach tried to assault my sister and her friends during training camp.
Um, that's...
He also made them play basketball in their swimsuits!
That's messed up, yo!
I get so damn worried just thinking about that bastard hanging around my lil' sister...
Whatsamatter Charles?
I'm sorry, Gregg
Is me
Yo What?
I'm dat coach
I punched him without thinking.
Sheeeeeit!
You heard about Kareem's brotha?
Not really. I just know they aren't on good terms with each other.
I see.
Okay! Let's start practice!
Nice shot, Nana.
Das rite!
Fuck off, outta my way!
It's time for the adults to use the court.
Adults?
Yo Nana, are middle school students adults?
Watchu saying', Mayumi?
We bought adult tickets for the bus ride here!
I see. So seventh graders are adults.
Hey! You adults need to line up after us!
These niglets came here first.
You wanna wait in line or play together with them?
Huh? Why the fuck do I play with grade schoolers?
But I'll play you.
Let's bet on who gets to use this court.
Okay! Just what I wanted!
That's that, then.
He's here!
Yo! We're playing a game with them!
Huh? Why must I play along?
Suga Ryuuichi.
Are you Charles Barkley?
Long time no see, nigga
I heard your school's team is no more. Y'all are weak
I'm about to become a starter.
I'll become the muthafuckin' ace at Itoda Business High, the strongest team in the prefecture.
Congratulations.
That's all?
Nana, be glad. I've changed my mind.
What?
It's been a while, so let me see.
Your ape-hoop skillz
Sorry for bringing the two of you into this.
Nah son, it's cool
You sure I'm good?
Yeah, I want u
That Mayumi probably plays center.
Please help me out.
Okay! I'll do my best!
Um, Charles Barkley-san.
This nigga someone we can't lose to?
mhm
I can't lose to him at all
Aight
I'll do muh best
Charles!
My B!
Pass was shit, anywys
I'll get it next time!
Kobe's off her game
Yeah she's makin' mistakes
Kobe ain't the only one trippin'
Fuck do I do? I can't stop her!
Kareem!
That Mayuri is putting on a lot of pressure.
Kareem's getting screwed!
Put your Fucking Backs into it!
GO!
Kareem! Behind ya!
Got it!
Its all good, Kareem, We'll get 'em next time
Okay!
Kobe, relax nigga, relax
Okay! I'll do my best!
I'm sorry! I...
It's not your fault. Don't worry about it.
Get that weak shit outta here!
Charles, cut the crap, alright?
Let's start the main event already. You and me.
1v1
That was...
That was a jab step.
Jab step?
To put it simply, he's a bitch.
He's using dainty little faggot steps
Not one nigga in this hood can counter it
Not even Charles Barkley
Charles...
Whatsamatter? You comin or wat?
Then here I come.
I can't lose to his pressure!
This is it!
Well, that's that.
Seems like I overestimated your skills.
I was kinda looking forward to playing you during the prefectural tournament.
But I guess you can be my bitch!
You know that's all you can become, right?
That's why you went to a weak elementary school to become their key man.
But that's all you've got.
You ain't nothin!
That's my Ryuu!
Now we can use the court all we want during our fall break!
Let's go home for today.
It's all my fault!
Nah son, it aint you
It was that bitch Kareem!
And our pussy of a coach
Right, Charles?
Yeah.
But!
Charles can't forgive himself right now.
Just let him be, aight?
Yes.
You showed some weak shit today
You better check yourself
Before you wreck yourself
Nigga your passes are 2slow!
You supporting cast need to do all you can to help me out!
Nothing will end like this.
We ate shit...
Same
Hey now.
If you two feel down, then Charles Barkley will feel even worse.
But Kobe was doing awful!
That's right. Usually you can catch his passes easily.
You're right.
I wonder why?
Oh? I know the reason.
Me, too.
Fucking tell me!
Listen closely. Ya gotta go to Charles's house tomorrow morning
Practice with him, get him comfortable
Okay! I got it!
Hmm, maybe that's not enough?
Tell me anything!
I'll do my best!
Hehehe!
Well then...
We'll end here for today.
O-Okay!
Jab step... How do I defend against it?
Um...
Kobe?
The bath is where you can scrub a dub dub clean!
Open the door! Let me in!
Ahhh fuck my B
Nah It's cool
It was all my fault, mang, I kept missin dem passes
Shut the fuck up Kobe, I told you you did fine
But...
Oh... Mabye I should be nicer
Then can you scrub a dub dub my back?
Okay!
Charle's Barkley  your ass back is huge.
hehe, yeah, it's a nice cake
Your back.
I'm much too small to be of much help.
Kobe, you couldn't catch my passes yesterday, right?
Yeah, whatever
Are you frustrated?
Shut up Kircheis!
k
Then if we play them again, can you finally catch my passes?
Probably not!
Put me through da training, ah can do it!
So please let me stay by your side!
Thank you.
Sorry, everyone.
You saw your coach get his front doors knocked in
I'm pissed as fuck, too
I'm ashamed that I couldn't do anything in front of Suga.
That's why I'm thinking of challenging him to a grudge match.
So can you all help me out once again?
It's not just me. I want us all to play as a team and win!
Count me in, nigga!
Let's do this !
Nana-san will only be there for the fall break. We don't have much time left.
That's the spirit, Charles!
Oh!
Let's show them whos' top dog, Onii-chan!
You need a helper?
Anne Donnovan?! You gonna help me out?
Don't be retarted
Actually the fifth graders asked me to come.
Yao Ming and the other niglets?
Yep.
She said she'll feel bad for beating you after you've lost so many times.
Sounds like something Wilt and Larry would say!
Anne, I'm all calm now, thanks mang
Nah son, my pleasure
Sorry.
I'm not sorry for punching you!
Fuck you
Anyone would be angry if his sister is being cared for by some stranger!
Cared for!?
That was a big misunderstanding! Nothing happened!
I'm just saying that I didn't explain myself properly!
That's good, then.
Actually, I have something important to tell you.
Kareem's coach?
I can't not think of no one else. Please help me a brotha out
No
Kareem hates me.
I'm so moist and unrefined...
Whenever I raise my voice she gets scared.
Bitch can't even look me in the eyes!
No chips, mang, I ain't doin that
I'm sorry.
I see.
But you know, Popovich
Kareem. Kareem! Wake the fuck up!
Sup brotha?
My B, I'm all tuckered out
What if you catch Mega Herpes?!
THEN I'LL GET AN ABORTION
Sorry, I ... I don't know
Kareem is changing, bit by bit.
You've been training until very late recently.
R-Really?
Maybe you're right.
Why are you working so hard?
I want to change.
These niggas like fam to me, you see?
But ah can't do nothin' for 'em
I gotta change myself, little by little!
Gotta work hard!
I see.
You're really hot, Kareem
We have a special guest who'll help you out in your special training.
Kareem's brother, Gregg Popovich
Nice ta meetcha!
You gonna piss yourself, Gregg?
Dirk, shut he fuck up!
Kareem's brother is here!
Yeah.
Let's do our best together, mkay?
Shit yeah, son!
Kobe!
What?
Your skillz are through tha roof!
But it's still not like myself.
You were the same during morning practice, though.
I'm really sorry.
I think it's time for you to try out that plan, Kobe
Oh! I want to try it out, too.
No, fuck off, this is Kobe's plan
Plan?
Somethin' to jumpstart her playin' skills
She can do dat?
Yeah son, but she gon' need help!
Coming!
Evenin' nigga
What do you want?
What's up?
Actually... Um...
Can ah sleep wit you tonight?
Preview: What's with that middle schooler!?
Fucking hell I'm mad!
Bitch nigga thinks she's hot shit?
Ahaha but
I know mah niggas can rock their boat upside down!
Smack the niggas wit a fryin' pan
Watch out whities!