The city.
A place where people gather, are born and raised, and one day pass on.
Maruko Shopping District
But sometimes through the carelessness of the gods,
the lives of the city's residents can be thrown into chaos.
Hotori! Dinner's ready!
Hotori! Did you hear me?
12th Street
"Soremachi"
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
“And the town still turns (part A)” from Vol. 2 Ch. 13
Hmm, so this is the café you work at?
Shouldn't you be at ping pong practice right now?
I'm ditching today. Can I order now?
Sure, what’cha want?
Cutlet curry, hold the cutlets.
And an iced coffee, hold the ice. And make it hot.
Come again?
So you just want curry and coffee, right?
I wasn't talking to you, dumbass.
So very sorry. I just work here too, that's all.
Hey, what's going on here? It's kinda tense in here.
She was an upperclassman at my middle school.
She's all pissy because I didn't join the ping-pong club in high school.
She gave up 'cause she couldn't beat me, so she ran away, the little wuss.
I won't take you back now, even if you beg me to.
Hey, quit fighting over such a stupid disagreement.
Oh yeah! I've got just the thing for you two.
The magnifying pendant!
At first glance, it looks like an ordinary magnifying glass.
But wait! The other end is actually a fountain pendant!
That's fountain PEN. No "dant".
It's a little heavy, but it still writes great.
Kon is a doofus
Two completely different instruments, combined into one amazing detective tool!
So you two stop fighting and get along with each other!
Huh? I thought I could work this out just like Moori Motonari's "3 arrows" story.
But it seems like they're not getting it.
This pen looks like it was a gift.
Well yeah. How many high school girls can afford a foutain pendant?
My uncle gave it to me as a present when I entered high school.
This is a Montblanc.
Oh, I'm sorry, but we don't serve montblancs here.
We've got coffee jelly, though.
No, not the food. Did you modify this yourself?
Sure did! I'm gonna patent this!
I just chopped off the end of the pen, and super glued the magnifying glass to it!
Well, as long as you knew what you were doing, I guess it's okay.
But Monblanc pens are pretty fancy, you know.
I think they cost tens of thousands of yen.
Sorry to burst your bubble Hotori,
but someone's beat you to the punch.
See? The pen cap has a magnifying glass on it.
It's pretty popular among us old folk.
You can go home early today. Get some rest.
Let's see... I think I've got something you might like.
Found it!
Here. You can have this whistle, so cheer up, okay?
Aren't you going to change out of that?
Isn't your house the other way?
So that's the look of someone who's lost everything they used to believe in.
It's like she's been dowsed in despair.
Desperately seeking a light of hope amidst the darkness.
Incoming call
Ayatori Residence
Arashiyama residence...
Uncle!?
What impeccable timing you have.
That? Oh, you meant the fountain pendant?
Yes, of course I'm using it!
I always carry it with me. I've got it with me right here.
By the way, how much did this cost, exactly?
A hundred thou-
During summer vacation? Yes, I'd love to come visit.
Thank you.
Hey mom, phone call from the Ayatoris.
Okay, thanks. Hey, what about work?
Come visit us
over summer vacation.
I'll refill the ink for you.
It's the de-cap-itation caper!
Okay, think positive.
I'll just come up with some kind of trick to distract him when I visit.
A trick... mysteries have tricks...
Mysteries... I wonder when Hiroto Shimabe's new book is coming out.
I wonder if Mystery Magazine published any updates on it...
Mystery Magazine
Weekly
Oh, I know!
That's it!
Grand
Prize
5 million yen for typed entries
First prize, 5 million yen!
That's more than enough!
The deadline's coming up soon.
But they'll publish 3 months from now.
I can still make it!
I can buy another fountain pendant by summer!
No, writing a detective story and getting the prize money is the ONLY way to get another fountain pendant!
What would I do if I actually won first prize, though?
Do not disturb
Snacks and refreshments are appreciated
I stood on the deck of the ship, watching the waves and enjoying my jell-o.
But little did I know that a horrifying incident was about to take place.
Murder on Jelly Island
I can see Jelly Island!
So that's Jelly Island, home of the world-famous jelly...
I've heard stories of an Abominable Jellyman that lives on the island.
I'm so scared!
Welcome, friends. I am the master of Jelly Island.
Please, help yourselves to some jelly.
I want strawberry jelly.
This person might be the Jellyman!
This is some pretty good jelly, huh?
Verily. Jelly Island's jelly is quite delectable.
What happened!?
Oh no! Tatsuno's dead!
She's been decapitated!
Who could have done such a thing?
The legend of the Abominable Jellyman was true!
Everybody stay together!
The murderer might be one of us!
No, the Jellyman did it!
I don't trust any of you! I'm going on alone!
That was Kon's scream!
Now Kon's been killed too!
Heh, now I know who the culprit is.
I thought it was strange that the body of the first victim, Tatsuno, disappeared without a trace.
But in fact, it's just the opposite!
The murderer is YOU!
Kon!
But she's already dead!
This isn't blood. It's strawberry jelly.
Observe. She merely buried herself!
The only victim here is Tatsuno!
Dammit! She wouldn't join the ping pong club, so I killed her!
All right, you're going downtown.
Splendid work as always, Ms. Arashiyama.
Inspector Moriaki.
'Twas a dreadful case...
But perhaps Kon was also a victim... of society.
The end.
You sure seem happy today.
You looked like you hadn't been getting enough sleep recently.
Oh, Kon...
Ms. Arashiyama, when is your next book coming out?
Please give me your autograph!
Me too, if you don't mind, Ms. Arashiyama!
Everyone line up and prepare more flattery for me.
I’ll still come visit you when I'm famous.
Huh?
However, one week later...
I'm home!
Hmm? I got something from Mystery Magazine.
It's still a long time before they announce the winners...
Let's see..."Thank you very much for your entry.
However, we regret to inform you that your submission did not advance past the initial round of our rigorous evaluation."
Rigorous
Submission
Initial Round
Please do not be discouraged. Rather, we look forward to seeing you improve as a writer.
T-This can't be happening!
I spent two whole weeks writing that! It's not fair!
H-Hey little girl, you okay!?
Call an ambulance!
Sorry for jumping out in front of you like that.
I'm fine though, don't worry.
I'm calling an ambulance righ now, okay?
Wait! Don't move the body!
Oh man, she's a goner...
Hmm, this might be a little... no, a BIG problem.
Hey, I can see through myself!
Ah! I'm floating!
Hey, what gives!?
This isn't funny!
Hey, something's coming!
Who the heck are you guys!?
Go away! Shoo!
No really, this isn't a good time.
I said wait! Put me back down!
Hey, if you're just gonna goof off, can you let me slide this time?
Hey! Is that supposed to be my life flashing before my eyes!?
The city is home to many people.
And just like that, there is now one less.
Place thine heart upon this scale.
“And the town still turns (part B)” from Vol. 2 Ch. 14
If thine heart is of lesser weight than this plum, thou may enter heaven.
Be it heavier, and thou be banished to hell.
There's no way a heart could be lighter than a feather!
No! The holy feather!
Think of something better to compare it to.
Like a can of coffee or something.
Annoying Moving Armband That I Don't Want To Typeset: Guide
What are you doing here!?
You're Japanese, so get in the Japanese line!
Come back here you little brat! I’ll throw you into hell!
Deceased Reception Desk
Please wait quietly until your name is called.
Ms. Arashiyama... Ms. Hotori Arashiyama...
Okay... Ms. Hotori Arashiyama, yes?
Is this you first time dying?
Yeah.
Cause of death: accident. No negative karma.
Okay, that will be all.
There aren't any problems, so you should receive your proof of residence in about 2 to 3 weeks.
This place kinda reminds me of city hall.
Hi there, sorry about before.
My job is to assist new residents, so feel free to ask me anything.
Is this really the afterlife?
It's not exactly how I pictured it.
Nobody's got halos or those triangle thingies?
We stopped doing those decades ago to cut costs.
It's not quite the same, but you can have this.
Ooh, pretty.
It looks great on you. It's called a "silent flower".
'Cause dead men tell no tales! Get it?
I've always wanted to say that.
Well? Wasn't that hilarious?
Are you trying to kill me?
Lay off, would you? I just died y'know!
How about a little consideration?
Heaven
21st District
Scallop
Rainbow Frisbee
Yakisoba Skewers
21st District Heaven Station
Porn
Books
Tobacco
Circle K
What's this place? An arcade?
The Fun Zone
Fun for kids, adults, and even high school girls!
Arcade
Yakiniku
Yoga Class
The one and only place in Heaven where you can interact with the world of the living.
How about we have some fun?
It's on me today.
So they've got photo booths in heaven too?
Photo booth? Honestly, you living folk...
Don't treat me like I'm some hick visiting the city.
This is called "Spirit Photoshop".
You can make ordinary Earth pictures into spirit shots.
That sounds like fun!
If you have anyone in mind, go right ahead.
How about Kon?
What's her full name?
Futaba Kon.
Perfect! It just so happens she recently dropped some off to be developed.
Now we buy hands, faces or poses, and place them in any photo you like.
Hey, does it have bunny ears?
Wouldn't bunny ears make for a hilarious picture?
Oh, those kinds of poses are rather expensive.
It's a bit pricey for us common folk.
Yeah, you're right.
Stuff like faces, fists, or will-o’-the-wisps are much cheaper.
No wonder all those pictures look the same.
Okay, I'll go with this hand then.
Now that I've tweaked her picture, I wanna see Kon's reaction.
Yes, of course.
Okay then, you can try these next.
Deposit 100 yen, and you can view the Earth for a brief time.
Hey, I see it!
It's a bath house.
Men
Women
Wow, this is so cool!
Men
Women
Huh? Mosaics?
Private places cannot be viewed.
Oh yeah... whatever happened to my body anyway?
Maruko Hospital
Hey, there's mom.
So you're saying Hotori's going to be like that permanently?
It breaks my heart to say this, but we don't believe she'll ever regain consciousness.
That can't be...
Please, you've got to do something! Please doctor!
Where's dad running off to?
Takeru... Yukiko...
Stop crying, Yukiko.
I said stop crying!
Crying's not gonna bring her back.
Hey, I said stop... crying!
Why? Why did this have to happen?
What did Arashiyama do to deserve this?
It'll be okay. Hotori will get better.
How do you know that for sure?
I just do!
Don't give me that crap!
How can you say that so easily!?
Because!
Becuase Hotori can't die yet! She just can't!
Yes... I see...
You have my condolences.
Thank you. Please excuse me.
I don't care! Bring me that fucking driver's head right now!
I'll run HIM over with my truck!
Just calm down, guys!
Huh!? You trying to defend him?
You're gonna regret it, pal!
Stop it, guys.
Hotori would resent us for that.
Thank you. My business here is finished.
Zenji, please watch over Hotori for me. Please...
Sorry, Uki... there's nothing I can do.
WHY!? Why did you have to die, Arashiyama!?
I... I never got to tell you how I feel...
I still haven't told you that...
...to your face yet!
Why is this happening!?
Please, God! Give Hotori back to us!
She didn't even make it past 16!
Can't you do something about it!?
This is the first time anyone's been this worried about me.
I'll have to be more careful next time...
I'll try to be less of a klutz...
Oh yeah... there won't be a "next time"...
Ever... again...
I wanted to be with them a little longer.
I wanted to live a little longer!
You must've had a wonderful life if you feel that way.
There are people who end their lives of their own volition, you know.
Besides, this place has its good points too.
Everyone comes here eventually.
If you just work hard and be patient, you'll see them again soon.
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
I'm gonna work hard and make lots of money so I can put bunny ears in their pictures.
That's the spirit!
Well then, I'll help you find a job then.
You're young, so how about dressing as an angel and greeting the deceased?
Oh yeah, like those kids?
My son does it too.
Ms. Hotori Arashiyama.
Please report at once to the Heaven Immigration Bureau.
That's me...
What!? I can go back!?
Yes, that seems to be the case.
In your case, your body on Earth is perfectly intact, yes?
Your brain made a miraculous recovery, so you may return if you wish.
Sorry, you can't come with me, mister.
People return just like you every now and then.
You take care now, and don't worry about me.
When I get back, I'll go visit your grave.
Sorry, but once you return, you'll lose your memory of your time here.
Oh, that's too bad...
Well then, hope to see you again next time!
All right, are you ready to go?
Being a guide sounds like a nice job and all,
but really, all I do is just help them come to grips with the reality of their deaths.
It's the saddest, most cruel job there is.
That girl being able to return is like a special blessing to me.
Come on, let's get back to work.
It feels like I just had a really weird dream.
Huh!? What the heck!? Is this Candid Camera or something!?
Doctor, come quick! Ms. Arashiyama's awake!
The city.
A place where people gather, are born and raised, and one day pass on.
But sometimes through the carelessness of the gods,
the lives of the city's residents can be thrown into chaos.
Love, Tatsuno
Yet, still...
Hotori!
Hey, Kon!
I was worried sick, you idiot!
Yet still, the city turns.
So, then once my dad dumped 3,400 yen into the donation box, I woke up.
I mean, it's like "you're worth about 3400 yen".
Sounds about right.
Oh yeah, and about that fountain pendant.
I told them it got crushed when the truck hit me.
Your brain's only good for getting yourself out of trouble, huh?
By the way, Hotori.
I think this mess you caught up in was because an evil spirit got a hold of you.
Huh? Have you gone crazy or something?
Why the heck would you say that out of the blue?
Shut up! Just look at this.
See?
We took this picture together the other day, remember?
Look at your shoulder.
What's that!? That's freaky!
And the town still turns.
And the Town Still Turns
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!