Everyone
has
their place
Everyone
has
their place
Everyone should know their place in this world. Monks are to be monks and commoners are to be commoners. Emperors are to be emperors and retainers are to be retainers. Disregarding one's place is evil.
Says
Priest
Myoue
from Tsuganoo
I do not claim I can ever reach the Pure Lands.
I merely desire to live this life as I am meant to.
from Tsuganoo
I'm sorry I made you tag along and tolerate my pastimes for such a long time.
This is the last of my selfish acts.
You should carry Priest Myoue from now on.
Take good care of things in my absence.
One day I promise I will return with the beginning and end in tow.
I promise.
Wait for me,
Myoue.
Thus spake Myoue, the priest
Celery
Juice
Hey, that's mine!
I ain't treating you! Cough up my dough!
Hey! You!
Answer me!
Come on!
You're gonna pay for this.
In retrospect, I've been down on my luck for as long as I can remember.
Let's take the day off.
Yuck!
Surely a single can of juice is nothing to get worked up about.
More importantly, why is one of us skipping the meeting to waste time?
This is a yearly occurrence for him.
He must feel he trained in vain with the utter lack of donations.
That's precisely the reason.
He doesn't want us to see him while he's not going at full steam.
It's his own fault if he gets his hopes up and is delegated to the holding track.
Now you're being hard on him.
He always looks at me like only he is suffering.
Are we not on the same train?
Well, not really, but that annoys me even more.
He cannot return by now, just as he never could.
That reminds me of a story.
There was a certain dog that kept waiting for his master.
He just kept waiting for his master's return in the same spot.
But his master had died already.
The dog kept waiting and waiting, unaware of his master's death,
until at long last he tired of waiting and died himself.
What a tragic story.
Can't you feel the tears welling up?
Did the dog have no legs?
No voice to call his master?
Ears to listen for replies?
What if he did?
Then he was a stupid dog.
Why do you say so?
Surely his master never told him to die.
Hachiko
He should have gotten on with life at some point.
I see. An opinion that befits you.
I have my own opinion regarding this story.
Was the dog truly waiting for his master?
If so, would he not have acted differently?
But if the dog was waiting precisely for what came in the end...
Silence! Don't lampoon the dog's devotion! That's depressing!
Oh my, absit omen.
Who knows what the dog really wanted?
Wanna get on the train, then?
Oh, Inuyama! 'Sup?
What'cha doin' here?
Taking Myoue out for a walk?
Just kiddin'!
Come on, don't be mad, Myoue!
You waiting for some chick?
Drop it.
What are you doing here?
Just my little sociology excursion.
I'm on my way home now, though.
Did you come to welcome me, Inuyama?
That's so nice of you! Thanks!
What now?
Nothing.
I feel like she is somehow connected to the remnants of my memory from centuries past,
and yet she feels completely unconnected as well.
In the end, I keep her close out of an inability to tell.
What's for dinner?
Fish!
Come on! I want meat!
We got bananas at the library today!
Want to swap seats?
No, thanks.
We'll be fine! Let me!
No!
Bishamaru
the Peerless
A fiery spirit and punch!
A breathtaking adventure!
Premiere
Hey!
Can you please shut up?
I'm so gonna kill you...
You told me to shut up.
What the hell?!
Almost everything's sold out!
The train has departed again,
and on goes my long time of waiting.
It feels sad, sort of.
Yeah.
Hey, didn't it ever occur to you to get on that train and see if it takes you home?
Oh, man! It never did!
You can be pretty smart, Myoue!
Can it!
I'll try next time it turns up.
Not now though.
I've got plenty to do.
Oh, really?
Can I go home now?
You can't!
Can't you go to the forbidden place alone?
No! You'll never hear the end of it if you don't go!
Aun are waiting for us!
We promised we'd see them.
Myoue!
Yeah, yeah.
And be cool.
Of course.
I think Aun are really cute! Aren't they?
They're the first...
relatives, or family, for me.
But they aren't human like you. You okay with that?
Sure.
Normally that'd be relevant when accepting your family...
Was there nothing easier you could've picked for a name?
Like Tarou or Jirou or something.
Those sound like my grandpa's name.
Huh?
That isn't even true!
I think it's cool as heck.
"A" and "Un" stand for the beginning and the end.
Take this!
Keep the change!
Damn! Wait, Koto!
There are things to regret no matter what we do.
Some have their beliefs and decide things from their gut.
I live my life feeling that pride is harmful.
I have until now and will in the days to come.
Even then, I will wait.
I trust a day will dawn for me where all will be brighter than it is now.
Wait! Lemme give you a good beating!
Like hell!
Damn! Wait!
I'll keep waiting.
To be continued.