Enjoy!
Excellent!
Well done, princesse Haruka!
Le thé de l'après-midi lesson is achevé!
Hooray!
Your practice has paid off.
I see. So you've been taking lessons like these to become princesses.
Tch, tch, tch!
You're still far from becoming a Grand Princess!
Come on!
Aroma...
Vous are still but a trainee, non?
Vous failed le test once before, non?
Trainee?
Despite his looks,
he's a butler tasked with everything from serving Prince Kanata to official government work!
Or rather, a trainee!
A butler trainee?
And I'm a maid trainee!
So after all that high-and-mighty talk,
you're just a trainee?
I accomplished the critical duty of finding the Precures!
I could ace the test now with my eyes closed!
Can vous, now?
I can.
D'accord!
Then vous shall take le test again.
Your task...
will be to earn la princesse Haruka's approval by serving as her butler all day tomorrow.
No sweat!
Hey, I want to take the maid test, too!
Then vous shall be judged on housework!
Now then...
Puissance des fées lesson!
Wait, what happened?
Vous will see tomorrow matin!
I'll start by waking her up with black tea!
Followed by a morning study period and a refined lunch!
Then equestrian practice...
Hmph, it's perfect!
This time, I'll be the perfect butler!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Spread wings... prinshesh...
Good morning, Princess Haruka.
Huh?
I've prepared an early morning tea for you!
A boy?!
A boy?
Ouch!
What're you—
It's me, Aroma!
This is how I woke up!
Where's the boy?!
False alarm, sorry.
Guess I had a weird dream.
An Aromatic Transformation!
Aroma's Butler Test!
Run for it!
So that's what her puissance des fées lesson did...
Way to wake the whole dorm up.
So, Perf should also be...
Found you!
You weren't in your rooms, so I looked everywhere!
Are you... Perf?
Shirogane, dorm mother.
Who might this child be?
Uh, she's...
A child actress I know!
She's playing a trainee maid as her next role, so she wanted to learn to clean and stuff...
right?
Perf?
Phew, we made it out without getting caught...
For now, can start off with some breakfast?
I'm starving...
The time for breakfast is already over.
Huh?
It is now time to study.
What?
We have to follow the schedule.
But we're outside!
Not to worry!
Dreamy Hill
Library
That's unladylike.
Not my fault!
To vacuum, you must start from the corners and carefully work your way in.
Otherwise...
well, take a look.
Miss Shirogane's taking this seriously...
Perf was supposed to be tested, not trained...
Be sure to wring the cloth.
Okay!
But I think she needs this more.
It is now time for lunch.
Finally!
I already made reservations!
How butlery of you!
That's nuts!
Aroma, do you have money?
You're going to pay, of course.
I'm so sorry!
Full bloom yumminess!
Eating in a place like this?
Aroma, sit down! Let's eat together.
A butler can't sit at the same table as his master!
But...
That girl's not giving him any food!
Don't point!
Hey, don't be a meanie!
Thanksh for the food!
Your manners are far too poor for a princess!
Sorry...
And now we're behind schedule...
At this rate...
Okay!
Aroma, what else did you want to do?
We'll do it all!
I promise I'll keep up and help you be the best butler ever!
You got it!
There's still plenty left to do!
Let's get started!
Okay!
First, equestrian practice!
Right!
Ride naturally!
Next is a garden party!
Right!
Welcome to Princess Haruka's garden party!
Garden party?
Looks like a picnic to me.
Please everyone, enjoy!
On the double!
On the double?
Oh no, look at the time!
Wha?!
My apologies, but I simply must be off!
Adieu!
Perf, clean this up, please!
Good luck, Bro!
Is this part of his test?
Maybe?
Next, a leisurely shopping trip!
Right!
A dignified stroll!
An elegant café break!
Right!
Dancing!
Piano!
Right!
Movies!
Next...
Right!
Is something wrong?
I'm going for a stroll.
Then I shall accompany—
Dear me.
Lock!
I shall be the one to guide you...
toward the despair your Key desires.
I like chivalrous vassals.
Come with me.
I'd be honored.
Curse you, Lock!
You dare steal my thunder!
Pr-Princess Twilight!
Aroma, good work today.
Now, I shall announce the results of ton test!
Oh, I'm nervous too!
So? Did I pass this time?
Sorry to say, but not this time.
But why not?
He was working so hard!
Aroma, vous have not changed since ton last test.
Vous still lack what a butler needs most.
Do vous really not know?
No, I don't!
Aroma!
Aroma...
Hairpin style!
Why?
Even when things seemed grim, I was a perfect butler!
What the heck could I be lacking?
Madam!
Look out!
Crossing signals are there for a reason.
Are you hurt?
No...
Is he all right?
Yes, Madam, he's perfectly fine.
Oh, thank goodness!
Th-Thank you for saving me!
Um, who are you?
I am the butler of the lady before you.
Wha?!
Do these bags... belong to her?
Oh, worry not.
B-But it's a butler's duty to protect his master's belongings!
There's more to a butler's duty than that.
You should avoid jumping into traffic in the future.
Good day.
There's more to it?
Thank you, Oikawa.
I knew you could save him.
It's a pleasure to live up to your expectations.
Even if I don't say a word,
you always act exactly how I'd wish.
It's quite the lifesaver!
Act as she'd wish?
Can we start off with some breakfast?
Aroma, sit down! Let's eat together.
We'll do it all!
I promise I'll keep up!
But I...
Aroma!
Thank goodness I found you!
Haruka...
I brought this!
It's important for butlers, right?
Thank you...
Sorry.
I wound up holding you back.
I know you tried really hard,
so I guess I'm not good enough.
Aroma?
What's wrong?
Now then, to the mansion?
Yes.
How about her?
She'd certainly bring forth a superb despair.
Very well.
Do as you wish.
Show me your dream, 'kay?
Madam!
I'll serve you for life!
Huh?
Oikawa?
An expert servant will also do.
Continue, Lock.
Well, if you insist.
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
A Dyspairvil!
Haruka!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Dyspair?
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dys!
A butler Dyspairvil? It couldn't be—
Oikawa?
Oikawa!
Madam!
Aroma, look after her!
Got it!
'Kay, you're right on time, Cure Flora!
Lock! Twilight!
Dyspairvil, entertain our guest.
Dyspairvil!
Dys! Pair!
Ow...
Dys!
Pair!
Dyspairvil!
Hide here!
Flora!
Vil!
I can't do anything to help her!
No, there's one thing I can do!
Oh?
Dyspairvil.
'Kay, looks like your pal turned tail and ran.
Poor girl.
Get crushed alone, 'kay?
You're wrong.
Aroma didn't run away!
Aroma's a butler!
Even when we're apart, our hearts are one!
We both fight to protect others!
How futile.
Get her, Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil.
Dyspairvil...
You'll make a lovely pressed flower once we're through.
Minami! Kirara!
Farewell, self-proclaimed princess.
Dyspair!
Fun's over, princess!
You're dealing with us now!
Mermaid! Twinkle!
Are you all right, Flora?
Yeah!
Aroma told us you were in danger.
Totally!
Gotta hand it to him for running all the way to the academy!
Well, he is a butler!
Dyspairvil...
Guess we gotta deal with this guy first.
Let's go, Mermaid!
Right!
Dyspairviiiil!
Luna!
Shine, O Moon!
Precure!
Full Moon Humming!
Dyspair!
He's quick!
Then I'll slow him down!
Ice!
Rage, O frost!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Dys!
Dyspairvil!
Now's our chance!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
That will do for today.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Your madam awaits you.
Oikawa!
Thanks for today, Aroma!
You saved me back there!
Haruka...
Hm?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
During the test, the only thing I could
think about was how I could prove myself.
I didn't consider your feelings at all.
And even then, you still tried so hard for me!
What I lacked was the ability to respect your wishes.
Aroma...
Bravo, Aroma!
Vous finally figured it out.
Vous are now un pas closer to becoming a butler!
Does that mean he passed?
Huh?
Let's see...
It's fine!
I'll go back to square one and train with a new perspective!
I'll train too!
Then let's race to see if I can
become a Grand Princess first!
Tch, tch, tch!
I'm certain I won't lose to you!
You tryin' to say something to your master?
You're not my master anymore!
Hey, Aroma!
It seems he's still suited to being a trainee.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Wow, the beach is so pretty! Right, Minami?
I've spent many summers here.
I've made friends as well!
Wait, the dolphins are your friends?
Its name is Kina.
Could that person be...
He is!
Dear brother! I missed you!
Go! Princess Precure:
A Vow to the Sea!
Minami's Dear Treasure!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Aichi Prefecture - Saki (Age 8)
Wakayama Prefecture - Tomoka (Age 7)