An ambush?!
I will give you credit for making it this far.
We are here to take back our friend and the top-secret ninja art scroll.
If you get in our way...
we will show you no mercy!
How dare you traipse into our home and take such a high-handed tone!
You really do sound like a spoiled little princess.
Will you slap me across the face with a wad of bills next?
Let's do this!
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
It sounds like your friends have safely made their way inside.
My friends?
Is this going according to your plan, Ms. Suzune?
No matter. You're going to be more entertaining, after all.
No!
If you lose you'll die, right, Haruka?
It's all right. There's no possibility of us losing.
I'm not so sure.
Oh, you can still talk, Ms. Suzune?
You'd do well not to underestimate Hanzo Academy or Kiriya.
Every time a student loses,
they examine the reason why...
and pinpoint what they did right and improve on it.
They do it without fail.
Then, you're saying that we fought against Hanzo Academy in order to develop their girls?
You were my best ninja students.
I had to have opponents who would measure up to you as well.
What's your objective here?
Whatever your purpose is, Ms. Suzune, I owe you for rescuing me from Hell.
Haruka!
Relax. The next time we meet, Hibari, I will make you my puppet for real.
I'll deal with her!
The rest of you, please go on ahead!
No way!
We're not going to leave you here by yourself!
You wouldn't be holding me in contempt, would you?
No. All the more reason for this.
Battle sphere!
Wha—
Ikaruga!
Let's hurry on ahead.
Hey, Yagyu!
Ikaruga will not be beaten.
You're right. What good will it do if I don't believe in her?
Okay, let's go, Asuka!
R-Right!
Castle Showdown
It's like a maze in here.
Given how huge this place is,
it's even worse than our school.
All we can do now is just keep going on!
U-Um... Is it true that you came from Hanzo Academy?
Why did you become a dark ninja?
You've been to Ninja Island, right?
"Hang in there. Super-ninja or bust!"
You're one who wrote that on the ceiling beam, right?
How do you know?
I don't know. But when I saw you, I suddenly saw that writing.
Hang in there. Super-ninja or bust!
Hazy though it may be,
I'm impressed that you were trained enough to acquire the second sight technique.
That's my master for you.
I-I never had that technique taught to me.
Ninjutsu is a skill of the mind.
As the mind grows, techniques develop,
and the strength of those techniques becomes the strength of the mind.
Eh?
Ms. Suzune, what are you—
Ms. Suzune?
If there is something you want, stake your life to go get it.
That's what it is to be a ninja.
Something I want?
Drawing me inside a sphere for a one-on-one.
You seem pretty sure of yourself.
You truly are disagreeable in every way!
You've always been that way!
Always?
That mansion up on the high hill...
Those of us who were poor grew up with that mansion looking down on us.
A great deal has been donated via NPO contributions.
That's the girl... from up there...
It is the duty of big business to save the less fortunate children of the world.
My parents never got any help raising me.
They sacrificed so much... even their lives!
Virtuous ninjas? Please, don't make me laugh!
The only "virtue" you possess is hypocrisy!
You and your family are an example of that!
Secret ninja art! Niflhelm!
Those were direct hits!
The love of your family, who loved you so much, they gave their lives for you...
All the suffering I've lived through would've been worth it if I'd had but a fraction of that.
H-Hold on, what are you saying?
Regardless...
I can't afford to be beaten here!
Wh-What is this?
It's no use!
A trap?
Katsu! Yagyu!
Stay there, Asuka!
I hate to say this, Asuka, but we've gotta leave this to you now.
But...
It won't be good for them if they let any more of us further up.
Katsu!
Go!
Yagyu!
You dummy, what are you waiting for?! Hurry!
You guys...
Aw shucks, we let one of them get upstairs, didn't we?
The trap didn't trigger in time.
That Asuka has quicker feet than I anticipated.
Huh, like it doesn't concern you.
So you are lurking around here!
That's okay. I wanted to take my revenge against her anyway!
I guess I'll take care of this one right away, then.
How nice of you to say!
I never liked you from the moment I first saw you!
Where is Hibari?
Don't you ignore me!
Katsuragi...
Yeah.
Wha—
Battle sphere!
Heh, it bugs me that I'm copying Ikaruga, but still...
Doesn't matter to me.
I'll just defeat you anyway.
Hmph! Can't ignore me any longer, can you?
I protect what I want to protect. That's all.
Why is it that you want to fight me?
Until I defeat you, I won't be happy with myself!
I can't allow myself to be beaten by anyone!
I'll give you one word of warning.
Warning?
If you talk while fighting, you'll bite your tongue.
Who asked you?!
Those eyes...
Fear, pity, anger...
All fatal distractions.
Divorce yourself from emotion.
Stay cool at all times, and you'll survive.
Why is this? When I look into those eyes,
it's like I'm touching something I haven't—
What are you standing there for?!
What is this upsetting sensation?
Upsetting? I used to have feelings like that?
What are you babbling to yourself about?! Come fight me!
I don't need you to tell me! I'll fight you!
Secret ninja art! Thrust!
Come on!
I won't lose...
I'm not gonna be beaten either!
Senran Kagura
What, do you think that I don't have anything to protect?
I do too!
Entrance Ceremony
Serpentine
Academy
for Girls
I, too...
have something to protect!
I know.
Wh-What? What do you think you know?
I don't know what it is you want to protect. Not interested either.
But if that is what you are fighting for...
You mean, people not ignoring me?
Otherwise, I would just end up denying myself.
That's more like it!
Wait, why am I acting so pleased?
Secret ninja art! Walküre!
Not bad.
You too.
One more floor to the top.
Just one, huh?
Homura!
I was expecting more of you.
Is Hibari all right?
She's in a cell. We caught her eavesdropping.
I knew Hibari was trying to get the scroll back by herself.
If you want to go any further,
..you'll have to defeat me first...
granddaughter of Hanzo!
Battle sphere!
I won't submit to you!
Let's see what you can do.
What a shame, I turned back when I heard something, and just as I expected...
Haruka, please, let me out of here.
What will you do if I do?
I have to tell everyone that if the Serpentine girls lose in a fight, that curse will kill them!
So what?
Eh?
Unless you beat us, you'll be unable to attain your goal, right?
But this doesn't have anything to do with a ninja's mission.
It has nothing to do with it, all right.
Eh?
This is the only place we have, after all.
I told you before, remember?
Everyone came here for different reasons.
Is this a sanctuary from Hell for you too, Haruka?
My father is the director of a large hospital.
Your father?
Public reputation aside, he was an awful man,
hushing malpractice suits with money left over from tax evasion.
He only came home once in a while.
He always gave the same reason.
Instead of taking out her frustrations, my mother doted on me.
Doted? No, it wasn't that.
I was simply my mother's dress-up doll.
Oh, how adorably gorgeous.
Even after I was in middle school, my mother's abnormal smothering continued.
I just kept quiet and put up with it.
But little by little, I think something inside me broke too.
I'll burn everything down, and that will be the end of it.
Once it's over, I'll be free.
I take a dim view of children playing with fire.
That was when Ms. Suzune scouted me.
She has a keen eye.
We aren't afraid of dying.
After all, we've all but died once already.
Why?
Why don't you try me out first,
to see if you all can really beat us?
What's wrong?
Come on, take a shot at me!
Ninja morph!
Yagyu, I'll do my best, all by myself!
I won't make you worry about me anymore!
Battle sphere!
Oh, my.
Haruka, will your Entity Crest extinguish right after you lose a fight?
Well, there're some subtleties to it.
Huh?
The Crest is activated only upon
.the caster's acknowledgment.
Sometimes, it's hard to tell if
.someone's won or lost, right?
So it's just a matter of preventing the Crest from activating!
How? Like I said earlier...
The notion of you being able to beat us...
is laughable, no?
Nope.
Winning isn't the most important thing.
It's not being beaten, whether by an opponent... or...
by yourself!
Secret ninja art... Come to me...
I won't fall for the same trick twice!
Wha—
H-How careless of me...
Everyone... Listen to me, everyone!
Hibari!
Don't fight them!
Don't fight them?
When a Serpentine student loses in battle, they lose their life!
They lose...
...their life?
That's the curse placed upon them.
That's why you mustn't fight them!
Oh, no.
What powerful telepathy.
Was that really from Hibari?
Homura!
Are you cursed to die if you lose?
It's not a curse so much as an Entity Crest, to be exact.
You're conscious of that while you're fighting, Homura?
Of course I am. If I fail, I die.
That is the way it ought to be for a ninja.
No way... What you're saying...
is plain wrong!
How inhumane!
It's all right. There's no chance of us losing.
Are you serious?
Don't worry.
How can you go about things that way?
You've gotta be kidding!
Good grief, who asked her to go and do that?
Hibari! Hibari is safe.
Hey, I'm still here, you know!
I just got done telling you not to ignore me, didn't I?!
Wh-What?
I can't afford to waste any more time on you.
Catch the man who is up on the top level!
He's the only one who can release the curse!
The scroll is up there too!
You are such a blabbermouth.
Secret ninja art! Death Kiss!
This time, I'll turn you into my puppet for real.
Secret ninja art!
Phoenix Flame Dash, One!
Tornado Spindel!
We gotta get up there, somehow.
Hey, how do I get to the top?
What good will it do you to go there?
We're ninjas. We're ready to take lives if we have to.
But it's not right to allow our own lives be controlled by others, is it?
It's impossible.
The way is completely closed off.
Who moved those?
All right! Let's go, Yagyu!
I'm heading to the basement.
The basement?
Hibari's voice was coming from below us. I can tell.
Okay. You go take care of Hibari.
H-How did you get that kind of power?
Ninjutsu is a skill of the mind.
There is a greater evil that we should all be really fighting.
An evil that would use forbidden arts to compel you to fight.
A greater evil?
When I felt that, my pride as a virtuous ninja gave me this strength.
In other words, you virtuous ninjas are a soft bunch, huh?
That TV show that you said you saw...
it was to announce to the world that he was adopting a child.
Adopted? You don't mean, you're...
He made it seem like he was charitably taking in an orphaned girl.
In fact, he did it simply to have a successor to the ninja family line in place of his less gifted son.
All I have to my name is my mission to live as a ninja.
I know nothing of this familial affection you speak of.
Why... Why are you telling me this?
How am I going to keep on hating you?!
Next Episode Preview
I will overcome whatever trials and tribulations
so I can offer my protection, together with everyone else!
I won't submit to you!
The final episode, "Top-Secret Ninja Art."
Top-Secret Ninja Art
Come get it like your life depended on it.