Sis, is that you?
I'm home!
Feel free to leap into my arms!
No thanks.
Come on, I'm finally back home.
So boring.
taikutsu na madobe ni
Sitting bored by the back window,
fukikomu kaze ni
A breeze blew through the room
kao wo shikameta no wa
The reason I screwed up my eyes
terekusasa no uragaeshi
Was to hide how embarrassed I was
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
aimai ni unazuku tenohira no kyou
I gave a faint nod from the edge of my palm
egaiteru jibun wa sukoshi oogesa de
The "me" I was trying to be was a bit more than I was
nani ka kawarisou na ki ga shiteiru yo
I get the feeling that something is going to change soon
kokoro ni yobikakeru kimi no sei da ne
You reached out to touch my heart; it must be because of you
kumorizora nozoita yokan
I had a feeling, looking into the clouds
te wo nobasou itsu yori mo chikaradzuyoi yuuki de
I reached out my hand, with a stronger courage than I'd ever had
hikari mo kage mo mada tookute
The light and the dark are still so far away
sore demo bokura wa
But even though they are
yasashisa no riyuu ga shiritai
We still want to know how people could be so kind
ima wa dare no namae demo nai
Now it doesn't matter whose name it may be
kagayaki no kanata he
Beyond the horizon's light,
zenbu kako ni naru mae ni
Before it all becomes the past,
mitsuke ni ikou
Let's go and find out
What Everyone Needs
What EveryoneNeeds
A present from South America?
Yeah. You wanted one, right?
Not really.
It's pretty rare for you to watch TV.
What about the paper?
I don't feel like thinking.
You look like you have some free time.
But I do have plans.
Plans?
Like what?
Napping.
I know a place where you can get 5000 yen just for sitting around.
How about it?
Want to do it? Maybe not?
Okay, that's settled then!
I'll tell them you'll do it.
Here.
You'll need it while you're working.
Hello, Oreki residence.
Oh, Satoshi-kun? It's been a while!
Yeah, I just got back.
Houtarou? He's here.
Just one moment.
Houtarou! Satoshi-kun's on the phone!
Houtarou, did you finish reading that book I lent you?
If you're done with it, can I get it back?
Mind if I come over to pick it up?
After work, sure.
Work? You?!
What's gotten into you?!
Nothing really.
Sis's friend can't lifeguard the public pool today, so I'm going in her place.
Oh, your sister.
I see.
It's hard to imagine you breaking a sweat.
I have to go now.
Got it.
I'll head over later to throw
some cold water on you.
Whatever. See you.
Bye.
Houtarou!
Hey, we came.
I didn't think all three of you would come.
I called them up as soon as I got off the phone with you.
I told them they'd never get a chance to see it again.
Is this what you were talking about?
Right!
Houtarou, working!
I'm not really impressed.
Well, it isn't every day we go to the pool. Let's have fun!
I guess, since we're here...
Hey, you!
Quit starin' at my woman!
Come on, stop that!
I wasn't...
Please calm down, sir!
What's up with him?
I pray I don't have to deal with them...
Okay, here I go!
Here!
Okay!
Here.
Chitanda-san! Do something funny!
Sorry, Chii-chan.
Okay! Penalty game for Chitanda-san!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Here we go!
My turn!
Here I go!
Hey.
It's my shift now.
Go take a break.
Oreki-san!
Would you like to eat lunch together?
I could've made a better lunch if you'd told me earlier.
Tell that to Houtarou.
Why?
Because we're talking about Houtarou, a sloth in human clothing!
Suddenly he feels like working!
We can't pass up seeing that.
Right, Houtarou?
It's a lot of fun getting together like this, though!
Well, I guess.
Either way, they just don't mix.
What doesn't?
The pool and Houtarou!
Right!
Don't be so mean...
Swimming trunks and Oreki don't mix either.
Yeah, yeah!
And the sun and Houtarou!
The sea and Oreki!
Summer and Houtarou!
Come on, stop that!
Right, Oreki-san?
Now then, why don't we get back to the pool?
Yeah. I'll clean up the trash.
I'll put the chairs back.
What? You want another one?
Well, okay then.
Let's go get you another.
What a surprise.
Yeah.
How's the job?
Normal, I guess.
I'd like to try it myself some day.
They're so fast!
Maybe he wants to be a swimmer when he grows up.
We might have a future gold
medalist in that pool right now.
Who knows?
It's a simple question of whether he has the ability to or not.
If he's special, then he will.
If he's normal, then he won't.
Do you want to be special?
Not really.
Either way, I'm just a normal person.
You are special, Oreki-san!
At least to me!
Fukube-san and Mayaka-san are special too!
Everyone I meet is special to me!
That's your personal opinion.
I'm talking about the public opin-
What's wrong with a personal opinion?
You don't have to worry about being special or normal compared to everyone else!
It doesn't matter who it is.
So long as they think you're special, then you're special!
Um... I...
See you later!
Hakuro
When the gloom heavens,
And the gloom glitters white.
Hyouka
You are special, Oreki-san!
What's wrong with a personal opinion?
Oreki-kun, it's my shift now.
Take a break.
Um... Oreki-san?
Um...
There's something I'm curious about...
It's in your area of expertise.
Do you remember that woman with the red swimsuit?
When we had finished eating, she had something white on her left ear.
But it's not on her ear anymore.
How did you notice something like that?
I just saw it by chance.
So? What about it?
What do you mean, "What about it?"
What if it were an earring or a stub?
If someone steps on it, they might get hurt!
Oreki-san, could you help us look for it?
Over the entire pool area? Are you serious?
Are you sure it was on her ear?
Yes.
Then we should ask her about it before we start looking.
I'd like to, but...
It's a bit hard to ask...
It's not like you're asking anything weird.
It'll be fine.
Then why don't you ask her?
No thanks.
Please, Oreki-san!
Oreki, you're a lifeguard, right?
Come on, Houtarou.
I'm curious!
What? That guy who was yelling?
Now that's just troublesome.
I don't want to make a scene, so could you look for it discreetly?
But I can't do it alone.
I'll have the other lifeguards look around the poolsides.
Could I get you to check inside the pools?
I'll help you too!
Me too, of course!
Well, guess I will too.
Thanks.
Okay. How should we look for it?
We might want to split up and look for it.
Good idea. What do you think, Oreki-san?
Up to you.
Hey, could you at least pretend to be motivated?
That's right! Otherwise you're getting paid for nothing.
At least decide how we should split up.
Fine, I'll do it.
Chitanda-san and Mayaka handle the steps.
Houtarou gets the water slide!
And I'll take the diving board!
What do you think?
Okay!
Sounds good to me.
Good luck.
Houtarou.
Is this job something you have to do?
Who knows?
What, you never gave it any thought?
What's your motto even for then?
Well, sorry.
Right. There you go.
At least complain or something.
You have to respond when people talk to you.
You're boring otherwise.
See you in a bit, then.
Oreki.
Quit slacking.
I'm not slacking.
I found a marble, so I came here to throw it away.
Oh, really?
I'm getting depressed just looking at you.
Frankly, it's annoying.
Then stop looking at me.
Before, I'd only get pissed off looking at you.
That was annoying too.
You're annoying either way, so at the very least, be more like the old you.
It was better when you had some fight in you.
Better, huh?
Did you find it?
No, but we might not need to look for it.
Does that mean you've figured something out?
It's okay.
Chitanda, did you really see an earring?
Not clearly...
I just remember that there was something white on one of her ears.
If it was only on one side, then it might be a stub.
No.
I'm not asking about the kind of accessory.
I'm asking if what she saw was an accessory in the first place.
What do you mean?
Look at that.
If she were wearing something on her ear,
she wouldn't just hit her ears like that.
Which means?
Whatever was on her ear had to get on there without her noticing.
But then what was on her ear?
Well...
Satoshi, could you carry Ibara in your arms?
Sure.
In a place like this?!
Then what about Chitanda?
The problem isn't who's holding me!
It'll be like I'm a little kid! It's embarrassing!
Well, that's because I want to see how a little kid would do it.
And why do I have to do that anyway?
To prove my theory.
By theory, you mean this case?
Yeah.
I don't mind.
Okay, fine! I'll do it!
You're pretty strong, Chitanda-san.
What's that supposed to mean?
I didn't mean it like that!
That's just the way it looks.
I thought so.
What do you mean?
Her hands.
You'd usually put them on the shoulders.
Hey, can I get down now?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Look at that.
I saw that woman holding that little kid earlier.
I'm guessing they're mother and son.
Now, what would happen if she held that kid while he was holding ice cream?
I see!
The ice cream could touch her ear just like that!
Exactly.
Then it's not on her ear now because...
...it came off while she was swimming, or someone told her.
Something like that.
Um... Oreki-san!
What now?
Um... I...
I think that how you do that is amazing!
Flattery's not going to get you anything.
Okay!
It's been a while since we've seen you so cynical.
Is that bad?
Definitely bad.
It's hard to know what to do when you're not.
Oh, right! I haven't had a chance to thank you yet.
Oreki-san, thank you very much.
Sorry to cause you so much trouble.
It's fine...
Chii-chan, don't!
I'm the one who said it could have been an earring or stub.
Sorry, Oreki.
It's okay. Just stop it.
Alright! Now that that's over, I'm getting kind of hungry.
Maybe I'll get some ice cream-
What about ice cream-
Oh! Hyouka!
Fuku-chan!
Yesterday, you said you'd definitely have your manuscript done by today!
So, is it done?
Well, it's kind of done, but not really...
That means it's not done yet!
Right?
That's one way to put it...
It's the only way to put it!
Fuku-chan, we're going back, and you're finishing your manuscript!
I'm not letting you go until you're completely done with it today!
There's just a bit left to do!
I can finish it on my own!
You think I'll believe that?
Chii-chan, Oreki, sorry!
We're going back now.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye-
I hope they can finish that manuscript.
Who knows?
Well, they say life is good when someone needs you.
Best of luck either way.
When you need someone...
It looks like I needed you today.
Thank you again.
Seriously. It was a real pain.
That was mean.
But, you know...
that might not be so bad.
No, nothing.
Oh, by the way, Oreki-san,
how did you know that the white thing was ice cream?
Oh, that? That was easy.
There isn't anything white around here but that.
Well, I guess there's one other thing.
I think I should go now too.
Have fun with the rest of your work.
S-Sure.
Hey!
It's your shift now.
Sure...
What a pain.
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep
mebaeteta nukumori atatakakute tomadou
I felt a growing warmth; it felt so nice that I couldn’t think
konna kimochi wo mada anata wa wakaranai no
But these feelings I have, you still don’t know they’re here
sono shisen ni wa imi nante betsu ni nai hazu
I don’t think there’s anything special in how you look at me
datte tomodachi ni shiteru no to onaji
It’s the same way you look at your friends
akegata ni kieteku chiisana negaiboshi
Fading into the dawn, my tiny wishing star
yoru no aida de no mahou
Magic that lasts only the night
konya koi ni kawaru
Tonight’s the night we fall in love
shiawase na yume de aou
Let’s meet in our sweet dreams
kitto ne mitsukete ne
Please come and find me
madoromi no yakusoku
A promise for when we sleep