No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You don't need to, really!
People are eating, so don't do it!
It's better to see it with your own eyes than to hear about it!
Now, see for yourself!
It's great, isn't it?
Aisaka is finally back.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, why are you girls screaming?
Speaking of which, Valentine's is nearly here.
I doubt these festive youngsters will listen to anything I say.
Oh, Valentine's...
I nearly forgot about it.
Stop pretending! Those lies won't work on me!
Miss?
You plan to make out while I'm not paying attention, right?
Doing such indecent things at school...
You know, it's really pointless to give or receive chocolate at school.
School is a place to learn.
W-We're being lectured by Haruta...
Huh? Am I wrong?
Then what's school for?
Health care and PE, right?
Oh, yeah.
Takasu-kun, Aisaka-san, please come to the interview room after school.
My Silky Love
nijuu yojikan zutto
Every hour of the day
My Silky Love
kimi no koto omoutabi
whenever I think about you
My Silky Love
modokashii kono kimochi
these impatient feelings
My Silky Love
tada afurekaetteku
just overflow
suki to ieba kantan nanoni
It would be easier if I just tell you that I love you
kimi ga mae ni kichauto
but when you appear in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
my personality stands up and interferes
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku nanoni
That's just the way I am
donna ganbattemitemo kabe wa kuzusenai
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
I want you to realize my feelings
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
That's why I always gaze at you with the message of
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
"I love you"
saidai no yuuki de
with all of my courage!
yaburesouna SILK no HEART
My heart made of silk feels like it's about to rip apart
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
After meeting you, I finally realized
ai ni wa bukiyou dattandatte
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
My scars from love that I've almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashitano kyun to
have started to ache all of a sudden
itsuka wa watashirashiku suki to
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
I must tell you that I love you, or else I'll become even weaker
The Road We Must Advance on
Takasu-kun, you still can't turn in your career assessment?
And Aisaka-san, you haven't even turned one from first semester in...
I'm sorry, I'm still discussing it with my family.
Your mother wants you to go to college, right?
Yasuko has-
My mother has always been a hard worker, but sometimes she pushes herself too much.
I don't want to be a burden anymore, so I'm not planning on going to college.
That is what I wish for.
So Aisaka-san, what's your reason for not turning it in?
I come from a rich family, so I won't ever need to work.
That's also why I don't need to study. Plus there's nothing I want to do.
Seriously, you two...
Even if I don't go to college-
I understand. It's just that you'll be on your own for the rest of your life.
You can't just blame stuff on others. No one will take responsibility for you.
That's why I want you two to carefully think it through.
Takasu-kun, you haven't gone against your mother's intentions, have you?
Sign: Interview room
After you've finished filling it out, bring it to the staff room.
The rest of my life, huh?
What are you-
Hey, that's the career assessment form-
Hey!
I don't need something like that.
It's impossible for me to think about my future.
I can't even recognize myself right now.
I've always, always denied my present self.
"Why is this happening?"
"What should I do to avoid it?"
How can I know what I want to do later when I don't even know what I want to do right now?
There's one thing I want to do!
I want to fall in love normally!
Hey, what's wrong?
Y-You don't even have someone - no...
Someone I like? I don't even know who it is.
I wanted to be born into a normal family, then raised as a normal good girl,
then have a normal encounter with a guy and become friends normally.
I wanted to fall in love normally like that...
Why are you using past tense?
I told you, it's impossible.
I mean, the conditions are already wrong.
I'm not normal at all.
What do you mean by "normal"?
What's right and what's wrong?
Who's there to decide on those things?
Hold it, why are you suddenly lecturing me?
Oh, no... I didn't mean that...
Where are you going?
What about the career assessments?
I'm going home, I don't give a damn about that.
Taiga...
3. I wish to find a job.
Excuse me.
I told you already...
Didn't I already refuse?
I've always been-
But Kawashima, think about it one more-
I don't have time to think about it anymore.
Bye, I'm going home.
Wait, Kawashima-kun!
What are you doing standing there?
Hurry up and chase her!
Hurry!
What do you want to do to my shoe?
Huh?
Give it back.
You have a shoe fetish?
Gross.
Hey-
I can't believe this.
Why are you trying to set a record for long throws at a time like this?
I said I'm sorry.
Hey...
Why were you called to the staff room?
I said I wouldn't model the school uniform for a school information pamphlet.
Why did you refuse? Isn't that your speciality?
I just don't want to do it.
I don't even know how much longer I'll be at this school.
Don't tell me that your fight with Kushieda-
No, a trivial person like Kushieda Minori couldn't have an influence on my life.
Then why did you say that?
To be honest, I planned to leave after first semester.
News about the stalker thing has died down too.
I've never heard you mention-
I decided I wanted to stay here a bit longer.
I wanted to be with you guys tomorrow, or even the day after tomorrow...
Then why?
I watched Taiga get hurt and understood her pain.
I thought that, since I understood her, I'd save her if no one else did, or something like that...
Now I realize that everything would sort itself out if I left.
Kawashima, you-
Wait!
Why now of all-
Taiga? I'm really bu-
What about the shop?
My part-time job at the cake store too...
They even made a cute uniform for me...
I contacted both places.
Just rest and don't worry about anything.
Okay...
S-Situation...
Yaa-chan is sleeping, shh...
Ryuuji, how's Yaa-chan?
Oh, don't worry about her.
Thank god, seeing her faint from my window scared the heck out of-
Ryuuji?
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to buy something for Yasuko to eat.
Wait, Ryuuji! What about your coat?
Ryuuji?
You left your cell phone, wallet and key! Your eco-bag too!
Get a grip on yourself, idiot!
Gosh, put it on already!
You too, why are you like that?
Wear this.
No, I'm all right! You wear it!
Ryuuji?
Hey, you...
Go home.
No.
Go home, seriously.
No! You're acting all weird now!
Just go home!
Ryuuj-
What were you doing?
It's all my fault.
Yasuko fainted because of me.
It's my fault...
It's all my fault...
What are you talking about?
She has anemia! It's her body! It's not your fault!
If I weren't that useless...
Yasuko would have more faith and trust in me...
She would rely on me more... then things like this would never happen...
Ryuuji!
Ryuuji...
What should I do?
Everything's all right!
All... right?
Yeah, everything's all right!
Everything's all right, I'm a superb mom!
Ryuuji...
What's wrong? Don't go...
I'm fine now.
I have somewhere to go.
That's troublesome...
Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow are the busiest times because of Valentine's Day.
I'm sorry, she really can't come.
I don't think I'll be able to find a substitute at this time...
I'm sorry!
I'll do it.
You can?
I'm saved!
Taiga?
It's not for you.
I want to do something for Yaa-chan.
I'll help too!
I was fired from my part-time job at the cake shop?
But-
It's only normal.
I'm sure I'll be able to find another job.
W-Why are you comforting me?
W-Wel...
Welcome...
No one's coming...
Say it with a stronger voice!
I mean, your face wasn't born for advertising food.
You...
Oh, you guys are really working!
Yo, Taka-chan!
What are you doing-
Haruta-kun, which one do you like?
They say if you buy big ones, bad things will happen.
I don't think so.
Then I'll take that big one.
May I have this one, please?
T-That'll be 580 yen...
You have an elder sister?
She's not my sister, she's my girlfriend.
Bye, have fun with your jobs!
Don't you feel cold?
Let's go to a warm place.
Sure.
Why?
The world really has changed.
Noto! Why are you here?
Well, I just happened to pass by...
Oh, yeah, has anyone else come by?
For example, Ami-chan, or even Nanako-sama...
Kihara didn't come.
Huh? No! I don't really care!
Well, you see...
I was just wondering if Kihara will give Kitamura chocolate or something...
Then what will happen?
I'm fine with it either way.
I mean, look, Taiga, you care about "that," don't you?
What? What do you mean by "that"?
Besides, why does Kihara Maya buying chocolate for Kitamura-kun concern you?
Oh, I see. You like Kihara Maya.
So people who realize their feelings after fighting really do exist...
I'm just interested!
W-W-W-What are you talking about?!
That's so strange, Taiga!
I don't think it's strange at all. It's perfectly normal.
A male's stamen and a female's pistil...
Idiot!
There's something wrong with your brain!
What's going on with him?
Crap...
We'll be scolded if we mess around anymore.
I guess there's no other choice than to summon the lethal weapon.
I thought you were by yourself.
Y-Yo.
I'm going home.
Well, since you came...
Here, stupid Chihuahua, hold this.
Huh?
No thanks. Don't make me do weird things.
I'm beautiful, so I naturally grab people's attention.
Yes, yes, you're beautiful! You're really attractive!
That's why you should take this and say "I love the chocolate here!" out loud.
What's this?
You want me to advertise?
Yeah.
No thanks.
Why would I do such a lame thing?
It's all right, stupid Chihuahua.
Oh yeah, how about you buy one for yourself?
You could give it to Minorin to make up with her.
Huh?
Contrary to popular belief, I care about you.
You want to get on good terms with Minorin, but it's not working out for you.
The shaking delicate heart of a Chihuahua-
Hey, why are you making assump-
If you're embarrassed, I'll call Minorin for you.
My, Valentine's Day came just in time.
You!
Hey, isn't that Kawashima Ami-chan?
You're right! She's so cute!
Her face is so slender!
It's really Ami-chan!
Is she buying chocolate at that place?
I love the chocolate here.
Even my model friends say it's good.
I want to buy the same kind as Ami-chan's!
Wow, she can be helpful from time to time.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'll be right there!
Ryuuji, where are you-
Excuse me, I would like this one.
C-Coming!
Hey, Kawashima!
You really like chasing after people, don't you?
You have potential to be a stalker.
You too, you like running away, don't you?
Not just from me, but from a lot of other things too.
Listen, I don't think it'd be better if you left.
Besides, you'll disappoint everyone if you leave.
Everyone adores you.
Everyone?
Yeah, everyone.
You really don't get it.
Look, Taiga can't handle it by herself.
Oh, crap!
Actually, I'd be happy even if it wasn't everyone.
I don't get it myself either.
Thanks! I'll be counting on you tomorrow!
We've reached our target already, so it's pointless to buy the rest.
It's all right, I'm going to give them out.
Give them out?
Yeah, I caused a lot of trouble for people on the trip.
Like Kitamura-kun, and Minorin, and the stupid Chihuahua.
And also...
If I gave you chocolate, would you be happy?
Because I don't know.
W-What don't you know?
I wouldn't be human if getting chocolate from you didn't make me happy.
Oh, okay.
Then I'll try my best.
Just giving you guys store-bought chocolate is rude,
so I'll try to do something nice with it.
Hopefully I can make everyone happy.
Oh, it smells great!
You're going to the shop already?
I'm all healthy now, so it'll be fine.
I need to thank Taiga-chan...
Hey...
Why did you bring us all here?
Today is Valentine's Day,
so I made some chocolate to say thanks.
You made it by yourself?
Amazing!
It'll be such a waste to eat it!
Wasn't that the chocolate you were selling yesterday?
You're really good at telling lies-
No!
The wrapping was nice so I reused it, but I made everything inside.
Here, this is for you.
Thank you for yesterday.
I won't help you with stuff like that anymore.
Yesterday was an exception.
Next is Minorin's.
I know you went to save me during the field trip.
Thank you.
You don't need to be so formal...
I'll come to save you whenever you're in trouble!
Minorin!
Ryuuji,
you too, thanks.
Share it with Yaa-chan, okay?
Okay...
Next is Kitamura-kun's.
I put the most effort into this one.
Oh, is that all right?
It's all right, you were the person who carried me from the bottom of the cliff, after all.
Crap, I didn't tell Kushieda to-
Oh, gosh!
I wonder if my eyes were all white...
I really didn't expect that to happen!
I rolled down like this, and there were some weird noises in my head.
I finally found out what fainting feels like.
It's like dreaming.
I felt like I blurted out things that I wasn't supposed to say.
When I regained my consciousness, I started to panic...
What do you think you blurted out?
I can't say it! I really can't say it!
Minorin, I can't tell you!
Tell me.
I can't! Anyway, it was just my delusion!
Just tell me.
It's something that no one should know!
I'll be ruined if people find out.
I won't be able to live anymore because it's something really, really messed up.
Just kidding.
You didn't hear it, did you?
Yeah, I heard nothing, right, Takasu?
No one heard anything, it's all right.
Liar.
You think everything will be all right if you pretend you didn't hear it?!
W-What are you doing, Minorin?
Taiga, you're glad that no one heard it because that solves everything, right?!
Takasu-kun was the one who saved you, but he just didn't tell you!
He didn't tell you because of what you said, right?!
Why, Taiga?
Why... Why can't you just be honest for once?!
It hurts!
Kitamura-kun?
My, you look scary.
Stupid Chihuahua...
Hey, Takasu.
Do you think it'll be all right if you let Aisaka run away?
Are you okay with it?
Look here, Taiga!
Look at me!
No!
What do you see me as?
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm Minorin, your best friend, right?!
Didn't you say you like me?
Then believe in me!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Let go of me!
Taiga, I believe in you.
I don't think you're the kind of person to blame others for your inability to go after what you want!
Or are you someone like that?!
That's not it...
I just want you to be happy...
I just want the Minorin I love to be happy...
Cut it out!
My happiness can only be.... can only be made with my own hands!
My happiness doesn't depend on anyone but me!
This is all we can do.
That's right.
Taiga!
Ami, are you betraying us?
Bad things will happen if you don't chase after her.
Takasu-kun, I'll chase after Taiga.
I'm not done talking with her yet.
What are you doing to do?
What am I going to do?
What will happen if I chase after her?
What will I do after I find out how Taiga feels?
She obviously wanted to hide it...
Takasu-kun!
I...
nemurenai yoru ni wa
On nights when I can't sleep
hitori de tameiki
I heave a sigh to myself
minna wa dou nano
What about all of you?
nandaka samishii
I feel kind of lonely
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
A single seed in a vast landscape
nekko nobashite
sprouted its roots
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
It bore a fruit that was still unripe
ORANGE iro ni hayaku naritai kajitsu
The fruit that wants to turn orange as soon as possible
kimi no hikari wo abite
by basking in your light
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
My ideals and dreams keep on flourishing
kizuiteyo nee
Come on, notice it already
ORANGE kyou mo tabetemitakedo
Today, I ate an orange
mada suppakute naita
but I cried because it was still sour
watashimitai de nokosenai kara
It reminded me of myself, and I couldn't throw away the rest
zenbu tabeta
so I ate it all
suki da yo
I love you
nakeru yo
It makes me cry
suki da yo
I love you
Next Episode Preview
Confession
Hey, Taiga, it's about to snow.
The laundry is still outside...
Not just that,
I think I left a lot of things out.