Time   Fifteen Forty-seven
DECLARATION OF WAR!
So, whoever loses this game of rock-paper-scissors
will go to class D and declare war on them, okay?
DECLARATION OF WAR!
Plain old rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Let's spice it up with some mind games.
All right, I'm going to use rock!
Very well, if you don't use rock...
I'll murder your ass.
Rock, paper, scissors!
DECLARATION OF WAR!
A mosquito bite hurts more than your fist!
My right hand is here
DECLARATION OF WAR!
A mosquito bite hurts more than your fist!
Go on ahead.
No frickin' way!
You'll be fine, bro.
Class D loves cute guys,
so you'll be fine.
Yeah, no problem for me.
That said, you're one hell of an ugly bastard.
What was that?
You can examine me from head to foot in all 365 degrees.
Beauty POV
The limit of how beautiful
a person can be
I'm hottest guy you'll ever find.
That's five degrees too much.
He probably means just five degrees.
Looks like a fag
DECLARATION OF WAR!
I hate you all!
Good luck.
Time   Sixteen o' Five
I'm ruined for marriage...
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Time    Ten   Thirty
Fumizuki Academy
The ESB between class F and D will be carried out this afternoon, as planned.
Principal's Office
Head of Sophomores       Youko Takahashi
Great.
Principal:   Kaoru Toudou
I love idiots who never learn.
I wonder if they'll win this time.
Eleventh Period
Arch-enemy and Love Letter and Blitzkrieg
Well, regarding that...
What about it?
Yuuji Sakamoto's test scores have been dropping at a consistent rate.
What? And he wants to beat class D?
He's defiling the ESB.
Does he think it's all just fun and games?
No, Principal.
Please take a look at this...
Time   Fourteen  Thirty-five
Year 2 Class F
Move everything out of the way.
Representative  Yuuji Sakamoto
We won't be able to move
freely if the enemy busts in.
If we win, maybe we can switch facilities with class D.
Minami Shimada
I guess we'd have to say goodbye to these cardboard boxes.
Hideyoshi Kinoshita
Yo
...
We can finally have a normal classroom.
Let's win this, Himeji.
...
Yes, let's, Yoshii!
Mizuki Himeji
Surprised
Love Letter
That's the love letter for Yuuji, huh...
Misunderstood
But Yuuji already has Kirishima.
Should Mind His Own Business
I guess it's pretty difficult for her to deliver it in this situation.
Excuse me, the subtitles are taking away my screentime.
Year 2 Class D
The idiots from class F have declared war on us.
Representative  Genji Hiraga
They're targeting our facilities.
We've gotta teach them that idiots only deserve crappy classrooms.
New Building
Old Building
Let's start the strategy meeting.
Strategy? Do we need to go that far?
We have Himeji with us, so they'll be a piece of cake.
Himeji is as strong as a member of class A, after all.
Old Building
You guys are too naive.
Class E only lost because Mizuki Himeji's existence took them by surprise.
The same trick won't work twice.
Our classroom is located on the far end of the new building.
And class F's classroom is in the old building.
The battlefield this time is larger, so the troops won't be as concentrated.
We have the advantage here because our average is higher than theirs.
If we have Himeji go solo,
they'll probably focus all of their attacks on her. She won't be able to make it to their rep.
Then what should we do?
We'll blitzkrieg them.
Our scouting forces will assault the enemy lines
and make way for our main forces by opening up a hole in their defense.
Himeji.
Yes.
You'll charge to the enemy's nest through that opening
and take the head of class D's rep, Genji Hiraga.
Okay.
We can't win if we spread out our forces.
We're going to go all out! No defense at all!
We'll take them down before they have a chance to take us down!
Offense is the best defense!
They'll concentrate on attacking us, thus leaving their defense wide open.
Sakamoto's scores are the lowest of them all.
Without any defense, he's as good as dead.
We'll crush them and teach them a lesson in the process!
Time   Fifteen  Thirty
The war begins soon afterward.
Begin
All right, let's go!
Akihisa, you're the front line commanding officer.
Me!?
Yeah.
You're the key to our victory.
I need to come up with tactics that'll tip the balance...
Go disturb the enemy and buy me some time.
All right.
A snake?
Summon!
I got my ass raped!
What? You made it back?
Were you expecting me to die!?
We've already lost five people to the detention room!
Voyeur, bring the enemy list.
Akihisa, what was the enemy formation like?
This girl, this girl, and this girl were on the front lines.
And... Wait, where are the guys?
I don't have those.
I see...
They're all bad at math.
Should I spearhead them, then?
That was my plan from the beginning.
I'll get the math teacher Hasegawa as well.
What was the point of sending me out there!?
Sugawa, get ready for a special mission.
All right.
Time   Fifteen Forty-six
All hands, sortie!
We have a war to fight!
Mr. Hasegawa, please.
Permission granted.
Summon!
Let's go!
There's no way I'll lose to class D in math.
Watch and learn!
Those who were KIA must
receive supplementary lessons!
It's Ironman!
No! I don't want to study in hell!
They're not supplementary lessons... They're torture!
No, they are the very essence of education!
I will turn you into perfect students.
You'll learn to love studying and to honor Kenjirou Ninomiya!
So get ready!
All right, let's break through their defense!
Class F's Shimada has made it to the new building!
All right, now!
Seize Mr. Hasegawa!
Ambush by the toilets.
Mr. Hasegawa has been taken captive.
They had traps waiting.
What about Minami?
The math summoning field...
Crap! That's the classical literature teacher, Mr. Takenaka!
Classical literature, permission granted.
No... This is my worst subject...
Leave this to me!
Sugawa!
Buy some time for me.
All right, hang in there, Minami!
But how?
Is it you, Sissy? Is it you?
M-Miharu...
I refuse to follow his orders like a puppet!
What?
I still intend to fight you, though.
Summon!
The fact that our fate demands us to fight...
shows that we are destined to be together!
No, not classical literature!
I'll help you!
Kinoshita!
This is an announcement.
Ms. Funakoshi, you have an important message.
It's Sugawa!
Ms. Funakoshi, Akihisa Yoshii is
waiting for you in front of class D.
Funakoshi. Math teacher. 45 years old. Female. Single.
She's way past the age of getting married.
She uses grades to threaten students to go out with her. Rumor says she's still a virgin.
Yoshii said he wants to talk to about things that cross the boundary of teacher and student.
Please hurry to class D.
Sugawa!
There's Ms. Funakoshi!
Commander Yoshii, you're amazing!
You are a true man!
I can't believe you sacrificed yourself for our class...
We mustn't let him die in vain!
Sugawa!
You're still an amateur, Hiraga.
We've already prepared to call for a math teacher.
Voyeur, get rid of Mr. Takenaka.
Understood.
Teach, your wig's slipping off.
Excuse me, I've got to go!
Right now!
Ms. Funakoshi, please!
Math
You are so dead.
Route is clear.
It's your turn, Himeji.
Summoning Being... Summon!
Too slow!
Emergency!
What's the matter?
My secret cameras are showing enemies!
Found him!
He has no defense! Let's take him down right now!
What's the rush?
Let's have a little fun.
Time   Sixteen Eighteen
You cheeky little bastard.
I guess you were called a child prodigy for a reason.
No way...
Aren't your grades the lowest?
Seems like your intel's pretty old.
The graphs I got Voyeur to leak didn't have the latest scores on them.
Now then... Let's do this.
Why?
I'm sorry.
No enemies will stand before me!
Time   Sixteen Twenty-five
END
We did it, Yoshii!
Who would've thought Yuuji actually studied?
This is just the beginning.
Our final destination is class A!
We'll take down class B next!
Class B? Nemoto's class?
We will declare war on class B after we've replenished our points.
And that brings me to my other point, Akihisa.
I have a mission that only you can do.
What do you have to say?
Man, you always fall for it.
Class F declaring war on us is just hilarious.
We'll show them who's boss.
Are you sure about that, Kyouji?
Class F has defeated both class E and D.
Are you scared of them, Yuuka?
You're kidding.
No matter how hard they try, they won't be able to beat us, class C.
Then there's no way we can lose to them either.
I guess you could say that...
There must be some trick that lets them keep winning like this.
So we're not going to risk going up against them directly.
Kyouji...
See? I'm not dumb.
I'll pay them back for what happened last time.
Temporary
That concludes our plan.
I want your cooperation, everyone.
We can win this!
Time   Seventeen Twenty-eight
All right, you're all dismissed.
Thanks for today!
You're sure about not trading facilities with class D?
Yeah, I'm planting seeds for future battles.
Planting seeds?
Just wait for them to sprout.
Time   Seventeen Thirty-one
What the hell happened?
This is unbelievable...
Who did this?
I'm afraid that class B did it.
They wanted to break our utensils to
prevent us from replenishing our points.
Man, did they seriously think this'd work?
Lame.
What's the matter, Himeji?
No, nothing...
You're going to fucking pay for this, Nemoto!
You bet your ass he will!
Guys, calm the hell down!
But...
Winning the ESB is the best
revenge we can get on them.
But we won't be able to win if we lose our calm.
He's got this all planned out.
Time   Fourteen Fifty-one
The showdown of hatred between class F and class B finally begins.
Next Day
Begin
It's time for war! Let's go!
Charge!
They're here.
What a bunch of idiots.
Proceed according to our plan.
They can't win.
Take 'em down!
Dammit... They're way too strong!
Are we really going to lose this?
Yeah, these guys are no slouches.
Yoshii!
Himeji, it's not your turn yet.
Orders
Sakamoto said to use this when you're in trouble.
Yuuji said so?
This is...
All right!
Listen up!
Class B's rep Nemoto has a girlfriend!
What?
His girlfriend is the rep of class C, Yuuka Koyama!
What!?
Not only that... He made his girl-
friend cook lunch for him!
WHAT!?
As the rage on the battlefield has reached unfathomable heights...
the members of the FFF have forgotten all about the hell of supplementary lessons
and have transformed into the messengers of genocide.
We cannot forgive you...
How dare that bastard...
Do you understand the pain of being alone!?
What are these guys!?
I give up! Let's retreat!
The tables have turned!
Charge!
Are they crazy!?
Aren't they scared of supplementary lessons!?
What's the matter?
Class F is a bunch of lunatics!
They're suicide bombing our forces!
I guess I need a little more insurance.
Time   Fifteen Twenty-one
Those who were KIA must receive supplementary lessons...
Sugawa, I won't let you die in vain.
You helped me vent!
He's still mad about what
happened with Ms. Funakoshi...
We've lost quite a few people.
We need to redo our formation.
Go replenish your points if you're running low!
Himeji-
Isn't that Nemoto?
Why did you sabotage our classroom?
Do you have proof that we did it?
Well...
Yes, we did it.
I have proof as well.
I'll teach you a lesson! Summoning-
Whoops, that was close.
Isn't it thoughtful of the perp to present the evidence himself?
No...
I found some pretty interesting stuff.
Writing love letters in this day and age is pretty cute, I'd say.
Give it back!
I wonder what's written in it...
Whoops...
I guess I'll enjoy the contents later.
You jerk...
Well, just so you know, we would've won even if I didn't do this.
It's just in case.
I'll give it back to you once the ESB is over.
Assuming I don't change my mind, that is.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Running away?
If you are, I'll tie you up.
Yuuji, I need to talk.
What's up?
Please let Himeji rest for this battle.
Did something happen?
I can't say.
Fine, if you say so.
However, you'll take over Himeji's job instead.
All right.
Launch a surprise attack on their main camp.
I'll let you handle the specifics.
Can you do it?
I'll try.
No, I will do it.
I like that spirit, Akihisa.
Time   Sixteen Twenty-eight
Oh, and, Yuuji...
What's up?
Time   Sixteen Twenty-nine
Akihisa, are you serious about this?
This is the only way I can take them down with my own strength.
But you don't have the permission to summon...
Don't worry, I have this.
Awaken!
Go!
This is nothing!
What's going on?
I'm not done yet!
Are you okay, Akihisa!?
This is nothing!
I will...
win this fight no matter what!
No matter what...!
For Himeji!
There he is!
Did you think I'd leave myself open?
Your surprise attack is a failure.
He took the bait.
Voyeur!
What?
Health battle... Summon!
No way...
He brought a teacher with him!?
Ironman Nishimura, the teacher in charge of the detentions,
can permit summoning of any subject and possesses godlike athletic skills.
Jesus Christ...
Battle's over!
The winner is class F!
Too bad, Nemoto.
Sakamoto...
I have a proposal for you guys.
Under normal circumstances, you would have to trade your facilities with our cardboard boxes.
However, if you agree to my
condition, that can be avoided.
Condition?
Nemoto, if you wear this and listen to my orders, we won't need to trade.
What?
What the hell are you talking about!?
There's no fucking way I'll do that!
You've got class B's unanimous consent!
Yeah, we'll make it happen! Just leave it up to us!
We'll force him if he says no!
Hey, I'm not going to-
Is this okay, Akihisa?
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
Here, Himeji. This is yours.
Thank you very much, Yoshii!
Thank goodness...
Umm, Himeji...
About that letter...
Yeah, it's the same letter from last time.
I couldn't bring myself to deliver it...
And that caused a lot of trouble for everyone.
Himeji...
This letter has caused me a lot of pain,
but it's also brought me a lot of happiness.
So I'm fine with the way things are.
I don't want to rely on this letter anymore.
I will deliver my feelings personally.
Although I don't think I can do that anytime soon...
There's one thing I can say for sure right now.
Yoshii...
What's the matter?
May I call you Akihisa?
Wait! The FFF will go berserk if you do this...! And to Hideyoshi, this is...
May I, Akihisa?
Sure.
Yuuji, what's driving your desire to wage war?
Do you want better facilities?
I don't give a damn about chairs and desks.
I just want to prove to the world that grades aren't everything.
That's all.
So don't hold back, Shouko.
Very well then.
We'll fight you with all we've got.
Question 12: What do you call a joyous resolution in a novel or play?
Last boss fight!
You don't have enough exp.
Next episode: Love and Courage and Our Fight Has Just Begun (temp).
This will be on your test.