I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Childhood
Reunion
You...
Yuu?
What the hell are you doing?!
Activate the curse and kill him immediately!
What?
Do it now!
But...
Tsk. You little shit!
What the fuck?!
Why didn't you kill him?!
Huh? But he's...
H-Hey, are you okay?
I don't need you sniveling over me!
Eyes on the enemy, you fuckin' brat!
This is a goddamn battlefield!
What the hell, Yuu?!
You could've killed him just now!
Why didn't you activate the curse?
Yuu, what's wrong?
Yuu...
Mika...
My family is...
with the vampires.
Mika! It's you, right?
Mika...
I-It's really you!
Y-Yuu...
My, what an adorable reaction.
It's your dear, long-lost Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
The one you've been dreaming about all this time.
What a wonderfully destined reunion.
I'm almost in tears.
So, what would you like to do?
Those humans have most likely been manipulating him.
I'll save him.
From the filthy hands of those wretched humans?
Yes.
But he's a human himself.
We vampires were never meant to coexist alongside them.
Ah, how does this sound?
I'll take a page out of Krul's book.
If I turn him into a vamp—
If you lay even a finger on him, I'll kill you.
I'm kidding, of course.
It's not like you to get so worked up.
Shall I lend a hand instead, then?
I'll take care of the other humans,
so you can save your beloved princess.
I see you've made friends, Yuu.
You're too kind.
But they're taking advantage of your kindness.
The greed of the humans, your so-called "friends," knows no bounds, Yuu.
Shall we get to work?
It's time to kill all the humans! Except for Yuu, of course.
I hear my presence is required,
Seventh Progenitor.
Oh, Crowley.
I've been waiting for you.
He's...
I made a little detour on the way.
Did you come across something of interest?
Well, I suppose we might as well
call it a day, now that you're here.
Oh, how about we take them as livestock?
Capture the vampire extermination unit alive.
Operation Domestication.
Sounds good to me.
Shit, more nobles.
We're done here.
All units, prepare to retreat!
Huh?!
W-Wait a minute!
My last family member, Mika, is over there!
So... So we can't retreat!
So you're trying to get everyone here killed, is that it?
Yuu.
Yuu, he's right.
We have no choice.
Retreat!
Keep your formation and retreat to the second defense line!
Uh-uh, no escaping allowed.
Break up!
You!
Are you insane, Yuu?!
It was you!
Yuu!
For fuck's sake...
Lieutenant Colonel?!
You're fast, but you lack experience.
And even a lion can be brought low by his injuries.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
Move.
End of the line, sweetie.
Oh, nice. Not so stoic after all, huh?
Mito!
I'm fine.
Looks like they plan on holding us off at all costs.
We'll have to kill them.
Easier said than done.
If we could do that,
we'd be on our way back home by now.
Give it up.
You have no destiny but that of livestock.
You heard the man.
Focus!
What are you doing?!
Stand up!
S-Sorry.
Well, well, we meet again.
This time, I won't let you go.
Guren!
Behind you!
First, I'll have a taste of your—
Why the scary face?
I'm just fooling around with you.
Mika.
Yuu, leave everything behind and escape with me.
Huh? What do you mean, escape?
Actually, why are you even with that vampire?!
It doesn't matter!
Yuu!
Eyes on the prize, dear.
Hey! Hold on!
Quit messing around, Mika! Give me an explanation!
You shouldn't stay there for any longer, Yuu.
You'll be deceived by the humans.
Come with—
Just stop, goddamnit!
That's enough!
They'll deceive me?
What are you getting at?
Aren't you also...
Y-You're not human anymore?
I-Is it my fault?
Is it because I ran away?
No! You did nothing wrong!
But...
Let's just go.
It's not safe here.
Yuu, please.
I can't, Mika.
I can't go.
My friends are—
They're not your friends! Don't let them deceive you!
They're just using you!
Shinoa!
Please, Yuu!
Don't look back!
There's nothing for you here.
Nothing!
Unhand her!
Yuu!
Let go!
You mustn't, Yuu!
Let go of me!
You can't go!
They're just trying to use you!
No!
Stop it!
Come with me, Yuu!
Shut up!
Y-Yuu, run away...
Livestock don't talk.
Please, stop...
It's too late, Yuu.
You need to give up.
Y-Yuu...?
Hey, Asuramaru.
Hm? What?
What's going on here?
Are you trying to possess me?
I've done nothing of the sort.
But this is a problem.
Huh?
I never thought I'd be intimidated by the monster inside you.
Look at that sky.
The heavens are opening,
as if to shine on this cursed world.
Mika's right, Yuu.
It'd be best if you escaped from the humans with him.
Otherwise,
your own humanity will be—
What's wrong?
I guess it's too late.
The monster within you is about to be unleashed.
It's started.
So they really were experimenting on him.
No, Yuu!
Come with me!
Well, looks like we have quite the predicament...
Now that's something you don't see every day.
Yuu!
Aw, now my clothes are all dirty.
What is that?
The humans came up with such a scary monster.
Well, Ferid?
Hm?
What have you created?
I wonder what, indeed.
Looks like your species' specialty to me—
human experimentation.
Your limitless greed never fails to astound me.
Honestly, it's rather scary.
Not to mention, it always breaks free
of your control one way or another.
See?
S-S-S-Sinners...
All sinners must be s-s-slaughtered...
Shinoa!
You have to do something!
There's still a chance we can bring him back!
What?
Stop, Yuu!
You mustn't kill humans!
Wh-Why did you...
Shut your treacherous mouth, human.
How dare you treat Yuu like some plaything?
Damn, my injury won't heal.
Slaugh... ter...
Shinoa!
Hurry the hell up or we'll all die!
Y-Yuu, please! Snap out of it!
Don't touch Yuu with your filthy hands!
Yuu!
Please, Yuu!
Yuu...
Damn those humans...
Damn them all to Hell!
Quite a show, isn't it?
That's my trump card.
What a shame it did absolutely nothing.
Oh, but it made all the difference.
After all, we were just stalling for time.
Oops, caught red-handed.
But it's too late.
Pierce the enemies, Byakkomaru.
Oh, and try not to hit Guren.
Boom.
Shit!
Whew, that was close.
If it weren't for his big mouth, I might have died.
Oh, deary me.
Not bad for an Ichinose scumbag, Lieutenant Colonel.
The Hiiragi family will take it from here.
Move out!
Take the nobles alive!
We'll show them that we humans,
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army,
and those of us in the Hiiragi family
have no mercy for those who oppose us.
Attack.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
We're All
Sinners
"We're All Sinners."