It's my second year of high school,
and May is already over.
Even though Edogawa asked to be friends that day,
she hasn't been remotely friendly since.
However,
there's a good reason for that.
Edogawa has a secret that nobody can know about.
secret
I'm sure that even though she wanted to be my friend,
she was scared of her secret getting out,
so she closed her heart to others.
However,
I have finally learned Edogawa's secret.
It's not what it looks like!
I-I'm not a boy, but...
how do I put it...
My body...
sometimes grows a penis!
Since I learned a secret that only we knew,
I sympathized with her as a friend and a sister,
and swore to protect her.
God's hand paints the seasons
that pass my sight
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 10
Trying to Fight an Invisible Enemy
Second Year Left Class
A penis... a penis...
What are you on about, Sasami?
Is your brain afflicted with necrosis?
Huh?
Oh, no, just the troubles of puberty...
But still, we're finally in our second year, so why do we still have no friends?
I thought I'd be
so cheerful that people couldn't stay away,
Maybe I'll Make
100 Friends!
and then I'd made tons of friends!
So much for that...
Was that an impression?
My hands are tired.
I cannot believe I must hold my own chopsticks.
Quite the bother.
Please do not mimic my tone.
Meals are meant to be gained on one's own strength.
All Natural
Strawberry
Dairy Product
Milk
But you can feel so much love when someone feeds you.
Coffee
Milk
Classification: Milk
Store Under 10C
There is no love.
There is only the obligation of doing a chore.
That's mean!
And to think I love you so much!
Do not shout phrases that invite misunderstandings.
Don't shrug me off, I really like you...
I'll feed you too.
Were your hands not tired?
Just this once.
Your words may reject it,
but your kindness won't let you resist,
and now that you're caught, you'll be feeding mouth-to-mouth before you know it!
Your plot was that wicked?
Sasami, you terrify me.
It's like those two really are lovers.
They're probably not into guys.
They're probably not into girls that are into guys.
Kneel before me, plebeians!
Wait, that's not right.
Good afternoon, everyone. Right?
Good to see you're all shut up like good little morons.
"First Annual Second Year Left Class Get-Together."
First Annual Second Year Left Class Get-Together
Place: Nine-Headed Dragon Shrine,
for a three-day two-night Love Love Resort!
"Place: Nine-Headed Dragon Shrine, for a three-day two-night Love Love Resort!"
night Love Love Resort!
It's a bit sudden, but we should enjoy our upcoming vacation.
First Annual Second Year Left Class Get-Together
Place: Nine-Headed Dragon Shrine,
for a three-day two-night Love Love Resort!
So we're going to a refreshing, all you can eat, all you can drink resort!
And it'll be completely free!
The more the merrier, so you're all invited!
You are quite fortunate to share the same class as I, Edogawa Jou.
I invite you in the hopes that you will remember it forever!
N-Not that I need you to come...
You're not busy anyway, so it's an order!
Let's all go together!
Chances like this only come once in your droll, pallid lives!
So despair!
We're in despair!
Now, spread these out, plebeians!
Now, elegantly, elegantly!
Flavor and beauty are right here.
Don't tell anyone, got it?
Uh, sure.
If you tell anyone,
I'll kill you.
Hey, Edogawa.
What?
Can I come on your trip too?
Of course.
Actually,
I'll kill you if you don't.
Certainly a cold.
You should give up on that get-together.
Don't wanna...
Edogawa's gonna kill me.
You can't go on a trip with your fever!
Even if you'll hate me for it, I'll stick to you like glue to make sure you stay indoors!
Oh, if you need anything, press this button,
or say the magic words, "Bro, I weally weally love you!"
I'm too sick for that one.
Then go to sleep, Sasami.
Brother, you idiot...
Yay, yay!
Good morning, Mamarin!
¿Como estas?
Tama?
Why are you here?
Watching the house.
Tsurugi told me to go look after Mamarin.
That Ammy...
She runs off on the trip and leaves me to babysit...
Trip?
I wanna trip too!
Lets trippy together, Mamarin!
I wanna go too.
A trip with you sounds...
Oh, there's an idea!
So if we do that, we'll solve everything.
Got it?
Y-Yeah...
Not too heartening.
Well, just sit still.
Hey, that tickles!
Great Yamato, of all lands most supreme.
Enclosed by ranks of verdant banks on surrounding hills.
Great Yamato, unmatched for beauty.
Oh?
I turned into Mamarin?
That kiss earlier was on one of your energy lines connected to your spiritual energy.
And with that line, I can pilot you.
Like a super robot.
I'm a super robot?
I'll be able to see, hear, and feel everything around you from this room.
Now you can go to the get-together in that form.
Sure! I got it!
Now, here we go.
You rang, Sasami?
Seems you need my love!
So where shall I paint my love on you?
Now, show me where you need it the most, ¡mi hermana!
Thoughts, become words,
become written and sent!
Sasami has entered the chatroom.
Tama, can you see this?
Um, Mamarin?
Tama has entered the chatroom.
IS THIS RIGHT?
In Japanese?
Is this right?
Well, you can keep the name, I guess...
Anyway, do as I say.
I'll do my best!
Is something wrong, Sasami?
Tell my brother I got over my cold.
Tell my brother I got over my cold!
Don't repeat me word for word!
Just show him that you're all better.
Look, I'm all better!
You seem abnormally better.
Now beg to go on the trip.
So Bro, can I go on the trip?
Please, Bro, Mamarin—
I mean, I've been dying to go on it!
So grant my wish!
I mean, please!
Well, you see...
But why not, Brother?
I love you when you're nice!
Wh-What's gotten into you, Sasami?!
Voicing your true feelings so suddenly could give me a heart attack!
Ah, so you want marriage!
I've prepared all of the paperwork besides your signature,
so all that stands in our way is the law!
Marriage?
We're gonna get married?
Normally when I say these things,
you respond by thrusting a fist into my stomach or wringing my neck!
Am I dreaming?
No, even if it's a dream, I finally have my happy ending!
No, my true ending!
I can die in peace!
We can't love each other if you're dead.
And I wanna love you lots, Bro!
What the hell are you doing?!
Just hurry up and get outside!
I'm trying ultra hard!
Now, Brother, let's go on that trip!
A honeymoon!
Now we're off, Sasami!
To a new chapter in our love story!
Yay, yay!
That can't be good.
Now, here are your guide pamphlets!
Elegantly, elegantly!
Now, go say hello to Edogawa.
Thank her for inviting you to this trip.
Sure!
Thank you, Edogawa!
I'm doing my best as Tsukuyomi Sasami!
Don't let that slip!
This is rather convenient...
What is?
Oh no, I welcome you.
If everyone's here, board the bus!
Like cattle.
Yay!
Allow me...
There's no room left.
Huh?
Oh, Sasami!
Our love, rended asunder by fate!
Natsumi
"It's morning... Brother."
Hey, it's Tsurugi!
Tama, what're you doin' here?
Huh?
I getcha.
Seems like you're up to somethin' fun.
Good morning, Tsurugi.
Oh, a chatroom!
Lil' Tsurugi has entered the chatroom.
Sounds like you had a neat idea, Sasami.
I thought for sure you'd be makin' that pillow wet with tears.
Hey, there're other places you can get wet, y'know!
Why do you never miss a chance for sexual harassment?
I felt bad about leaving Tama all alone, so this is perfect.
But be careful.
You gave the Supreme God's power to your mom,
so you're defenseless.
Don't worry.
I'm in the safest place in the world.
Huh?
Kagamin has entered the chatroom.
Well isn't Kagami lucky?
When she heard you weren't coming, she got all pouty and sad!
I did not pout.
As for being sad...
I was just sleepy.
Morning, Sis!
You're playing Sasami, so call me "Kagami" instead of "Sis."
I see.
Morning, Kagami!
You dare talk to your sister like that?
Hanawa
So what do I use?
I think that cold medicine is working...
I've had enough...
Not that I did anything...
I'll nap a bit.
Good night, Brother.
Sasami has exited the chatroom.
Mamarin went bye-bye?
Guess the kid fell asleep.
Is she gonna be okay, Sis?
I told you, stop with the "Sis!"
So what do I use?
I've got an idea...
I see!
My dear sister.
Wh-Why would you say that?!
Because it works with both friends and family!
Is it weird, my dear sister?
Was I wrong again, my dear sister?
Was I a bad girl, my dear sister?
S-Stop...
My body's...
going numb!
Oh well.
It's a bother, so I shall permit this expression.
I love you, my dear sister!
Now they started with the "dear sister" stuff!
Totally lesbos!
Like, butch and femme!
They've gone to a world we can't enter!
Farewell, my first love!
You really are the centers of attention.
Uh...
my bad, who're you, again?
How cold.
I am the head of Konohanasakuya Academy's second year class...
Uh...
K-Kitsunebi Youko.
That's it.
Oh, well my bad!
I'm awful at rememberin' names!
Let us get along well on this trip,
Ms. Yagami.
Towado Aomori
Tsugaru
Nine-Headed Dragon Island
Nine-Headed Dragon Shrine
Hotel
Bow before the gods.
Bow before each other.
Keep your eyes on each other...
On your marks...
go!
Dig in!
Now take all you like, eat all you like,
grow as fat as you like, and bear regrets, you plebeians!
The goddess who granted you such freedom is none other than I,
Edogawa Jou!
Worship me, call me your Marrianne!
Edogawa, aren't you having any?
It's gotta be lonely just standing there.
Wassup, Kagami?
It's all free, so shovel it down.
That girl intrigues me.
Could it be love? Infidelity?
Aw hell, just go for it!
I just found out how hot cuckolding is,
so I can totally fap to this!
Sasami has entered the chatroom.
Morning. I slept a lot.
Sasami, you're up.
How ya feelin'?
Not great.
My cold is still here.
Here, have this.
Sasami, you share her sense of taste, correct?
We shall grab anything you wish to eat, so help yourself.
Thank you.
You're pretty nice today, Kagami.
I am always a veritable angel.
Hey, you havin' fun, Youko?
Throw back some booze, fill your belly, and let's talk!
Then we'll hit the bed to get along.
Lemme at them boobies!
Should we leave them be?
It is a sibling's shame.
I have no desire to involve myself.
Now, attention!
It seems the baths are prepared,
so anyone who's finished eating, please get in.
Sweet!
We're goin' to the bath, yeah!
From "I'll wash your back,"
to "Now I'll wash your front..."
And we'll have our naughty scene!
Tsurugi, you're a genius!
Baths are places of hopes and dreams!
What reality do you live in?!
Edogawa, come with us!
Huh? No, I...
Shoot.
It's sprouted out right now!
Let's go!
I want to scrub each other's backs!
Scrub each other's backs?
Sorry, I can't...
C'mon, why not?
I can't!
I-I have stuff I need to do!
You people can just do what you like!
Leave me out of it!
Stay away from me!
Wh-What?
You take things too seriously, Edogawa.
You were just thinking you had clean up the dishes, right?
Get close to Edogawa
Ask her if that thing grew again.
Did that thing grow again?
Don't worry, I've got you.
If we all help, it'll be over sooner,
so don't take it all upon yourself.
We're all on your side, Edogawa.
Sure, I'll help.
Yeah, we can at least clean up after ourselves.
Nine-Headed Dragon Ho
Bath
I'm takin' the first dip!
Are you a child?!
It's still out, right?
If worse comes to worse, you can hide it with this.
Hide what?
It's something that turns into a lethal weapon when its user looks at naked girls, or something.
Do you know what that is?
Y-Yes...
Stay by me.
I'll take you somewhere empty.
The water's white here, so it should hide it.
Ah, this feels nice!
I-It does...
So there ya are, Sasami!
Bad Manners.
May we join you?
When ya look real close, you've got no tits, Kagami.
Drink more milk. It's good for ya.
Your advice was not asked for!
I ain't seen Tama all day,
and Youko ran off to boot.
Life's no fun without some huge tits around.
And there's Edogawa!
That body sure don't fit a high schooler...
Now, get in real close with your teacher...
Oh no!
What's wrong, Edogawa?
Are you hurt? Do you want a rub?
D-Don't touch me!
Sorry!
Something's poking me!
Something really weird is poking me in the butt!
Lemme in too!
You can't!
You'll have to beat Tama if you want to get through!
I don't care about washboards right now!
You can touch me when we get home!
But I wanna touch 'em now!
You can't touch Edogawa right now!
She's got a big, black weapon that's ready to blow its load!
Aww yeah gurl, take it!
Hey look, it's Ms. Youko!
What?!
Wowwy, she's ten times bigger than Tama!
She better be nekkid! Where is she?!
Ms. Youko!
Phew, we're safe.
My sister's really pushy.
You're okie-doke now, Edogawa.
Why?
Huh?
Why do you protect me?
You covered for me at dinner, too.
You helped me keep my body a secret.
And you still protected me now.
Why do you try so hard for my sake?
Well you see,
you might laugh at this,
but I was happy.
When you said you wanted to be friends when we first met.
That's it.
Is it wrong to try for that reason alone?
Sharing a secret
and trying to protect it...
it makes me feel like we're friends.
You see,
I want to be friends with you.
Being friends?
I'm not used to it.
Because...
one day, I'll kill you.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Good, nobody's here.
Everyone's on that trip.
Now's my chance...
Ah, ah, mic test. I'm silly.
Even though we say our goodbyes,
I start to miss you right away (In the stream of love)
Until I board the train,
I want to listen to your voice (Just feeling your heart)
I've always wanted to try singing the ending.
I think we'll get the bigwigs mad if I don't sing at least once.
Guess I should have practiced more.
I want to give the best performance I can!
See, I've got a good, marketable side to me!
I can hear your voice
Man, it's hard to go with the recording.
I don't talk to people often, so I can't get my voice out.
The light shines the color of love
Let's hold hands forever
I want to feel the osmosis grow
Good job, Mamarin!
Huh? Tama? You heard that?
Yup! We were connected, so everyone heard it!
It can't be! NOOOO!
Next Episode
It's time for Frivolous Foreign Films,
It's time for Frivolous Foreign Films, but due to an overtime in baseball, we were going to change to Dawdling Debates, but due to a guest's hospitalization, we rushed to make do with a rerun of the Nonchalant New Year's Special '99, but found that someone taped over it with some drama, so we gave up.
but due to an overtime in baseball, we were going to change to Dawdling Debates,
but due to a guest's hospitalization, we rushed to make do with a rerun of the Nonchalant New Year's Special '99,
but found that someone taped over it with some drama,
so we gave up.
Next time, on Episode 11.
Next Time, on Episode 11
Love is an Urban Myth
Love is an Urban Myth.