Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Well, let's get crackin'.
Let's-a-go.
Stop messing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
They bought me another cell phone!
Don't put it in the wash this time.
I'll put it somewhere obvious.
Hey!
Give me a hand, Tsukasa.
Coming!
Aspiration
Ba.
L.
Sa.
Mi.
Annoyed.
C.
Huh?
Annoyed.
There it is.
Vinegar.
Annoyed.
Too much!
I'll input it for you so hand it over!
That's irritating!
I-It's okay.
Don't worry.
I can do it myself.
I'm here to play!
Cousin Yui.
Welcome!
Whatcha doing?
Playing a dating sim that just came out.
Then I'm gonna borrow some random manga.
'Kay.
This game is age restricted...
...but did she not notice...
...or is she letting it slide?
Which one is it, officer?
And so...
...we beef things up during
Traffic Safety Awareness Week.
Like detailed checks...
...and explanations of traffic laws...
It's pretty rough.
And sometimes, they start yelling at you.
But when I look at how she usually acts...
Scary! Scary!
...she's not very convincing
when talking about laws or safety!
I'm totally shocked!
AAAAAAAA
Nashima Shika Clinic
I've heard that colds are lasting longer this year...
...so I need to get better quickly.
Based on my number...
...I'll probably be here a while.
I'll read while I wait.
Mr. Ando.
Mr. Shigeo Ando.
Ms. Takara.
Ms. Miyuki Takara.
Are you here?
Then the next person.
Ms. Mariko Nishiyama.
Huh?!
What?!
Did they call me?!
What time is it?!
I need to pay more attention to my surroundings.
We will soon arrive at the final stop, Kamata.
Where am I?!
So I taught Tsukasa how to text message the other day.
'Cause she had no idea after all that messing around.
Yay!
And she must have been really happy about it...
...since she's constantly texting me.
Yay!
Must suck for the recipient.
Well, there's nothing to worry about.
Sender: Tsukasa
She's the type to start off excited...
...and eventually lose interest.
Some people are just childish like that.
She sent another one.
If she doesn't get bored, you'll be pretty swamped.
And does she even have that much to talk about?
We're practically together 24/7.
And she apparently learned how to use symbols.
Look.
How about we buy soy cream-man
on the way home again today?
What's all the stuff at the end?
You can tell she's having fun...
I haven't even seen half of these before.
I guess she's finally gotten the hang of it.
Yeah. But I prefer the one with an afro
A
Really? But they probably aren't
actually
performing
Really? But they probably aren't
actually
performing
Really? But they probably aren't
actually performing
Yeah,
might be
Yeah, might be
I see
Heh
Hey.
I know how you feel...
...but could you stop spamming family members?
Do you have a minute?
What?
I'm not sure about how to use
text messaging on a cell phone.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's really easy, Dad.
You're so hopeless.
I'll teach you.
So I guess some people get all
snobby after they've learned something.
Um...
That smell is beyond words.
Right?
It just stinks too much.
Seriously.
You've got a lot of stuff saved on here.
Hey!
Stop going through that!
You've got messages that shouldn't be seen?
Not really.
No reason.
It's a man.
Definitely a man.
It's not!
She's not picking up.
Guess I'll call her house.
Hello, Kagami?
Konata?
You should answer your cell.
Well...
It didn't ring so I didn't notice.
Honestly...
Doesn't that defeat the purpose?
And where is that thing anyway?
Your cell phone really serves no purpose, huh?
Anyway...
About next weekend...
Someone's talking to me.
Hold on.
Hey!
Hurry it up!
Wait a bit!
You've been on the phone too long!
Can't wait any longer!
Sorry. Sorry.
I got in trouble for being on the phone too long.
Sorry.
But I figured you guys would be lax about that stuff.
Sounds like it's pretty strict.
Nah...
We were in the middle of a fighting game.
Tell me that earlier!
In this place...
...my point cards shine with an invisible magic.
You end up making unplanned purchases, yeah?
You really wing everything.
Though I kinda understand.
She's here.
In this city, we have Ani**te and Ga**rs...
Two anime stores...
There exists a person who buys
the same thing from both stores...
Legendary Girl...
A!
Legendary Girl A shift!
Welcome!
The DVD for Haruhi Vol. 5's in stock!
Limited edition!
Regular edition!
All ready!
And we've got loads of related items!
That's right..
Just display every item we have in stock.
She'll buy whatever she can.
I wanted a limited Aquarian Age bookmark today.
Need to go to Gamers.
No good!
Then we'll do a sleepover
this weekend and play all night.
We usually do stuff at our place...
...but can we go to your house?
I'd like to go over every now and then.
It's not that you can't...
...but my dad's usually home because of work.
Oh.
So that just increases the burden on me.
What burden?
I'm kinda looking forward to
seeing what Konata's house is like.
Yo.
Welcome.
Sorry to impose.
Thanks for having us today.
Welcome.
I've heard a lot about you two.
You're shrine maidens who live at a temple, right?
What have you been telling him?!
So do you usually wear yellow hakamas?
And like, that's the first thing he has to say?
We're here.
This is Kona-chan's room!
Crazy as expected.
This is cute!
This door...
Probably hides a stash of stuff you don't want seen.
A door that must never be opened.
Nah.
I share most of that stuff with Dad...
...so he handles storage.
You share...
Oh, yeah.
Your dad's an author, right?
Then have you ever gotten hooked on a
light novel or dating sim your dad wrote?
Nah.
He doesn't write any of that stuff.
Really...
Didn't expect that...
But...
He likes that kind of stuff...
...so wouldn't he want to write them?
He's like a lurker...
According to him...
...he plays dating sims and life sims on his own time...
...so he doesn't feel the need
to bring it to the workplace.
I've been at a loss for words for a while now.
Guess that's the Izumi family for you.
My dad was being all clingy the other day.
So I tried saying, "You're annoying, Dad!"
That's a little harsh, you know.
Then he's like...
Couldn't you at least say,
"I hate you, Dad!" or something?
No.
That's not quite right either.
But your way of thinking
wouldn't fulfill his expectations.
Yeah.
No idea what you're talking about.
Let's take a break.
This is it!
Even TV shows are starting to look like 2ch.
I guess.
Not that I would know.
Oh, yeah.
For someone hardcore,
you don't use much of that lingo.
In normal situations.
In chatrooms, I'm like this.
Wow...
Is this even Japanese?
If you can read this, you've lost.
Is there anything I can help with?
Then serve the salad.
Let's eat!
It's great!
Sure is.
A job well done.
This is nothing for someone
who does housework on a daily basis.
If you did more housework, you might get better.
Mind your own business.
Look, Konata.
It's perfect.
It's a scene out of my dreams!
A man eating a meal with three high school girls...
H-Heaven on earth...
Sakura...
...happens way more than it should in dating sims.
Tohsaka... Tohsaka's your sister!
Really now...
It gets chilly when it's late.
Should have put on a jacket.
A shooting star!
I couldn't make my wish three times.
It's pretty hard when they come out of nowhere.
But I'll pull it off one day and have my wish granted.
Tsukasa's a dreamer...
But it's impossible from a practical standpoint.
It's a superstition because
you know it isn't going to work.
Why does this one have no dreams...
Want a drink?
Thanks.
You switched hairstyles.
For fun.
While we were taking a bath.
Why do the same parts feel
so different on different people?
A photo album.
Can I take a look?
Sure.
Kona-chan's so cute!
You haven't changed much.
And like...
...you sure are close with your dad.
That's my mom.
No way!
So young!
Don't I look like her?
She was legal, right?
I always wonder when I look at Dad.
What did Mom ever see in Dad?
Hey, now...
You look just like your mom, you know...
Then in that case...
What would be your type?
Mine?
When you put it that way, I don't really have any...
Really?
Spill it.
Which means Mom was okay with anyone.
And she said something about
knowing Dad since they were little.
Well, that's a little...
Couldn't let Dad flounder around by himself.
You don't even hold back for your parents, huh?
But when I look at my mom...
In manga and games these days...
...a lot of middle schoolers look mature...
...and a lot of adults look really young.
What is this?
Do you want me to say something?
I wish Yuki-chan could have come.
Well, she's busy.
That's it!
I'll text her so she isn't lonely.
Miyuki's really considerate so stop that.
I got a reply.
I'm glad you're having fun.
I'm working hard to finish my homework right now.
Please invite me again next time.
I forgot we had homework!
Do something, Kagami!
Our class didn't have any.
Can I go to sleep?
Wait!
That shooting star.
It might work if I use short wishes.
Uh, you think?
What are you doing?
Studying how to say wishes faster.
Stop escaping reality and get your homework done.
Hey, Yuki-chan.
I didn't get this part in class earlier.
That part?
Konata leads to Kona-chan.
Miyuki leads to Yuki-chan.
Then what nickname would you use for Kagami?
Kaga-chan?
Gami-chan?
Kagami means mirror.
Kyo also means mirror.
[
]
Maybe Kyo-chan.
Pronounce Kagami a different way.
Kyo.
Good naming sense.
Kagami means mirror.
Kyo also means mirror.
Kyo also means strong.
It feels strong like her, too.
And you could use this Kyo-chan, too
Kyo also means evil.
Th-That wasn't my intention...
We probably shouldn't tell Sis.
Then what nickname would you give yourself?
Tsuka-chan?
Kasa-chan?
Hi-chan, I guess.
It's harder with my first name.
I see.
You give off the whole hi-hi image.
That wasn't my intention...
Okay.
Then I'll start calling you Hi-chan.
What?
Huh? Huh?
But it feels kind of weird...
...if I chose it myself...
And what about that?
That?
Doesn't matter.
Want revenge, Sebastian?
Name's Shiraishi.
Hey!
Kyo-chan!
Is she calling me?
It's too hard to understand so stop that.
Then how do you want me to call you?
Doesn't Kagami work?
A nickname would be better.
Like Kona-chan or Yuki-chan...
Then call me Kagami the Great.
Hey!
Kagami the Great!
She really did it!
What is it?
Just trying it out.
Sorry for the wait, Kagami the Great.
What's wrong, Kagami the Great?
Whoa...
My bad...
Please...
Just call me normally.
Good lucky!
Okay!
We're already on the booming
tenth episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami.
Hello!
I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi!
And right off the bat...
...we have our fourth character introduction...
Kagami Hiiragi!
She serves as a punch line character in the show.
But isn't she just a tsundere?
What an obvious setup.
I beg to differ.
The classification of Kagami Hiiragi
as a tsundere is a bit hasty.
Then what?
First, do we comprehend the true
meaning of the qualities of a tsundere?
No, unfortunately...
...the word tsundere has suffered misuse and decay...
...and one could say that the definition has evolved.
To begin with, the word tsundere
was born in the year 2002...
...an Internet term...
...but the original definition was...
...a character who starts off hostile...
...and eventually becomes affectionate.
Yes!
In other words...
...it was supposed to describe a change over time!
Do you really understand?
And now...
...it is used to describe the
multiple faces of a character.
In other words...
...hostile on the outside...
...and affectionate on the inside...
...would be how the word is currently understood.
I declare here!
This is plainly a mistake!
We must bring back the true meaning of tsundere...
...and restore this depraved nation!
Rise up, citizens!
Not bad, Sebastian.
Who's that?
So what is Kagami if not a tsundere?
You meant me?
I don't really get this complicated stuff...
...but if you insist...
...do you have a replacement for
what's currently known as tsundere?
Uh...
It's not that I don't...
Maybe cool-dere...
No, that's wrong.
Deretsun?
You got no sense at all.
Tsundere's fine.
No, that's...
That's wrong!
That's it!
Let's ask the viewers to
come up with a new expression!
Good idea!
Delegating, huh?
So, everyone in front of the TV!
Yes, you!
Try to come up with a new word
to describe characters like Kagami!
And rewrite the modern lexicon!
Dubbed the Complete Tsundere Debate!
You can find more details
on the radio show and home page!
We're waiting for your passionate ideas!
This is the end.
Oh, well.
Lots and lots...
Bye-bee.
Bye-bee!
Fast forward!
Whoa, I talked a lot today.
The most ever, yeah?
Huh?
Akira-sama?
Wh-What's wrong?
Satisfied?
Yes! Uh...
This is the most I've ever spoken.
I think I did a fair job.
I'm going to dinner with the
executive and producer from your studio.
Uh...
We're gonna discuss your future.
Uh, h-hold on a sec.
What do you mean?
No point in telling you about
how your future's looking.
No, no, no, no, no!
And aren't you still working at CoCo*chi?
That's only during the day.
And it doesn't pay much.
And the grill place?
I'm still doing that.
Or that doesn't even matter!
That's intruding into my privacy so stop!
I'm next.
Tsukasa.
How about this one?
This works!
Right, Yuki-chan?
I know this.
Then sing it.
Thanks, Kona-chan.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
They chose a song?
This song was popular when
we were in preschool, right?
Don't really know.
I'm sorry.
Neither do I.
I remember.
Our older sisters sang it a lot.
Songs sung by parents and older siblings...
...while from an earlier generation...
...tend to be memorable.
Caved, huh?
Can't be helped.
It's really high.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Kagami.
When you go out to eat...
...and order something with liquids...
...and a few drops splatter onto your clothes...
...it's pretty depressing.
And it really sucks if it's curry sauce.
And you happen to be wearing your favorite clothes.
Leaves you down the whole day!
And when you buy a box lunch
with sauce from a convenience store...
...and you carry it level so the contents don't spill...
...but once you open the bag...
...you discover that it spilled
inside and everything's a mess.
Makes you lose your appetite.
And when you ask them to bag
hot items and cold items separately...
...and they bag the cold drinks with your magazines...
...and the paper sucks up the condensation...
...and the magazine's all soggy...
...and you're like what was the
point in bagging them separately then?!
Next time:
The Many Ways to
Spend Christmas Eve    .
The Many Ways to Spend Christmas Eve.
Look forward to next time!