You were alive?
Cal Devens.
What happened?
I saw a ghost.
I swore to protect her and promised I would return to her side.
But I let her die all alone.
That's what I had always been thinking.
It wasn't like that, was it?
She was the one who did the sniping yesterday.
Is that so...
As a sniper, Cal...
...has joined Inferno.
Master Huang, I, Xu Jian Fa, am truly honored to celebrate your birthday and knit our brotherhood closer.
Xu, don't be modest. This is fit to honor your accomplishments in expanding us into West Japan.
Fairly soon...
...the Kanto region will be part of our territory as well.
A good prospect.
Brother, let us raise a glass to our success.
The Godou clan's request was to eliminate Xu, the Triad boss, right?
Is there a problem?
Is it necessary to make that Huang fossil into an enemy as well?
He aids an enemy of Inferno.
Huang helped you when you were being chased by Inferno.
He... knows too much.
You have no sense of right and wrong?
That's your burden, not mine.
This is Gregor, over.
Copy that.
My group has arrived at the scene.
We're ready to go in.
Remain on position.
What's Phantom doing?
Beats me.
She wasn't interested in this operation. We'll make do without her.
Do you agree?
You may be right, this operation doesn't fit her as the plan is to cut their ties.
Gregor, execute the mission according to plan.
Phase one, Parker's squad infiltrates the building from the rear and eliminates all guards.
Roger.
I estimate it will take them 3 minutes to smoke out Huang and Xu.
Unsatisfied?
Not at all.
Phantom could do it in 10 seconds, though.
10 seconds?
She...
You bastard!
W-What happened?
What the hell?
Watch out!
Fuck!
What have you done?
The fastest and most efficient thing, I suppose.
This is Japan, you can't kick up such a huge fuss.
No matter if it's Japan or America,
the value of human life is the same.
This way, Master Huang.
Okay.
Who would stage such an attack out in the open?
I have someone in mind.
You are Scythe's...
Does he want to repay the favor of saving him with my death?
Favor? What's that again... ?
Master Huang!
Oh, you have guts. You're still not giving up.
Since I like that, I'll stay with you for a while.
Do you like playing games?
We fight once the song is over.
Don't make fun of me.
I don't know what organization you belong to, but don't think you can get away with this.
Oh, I get it, you don't know.
Phantom.
If you're a mafia man, you've probably heard the name before.
Yep, that's...
...me.
If you beat me, I'm sure the whole world will sing your praise.
Choose a better line of work in your next life.
Adios, chink.
I pulled the trigger.
I taught her how to kill.
I lead her down the path to a world of darkness.
I ruined her whole life.
With these hands of mine.
I'll have our escape prepared soon.
Before that...
I understand.
Where were you yesterday?
I went to visit an acquaintance.
Did you make contact with Zwei?
Mind your own business.
I'll deal with whomever gets in my way.
I see.
Next up is your turn,
Reiji.
Excuse me...
Good morning.
Reiji-san, did you go home early yesterday?
Um, I went to look for you after school, but couldn't find you.
Oh, some stuff came up.
I'm not trying to stalk you.
I never thought you were.
Okay.
Snow?
You're right...
It didn't say snow in the weather forecast.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
That was some flashy work, Ms. Garland.
Public Security has started investigating.
I recommend you immediately have the ones involved in yesterday's shootout leave the country.
Don't worry about that, they already have.
Most of them.
That's good to hear.
At any rate, I'm truly grateful for not leaving evidence...
...of the Godou clan's involvement and for the successful assassination of Xu.
However, from now on...
...we would be thrilled if you were to inform us of activities in Japan.
Excuse me.
It wasn't a difficult mission.
If it had been executed according to plan, it would have been clean.
It's my fault because I didn't consider Phantom's appearance.
I should have anticipated it would turn out that way.
There's no need to blame yourself.
It's a fact there's problems with Drei.
But I can sympathize with her, she's impatient.
Drei, that is.
Right now, Drei isn't legitimately entitled to being Phantom.
That's because she couldn't put an end to her relationship with the previous Phantom.
Once she becomes the true Phantom,
I'm sure Drei will be more calm and composed.
In other words,
once she fells Zwei by her own hand.
Reiji.
You didn't bring a lunchbox today, did you?
Yeah, but how do you know?
Alright, let's go to school's cafeteria.
I don't mind, but what about your lunchbox?
I already ate it after second period.
Well then, I declare that Motegi be permitted to sit in this spot.
Thank you.
Hi there, do you remember me?
Of course, my brother told me you're Motegi-kun The Unpopular.
How are you introducing me?
Aren't you just using me as well?
I beg you to spare me some of your happiness, please!
You have some serious problems, man.
It's alright every once in a while, brother.
You agree?
I'm honored to be of the same opinion as Elen-chan.
Maybe there are some things we have in common.
Cal can't easily attack us in a crowd of people.
You're right.
Watch over my spot. I'll go get some food.
Oh, okay.
Mine is lunch B!
Order for yourself.
Was your pressing business the other day concerning Elen?
There were some things about our house that needed to be discussed.
I'm so sorry, even though I knew he was on a date with Mio.
It wasn't a date.
In that case,
you should have told her earlier.
Well, it's kind of embarrassing.
You don't understand a girl's feelings.
A guy like that doesn't deserve his side dishes.
Why are you eating mine?
Because you're sucking up all the happiness.
What are you talking about?
Huh? You dimwit, can't you see the situation?
Not many are blessed with such luck.
Exactly.
Take for Motegi for example.
Huh? What?
Someone asked me to deliver this.
Thank you.
Sorry, I'll be off for a while.
What a shame...
What is it?
It's a request from a junior.
My tiny bit of bliss...
Be happy it was there at all.
Well then...
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going to make sure no one pesters her.
Elen is popular, you won't last long if you bother every time.
You siscon.
But...
Please go after her. She's your only sister after all.
Sorry.
I'll make up for this later.
What do I get?
Dream on.
Elen.
Are you looking for someone?
Do you want to kill me?
That's right, you're able to kill me.
Not by command or from being cornered.
All you need is your own free will.
That's your trait, Zwei.
There's a big gap between you who instinctively kills and Ein who was designed for mechanical obedience.
That is to say, you are a failure.
In spite of that, you were the forerunner of a new cadet for me.
I have been struggling with the concept of "hatred" lately.
Have you seen my third creation?
Drei.
What have you done to Cal?
In the end, I didn't do anything.
I applied no brainwashing or mind control, I even left her memories and emotions intact.
However, one thing I amplified manifold.
Her innate hatred.
I'm grateful you left me the finest material.
Scythe, you're...
Unforgivable? Deserving of hate?
You can't kill me here, though.
The risk is too high.
Good self-restraint. You have both serenity and hatred.
A fantastic balance.
Drei acts with unbridled fervor at times. She doesn't know restraint.
But,
at least she is wise enough not to kill in public.
You don't say...
You have to hurry if you wish to come to her aid.
Show yourself. No one will disturb us here.
Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you "ex-Phantom"?
I've been living 'til today...
...because I want to hunt down and kill him.
That's the only reason.