Training or not, isn't running 10km every morning a bit much?
What are you, a baby?
Don't worry, we know!
We have to reach the next stage as Precures to save Trump Kingdom!
And this training will help us reach it!
As this is the tenth day, this should be the final session!
That girl's there again...
Morimoto?
Finally! Goal!
You okay, Rikka?
Do I look okay?
Man, I'm hungry!
Then shall we eat breakfast at my estate?
Can we really?
Absolutely not!
You have no time to waste!
Your final day's schedule is packed until sundown!
But I wanted to go to the festival with everyone!
Training comes first!
Come on...
I agree with the need to train...
But is this not a bit excessive?
No, we need to train as hard as humanly...
Are you okay?
Aguri!
Um...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Heart Pounding!
Aguri's Summer Vacation!
She should be all better after a bit of rest.
Thank goodness...
Thanks for looking out for her.
Are you a friend of Aguri's?
W-We're not really friends!
We're just in the same class...
What's your name?
Morimoto Eru.
Nice name!
So, how is Aguri at school?
C'mon, tell us!
Oh, sure!
Aguri always acts really grown-up.
Playing dodgeball indoors could get someone hurt!
She'd never let anyone tell her she was wrong, even upperclassmen,
and everyone admires how she stands up for herself!
Sounds just like how she is with us.
I was just noticing how well she seems to get along with you all...
since she doesn't seem interested in her classmates...
Huh?
I mean, it's not like she ignores us!
She talks to everyone,
and she does her work in group projects,
but she never does anything more with us...
So, Eru, you want to be friends with Aguri?
Huh?
Uh, th-that's not really it...
It totally is, so leave it to us!
The Happy Prince all over again...
Aguri!
You're all right!
Morimoto...
She was worried about you, so she stayed here the whole time!
I'm fine, so we need to resume our training!
Now now, know your limits.
Straining yourself when you're sick is bad for the body.
Taking breaks is important as well.
And that means...
that today's training is officially over!
So how about we go to the summer festival with Eru?
Summer festival?
Yeah! There'll be fireworks!
Not to mention the Super Special Scrumptious Sweets!
Super Special Scrumptious Sweets?
Why would I go to a festival for that?
What say you, Eru?
W-Well, if Aguri's okay with it, I'd like to go...
Sounds like a plan!
But...
It's important to spend time with your friends.
I understand.
Great!
We'll meet at 7 by the stairs leading to the festival plaza.
Okay!
I'll see you at 7, Aguri!
Take care!
Why did you do that?
I'm not opposed to spending time with friends, either.
But right now, there's something far more important at stake!
Is that the reason why you haven't been making friends at school?
Exactly.
I used to be the same way.
Of course, I still haven't forgotten Trump Kingdom.
But I've learned so much from spending time with everyone.
Aguri...
it's good to have friends.
I understand...
Blasted Cure Ace...
Despite my irrefutable beauty, she dared upstage me?
Makes your stomach turn.
All I care about now is seeing her put six feet under!
Dish best served cold.
What have you been eating?
Streeeetchy ice cream.
Streeeetchy, you say?
Why, that's it!
You can't have any.
She can only stay as Cure Ace for five minutes.
So if I can undo her transformation by streeeetching out the battle, I'll win!
Make sure you pretend to be dolls.
You got it!
Will this really work?
Oh!
Eru!
Thanks for waiting!
Um...
Where's Aguri?
Huh?
There are so many yummy-looking sweets!
I want to eat them all!
Found ya, Aguri!
You're not easy to find!
You were late, girls.
Come on, didn't we agree to meet by the stairs?
Huh?
Oh, don't worry.
Anyway, that yukata looks great on you!
This is something my grandmother gave me...
It's so cute, Aguri!
Thank you, Morimoto.
Um...
Eru's looks cute too, right?
Yes, it's very cute, Eru...
Now, how about those Super Special Scrumptious Sweets?
In time.
First, we enjoy the festival!
Um...
Wanna do the Goldfish Scoop?
Goldfish Scoop?
I did it!
The net broke...
Too bad!
I see. It's called "Goldfish Scoop" because you scoop goldfish.
But I wanted this black moor...
Don't worry.
I'll show you the reason they call me the "Goldfish Super Scooper"!
My stall ain't that easy.
Here I go!
Didn't seem too super to me.
Then allow me!
Think you can, little lady?
Wow!
Watch it!
Keep your dolls outta the water.
But I tell ya, toys these days are really somethin'...
I shall try next!
You can do it!
Listen, try to scoop on the water's surface at a 45 degree angle.
I understand.
It's time!
Aguri, you're soaked...
As are you, Eru...
I hit it!
Too bad!
Ya gotta make it fall off the shelf!
Allow me...
Makopi's aiming at the Makopi card!
Hey, congrats!
It takes more than just aim.
You have to predict the bullet's trajectory.
Just shoot already!
Congrats!
I shall avenge Eru's honor!
You can do it!
It's time!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Wow, Aguri!
Yummy!
But this is just regular shaved ice.
What about the Super Special Scrumptious Sweets?
Want a bite?
N-No...
Here.
Yummy!
The bitterness of the green tea envelops the sweet azuki beans!
Bravo!
Please, have a sample of mine!
Sure!
All right, we're all having a shaved ice swap!
A brilliant idea!
Her true colors shine when sweets are involved...
It's strange.
The ice you all shared with me tasted better than mine.
No surprise.
It's because you were eating with everyone!
With everyone?
Yeah.
A friend of mine said the same thing.
Wait, could the Super Special Scrumptious Sweets have been...
Geez.
If all these people weren't here, I could have the show all to myself.
But I guess it's more fun with more people around...
Aw, just...
have it for yourself.
We shall grant...
your desire two-fold!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
It's the summer festival!
Everyone, go home!
Did you finish your homework?
It's a Selfish!
Eru, let's escape!
Girls, let's go!
Right!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor summer festival who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
You appear once again, Precures.
Huh? Our target's gone.
Hold on! Where is Cure Ace?
Even without Cure Ace...
We can fight you on our own!
Why you insolent...
Destroy them!
Yo-yo yo!
Time to pop off!
The girls...
There she is!
Target located!
You need to cut it out!
Eru, run!
Worry not about me, just run!
Now is your chance to finish her off!
We won't let you!
Seeelf!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Let me go, Eru!
I won't!
I want to be your friend, Aguri!
But why go so far?
You helped me, Aguri!
When all the boys were making fun of my frizzy hair...
There's nothing more deplorable than ridiculing someone for their appearance!
You should all be ashamed!
It's a waste of time to be distressed over what other people say about you.
After all, your hair is very cute!
I was so happy!
So this time...
I'm going to save you!
You held something I said to you so dearly...
You're overflowing... with love!
Thank you, Eru.
Aguri...
Prepare for a ring out!
Eru, I have a secret,
but I can't tell you what it is.
Will you still trust in me?
I will!
I trust you, Aguri!
Then will you close your eyes and wait patiently?
Yeah!
Ai!
Precure Dress Up!
Kyupirappa!
Love's trump card,
Cure Ace!
Beauty is the mark of the righteous!
With a single wink,
I shall pierce your heart!
Cure Ace!
She's arrived!
This attack will streeeetch it out for five minutes!
Yo-yo yo!
Poppin' caps!
Ring around the rosie!
Cure Ace!
One minute down.
Four more until your transformation wears off!
Then we'll wipe out the Precures,
and suck out all the Psyche from humankind we can get!
Eru is waiting for me out of trust.
And for her...
I shall fight!
What?!
Though I fight for more than just her.
For daring to harm my dear friends,
you shall not escape unscathed!
I understand why you invited me to this festival.
Until now, I thought only of myself.
But you made me realize that there were people who cared about me right by my side.
And that realization gave me the power of love!
That's right.
But you were the one who taught us that to begin with!
I meant to teach you, but you girls ended up teaching me.
Seeelf!
Leave this to me.
Beautify!
Love Kiss Rouge!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love loooove!
Hey, we didn't even hit three minutes!
Shut up, you!
Our streeeetch out attack failed!
Eru.
It's okay now.
Aguri...
I'm so glad you're safe...
My heart is pounding...
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Professor Davi, we beg of you!
Wh-What is it?
I want to help Mana!
I want to study with Rikka!
I want to sing lullabies for Alice!
So we want you to teach us to transform into humans!
I see. Leave it to me!
Dokidoki Precure:
It's All For Mana!
Charles's Big Transformation!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!