There's something in this world that nobody has seen yet.
Fluffy bangs
give a gentle expression
Gently capture women's hearts
This reeks...
of being fake.
Mold
What the hell. It's getting moldy again.
And I recently wiped off the mold too.
It's something gentle and very sweet.
Where did I put that rag...
And if you were able to put your eyes on it, then you would yearn for it.
That's why the world has hidden it.
To make sure that not just anyone can get their hands on it.
Shit, I can't wipe it off!
But at some point, someone will find it.
That one person who is supposed to find it is also the one who will be able to find it.
That's just how it is.
Tiger & Dragon
Eco, eco, eco, ecology~
Inko-chan, you're still resting? It's morning already.
I got you!
How cold of you, Ryuu-chan.
I told you last night that I have school from today on, right?
Oh, the opening ceremony.
Congratulations on passing last year.
Should you really be sarcastic towards your son when he's going into his new school year?
Hey, the room is dark. Open the curtains!
They're open.
The Takasu House
That's a huge apartment building.
I wonder what kind of people live there.
After it was built, the sun quit shining here and our laundry doesn't dry well.
HERE
Every morning there's mold, moldiness, heaps of mold...
That sharp look! You're beginning to look more and more like your dad!
...more and more like your dad!
Don't compare me to tha—!
Oh, so cool! Even more like your dad!
Are you leaving already? What about my meal?
It's where it always is.
That was...
That was the only thing I didn't want to hear.
It's because of this look in my eyes, which you always praise, that I... I...
Hey, wait up!
T-Takasu!
What the hell are you doing?!
What? Wh—
I didn't mean to!
Please accept this and spare us!
This is all we have! It's true!
S-See? We're not annoying you, are we?!
No, I...
We're sorry!
I...
Lost and Found Items
Oohashi High School
General Affairs Department
Again? You sure pick up a lot of wallets.
Uh, yeah.
I hope we end up in the same class again!
Yeah.
It's there!
Hurray, we're in the same class again!
Crap, not this again...
Hey.
We're in the same class again, aren't we, Takasu?
Kitamura.
Oohashi High School Opening Ceremony
And now this year's opening ceremony has ended.
Everyone, please head towards your individual classrooms and prepare for homeroom.
A new class. It seems that I have to start off by clearing up all the misunderstandings again.
It'll be okay.
I already know, so it won't be necessary for everyone.
Yeah, thanks.
That's right. There are people like him who understand.
And in this class...
Hey, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year too!
You're in class C too, Kushieda?
Takasu-kun, right? Do you remember me?
I appear from time to time around Kitamura.
K-Kushieda Minori, right?
Oh, you remembered my full name! I'm so glad!
And with that, let us passionately enjoy class in high spirits!
Yeah.
O-Okay.
And then—
What's wrong, Takasu?
I-I just need to go the bathroom.
Okay, I'll go on ahead.
What?
Holy shit! He's already heading into a decisive battle!
Takasu Ryuuji and Aisaka Taiga. The most dangerous ones are already clashing!
Whoa, she's so small, just like a doll. But somehow...
Somehow there's this hateful...
As if you'd get eaten if you missed one step...
Whoa, it's true! The delinquent Takasu and the Palmtop Tiger are—!
Shh!
Ferocity of a tiger
But small
Palmtop... Tiger...?
I get it! Palmtop Ti—
Yeah. Fits perfectly.
Okay, that's it for today.
Those who haven't turned in the new questionnaire, please come to the faculty office later, okay?
Okay, Takasu-kun?
Ah, yes.
Are you okay, Taiga? You were late.
I went to the doctor, and he said that it's caused by house dust.
A modern-day illness, must be tough.
So the Palmtop Tiger is friends with Kushieda Minori.
The one with problems here is me.
You okay?
Yeah, I guess.
But, you know...
They were amazing, Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun!
The Palmtop Tiger sure is strong.
Anyways, Takasu only looks scary. He's not actually a delinquent.
Really?
Seems it will be easier to clear up the misunderstandings.
Taiga, 'sup?
N-Nothing.
T-Takasu-kun, you aren't lost about where to go with your life, are you...?
What?
B-Bu-Bu-But... I really need you to turn in your questionnaire.
All of the other students have submitted theirs already.
Oh, I'm sorry, I forg—
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
You don't want some stranger coming in and telling you what to do
while you're still deciding on what to do with your life, right?
Please forgive me!
Fire Cabinet
I'm late.
Time Zero will be ove—
Are you okay...?
My bag, my bag...
I'll just leave her be...
Wha—!
What ar — What are you do — What are you doing?
What are you—
I just came here to get my—
That's your bag?! Isn't your seat the ne—
I got the placements of the seats mix — mixed—!
Why does she want my bag?
Hey, stop it already!
Why, you!
A-Aisaka?
H-Hey!
Idiot!
She's a mess.
This room too.
Your dad is in heaven, you see.
He was so cool! He'd hide weekly magazines behind his shirt in case he got stabbed.
I'm going numb just from the thought!
Just because I look like you...
I'm having mountains of trouble, you know!
If I didn't have this face, no one would be afraid of me
and I wouldn't end up getting involved with the Palmtop Tiger.
I'd have more faith in myself.
Best Driving Collection - Spring
And then...
Oh right, the new questionnaire.
What's this?
To Kitamura Yuusaku
To Kitamura Yuusaku.
From Aisaka Taiga
From... Aisaka Taiga?
Oh, I get it.
"You put this in my bag by mistake, right?
I can't imagine what's inside since I didn't peek!
So I'll just return it to you, then!"
Shit, I gotta reseal it!
She... She's one hell of a klutz, isn't she?
Gonna sleep.
Yasuko... isn't supposed to be home yet, right?
Yay, let's drink more!
Takasu Yasuko
Professional Name: Mirano
At work
Heeey...
The window's...
Ow!
W-What the hell...
I know someone this small...
Aisaka!
Use a tissue!
What the...
W-W-What the...
...hell..
...are...
...you...
...doing?!
Forget about it.
Forget about...?
Oh, that le—
—tter...
I can no longer live on now that you've found out about that. I have to die!
Then don't try to kill me!
I don't want to die, so I've got to kill you!
Or... you could forget all about it!
That's impossible!
It'll be okay, I'll just hit you on the head with this. Even if I can't kill you, I can send your memories flying away.
Don't send them flying!
Listen, that letter—
Shut up.
What...?
Shut up, shut up!
You saw it, didn't you?! You read it, didn't you?!
I'm trying to tell you, I didn't-
No, that won't do.
So you have to forget all about that l-l-love letter!
It was empty!
Em...pty...?
Yes. There was nothing inside.
You're lucky you didn't turn it over to Kitamura.
So let's just leave this failure be and—
H-Hey!
Just how hungry are you?
I got tired of the convenience store.
Convenience store? What, don't your parents fe—
Everyone has their family issues, I guess.
Here.
If you had just quietly handed over the bag earlier, things wouldn't have ended up like this.
How do you intend to make up for it?!
It's still stuck to your face.
Hearing that from a guy who was born only to add the scent of garlic to the oil used in this fried rice...
Now listen here...
How is a love letter embarrassing?
You see, that's not even close to being embarrassing. Just wait.
Behold!
What's all this?
Do you know what that is? You don't, do you?
That's a list of songs I would use if I were to put on a concert for the girl I like.
That's a poem I wrote for her without realizing it.
MDs to play while I'm on a car trip with her.
I don't have a license, of course.
I have plans laid out for all seasons of the year.
Disgusting, isn't it?
Since I don't have the guts to confess to her, I just have to imagine like this.
It's horribly miserable, but I don't think of it as embarrassing!
You've got to have faith in yourself!
You've gone beyond imagining and went and took action!
You've got to think about the future, passionately, in high spirits!
"I present this to thee, Kushieda Minori."
Yes, just like Kushieda Minori!
Wha—!
So you like Minori?
How impudent.
Learn your place.
Shut up! You're not one to talk!
What's with you?! You said you'd forget!
Shut up! Goose, goosebumps!
I'm sorry, Inko-chan. Did we wake you?
What are you showing me?! How disgusting!
What are you saying about my precious family?!
I-I-I-I—
That's it! Are you going to present yourself to the visitor, Inko-chan?
Go ahead and say your name!
Inpo!
No, you see, Inko-chan isn't feeling well today...
Whoa, it's already this late!
E-Either way, we're birds of the same feather! I won't tell anyone about the letter! Can't you be okay with that?
No.
Why?! No wait, you've already gotten a meal, just leave!
Rather, please leave? My wacky mom is about to come home!
No fucking way!
I can't trust you.
And besides...
How are love letters? They're not fashionable anymore, are they?
Why are you fidgeting now?!
I'll give you advice on romantic relationships any time, but it's already late, so how about tomorrow...?
Really? You'll help me?
I will. I will I will I will! I'll do anything!
Anything, right? You'll obey me like a dog? You'll do anything to the extreme?
Yes, I will. I swear!
So, let's just end it at that, okay? Okay?
How did she get in through the window?
Well then.
I'll walk you home.
No, it's okay. It's close, and I've got this wooden sword.
Wait, that's just dangerous.
Hey, that hole...
Oh, that? I can just cover it up with some paper.
Here.
You can use this.
If it ends up costing money, I'll pay you later.
See you, Ryuuji.
Yeah.
Wait, did she just call me by my first name?
Yes, this is the Takasu residenc—
Get the hell over here! You're—
Yes?
You hung up, didn't you?
Come over where?
Huh?
The veranda, why?
How?
You said you'd do anything, just like a dog, right?
Wait, that was about yesterday's thing about Kitamura—
If you don't come, you know what will happen, don't you? I can show you what will happen if you want me to...
Um, you see...
Wait ten more minutes! The seasoned rice will be done in ten more minutes!
Three?
You want some too?
Whoa.
Excuse me?
Huh?
It's open?
What the hell is this smell?!
Aisaka-san, I'm coming in.
Something smells horrible.
Aisaka!
Aisaka. Aisaka! Aisaka!
Your kitchen!
Allow me to—!
Please, allow me to clean your kitchen!
What, sleeping again?
She looks handcrafted...
The sleeping Aisaka really looked like a doll.
The house had no trace of anyone really living there. It looked like it was part of someone's doll house.
But it was too large to be someone's doll house.
It'll take fifteen minutes, I guess.
Alright!
What's... this...?
Hey.
I'm still at it, but it's a lot cleaner now, isn't it?
It was horrid!
The water clogged up in the sink was rotten.
The drainage was awfully moldy and all the waste was like hell spawn.
And the room was full of dust...
Trespassing. Forced cleaning. You didn't go around marking the place, did you, dog?!
Dog?
I'll have to apologize to the other dogs. You're a mongrel of a dog.
Mon-grel.
What an ungrateful bitch, when other people have—!
Hey, where's your table prayer?
Dear god of rice and producers of this product, I thank you for this meal!
Oh you...
Hey, your nose stopped dripping.
Yeah, since the room's all clean...
What did you just say?
Shut up!
Ryuuji and Taiga
Next Episode Preview
Disoriented agreement.
Surfacing misunderstandings.
The power of genes.
Taiga, you...
You're one hell of a klutz.
Shut up and rot.