If I can't kill, I'll be killed.
Are you awake now?
There's no need to be scared.
I'm not going to attack you anymore.
You're...
I have no name.
But if you must, call me Ein.
At least, that's what they call me.
Ein,
why did you attack me?
To have you prove your skills.
My skills?
You were endowed with certain instincts from the moment you were born:
an instinct for killing,
and an instinct for surviving.
Instincts that define an assassin.
That can't be...
I don't understand.
Besides, what proof do you have?
You tried to kill me.
In that situation,
any normal person would have panicked and would have been killed as a result.
But you were different.
You chose to act before assessing the situation and managed to survive,
Zwei.
"Zwei"?
That's your name.
Don't just make up weird names for me!
I've got a proper name, and it's-
My...
name is...
You no longer have one.
It's pointless to try and remember it.
What are you talking about?
Your memories have been erased,
by Inferno.
Magnificent.
Investigations revealed that the victim was a well-known crime lord.
Your Phantom is truly a masterpiece.
It is presumed that his murder was a result of the ongoing gang wars in the area.
I'm honored, Mr. McGwire.
I never imagined a kid like her could be so capable.
Exactly.
That's precisely why I've given her the title of "Phantom."
You've achieved quite an accomplishment.
You have birthed us a specter that is truly out of this world.
Well, it's all thanks to Ms. McCunnen's support.
It appears you have some capable people working for you, Claudia.
But I must say, you took your time in eliminating that journalist.
I beg to differ.
Also, you allowed tourists to witness your attempts at eliminating him.
I have no idea where you've heard such stories from,
but all witnesses have been taken care of.
The corpses have also been accounted for.
Excellent.
Did Phantom take care of that, too?
Yes.
You were supposed to be killed,
so that all evidence relating to the incident would be erased.
But Master noticed your talents,
and decided it'd be a shame to let you die.
Master?
The Scythe Master.
My master.
Master then stole your memories,
and prepared a new life for you.
A life as a member of Inferno;
a life as an assassin.
An assassin?
Me?
You will become Zwei, my alter ego.
That's ridiculous!
Why would I even-
I couldn't possibly kill a-
You can refuse all you want,
but when you do...
you will die as originally planned.
Right here. Right now.
You will change if you want to live.
You can no longer prove your existence other than by killing.
I...
I don't want to die.
This is a dream.
This whole thing is just a nightmare.
If that's how you want to console yourself, that's fine.
Just think of it as one big dream.
But I'm telling you now, it's going to be a long one.
Change into that.
You'll be with me day and night starting today.
You will follow every order I give you.
Understand?
Let's get started.
Zwei's progress is coming along nicely.
He's faithfully dedicating himself to the training.
He's quite obedient.
Even thinking will become a chore if he continues that rigorous training regimen everyday.
That's right.
That's how you break them.
Let's produce something that won't betray our expectations, Ms. McCunnen.
You had expectations?
What is mine is yours.
Everything's for Inferno, after all.
This is how you hold it.
Don't place your finger over the trigger.
Focus all your power to your fingers instead of to your shoulders.
This is the rear sight, and this is your front sight.
Focus your aim through the rear sight into the front sight.
When aiming, stabilize the gun by stretching out your right arm,
and pulling back with your left.
Even then, most of the power should be localized to your hands and not to your arms.
Don't panic when you pull the trigger.
Pull it as if you're squeezing gently.
Shoot.
Fire the remaining five rounds in succession.
You should be able to hit the mark all six times from this distance.
Once you can do that, we'll work on your speed.
Your target is to fire six rounds in four seconds.
First, concentrate on hitting the mark.
That's still too slow.
Looks like you can shoot accurately,
but at this rate, you'll die before you can even shoot your target.
Repeat.
I will successfully fulfill any task given to me.
This way, I won't have to think.
This way, I can be at peace.
I'll even forget the many questions I have...
and with it, my daily life.
I'm going out.
Carry out the usual regimen.
You're going out?
I've got a job to do.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
He's the Scythe Master?
We haven't had a sniping assignment like this in a while,
but I guess it won't be a problem for you.
You will be 700 yards from the target.
You'll be using a Remington .308 for this assignment.
The current weather at the location is cloudy with slight winds,
and it'll most likely stay that way until tomorrow morning.
The details are inside.
Any questions?
No.
Good.
So, how's Zwei coming along?
He's finished the basic regimen.
Tomorrow he'll start on a different training regimen.
I guess I should start getting his practical test ready then, eh?
Don't mind me.
As you were.
I guess we've never met before.
I'm Claudia McCunnen.
I'm sure there's much more you want to know about me other than my name.
No, there isn't.
But I'm sure you're interested in learning about Inferno since they did pick you up.
I'll take your silence as a "yes."
Inferno...
is trying to bring about a new sovereign order into a world without legal order,
or something like that anyway.
If gangs and mafias could be compared to nation states,
then Inferno would be the United Nations.
Inferno's goal is to unite the underworld.
An utopian thought like that would not even be said as a joke a while back,
but now it's being turned into a reality by...
Phantom.
That's right. Your coach.
Phantom's power is absolute.
Her existence, as something that can effectively eliminate targets,
provides the highest level of confidence to Inferno,
while striking the greatest fear in the hearts of its enemies.
Without a doubt, she is the greatest assassin.
But...
In the end, she's only a puppet of the syndicate.
Both Phantom and I have no choice but to live as slaves.
As you say, we may be forcing this lifestyle upon you,
but you're not a slave.
Even you  possess a freedom.
It's called speed.
Speed?
Even in a set course, you can accelerate towards any goal,
so long as you desire and work for it.
Even if that goal is to stand right at the top of this syndicate.
How you progress through it is completely up to you.
But don't ever think of yourself as a slave again.
That kind of thinking will only result in you giving up your worth to those who belittle you.
I wanted to discuss more with you,
but there's work I need to tend to.
Goodbye, Zwei.
You know, cars are driven by people,
not by puppets.
Even in a set course, you can accelerate towards any goal,
so long as you desire and work for it.
Desire, work...
I'd forgotten about those two words all this time...
Ein.
What is it?
Did today's mission involve killing someone?
Yes.
Why are you an assassin?
I don't know.
I've never been told about my past.
That means...
Yes.
I'm just like you.
They erased my memories and turned me into an assassin.
But so what?
Surviving the moment...
is all that matters.
There's nothing for us assassins in the past or in the future.
But this woman called Claudia said...
Claudia?
She came here this afternoon.
She said that we're not slaves and that we, too, have freedom.
If that  is what you want to believe.
But soon, like me, you won't be able to feel anything.
It's the only way of coping with this way of life.
It won't be long for you either.
You'll understand when you finally kill someone.
It's easy to pull the trigger when you're just aiming at bricks...
But...
Fire.
Fire, Zwei.
Zwei...
This is just the prolongment of a dream;
a dream that will not end until you die.