When did you last replace your shaft?
After the mop up, sir. That was six days ago.
Right. She's clear.
Okay, you're good. Who's next?
I'm with squad 42. Christa Lenz, sir!
Well, let's take a look.
So now we can actually get in trouble for killing Titans?
Yeah, it's crazy, but they were valuable test subjects.
I know that. What I don't understand is why
they're trying to find the killer among the cadets.
Right, we're worn out enough as it
is from cleaning up the battlefield.
Who'd have the energy?
Guess someone hated lookin' at
those Titans even more than I did.
Mm. The sad thing is they may've actually
helped the Titans more than anything.
All that knowledge lost, and for
what, someone's personal revenge?
It just doesn't make any sense.
Well, it might sound dumb, but I'm glad they did it.
Before I'd actually seen a Titan, I was convinced
I wanted to be a Scout and take 'em all on.
Now I never wanna lay eyes on one again.
And today, we have'ta pick which Regiment to join.
Jean. Are you really gonna do it?
I guess regret's the order of the day.
Right about now, we're all wondering
why the hell we ever put on this uniform.
Standing here, watching our friends burn.
How could we possibly think anything else?
Sorry, Marco.
I don't even know which of these bones are yours, anymore.
If I hadn't become a soldier,
I would've never had to worry about who's next.
So, you're tellin' me it's better
to just cut our losses, is that it?
Let all the death and destruction be meaningless?
We have to fight. I know that's the right thing to do.
But I also know I'm not a suicidal maniac like he is.
Huh?
Promise me you're not gonna take this the wrong way.
But I don't think you're a
good leader 'cause you're strong.
I think it's 'cause you know what it is to be weak.
You're one of us.
You're scared out of your mind, just like we all are.
It makes you alert; sympathetic.
So, what am I going to do now?
Hey guys. Question for you.
Huh?
So have you decided yet?
Which regiment you're gonna join?
I've made my choice. It'll be rough, but...
Dammit. I'm gonna join the Scouts!
Ah, hell. Hey, Annie. You think Jean meant it?
You think he's serious about signing up with the Scouts?
Wait. Jean said that?
Who cares?
So you're sticking with the MPs, huh?
I'm really startin' to think I might go that way, too.
Tell me something.
If someone ordered you to die, would you do it?
W-What? Of course not.
Well, then my advice is do what's best for you.
And what about you, Armin?
Oh, uh, I think I might.
If the situation truly called for it.
And I knew that my sacrifice might save others.
Not that I'd want to.
So, you've decided then.
Mm. I've planned to join the Scouts from the start.
Come on. Not you too, Armin?
I'm impressed. For a mouse,
you've got guts; I'll give you that.
Uh. Thanks, I guess.
You know, I'm beginning to suspect
you care more than you let on.
Huh?
It's just, the way you're trying to discourage
us from the Scouts, you're looking out for us.
Is that why you're joining the MPs?
I bet you think you can do some good there too, huh?
No, not really.
I just want to live.
The only person I'm looking out for is myself.
After that whole inspection, they didn't turn up
one person who used their ODM gear without permission.
So who could'a done it?
Beats me. And right now, I'm more
concerned with the recruitment drive tonight.
How many cadets are crazy enough to join
the regiment with the highest casualties?
Hey, Eren! You know if anyone in
your class is thinking about joining us?
Yeah, there're a few.
Or, at least, there were.
I'm really not so sure now.
Fall in!
Make ready, people! We're going on patrol.
Yes, sir!
Good morning, captain! Reporting for duty!
Eren. You will stay within ten meters of me at all times.
The only reason that you're out of your cell
is because I'm keeping an eye on you. Understood?
Yes, sir!
Let's ride!
Hyah!
Jean! You're really set on the Scouts?
Yeah.
Whoa, are you serious? I mean. Aren't you terrified?
Huh? Of course I'm scared, I'm not an idiot here.
Uh. Then why are you...?
Because I am scared of the Titans.
And I want to do somethin' about it.
Huh?
But listen, I understand that
joining the Scouts isn't for everybody.
I won't guilt trip you.
Unlike a certain suicidal maniac.
Eren, huh?
Guess he's already been a
Scout for a while now, hasn't he?
Cadets! Fall in! Head over to the
platform! Time to make your choice! Move it!
At the end of the day, there's nothing that anyone
could say to persuade you into risking your life.
Same goes for me.
So believe me when I say this decision is all mine.
Good evening.
I am Erwin Smith, Commander of the Survey
Corp, also known as the Scout Regiment.
Today, you will choose your regiment.
Let's cut to the chase here. The Scouts need you.
We need all the warm bodies we can get.
After the recent Titan attack, you now know
first-hand the horrors of which they are capable.
As well as the limits of your own skill.
However...!
This battle's aftermath gave humanity
a new chance for victory.
I refer to Eren Jaeger.
After selflessly risking life and limb,
he has proven, beyond a doubt,
his unwavering loyalty to our cause.
Hope lives in him.
Eren didn't just help to deter the Titan invasion.
He's offered us a means to
discern the truth of their origin!
Intel suggests that the cellar of Jaeger's home in
Shiganshina holds a vital secret regarding our enemy.
We will form an expedition to find this secret.
Find it. And use it to break free from the Titans'
tyrannical hundred-year reign once and for all!
The cellar, huh?
Things have progressed this far?
If we can figure out what makes 'em
tick, we can hit 'em where it hurts!
I know the Scouts desperately need recruits,
but going public with this is out of line!
Maybe it's a ploy. A covert strategy?
Question is if he's baited the hook,
who does he intend to catch?
Before we can reach the
aforementioned cellar in Shiganshina,
another problem must be dealt with.
We must first retake Wall Maria.
Of course, this is much easier said than done.
And now that the gate at Trost
has been rendered inaccessible,
we'll be forced to stage future operations
from the Calanath District, further east.
Thus, the battalion route we've spent the last four
years establishing is now completely useless to us.
Over the course of those four years,
we've incurred losses in excess of 60%.
60% in four years. That's a horrifying figure.
One month from now,
we will conduct a recon mission outside the walls.
Recruits from among your ranks
will be expected to take part.
I estimate a third of them will die.
After four years, most will be dead.
But those who endure will be amongst
the most capable soldiers alive.
Now having heard this dismal state of affairs,
whoever still wishes to put their life
on the line and join us, remain here.
But first ask yourself. Can you give your heart?
Can you give everything for humanity?
That is all.
Those wanting to join other regiments are dismissed.
Commander! I think that you may've
overly intimidated the cadets, sir.
None of them are gonna stick around.
Dammit! C'mon, I've already decided.
Stop making me feel like such a fool.
If I don't leave now, I'll
have to go through it all again.
I left my village. The MPs were the whole point.
I wanted Mom to be proud.
I wanted to be treated right.
Everyone respects them. Period.
But there's no going back.
Not after you've seen it.
Seen them up close, and...
Seen how they eat people.
I ask you, if you were ordered to die, could you do it?
We don't wanna die, sir.
Of course. Let us hope that you don't then.
You who stayed, you are now one of us.
Allow me to welcome you to the Scout Regiment.
This is a genuine salute, soldiers!
Together, we give our hearts!
Sir!
Everyone.
Joined the Scouts. This is so stupid.
This is scary! I just wanna go home.
Ah, man. What the hell?
If you're gonna keep crying, then don't stay.
Those of you standing here have worked through your fear.
You have proven yourselves courageous.
Each one of you has my respect.
Attention!
I'm Section Commander Ness.
And this girl is my horse, Charrette.
Fair warning. Charette is rather partial to pulling hair.
So I'd watch out if you don't wanna go bald.
We're glad to meetcha.
Hey, stop that, ya freak!
Can I get a hand here, you guys?
Our training began in earnest the next day.
However, the lessons were rarely combat-oriented.
With an emphasis on memorizing Commander
Erwin's long-range scouting formation.
Despite being such a precisely detailed,
meticulously calculated formation,
Eren Jaeger's position was somewhat less than clear.
You rookies will be here.
between the wagon defense squad
and the Scout support squad.
You will run spare horses as well as relay signals.
Our Special Ops squad'll be positioned
here, on standby. Behind the center rank.
So we'll be pretty far back then.
It's the safest position in the formation.
The supply wagons don't even get such fine treatment.
Our goal this time around is
to simply leave, then come back.
Today's expedition will serve as a sort of test run.
To see if we've got a shot at
getting you all the way to Shiganshina.
Understood. Either way, I still don't really know
how to use my ability or if I can even control it.
Eren. Do you understand what the
Commander was asking you about back then?
Huh?
Who do you think the real enemy is here?
What did he mean by that? What do you guys think?
Not a clue.
Well, if I told you that I knew what he
meant, I'd be lying to you. That said I...
It's entirely feasible, that this
operation has an alternate goal.
And yet, the Commander has decided it's
best to withhold it from the rank and file.
If that's the case, leaving and coming
back is all we need to concern ourselves with.
Have faith in the Commander.
I will.
Today's training has concluded. Return to base.
Whoa. I don't believe it! Oruo! May I be
excused to talk to my friends for a minute?
Fine. Just don't take too long.
Hey Mikasa! Armin!
Eren!
Man, am I glad to see you guys!
Eren. Have they mistreated you in any way?
Like subjecting you to any cruel
experiments, or some sort of mental anguish?
No. N-Not at all.
That pipsqueak took things way too far.
I will make him pay for it one day.
Hold on. You mean Captain Levi?
Hey! Eren!
Long time no see!
Oh, hey guys. You're all here!
Whoa, wait.
If all of you are here, then does that mean...
You're saying that you guys all joined the Scouts?
Well, yeah. Why else would we be here?
Of course. So then Jean, Annie, and
Marco went to the Military Police then?
Wait a sec. You joined, too?
Marco is dead.
He what? Wait, what are you saying?
Marco's not dead.
You're just kidding around, right?
I wish I could tell you he died nobly or heroically.
Truth is, I don't even know how he went out.
He died alone. There was no one there to see it happen.
Marco's dead.
Alright, rookies! Form up!
Your uniforms are here!
So then, you guys are really...
Yes. We will be in the upcoming operation as well.
Hey. Eren. I heard that while you were in your Titan form,
you intentionally tried to crush Mikasa.
You mind telling us what that's all about?
You're wrong. He thought he was
just swatting a fly, nothing more.
I wasn't asking you.
Oh, by the way. That cut on your cheek looks pretty deep.
Just how did you get that, again?
Apparently it's all true.
When I was a Titan I... I tried to kill Mikasa.
"Apparently?" As in you don't
remember whether you did or not?
So basically, you can transform
into a 14-meter tall monster at will,
but when you do, you don't
actually have full control over it?
Not yet. But that's right.
Do you hear that everyone? What a fine situation this is.
Our lives and the fate of all
mankind rest on his shoulders.
I'm guessin' we'll probably all end up like Marco,
dead well before Eren even knows it.
Stop it! What's the point in chastising Eren now?
Just give it a rest.
Listen, Mikasa. Unlike you, most of the rest of us
aren't willing to just throw
our lives away for him on a whim.
We need a reason. The truth.
We want to know what we're laying our lives down for.
Otherwise, we might hesitate when the time is at hand.
What we want is a guarantee from Eren.
Show us what you're worth. Prove it to us.
We're asking you to make us
believe that you're worth dying for.
You think you can do that?
If you can, then we're with you. All the way!
Right.
Commander. The time approaches.
Titans in the vicinity have been lured away!
Gate opens in thirty seconds!
Awesome, it's the Scouts!
See that symbol? They call it the Wings of Freedom!
So cool!
This is it! The day has come for
humanity to take another step forward!
Now let's show those Titans exactly what we're made of!
Open the gate!
Forward!
It's officially begun. The 57th Recon Mission!
Scouts, move out!
The Scout Regiment takes up its long-range scouting
formation, and begins to make progress beyond the wall.
Their efforts, however, come to an abrupt halt.
A new foe presents itself. An
enigmatic Titan displaying intelligence.