Open!
Hanna-chan? What's wrong?
Question. Suzuko-san,
have you heard any rumors
about Selector battles?
No.
Acknowledgment.
Why? Did something happen?
Denial. Nothing in particular.
Remember what Mizushima-san said?
That the battles would begin again.
So I'm gathering information, just in case.
But...
Understanding. Don't worry.
I don't want to get involved
in the battles myself.
Oh, Hanna-sama,
you're not going to tell her you
were chosen as a Selector?
Foolishness.
Suzuko-san seems to have not been chosen,
so there's no need to tell her.
You're so kind.
Request.
Actually, there's something
I wanted to ask you.
Give me more details about these battles.
I don't know any more than
I told you yesterday.
Wait...
Perhaps I did know something else...
But I forgot.
You're going to rip me up?
Stop! Don't stop!
Hanna-sama, when I didn't tell
you about your brother,
you didn't do anything to me.
You may punish me now by
torturing me, if you wish.
Refusal.
That was a necessary experience for me.
So in a sense, I'm grateful
to you, Anonymous-chan.
You are?
What a shame.
Hitoe's out with a cold today.
I got a text.
Ruuko? Ruuko!
Sorry...
What did you say?
If you want to talk to someone,
I'm always here for you.
Yuzuki...
The Selector battles are still continuing?
Yes, that's what a girl
named Mizushima-san said.
But you stopped them, didn't you?
But she says they're not over.
No...
So she asked me to help her end them for real...
Umph!
But I told her no.
Was that really the right thing to do, though?
It was.
You did enough last time.
It's not your problem anymore.
Yeah...
Hitoe, are you okay?
I'm fine, Midoriko.
Oh! Midori-san!
Midoriko is fine.
I'm sorry, I wasn't thinking.
It's okay.
Anyway, why did you stay home from school?
I wanted to get ready for things.
There's this new stuff,
the coins and key cards.
Get ready to fight?
If you lose this time,
you lose your memories, right?
There are lots of memories
I don't want to lose.
Hitoe...
What are you doing after school?
There's someplace I want to stop by.
Does it have to do with the Selector battles?
Yes.
What happened?
Nothing, I just want to look into some things.
I want to help.
Tell me if something happens.
Thank you. But nothing's
happening right now.
Piruluk.
What?
We're starting with three
coins this time, right?
Yeah.
Everyone starts with three.
Do these coins include the
memories I lost last time?
No. These coins are your memories,
split into five parts.
But if you win all the battles,
you can alter one of your memories.
You should be able to recover
your lost memories that way.
And the key card, too...
The basic rules of the
battles haven't changed,
but this new element allows you
to change your coin skill.
Change it?
I don't know what will happen...
But I think these cards will
determine the winner.
So I'll need to test how
they work in a battle?
I'm sorry.
There's no need for you to apologize.
Piruluk, I have another wish.
I want to end this cycle of darkness.
Be careful.
It feels like there's more to these
new battles than it looks like.
Practice was extra tough this morning,
so when I ate lunch, I got really sleepy!
I actually fell half-asleep.
You're not supposed to fall asleep!
But I was half-awake, so it's okay!
Jeez...
Back then, I was the one who fell asleep.
Chi-chan?
What?
Why did you believe that we
were childhood friends?
Why...
I just couldn't imagine you lying, maybe?
And the old me that you tell me
about really seems like me,
so I think it's probably true.
Someday, I'll remember for real.
When that happens, let's talk
a bunch about the past.
Yeah.
I'm back.
Tama!
You shouldn't sleep here!
Tama-chan was so excited to help
with the cleaning, she got tired.
Let her sleep until dinnertime.
You're right.
It's so clean now.
Tama's a lot more useful than you are.
What? I'm helping with stuff, too!
It was true...
Ruuko told me today that the
Selector battles were continuing.
So Ruuko has an LRIG now, too?
No, I don't think so.
A girl named Mizushima, who was a Selector,
said that the battles are continuing
and asked for her help.
But she said she refused.
That's right, thinking about Tama-chan...
Let's not tell Ruuko.
Yeah, I think that's best.
Anyway, I'll gather information.
Thank you, Yuzuki.
This is insane.
We went through of all that to end this.
So why did it come back?
Unproductive.
No useful information gained.
Why not give up and fight a battle instead?
Refusal.
I have some free time today.
I'll head over there.
We Have
Battle Tables
Oh, welcome, Hanna-san.
It's been a while.
Hello, Kurebayashi-san.
It's rare for you to come to Shinjuku, isn't it?
Research.
I heard a rumor I could use for a column.
Have you heard anything about it?
What rumor?
Question.
Have you ever heard of Selector battles?
Affirmation? You have?
No, I haven't.
Some kind of new card game?
Hearsay.
I've heard a rumor
that there's a special kind of WIXOSS
battle held by the chosen.
And the losers forfeit part
of their memories.
That wasn't the rule...
Question.
Then what was the rule?
Er, no...
I mean, that's different from
the rumor I heard—
Suspicion.
Didn't you just tell me you'd heard nothing?
Well, I just remembered.
I heard a similar story...
But it's just another urban legend, right?
Distrust. You really think so?
Hanna-san,
I think it's best not to get
involved in those things.
Acknowledgment.
Thank you for your concern.
But I've already reached a point
where I can't turn back.
If you run across any
information worth knowing,
contact me.
Yeah. Okay.
Success.
I met an information source.
But she's not a Selector.
Hypothesis.
She's probably a Selector
from an earlier battle.
You really are smart, Hanna-sama.
Wow, it's so cute!
Oh, man, you're right.
In the Selector battles...
I accomplished nothing.
Akira-chan, can you make a sillier face?
Okay!
All the stuff Akira's doing lately is like that.
Yeah.
She's turning into a comedy character, right?
Sorry!
You asshole!
What the hell's your problem?!
I apologized.
This man molested me.
Hey!
You want me to end your life just like that?
This scar is all I have left.
Do you know where the other Selectors are?
I can sense their general location a little.
I didn't used to be able to...
They want us to be more
proactive about battling.
Where are the closest ones around here?
Let's not do this.
Why?
Because this place is...
Where I fought Satomi.
If you can sense a Selector here...
It might be Carnival, so...
If I fight, I'll lose?
Satomi was the bookmaker,
and Carnival was his former LRIG.
She must know a lot.
And I need that information.
You don't care what happens to you, do you?
I just want to atone for my sins.
You talk like you're a cold person,
but you were always nice to me.
So I'll do whatever I can for you.
But I won't help you commit suicide.
All right. Thank you.
Kiyoi, a Selector is coming!
Hey, you're a Selector, right?
Let's fight.
I'm having a bad day.
Aoi Akira...
Who are you?
Piruluk.
I was your LRIG.
So you were chosen as a Selector again?
Oh, it's you, Piruluk-tan?
I remember you!
You haven't changed, have you?
Yeah, right...
Why haven't you changed?!
Piruluk, you bitch! Screw you!
Why am I the only one who
had to end up like this?!
Everyone used me as a stepping stone!
You were laughing at me, too, weren't you?!
Right?!
Do it.
You know, don't you?
That continuing this will only
hurt everyone involved.
I don't care! Fight!
I ended up with this face
because you were weak!
You lost because you
underestimated Kominato-san—
Shut up!
It's your fault for being weak!
Don't try and blame me!
I only spoke the truth.
You used me, right?
Come on, feel some responsibility.
Feel some responsibility for ruining my life!
That's the way.
Open!
So this is what the stage looks like this time?
Let's deal with anything we don't
understand as we fight.
Together.
Right.
I always hated that self-satisfied
look on your face...
Yahoo!
You're up first, Aki-lucky!
I'll make your face twist with pain soon.
Grow!
Summon two Nyphonium.
Draw.
Magic Hand! Noisy! Star Arrow!
Piruluk!
Combos... That's new.
Hang on a minute!
You're calling your LRIG Piruluk?
You are creepy that way, aren't you?
Oh, did that hurt you?
That makes me happy!
Grow.
Summon Manomin.
Discard hand and attack.
You still like tossing away cards, huh?
I guess you're too stupid to
learn more than one trick.
And you're still trying to provoke
and distract me, aren't you?
What?
I'm not trying to provoke you.
I'm trying to help you out.
Keep doing the same thing
over and over, and you'll lose.
Grow.
Black?
When I was with you, Piruluk-tan,
I used a blue deck, right?
But this one suits me better now.
Bloody Out!
Piruluk!
Aki-lucky, want to follow up
with another attack?
Nope. Turn end.
Akira's fighting style has changed, as well.
Before, she just used brute strength.
What do we do?
Coin bet.
Peeping.
Okay, me, too.
Coin bet.
I can't tell...
You're panicking, aren't you, Piruluk-tan?
But you can't help it!
Happening!
Happening is a coin skill whose
effects can't be predicted.
There's no way to tell what it'll do.
Oh? That's what it did this time...
Ironic!
Your favorite tactic's come
back to haunt you!
Hey, you okay?
If I'm strong when I pair up
with an LRIG who's not you,
that means you're useless!
It's because I'm so smart, isn't it?
Shut up!
If you interrupt me with your crap
when I'm talking, I'll rip you in half!
Aki-lucky, you're scary!
Piruluk!
It's okay.
I can still fight.
Akira really is strong.
Kiyoi, there's something
we haven't tried yet.
Piruluk, tell me how to use my key card.
Okay.
Say "Unlock" and bet a coin.
Unlock.
Coin bet.
What is that?
I... I don't know!
What's this?
Let's go, Kiyoi.
Coin bet.
Catharsis!
What the hell was that?!
Huh? Whawhawhat?
This time, if you lose a battle,
you lose your LRIG, huh?
So it seems.
What the hell did you just do?
Give her back, damn it!
What is this?
Screw you!
Piruluk, you bitch!
It's true that I used you, once.
I can understand why you'd hate me.
But I have a responsibility to
end the Selector battles.
I don't care!
I'm going to beat the shit out of you
and make your face twist with despair!
It's been a while, little bitch.
Carnival...
Yes.
I hope you can keep calling me that.
I did like Kou,
but I don't like using the name
of someone who failed.
Failed?
He lost the battles, and now he
can't have any more fun, right?
I plan to keep the battles going forever
and enjoy them for eternity.
Enjoy... this?
This world is so boring.
But that is different.
Little bitch, you know
what I'm talking about.
You were having fun, even if
you wouldn't admit it, right?
Your battle with Aoi Akira.
Now, let us begin a battle where the
weak are devoured by the strong!
How exciting!
I can hear the screams of girls
begging for their lives again!
Very well.
Let us begin.
But I won't let you have your way.
This time, I will put a stop
to these Selector battles
and this endless cycle of despair!
Sounds fun.
Try it.
Initiation / Usual and Unusual
Riru?
Hello again, Suzuko.
You're so nice, Riru.
The Selectors become LRIGs?
There's still too much we don't understand.
Kanae-san!
If you lose, your opponent steals your LRIG.
Another new Selector has been chosen.
Crowding / Loser and Winner
Crowding / Loser and Winner.