Listen to me, Dela.
The fortune said that our princess lies to the northwest of here.
Northwest, you say?
If you can keep me informed of your whereabouts each day,
I can tell you which way to proceed from there.
I understand, Lady Choi.
Choi?
Your Highness!
Hey there, Your Highness.
Done with your siesta?
Dela!
Oh yeah, Dela.
Are you really leaving?
You will soon ascend to the throne, my prince.
We must summon your bride, and our princess, before then.
According to custom, yes...
We must follow our customs.
But I'm worried about Dela traveling so far away.
Dela.
Be careful on your travels.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Of course. You needn't worry about me.
Dela!
You always act too high and mighty around the prince!
It's all right, Choi.
Dela and I have been friends since childhood.
Take care of your health, Dela.
Take shelter during bad weather, okay?
If the journey proves dangerous, turn back at once.
Also—
Dude, you're way too picky.
Y-You really needn't worry, Your Highness.
Hey! Get off him!
The time has come, Dela.
I understand, ma'am.
Go forth, Dela!
Embark upon your journey.
The sound of this shell will show you the way.
Dela!
May great blessings shine on your path!
I'm exhausted.
For one thing, I haven't even left the island once in my entire life.
This place smells like the prince.
I suppose I'll take a break.
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
So mochi-mochi!
Hey! Don't chew on me!
Hm...
So my girl's supposed to be the princess?
Episode 11
No Way! That Girl's a Princess
Dela.
Is Tamako really a princess?
We had someone that amazing among us all along, huh?
Hm...
Dela! I heard about Tamako!
Are things already decided?
Huh?
No. But she is a candidate.
Who woulda thunk our market'd give birth to a princess?
I've always felt there was something different about Tamako.
Right, Dela?
I suppose.
Oh hey, Dela!
Hm?
In the dusk...
of the music room—
I've returned, my girl.
Welcome back, Dela.
Oh, so yer back.
As of just now, yes.
Yoink!
Here you go, Dela.
Hey, I was gonna put that out for sale.
Delicious!
Isn't it?
I can't muster up...
Hey! Stop singing.
I get it.
Lady Tamako.
Dear Father.
Breakfast is served.
Come on, Choi. Don't call me "Lady"!
Just Tamako's fine.
I'm sorry, but I can't,
for you just might be my prince's bride... my princess.
Lady Choi.
This must be some kind of mistake.
It is no such thing.
Lady Tamako has the sign that proves it.
What?!
She smells of flowers, just like the prince.
What's more, she has a mole on her neck.
Every princess of the Mochidis Gusting family has had some sort of mark in that area.
But this is a birthmark I share with my mom...
Last, but not the least, you have a
deep personal connection to mochi.
Anyway, make sure you treat
her like a princess from now on.
Yes!
I think this must be some sort of mistake, though.
If you become the princess, you'll be granted the name of the royal family,
and become Tamako Mochidis Gusting.
What?!
Like hell that's happening!
Whoa, that was surprising.
After listening to it again, I now realize how bad for the heart that name is.
By the way, uh...
Oh, yeah!
By the way, I've almost got enough!
You know...
The market's point cards!
Oh?
point card
Did you know? You get a prize if you collect a hundred of these!
A hundred?!
What's the prize again?
A medal!
It's a special medal just for our market.
I've never seen it, but apparently it's engraved with a pair of bunnies pounding mochi!
It's taken me a long, long time to make it this far,
but the time has finally come!
Today's Medal Day!
Have a safe trip.
Be careful.
Not you too, Dela.
See you later.
Wait, what was that?
Mochizou?!
Tama—
Tamako's the princess of some c-c-count—
I'm not a princess.
Really?
I thought as much!
Come on, it might be true.
Ah, Mocchi!
Oh, right.
Look at this!
I only need three more points to have a hundred of these!
Come on, take a look.
Isn't that awesome?
Yeah. Way to go!
Thanks. I'll get them today.
What?!
A prince? Tamako's really marrying up.
Wouldn't want Tamako marrying low.
Hey, that rhymes.
C'mon, do you believe everything you hear?
This is Tamako we're talking about.
No way that's happening.
Not this suddenly, anyway.
I know, right?
When did you get here?!
Just now.
She's like a ninja—
How'd it go, Princess?
I'm sure Choi just has the wrong idea.
That'd be a real shame.
But there's a chance it might be real!
I see Shiori believes in the unexpected.
Tamako.
I'm not saying Choi isn't trustworthy, but you'd better be careful.
And Midori believes in conspiracies.
For the record, I believe in the almighty yen.
They probably scouted Tamako to be a mochi maker for the Mochidis Gusting family.
And she's going to create the island's most famous mochi!
Choi's a real schemer, all right!
Uh, no way.
None at all?
Geez.
Lady Choi.
I can't bring myself to believe that my girl could be the princess.
Also, you haven't once told her fortu—
All done!
Come now, Dela.
We really must fix your communications system today.
Excuse me?
The repair instructions finally
arrived from our country today.
Is that so?
Forgive me.
Huh?
Let's ask Choi directly.
Hey!
The prince is that guy we saw, right?
Come to think of it, Dela did project something back then...
Actually, wait.
I'm surprised you even know about that, Shiori.
Huh? Oh, sorry.
Hey, what's going on?
Huh? Oh, Tamako. Sorry about that.
It's okay. Anyway, I'm going to reach the market's points goal today!
So can we go dinner shopping on the way home?
Mos def.
Oh, hey. Welcome, Princess.
"Princess"...
All of a sudden she's a VIP...
Stop it, you guys!
Two blocks of firm tofu, please.
Sure thing.
Can I get a stamp on this?
Sure.
There.
There you go.
I did it...
I did it!
I'll go home and get the rest of the cards,
so could you guys wait for me at Usa Bath?
Okay.
I'm home!
Lady Tamako!
Hello, Choi!
Tama—
Sorry, Choi. I'll be right back, okay?
What's this all about, my girl?
Dela!
What seems to be the matter, my lady?
Wow!
My girl.
You should be happier about being
considered the prince's bride than this.
Yup.
But that came out of nowhere.
I got this medal using the cards I've been collecting ever since I was in elementary school, you know.
In my eyes, this is what makes me more happy.
Tamako.
You finally did it.
Yup!
It seems I'm the only one in the market with one of these.
Well done.
Yup!
Lady Tamako.
Sorry to bother you when you're busy, but...
Hm?
Tamako Market
Oh, Mamedai!
Your Highness!
I'm glad to see you're in good health, Choi.
Ah! Is he the one?!
This is the lady I wrote to you about.
She's Tamako Kitashirakawa.
Um... hello.
"Tamako Kitashirakawa"!
All she did was reverse the name order.
Oh my god!
What now?
Those pillars are amazing!
It is my pleasure to meet you. I'm Mecha Mochidis Gusting.
What?!
Calm down, Mamedai!
It's his name. There's not much he can do about it!
Are you all blood-related?
Dela and I might share the royal family's name,
but we're not related to them.
All the retainers of the royal family receive their surname as well.
Lady Tamako, I hear you've taken very good care of Choi and Dela.
Thank you very much.
Oh, don't mention it.
You're welcome.
Because of that, I was been thinking of giving you my thanks in per—
I guess he's not 100% yet.
How'd it go, Lady Choi?
We were able to introduce the prince and Lady Tamako to each other.
That's me for you.
Aren't I useful?
A regular cellphone'd be more useful than you are!
He looked like a kind, gentle guy.
Indeed! He's a wonderful person!
He's very wise and cheerful.
But he's also very humble, and his subjects love him!
He looked like he was still a kid, though.
He certainly is young, but he has a firm head on his shoulders.
How are we supposed to tell
after such a short conversation?
There's not much point in telling Choi that, Mochizou.
Hey, Choi.
I really don't think I'm a princess.
Sorry for causing such a fuss, everyone.
You can go back to your stores now.
Tamako...
Hm?
Lady Choi?
What'd you think? Pretty great, right?
Yeah. The prince seemed like a wonderful person.
I meant the pillars.
I wanna see them in person.
I have to know how they're put together.
Hold on a second!
What's up?
Why's it sound like you've come to terms with the whole thing?
This sudden turn of events...
If I had to compare this to something, it'd be like taking my stuffed bear away from me...
Something like that...
Yeah. I get what you're saying.
It's kinda scary, isn't it?
To see something change so suddenly before your eyes.
Midori.
I feel like I'm peering into the Star Gate here.
I'm totally shaken.
Yeah.
But I'm sure Tamako's the most scared of all.
You're right.
He really was a prince, you know?
He called Sis "Lady Tamako," too!
I couldn't believe it!
Really?
And what did Tamako say?
Sis was...
I'll be making tofu patties tonight.
Let me take care of it, Lady Tamako.
Thanks, Choi.
Let's make it together.
Okay.
Will you mix this for me, then?
Sure.
Things are moving quite quickly.
You can just use your hands.
She's even had an interview with the prince.
Does that mean it won't be long before this is all finalized?
Dela!
Huh?
Get down from there. It's disrespectful.
Right away!
I see.
So I can't ride on my girl's head anymore, eh?
Hey. I'm goin' out.
Where?
There's a meeting at Usa Bath.
What?
Was there supposed to be a meeting today?
What about dinner?
I'll grab some udon noodles on the way back.
Whaaat?!
But we're having those tofu patties you love so much!
It's not like I love tofu or anything.
I just eat it because it gets served.
You meanie!
If you're gonna be like that, I'll just go get married, okay?
Hey, hold on a second.
Where do you think you're going?
To the meeting.
Hey!
She only said that in the heat of the moment!
I know that already.
Really?
Very well, then.
Isn't this your country, Dela?
Indeed. 'Tis a wonderful place.
What's up, my son?
He's too anxious to be alone. Right?
Th-That's not it.
What do you think about this, Dad?
Huh?
Ah, I'm sorry!
Don't be so on edge, Father!
Huh.
Huh?
It still doesn't seem real, does it?
Oh, so you're back, Sayuri?
I got curious about this whole Tamako thing.
Oh, I need to make tea.
Thanks, really.
Well, this might do Tamako a lot of good.
We want Tamako...
...to be happy, don't we?
But she's still so young!
She's only as old as Midori.
Hey! Aren't you forgetting that
Tamako has feelings of her own?!
Tamako, a princess? Unbelievable!
Mamedai...
She may not be a princess,
but if Tamako finds someone nice in the future, you've got to send her off with a smile.
She's taken really good care of the shop and your home, hasn't she?
But you see...
You can't keep her chained down here forever.
She might say that she won't leave this market.
But...
If it makes her happy...
What the hell are ya guys blabberin' 'bout?
Tamako's...
Tamako's my daughter!
Good grief.
How about a little consideration?
You loved this track.
The one you used as inspiration to write that song for Hinako.
When you let go of something precious to you,
there are things you get in return.
Holding on to the things you have might
not be the be-all and end-all of happiness.
Alcohol?!
I tried making it an Irish coffee.
My girl.
A glass of water, please.
Coming right up.
Dad hasn't come back yet, has he?
Hm? Yeah...
I wonder what's keeping him.
Well, there are times when people wish to be alone.
I see.
Dad?!
You okay?
I'm okey-dokey!
Dad, I'm sorry about what I said earlier.
Tamako...
Darako?
Naw, Tamako.
Make sure your happiness comes first.
Not the chicken or the egg?
Hey, you there!
Go back to your room if you wish to sleep!
It's too cold here!
princess mochi
flower with a princess design
strawberry
Tamako.
You see...
Regardless of where you are, or who you're with...
I'll be fine as long as you're happy.
And it's not just me.
Everyone in the market feels the same way.
That's all. Good night!
Over.
Good night.
What the heck?
What's with everyone?!
Do you want me to leave that badly?!
I oughta just turn you all into mochi!
Tamako.
Oh, Anko.
Sorry...
Did I wake you?
Nah.
Wanna sleep together?
Face the other way, Tamako.
Let's play Koala.
Okay.
Good night.
Yup.
The desire to stay the same. The desire to change.
There are always two sides to the human heart.
And yet, we carry these irreconcilable
feelings as we set forth into tomorrow.
Maybe I should put the medal up here.
It's gooone!
What's wrong, Tamako?
I can't find the medal!
What's gotten into you, Tamako?
It's gone!
What is?
The medal!
It's gone!
Geez, what's with this fuss first thing in the morning?
When did you notice it was gone?
After I got the medal, I went around showing it to everyone,
then I put in my bag, and then this morning, I realized it was gone.
Did you look inside the house?
I did!
Every nook and cranny?
Kaoru...
Serves you right for showing it off to everyone!
Dela!
You got your just deserts for
flaunting it everywhere, my lady!
I guess it's gotta be in the house...
I'll give you all of my point cards.
I've got around fifty!
Thanks a lot, but it doesn't count unless I collect them myself!
My medal!
Could this be what you're looking for?
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
One year sure does fly by, doesn't it?
Tamako here.
When it gets close to New Year's, more and more people start pounding mochi.
You can control the softness of the mochi by
adjusting the amount of water you add by hand.
Final Episode  Another Year Draws to a Close
I hope everyone eats a ton of mochi!
Tamako out!