Look, it's President Maki.
She's always so prim, proper, and perfect.
She paints such a pretty picture.
But she seems to be somewhat listless today.
That said, I love this side of Fuji's Princess too.
Nyorbit!
How could Fuji's Princess fall like that?!
Wait, why does she have so many apples?
I-I'm sure she needs those apples for student council work.
She looks like she has no idea what's going on!
What's wrong, Maki?
Did you trip and fall?
You okay?
Riko...
How unusual to see you be a natural klutz.
Holding That Hand
I-I know, right?
Anyway, why'd you bring apples?
W-Well,
it looks like I carelessly mistook them for work documents.
Can you really write that off as a "careless" mistake?
Knowing you, I thought you were gonna
use these for love research or something.
N-No!
Um, things are going to get hectic now,
so we should cut down on the research for a while.
Oh, right!
I need to go to the faculty lounge!
Thanks, Riko.
Bye!
Benyomin!
She's yelling out some awfully weird things
since she's not used to being an actual klutz.
There's definitely something wrong here.
I can't believe Maki would suggest cutting down on research.
Did she really hear that, after all?
We don't know for sure just yet.
This is Maki we're talking about.
She might nonchalantly start doing some love research anyway.
Okay!
Say, Maki.
What's the matter, Eno?
"What's the matter," you ask?
What happened to today's love research?
The underground paper's going to start printing soon.
We can't take things too easy.
We also need to take care of all these advice requests that Ichikawa brought us for edition two and on.
Well...
Uh...
We delayed some student council work
to focus on the underground newspaper,
so I figured I should take a break from love research for a while and take care of this.
Do we have that much work piled up?
It must be true since Maki said so.
That aside...
...something feels off.
You messed up your calculations there.
What?
Oh, you're right.
Thank you, Sayo.
It's okay, but this isn't like you.
I-I'm trying to be a girl with a few chinks in her armor.
Oh no! I ended up writing a letter of challenge instead of a love letter!
You look like you'd be done for quick if you showed any chinks in your armor.
Hey, Ma—
That totally caught her by surprise!
And then she tripped and fell.
How'd that happen?
Hilarious, right?
In the end, we never did any love research after that.
God, this is kinda depressing!
If things are gonna stay this awkward, then I'd be better off just...
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
Main menu
News & Weather
Fortunes & Games
Entertainment
TV & Media
I gotta call her,
even if it's a cowardly thing to do.
Hey!
No calling people this late at night.
You spend too long on the phone as it is.
B-But this is important!
All the more reason to put the phone down.
Look them in the eye tomorrow and say it face-to-face.
You're right.
I should do it face-to-face, shouldn't I?
I'm so pathetic.
Riko?
More! Scold me more!
What?!
Yell at me! Abuse me! Kick me and call me a loser!
Stop saying things that could give our neighbors the wrong idea!
I have to tell her today for sure!
M-Maki.
Um, I...
Er...
What is it?
It was you?!
What's with that wig?
Eno and Suzu had something to do in the faculty lounge, so I'm looking through things since I'm bored.
Taking a good look shows how ridiculous this is.
What, are we throwing a party or something?
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
I need to press her on how she used the council budget.
What does she even plan on using these things for?
Seriously, her ideas are too stupid for me.
Moboge!
H-Hey, Maki?
"Moboge"?
I'm fine.
I just spaced out a little.
Maki, uh...
We need to tal—
I-I'm sorry.
I have a special extra lesson at cram school today,
so I need to take the day off.
Bye!
Wait a s—
Fast!
Look, I'm in no state to play the
straight man for a half-assed comic.
Things have been weird since the other day.
Have you still not confessed to her?
I need to be ready for it as well.
Oh yeah!
Put on that wig again.
Let's practice!
What?
I'll treat you to something soon.
Now I don't feel like it.
Mah name is Maki!
You ruined it with just one line!
Imma stick my heels in guys' heads again today!
You mean "make them go head over heels"!
Aw, jeez. Your glasses bother me, so look the other way.
Try to talk and sound like Maki too!
Well, aren't you demanding?
Riko, what did you want to talk about?
This has gone beyond sounding "like" her!
Er, uh...
Get on with it.
You're annoying me.
If I had to use an example, I'd say it feels like I found some shells in my clam soup.
Just shut up!
Also, what is with you and shellfish?!
The first edition of the underground newspaper should be done soon.
Yeah.
Now that the storage room next to the student council office is empty,
the newspaper association can finally move in.
Nyanmar!
Nyanmar?
Wait, it's Maki!
A-Are you okay?
I'm... fine.
What's with you? Jeez.
Oh, you're practicing how to be a klutz, aren't you?
Look at you, getting all excited because you haven't done this for a while.
Let's all do it together.
We could get some accurate advice from Riko!
But man, I'm amazed at how Riko keeps going along with this.
She has to put up with you going wild so often.
Just kidding.
O-Oh no.
I just can't seem to keep my mouth shut these days, so I keep drooling.
I'm taking the day off from the student council today. Bye!
It was just drool!
My being popular was all a lie.
But I didn't mean any harm.
The lies just kept growing while I was being stupidly stubborn.
What a long-winded and pointless excuse.
It's like an adductor muscle
that's hard to cut out of a clam.
Enough of that already!
Stop talking about your breakfast!
You're not fit to be my friend any longer.
You're just a Riklam.
Don't even joke about that!
I'm worrying here because I'm scared
things won't stay the same, you know!
Say...
Are you the only one scared of that?
You freeze up at critical times because you keep trying to use that peabrain of yours.
Sayo...
Yeah, you go hiding in that shell of yours.
Seriously, knock it off!
That one meeting,
the broadcasting room hijack,
and when I said I was quitting the student council.
What was on your mind at those times?
I was...
This is bad!
Maki's—
She was acting all weird and
shedding tears that were like drool!
No!
She was drooling like she was crying!
Now that's weird.
What about Maki?
Oh yeah, you've also been acting all weird recently.
No wonder I haven't been feeling right either.
I-It's not like that.
It is.
I mean,
you haven't been playing Maki's straight man at all!
Well, maybe it's because she hasn't been playing the comic lately.
The two of you are so normal right now that I...
I...
I want you two to go back to how you were!
Maki and Riko not being a double act just doesn't feel right!
Is that all we're good for?
But Sayo, Eno, and Suzu...
I'll make it up to you three as well,
so let me take today off from the student council!
Later!
Yeah.
You're better off like that.
Kurahashi probably has a rough time with you too.
I just hope you two being "friends" isn't another one of your misunderstandings.
I don't feel like going to cram school either.
Huh? Maki?
Nagino.
Crap, this feels way too good.
Not going to class?
N-Not yet.
Oh, you're waiting for Riko?
Huh?
Wait, did something happen with her?
Hey, if it isn't Nagi!
I haven't seen you since our last match.
Yeah.
I'm joining this cram school today.
You're dead!
It's not what you're thinking!
She's a friend of Riko's!
Riko's?
Do you know Riko?
We went to the same elementary school.
Is she really a friend of that crude tomboy?
I really am her friend!
Wow.
How crudeness will rub off on you, you know?
She's gone far beyond "not girly."
That's just a dude.
A dude.
B-But Riko's cool, nice, and popular!
Popular? Riko?
The heck? Did she say that?
Man, the girls at Fuji Girls' sure are naive.
Maki!
I didn't know you went to this cram school, Riko.
You shouldn't go around tricking sheltered princesses.
Well, I am shocked she actually believed it,
but I guess that's Fuji Girls' for you.
What's so funny, you asshole?!
See? This is what she's like.
Just so we're clear, I'm the only bad girl at Fuji Girls'!
She trusted me, but I ended up hurting her like this.
I had my priorities all mixed up!
Maki's...
Maki's not to blame!
It's all my fault.
Mine!
But dude, you can't call it a complete and utter lie.
I was in love with Riko, you know?
Huh?!
F-For real?!
Yeah, but I got rejected.
And Maki here knows about that.
It's the only reason she said what she did.
Got that? You should apologize.
Go on.
I-I'm sorry!
Maki...
Riko...
What?!
Embarrassment
What's this, a fight?
What? Where?
I can't see a thing!
I-I'm so sorry!
M-Maki!
Ow!
Dammit, I feel so embarrassed.
And it's all this idiot's fault.
U-Um...
Just to be clear, I only did it because I felt sorry for Maki!
It's not like I did it for you, okay?!
You dumbass! Loser!
If you got that,
hurry up and go after her.
Y-Yeah.
Nagi!
You're a really nice guy!
Thanks!
Sorry I made you embarrass yourself!
See ya!
She ran away from him.
What?!
Did he just get rejected again?
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
Poor guy.
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
Hey there, Mr. Really Nice Guy.
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
The Embarrassment
Strikes
Back
J-Jan!
Did you see all that?!
Don't call me that.
Good grief. You got rejected by her of all people.
And you embarrassed yourself protecting her.
There's no way I'd be able to do that.
Kurahashi has terrible taste.
Huh?
Yours is even worse, though.
Massive!
This is Maki's house?
Still, I never thought this dumb handkerchief I confiscated from Maki would come in handy like this.
I'm a nice, earnest girl!
Riko.
M-Maki.
Sorry about earlier.
I lost my cool.
It's only natural.
How'd you find my place?
Oh, it was thanks to this handkerchief.
Wait, that's...
See? That strategy really is effective.
Don't be stupid. It just happened to be useful this time.
Forgive me!
Huh?
Kneeling is the coward's way out!
W-Wow, this carpet smells nice.
By the way!
This seems a little patronizing.
What if I lean forward?
Hang on, it looks like I'm on a break and chilling out!
In that case...
We need to talk!
U-Um, take a seat first.
Sorry!
My being a love expert was all a lie!
In truth, I'm on an endless broken-heart streak.
Just like you, I'm a complete beginner at love!
I'm really sorry I lied to you all this while and hurt you.
Is that all?
Is that all you hid from me?
Y-Yeah.
She's mad.
Of course she'd be mad.
That's how we became friends in the first place,
yet...
She can no longer trust me, can she?
Sorry I'm like this.
I'm so sorry
for being such an idiot.
I'm sorry.
So I'll stay away from you.
The student council too. I'll quit—
I'll... quit...
Riko!
I'll...
I...
I don't wanna quit!
I know I'm being selfish,
but I wanna keep doing stupid things with you guys.
I want to be friends with you.
Best friends.
Now we're even.
I'm so glad.
To tell the truth, I was so worried this entire time.
Worried that I was causing you trouble by misunderstanding things.
Worried that you might've been
forcing yourself to go along with me.
Maki...
You yelled at me saying that I shouldn't use that handkerchief because it was dangerous, didn't you?
That made me really happy.
It was just the obvious thing to do.
I didn't want us to be friends forever because you were a love expert or anything.
That had nothing to do with it.
It was because you're the kind of person who
thinks helping people is the obvious thing to do.
Let me answer your question.
You know, the "How would you feel if I were a beginner at love?" one.
To be perfectly honest,
I felt a little sad and disappointed.
But more than that, it makes me happy.
I mean, we'll get to experience all kinds of things together
and worry about things from the same perspective, right?
Nothing could be more wonderful than this!
So...
Let's have fun from now on too,
Riko,
my best friend.
Come on, Riko.
You're like a baby.
You're no better!
No way.
Really?
I'm really sorry!
I'm not fit to be admired!
That wasn't what I admired about you!
You, my Wine, had been the target of my admiration long before that!
The
Wild
One
The
Wild
One
(Wine)
You must've found it hard to confess since we were all getting excited by ourselves, right?
Suzu...
You should be more mad at me!
But that's what I love about you!
No way.
Really?
I'm truly sorry!
D-Don't screw with me!
You bossed us around like you knew it all!
I can't believe this!
Wh-What?
You reap what you sow.
Now listen up.
You'll be my slave for a while.
I'm gonna work you like a horse!
I'm really thankful for your normal-sized heart.
But that's what I love about—
The things that worried you didn't worry me at all.
I mean, this place is filled with idiots.
Say what?!
Sayo...
Of course, you'll still have to make it up to us.
Suzu.
Oh, so this is why you placed that order.
Reinforced slapsticks!
Huh?!
Wow, these are nice.
Surprisingly easy to handle for their size.
As requested, it has 1.8 times the
attack power of the normal version.
I pulled it off by putting some thin plywood inside.
Good job.
Relax. It'll be an open-casket funeral.
W-Wait, time out...
Charge!
Stop—
Ouch!
Excuse us.
Huh?
Did something happen?
Oh, nothing. We were just strengthening the bonds of this student council a little.
Wait, could it be...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's finally complete!
The student council and the
newspaper association present:
A lifeboat to girls in need of help!
The first edition of the underground newspaper!
Fuji Girls' News (UG)
The Underground Newspaper has finally launched!
Nice. I love it.
This is fantastic!
Not bad.
You've put things together well.
Of course.
Momo put everything she had into the article!
I didn't do it alone.
I had Nana and the rest of the newspaper association.
Most importantly, this is the fruit of the student council's enthusiasm.
Girls, we can't be sitting around now!
Let's prepare for the second edition by doing some love research right now!
I'll do my best!
V-Very well.
I'll help too.
Sure, I guess.
Riko.
All right!
Love Lab begins now!
Yeah!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever