karuma nando mo onaji koto wo kurikaeshi no naka wo
Karma, in the midst of ever-repeating events
ochite itta
it fell...
karuma kono karada wa rasen no you
Karma; this body is like a spiral
umare kawatte mo nao mayoi tsuzuketeru
Even if it's reborn, yet it continues to wander
yasuraka ni... owari ni shiyou
Tenderly... bring it to an end
onore no aza de
With my own birthmark
I have to kill... or I'll be killed!
Are you awake?
There is no need to be afraid.
I won't attack you anymore.
You are...
If you are asking about my name, I don't have one.
If you don't know what to call me, call me Ein.
That's what they call me, after all.
Ein.
Why did you attack me?
To show that you had talent.
Talent?
You have a talent you were born with.
A talent for killing.
A talent for surviving.
An assassin's talent.
That can't be...
I don't get it.
Anyway, what basis do you have for...
You tried to kill me, didn't you?
In that situation, a normal human would have fallen into a panic and been killed.
However, you are different.
You took action before you understood the situation and survived.
Zwei.
Zwei?
That's your name.
You're wrong.
Don't make up weird names!
I have a proper name...!
My name... is...
You don't have one, anymore.
There is no point in thinking about it.
What do you mean?!
Your memories were erased.
By Inferno.
Wonderful.
The journalist, who was shot and killed...
Your Phantom is a masterpiece, Scythe Master
...is thought to have been caught up in a syndicate's inner struggles.  Now then-
It is an honor, Mr. McGuire
This style... it's hard to believe it is the work of a kid.
That's right...
That's why I bestowed upon her the title of Phantom.
Your accomplishments are great.
You've created an apparition that is not of this world, after all.
No... this is due to Ms McCunnen's support.
You have a good subordinate, Claudia.
By the way...
I heard you had difficulties exterminating that journalist.
No, it's nothing like that...
I heard he saw the site of the disposal... a normal tourist.
I don't know where you heard that, but all witnesses have been disposed of.
The corpses have been accounted for, also.
Oh...?  That's wonderful.
And did you use Phantom for that as well?
Yes.
You were supposed to have been killed.
For the sake of completely erasing all evidence.
However, Master recognized that talent and thought it would be a waste to kill you.
Master?
Scythe Master... my master.
Master stole your memories and prepared a new life for you.
An Inferno member.
A life as an assassin.
An assassin?  Me?
We are going to have you become my other half, Zwei.
Don't say such stupid things!
Why would I do such a... become a murderer...!?
It's all right to refuse.
However, at that time...
...you'll have you die as originally planned.
Right here, right now.
If you want to live, you must change.
Now, your existence is only validated by killing people.
I...
...don't want to die!
This is a dream.
This... All of this is a bad dream.
If thinking like that comforts you, that's fine.
Just think of it as one big dream
However, it will be a very long dream.
Change into that.
From now on after six in the morning, you are with me.
You will obey all instructions.
Understood?
Let's begin.
Zwei's progress is steady.
He is obediently completing his training.
He's quite submissive...
With that difficult training every day, even basic thought becomes painful.
Yes, that is basics of training.
I will show you results that will not betray your expectations, Ms. McCunnen.
Did you think I had expectations?
My pawns are your pawns.
Everything is for Inferno, after all.
This is how you hold it.
Don't put your finger over the trigger.
Put your power in your fingers, not your shoulders; grip it with both hands.
This is the rear sight.  This is the forward sight.
You aim by aligning the valley of the rear sight with the forward sight.
When you take position, straighten your right arm, and put tension in your left.
It will stabilize the gun.
Even so, most of the power should go into your fingers, not your arms.
When you pull the trigger, don't hurry; squeeze it gently.
Fire.
Fire the remaining five shots one after the other.
At this distance, you should be able to hit it every time.
Once you can do that, we'll work on speed.
Your goal is six shots in four seconds.
Concentrate on making hits first.
That's still too slow.
It looks like you've got the accuracy, but at that rate, you'll die before you can shoot down your target.
Repeat. Repeat.
I will complete the tasks I am given.
If I do that, I don't need to think...
If I do that, I will be at ease.
I will even forget the many questions I have.
My everday life will disappear.
I'm going out.
The training menu is the same as usual.
Going out?
It's work.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
That man is... Scythe Master.
It's the first sniping mission in a while.
Well, it is an easy one for you.
The distance to the target is seven hundred yards.
You'll be using the Remington .308 for this.
The weather at the site is cloudy with a gentle breeze.
The weather center said there will be no changes until tomorrow morning.
The details are in that folder.
Any questions?
No.
Very good.
By the way, how is Zwei?
His basic training is pretty much complete.
From tomorrow on, we will begin a different training.
I guess it's about time that I readied a practical exam.
Don't worry about me.  Continue.
I guess I should say 'Nice to meet you'?
I am Claudia McCunnen.
Is there anything you are concerned about me other than my name?
No.
However, you are interested in Inferno, the
organization that picked you up, aren't you?
Since you didn't answer, I'll take that as a "yes."
Inferno is... Hmm... I guess you'd say a group that is trying to create a different type of order in a world without that order.
If you consider gangs and mafia as countries of their own, Inferno would be something like the UN.
What Inferno is aiming for is the unification of the underworld.
That kind of a dreamlike story wouldn't have even been worthy of being called a joke just a little while ago...
However, the thing that is bringing that to life is...
Phantom.
Yes, your instructor.
Phantom's power is absolute.
She, who can absolutely eliminate any target, has Inferno's greatest trust and bestows the greatest fear upon resistant organizations.
She is the greatest assassin.
However...
In the end, we are people who are just being used by the organization...
Both Phantom and I...
We have no choice but to live like slaves.
It's true that we only offer you a single way of life.
However, you aren't a slave.
Even you have freedom.
It's called "speed."
Speed?
Even if it is a determined course, as long as you desire it and work for it, you can accelerate as much as you want.
You might even come to stand at the pinnacle of the organization.
How to run through it is up to you, after all.
Don't ever think of yourself as a slave again.
As long as you think that way, you are
giving victory to those who belittle you.
I wanted to talk about this with you more, but I have work I can't get away from.
Goodbye, Zwei.
Cars, you see, are things that people drive...
Not puppets.
Even if it is a determined course, as long as you desire it and work for it, you can accelerate as much as you want.
Desire... striving... I had long-since forgotten those words.
Ein?
What?
Did you kill someone during today's mission?
Yes.
Why did you become a killer?
I don't know.
I wasn't taught anything about my past.
That is...
That's right.  I'm the same as you.
I also had my memories erased and was made into an assassin.
However, what about it?
Now, at this moment, I have survived.
That's all that matters.
Assassins have neither a past nor a future.
However, a person named Claudia said...
Claudia?
She came here this afternoon.
She said that we weren't slaves, that we had freedom.
If you want to believe that, then do so.
However, eventually you will come to the point where you don't feel anything.
Because there is no other way to endure this way of life.
Eventually, you will become this way too.
When you've killed someone, you'll understand.
Pulling the trigger is easy.
As is aiming... if it's just a brick.
But... but...
Fire.
Fire... Zwei.
Zwei.
yami ni iraretara massakasama ni
If stays in darkness, it turns upside down
ashi wo jama ni shi fukaku nikushimi wa tawawa ni
The foot is caught deeply; Hate is looming
kyoushitsu wa hana to sabi midare minoru yume no kashi
The classroom is flowers and rust; ripening dreams of pastries
nou dake se dake harawata
only the brain, only the back; guts
te wo kake yo
offer your hand
mei wo made
hold the command
souhaku ni hiraku yubi
Fingers that open palely
mamieru mae ni
Before facing it
moshi mo omae ga
If you
nousatsu sanagara mayoi netami
are bewitched and jealous
uchikudaku koto dekiyou ka
can you break it
monzetsu se yo
Faint in agony
tada kudasuru toki ha
But when you drop off
risei wo tori
and acquire reason
chi wo haki doku ni mamire
Blood is smeared by poisoned vomit
naraku e no mukawan
Head to hell
soko de shika mienai
Only there you can see
ten wo aogi yaketadare teyuku asu wo warae yo
Face the sky and laugh at the burnt sky
This is a continuation of the dream.
A dream you will never awaken from, until you die.
{This is a work of fiction, any similarity or likeness to any events or persons is purely coincidental}