And so, we shall handle this matter by taking the actions we've discussed.
Understood.
Madam, what of this transaction?
I shall decide once I have read it in detail.
Understood.
That will end today's meeting.
Excuse us.
Yes?
Mana and the others have arrived.
Ai, are you well?
Makopi, what's wrong?
I was thinking about my queen...
Yeah...
We have to find her soon.
It'd be nice if we had a clue, no matter how small...
A clue...
That's right!
My queen loved roses!
Roses?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Well, knowing she likes roses isn't much...
Speaking of roses,
take a look.
Rose Lady Contest
Rose Lady Contest?
A contest to find the best rose-loving lady.
The victor shall be awarded the newly discovered Royal Yellow rose.
That's my queen's favorite rose!
But it only grew within the royal palace,
so it shouldn't be in this world.
What a mystery!
So, shall we enter this contest and obtain the Royal Yellow ourselves?
This rose may provide a clue to the queen.
Great idea!
You're a genius!
We've Finally Found It?!
A Clue Leading To The Queen!
Itsutsuboshi Rose Garden
So the contest is being held at this garden?
It's beautiful!
Anyone who loves roses would come here, even the queen!
Did someone call for me?
Why yes, I've graced this garden with my royal beauty.
Oh?
So cute!
Could she really be the queen?
Hey, do you like roses?
Roses?
Hate 'em.
I have no mercy...
for things more beautiful than I.
S-So?
Probably not.
Oh, that's cute!
Give it to me.
Huh?
Huh?!
Sorry, but I can't...
Then will you trade it?
For the fate of the world?
Just a joke.
I must be going.
I need no farewell.
What's with that girl?
You're a moron.
Why would you go into Beast Mode after what happened to Bel?
Excuse me for wanting to beat the Precures.
And did you beat them?
Shut it!
King Selfish's wrath is vicious.
You don't have a choice either, Mammo.
I don't need you to tell me that.
Today will be the day I defeat the Precures.
Beautifully...
and mercilessly.
Itsutsuboshi Rose Garden
Thanks for waiting, ladies and gentlemen!
The first stage of our Rose Lady Contest will be...
the social dance!
S-Social dance?
I've never done that before...
At first I thought a gaggle of chimps had gotten lost in the garden,
but I see it's simply Alice's tagalongs.
Chimps?
Oh Lady Reina, calling them chimps is too cruel!
Is it?
Well, perhaps chimpanzees would be more palatable?
You're brilliant, Lady Reina!
It fits perfectly!
When you talk like that to Alice, she'll...
You will take back your insults to Mana...
right this instant!
What is it?
When Alice hears someone insulting her friends,
she gets mad and loses control!
Back in elementary school,
she beat the pants off of some middle schoolers that were bullying Mana!
Why Reina, you're as clever a jokester as ever.
This is Itsutsuboshi Reina, the owner of this garden and an old friend.
Less of a friend, more of a rival.
From the family that forever one-ups the Yotsubas,
I am the rose of the Itsutsuboshis,
Itsutsuboshi Reina!
Might you be entering the contest as well?
Why, yes.
There are none more deserving of the title of Rose Lady than I.
I take it by your "as well" that you are entering too?
Yes. All four of us are.
Hm?
Are you not Kenzaki Makoto?
I am.
H-How underhanded!
You're entering despite being an idol?
Huh?
You're abusing your celebrity status to draw the judges' attention!
Yeah! You cheap, cowardly chimp!
I know that will get to her.
Hold on a moment.
This contest searches for the best lady.
Being an idol or not has no relevance.
That's right!
So be it.
I shall defeat you with my own skill.
We're off.
Lady Reina,
do you not think Alice will prove to be a difficult opponent?
Worry not.
If I insult or endanger her friends, she'll lose her temper and explode!
She'll be instantly disqualified.
So I'll have to step up my attacks to get through to her!
Yes!
Rose Lady Contest
I've never done a social dance before...
But I'm managing!
My skills on stage are coming in handy!
What are you doing?
Don't worry.
We made a crack in her heel.
A little more...
Ow...
Mana!
Don't tell me...
How clumsy!
A clumsy chimp, at that!
Now, get angry.
I see!
She did that on purpose to get Alice angry!
Don't worry!
I can just do this!
This'll make dancing easier.
Now, let's get back to our dance.
Mana!
Our next stage will be painting!
Now then,
begin!
Oh dear...
So that Reina girl was trying to make Alice mad to disqualify her!
I'm sure she has more tricks up her sleeve.
I've finished, everyone!
I'll be done soon.
I beg your pardon, my hand slipped.
There's not much you can do about that!
Will you two just...
You've made our paintings even better.
Think of it as a Pollock-esque drip painting!
Wow!
Teach me how to do that!
Certainly!
I'll get her next time!
Rose Lady Contest
Now, our next stage...
is the piano!
Piano, huh?
I think I can do this!
Now, our star performer, Hishikawa Rikka!
Right!
You can do it, Rikka!
You've got this!
Leave it to me!
A cat?!
What's a cat doing in there?
And I don't want to wake it when it's sleeping so peacefully...
Oh my, I know cats and dogs don't get on well,
but neither do cats and chimps, it seems.
Looks like you can't play, can you?
Maybe Alice can keep her cool,
but I've had all I can take!
Agreed.
What a gentle melody!
My anger's melting away.
Judge Nukuga
Judge Koga
And she's letting the cat sleep...
by playing her own composition that avoids the keys it's sleeping on!
You're amazing, Alice!
I hate it!
Rose Lady Contest
Now, we shall announce the two remaining finalists!
Our first lady is...
Itsutsuboshi Reina!
Naturally.
And our second is...
Yotsuba Alice!
You did it!
Our final stage will be tennis!
This game will decide the winner of this year's contest!
You can do it, Alice!
You can do it!
Right!
Reina
Alice
After a breathtaking series of volleys,
Reina
Alice
the match has come down to a tiebreaker!
Reina
Alice
And if Alice takes the next point, she'll win!
There was light in Alice's eyes!
Something was shining over there!
Let's go!
There!
So you came.
Oops, our hands slipped!
Clumsy, clumsy, clumsy!
You chimps are covered in mud!
This'll have to make her mad!
Come on, come on, come on!
Why aren't you mad?
To protect my friends!
Your friends aren't feeling very protected!
So get mad!
For some reason, I don't get mad anymore!
But why?!
I do not know...
but if I changed somehow,
it was thanks to my friends!
Alice...
What's so great about that mud-covered trash?!
To me, they're the shiniest treasures I could ask for!
Game!
The winner is Yotsuba Alice!
She did it!
Brilliantly done.
You useless curs!
Get out of my sight!
We're sorry!
Alice didn't beat me on her own strength.
It was all because of her friends.
Those friends of hers should just disappear!
But in truth, I want friends too...
Aw, why not make them disappear?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Reina!
Grant me your darkness!
Say hello to Mammo Beast!
That's a... rose?
I see, roses have thorns that keep friends away.
Let's go, everyone!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh poor rose who has lost her love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
My heart doesn't need that!
Oh no!
This is how you keep friends away!
With Heart and the fighters out of the way,
the barrier user won't be any threat!
W-Wait, since when could you do that?
I swore an oath that day!
I'd use the Precure's power to protect those I hold dear... my friends!
Your friends?
Who needs those?
I do.
Until I met Mana, I had no friends.
I always wanted friends!
That feeling made me rile up in anger when my friends were insulted.
Cut the speech!
But since I became a Precure with Mana,
we've experienced so much together...
that our bonds have grown even stronger!
Because we trust each other more than ever,
nobody else's words can ever shake my resolve!
Alice!
And what good is that?!
Now that I've obtained true friendship, I'll no longer hesitate!
If it's to protect my friends,
I'll use every ounce of power I have!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
What can you do with a barrier?
Thanks, Rosetta!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Precure Heart Shoot!
Huh?
What was I...
I'll remember this!
Here.
Can you find your queen with this?
Not yet...
But it was thanks to you that we got this rose.
Thank you.
Oh no...
It was thanks to you all!
I've never seen you get that serious.
It was great!
Makopi complimented Alice!
She's never complimented us...
You were cool out there, Alice.
My heart was racing!
The Precures are getting even stronger!
That's good to hear!
This is...
Blasted Precures...
Told ya so, Mammo.
I think I'll take a break for some R&R.
If you want a break, I'll be happy to oblige.
Break your neck, that is.
Who're you?
A little princess?
Why yes, I am.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Regina.
King Selfish's daughter.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Oh no! Rikka...
has gone astray!
Dokidoki Precure:
A Dream or a Promise!
Rikka's Numerous Woes!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!