"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Yutaka! We're gonna get going pretty soon!
There.
Now, my dear younger sister!
Your new life starts today!
Let's go with some enthusiasm!
"Under One Roof"
I'm here to report Yutaka's
acceptance, and to say hi!
Oh, welcome!
Now, Yutaka...
I-I'm sure I will be causing
many problems from now on,
but I give my best regards!
Just think of this as your own home.
Okay!
First of all, congratulations
on getting accepted!
Thanks!
Really, I'm so glad she got in!
Now you can be reunited with
that handkerchief girl!
My life is just that of a winner's!
Yeah!
"Going back in time"
"The day of Yutaka's entrance exams"
Um, are you all right?
Do you want me to go to the
nurse's office with you?
So she called out to me, and
even lent me her handkerchief.
I'm happy because I think I'll
have a very good friend now!
But, Yutaka, she might not get in.
That's not true! People like
that are sure to get in!
I understand how you feel, but...
I'm sure that she's smart too!
Thanks for the completely
baseless counter-argument.
But you know, Yu-chan...
What are you going to do if
you don't get in, Yu-chan?
It's true that there is that possibility...
Well, I'm sure that if it's you,
Yu-chan, you'd be all right.
That's right! Maybe I'll get to
see her one way or the other,
on the day they announce who got in!
I see...
I have to return the handkerchief to her.
"Acceptances and rejections
will both be notified by mail."
"And..."
"Orientation and Uniform Fitting Day"
Um...
Here...
I'm so glad to see you.
I've been wanting to return
this to you all this time.
You came to deliver this?
Yes.
I guess I troubled you instead.
I didn't think I would see you again,
so I had intended to give it to you.
You thought that I wouldn't get accepted?
No...
Oh, I see.
The fact that you're here now
means we're in the same grade.
I'm sorry.
Oh... you had thought that
I was a family member
of someone taking the entrance exams...
My family is picking me up today.
Oh, okay.
Then I'll say goodbye here.
Um...
I give you my best regards
for the next three years!
I'm so glad.
Making such a wonderful friend
in high school already!
I forgot to ask her name...
When you see her again, make
sure to ask for her name.
Yeah.
Yu-chan, are you feeling sick, by chance?
Yeah... I think I got a bit carsick.
Even though I took medication...
I'm sorry to worry you.
Yutaka really is a frail girl!
No, while that's indeed the case,
Sis, recognize that it's
also partly your driving!
It even gets to me a little.
But I'm the only one going to
Ryouou from my junior high.
I get sick really easily like today, too,
so I'm worried on whether or not
I'll get to know my classmates.
Yutaka, you're a good girl,
so it'll be all right!
You're treating me like a little child!
"Weak from illnesses + sister element
+ pure + cute = walking moe factor"
Conversion in my head.
Yu-chan, if you teamed
up with our Miyuki-san,
I'm sure it would be something amazing.
That's right... I'm already at
Konata-oneechan's house now...
Sis, good morning.
You're up so early, even on a holiday.
Oh, morning.
Or rather, I'm about to go to sleep now.
I was up all night playing 'net games...
My living conditions really did change!
We're finally going to be facing
college entrance exams next year.
All the cram schools and textbook
salespeople are calling lately.
It's a real pain.
I hear that you can tell it's
those calls if you get Caller ID.
Those types of calls usually have
their numbers as "restricted."
I'm home!
Caller ID, huh...
I have returned home!
Oh, is that so?
That must have been some trouble!
No, no, we're like that ourselves.
Yes, yes...
Now, since my daughter is back...
Yes, then on another occasion.
Please excuse me.
Who was it?
It seemed like you were having
a lively conversation.
It was a salesperson.
Um, didn't you mention
that you could recognize
those types of calls right away?
Yes, but you see,
I was a bit bored, so I wanted
to have a conversation.
I ended up talking for over an hour.
For both items together, the total is...
What was that about winning
the national championship?!
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
Tsukasa, the world is always
at war. There's no mercy!
The other day, there was a point-reward
item that I kinda wanted...
I thought about playing offense or defense,
and in the end redeemed it...
But now, there's a new item
out that I want right away!
See, that one over there!
I don't have enough points
left! What should I do?!
You really enjoy life, don't you...
Um, your total...
Which would you like,
smoking, or non-smoking?
Um, since we're underage,
we'd like the non-smoking seats.
Then, this way.
Oh, I'm going to go to the bathroom first.
Sure.
Hey, Tsukasa, over here!
Welcome back.
I'm back!
Um, I always think about this,
but why are bathrooms in places like this
often located on the same
side as the smoking seats?
That's true...
We're going out of our way to
pick the non-smoking seats, too.
But seriously, I wonder why that is?
Of course, it's because it's
better to be closer to water
in case someone causes a fire or something.
They have buckets and hoses and stuff.
Oh, they have hoses too?
They do. Of course they do.
This is why people who never
contribute any labor to society
are so troublesome. Oh, brother.
Shut up!
It's like putting a lid on a bad odor?
Or rather, let's stop this
conversation during a meal.
Bad smells and toilets and all.
Today, in the metropolitan area,
there has been a series of incidents
where elementary school girls
were called over from behind
by a stranger while on their way to school.
Criminal cases that target children
have been on the rise lately.
The academic committee informed
all schools to be on guard.
You should be careful too, Yu-chan.
You're right.
Unforgivable!
Though, I have to say I can
understand how he feels...
You understand?
They're making such a big deal
of it every day like this!
It's sad to think that there is someone
who would still call over
children they don't know!
I would like to say one thing to them!
"Aren't you jealous of me?"
I don't know what you're thinking about,
but please don't do anything that
would get Sis Yui to arrest you.
Lucky Star!
Excuse me!
Yes!
Yoohoo! I'm here!
Welcome!
By the way, where's Kagami today?
She's out with friends from her class.
I see...
It's... somehow... frustrating,
or rather, a bit lacking...
You're lonely, aren't you?
It's gotten really warm lately.
It has.
There's no homework during spring
break, so it's so peaceful.
It is.
A line like that is reserved for
someone who always does their best
to finish her homework by herself, I think.
Don't hit somewhere strange!
Impossible?!
You know, when you play
robot games like this,
do you know who all the
characters are and stuff?
Yeah, to a certain extent.
I see...
You said that your tastes in manga and anime
He completely burnt out,
and turned into white ash.
have been affected by your
dad, come to think of it.
Yup, yup.
Then, when you were young,
you weren't able to keep up with all
the conversations that girls had?
Why? I had more chances
to see that kind of stuff,
so I could totally keep up, you know?
Eh? Uh... Is that so? Wait...
Is that your final answer?
It's my final answer!
What a pause... It really gets to me.
His face is scary, and it's so huge!
Oh... Iooking at the time,
I'm sure she got this question wrong.
It's the end of the show.
Wait a minute, Tsukasa!
Quit using the time left until the commercial
to guess whether they got the right answer!
But I can't bear all the suspense!
They drag it on for so long, too!
The show is all about enjoying that!
But that's so like Tsukasa.
S'up.
Yoohoo!
Let me introduce you. This
is my cousin, Yu-chan.
Pleased to meet you. My
name is Yutaka Kobayakawa.
My friends, Tsukasa and Kagami.
Oh, these two are the ones that
Sis is always talking about.
Oh? I wonder what she says about us?
What kind of stuff have you been telling her?
Though I can tell from her reaction...
See? Isn't it just like I told you?
Yutaka-chan, are you done with
your graduation ceremony already?
Oh, yes, it was the other day.
Graduation! That really takes me back.
I don't remember my graduation.
Yutaka-chan, did you get the second
button from the top from any guys?
No, no, nothing like that.
Our junior high uniform tops were blazers.
Come to think of it, lots of
schools are like that these days.
Or maybe they don't do all the
"receive something from the person
you're interested in" stuff anymore?
You think so? That's a bit lonely...
Though I didn't do any of that, either.
When I look at blogs on the 'net,
there's still some of it
going on, more or less.
I see.
But that's all about getting something
from the guy you like, right?
Well, I think that's how it is.
Then, at the point that you go to get it,
you're basically confessing your love to him,
so why don't you ask him out properly,
and get the actual person,
and not just a button?
Gotcha!
Well, that's the ideal, if
you talk about ideals...
That's right! Yutaka-chan, weren't you
interested in someone or anything?
Oh, no, no.
I used to stay home from school sick a lot,
and even when I attended, I
would get sick really soon...
I really dragged down the
atmosphere around me.
Besides, I'm really short, too,
and my physique is so childish...
People always used to make fun of me.
Nothing like falling in love with
someone, or someone falling for me.
It's all right! Yu-chan, as long
as you don't choose your partner,
there's a big need for you!
Need?!
Po-cky.
Yu-chan, let me see your yearbook.
Oh, I wanna see the yearbook.
It's kind of embarrassing.
I'm not in that many pictures, either.
What class were you in, Yu-chan?
You looked at the round circles they use for
people who were absent on picture
day before you asked, didn't you?
Oh, you figured that out after all?
The difference between junior
high and high school?
Yeah.
Like, where you're not forced
to join an extracurricular club?
Doesn't that depend on your school?
We're a prep school,
so the curriculum may be wider and
more fast-paced than in junior high.
And it takes time to commute to school,
so it will take a bit of stamina, maybe?
One definite difference would
be that the farther you move up,
from elementary to junior
high to high school,
is that you spend more
time sleeping in class.
Especially on the subjects
you're not good at!
Oh, that might be right!
The teacher starts sounding like
they're talking a different language,
Just make sure that you
don't end up like that.
and when that happens your
consciousness starts to drift away!
Right...
Oh, Yu-chan, you brought
your junior high uniform?
Yeah. Our uniform was pretty plain,
so I thought I'd be able to
wear it as street clothes,
since this isn't my home area.
I see...
Kagami, what did you guys do
with your uniforms and stuff?
We gave them to younger
girls in our neighborhood.
What about you?
Mine?
Though I'm sure you couldn't
find anyone to give yours to.
Shut up! How rude!
Me, I'm like Yu-chan, and took the
effort to keep it for cosplay purposes!
Cos?!
When you put it that way,
it sounds really bad.
I mean, it's cosplay.
But in any case, our alma mater...
When we talk about stuff like this,
it makes me want to drop by my
elementary or junior high and say hi.
But there have been a lot of run-ins
and strange campus visitation cases,
so it would be bad to be misunderstood
and get weird looks...
Well, in your case, you won't
have to worry about that at all.
Am I right in assuming
that wasn't a compliment?
But vacation sure passes by quickly.
You're right. Before you know it,
school's about to start again.
Spring has those physical exams
and fitness tests of all sorts...
They're a pain.
But Kona-chan, you have good
motor nerves. I'm jealous.
Hey, Tsukasa...
Which nerves are the motor nerves, anyway?
Hello, everyone!
Sorry I'm late, but Yutaka,
congratulations on graduating!
Oh, Sis, welcome.
Since we're celebrating a graduation today,
let's all go drinking together!
We'll invite Uncle, too! It'll be my treat!
Sis... No, that's not good, Sis!
Officer, we're still underage...
You shouldn't do that, Sis!
Sis, I don't think we can
go in places like that yet!
They won't catch on if you go
in with your head held up high!
I used to do it all the time
back when I was a student,
but I was never caught once!
No, no, no, we can't possibly do that, Sis!
No, I'm sure they'll catch on, mostly
thanks to your two relatives.
I see...
Don't sweat it.
Now that Yu-chan is with us,
wanna go to Land for once?
It's spring vacation, after all.
Oh!
Um... I'm very happy about that,
but since I'm imposing
on you by staying here,
I don't need you to worry about me so much...
And actually, I went there the
other day as a school field trip.
Oh, come to think of it, I had
a field trip like that too.
But, Yu-chan, were you all right?
Yeah. My health kept up
with me, and it was fun.
I was with my friends, too.
No... More like the height
restrictions on the rides...
Of all things! I was fine!
I'm in high school now, okay?
And so... I was thinking as I was
watching those school drama series,
junior high and high school are
different in all sorts of ways, right?
Well, yeah.
You don't have class meals
in high school, right?
Oh, that's right.
It's mostly your own lunches, or
meals at the school cafeteria.
That, and buying boxed lunches.
Do you make lunch every day, Sis?
Well, yeah.
Wow, amazing!
It looks like things will
be tough from now on...
She's really good at games and stuff.
She has a very wide range of communication.
She can cook and do household chores!
Lately, I'm starting to understand the
pressure you feel as an older sister.
When she looks at me like that,
I've got to give it my best.
Right, Kagami?
Huh?
Sis Yui driving the car recklessly.
Heya! You doin' good?
Sis Yui getting drunk and coming
back to her family home.
Homework? It's fine as long
as you write something vague!
Sis Yui being rather irresponsible
for all sorts of things.
But... I wonder if it all
depends on the person.
For starters, talk so I can understand you.
Lucky Star!
It's my final answer!
Oh, dammit...
I seriously can't put up with all of this.
She's irritated today...
I thought I finally got around to showing up,
but when I checked the recording,
I'm not on screen at all!
Do it... Should I do it?
What are they thinking
when they make the show...
Why do I have to fall behind all those
idiots who have no sense or talent...
Akira-sama, call the title! Call the title!
Huh?
Uh... Please call the title...
Her eyes are so tiny!
Morning luckies.
I don't have time for stuff like that.
It's impossible! I'm disgusted!
Just my voice, just my voice!
There's no point in that!
Um, I wasn't on screen, either.
I couldn't care less about you!
What wind!
You know, did I ask about you right now? Huh?
Did I bring you up even this much
in the conversation right now?
Uh... No, not one word about me.
Then why do you stick your face in there?
Why do you come sauntering out?
Are you stupid?
You always, always butt in
with your me-me-me thing...
That's what you call self-centered!
You should just stay back! Someone
as lowly as you, Shiraishi!
Oh, my mouth is going to rot!
Look here, okay? The problem at
hand is that I, Akira Kogami,
was not shown on screen in the main segment.
That's right...
I ask you, what am I? I'm an idol, right?
When you mention an idol,
your face is your life!
It's all about showing up on
screen... What do you think?
Yes. You are absolutely right.
I can't hear you.
Wh-What the staff for this episode
did is completely inexcusable!
Oh? What are you writing?
"Akira Kogami" "Revenge" "Plan for a perfect
appearance in the main segment!!!"
So, Akira is asking of you!
So that Akira can show
up in the main segment,
everyone's help is necessary!
So, putting it straight,
I'd like your support!
Any method is okay! In any case,
just keep pushing harder and harder!
I really want you to see Akira's fine acting
as a top-rate actress in the main segment!
Well, speaking just between you and me,
A "want" call...
comparing the other cast members
to the charm of me, Akira,
there is a giant wall as big as that between
an Oscar-winning Hollywood actress
and a kindergarten class skit!
You there, that wants to see lots
of that pretty, gorgeous acting!
The chance is right in front of you!
Don't overlook it! Your one letter!
Your one homepage comment!
They'll come true with Akira in
the main segment of Lucky Star!
So when this broadcast is over,
What? Stop her?
you should get a postcard
ready, or your computer...
Akira-sama, um...
Shut up! Why are you
chit-chatting with me now?!
This is the good part!
How many times do I have to tell
you to not get in my way...
Oh? Already? Oh, I wanted all of you to know
so much more about how fabulous Akira is...
I'll show you all lots of my true
charm next week in the main segment!
Just kidding!
Well... Please look forward
to the next episode...
Bye-nee!
Oh, it's over. It's so painful.
Hey you, get the producer over here.
Eh? Who, me?
In the first place, this week's
corrected script is wrong.
What is the title of this segment?
Well, um, it's Lucky Channel.
The script said "Lucky Paradise."
Well, um... What is it?
Furthermore! They have some
nerve to treat me that way!
Just because the previous
show he worked on was a hit!
Isn't the producer getting
full of it? Like, full of it!
No. I think you shouldn't be
saying something like that...
Mr. Miyagi!
Hello! This is Minoru Shiraishi!
Now, then, I'd like you to listen up!
♪ I was spending my days
wishing for excitement ♪
♪ Who was it that granted my wish? ♪
♪ A future that you seemingly
(can predict) but can't ♪
♪ Even then, I know one thing ♪
♪ To the end of time, BOOOON! ♪
♪ This feeling that
is a warp and a loop ♪
♪ With an imagination that engulfs
anything and everything, let's play ♪
♪ Something on one sunny day, more
fun than any magic possible ♪
♪ Endlessly pours down,
it's not impossible ♪
♪ When we see each other tomorrow,
we're all humming as we smile ♪
♪ Let's gather happiness,
such a thing is so easy ♪
♪ Chase after me, try to catch it ♪
♪ A big dream... You
like dreams, right? ♪
"The End"
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's up with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
I am Minami Iwasaki.
I am Yutaka Kobayakawa.
Iwasaki-san, apparently the two of us
are supposed to introduce the next episode.
Do you know what it's about?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Eh? Really? That's rather troublesome...
I don't know anything about it either.
Then I guess I'll wrap it up now.
Next episode: I Can't Suddenly Change.
We haven't said anything.
I wonder if it's all right.
Please look forward to it.