Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Oh yeah...
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Yo!
Ah, Onee-chan.
How was your test?
About how I usually do...
Not good.
During exam periods, we have more free time than usual...
But before you realize it, you end up doing the things you normally would...
And you end up cramming the night before.
I think you need to be more aware of the fact that you're a person applying to college.
Under the Sun
"Thousands of manga and games were confiscated from the suspect's room."
"It is believed that other crimes can also be attributed to him."
Not this again...
That's amazing.
There was another story about a person like you on the news.
Every time this happens, it makes me think how it's unfair.
They always use manga like those as examples,
when there are good manga out there as well, waiting to be discovered.
I guess so...
I feel sorry for them.
Kagami, you're such a good person!
Normally people would just label me as a desperate otaku and make fun of me.
Looking at the people around me,
I notice a lot of times sisters tend to absorb the characteristics from one another.
Like you and Yui-neesan.
Or Tsukasa and Kagami...
Sure sure.
So I was having a conversation like that with Onee-chan this morning.
Minami, you're really attached to Miyuki-chan.
It's as if you were sisters.
I see.
Absorption, was it?
Kona-chan, happy birthday!
Oh!
Though I would have forgotten if Tsukasa hadn't mentioned it...
Congratulations.
Thanks guys!
It's nice to celebrate your birthday with a bunch of people, but...
...at this age, I can't really be happy about getting older.
Really?
It makes me super happy!
Why's that?
Do you want to get a driver's license or something?
That way, I can play eroge now.
Haven't you been openly playing them up until now?
Of course not...
You've grown older,
but you haven't changed at all, on the inside or outside.
Let me go!
Miyuki probably gets mistaken for being older than she actually is.
Because she seems so mature.
Well, when I go outside in casual clothing,
I occasionally get mistaken for an office lady.
So you skip the college student look.
In your case,
if you went outside in casual clothing, people would think you're in grade school.
Say whatever you want,
starting from today onward, I'm an adult!
What are you talking about?
Besides,
if you're an adult now, you shouldn't be making a big deal out of games and manga anymore, right?
B-But you still need to have a child-like heart filled with passion and dreams!
So what does that make you?
This?
While Onee-chan is out working, we're going to prepare a surprise birthday party for her.
Sorry, I'm late!
All right!
Let's get everything ready.
Yeah!
Happy Birthday
Onee-chan
Perfect timing, it must be Konata.
I wonder if she'll be coming home soon.
Konata?
I'm sorry!
I forgot to mention, but the guys at my work are throwing a party for me,
so I won't be eating dinner at home tonight.
And I'll probably come home late as well.
Yutaka.
Doesn't this taste great?
Yeah, I tried...
Yui-chan, you can take that off now.
Future aspirations, is it?
I have dreams and stuff,
but when you actually think about it, it's pretty tough to decide.
That's true.
The major you decide on now will greatly affect your career in the future.
First choice is nutritional science.
Second is fashion design.
Third is marketing.
Yeah.
Since I like cooking and crafts.
So you wrote down your dreams.
And what about you, Miyuki-san?
I want to become a doctor, so while I didn't write down colleges,
I put down medical schools for all three choices.
That's Miyuki-san for you.
You have clear goals.
How about you, Kagami?
Me?
My first choice is law.
My second choice is economics.
And my third choice is literature.
What's that.
How boring.
Is that a bad thing?
What about you?
First Choice
Brigade Chief
Second Choice
Nanto Shinken Master
Third Choice
Storyboarder
You're going for the punchline, aren't you?
Actually, do you have any specialties other than the staring game?
Specialties...?
I can name every Pok***n!
That's certainly amazing...
Though it has nothing to do with your future.
Here it is!
I'll just go pay for this.
When you buy magazines or manga,
you always take the one on the bottom, don't you?
Everyone touches the one on the top.
I'd rather buy a cleaner copy.
Ah, I know what you mean.
It's like going to a sushi-go-round...
...and ordering straight from the chef instead of taking the ones spinning around.
I mean, most of the time the ones on the belt are already dry.
Kagami, you do that?
What a rude customer.
No way, you mean you don't!?
That's kind of cheating.
I've been wondering,
but how can you stand reading books with nothing but text in them?
Don't you get sleepy?
But this is a light novel.
So it's almost like reading a manga.
Eh, are you sure?
There are plenty of insert pictures,
and the expressions aren't that difficult to understand.
Do you want to give it a shot?
Um, well...
It's already been made into an anime, so I'll just watch that.
If it was a manga, you'd normally say how the original has its own way of expressing things...
...and check both out.
Just read it already.
I regret, but I'll have to pass.
But you know,
you read lots of stuff besides light novels.
How should I put it...
The more literature you stash under your belt, the more refined your soul becomes.
I guess it's like food for the soul.
I see.
What is it?
By that reasoning,
you eat a lot of snacks to make your body more refined, am I correct?
Shut up!
Aren't there also light novels...
...serialized in the magazines you read?
Not just comics.
I usually look at the pictures, though.
So you talk big,
but your "love" doesn't amount too much, does it?
So you skim over it, don't you?
Fine, I get it!
I'll read it!
Oh no, it's fine...
No need to force yourself.
I only skim it because I have lots of other stuff to read!
That's why I said it's fine.
I didn't say a thing.
Oh, no!
I forgot my world history textbook.
I was reviewing and left it on my desk...
Konata, lend me your world history textbook.
You leave it here, don't you?
Sure.
Did you forget yours?
Yeah...
That's unusual.
Here.
Oh, Hiiragi,
that's a fun-looking textbook.
N-No, this is...
It's hard to focus...
Guess I'll get something to drink.
Ah, damn!
Huh?
I thought there would still be some leftover since I just bought it the other day...
Guess it gives me a chance to get some fresh air.
Closed for the day
They're closed!
This must be some kind of a trial.
Your total comes to 320 yen.
Huh?
What's the matter, Onee-chan?
Man...
Did you ever notice that when you're frustrated,
you make a bunch of trivial mistakes that end up frustrating you even more?
I know what you mean!
Everything you do just doesn't go your way.
Like a negative spiral?
That's right!
I baked a cake.
Do you want some?
Yay!
Studying for exams is hard,
so you need a change of pace every now and then.
That's it!
I'll bake cookies tomorrow.
Oh!
That sure relieves the stress.
I'm counting on you!
Afterwards . . .
Now I've become stressed about this...
Right?
Don't you think so, Iwasaki-san?
I know.
Those two are just so busy, they keep missing each other.
I know what you mean.
That's right...
Onee-chan is busy preparing for college...
I shouldn't disturb her studies!
I'm sorry...
I'm going to talk in a softer voice.
Yu-chan.
When you're off the phone,
Let's go play some video games.
A fighting game!
Say what!?
I guess this will be the last year I wear this uniform.
It really makes me wonder...
There's something inside.
My favorite handkerchief that I thought I lost...
It was in the pocket of my summer uniform, huh?
Didn't we have some wasabi octopus?
I wonder what this is?
What was this?
It's changed so much I can't even tell...
It sure does rain a lot during the rainy season.
It does.
Just when it was getting really hot...
And when we change to summer uniforms, it suddenly gets cold.
How annoying.
You guys are still here?
Sensei, you're lucky since you can wear whatever you want.
What are you talking about?
It's so much easier having a uniform, that way you don't have to think about what to wear every morning.
Sensei, you must be really...
Yahoo!
It's the rainy season!
It's so humid!
Yui-neesan.
Onee-chan.
There's so much rain, it really makes you depressed.
Would you like some tea?
Yes, please.
Well, then how about a more pleasant topic?
It's almost been a year since you got married, right?
That's right.
Time sure flies.
An image of the raining sky...
...is like the image of Yui-neesan's heart...
...as her first anniversary approaches, but her husband is still away on a business trip...
And her heart is...
I'm sorry, that was my fault.
It's okay...
I'm used to this kind of pain.
Here, have something warm to drink.
Bu, it's still depressing...
It's delicious!
I'm glad.
Geez.
At this rate my love is going to wear out!
If we took it to an auto repair place,
it'd probably be good as new in about 45 minutes.
You could at least comfort me...
I'm sorry, I just...
Hello?
Eh?
Oh, so you can make it back?
Didn't even take 45 minutes.
It was instantaneous.
It was.
Eh?
You haven't gotten those clothes back from Matsuri-oneechan yet?
No...
That's no good.
If you don't ask for them back,
she'll end up taking them as her own.
That would be bad!
I really like those!
I envy Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san for having two older sisters.
I guess.
Really?
If you ask me, I'm more jealous of only children like you two.
Right?
Well, I do feel that way at times...
But you know,
if you have a large cast, you can do a whole lot more.
Like the old story...
...of an American mother and her four daughters who await the return of their father.
Or an enigmatic group of female thieves who target works of art.
One, two.
Oops, one too many.
Geez, she turns every conversation into something about anime or games.
Hey, Kagami.
Did you get the groceries for dinner?
Eh?
Ah!
Tsukasa, you forgot to tell her?
Sorry...
What? What?
What's going on?
Did you forget?
Mom and Dad are out tonight.
Their trip was today?
That's why we were supposed to buy the groceries for dinner tonight.
I completely forgot.
I even called Kagami's cell phone,
and left you one message.
You have 1 message
Matsuri,
why don't we just settle for what's in the fridge?
I finally get a chance to cook something...
You can cook next time.
Eh?
Geez.
Kagami and Tsukasa, this is all your fault!
I'm sorry...
Fine, I'll go right now.
I think you went too far, Matsuri.
But...
Hey, does she even know what to buy?
Geez, what's with her?
She doesn't even like to cook that much.
Why's she all worked up now?
Onee-chan!
Tsukasa!
Onee-chan, you don't have the shopping list, right?
They're late...
If you're going to be worried, you should have gone yourself.
You're late.
What's the matter?
Matsuri was really worried.
The usual store was out of saffron,
so I suggested that we substitute it with curry powder,
but Onee-chan insisted that we find some, so we went to the supermarket further away.
Geez, you didn't have to go that far.
Well, sorry!
Come on now, let's make dinner.
Man, I'm starving.
Here.
Sorry for the wait.
All that's left is Matsuri's specialty.
Done!
It looks delicious!
Looks like it cooked rather nicely.
Hey, Matsuri-oneechan,
when did you learn to cook this?
I went to a restaurant with some of my college friends the other day...
...and this dish was served.
It was so delicious that I wanted to let you all try it,
so I asked for the recipe.
I'm surprised they actually told you.
C'mon, let's dig in.
Okay!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Listen to this.
Your father got the dates wrong.
What do you mean?
The reservation was apparently for next week.
Such a basic mistake, straight out of a comedy.
Just in time?
You haven't eaten?
No.
Paella, is it?
Matsuri-oneechan made it!
Wow, that's amazing!
Yeah, but Kagami was the one that did the shopping for the ingredients.
She even went all the way to the farther supermarket.
Then, I guess we'll help ourselves.
Good idea.
Hey, this is pretty good.
Ah!
Who took the mussel?
Mussel?
Was I not supposed to?
How could you!
I was saving that for last.
Then put your name on it.
Stop fighting.
Yo!
I think I'll accompany you after school today.
Is there something you need to get?
Yamada Shi**a's new book.
Though lately we've been getting a lot of assignments,
so I don't really have much time to read.
Yeah, I have a pile of unread manga beside my pillow.
But I can't help myself and end up buying new ones.
I kind of know what you mean.
Why don't you just finish your old ones before you buy new ones?
Well,
it's more reassuring if you just buy it ahead of time.
Or you might feel empty otherwise.
Right?
Don't look at me!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
Okay!
We're coming at you full of energy today as well!
Lucky Channel is already on its 17th episode, how time flies!
Okay!
And your navigator is...
Even a red rose has thorns!
The platypus of the idol world!
Kogami Akira!
And...
Hey there!
We've invited a really big guest for you guys today!
How long are you going to make me wait!?
Crap.
He really showed up.
Sorry, sorry.
He sure did.
Um...
Today's guest is the Anime Manager,
Special Guest
Anizawa Meito -san
Anizawa Meito-san.
Okay!
This show is weak!
But, well...
Lucky Star is a slow and laid back anime...
...about ordinary high school students.
Which is why...
...Lucky Channel, too, should take it nice and slow...
No way!
Where'd he go!?
He's fast!
Listen to me.
Do you know what the three most important elements for determining an anime's success are?
The three elements?
Um...
Seiyuu, animation, and scenario?
Wrong!
My back is burning in red flames!
The answer is...
The answer is?
The staff and cast's love for the work!
And also time!
And then production costs!
Though those are all factors out of our control...
Understand?
No matter how good the original work was,
if the scenario is bad, it's hopeless!
Now matter how hard the seiyuu try,
if the characters aren't in color, there's no point!
Just take a look at Shiraishi.
W-What the... I'm white!
Everyone has to do their part!
Each part requires its resources!
The love and passion put into it...
Is what makes everything come to life!
Is that how it is?
You.
You're currently Kogami Akira-san, right?
Currently?
I always was, and always will be Kogami Akira.
When you were Rou**n!
Gao**nger!
**tato!
Mai**i!
Weren't you filled with passion!?
What are you talking about?
If you still have any regrets...
None, none at all.
Then you must put everything you have into Kogami Akira...
...and burn up!
Like I was saying...
Yes!
I will burn to ashes as Shiraishi Minoru!
Well said, Shiraishi!
All right.
For starters, we'd better...
Practice on working the audience!
You were the MC at an event recently, correct?
Bye-bii...
You were watching?
Of course! It's the nature of my job!
Good work, everyone!
It was a huge job!
I'm going now.
I was a nervous wreck the entire time!
Exactly, you have a lot to learn!
Take care of the rest, Shiraishi.
First, your ad-libs are weak!
Yes!
You can't be losing to someone like Sugita-
Shiraishi Minoru
Theater
Ma'am!
Are you unsatisfied with your husband?
Hello. Shiraishi Minoru here.
And now, listen to me!
aimai 3 SENCHI sorya puni tte KOTO kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchacchau
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & RELEASE gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase FUU! ase FUU! no tanima ni DARLiN' DARLiN' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
Shiraishi
nanka DAru- nanka DEru-
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiTEru are ikko ga chigatterunru-
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayamiNBo- koutetsubo-
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbo- i-kagen ni SHINASAI
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta AITSU no hoteru KARADA tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsu- no onya no KO
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu HARIGANE okawari DA-DA-DA!
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON o-endan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
LET'S GET! CHERI-PAI
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kange-kai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
LOOK UP! sense-shon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan ... shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bo-zen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte SHIRENJA-
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
SE-RA-fuku dakara desu <-- ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
Fast forwarded for your convenience.
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu <-- KYA? WA! iiv
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 PIKUTO suru madette chu-cho da yan
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte YEAH! harikitte YEAH! MY DARLiN' DARLiN! P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Too boring, Shiraishi!
Stop following protocol!
Heil Brayking!
Manager!
All right!
Listen up!
Mind set for becoming a good seiyuu!
Rule No.1!
Mind set, rule No.1!
If you can't beat them, join them.
How sad!
Next time: "To Each Her Own"
「 To Each Her Own 」
And that's the last of Anizawa.
Say goodbye.
Finger!