The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
He comes by every once in a while.
It's been a while, Kida Masaomi.
What?
Tanaka Tarou
They got in a fight with another gang and vanished.
The Yellow Scarves
We really can't ask Orihara Izaya about that huh...
Those bastards dragged me back... damn it. Damn it all!
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Mikajima Saki
Your friend was hospitalized?
Who told you?
I saw it from the window.
You were here everyday.
A girl, right?
A quirky, charming high school girl, with glasses and a nice body.
Do you love her?
Yeah. I'm in a love triangle with her and my best friend.
If you add me, it'll be a square.
We're already over. Finished!
All finished.
Right?
Then why are you here?
Were you feeling nostalgic?
Sorry. I'm heading out.
You'll come back.
That's just how things are.
That's why you can go out with as many girls as you want, and I don't care.
Because in the end, you'll love me more than you'll ever love them.
I didn't need to ask.
The same thing, over and over again.
Even if you date tons of girls, you'll still come back to me.
Then you'll love me, more than you ever loved her.
But I didn't want to hear her next words.
Izaya told me so.
When you look at it like this,
you feel like a god.
It feels pretty good.
Three-way struggles are nice.
Especially when all three of the leaders are so closely connected.
God attack!
The hotter the honeymoon,
the higher the flames of despair.
Look! The pawns burn like garbage!
Now, then...
How will each of the non-pawns move?
Kadota and his gang,
Shinra, Simon...
I guess Shizu would be the king.
Celty's the queen.
So the joker is...
Who cares?
It's been fun.
You think so, too, right?
Out of Your Control
Raira General Hospital
-One Year Earlier-
I heard she hadn't died.
Good to hear...
As long as she's alive, the rest will work itself out.
Izaya...
You're smart.
You know that what happened to her is your fault.
I think it was pretty wise of you, not letting your feelings
overwhelm you and trying to punch me.
Right answer.
It's natural to direct your anger at me right now.
I was deliberately provoking you.
She's in a coma?
I hope she wakes up.
Or would it be better for you if she never does?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
You're scared, aren't you?
If she wakes up, she might blame you for it.
But what if she dies?
Are you gonna spend the rest of your life feeling guilty?
In other words, whether she lives or dies, it won't affect the guilt you feel at all.
You can't get away.
The past will follow you, wherever you go.
Forever and ever and ever and ever...
You know why?
They're lonely.
A person's past and memories are very lonely things.
I don't believe in God.
There's no proof of his existence.
In a world where there isn't even proof of the future,
the past exists.
Even if it's tainted with misunderstandings and delusions,
if the people themselves believe in it,
the past is the truth to them.
And if you base your actions or your life around it,
in a way, it's a type of god itself.
I have no idea what you're getting at!
Sure you do.
You can't get away from her, ever.
Your guilt will become your past,
and she your God.
But isn't that fine?
You love her...
Anri's back to her old self!
Glad she and her looks are safe.
Don't talk like that.
But I'm really relieved.
Really.
U-Um, thanks, you guys.
No need to thank me.
As long as you and your looks are safe.
Same for me, except for the "looks" part.
Yeah?
OK.
Got it.
Be right there.
Sorry! A friend has something he needs right away!
Yeah?
If you need to hate someone, hate my friend all you like.
Hating someone's free, and it doesn't hurt me at all.
Two birds with one stone!
Two chicks with one guy!
Two chicks with one guy?
See ya tomorrow!
Was it really that important?
Kida's been acting weird lately, don't you think so?
Really? Are you sure you're not overthinking things?
I've never said anything about the Yellow Scarves to Mikado.
This reality and the one that exists when I'm with him are both true to me,
but I feel like there's a big difference between them.
We spent all our days fighting.
That was the only thing that connected us.
I wanted someone to say they liked me,
that I was a good person.
That was when I first met Saki.
I like that scarf of yours.
You're much cooler than the rumors say, Kida Masaomi.
What?
How did you know my name?
You an esper?
Maybe like Esper Ito?
You just keep reading my mind like that, and I'll stuff you in a bag and take you home!
Yes...
Aw, you're so silly.
But it's not me.
There's another esper.
Who's that?
Got a girl here with the sixth sense?
They're amazing.
They know everything.
That was when I met the man
I really wish I hadn't.
Hey there.
Kida Masaomi, right?
Who're you?
Orihara Izaya.
Information Broker.
I'm kind of her guardian.
Not her boyfriend or anything!
Don't worry.
Pleasure to meet ya.
General!
I told you, call me Kida
Masaomi, not General.
But that's just kinda...
We can't find out anything
about the Dollars.
Some of our guys are members,
but we don't know who their leader is.
They say, even at their first meeting,
six months ago, no one could figure it out.
They doing anything?
The leader issued a request for information on the Slasher.
Maybe they really aren't behind the attacks.
Even so, they're still fishy.
Anything else?
Horoda was taken out by that Black Rider.
Horoda?
A bit back, I was making fun of some weirdo in a white gas mask,
when the Black Rider got me...
The Black Rider?
Yeah, some kind of weird black oil enveloped me...
Yeah...
Wonder who the Black Rider really is.
Some say he's part of the Dollars.
Whatever.
By the way, you guys are older than me, right?
Well, yes...
Don't bring in anyone older than you.
We start seeing names like "Someone of the Something Gang", and we're done for.
We're kids!
We've got a lot of members,but we can't win against adults.
We'll be used and thrown away!
Like how Orihara Izaya used me.
From then on, whenever I wasn't sure about something,
Saki would tell me to ask Izaya.
She would always bring up what he thought about things.
I'm glad this could be resolved to your mutual benefit.
At first, everyone was pretty annoyed,
but actually, if you did stuff his way, things went well.
I didn't trust him.
I tried to keep as far away from him as I could.
Izaya's amazing.
He knows everything.
He's never wrong.
So if he told you to jump off a bridge and die, would you?
Probably, yeah.
I kinda pitied her.
I wanted to free her from him.
So, you think we're dating?
I don't know.
What are you doing with a guy like me, anyway?
I like you.
Did he tell you to?
Just at first, yeah.
He doesn't get involved in other people's love lives.
Then why do you still like me?
You're cool!
You're cute, maybe.
Do you like me?
If you stopped your fanatical worship of him, I might!
I can't!
I'd be happy if you overlooked that one flaw.
So you know it's a flaw?
Yup.
Not that I'm gonna fix it.
If you think it's a flaw, fix it.
I'll help you.
So we started to date.
No one was mad at me for dating Saki.
I was serious,
and the Yellow Scarves were too busy fighting Blue Square.
They fought dirty.
They'd fight small groups with big ones.
They wouldn't attack unless they were sure they could win.
Over a hundred of my friends were hurt.
Everyone was scared.
So was I.
I was afraid of losing my place in life if I disbanded the Yellow Scarves.
So...
Ask Izaya.
I relied on him.
I was too scared to do otherwise.
Welcome!
I told myself it was for everyone else's sake.
Come in and let's chat.
His information changed the Yellow Scarves dramatically.
He didn't just give us information on where they were,
he gave us information on how to fight.
We'd been losing, but we weren't any longer.
Your information's so awesome!
Eventually, I lost my fear of him.
Actually, I was enjoying my victory, but...
Kida Masaomi?
Who's this?
Hello!
This is Izumii, head of Blue Square.
I have a quiz for you!
Question 1: We've got a special guest here today!
Who do you suppose it is?
Hint: It's someone very, very, very important to you!
Hey!
Time's up, but I bet you figured it out, didn't you?
That's right!
What did you do with Saki?!
Question 2: What do you suppose she looks like right now?
Question 3:
What bone was that, that just broke?
Hint: She won't be walking for a while!
Final Question:
What's going to happen to her if you don't come to
the parking garage, where you trapped us, in twenty minutes?
I regretted it. I'd been a fool.
I'd figured this was just a bunch of middle schoolers fighting.
It wasn't.
It was a war.
And I'd started it!
Orihara Izaya
Pick up! Pick up, damn it!
Kida Masaomi
The person you have dialed is-
What the hell?!
Izumii, she fainted.
Boring.
We just broke her leg in a few places.
I ran.
I had to go.
I would go there and kill every one of them who had made her scream.
The person you have dialed...
So yeah, the Yellow Scarves?
We're gonna beat down their leader.
I said, I ain't down for it.
No, it looks like we kidnapped
his girlfriend.
She's a kid but pretty hot.
It'll be plenty of fun!
Kidnapped?
I see.
I'll be right there.
Right?
You can't pass this up-
When you wake up, tell Izumii that I'm done with the bastard.
I couldn't move.
What I had just been feeling was gone.
Why... Saki was in danger,
and I couldn't move.
Why?
Why am I so scared?
I thought I could do anything for her!
I was just a powerless middle schooler.
You think she'll die?
Not that I care.
She's not bleeding, so it's fine.
Sup!
Oh my, my, my...
You actually kidnapped her!
What? It's just you, Yumasaki?
Where's Kadota?
Thus, unlike in the movies and manga,
no help came,
and a terrible fate awaited her.
So I was thinking...
If a hero appeared and saved her,
maybe it'd turn into an anime,
and I could be, like,
another world's savior with superpowers,
and I'd get all the chicks and
my dream of building a harem!
Dude's one creepy bastard.
So, yeah. Here goes the "Make me an
anime hero via a happy ending" plan!
Banzai!
Hurry!
Damn you, Kadota!
We shouldn't move her too much.
We should get her to a hospital.
You guys sure you're OK with this?
We're with you.
We don't care about Blue Square.
Honestly, I always thought Izumii and
Horoda were a couple of assholes.
Agreed!
It'd be cooler to throw it out the window.
I don't litter.
Eventually, Saki woke up.
The leader, Izumii, was arrested,
thanks to her testimony.
A weakened Blue Square
was forced to disband.
Hey.
You're Kida, with the Yellow Scarves.
Who are you guys?
I dunno how to put it...
I'm Kadota.
I heard you betrayed your
gang and saved Saki.
Umm... Thank you.
Actually, we just went to see her.
She said you haven't been there.
It's got nothing to do with you.
We were asked to give you a message.
She said she can see you
quite well from her window.
Thanks for coming.
I told her that you were stopped by
Blue Square and couldn't make it in time.
She wasn't angry with you.
Later.
Why... Why did you tell her that?
When did I ask for that?
I'd have told her that,
even if you'd told me not to.
You know what happened, right?!
I... I ran...
I couldn't move!
Yeah, I know.
And you're still running from her now.
You want me to lie to her?!
After I ran away from her...
Listen, kid.
If you feel guilty for running,
then for the rest of your life, you must
live with the pain of lying to her.
That's how you can make it up to her.
And if you don't want to lie to her,
then don't run.
Face her and say it!
I'll let you run from the past.
But don't run from the present
and the future.
Hey, Kadota's saying something cool.
Wow!
We'll call him poemy bunny boy!
I never did go.
I tried to go.
I went many times.
Just to tell her I wanted to break up.
But I couldn't.
I left the Yellow Scarves.
You decide on which high school you're going to?
I'm going to Raira Academy.
It's close.
I kept talking about how great a place Raira was.
I was lonely.
When I was talking with him, I felt calm.
You come, too.
And then I met him again.
I met Anri, too.
I thought my peaceful high school life would continue.
But...
Damn them... Damn them for bringing me back.
I was never going to go back.
You can't get away from her, ever.
Your guilt toward her will become your past, and she your God.
That's right.
That's why I'm here.
I'm going to defeat the Slasher who hurt my friend, Anri.
If the Slasher is in the Dollars, I'll take them down, too.
I won't freeze this time.
This time, I will...
Who's there?
What is it?
A girl was looking in here!
I've got men chasing her!
A girl?
Is it the Dollars, you think?
I want to talk to her.
Catch her, but don't hurt her.
Right!
I'll go around this way.
I should be certain about this.
It's why I came back.
So why... Why am I so uneasy?
Why?
Why is Kida...
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Next Time
Dullalala!!
Anarchy
The girl ran.
On and on, she ran.
To escape the shadows that followed...
To escape the cruel truth she had learned...
Next time:
Anarchy.