I'm Ryuugamine Mikado.
Whoa!
Is it really you, Kida-kun?!
There aren't as many color gang members as before.
Most of them got arrested for starting a gang war in Saitama.
I'm Sonohara Anri.
Nice to meet you all.
Harima-san!
I'm sorry! I thought you were someone else!
If you pledge to be a bona fide Ikebukuronian,
you will overcome this ordeal!
I found...
my love!
I-I'm sorry!
Really!
I'll give it back! So please!
Please forgive me.
Sheesh!
I'm really pissed!
It's my fault, Selty.
It's all because I accepted such a stupid job.
The job itself was supposed to be quick.
But then that thing just appeared.
You are not human!
Monster! Monster!
You monster!
You heard voices from your wound?
They called me a monster!
How rude!
They could have at least called you a "devil woman" or something.
What the hell was that thing?
What do I do if it's an alien?!
Selty...
Am I supposed to laugh about this?
M-Monster!
Let's go!
Apparently, this city is made of jokes, coincidences, and whims.
This situation might be a result of God's whims, or maybe it's just one of his jokes.
I fell in love at first sight with 37 girls during the opening ceremony,
and even though I'm going home with the bespectacled girl that's in my top five,
because of some development that would put soap operas to shame...
the mood's ruined by some dumbass.
Screw this...
It was pretty hectic last time, right?
Y-Yeah.
This ain't going anywhere.
Dude, you really surprised me back then.
I didn't expect you to take the initiative.
Th-That's not true!
No way! Mikado!
But in the end, you saved me.
I wouldn't have wasted such an opportunity if I were in your shoes.
By now, we'd be in WGP talking so romantically about love...
So please go out with me!
Kida-kun!
Um... I—
Nah, you don't have to reply right now.
I'm waiting on a reply from seven other girls,
and I'm trying to make up my mind on who to date.
Sonohara-san, you don't have to take him seriously.
You'll just wear yourself out.
Plus he talks like a big playboy, but he's really just a peanut.
Even when he hits on girls—
Hey, Mikado!
This guy, known as Ryuugamine Mikado, is my best friend.
It's only been a couple of days since he came to Ikebukuro.
He's an honest, naïve guy with an unexpected stubborn side.
Thus, I just can't leave him alone.
And I'm stuck in a love triangle with this pure-hearted boy.
Is this what they call "youth"?
You two seem to get along pretty well.
Of course.
We're so close we're inseparable.
To explain this situation...
We have to go back to the opening ceremony.
I'm Yagiri Seiji.
Nice to meet you all.
Take your seat, Yagiri.
I won't.
I don't think I'll be able to come to school for a while.
Nah, perhaps I'll never come back.
I have to take care of something very important to me.
I can't deal with you people.
Bye.
H-Hey, Yagiri!
Wait!
Wait, I said!
I thought, "There are so many weirdos running around,"
Yagiri! Wait!
when Mikado told me about it.
Please wait!
That was literally the moment when I fell in love.
My heart gave a big ba-dump when I saw her cute smile.
Oh wait, she didn't smile.
Leave me alone!
Wait!
Hey.
Is something wrong?
And thus she claimed the top spot of my "girls I'm gonna make my girlfriend" list.
And today...
Hey, Sonohara.
Are you heading home?
Yes.
Say, Sonohara.
Is something bothering you?
You aren't in trouble, or getting bullied, are you?
No.
Come talk to me if something happens.
I'm fine.
Well, if you say so.
Oh yeah, Harima still hasn't come back?
You two were in the same class back then.
It wasn't easy to get you two in the same class here too.
Your junior high teacher, Saitou-sensei, told me to take good care of you.
So you don't have to be polite with me, okay?
Oh yeah, I'll give you a ride home.
Did you hear about it?
There was another slasher incident in Ikebukuro.
Whoa, Nasujima-sensei, is that sexual harassment I see there?
Wowzers! You even made the timid, pure, bespectacled class rep moan.
This is literally sexual harassment, isn't it?
Or with a Russian accent, "Sexy kharasho"?
Cut that out, Kida!
Sonohara, don't get the wrong idea and start silly rumors.
Does she look like such a frivolous girl?
Yeah, she doesn't.
Seriously, you have to tone your jokes down.
No worries. I'll be the one spreading the rumors.
I guess I was like a Champion of Justice.
Shit, that was so cool of me.
She's so gonna be head-over-heels for me.
Kida-kun?
Sonohara-san?
Nice fucking timing.
Sorry for the wait.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hey, you should really watch out.
Most of the rumors about Nasujima are just that,
but it's true that he went after a student:
A sophomore named Niekawa Haruna.
She transferred out during second semester last year.
People almost found out that she was dating Nasujima.
Are you serious?
It's unknown if she made the decision herself, if she was threatened by Nasujima,
or if the school forced her to transfer.
Well, if anything happens, Mikado and I will save you.
Right, Mikado?
Oh, yeah.
I still don't really get the whole story,
but I'll do anything to help you.
Silly.
You're supposed to say, "I'll make the impossible possible with the power of love."
Otherwise you're not a man.
Really?
That's an oxymoron.
It's just appropriate in that situation.
That aside, about the other day...
Those bullies went to the same junior high as you, right?
H-How did you know that?
Well, that's what it sounded like from your conversation.
In junior high, someone with authority was helping you,
but since that person's gone now, they started bullying you again.
Oh, what was it?
You still can't find your missing friend?
It's Harima Mika-san, right?
It's not that she's been absent,
but she never went home until the entrance ceremony.
Hey, isn't that something for the cops?
She texted me, and she also told her family.
It said, "I'm taking a little trip to relax. Please don't worry about me."
A trip to relax?
Did something happen?
Well...
Can you listen without getting shocked?
Everything in the past few days has made me immune to any kind of shock.
Harima-san...
is a stalker.
I see.
So the guy you were badgering with questions the other day...
He's the one being stalked—
No, rather, Mika-chan, who wanted to be loved by him but was rejected, took a trip to forget her bitter experience.
It's best to leave it to her family to handle that.
If things get worse, they'll call the police.
Were you two good friends?
What's up with that question?
Well, we were always together.
He's pretty sharp when it comes to certain things.
I'm really clumsy, and not sociable.
But it was always Mika-san that helped me out.
She went as far as going to the same school as I did,
and it felt very awkward for me.
Well...
"She didn't want to let go of you because you made her look better."
Even if you think that, you shouldn't say it out loud, Mikado-kun.
I know.
Know what?
That I was just being used by Mika-san to make herself look better.
But I was using her too.
It's easier to depend on someone else.
I didn't think I'd be able to live if I didn't.
But I don't think I need her anymore.
I got used to it.
I decided to be the class representative
just because she wanted to do it too.
I thought, "At least I can do it in her stead."
I thought, "I can surpass her if I become class rep."
I'm so despicable.
I think it's even more despicable to tell other people about this.
It sounds like you're asking for forgiveness.
Surpassing her is the right decision.
So, why don't you face it straight up?
E-Er...
You're right.
Thank you.
I really like this part of him.
Kida-kun!
That's so lame!
Oh, yeah?!
What? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yes, the strongest.
Are you a journalist?
What do you mean by "strongest"? It sounds so silly.
Well, the strongest is the guy on the black bike.
Yeah, I've heard of him.
The headless one, right?
You've got to be kidding me!
Oh, and then there's the slasher.
Yeah, him.
But the strongest in this city would be the Dollars.
Dollars?
Yes, Dollars!
My home's the other way.
Thanks for today.
See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye, Anri-chan!
I've been thinking...
I think Yagiri-kun and Mika are together.
The victim and the stalker?
Like Yagiri-kun has been kidnapped by his stalker.
That makes sense.
Searching for someone, eh?
What should we do?
Forget about it.
She said it was fine, right?
I guess it's impossible to find them without the help of an organization or something like that.
Like the Dollars.
Mikado... You aren't thinking about joining them, are you?
Of course not.
Seriously, forget about it.
The foolishness of youth makes people join color gangs,
and then they end up regretting it.
Yeah, but we're still young.
I was really depressed before Mikado came here.
I can be this cheerful thanks to a lot of people.
Including Mikado.
He was innocent when he came here, so the heated atmosphere of this city is getting to him.
It pains me to see him acting so cautiously.
Well, I could splash some water on him,
but when I see the glimmer in his eyes, I just can't do it.
That's why I'm trying to spend as much time as I can with him.
If I could, I'd do anything to prevent him from getting near the dark side of this city.
I too...
Bang.
...swore never to go back there again.
Is someone spamming the channel with crap?
Sounds like an alien.
Maybe he's laughing.
So scary...
I mean the "haha hahas."
No, I'm not saying aliens are scary.
Tsumiuta?
Or Zaika?
"Wealth"?
I'll take a look at it later.
Anyway, you've got a job, Selty.
It's from Shiki-san of the Awakusu Group again.
It's not a very pleasant job though.
Will you do it?
Another delivery?
Yeah.
Well, you have to get the stolen goods back first though.
I have no idea what the goods are.
I think it's better not to know.
I know.
So, about the goods...
The thief's on the run.
We have an idea on his location, so we should be able to corner him easily.
Roger.
The slasher has been quite active lately, so be careful.
The slasher?
Yeah, dude.
Looks like he appeared again.
He just slashes people without killing them.
Well, you can't call him the strongest then.
The strongest in this city would be...
Simon from Russia Sushi.
What about the informant that moved to Shinjuku?
Orihara Izaya.
Then it has to be that guy...
Heiwajima Shizuo!
The strongest color gang?
Dude, it's the Dollars.
They don't have a color.
Those peeps in yellow were the big shots until last year though.
Yellow?
Yeah, the Yellow Napkins.
But I heard that they fought the Blue Squares last year, and they wrecked each other.
Dude, I heard they revived recently.
Please don't stop the orders from comin'!
Engawa and scallops are really cheap!
Speaking of which, haven't they stuck out too much recently?
Who?
The yellow guys?
Oh, so you noticed them.
By yellow, you don't happen to mean...
Yellow Snapkins!
You mean "Yellow Napkins."
Yep, yep, them.
That was Hermes, right?
No, they were annihilated in the fight with the Blue Squares.
Oh, right.
I heard their boss went AWOL.
Welcome!
Could you tell me about the Dollars?
One of my friends wants to join them, and I want to stop him.
Why are you asking us?
There's no one else I can ask.
He can't just go to Orihara Izaya obviously.
We don't know that much about them either,
but we'll tell you everything we know.
Sometimes I feel like I'm getting sucked in by this town.
But Mikado, I won't let you go to that side.
Mikado?!
Sorry.
That won't work, bro.
We're Yellow Napkins, ya see?
Yagiri-kun!
Huh?
That's not Harima Mika.
I don't know who you are, but please don't get in the way of our elopement of love.
Elopement of what?
Shall we go?
So, who was that?
Kida-kun.
Are you guys really from the Yellow Napkins?
Isn't that obvious, Sherlock?
I'm asking because I don't know.
You fucking...
K-Kida-kun!
Oh man, Mikado-kun... Why are you here?
M-Monster!
Let's go!
Sheesh dude, stop worrying me.
That's my line.
Perhaps I'm the one relying on him in the end.
Yeah.
Ever since Mikado came here, I've felt that my bravado is actually becoming more than just show.
Maybe this time I can meet her without running away.
Come in.
That's what I really think.
I didn't think you'd come,
Izaya-san.
Hey.
How's he doing?
He visits me from time to time.
He was just here.
I'm home.
Haruna, did you eat already?
Haruna.
Oh, I blacklisted that spammer.
Looks like it's gonna be peaceful here.
I hope so.
Oh yeah. I heard that some of the Yellow Napkins
got their asses kicked by the slasher yesterday.
Who are the Yellow Napkins?
I wonder if the slasher is a henchman of the Dollars?
What? Really?!
Looks like this might turn into a war.
Things that happen in this city might seem unrelated at first glance,
but I'm sure there's a link somewhere.
Maybe this city holds a distorted reality that's beyond our ability to fathom.
However...
Good morning!
G-Good morning, Sonohara-san.
Good morning.
I just realized this,
but I really like our relationship the way it is now.
One day I'll connect the dots,
and unveil the picture that's currently invisible to us.
I believe that our relationship will stay the same.
Dollars?
Well, I can't say much about them.
Anyway, let me fill you in about the details of the now-legendary Kaztano Incident.
Next time: On the Move.
However, do not call me "Dotachin."