You little!
Oh poop!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
I know where this is going!
Okay, no time for that right now!
That was way too close.
Why does it make me feel so warm inside?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Can we really go on like this?
What are you saying?
I believe she has been exposed to too much of the Precure's sacred light,
corroding the darkness within her.
Farewell, Sasorina...
The Flower of Your Heart is a Desert Bloom!
You're quitting as president of the student council?!
Yeah.
My term comes to an end this month,
and I know I'm going to need to dedicate
more time to fighting the Desert Apostles.
Well, yeah, but...
I intend to not seek reelection so I can focus on being a Precure.
Now hold on just a sec!
Ever since you became president, Itsuki,
the school's been a much nicer place to be!
And that's all thanks to you!
Thank you for that.
But my mind is made up.
I think I'm going to suggest my current vice president, Satou, run for the post.
Satou?
Student Council Office
Finally...
my time has come!
We are entering the age...
Student Council President
of me!
Man, I could get used to this!
Student Council President
Once I become president of the student council...
President Satou, these are for you.
Hey! Wait your turn!
Who do you think you are?
We all have to share President Satou!
All the girls in the school will be enamored with me.
I'll be able to take my pick!
President!
Satou,
I really hope that's not the actual
reason you're running for president.
No, um, I was just...
I'm sorry you had to see that.
The role of president requires you work
tirelessly for the benefit of all of our students.
I-I'm so sorry!
Professor Sabark,
I ask that you remove Sasorina from the line of duty, and take her to the Planet Fortress to recuperate!
I'm sure you're aware, Professor, but I fear she does not have the will left to partake in our struggle.
Not so fast, you two!
What are you saying here?! Do you really think I can't handle this?!
Professor Sabark, send me out there, please!
I know I can defeat those damn Precure if I try!
What?
You can't. Not like this.
Don't you dare look down on me!
Professor Sabark, please let me handle this! I beg you!
Very well.
You have my blessing.
But I shall not accept any further failures.
I don't intend to fail.
I'll show you just how strong I can be!
Sasorina.
You'll need these.
With three times the dark power, you
might just be able to beat the Precure.
But your body won't take the strain for long.
You'll have to make it quick.
Don't expect me to thank you.
Oh god, why did she have to walk in then?!
What do we have here?
The Flower of your Heart is wilting quite nicely, boy.
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Student Council Office
I'll go check the classrooms!
You two get out while you can!
Itsuki!
President!
Calm down, it's okay. Let's get out of here!
Okay!
Everybody leave the school grounds and meet up at the park!
Ms. Tsurusaki!
Can you get her to safety for me?
Myoudouin!
Ow...
You okay?
Oh, president!
I'm going to go look for Myoudouin!
Ms. Tsurusaki!
Itsuki!
Are you two all right?
Yeah.
Schoooooooooool!
It's Satou!
Everyone run!
Come on, you three!
We have a school to protect!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Schoooool!
Precure Body Punch!
There you are, Precure!
You again?!
Hmph! Don't worry, you won't be around to see me again!
This triple-powered Dark Bracelet will soon see to that!
Be on your guard.
She's clearly not her usual self.
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
It's time you saw what the Desert Apostles can really do!
Unite!
This is the power of three Dark Bracelets!
Enough to defeat you Precure for good!
Double Body Punch!
Precure Silver Forte Wave!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
With all this power, I'm invincible!
But that's not all I can do!
Look how much power three Dark Bracelets provide!
She might just be able to do this.
Hand over your transformation
devices, or I'll stomp you all flat!
Did you hear me?! Do it!
No! We won't give up!
Sasorina, we're going to make you give Satou his heart back!
You still want to fight me?!
Who cares about the Flowers of their Hearts?! Who cares about you Precure?!
It's all pathetic!
Damn you, Precure!
Let's finish this.
What?
Let's use the HeartCatch Mirage and put an end to her suffering!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
I can't lose...
Not like this... I'm a commander of the Desert Apostles!
We have to stop them!
This fight is beyond her now.
It's better this way.
You're sounding as bad as me.
Sasorina, you did yourself proud.
Kumojacky...
Kobraja...
Thank you.
A dogtooth violet.
In the language of flowers, it means both
"to suffer through sadness" and "jealousy."
You shall be made to pay for this!
We were wrong to treat you so lightly.
Next time we meet, your ends are certain!
Peaks Medical Clinic
I feel like I've been living a terrible dream.
Man...
We really gotta do this?
Do we have to?
Satou's working so hard for the school!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Sasorina was crying as she died, wasn't she?
I suppose that means the Desert Apostles have hearts too.
I bet Kumojacky and Kobraja are gonna be even harder to beat.
But that doesn't mean we're going to let them beat us!
Right! We're winning this!
All right then!
Back to work!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
It'sh time for us fairies to show our shtuff!
Precure! Open My Heart!
Our noble fairy souls give rise to the power of justice!
Take this! Beam!
You got me!
Now, purify her!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Fairies Transform?!
We're Putting on a Precure Show!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!