Meet Mitsuki Koyama, 12 years old.
Her dream is to become a singer.
But, poor thing,
she only has one year to live.
We're a couple of Death Spirits
and we were sent to make sure
her destiny doesn't change.
But somehow we ended up
turning her older and
helped her win an audition!
Do you think that counts as
changing her destiny?
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
That girl passed the audition
because of you, Takuto!
Wow, I was surprised too.
I didn't think she'd pass.
Don't talk as if it's
someone else's problem!
Hey, stop yelling, Meroko.
You haven't forgotten
our goal, have you?
It's to not let her live beyond
her remaining one-year life span, right?
Exactly!
Then there's no relationship
between that and whether or not
she passes the audition.
Oh, that's right!
No, it's not!
It'll be easier if
she stays at home.
It'll be a pain if she becomes
a singer and goes out everywhere!
After all, we used our powers to turn
that human into a sixteen-year-old,
so a simple letter of apology won't do!
What's so funny?
Nothing, just thinking about how
you two get along so well.
- What?
- D-Does it look that way?
Well...that's because...
We are the Death Spirits
who can even quiet crying children!
Green Onion Ramen!
Huh?
Thank you very much.
Huh? Yeah...don't mention it.
By the way, that song
you sang at the audition...
What's the name of it?
That was a song my father,
who was a musician, wrote.
I see...
Is something the matter?
Well, I recall hearing it somewhere,
but maybe not...
Huh?
Hey little chest!
Don't get carried away just
because you passed an audition.
W-When I'm like this I look fine!
Really, looking like that?
Meroko!
Stop trying to start an argument!
Oh, but I can't go home like this,
so please turn me back
to my previous self.
Yeah, of course.
Oh.
Amazing, I'm back to
my previous self.
Your chest is back too.
P-Please don't look.
C'mon prude...
Hey...
Huh?
You want to become
a singer that much?
Yup...it's a promise.
A promise?
A promise to Eichi.
Eichi?
Just who is this Eichi guy?!
Your boyfriend?
Is he?!
H-He's not my boyfriend!
Not yet.
So he's the man of your dreams?
Yeah...
Until two years ago,
I was in an orphanage.
Until my grandmother
came to get me,
Eichi was there too.
He shared his true feelings with me,
but before I could give him a proper answer,
he moved to America
because the family that adopted him
needed to move there.
No! No!
Don't go, Eichi.
Don't cry, Mitsuki.
America isn't that far away.
But...
Hey, make me a promise.
That when we meet next,
we'll be closer to
our dreams than we are now.
Me an astronomer...
You a singer...
Mitsuki...
I like you.
Even when I'm away from you...
when I look up at the sky,
I'll look for the moon.
That's why you need to shine brighter...
so I can find you right away.
Shine brighter and brighter...
Nothing since then?
What do you mean
nothing since?
You haven't communicated since then?
There's email,
there's international phone calls.
Well, I don't know where he is.
Oh...
But if I become a singer
and become famous,
my name might even
be known in America.
And if that happens,
Eichi will probably...
he'll probably notice me.
You're single minded.
Well perhaps I'm being
too optimistic?
What? What's with
the scary face, Takuto?
How scary!
What's up with you?
I thought you genuinely
wanted to become a singer.
But it's for a guy!
Huh?
It's not genuine!
You can't become a good singer
with such a fake motive.
You should stop singing right away!
Wh-Why are you saying such things?
That's right! It's alright that
she's doing it for a guy.
No, that's not!
What?
I'll do my best to sing.
Really! No matter how hard you try
the fakeness that permeates
your efforts will come spilling out!
That's cruel...
My desire to be a singer
is not fake!
That's right!
What's fake about it?!
What's genuine about
"doing it for a guy"?!
In the first place,
there's something wrong about
not contacting you for two years!
You've been dumped, Mitsuki.
He's probably got a girl over there
and he's having fun!
E-Eichi wouldn't do such a thing!
How do you know that?
Because it's Eichi, that's why!
What? That's ridiculous!
Hey, that's enough, Takuto!
In any case, I'll never help
someone like you again.
Someone who takes
singing so lightly!
H-Hold on Takuto!
Takuto!
I said Takuto!
Really, what's he angry about?!
What kind of person obstructs fate?
"A person whose fate is obstructed..."
"...usually involves a person who is loved."
This Eichi guy, we really need
to keep an eye on him.
What in the world
are you doing?
I didn't say no to
the audition to be mean.
I stopped you because...
I determined it would be impossible
in your present condition, Mitsuki.
I'm sorry.
But now you understand?
Huh?
That you won't be able
to sing for awhile.
Oh, no, I passed!
Passed?
What should I do?
Should I tell the doctor
what really happened?
But will he believe the part
about the transformation?
Also the part about the Death Spirits?
What do you mean by pass?!
Did you pass the audition by chance?
W-Well...
Don't say it!
He won't believe you one bit!
Umm... It's modeling.
Oh, modeling.
Well, I guess modeling is alright.
But definitely don't over do it.
Y-Yes.
By the way, what did you do
about the resumé?
Did you put your grandmother's name
in the guardian column?
W-Well...actually...
Did you perhaps use my name?
I-I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Let's keep it a secret from
your grandmother too.
A-Are you sure?
Yeah, I understand your feelings, Mitsuki.
It's for Eichi's sake, right?
Yes.
You shouldn't leave the house
without telling me!
On top of that,
having the doctor take you to
the amusement park!
There's a limit to shamelessness!
The amusement park?
So that's how you explained it.
Thank you, Doctor!
Do you understand?
I'm sorry!
If you do it again,
there'll be no excuses!
Yes...
That's all.
You're excused.
Yes.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
What is that?!
What is it?!
Th-This...
Well...well...
I got it in a game.
I see.
E-Excuse me...
What a pesky old hag.
I thought, "yikes, she might
tell you to go throw me away."
But now you're one step
closer to your dream.
Yup.
By the way, what's Eichi like?
If you have a photo, show me.
Come on, come on.
Well...
Y-Yeah...
Wow!
He's pretty handsome,
how old is he?
He's six years older than me,
so he's eighteen now.
So this picture is
when Eichi was sixteen...
How cute.
There's something wrong about
not contacting you for two years!
You've been dumped,
Mitsuki.
Eichi wouldn't...
Eichi wouldn't do such a thing.
So this is where you've been.
Leave me alone.
Then there's nowhere for me to go.
What?
It seems she wants to be alone too...
It was difficult for me to stay there...
Eichi...
It's your fault, Takuto!
What?!
She's depressed because you said
"you've been dumped"!
Well it's natural to think that!
Am I wrong?!
In the first place,
it's weird to keep thinking about
a guy who's dumped you!
- It is weird.
- Right?
There's no way
the Takuto from the past
would have used
his powers carelessly.
Huh?
Have you fallen for her?
Idiot! That would never happen!
I-I did it as my duty!
Besides, I said "you've been dumped"
because, in general...
- long distance relationships don't work out.
- There is something weird going on.
- You know, they gradually...
- Takuto is mine!
Alright, go ahead.
Fortune telling?
Yup, I'll read your fortune
for the day.
Now, pick one card.
Okay!
Well...
Let's see.
That's great!
Today's your lucky day!
That's lucky?!
It's way lucky!
And your lucky word is...
"shopping."
Something good is bound to happen.
Alright, let's go out!
Yup!
Grandma's out today too...
Oh, but I need to ask Ms. Tanaka...
M-Mitsuki, did you need something?
I'd like to go shopping but...
Oh, you need your grandmother's...
I wonder what she'd say if
she found out
you listen to music behind her back.
Huh?!
She might get mad at you.
Let's go.
Where's she going?
I guess I should leave it to
Meroko since she's with her.
It's almost that time, Mitsuki,
so can you wait at the usual place?
Yes, I understand.
So...so, please wait for just a minute.
Hey, hey!
There's somewhere I'd like to go too.
Oh, I'll be awhile,
so can you wait outside?
Alright.
Death Spirits go to
the bathroom too.
She's gone.
There's a reason I had to
have her come out...
Now! Mero-Mero Change!
It's mine!
Oh!
I wonder what that
"something good" will be...
Oh...
Is that?
It's been a while, Mitsuki.
Huh?
Eichi?
Yup.
That's...
I-It can't be...
Of course it can.
Actually, it's not.
If your wish to see Eichi is fulfilled...
you won't need to become a singer.
And also...
Takuto will give up on you because
your true desire has appeared.
That's why...
I-I'm having a dream, aren't I?
It's not a dream.
While I was in America...
not a day went by that
I didn't think of you.
That's why when I heard
you'd become a singer,
I rushed back here to Japan.
Huh? Who'd you hear that from?
Wh-Who...
I-I know someone at
the record company, so...
What a total coincidence!
Not a coincidence so much as...
...fate.
Fate.
By the way, did your voice
sound like that before?
M-My voice may have changed
from living in America.
You know,
America is such a huge place.
Eichi, you're funny.
Th-Think so?
Oh!
W-What next?
I need to apologize to you for something.
I had doubts about you, Eichi.
Well...I thought you had
forgotten about me.
What?
- Is that all?
- I'm sorry!
Mitsuki...
Can you still like me as I am?
O-Of course.
That's great...
I wasn't able to answer you
properly back then.
But now...
I can also say that.
W-Wha—?
I lik—
I-I'm sorry!
Huh? Eichi.
Where are you going?
Mr. Death Spirit...
That's not Eichi, it's Meroko.
What? No way.
It's true.
Death Spirits are able to transform.
Is that...so?
That's right.
Huh?
There's no way Eichi would be here.
Thanks for waiting.
What's the matter, Mitsuki?
It's nothing.
You look pale.
Alright, let's go...
That was cruel!
How could you do such a thing?
I thought it was a good idea.
How could it be a good idea?
You toyed with something
that a person was serious about,
you toyed with
a person's genuine feelings!
I'm sorry!
An apology isn't enough!
What?
Huh?
You said "genuine."
Didn't you say "fake" before?
Huh? Did I say that?
You did!
You said, "What's genuine about
doing it for a guy."
Th-That was...
in reference to the motive
for becoming a singer.
This and that are two separate things.
Are they?
What I did was terrible.
But what about you who used the words
"you've been dumped"
without even knowing about Eichi.
What about that, huh?
Can you say you haven't
hurt her feelings?
Look...
"You've been dumped"
was merely my opinion...
Or rather...
just one possibility...
No... it's...
Sorry.
No, I'm to blame too.
What?
If I really believed in Eichi,
nothing anyone says should
bother me.
That's why I won't waver anymore!
I like Eichi!
But I like singing almost as much...
If I like both,
I need to believe in both,
in Eichi and in singing!
If not, my dreams won't come true!
There's no way
these feelings are fake!
I guess there's no way around it.
Go as far as you can with it.
I'll help you with
your dream for one year.
Are you sure?!
Oh!
My blood is effective as long as
I don't extinguish it.
I'll transform you anytime.
When I'm not near,
blow on this whistle and call me.
I'll rush over...
Thank you, Mr. Death Spirit!
Stop calling me "Mr. Death Spirit."
Call me "Takuto"!
OK, thank you, Takuto.
Don't mention it...
Could what I did
have had an opposite effect?
Oh, it's Miss Rabbit!
I wanted to thank you, Miss Rabbit.
Thank me?
Yup.
Because it really was
my lucky day.
Transforming yourself into Eichi
was to give me courage, right?
I'm really sorry!
Huh?
Why is Miss Rabbit apologizing?
Who knows?
I'm sorry!
I won't ever do it again.
Eichi...
I passed the audition.
I will definitely come to see you, Eichi.
Oh no! Oh no! Takuto!
I heard a manager is coming
to visit Mitsuki!
Impossible! That means—
That's right.
But, remember how Dr. Wakaoji is
supposed to be Mitsuki's guardian?
Wait a minute.
He only knows Mitsuki as
a 12-year-old,
and the manager is gonna be expecting
to meet 16-year-old Mitsuki.
What are we gonna do, Takuto?
Darn it!
It's all so complicated.
How are we gonna to keep
everybody fooled?
Next time on Full Moon:
"Along Came the Manager"
- Look forward to it!