Ah, Cherry...
Good morning...
Good morning.
Geez...
Good morning!
Everyone's coming over today,
so be a good girl, okay?
Hello.
Yes.
Hello, Miyuki-san.
I baked some cookies yesterday.
I thought I'd bring some over for you to try, Minami-san.
Hello, Cherry-chan.
Would you like to try one too, Cherry-chan?
H-Hey, Cherry!
What are you doing?
Well, dogs sometimes tend to do that.
Ah...
Would it be all right if I gave her a cookie?
Ah, yes.
I'm sure she would be happy to have one.
Here.
She went to bury it.
She didn't eat it, did she?
Ah, it's Cherry-chan!
Her nose is all black!
Huh, that's strange...
Where did my cell phone go...
Cherry-chan...
You didn't bury it, did you?
C'mon...
Keep on looking around.
R-Right!
You sure have a dirty face...
You always seem to have it so easy...
Meanwhile, Tsukasa loses her phone...
Konata is way too late,
and didn't even bother to call us, as usual.
Ah, geez!
No, because I am~
A Scorpio woman~
I'll laugh heartily~
Until I'm satisfied~
Hello!
Hello, Cherry!
Your paws are so hard...
Not comforting at all!
These paws aren't as squishy as they are in manga.
I'm in despair!!
Hm?
Hmm...
No reaction whatsoever.
Cherry, stupid dog.
There are times when she won't wake up, even if you call her.
Also, she's not stupid.
Cherry, you stupid dog.
Cherry, you lazy bum.
L-Lazy bum?
Cherry...
You fat dog.
Drooling dog.
Stupid dog.
Lazy bum.
Oh!
At least she's aware.
A stupid dog like yourself that sleeps all day deserves to be called a lazy bum!
Whenever I try, no matter what I do, she never wakes up.
Ah, she's sleeping right here.
Hello.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Hello~
Hello.
You're such a cute and quiet dog, aren't you?
Thank you, thank you.
Cherry-chan, you're so cute!
What are you doing?
Cherry-chan was being so quiet...
So I couldn't resist...
But to have a huge dog like this lying in the hallway...
This house sure is easygoing.
Well, she's so quiet.
Just looking at her makes me feel at ease.
I have a dog at home too, so I totally know what you mean.
Anyway, didn't you need to use the restroom?
Oh, right!
Excuse me for a bit.
Ah...
So relaxing.
Wha-!?
You're so quiet around the others...
Why are you suddenly reacting to me?
Slowly...
Oh...
You're a good girl today, aren't you?
Okay, shake.
Not gonna do it, huh?
You're Minami-chan's dog, so I thought you would be a bit smarter...
Oh, I know!
Wait, wait!
Sit, girl!
Sit!
What an honest dog...
Well, then...
Shake!
H-Hey!
Lay off!
Please stop...
Here.
I don't understand big dogs at all...
What the-!?
D-Don't spit it out!
Minami, dinner time!
Mom, Cherry's not eating her dinner.
Seems like it...
I even put in some of the canned food you got for her.
But she still won't eat it...
I thought she liked that stuff.
Cherry...
Cheer up.
We're all worried about you.
What happened to your face?
What were you digging up?
Oh, I get it...
You were eating the stuff you buried?
That's fine...
As long as you're happy, Cherry...
That's all I need.
Still, that was pretty sudden.
Druid
Chat Window
Party
Shout
Battle
General
Why did you start playing online games, Hiiragi?
Eh?
Sensei, believe it or not, Kagami is a big fan of the artist who worked on the anime tie-in for this game.
Seriously?
So you've finally given in to the dark side, huh?
Konata!
Druid
Chat Window
Don't say unnecessary things!
Soldier
Chat Window
Huh?
But if you want to copy the anime, then aren't the Hiiragi sisters a mis-casting?
It should be the reverse.
Ouch!
Druid
Konata!
Kagami, thx!
Nothing to it.
Mage
Shout
Battle
Sensei...
For the sake of our own survival, swapping them would be a fatal mistake.
I see what you mean...
I feel a lot safer this way.
Druid
Shout
Battle
Hey, Konata...
I have a feeling that the jobs we have in the game,
and the ones that are in the anime, are different...
Oh, those are higher level jobs.
We have to transfer professions from our current jobs to get those.
How do you switch jobs?
Coming soon.
Chat Window
Huh?
Well, it happens all the time.
The anime and game are meant to progress concurrently,
but once the anime finishes airing, it's all "coming soon".
Chat Window
Mage
But when you're in a game world like this, you start getting immersed.
And you really do get reminded of those game-based anime.
Battle
Oh yeah, like the one they set up to look like an online game but was actually offline.
I wonder why they didn't release that online.
I honestly believed that it was an online game and initially went looking for it all over the place.
Mage
That does seem to happen often.
Tsukasa, just hit ENTER.
Ah.
Aah, aah...
Yay, I can finally talk!
Battle
I was wondering why you weren't talking...
Chat Window
If you don't hit the ENTER key, you won't talk.
Scout
Battle
Chat Window
Man, it's so nice forming parties with people you know.
You're absolutely right.
Pick-up groups are hit-or-miss, so it's a gamble every time.
What do you guys usually do, Kona-chan?
Just start spamming for groups, or form one myself...
Then again, there are lots of times when no one picks me up...
If you miss the prime time for groups, then you end up playing solo that night.
'Cause no one ever wants to be the party leader.
And everyone just looks for groups.
Not to mention there are lots of times where there are too many of the same class.
And if you form a group in a rush, you could end up wasting even more time wiping.
I have absolutely no idea what you're talking about!
Mage
Battle
Chat Window
Tsukasa's spells never do much damage, do they?
That's weird...
Mages are supposed to be strong enough to solo-farm...
Where are you putting your stats?
Stats?
Eh!?
B-But normally in games, when you level up, you just automatically learn spells...
So I thought this was just like that...
Indeed...
Soldier
Here it is!
Now that I'm Level 10, I can attack twice!
If I keep leveling up, I wonder if I can pull off three attacks...
Hmmm...
What is this feeling of déjà vu...
It feels very much like I'm playing a Lodoss tabletalk RPG...
More nonsense...
Scout
This game's got a lot of emotes.
Sensei, we should make a victory pose for our party!
Soldier
Was this really necessary?
Yes it was, Kagami, especially because we're online!
This floor has 3 enemies and a hidden treasure.
For this boss, I'll pull him away and kite him, so you guys hit him with spells from behind.
He's weak to fire, so make sure you take advantage of that.
If you talk to that guy over there, he'll give you a quest.
Next, you just talk to the old man by the exit and you'll get some cash.
Mage
Kona-chan, you know so much.
Lately, all that information is floating around on the net.
There are some amazing sites that'll have a complete walkthrough uploaded the same day.
It's almost as though they're getting paid for it.
If only they could redirect all that energy into fueling society,
and make themselves useful...
Scout
With this invincible Pizza-La Shield, there's nothing to fear!
P-Pizza-La?
It's an in-game promotional item.
If you order a pizza, you can get such special items.
Why do I feel like you're falling into their trap?
Man...
Even though I'm aware of it, I still do it for the same reason.
You too!?
Eh?
A trip?
We're going to the hot springs as a family.
So I don't think we'll be on during the entire Golden Week.
Oh, I'm going somewhere with Yuu-chan too.
I hope it won't be too crowded.
Once GW is over...
Scout
Party
Shout
Battle
General
Chat Window
Battle
Sensei...
Don't tell me...
And so, what did this kid do after that?
This is the right answer.
Yes, Mayumi-chan.
All right, we're off to go see the ball.
Watch over the house, okay?
Okay.
Kagami, are you really not going to go?
Yeah, it's too much trouble anyway.
Are you sure?
You're going to miss out on this chance.
I'm starting to get a bit nervous.
Tsukasa, why don't you try participating?
Eh?
T-That's impossible!
We're off.
Make sure to lock up, okay?
Okay, okay.
Take care.
Still, this wife is pretty scary.
Do you think so?
Something like this is normal, right?
She didn't think so at all!
I shall make that wish of yours come true!
Where did you come from?
And what's with that get-up?
Now, now...
By the way, my current designation is mage.
What do you mean, "designation"?
Oh, is that so...
Your evil stepmother and sisters are picking on you, huh?
Huh?
What's this?
You want to go to the ball too?
No, I said nothing of the sort.
In other words...
You're the Fairy Godmother, and I'm Cinderella...
And thus, I must now get on a carriage and go attend the ball?
That's correct!
Which is why...
That's not even a carriage!
Don't worry about the details, Kagami.
Okay, let's head out!
Kagami, you get on as well.
No.
Geez...
Do you really want to have a carriage that much?
No!
I don't even know what the heck you're talking about...
And I never intended to go to the ball in the first place.
Now, now...
Don't talk like you know it all.
Anyway...
I'm not going, got it?
For sure?
For sure.
No matter what?
Enough!
*Sadness*
Geez...
What was she thinking?
Ah!
I forgot to have her turn that back to normal.
Whoa!
A-An earthquake?
W-What the heck is this!
Oh, Kagami...
I wouldn't go outside right now if I were you.
Is this your doing?
Yup.
Stop it already!
But you refused to leave the house...
I told you that I don't want to go, didn't I?
Then I'll just go to the dance hall like this.
Okay, fine!
I'll go, now stop all of this!
Aren't you looking forward to the ball, Kagami?
Not at all.
I bet the truth is you're really happy.
You tsundere, you.
Stop calling me a tsundere!
Besides, why is a fairy godmother such as yourself coming along as well?
Oh, yeah...
We should take this opportunity to get you all dressed up.
Hey, are you even listening to me?
Here.
I guess this is the default selection.
Hey, this isn't something you'd wear to a ball!
No, no...
I think you're more than qualified for that type of niche, Kagami.
What're you talking about?
Anyway, change my clothes back!
Huh, after I went through all the trouble?
I never asked you to!
Change it back right now!
Okay...
You didn't fix anything!
I guess you could call this another type of "default".
Besides, this is your usual cosplay.
Don't call it cosplay!
Somebody's gonna get hurt real soon...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
I'll do it right this time.
Ah.
It fell off.
Huh?
Sorry, but it looks like I can't change your clothes back to normal.
We've arrived!
Fighter's Ball In Saitama: Love is tough and endless
How about this?
Winner, Kuroi Nanako!
All right!
Today, I will escape from my life as a bachelorette!
You just wait for me, Prince Misao!
Indeed!
Win, win, and keep on winning!
Whoever wins this competition...
...will be my bride!
They're really getting into it...
Whatever, I don't care.
Oh, Hiiragi-chan!
I knew you would come after all!
*Love*
Be quiet.
Don't touch me.
Did you dress up like this just for me?
No.
Hiiragi, you're participating too, right?
Not a chance.
C'mon, just participate.
I'll fix all your matches.
Then why even have a competition?
First of all, I don't want to participate...
And second of all, I don't want to become your bride!
What's this, Hiiragi...
You're being pretty cold...
Don't worry, Prince, this is just her 'tsun' side.
Oh, which means deep down...!
No!
Geez...
I knew this was going to happen, which is why I didn't want to go!
Anyway, I'm going home now.
Eh?
You're leaving already?
When the clock strikes midnight, all the magic will be undone anyway, right?
If I don't leave now, the car will disappear.
How did she know?
Who cares, who cares!?
Let's play!
It's time for the fight predictions!
Are you a little kid?
Hey, Konata.
The house is still displaced!
Can't you move it back to its original location?
I fixed the Starring Inferno, so everything should be okay!
Why do I not feel reassured?
Is it really okay!?
Eh?
I guess time's up.
No way!
It's already past midnight?
What about the house?
I guess it'll have to stay like this.
Stay like this?
Can't you do something with your magic?
Actually, I was also on the receiving end of a magic spell...
Which is why I can't do anything past 12 AM.
What do you mean you can't...
Oh, right...
I just remembered a spell to reset everything.
Really!?
Then why didn't you say that earlier!
Well, you have to say this one, not me.
Then tell me already!
It's...
Do I really have to say that?
Yup.
Really loud, too.
Really loud?
Yup.
Ugh...
Things won't return to normal if you don't.
Fine, then.
I want to ****** with Konata.
Don't worry, Onee-chan.
I won't say a word.
No!
It's not what you think!
Oh yeah, I should go mail Kona-chan.
T-Tsukasa, listen!
Um, you have it totally wrong!
It was against my will...
What I mean is that she totally...
Here!
You did it!
That was amazing, Hiiragi-chan.
It was just luck, I swear.
There's no way I could hit that...
Hiiragi's little sister.
Don't give up.
Kusakabe-san.
Do you want to live in Hiiragi's shadow forever?
But...
No buts!
Today's your big chance to show your sister up!
Muster up some courage and prove to your sister that you can do it too!
O-Okay.
We'll show 'em the true power of a supporting character!
I-I'll do my best!
Oh, what a nostalgic scene...
There!
All right!
Here!
And that's how it's done!
I was so close...
Not bad, Kusakabe!
Here it goes...
Super Ultra Miraculous Eccentric Special...
...Serve!
An underhand serve!?
Leave it to me!
Nice receive!
Here!
Not bad...
Not bad at all...
Misakichi, Tsukasa.
We're gonna do a Jet Stream Attack on the attacker!
Roger!
By the way, what's a Jet Stream Attack?
Ah, you're not supposed to say that!
What are you guys doing?
Now the plan won't work!
Take this!
Have that!
Yes!
Eh?
Tsukasa!
Little Sister!
Something like that is impossible...
However...
Even when it's tough~
The tears had fallen.
After all, she's just a girl!
What's that?
Eh!?
You don't know it?
It's common knowledge for the Japanese!
You're the only one who feels that way.
Little Sister...
There's no point in sulking there.
You're gonna beat down Hiiragi today, right?
I...
I've always been relying on Onee-chan...
Yeah...
I'm sorry.
I'll do everything I can!
I got it!
Good job, Little Sister!
Guu~
One more point,
and our team will...
...win.
Let's do this!
We won't lose, Hiiragi!
I won't let it...
...end like this!
Here!
*Spin*
*Stop*
Just call me the Witch of Kasukabe.
There!
Go for it, Little Sister!
Hit it with everything you've got!
All right!
Ow, it hurts as if I just smacked into something.
We did it!
You really shined today, Hiiragi-san.
Eh, really?
Nothing less from Hiiragi-san.
Thanks.
That was amazing!
It was.
Darn it...
I suppose the supporting characters are never meant to win...
I still can't match Onee-chan.
But...
Someday, surely...
Heaven has forsaken us!
Hey, let's go.
Yeah...
I was just trying to get into the mood.
Stop messing around.
Come on.
This is a story that happened during a summer camping trip for our school.
We had decided to take a hike and were in the midst of our orienteering course.
Somehow, our group ended up lost.
How did this happen?
It's because you forgot the map and compass in the bus!
Besides, why did we have to go this way?
This way.
Well, I suddenly had the urge to climb a mountain.
And why is that?
Why, you ask...
Because the mountain's there.
Now now, Onee-chan.
How about we start by checking our cell phones?
As expected, out of range.
Me too.
I got nothing.
I guess we're doomed.
Ah, geez...
We should've been at the camping grounds by now.
That's true.
According to the schedule, we were supposed to start making dinner at 5 PM.
Reacted to the word "dinner", huh?
What about you, aren't you hungry?
Just a bit...
But I ate a ton of these on the bus.
Oh, again!
That one was me.
Anyway, how about we escape absolute starvation with these?
S-Starvation seems like a bit of an exaggeration...
But these...
One, two, three...
We're one short!
Um, may I?
This way, there will be six total.
If we give everyone a piece...
We can then break the last two into halves again...
How about that?
Yuki-chan, you're a genius!
Nothing less from our Miwiki-san!
Oh, it's nothing, really...
Now we won't have to starve to death.
Like I said, you're exaggerating.
However...
Izumi-san's words seemed like less and less of a joke,
and more of a reality.
I have a feeling we're completely and utterly lost.
Yes.
We've been walking the same area over and over.
Ah, if only we had a magnet.
I guess I need to smack you across the face with this.
Or perhaps I should shove it down your throat?
How scary!
Kagami, you're serious!
Um...
That looks like the Summer Triangle.
Therefore, I'm pretty sure this direction is east.
Wow Tsukasa, that's pretty amazing.
Tsukasa, did you like stars that much?
Um, this is the only one I know.
One of the big stars of the Summer Triangle is called Vega,
but it's also the Orihime Boshi.
We were born on Tanabata after all.
The Big Dipper also looks really beautiful.
Listen up, Kagami...
Until the day the Death Omen Star has fallen,
you must live your life to the fullest!
However, even if we do know the cardinal directions,
we still don't know how to get to the camp.
That's right.
Heaven has forsaken us!
Enough of that.
After screaming like that, I'm seriously starting to get hungry.
And whose fault is that!?
I never spoke of the idea openly,
but I was seriously starting to consider the possibility that we wouldn't make it back.
We're not descending...
Yes.
We've walked quite a bit, huh?
That's right.
I wonder if we lost our sense of direction inside the forest?
You may be right.
Story number ten.
In the silent forest...
You could hear the *pant* *pant* of their breathing...
What are you doing?
The Gathering of One Hundred Supernatural Tales.
If you tell a hundred ghost stories in a single night,
a real ghost will descend upon you!
Eh!?
When that happens...
You can feel a cold sensation on your cheek...
Stop messing around.
But a camp-out at night means ghost stories!
And after, love stories!
Huh?
D-Did I say something weird?
Story number eighteen.
I tried calling out, "Hey!"
But there was only silence...
Then all of a sudden-
Is that supposed to be the sound of you blowing out a candle?
Yeah.
In the Gathering of One Hundred Supernatural Tales,
you're supposed to blow out a candle each time you finish a story, right?
That's our Miwiki-san!
And then...
Huh?
What story was I on again?
Story number sixteen, probably?
You're going backwards!
Yes, this is Sazae-
Don't you mean Izumi!?
Where the heck are you guys right now?
Do you guys have any idea how worried we all were!?
What awaited our return to the camping grounds...
...were Kuroi-sensei's harsh words.
Which is why...
You must be extra careful from now on!
We're sorry...
You're hungry, right?
It's delicious.
Yeah, it really is.
Yep, yep.
Indeed...
The curry we had that day was truly delicious.
Perhaps, it was even the most delicious curry I had ever had.
And so something outrageous like that happened...
It was really a troublesome day.
Oh?
But you seemed to be enjoying yourself while you were telling the story.
Is that so?
Yes.
Very much so.
I suppose so.
Hey, Kagami.
There's a place I want to stop by on the way back...
We're going straight home with no detours.
Don't say that...
It won't take all that long.
No way!
But why?
You're getting annoying!
Don't say such harsh words...
Gah, get off of me!
Okay, fine!
But just for a little bit, okay?
Thank you, Kagami!
You're such a nice person, Kagami!
We're going straight home afterwards, okay?
Sure, sure.
By the way, Kona-chan...
Where are we stopping at?
Oh yeah, well.
Some pet shop that just recently opened up.
Pet
Shop
Oh, a pet shop?
How nostalgic!
Sign: Pet Shop: Minoru~pa~
Are you going to buy a dog or something?
I want to look at the bunnies.
I want to see the cute puppies.
Not at all.
This is what I wanted to look at.
Ah, this cat has really nice fur.
Konata, I'll remind you right now...
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't a witch or anything.
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
So don't bother it, okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
This cat isn't
a witch or anything.
So don't bother it,
okay?
I know that.
I won't go as far as
collecting its soul.
I won't go as far as collecting its soul.
Everything you've said up until now...
I am Zero.
I have returned!
I have
returned!
I will use you up like a ragged cloth!
I will
use you up like
a ragged cloth!
I will
use you up like
a ragged cloth!
I will
use you up like
a ragged cloth!
I will
use you up like
a ragged cloth!
I will
use you up like
a ragged cloth!
Ah, this cat must have a really nice lineage.
Yuki-chan, you come from a really nice lineage as well.
Hey, hey...
I don't think you're using that in the right context.
Well...
Right now, Miyuki-san is the Galactic Fairy.
Galactic Fairy
Although her appearance is slightly different...
These are the most famous frogs in Pekopon.
Ge~ro Gero Gero...
Ta~ma Tama Tama...
Ge~ro Gero Gero!
Ta~ma Tama Tama!
Ta-ma Tama Tama!
Ge-ro Gero Gero!
Ta~ma Tama Tama!
Ta-ma Tama Tama!
Ge-ro Gero Gero!
Oh!
I'm a dark-spotted frog.
I look like a Japanese tree frog.
I seem to be a bullfrog.
I'm a common toad...
Hey, wait a second!
Hmm...
Now then...
What happened here?
All right then!
For-For-For-Forgot my something...
For-For-For-
Forgot my something~
Party
Shout
Battle
General
Chat Window
Soldier
Oh!
That's...
Legendary Girl A!
This means...
I must have her buy something!
Battle
Behold!
The best armaments I have collected!
These slick deals...
Not even Legendary Girl A can resist them!
General
Chat Window
Dammit, she's AFK!?
Party
Shout
Battle
General
Chat Window
Sign: Lucky Channel
Oha-lucky!
It's this era's super super  idol, Kogami Akira here!
Long time no see, everyone!
And...
And...!
Her assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Moving on!
Wait!
Everyone, if he hears you call out for him, I think he'll show up.
But if you're really quiet, he might not hear you...
So please, say it as quietly as you can.
Hey!
Now then, one, two...
Minoru-senpai...
So you've appeared after all.
You didn't have to show up...
Hello. I'm the assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
You're not gonna do a little skit for us?
A skit?
Usually...
You would stop right in front of the camera...
Yes.
And then you would say, "And now, I'll put on a little performance..."
Right?
Now, let's try it!
Start!
How's that?
That's 10 years worth of experience for you.
Not bad at all.
Thank you very much.
And so, nice to meet you, everyone.
Speaking of...
Yes.
What's this?
Oh, this?
It's something that's pretty popular around these parts.
Nezumi Senpai.
Hmm...
Right now, it's totally in style.
I hear it's the best.
Okay, whatever.
Anyway!
What?
You don't even care?
Okay. What is it, then?
What I'm referring to is this entire situation.
What's up with this?
Eh?
What's up with what?
Well, it's a live-action filming.
A live...
A live Lucky Channel.
Something like that.
It's so loud!!
Now, now, now, now...
Let's calm down, okay?
I mean, c'mon...
Isn't this lovely?
It's lovely.
What is this?
What's up with that teary-eyed face?
I'm tellin' you, this is an animation!
Oh, but there was an animation.
Just before this.
What about me?
W-Well...
What about Kogami Akira?
Let me repeat myself...
Okay!
I'm this era's...
Right.
This era's...
Super Idol!
Right, right. That's correct.
Which is why...
We had you do this live performance that no one else could pull off.
I mean, it's a visual animation.
So we need to have some animations...
And also some visuals...
Which is why...
Ah.
By having both parts separate and then together,
it'll be twice as good.
I just realized.
What?
It's a bit like...
An Original...
Yes.
Visual...
...and Animation?
Animation.
Yes.
So, Shiraishi Minoru is an original...
...in the visual...
...as well as the animation?
That means the entire program is about you!
Wait...
That's not true!
Geez!!
You have it wrong!
Even though Akira is the one who's supposed to be the super idol!
You're absolutely correct.
Why are all the staff on Minoru-kun's...
Geez!
Okay, okay...
Please calm down.
There's not enough love!
Calm down.
I am shocked.
Shocked?
YOU wa SHOCK!
The skies have fallen from love.
Um...
Yeah...
YOU wa SHOCK!
Look...
My heart has fallen.
It's playing...
Look.
Um, the theme song...
See?
Even bound by chains, the heart burns.
What's this?
Oh this... this is nothing!
It'll disappear over here, so don't worry about it.
It is useless now.
The staff, everyone, loves you...
Those who interfere will be taken down by a single finger.
Don't worry, Akira-sama.
It's hot.
It's too hot?
Oh, excuse me?
Could we get some water or something?
YOU wa SHOCK!
Staff, may I have some water?
The pulse quickens from love.
Yes, please.
Some water please... ah.
Here, here it comes.
Thank you very much.
YOU wa SHOCK!
Now, please rest a little, okay?
Okay?
My pulse quickens.
Searching for you,
Yeah...
Anyway...
My wandering heart is now burning up.
This is fine too.
Yeah...
Like I was saying...
Now that I think about it, I'm a little thirsty, too.
Everything must dissolve and scatter apart tragically.
Excuse me, um...
Um...
Staff~
Um, could I also get some water here?
To protect our love,
Staff~
You departed on a journey.
Ah, yes.
I would like some water...
Had lost sight of tomorrow.
Wait...
Why are you taking the mic?
I don't want to see,
H-Huh, that's a bit strange...
Um...
Such a face that has forgotten how to smile.
Hey, where's my water...
My water?
Staff...
Reclaim the love!
I see...
You are already dead!
So that's how it is...
Huh?
But...
You know...
This is all wrong.
While this certainly is water...
It was not quite what I was expecting...
Hey...
It's...
Wrong...
Oh.
Welcome back.
You know...
I mean... seriously.
Yes.
Something like that...
Yeah, yeah...
Well...
You know...
And so...
Yes.
I've been thinking...
They kept on telling me, "You'll be in the main series."
Yes.
But those were all empty promises...
So then I tried being a pop star...
But that didn't last, either.
Right.
And so...
I even told them that I was willing to play some side parts or stuff like that in the main series, you know?
Right.
But here I am...
It'll be fine, Akira-sama!
You'll see!
Good things will happen!
But they haven't...
No matter what I do...
It's like there's not enough love in here...
Akira...
Akira-sama the ending...
Ehh!?
It's the end already?
Akira's so lonely!
That's it for today.
And then this!
Oh, this is new.
Certainly...
Right around here.
Around here.
Somewhere...
Please send all your love to Akira!
Please~
Yes.
And thus...
I await the next time we can see each other again!
But for now, bye-bii!
Bye-bii!
I'm seriously going to do my best.
I'm already at the top.
As high as the heavens.
Thank you very much.
What?
What is it?
Reproduction, modification, public exhibition
(broadcasting, streaming, Internet downloading, etc.), screening, enacting, distribution (retail or rental),
translation, or adaptation of this product is illegal
under law without permission
from the copyright holder.
You know...
Yes.
I've decided.
About what?
Well...
Yes.
I'm going to aim for the top.
Somewhere so high you can't touch me.
That's a good idea.
Something like that...
You're approaching it then.
Slowly but surely...
Like...
You know,
Itching your way to the top.
Right, it makes me think I should climb to the top.
Right, right.
Something like...
The both of us climbing to the top...
Zoom!
Zoom.
Let's do it; we'll go just like that.
And we'll figure it out just like that.
Right?
And we'll be at the top just like that.
Seems unreliable, but I'll give it a shot.
All right!