If I return to the beta world line,
Makise Kurisu will die.
I'll start the cracking now.
Wait!
The cracking...
don't do it.
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mono kodou no kazu sae
is a trivial matter with little glamor for you
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Even trapped in the past and lamenting the future
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
The dreams that stretch into "infinity" and the future we imagine
"mugen" ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
are vain privileges we allowed ourselves
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no kenri
"Finity", that's what the two hands of the clock show
"yuugen" sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
towards a cruel agreement and choice
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
Hacking to the Gate
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
and protect your smile
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
And once again, a solitary observer
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
is sucked into a time loop without sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
Paradox
Meltdown
Where's Okabe?
Dunno.
I've been busy.
Good luck, Mayushii!
You too, Daru.
Is today the last day of Comima?
Yeah, want to come?
They'll have lots of cute costumes there.
I-I'm not really interested.
I wonder what Okarin's up to.
No idea.
He said we weren't doing the cracking, and that was it.
What's he thinking?
They said it's gonna reach a high of 35!
Staying hydrated is the best way to prevent heatstroke.
Aren't you going to Comima today?
I'm leaving right now.
I see.
Be careful.
Okay.
It's really sunny out.
Bye.
Mayuri!
August 17th.
Each D-mail I undid delayed Mayuri's death by one day.
Erasing Suzuha's D-mail made the events of the 13th occur on the 14th.
Feyris, Rukako, Moeka...
If each one pushed it back a day,
then in this world line, Mayuri will die on the 17th.
Today, before 8:00 PM.
Okarin!
Did you find what you were looking for?
Yup!
It was almost sold out.
I got one for Daru too.
Oh, and there was a book on a robot anime I thought you'd like!
Want to go?
No.
I'm fine.
Why not?
You came all this way.
There's something I want to think about.
I see.
Tell me if there's anywhere you'd like to look.
Sure.
Are you okay?
Want to go home?
What are you talking about?
I wanted to think about, um,
the Organization assassins hiding in this building.
I need to do something to escape their clutches.
If I'm not careful, they might find me.
Follow the original plan until evening.
I don't think any bad people like that are here.
I'm going scouting.
Let's meet back here at 1500.
That okay?
Sure!
Okarin!
They're selling juice over there!
Five hours left.
Don't give up.
Before then, I'll have to find it...
a way for her to survive without changing world lines.
Assistant
Why do I have to help Hashida?
A notepad?
A list of circles at Comima?
I don't see one.
The rack?
The second shelf?
Don't look at the second shelf?
I'm seriously having you arrested.
What is it now?
It's me.
What's going on with the cracking?
You stopped it,
so we haven't touched it for three days.
Explain what's going on already.
What happened?
Mayuri will die today.
I heard you before.
Isn't that why you're doing the cracking?
To erase the first D-mail you sent—
No!
We aren't doing it.
I'm going to think of a way to save Mayuri without the cracking.
Why?
Things have changed. This is the only way.
What kind of things?
I can't explain now.
There must be some way,
some other way.
Some other way?
Please!
Explain.
If you don't, I won't be able to think of anything.
I won't be able to help.
You don't have time for this, right?
Don't hide things now!
Okabe?
We finally made it back.
Hey, want to stop by the lab, Okarin?
Mayushii was thinking of getting some food.
Okarin?
Are you tired?
No.
It's almost time...
almost time for her to die again.
Should I run?
No, that never works.
Okarin?
Let's go.
Hey, Okarin.
Why did you come with me today?
You barely went to see anything.
If you wanted to check something out,
I would've shown you around!
There aren't many things Mayushii knows more than Okarin about.
Okarin?
Thanks for coming today!
We've never gone to Comima together,
so Mayushii was happy!
Mayuri...
I wanted to see Rukako looking embarrassed in his costume!
It's a shame he didn't come.
Yeah, if he had, he would've been really popular.
I bet.
Then, Ruka would've gotten his photo on all the blogs,
and he would've become a worldwide superstar!
And then Mayushii would've seen it and said, "He's come a long way."
I could really see that happening.
It'd be even better if Okarin wore a costume too.
I'll consider it.
Really?
But in exchange, you'd have to do it too.
I know. We'll call Rukako and Christina,
and you can convince them to do it with us.
If you can do that, then I,
Hououin Kyouma the mad scientist,
shall make my costuming debut at Comima.
I see.
That's going to be hard!
But Kurisu was interested,
so Mayushii will try her best to do it by the next Comima.
The next...
Huh? My watch isn't working.
That's strange.
I just wound—
Okarin?
No!
This can't happen!
I'm so close!
Why is this happening?
Okarin?
Stay here!
I'm going to change fate.
I'll stop it from happening!
If I let that car hit me... If I die here,
something has to change!
Something!
Okarin!
Mayuri?
Mayuri!
Okarin...
Finally... Finally, I was useful.
Mayuri!
Mayushii was useful to you.
Okarin...
Hey, Mayuri...
You can't see the stars from here, can you?
This isn't fair.
I want to talk to you.
Kurisu
I'll start the cracking now.
Okabe?
How long are you going to lie there?
I thought I told you to leave me alone.
You did,
but you've been on the roof for hours
without so much as a peep, so I got worried.
I mean, I'm not worried, but...
Tell me.
Why did you stop the cracking?
You said it yourself.
You thought the FBI would come, and you got scared, right?
I can tell.
I'd prefer to be thought of as a law-abiding citizen.
This isn't like you.
What happened to your normal hotshot attitude?
The great mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma—
How can I act like that right now?!
Mad scientist?
Hououin Kyouma?
It's all bullshit!
I made it all up!
You didn't know?
I knew within five seconds of meeting you.
Did you time leap again?
What happened?
I've helped you with everything so far, haven't I?
Don't hold back now.
We've made it this far by thinking things through together, right?
This far, huh?
Suzuha and Feyris...
Rukako...
To come this far,
I sacrificed the things they loved the most.
And now, this is how it ends?
What do you mean?
Why?
Okabe!
Okabe, you were crying back there.
Hashida was worried too.
He thought maybe you had a bad dream.
Tell me.
I want to help you!
July 28th...
Mayuri and I went to Dr. Nakabachi's press conference.
There...
There, I saw Makise Kurisu collapsed after being stabbed,
but I don't know by whom.
I sent a text to Daru's cell phone,
which was connected to the Phone Microwave.
The first D-mail.
It was the message that moved us
from the beta world line to the alpha world line.
Deleting that message from SERN's database
and returning to the beta world line
means going back to that world.
If we return to the beta world line...
If we undo that first D-mail...
you will die.
Answer it.
Pick it up.
Mayuri?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Hey, Daru told me you were acting odd.
It's nothing.
Daru was wrong.
But...
I'm sorry.
Mayushii's been so busy with Comima
that she couldn't spend time with you.
Hey, you used to talk to Mayushii about all kinds of stuff, didn't you?
There were four Organization generals,
Geppu, Sudachi, Seiyuu, and Jakkou?
Genbu, Suzaku, Seiryuu, and Byakko.
That's right.
I really liked hearing about those things.
Hey...
If Mayushii is ever a burden, you'd tell me, right?
I'll leave you alone for now!
If Mayushii can do anything for you,
call me right away.
Mayuri?
You should go right now.
From your voice, I can guess what she was saying.
You should go see her now.
You won't be able to come up with any answers,
even if you stay here to talk to with me.
That's why you were sitting here alone, right?
Thus, you should go see Mayuri.
You'll only hurt my pride if you stay here and worry.
I'll be going!
This is Mayushii. I can't answer the phone right now!
It's me.
One of them said Mayushii left a while ago.
I see.
I'm sorry.
You came to see me because it's Obon, right, Granny?
I've only been having scary dreams lately.
In the dreams, terrible things happen to Mayushii.
She gets shot with a pistol,
or she's in a car accident or run over by a train,
and everything seems like it really happened.
It's scary, and it hurts.
And it's sad.
I try to scream for help as loud as I can,
but I can't.
Why do I have these dreams?
And at the end of the dreams,
Okarin always comes to save me.
Mayushii says, "Thank you, Okarin!"
But he doesn't hear me.
He holds Mayushii, and he looks sad.
He never cries, but you can tell he really wants to.
So Mayushii says, "I'm sorry," but he doesn't hear me.
After that, I wake up.
I'm sorry!
I'll talk about something fun.
Lately, there have been a lot of new lab members!
There's Kurisu,
Moeka,
Ruka, and Feyris!
Suzu too!
At first, it was just the two of us.
Kurisu is super smart,
and she talks about all these really hard things with Okarin.
It's so much fun.
Okarin looks happy now that he gets to talk so much.
But, you know, sometimes I remember...
the first time Mayushii went to the lab.
It was the beginning of spring, but it was snowing.
When I went to the lab after school,
Okarin wasn't there.
While I was cleaning up the room, he came in,
and I said, "Welcome back!"
But he didn't say, "I'm back."
He said, "Good work."
And then, every day after that, I'd go there
for about two hours, and we would barely talk.
It wasn't bad. We were simply there together.
Time passed so slowly, and it was nice.
Mayushii thought she really was like a hostage!
Did something good happen?
Yup!
Nothing good happened, but it was good anyway.
I see. You saw some kind of illusion.
It may be an attack by Organization General Illusion Conductor.
I see.
Then I'll have to be careful!
But I bet that Illusion Contactor—
Conductor.
I don't think he's a bad person!
Lately, I haven't spent much time talking with Okarin.
It used to be that, when I saw him,
I could tell what he was thinking.
But recently, I can't.
Well...
I can tell he's really suffering,
like he's always about to cry,
and I know he's thinking about me.
I don't want to be a burden to him.
I'm sorry! I was talking about something sad again!
Maybe Mayushii's been lonely lately.
Granny, I can't stay this way forever.
You can.
It's Okarin!
How did you know I was here?
I always know where my hostage is,
so you can't get away from me.
Never.
You shouldn't force yourself.
I, Hououin Kyouma,
am not so weak that I need you to worry about me.
When the time comes,
I'll tell you everything.
Okay.
We're going home.
But before that...
I know.
You want to get another Upa toy, right?
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
Our vision, controlled by someone, fills with cruelty
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
We can't escape the twelve rules
ansoku no asu wo negatta
We wished for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten