Bonjour, tout le monde!
It's time for le lesson royal de Madame Siamour!
Today's lesson is le makeup!
Makeup?
How splendidly mature!
I'm so excited!
Now then, tout le monde...
let's commençons le lesson!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Okay, done!
Guess that'll do.
You're as skilled as I expected.
You look stunning.
I'm used to this sorta thing from work, though.
You look pretty stunning yourself!
Well, the parties I attend give me
plenty of opportunities to practice.
Oh, how I envy you two.
I can't seem to get it quite right!
Oh my!
Says the girl who's got it on perfect!
Where'd you learn that?
I simply learned a bit from the maids when I was young...
Talk about luck...
You girls look simply splendid!
So, how's my makeup?
It's on too thick!
Vous must apply gently with la élégance!
I get the idea, but it's still hard!
This little guy...
That little guy is a Hope Kingdom fairy...
Kuroro!
From back then?
Seems he's finally woken up.
How do you feel?
We're glad that you're all right, Kuroro.
He just woke up and hasn't pieced it all together.
Seems he doesn't remember
a thing from his time as Lock.
Poor thing...
Leave Kuroro to moi!
Vous should study for le lessons!
There are many more hurdles on le path to la Grand Princess!
Teach Me, Siamour!
Making Dreams Come True 101!
How is it?
A bit... thick?
Of course it is...
How does this still happen?
Bonjour, Madame Siamour!
I'd really like some advice right about now!
Huh? Are you there?
This morning, Madame Siamour took Kuroro out that-a-way!
Which-a-way?
Into Dreamy Shore City?
Why the city?
So, she can just waltz out of the Pad whenever?
This could be Madame Siamour's first time in our world.
I'm getting kinda worried.
Dreamy 5         Dreamy Shore bound
Where should we start looking?
Our only clue's that she maybe went to the city, so...
Yeah...
Found her!
Madame Siamour!
Huh? She left!
Where did she go?
Huh?
Madame Siamour!
It's her!
She's gonna leave us behind again!
Madame Siamour!
She's gone...
Where could she have gone now?
Wait!
Over there!
Huh?
That way!
I'm pooped...
What a kitty!
Kitty?
Phew!
You really worked the crowd!
Thanks, kitty.
Meow!
Madame Siamour!
Oh, fancy meeting vous here.
Fancy meeting us?
We've been searching for you this whole time.
What've you been up to?
I'll tell vous later.
For now, moi has places to be.
Let's go, Kuroro.
Where are they going?
Let's follow them and find out!
Bonjour, tout le monde!
Nice to see vous again!
Allow moi to introduce my new friend to vous all.
I'm... Kuroro... Hi...
Play nice with him!
She's talking with cats...
She was talking with those birds earlier, too!
I knew Madame Siamour had expertise in numerous fields of study,
but I didn't think linguistics was one of them!
I suppose meowing is a language.
Oui!
Moi takes part in la local cat assemblies from time to time.
No wonder she looks just like a part of the gang!
So, she leaves the Pad that often, huh?
Oh no, a fight's breaking out!
Le calicos and le black cats
have never quite gotten along.
Hey, violence is wrong!
True. If vous feel vous have to settle le score...
Puissance des fées lesson!
Vous shall duel with fashion!
Fashion?
Are you nuts?
Whaaaaaa?!
The cats are talking!
And they're standing on their hind legs!
What do cats have to do with fashion?
Cats need their fashion sense, too.
Vous all clean votre fur every day, non?
Well, true...
It's settled, le fashion duel is on!
Le black cats shall decorate...
Boss Black Cat!
And le calicos, hmm...
why not dress up Kuroro?
Oui!
Ma princesses will help out, of course!
Vous will lead le black cats,
and vous will lead le calicos!
Us too?
This lesson will sharpen vos fashion sense!
The team with le better ensemble wins, oui?
All right, let's do this!
As a model, I can't let myself lose a battle of fashion!
Rest assured, black kitty, we'll make certain you look like a prince!
What should we do?
Let's see...
We can start by finding what matches with Kuroro.
Good luck, everyone!
The fight is on!
Oh, that's cute!
That too!
That's cute too!
Oh, I just can't decide!
Kuroro, what fashions do you prefer?
It doesn't matter...
Looking nice won't change a thing...
I want to go back to the kingdom...
I miss everyone... Sniff...
Kuroro...
Kuroro, moi feels the same.
But sorrow won't make votre dreams come true.
Then what will?
Stop!
Freeze!
Wh-What is the meaning of...
Right back at you.
Quit slabbing your mug in makeup and do your job!
I'll have you know...
Get going.
Oh, my vanity!
Use that to gather the humans' despair.
Am I clear?
C-Crystal...
Curse him...
Hmm...
Meow.
Très bien! Now then...
our winner iiiiiiiiis...
to be announced after le repos!
Wow!
It's lovely!
Now help yourselves.
How can this be so yummy?!
You never fail to impress, Siamour. They're all scrumptious.
Is it just me, or do these taste just like Marble Doughnuts?!
Ouioui! Je have sampled many of the town's delicacies for my own study.
You're a master!
Do you like it, Kuroro?
I-I do...
Good!
How to make vos dreams come true, leçon d'une!
Eat good food!
A full stomach is the quickest way to health and happiness!
Happiness, my foot!
The joy of others is naught but nauseating!
Shut?
Oh non!
Vous!
Pourquoi is votre makeup la catastrophe?!
Votre eye shadow is unfinished! Shame on you!
Look, this...
A mere fairy with such an immaculate coat?
Such arrogance!
And what's he doing playing dress-up?!
The cats are too?!
That is simply going too far!
I don't care who, just show me your dreams!
Huh? Wait!
Cease this, Shut!
Silence!
We wanna eat a bunch of fish!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
What? They're fish?!
Guess you are what you eat...
Girls!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Girls!
Get a grip and fight!
Where do you even grip them?!
Your hands will be naught but sticky!
Now...
it is naught but your turns next!
It is naught but over!
Madame Siamour!
Votre opponent is moi!
You're naught but to try as you might!
Naught! Naught! Naught!
She moves...
like a ballerina!
Beautiful...
You're clearly no mere fairy. State your name!
El professeure royal, Madame Siamour!
Disarray of le makeup comes from disarray of le heart!
Right now, votre heart is in great disarray!
Th-This is Close's faul—
Non excuses!
If vous have self respect, vous will do it right no matter who gets in votre way!
The fact that vous did not speaks to a lack of self confidence, oui?
Is something bothering vous?
Life has been fraught with ills as of late!
Aww...
This is what le fashion is for!
Finish votre makeup and cheer up!
Siamour, what are you thinking?
La color is bien, but it lacks boldness.
It looks like she's helping Shut with his makeup!
What?
Are you pulling my leg?
Let's try this.
You certainly know when to be daring!
Only because it looks so perfect on vous.
Then allow me!
What're you giving our enemy lessons for?!
Spreading smiles is la duty of la Princess Precures.
And cheering up a person in need is just good manners!
Even if we may be opponents,
it is la définition of la élégance!
Isn't that so?
True, kicking someone while
they're down isn't too graceful!
Besides, a crisis is a chance for one to come out stronger!
At all times, act with strength, grace, and beauty!
And fight fair and square!
That's my kind of princess!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Bien!
How to make vos dreams come true, leçon de deux!
Go with le heart strong and le chin up!
Let's finish it!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Oh!
Who is that stud in the mirror?
Bien! It looks wonderful on vous.
Vous pass!
Of course! I can do whatever I set my mind to!
I am b-e-a-utiful!
He left.
Open!
The door to your dream!
La Princess Precures will certainly reclaim le kingdom one day.
Je believe in them.
That's why moi will study this world as much as moi can.
Je want to be a good teacher to le étudiants when the day of our return comes.
That is my dream.
Dream?
Leçon de trois!
Treasure every moment with equal parts play and study!
Je am certain that will take vous to votre dream.
I'll try for real!
Until we return to our kingdom, I'll study and play with a smile!
Is that votre dream?
It is!
Bien!
Close, you must have noticed it...
this traffic stopping beauty!
What now?
Beauty is my middle name!
Who was that?
Who was that indeed.
Nonsense.
But no matter.
The Forest of Despair yet grows.
What is it?
It's thanks for saving them.
He says he found it somewhere and
wants you to have it since it's pretty.
Could that be Hope Kingdom's Royal Crest?!
Huh?
But how?
Does this mean...
It must be Kanata's!
So he...
Kanata...
Kanata must be near!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Scarlet!
With the strength to live beyond any past,
none shall extinguish my flame
If we join hands and trust in eternity
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Huh? Me, model? Kirara, save me!
Go! Princess Precure:
Simply Doomed!
Haruka's Princess Contest!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Iwate Prefecture - Yuina (Age 8)
Osaka Prefecture - Miyabi (Age 6)