I'll write you letters.
Okay, I will too.
I made these.
How cute!
They match each other.
Will you take one?
Sure!
Thanks!
Do they have names?
Names? I didn't think about that...
Why don't you give them names?
Huh?
Then...
Ril and Mel!
Yeah, sounds cute!
Ril and...
Mel!
Thanks! I'll take good care of her.
We'll be friends forever.
Yeah! No matter what!
Together forever!
Hey Dad, look—
Oh, turn right at the next corner.
I've returned.
Back to this city.
Memories
Front and Back
Homura
More! More!
And stop!
Here, those go over there.
In here?
Yes, right.
Excuse me.
Please let me help out.
Oh, you don't need to worry about it.
It's covered by our fee.
There we go.
Good morning!
Dinner Money
Everyone take your seats.
We have a new transfer student today.
Homura Suzuko
Her name is Homura Suzuko-san.
Due to family circumstances, she's transferring in as a second-year from her high school in Hokkaido.
Please introduce yourself.
Okay. I'm Homura Suzuko.
I used to live in this city until second grade,
and I'm happy to be back.
Please be kind to me.
Homura Suzuko
I'd like to be your friend.
All right, that's it for homeroom.
First period is chemistry over in the second science lab.
Hop to it.
Yeah.
The second science lab...
Wait up!
Excuse me.
Where can I find the second science lab?
Oh, it's up the central stairs and to the left.
Um, do you mind if I come—
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Sorry!
What were you talking about?
Nothing, just where the science lab was.
Daily Veggies
Your deck is amazing!
Isn't it? You're in for a nasty surprise if you think I'm the same as yesterday.
Okay, my turn!
Attack her LRIG directly!
Hold it! During your Attack Phase,
I defend with Storm Warning!
What?! Seriously?
Now I'm gonna lose.
I'm gonna stop by the card shop on the way home.
Deck? LRIG and card shop?
Okay!
From: Dad
To: Suzuko
I'll be home late tonight.
No Subject
From: Dad
To: Suzuko
I'll be home late tonight.
No Subject
From: Dad
To: Suzuko
I'll be home late tonight.
No Subject
From: Dad
To: Suzuko
I'll be home late tonight.
No Subject
From: Dad
To: Suzuko
I'll be home late tonight.
No Subject
Aw man, now I've made too much.
Warm it up before eating.
Homura Suzuko
Dear Suzu,
How have you been?
Are you used to Hokkaido yet?
I'm kind of lonely without you, but
These bring back memories.
Morikawa Chinatsu
Recipient Not At This Address
"Turn the corner at the white apartment building"...
There!
Fujihara
Can I help you?
Excuse me, I was acquainted with the Morikawa family who used to live here until three years ago.
Do you happen to know their current address?
No, I'm afraid not. Sorry I can't help you.
I see. Thank you anyway.
Go all in, Suzu!
Yeah!
I know you can do it!
Let's give it one more shot!
Okay!
Here I go!
See? You did it!
Yeah, I did it!
I did it, I did it!
You did it!
I never knew it was this short.
Let's play on the bars next.
Wait, I'm not good at that!
Don't worry, I'll show you how.
Where are you now, Chii-chan?
Welcome. Is this for here or to go?
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your cheeseburger combo.
Please enjoy.
Morikawa
You bought another new pack?
Yeah, I felt like beefing up my deck.
Wixoss is so addicting.
Gonna enter a tournament?
I might, yeah.
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Hello.
Oh, Mom, I'll have dinner too.
Really? You didn't eat at work today?
No, we were pretty packed all day.
And you're working on the weekends too.
Don't you think it's a bit much?
They're starting to rely on me more.
But that just means my pay goes up too.
Sorry about this.
Don't overwork yourself.
You're overreacting, Dad.
I'm doing this job because I like it.
I make sure to study too, so it's fine.
Hey, about that transfer girl...
Oh, Homura-san?
Did you see her bag?
I saw! What was that, a mascot?
It looked handmade.
Yeah, totally!
It's like something an elementary schooler would have.
And yeah, did you see how dirty it was?
Stop it, I'm starting to feel bad.
I'm sure it was all the rage at her school.
Back where she's from?
Yeah, out in the sticks.
Now you're being mean!
So that's a card shop?
Battle
space
available!
Battle
space
available!
We Buy and Sell
I wonder if they'll let me play it with them.
Isn't that Homura-san?
Yeah.
SIGNI, Spell, Arts...
There are so many of them! And this is...
A LRIG.
How pretty.
Welcome...
Selector...
Welcome, Selector...
I am the LRIG of the Beginning.
What?
Now registering your memories.
Welcome, Selector.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Welcome, Selector.
Selector? Me?
I am your LRIG. Give me a name.
A name...
Why don't you give them names?
R-Ril.
The same as that mascot, I see.
Huh?!
Why do you know that?
Because I am your avatar.
Avatar?
These are your memories.
People are built from their memories of the past.
Suzuko, these coins are your very self.
Cards?
Choose one.
Th-This...
Entry complete.
Your holding is one coin.
Let the battle begin.
What do you mean, battle?
For the next ninety days,
you will enter a fight with the other chosen ones possessing LRIG cards.
You are a participant in the Selector battles.
I don't know anything about that!
I've never even battled before!
I can't do it!
You cannot refuse to battle.
If you win, one black coin will turn gold.
If you lose, one gold coin will turn black.
If all five become gold,
you will be able to reclaim yourself and escape the battle.
However,
if all five become black, you will disappear.
That is the Selector battle.
Enercharge! Attack!
Damn, seriously?
Do you give up?
Stupid, I'm just getting started.
Don't want to admit defeat?
Do you want to play?
Huh?
We saw you at the card shop yesterday.
Come on, let's have a battle.
S-Sorry.
I don't really know the rules yet.
I'm really sorry.
Why won't you battle?
Those two are not Selectors.
Gaining experience through normal games
will be to your benefit in the real battles.
It's fine. I'm not going to battle anyway.
You cannot refuse. Didn't I tell you that?
Why?! Why me?!
You were chosen.
Says who?!
I never asked for—
That doesn't matter.
Homura Suzuko
You were chosen, Suzuko. That's all.
No. How am I even supposed to battle if you're telling me I'll disappear after losing once?!
The result will be the same either way.
Each coin has a limited lifespan.
What?
Even if you do nothing, it will eventually disappear.
Win in battle. You have no other choice.
You can't...
Even as we speak, your memories are being eaten away.
A Selector is approaching!
Right below us on the stairs!
Blinded.
I didn't expect to find another one in my school.
U-Um...
Challenge.
Hi!
I won't do it... I'm not going to battle.
Unfathomable. Are you not a Selector?
I-I...
Sorry!
Why...
Why am I a Selector?
I can't battle... I can't fight.
You aren't fighting alone.
I am your avatar.
Dinner Money
Morning...
Suzuko.
What?
Do you really not intend to fight?
Yeah.
Look at your coins.
My coins?
The coins are always in the palm of your hand.
In my hand...
The color...
I told you that they have a limited lifespan.
By tomorrow morning it will have turned to black, and you will disappear.
How could that...
What do you mean I'll disappear?
What'll happen to me?
Memories fade with the passage of time.
Emotions are eaten away.
And eventually, everything inside of you
will vanish.
Chii-chan...
No... I don't want to forget.
Hello there.
You're a Selector too, right?
Don't be so afraid.
I'm one too.
This happened all so suddenly that I'm not sure what to make of it.
It doesn't seem like we can put off battling forever.
I'm only a beginner,
but would you have a battle with me?
Suzuko.
This is your last chance.
To begin a battle, you need only to hold up my card and shout "open".
The cards will guide you the rest of the way.
Suzu!
I...
don't want to forget.
Open!
Where is this?
The battlefield.
This is where Selector battles occur.
Battlefield...
Bingo!
I knew you were a newbie!
And on top of that, you've only got one coin.
I've got four.
Anyway, I hope you don't mind if I win.
Don't hate the player, okay?
Preying on puny-looking kids is my own personal game theory.
We're first. It's your turn, Suzuko.
First? Th-Then...
Calm down.
Grow me as your first action.
O-Okay.
Grow!
Um, next...
You're damn slow!
Stop wasting my time.
If you're done, then end your turn!
This is why I hate beginners.
T-Turn End!
Suzuko!
No way, she actually ended her turn!
You sure you want to leave yourself open like that?
E-Excuse me...
It's mean to bully someone new to the game.
Shut the hell up, Guzuko!
Forgive me!
Grow, Guzu!
R-Right away!
Bring out the SIGNI and attack with everything!
Yes.
Ril!
I'm fine. It's your turn now, Suzuko.
What should I do?
The most important thing is to balance attack and defense and keep a steady formation.
Grow me first, and then summon SIGNI.
G-Got it. Grow!
Then I summon Valor Gawain!
Full attack!
Not half bad.
Guzuko! Summon Beanbag!
O-Okay!
Attack!
Ril, strike back with a Servant!
This is... a Selector battle.
I'm sorry!
Ril!
Ril...
It's not over yet.
I can't...
It's impossible for me!
We're going to lose!
Chii-chan...
Hurry it up and attack me already.
Not like it'll do you any good though.
I've got an impenetrable defensive Arts for you.
Any damage you do will be converted to Ener,
and I'll be able to smash your LRIG to pieces with this special trump card.
A defensive Arts... then even if I attack...
Suzu, all in!
He's only been targeting beginners like me this entire time.
He's conceited and looks down on us.
I don't think he's invested in his defense at all. But...
If it's true, then Ril...
Suzuko!
Bet a coin.
A coin?
You aren't battling alone.
Bet on me.
With your everything.
I bet a coin!
Honest!
"Honest"? Like someone who tells the truth?
It appears to be a coin ability.
How retarded! Listen, all that stuff about a defensive Arts was a big, fat lie!
Like hell I'd have something like that.
All I need to finish you off is to attack one more time.
That's why I hate beginners—
Why did I...
Ril, go!
Fuck!
How the hell did I lose to a damn beginner?
Just you wait! It won't go your way next time!
Congratulations.
Now you have two coins remaining.
Yeah.
Suzu, all in!
Ril, in a way...
I remind you of Chinatsu?
I was created from your memories.
If I resemble Chinatsu,
then that just shows how important she is to you.
I see. The Chii-chan inside of me.
Welcome, Selector.
For memories everything is given life
for memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Tell me of enigmas and fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Die memory, if only I could see you
die memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurisaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
I just want to end this game as soon as possible.
Aren't you a Selector?
What will disappear?
You just have to win.
So you have two coins, Onee-san!
Won't you use a coin?
I...
I won't lose.
Next time: Girl / Ideal and Reality.
Girl
Ideal and Reality