Can you feel the air?
Momoka-san, I...
11: CENTER OF THE WORLD
Hey, watch it! We're packed
like sardines in here!
Well, what can we do about it?
Why are we even rehearsing
in such a tiny room?
It was the only room they had left.
Really? Because the hall I saw
earlier was completely empty.
That's way out of our budget!
But can we afford to cut corners?
The festival's so soon...
"But can we affowd to cut cowners?
The festival's so closeee..."
We're just wasting time.
More importantly, we should fix the timing.
So I need to time the vocals better, right?
I can help you with the timing.
Thanks!
- Do we really need that final portion?
- I was thinking the same...
Personally, I like it as it is.
I feel both work well enough...
what do you think, Momoka-san?
Hm?
Hard to say since it gets really loud
with all the instruments at once.
Let me try to hear the final
part again without my guitar.
Let's give it a shot!
OK !
Ugh, I'm dead...
No way! Burton Sister are playing at the festival?!
Really?!
Do you like them?
Not really...
Shadow Theater / Togenashi Togeari / Wavering Songs / Dawnbreak Alley / Tissue Regeneration / Running Enthusiasts / Illusionary Flower / Velbet Dream / Raindrops Harmony / Whispers / Stardust Sonatune / Neon Mirage / Fluffy Yuna / Stardust Creek / Cery Veloce / Twilight Prepaid / Silent Maple Song / Abyss Radler / Burton Sister
Real hotties, huh?
I told you I don't really care!!
Look! We're there too!
Well, obviously. We are participating...
We're on the first day, huh?
Yep. And among the openers too.
That means we can enjoy the bands coming after!
Like this one, or that one...!
You sure are taking advantage of this...
Well, of course I am!
Might as well, given the chance!
Do we know how many viewers we'll have?
It's a long festival, so it depends on the time.
The headliners are sure to get a lot of viewers but,
The rest can also be left with just scraps.
Can we leave enough of a "scar"
if we got so many bands coming after?
- Well, actually...
- Hey!!
I heard about the festival!
So much for retiring, huh?
I'll be cheering for you!
- As I was saying, we might
play on the second day instead.
- Huh?
Another band had to cancel, so a slot opened up.
It'll still be the same stage, we'll
just be playing at a different time.
Second day will go all night long...
So that means we're likely to
have more people sticking around!
That's great!
So we're all cool with it, right?
It finally feels like the winds
are blowing in our favor...
Do you all have some time after this?
- This is...!
- Yeah.
Thought I might as well show you
where it is we'll be performing.
We'll be performing somewhere THIS big??
- Sorry, but no. That's the main stage.
- Main??
We'll be performing on a smaller stage on the side.
Eh? Wait, there's SEVERAL stages??
You really didn't know?
The stars get the big stage,
While we have to do with the scraps.
Obviously, Diamond Dust is on the big one.
I feel... happy.
Like... how cool is this!
We're gonna stand our ground
and challenge Diamond Dust
from our little small stage.
- Giant Killing!
- As they say, a cornered rat will bite a cat.
Hold up, hold up.
I don't think neither they
nor the fans see it as a battle.
We do. Me and Momoka-san.
Are you all sure you're okay with the schedule change?
We are, right?
That's it, then!
It's gonna feel good to
perform under a sky like this...
Momoka-san!
Can you let me use your guitar
for a sec during the festival?
Right, gotta bounce to work!
Huh? Don't you guys have the same job?
Yes, but Nina-san has decided
to take an additional job
On top of the one we share.
Can't tell if she's being irresponsible or impulsive...
I think she's made up her mind
that she can make it on her own.
She's really changed recently, huh?
Wait hold up, since when did she learn guitar??
Who knows...
From: Awa Tendou
Dear Subaru-san,
I hope you are doing well
amidst the lingering heat of summer.
I imagine you must be busy these days, but I hope all is well at school.
There will be an audition soon,
so would you like to participate?
Your previous work was quite well received, so...
I swear.
How is it that now she's the one who's so happy?
Fuck's sake.
LIAR
I'm no liar...
To think Subaru is still keeping
the band a secret from her family...
That's what you like about her, right?
Since you can relate.
N-not really...
I really hope one day you'll be
able to forgive your family as well.
As if that could ever happen.
No one can see into the future.
There's no way...
At least you can still reach them.
Even if you aren't seeing them or
talking with them, they're still alive.
The people that I cherish...
I can never meet them again.
But I'm still here.
Thank you.
How did you all get into music?
Good question... maybe because
I can connect with others through it.
Because it's somewhere I can be myself, I think.
That's right. I did...
So that I can forget about everything and feel free.
As for me...
It's so I can keep believing I wasn't wrong.
Woah, so many people came...
We're just getting started, this is the real deal!
What's your name again?
Ah! TogeToge! Togenashi Togeari.
Ah, right! Please feel free to park over there.
- So we're playing in the evening?
- Yes. Don't go forgetting now!
I was thinking of checking out the other bands...
Eh! But today's the big showdown!
Well, think it this way, seeing other bands playing will get us pumped up.
But no matter what, DON'T be late.
Sure, sure!
Can I come with you?
Nope, you can't!
Prick.
So I guess this is our green room?
Pretty much.
FOR: TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Wassup!
You came for us?
Mine-san?
- Can I come in?
- By all means!
It's been a while.
- Hello...
- Long time no see.
You could've told me you were coming!
Wouldn't be a surprise if I did!
Still, you were given a spot
on the second day? That's incredible!
Thank you very much!
Even if it was just pure luck...
And Nina-chan, how have you been?
Ah, I'm well! I'm still learning the guitar though...
I'm glad.
You've brightened a lot since last time.
...Really?
You've got the face of someone raring to sing!
Thanks!
Hey, how long are you gonna chat for?
Did you forget to introduce me?
Yo.
She's back for revenge!
Ah, sorry.
This girl's Kyoko.
Small world, huh?
H-hello...
Hi...
Kyoko is a big fan of yours.
I really love your voice.
Play with us some other time? How 'bout it?
I-if you don't mind having me...
Really? Hell yeah, man!
Let's snap a pic to celebrate!
Gimme your worst face!
Worst face??
Y'all, get in here too!
Huh? Why?
Ready?
Say cheese!
You all look so silly.
Why didn't you two join in? Cowards...
Oooh! We got a bunch of likes!
Lots of comments too.
They're saying they can't wait to see us!
We're finally getting noticed!
They've got all-you-can-drink!
Oh, nice!
Time to dig in!
Stop.
Just a bit, come on.
I don't trust your definition of "little".
Ah, Miura-san!
That is Miura-san... right?
Y-you got the wrong person!
Huh? Did I really...?
- Anyway--
- Stop!
By the way, has Subaru not returned yet?
Shouldn't she have had her fill for now?
Not fair... I wish she took me with her...
Oh, she already came back to the green room.
Oh, really?
STOP!
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
- Subaru-chan!
- Yo.
How was it? Did you get to see the band you wanted?
Yeah.
Sounds fun. Wish I could've been there though...
Heh. I wanted to make you jealous.
Since you've been so happy recently.
Something happen?
You know, a long time ago,
when I first went to a festival,
there's this thing a drummer
said that stuck with me.
Even if you work hard, you're stuck
looking at the backs of the others.
When I heard that, I could relate a lot to it.
That's what happens when
you're the drummer, after all.
Subaru-chan...
Yesterday, I sent my grandma a mail.
What about?
I told her that I didn't want to be
an actress, but do something else!
Really?
So let's keep this band going as long as we can!
Even if we mess up today.
Are you sure?
You're a self-centered monster
that only does what she pleases.
That makes you shy and hard to
befriend. No wonder you got bullied.
But that means you just can't lie to others.
And you just charge so blindly into everything you do,
That it inspires me to try and be the same.
Thank you.
I'm just lying though!
You liar!
Let's go!
Momoka-san?
Where to?
You'll know right away!
- It really is massive...
- It is the main stage after all.
The people are flocking!
Can you see, Tomo-chan?
That's why I hate these things...
Want a piggyback ride?
I'm happy to see you've gotten
used to flipping off this way.
It's starting.
This song...
Yeah. It's them.
Momoka-san...
Hello! Thank you for the warm welcome!
And for all those that don't know us yet, we are...
Diamond Dust!
Please stick till the end~!
How long do you plan to
keep playing the victim card?
You know you were wrong.
Stop bashing your head against the wall.
What are you, an idiot?
Leave me alone...
Here we go!
Announcing a debut, in a world ready to end.
As an uncertain future creeps in,
These boring days keep flying by,
Living in a dream that is neverending.
Besieged by enemies, you still laugh,
Even when you stare at me
like that, you wanna go crazy.
But that won't be enough to fill the void.
You can't scream, only relish
in the past efforts of others!
Your only wish is that things can someday change!
Keep screaming, no matter how long it takes,
As you get strangled by the cruel chains of fate!
A never-ending cycle of misguided sorrow!
Thank youuu~!
- Hope you're all having fun!
- To those in the back as well!
They've improved.
True...
When she joined as the vocalist,
She got blamed a lot for turning
the band into an idol group.
She probably didn't take kindly to those messages.
I bet she wanted a second chance
for people to judge her real talent.
And the fans seem to have picked up...
that she's serious.
- So they viewed this as a battle too, huh...
- They piss me off.
I love it when things fire up like this!
Momoka-san... let's go and steal
every last one of their fans!
Right!
Right then, Togenashi Togeari,
please come for a sound check!
OK!
Wow... Incredible...
Can the drummer please give me a test?
Alright!
Thank you, that's enough.
Could you test your mic too?
Sure!
Alright, thank you.
Thank you! Let's do this everyone!
Alright then, the bass please.
Of course.
Great. Will you be using any pedals?
Yes, for warping.
Alright, anything else?
All good!
It's almost time.
- Then how about we celebrate--
- By NOT drinking alcohol!
Oh? Where did Miura-san go?
I got a call from her earlier.
She said that she'll be in the audience.
Why keep her distance?
I think it's better that she's being professional about it.
- I wonder if that's why...
- Let's GOOOOO!!!
Togenashi Togeari! Whenever you're ready!
We're here!
So, are we gonna do one of those group hugs?
Ew, no.
Shirt: "NINA WAS RIGHT"
Will you... will you all flip them off with me?
Sounds great!
Hell yeah!
Cringe.
This is gonna be the biggest concert we've ever done.
Nina... I want to hear you sing
on such a stage. Let them hear it!
Let them hear our song! Channel all of our feelings!
I will!
Heh! Look at her crying!
We're starting, get it together!
I suck at guitar!
She really does, haha...
She sure sucks...
How very rock!
Ehm, nice meeting you!
We are Togenashi Togeari.
We are a, uh... band.
Though... I'm making it sound easier than it's been.
We're all cowards, distrustful, and foulmouthed.
Sometimes we're not even
serious about it and want to quit.
You talking about me?
The hell you mean by "foulmouthed"?
Am I wrong?
Sit down, girl.
Say hi to our guitarist Momoka-san,
and our keyboard Tomo-chan!
And our resident self-righteous
monster, vocalist Nina!
And our bassist Rupa-san!
Love me some drama!
And at the drums is...
Subaru!
"Give up." "It'll never happen."
"It's impossible." "Stop being in denial."
"You've already got it good."
"We all have it hard, you know?"
Reality tried to swallow
me with those very words,
All while pretending to smile.
So I'm going to use this song... to break free.
And also...
To turn those who never believed
in this song into believers.
To all those that tried to deny who I am...
I'll make you scream that I wasn't wrong!
No matter how much I'm given,
Even if I make it all my own,
my own, my own,
I can never catch up!
To tell someone they're aiming too high,
is a disgusting thing to say.
No one's trying to be better than them,
And the reason is simple:
We just want to find a way
to break through this void.
Once you start to look at it genuinely
It's like it's all sunshine and rainbows
And yet what you want to grasp
is blurred out of sight.
I don't want to die! I want to live hard!
I want it! I want it! My soul screams out!
This irrational irritation won't stop!
I cannot, I cannot, ever forgive,
I'm so pathetic!
I just keep making, making,
everything worse!
You just can't see the tears I'm hiding!
To tell someone to just obey,
is such a shitty thing to say.
TAKE THE RAGE OF LONELINESS
I'd rather defy you to the point of covering my ears.
I may be sad and alone,
But at least I kicked out the feeling of not belonging.
TAKE THE LOST JOY
I'm unable to cry with this hollow heart,
TAKE THE SORROW OF A LIAR
Suppressing the flame, my voice silent.
Ebizuka Tomo - National Piano Gold Medalist
AND POUR IT ALL
Everything I want to do, going to ashes, vanishing from sight...
POUR IT ALL
INTO THIS SONG
And yet what you want to grasp
is blurred out of sight.
I don't want to vanish! I want to destroy!
This rusted and tangled distorted commotion!
Even muddy transparency
can be pretty if turned to dust!
I'm pathetic, pathetic, I cannot stand it!
All meaning and words are gone,
my ideals but old fantasies!
Shirt: DROPOUT
I'm too scared to even resist!
VOID AND CATHARSIS
- Rupa-san!
- Nina!
- You're the best!
Momoka-san, I...
I wasn't wrong, right?
NEXT: The Skies Darken Once More