Ouch!
That day, I learned the secret of boxed lunches.
Yeah.
This isn't that bad for a change.
Four gays having lunch together, you know?
It's guys, not gays.
And the fourth one is missing.
Where is our great mastermind Kitamura, who had this brilliant idea, anyway?
Here!
Sorry guys, I had to get this from the student council room.
It was a tad too big for my locker.
W-What the hell is this?
Could this be...
A-A boxed lunch?
Right.
And then...
Are you serious?
That kind of boxed lunch has to be a joke!
Hey Haruta, don't make fun of people's lunches—
Oh wow.
Is this from a comic?
Yeah, a 2-D lunch box that came to life!
You haven't seen what's inside yet!
What's up, guys? What's so funny here?
Let grandpa take a look—
Minorin?
What's this?
Maruo brought gourmet food!
What are we celebrating here?
That lobster's antennae are huge.
Don't tell me 39 stands for...
...the "saku" of "Yuusaku."
Correct!
Yuusaku, your grandma prepared your lunch, didn't she?
What? Did your grandma make this?
Yeah. My parents are on a business trip in Guam.
My grandma is staying at my place until they are back.
It's homemade... and it's this good?
She got a bit overzealous, and voilà.
Well, she really cherishes you.
I really appreciate that, but I think she is overdoing it a bit.
That being said, I thought you guys could help me out.
Huh?
Are you sharing it with us?
For real?
Yes.
She'd be sad if I didn't bring it back empty.
What should I start with?
I guess girls should be fine with this.
Bon appetit!
Wow! This is delicious!
So good!
That's your grandma for sure.
Yummy! I always have room for this food.
What's wrong? You should help yourself too, Takasu.
All right. I'll have this Karaage, then.
Taiga?
What's the matter, Aisaka?
No need to hold back.
T-Then I want...
...the lobster.
I can't believe you. Hold back a bit, will you?
So you were aiming for the main dish! And I was wondering why you were being so hesitant!
That's none of your business!
W-Well, still...
It's okay, help yourself.
So tasty! The more I eat the better it tastes!
This is like heaven on earth!
What happened to your own lunch?
I had mine, but there's always room for lobster!
This is the ultimate dish! It's something out of this world!
It doesn't only look good, but it's super tasty.
Takasu?
Yeah?
Can I take a picture of your lunch?
Why?
You know, I want to show my grandma what an ordinary lunch looks like.
I-It's pretty plain actually. I had to hurry this morning.
It's okay.
Thanks, Takasu.
I don't want them to know that this is the limit of my culinary skills!
Guys, you can eat as much as you want.
Lobsters are so stupid.
They wouldn't be eaten if they weren't this tasty.
Same with crabs,  right?
Damn Yuusaku... I ate way too much.
K-Kawashima.
Uh...
Yeah?
About Kitamura's grandma...
Is she a chef or something?
Like cooking is her occupation or something?
Right?
I think she's just a housewife.
Just a housewife...
Yeah, I think so.
By the way, what's her name?
Why should I know tha—
Gosh, that face!
You really scared me.
By the way, your wicked face made me remember...
Her name is Miyo.
"Mi" as in the year of the snake.
Miyo-chan, huh?
Let me see your best shot!
You asked for it!
Next time I'll show you my best creation, Miyo-chan!
Hey, are you all right?
Kitamura-kun!
Wanna eat together?
Your grandma made your lunch again, right?
Yeah.
But today...
It's a normal size.
Right. It should be cheap and effortless.
Just enough to fill the stomach of a high schooler.
Now that the rules are set, it will be a real match.
Let's see.
What's wrong?
All right, come and get me, Miyo-chan!
Whoa, that looks good, Takasu.
So you're having cutlets today.
Yeah. These are leftovers from yesterday.
I quickly wrapped them in egg when I got up this morning.
Nice. Let's see what I have today.
I wonder what he has.
Going for expensive ingredients for your cherished grandson even if it means stomping the rules?
Caviar? Or shark fin?
Huh?
T-That's pretty... simple.
I did say rice balls were fine...
She took it too literally.
This is too simple to be called a high schooler's lunch.
The victory is mi—
Hold on!
Why is it shining like that?
It's sesame oil!
In other words...
Wait, that's—
Yum!
It has fried meat inside! That's a pleasant surprise.
And this is Korean seaweed.
This is how I like it!
Oh, and plums!
And what's this?
Jackpot! Tuna and mayonnaise!
My favorite!
There he goes exulting.
Fried meat to excite him,
then the mandatory plums,
and his favorite tuna and mayonnaise as the icing...
She provided him with an extravagant variety.
In comparison to that, mine is just an appetizer.
The same, dull flavor.
Thanks, Ryuuji.
The cutlets with eggs were good.
Thanks.
Wow, those rice balls look tasty.
Perhaps I should have it for dinner.
Well, the cutlets were tasty, but eating them for two days is a bit tiring.
Y-Yeah, I know.
We just had too many left over.
No...
I was provoked by Miyo-chan's culinary skills and just wanted something extravagant.
But if I have to follow the rules of a high schooler's lunch box,
then I have to make a typical excuse.
Yes, I had to mix it with eggs.
Just for that reason I made cutlets last night.
A housewife must be aware of repetition.
Although I exaggerated a bit yesterday,
I got back on track now.
Miyo!
You're calling my grandma by name?!
Boxed lunch... Boxed lunch...
What should I do?
What flavor should I go with?
Boxed lunch...
Hey, what are we going to put into the rice balls?
Salmon is a must, right?
But the usual one is better than the salted—
Rice balls?!
I can't win by making the same lunch as Kitamura's!
I'm talking about dinner, not lunch.
That's not important.
I was very confident in my abilities as a housewife.
I had pride in my abilities.
What?
But, in the end, my limit was the level of a high schooler.
Once you aim higher, it gets so much harder to win.
I was just a frog in a pond,
thrown into the big ocean where a shark called Kitamura Miyo dwells.
Tuna sounds pretty good too.
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm doing the shopping since you aren't any help.
I'm not helping?
All you did was fill the cart with snacks and pudding.
So what? I put in tuna, too.
Oh, and that's our dessert.
By the way, did you know? If you put soy sauce on pudding, it tastes like melon.
That myth isn't just old, but also terribly wrong.
What? Really?
Hmm, not melon then... maybe watermelon?
I don't have time for this.
Oh right!
What a shark doesn't have, but a frog does...
That's...
Youth!
Hey, Taiga!
Do you know where Kitamura-kun is?
You have to fill it to 5 mm under the line.
Not a drop more or less.
It's almost there, almost!
Zip it already!
You're the one always bitching about me eating this.
What's that? Cup noodles?
Hey, Minorin.
You even brought a water boiler.
That's kinda cool!
You two rock!
What's up? Are you eating cup noodles?
How nice... I'm kinda sick of cold food.
That smells good!
Nice!
Looks tasty!
Eating that at home is normal,
but eating it in class is revolutionary.
I'm just spicing up my boring lunchtime.
Kitamura's grandma doesn't have a sense for what young people like.
Today's victory...
...is mine.
Minorin, aren't you eating with us?
Nah, there's a club meeting today.
Hey, hey! Kitamuraman!
Let's get going, man!
Sorry for the wait.
Hi, Kitamura.
I overslept a bit, so I'm going for cup noodles.
You have hot water?
Y-Yeah.
Then let me have some.
You're a life saver.
My grandma gave me instant soup.
She told me to borrow hot water from someone eating cup noodles.
I thought no one would bring hot water,
but I was lucky, I guess.
I've got this and a sandwich.
Perfect food for a meeting.
Kitamura-kun.
All right, let's go, Kushieda.
Catch you later, then.
Yeah.
A sandwich sounds good too.
Then don't eat it.
No, you can't.
What are you doing?
Huh? What's going on?
Don't eat it! No!
What's that supposed to mean?
Cup noodles don't have enough calcium.
Hot!
Sorry for the wait! I'm coming!
Not enough.
Not enough at all.
Just kidding.
I put them on another plate!
Thanks, Minorin!
No need to thank me.
If it's not enough, just tell me.
We have a lot.
Literally, a lot.
Great!
Do you think it's a good idea to eat carbs right after school?
Cup noodles aren't enough to fill me up.
Not to mention, I didn't even get to eat that.
You know...
Ryuuji's lunches are actually pretty good,
but he's trying too hard the past few days.
Oh, poor Taiga!
You can no longer live without Takasu Ryuuji feeding you?
What was that?
Just kidding.
Food is the basis of everything.
It's no wonder you like to get fed.
Anyway, enjoy your stay.
Boxed lunches...
No... This isn't it.
It's not supposed to be like this.
This isn't how it's supposed to be.
Wow, look at all this festive food.
It looks delicious.
But I can't eat that much.
Where's Taiga-chan?
Beats me.
Oh yeah, can I take some to work?
Yaegashi-san's wife ran away,
so I'm sure he'll be happy about this.
You're such a great cook.
I'm off!
Guess I should eat, then.
Yummy. Yummy.
She should eat here if she's at home.
I bet she's pissed about this afternoon.
Not that I can deal with her tantrums or anything.
I'll create the ultimate boxed lunch in order to defeat Kitamura Miyo!
No matter what tricks I have to use.
Like putting curry in hardened rice.
Bringing sashimi in a cool box and putting it on top of rice to make a seafood bowl.
Or going with something colorful like the ones you see on parties.
Stop making noises as if you were ravaging through the leftovers!
S-Seconds!
You want more?!
Hold on!
Leftovers?
I failed when I used the leftover cutlets wrapped in eggs.
Then I'll go with something fresh and steaming...
Got it.
That's it. That's the only thing.
In... In...
Cheater?
You can call me that for all I care.
Inzaghi.
Whatever.
Do you know Filippo Inzaghi?
Yeah, I don't care. I'll play dirty.
I'll overcome this ordeal!
H-Hot!
What's this smell?
What's this?
This is...
This sound...
You've got to be kidding.
This isn't what I think it is, is it?
But...
A rice cooker?
For real?
No way.
It smells pretty good, actually.
It smells delicious.
I'm getting hungry.
So...
Why did you bring it, Takasu-kun?
Takasu?
Hey, Taka-chan!
Stop cooking rice in here.
This is hilarious!
Hold on!
And you too, Teacher!
How did you know it was me?
Stop accusing me without proof!
Who else but you would do something like this?
Yes, it's me!
Please forgive me!
Don't unplug it!
It's almost done!
Have mercy!
W-What's going on?
Idiot.
It's over.
Such a waste.
If you turn it on, you can still eat it, no?
When you cook it again, it doesn't taste as good as before.
So what?
You have fallen as low as possible already.
The taste of autumn.
Sheep's head, oyster mushrooms and more mushrooms...
What?
I thought I could win by combining them with steamed rice.
That's no longer a boxed lunch.
I know.
I started with the rules first,
but I broke them first as well.
And I lost because of foul play.
So what?
You just brought this on yourself.
Here.
I saw it coming from miles away that we wouldn't
have anything decent for lunch today.
I'll give it to the stupid dog who hit a dead end.
Did you make these yourself?
Are you making fun of me?
Even I can make rice balls.
You taught me how to make them.
Hot!
Cooked rice is like a dangerous weapon!
Deal with it.
If it's not hot, it won't stick together.
See?
What?
H-Hot!
What? I won't give it to you if you don't want it.
No, I-I'll take it.
Thanks.
And?
What?
Are you shivering from joy or what?
So salty!
Let's soak it in tea.
Now it won't be as salty as before.
Whatever, just hurry up.
Don't be so impatient.
Let's put on some honeywort first.
Here you go.
Thanks!
Hey, don't forget to chew.
Yummy!
This is good!
The plum makes the difference.
I'm such a genius.
I see.
Yeah.
I'm a genius?
Yeah. Putting that ridiculous boxed lunch you'd only see in comics aside...
No, actually that too.
Miyo-chan made her lunches to make Kitamura happy.
She made the rice balls because Kitamura wanted them.
And the onion soup because she knew he had a meeting at lunch.
She was just thinking about him.
Yet I...
Thanks for the meal.
You're the one who eats my lunches, right?
What's that supposed to mean?
After eating a bit, I got even more hungry.
Now I feel like pigging out.
Cutlets sound great.
Cutlets in tea!
Eating cutlets three times in a week?
Oh, I have some sliced meat left.
That's it!
Mille-feuille cutlets!
We should reheat the rice too.
I'll eat it with cutlets.
Okay, okay.
Aren't you going to eat my rice balls with tea?
Nah, I'll eat them as they are.
The taste was a bit unexpected, but it's still edible.
Was that an insult to my cooking skills?
What? No.
Yes, it was.
So put cheese on the cutlets!
What?
I've learned the secret of boxed lunches.
The boxed lunch you make for someone special...
...will taste good, no matter what it is.