kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
Frankly speaking, this snow is a real pain!
Especially after Command said to pay close attention on patrols.
Yeah.
You still haven't given up on Jacott-san, have you?
It's not really like that.
Well, that's fine.
You search and search.
And if you still can't find it, you just have to hope for the best.
What?
Somehow, I thought you looked a little like Rio-senpai for a moment.
What's wrong?
Beneath the cliff, at 11 o'clock, about 400 meters away.
Hang in there.
Please hang in there!
Even her clothes are frozen!
Kanata, take off her coat.
So we can switch coats.
This girl is...
A Roman soldier?
A Burning Snow Field
A Visitor
To think you could actually restore this facility.
As expected of the greatest genius in the history of the Academy.
With this, our victory is assured.
It's all thanks to you, Kannagi Noël-kun.
Noël-chan?
They found her while on patrol.
A Roman soldier.
It looks like her left leg is fractured.
Hey, her fingers are turning black and red.
Frostbite.
If we aren't careful, she'll lose her fingers.
The Helvetian Witch.
Leave her to me!
It looks like she'll make it.
With all her fingers as well.
That's great.
Where's Noël-chan?
She said she'll stay with her for a while.
But I wonder what's going on.
It seemed like she was trying her hardest...
It's just like when she tries to fix Takemikazuchi.
It seems like it.
A bugle.
She could be a spy, of course.
But I was surprised.
Well, of course.
No one would think they'd meet a Roman soldier in a place like—
That's not it.
It's the first time I've seen a Roman.
Everyone calls them the enemy.
So I thought, at first, they'd be more like demons or something...
I'm sure they probably think the same about us in Rome.
But then,
when I saw her, I thought that Romans...
...didn't seem all that different.
Wait, Kanata, you—!
Hey, Kana-chan.
It's almost time for school lessons to end.
They're still disputing at the peace talks, aren't they?
So I've heard.
Will you report her?
If that happens, she'll be taken to Central and interrogated.
It can't be helped!
During these uneasy state of affairs, an enemy has invaded!
A soldier should be prepared for torture—
Interrogation.
How we're going to deal with her is my decision.
Please give me some time, Kureha-chan.
Don't forget, Commander.
We are soldiers.
Can I ask you something?
When you were carrying her here, did you meet anyone on the way?
I don't know. I was in a daze.
Understood. Thank you.
Hey, Rio...
What would you do?
A Helvetian soldier...
What were you going to do with this?
Where am I? Am I now a Helvetian prisoner?
I don't understand Roman.
So you have taken me prisoner—
What was that scream?
What happened?
She woke up.
That's great.
From the Roman Empire's ground forces, 1st Armored Division,
13th Armored Battalion, Company B,
Staff-Sergeant Aisha Aldora. ID 1031021.
Why did you come here?
Imperial Roman Army, Staff-Sergeant Aisha Aldora.
What is your mission?
ID 1031021.
You've got guts...
Well? Have you learned anything?
This is going nowhere!
It seems like she doesn't understand any Helvetian.
All we've learned is her ID number and that her name is Aisha.
I'm the officer in charge of this fort, 2nd Lieutenant Filicia Heideman.
You have really nice breasts. The kind I really like.
Would you mind if I rub them?
Is it okay if I fondle your whole body?
Wh-Wh-What are you saying all of a sudden, Commander?
It looks like she really doesn't understand Helvetian.
But this is a predicament.
We can't interrogate her like this.
We have to hurry and find someone who can speak Roman.
Then...
Until we can interrogate her and write up a report,
we'll let her stay with the platoon.
But!
It's just for a bit. I thought I'd bet on something.
If anything happens, I'm not a part of this.
Aisha-chan, welcome to the Time-Trumpeting Fort.
"Time-Trum-pet-ing Fort"?
Yes, Time-Trumpeting Fort.
I see! So I actually arrived.
Grandmother.
Huh? Is it too hot?
She ate it!
Is it good?
To escape, you need strength. That's why I'm going to eat now.
I'm sure she said it's good.
What's going on? It's normal for Kanata, but for Noël to be so attached...
It could be... atonement.
Well! Have you ever seen a fossilized angel?
"Engel"?
Right, you don't understand a word.
I should have studied Roman.
That's true. If we could just
understand what she's saying...
We got a lot, didn't we?
Oh, Yumina-chan.
Do you have enough people to shovel the snow at the church?
Yes. The children are all helping.
That's good to hear.
I guess they aren't always little brats.
Yes.
People grow everyday.
Just like Kanata-san's bugle.
Rio would say she still has a ways to go though.
Oh? Weren't you staying in Treize?
A lot happened. It ended up being futile.
There's been a lot of difficulties there.
Come to think of it, I heard this horrible rumor about the fort.
Thank you for listening.
It sounds nice.
I didn't know that these trumpets still exist.
May I?
I think Rio-senpai would have let you as well.
A nice trumpet. To be able to see something like this—
Hey, that song!
Amazing! This is so wonderful!
Iliya-san's song resounds inside me, and it resounds inside Rio-senpai as well!
And the same song isn't just in Helvetia, but it resounds in Rome too!
Sound resounds, doesn't it?
Whether it's in Rome or Helvetia, it's the same.
First-aid.
Thank you.
"Danke"?
Precisely, thank you.
I wonder what "danke" is.
It means "thank you."
So we were seen after all...
This town hasn't experienced the full effects of the war.
But whether it is a parent, a child, or a relative, everyone has lost someone to the war.
It's always been peaceful, but it'll become miserable.
Do you remember Mikhail, the boss of that liquor store?
I was at his place until yesterday.
It appears that the Helvetian Army is undergoing a large-scale movement...
...and is heading towards this region.
If it's related to that Roman soldier being in this remote place, it's a serious matter.
Be that as it may, we can't ask her about it.
Naomi-san, do you know of anyone who speaks Roman?
Do I know of anyone?
My name is Yumina.
I am a servant of the Helvetian Orthodox Church.
May you be blessed a thousandfold with luck.
So, you're just one of those heretics.
There is but one true god. Such a greeting is blasphemy.
What did she say?
A simple greeting.
That's fine. Just hurry up and ask her.
Why are you here?
If you keep quiet, it will be a great bother for everyone here.
If you're the least bit thankful, then you should speak openly with us.
I'm not allowed to talk about my mission.
The reason I came here is to see the fossilized angel that's supposed to be in this town.
She said she came to see the Angel Fossil.
"Angel Fossil"?
What's that?
My grandmother... in that fortress... she was in that fortress.
"My grandmother was a soldier at the Time-Trumpeting Fort."
She was captured at the eastern front and met my grandfather.
"She was taken prisoner at the eastern battle lines and met my grandfather."
When I was still a child, she often told me about it.
"I grew up listening to her stories."
I had to see it once at all costs—the angel that my grandmother saw.
The Angel of the Apocalypse that brought judgement upon the world long ago.
That doctrine is wrong!
It was a demon that came to destroy the world!
It's all right. What exactly did she say?
She wanted to see the Angel of the Apocalypse that had destroyed the world.
That's why she came.
A signal to march.
This code is...
1st Royal Guard, 9th Independent Mobile Division.
The 9th...? It can't be. Colonel Hopkins?!
Is he a famous person?
He's called "The Devil of Vingt."
They say he revived weapons from the previous age and wiped out three cities in one night.
It's all right.
He doesn't know you're here.
At any rate, you should be worried.
It will be bad for you if you don't decide what to do fast, right?
If you hand her over—
There's no need to worry!
We are Helvetian soldiers!
I lost the bet.
You didn't make it in time did you, Rio?
Please wait!
Rio-senpai didn't want anyone else to suffer.
That's why she did what she could do.
Isn't that why she left?
But I still don't like this.
Even though everyone's the same!
Even though everyone's together!
I will now give an order as the
commander of the 1121st Platoon.
Furthermore, this order is my own judgement.
I am taking full responsibility for any consequences of this order.
Understood, everyone?
I am the commander of the 1121st Platoon, 2nd Lieutenant Filicia Heideman.
A few days ago, a Roman spy was captured in Treize.
Unfortunately, there was an accident before we could interrogate, so we couldn't confirm anything.
By coincidence, we received information that a Roman soldier was seen in Seize.
Do you know anything about this?
I do not, Colonel.
Understood.
Listen up! The 1121st's fort is now under the command of my 9th Independent Mobile Division!
Don't shout like that all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
Aisha-san was telling me about the legend of the Flame Maidens, but...
It's strange. She says that...
Do a thorough search!
Do you see them?!
How about there?
There's nothing here.
Search every corner!
Open up!
She should be here somewhere.
Cover the exits!
She says she hasn't asked for your name yet, Noël.
Her name is Noël.
Noël?
Noël Kannagi?
Yes.
She is... the Invisible Reaper?
"The Invisible Reaper"?
Is it a rat?
Noël-san!
H-Hello?
This is the 1121st Platoon.
A large Roman army has appeared on the border of Seize and Nomansland?!
Let’s remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let’s move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You’re just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know you know we’ll be happy!
let’s make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you count my precious hours?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
Resound into the Azure Sky
Next time: Resound into the Azure Sky