Sorry about the other day.
Don't worry about it.
My mom keeps telling me
I stay out too late as well.
That's what mothers do.
They live to nag and complain.
And with the whole
entrance exams thing lately,
Komachi and Mom have been
at each other's throats.
Oh, right. Komachi has her exams tomorrow.
We're even getting
the day off because of it.
Knowing her, she'll probably be fine.
Yeah.
But as her brother,
you must be worried, right?
You can say that again.
I mean, Komachi's really cute, so she'll definitely be popular,
which means she'll have to
be wary around guys,
and she'll need to keep people from finding out
she has a good-for-nothing brother like me.
It could ruin her reputation.
That's what you're worried about?
And you act like she passed already!
I can't tell if you're an optimist or pessimist.
Hey, did you make those yourself?
Y-Yes.
I happened to bake them last night.
Oh.
I've been trying my best too, but no luck.
For you.
Wow, thanks!
Er... just me?
Why am I looking away?
What about Hikki?
Have some if you'd like.
Th-Thanks.
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something genuine
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Later.
Yeah, see you.
Er...
Um...
Well, I'm off.
Uh...
What do we do about this?
I'm here to pick you up, Yukino.
Sis?
I don't think there's anything
you'd need me for.
Mom told me to stay with you for a while.
Why all of a sudden?
Oh, I think you know why.
That's something I have to do myself.
It's none of your business.
Do you even have a "self"?
You've been following in
my footsteps all along.
Do you really have
thoughts to speak of?
You've always been left free
to do as you please,
but you've never made
any decisions of your own.
Even now, you have no idea how to act.
What exactly do you want to do?
Could you take this
sibling spat elsewhere?
I wouldn't call this a spat.
We've never actually fought, you know.
Either way, it's not a discussion
to be had in public.
U-Um...
We really are giving it serious thought...
Both Yukinon and me.
Is that so?
Well, tell me all about it
when you get home.
Not like there's anywhere else
you could go, anyway.
E-Er...
Wanna come over to my place?
They did tell me to come along,
but what am I doing here?
I'm sorry.
I've caused you trouble.
Not at all. Don't let it bother you.
She's right.
There's nothing to worry about.
You're Hikki, right?
R-Right.
Yui's told me so much about you.
Mom!
Don't go running your mouth!
I wanna talk to Hikki, too!
Give it a rest!
Oh, I know.
Yukino's going to stay over, right?
She'll need a mat—
I can take care of that!
Sorry about that.
Looks like she's really happy you came over.
She's usually not this excited.
How embarrassing.
Nah.
You two must be close.
I'm a little envious of that.
Given how her mother and sister are,
it'd be hard for anyone, let alone Yukinoshita, to maintain a healthy relationship with them.
Sorry. Forget I said anything.
I'll be leaving now.
Hey, about that...
Why don't you stay the night?
B-But...
I sleep over at your place all the time, and everybody
has times when they don't wanna go home.
Well, you two probably can't talk it out with cool heads right now,
so why don't you take tonight
to think things over?
Let her know, just in case.
Yup. That might be good.
Yeah, you're right.
Hello?
We probably can't talk it out
with cool heads right now,
so I'll take tonight to think things over
and come talk to you later.
Letting you know, just in case.
Did she just...
Oh? Very well.
Hikigaya must be there with you, right?
Give him the phone.
Sis wants to talk to you.
What is it?
You're so nice, Hikigaya.
Still up?
I am.
What do you wanna do?
I...
Well, I know what I want to do.
I've made up my mind.
Tomorrow,
we're going on a date.
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
Come again?
Man, it's freezing!
Do you have your exam ID?
An eraser? Handkerchief? Spare pencil?
I'm good.
I shall be on my way, then!
Okay. Go break a leg.
Sine, cosine, tangent...
Looks like it's gonna snow all day today.
Incoming call:
Yui
Hikki, let's go on a date!
Uh, if I'm being the third wheel, I can leave.
It's fine.
I want the three of us to go.
The Sea Life Park?
You okay with here?
Yup! We won't have to worry
about the snow in here.
Whoa, sharks!
Sharks, eh?
Sorry I didn't tell you, Yukinon.
Come on, let's enjoy this.
Easier said than done.
Wow, hammerhead sharks!
Wait, you're allowed to
take pictures here?
Uh huh!
See? Hikki seems to be having fun, too.
Wh-What?
I was just a little surprised, is all.
I can take a picture of
you with the sharks.
For real?
Komachi's gonna be so jealous.
This is a "nurseryfish," apparently.
It says they live in muddy streams and don't swim much.
And they gobble up prawns and stuff that try to pass by.
Living the dream.
You're empathizing with them?!
Now that you mention it, this fish
does resemble a certain someone.
Right, Fishigaya?
We're not the least bit similar,
and neither are our names.
So gross.
Don't say that. They're living life
to the best of their ability.
But also kinda cute.
I don't know if you can call them "cute,"
but they certainly are endearing.
I'm pretty sure "cute" went out the window
the moment you called them gross.
A dogfish shark!
It's kinda like Sable.
How?
Catsharks? This makes no sense.
Surely they must resemble cats in some way if they're to take their name.
She has to react to anything
with "cat" in its name, huh?
She does have a pesky,
frisky love of cats, after all.
I guess it does feel like
a cat's tongue to the touch.
That's just what shark skin's like, woman.
Oh, there's a ray too.
I just felt something slimy!
What did you touch? Was it Hikigaya?
You'd better wash your hands.
Hello?
Could you stop treating me like a ray?
I don't discharge mucus
from my skin, okay?
Cat... Catsharks... Cat...
Meow...
Or would it be "sha"?
Just because they're sharks,
it doesn't mean they go all "sha."
What? Are you done already?
Yep. I wouldn't want to wear them out by touching too much.
I see. That's just like you.
What's "just like me"?
I'm not the nice girl you make me out to be.
Penguins!
Let's go, you guys!
Oh my god, they're adorable!
I need to take pics and
send them to Komachi.
Wow, they're swimming!
Doesn't this make you think
they're birds or something?
Uh, penguins are birds.
Shining in that blue sky
I-I totally knew that.
Humboldt Penguins
An airplane flies off into the horizon
.
What's up?
Something I kept caged in my heart starts stirring
I'll wait inside.
I lock away the feelings I want to express
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
.
Have you noticed two of the penguins cuddling?
Those two are actually mates. Once two Humboldt penguins mate,
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies.
They show their affection by grooming their partner's body
and calling out to them. We hope you enjoy observing the couple's behavior.
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies
.
And replace them with words I cannot say
they tend to stay with the same partner until one of them dies
.
I couldn't be honest until the end
Where's Yuigahama?
Taking pics of the fairy penguins.
Oh.
I tangled up the thread connecting us
Some are left free
all by themselves, I see.
Yeah. That one's pretty big, after all.
And cut you loose
Unable to find a place to belong
without a pillar of support...
If I'd told you I was sorry
Hiding in the crowd, going with the flow,
and following in others' footsteps...
Until eventually running into
an invisible wall.
Before those tears fell
Which fish are you talking about?
Myself.
If I'd told you I wanted to see you
Sorry to keep you guys waiting!
Don't you think these are like fireworks?
Before that vapor trail disappeared
Really?
Can't you see it?
Like, that one there.
It's going "pew, pop, pop, pop".
Maybe I could've avoided this endless heartbreak
Maybe I could've been here with you
Hello, hello, alone
You're too close.
I'm really glad we got to see this.
The three of us, together.
Made it to the finish line!
Hey, wanna take another lap?
Hell no. There's no point in
going to the same places again.
Y-Yeah. And I'm somewhat tired now.
Really? I think it'd be fun.
Besides, we still have time.
Hiding its instability,
it slowly continues to turn.
Instead of making any progress,
it simply goes around in circles.
Even so, eventually...
It's almost over.
What are we gonna do from now on?
Go home, obviously.
That's not what I meant.
About Yukinon.
And me.
And us.
What do you mean?
Hikki.
Here.
As thanks for back then.
Remember my request?
Handmade cookies?
You made these by yourself?
They didn't come out as good
as I hoped, though.
You're amazing, Yuigahama.
I said I'd try to do it myself—
try to do it my own way—
and this is the result.
So these are just a token of my gratitude.
You already repaid me for that.
Even so,
these are just a token of my gratitude.
I want it all.
What we have now,
and what we'll have in the future.
I'm a coward. I play dirty.
But I've made up my mind.
Really...
If we figure out how each of us feels,
I don't think we'll be able to stay the same.
So this is the final request.
Our final task
is to fix our problems.
Say, Yukinon.
Is that battle still on?
It is. The winner can order the loser to do anything they want.
I know how to solve the problem you're facing right now, Yukinon.
I'm pretty sure that's the solution to our problem as well.
And so,
when I win, I'll take it all.
She didn't specify a thing.
Putting it into words would confirm it for all of us,
so she kept avoiding it.
It may not be fair, but this is all I could think of.
I want us to stay this way forever.
What do you think?
Yuigahama probably won't go wrong.
I get the feeling she alone has been
looking at the right answers all along.
And I'm sure accepting her proposal
would make things easier for all of us.
However...
Are you okay with that, Yukinon?
I...
Yeah, now this is wrong.
Yukinoshita leaving her future
in someone else's hands
is absolutely unacceptable.
I...
I wouldn't min—
No.
I can't accept your proposal.
Yukinoshita ought to solve her problems herself.
"Yuigahama Yui is a nice girl."
I decided that regardless of its veracity.
"Yukinoshita Yukino is a strong girl."
And so, I burdened her with
the ideal image I had of her.
Besides, that's nothing but...
Nothing but deceit.
I don't want any vague answers or superficial relationships.
Yeah, I'm being stupid.
I know that it's out of the question.
I know how this will end.
I'll be left with nothing.
Even so, I want us to think, writhe, struggle,
and find...
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Don't you tell me how I feel.
Also, this isn't the final anything.
Hikigaya.
We still have your request.
It doesn't matter if we're wrong,
because every time we go wrong,
we'll continue to look for the right answer.
One more thing...
I have a request.
Would you care to listen to it?
Spring Always Comes to Life
Buried Underneath a Pile of Snow.
Sure. Let's hear it.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever