This is Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
She went on her first job as
the singer, Full Moon,
but she kept messing everything up
trying to come off as grown-up.
And immediately made
everyone mad!
But after talking to a bunch
of high school girls,
she realized she didn't have
to try too hard to be mature.
And work got easier and
ended well, soon after.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
I want to go, too!
You can't! You have to transform
into Mitsuki and stay here.
Otherwise, she wouldn't be able to escape
the eyes of that old lady and go out.
But, there's been nothing
like this before, right?
It wasn't convenient for
Dr. Wakaoji today.
In other words,
somebody has to take her place.
I have to transform her
into a sixteen-year-old,
so there's no way, right?
So you're the only one, Meroko.
But...
Meroko, please.
Today is the recording of
my important debut song.
So...Please?
Fine.
Really?!
But there'll be a time
when she'll stay home for once...
- And then Takuto and I can go out, right?
- All right, let's go.
Hey, did they just ignore me?!
It's this studio, right?
Wooow.
There are tons of fans.
I wonder who in the world is here.
Who cares who it is?
More importantly...
What? Who is it?
Who is it?
Hey, Wait!
Say-say,
those are the Guitar Fighters.
They're going to be recording now.
Awesome!
Hey-hey.
Didn't you come to record, too?
What?!
But... But...
Jeez.
Let's go.
Okay, we're going in.
Hey, Mitsuki!
Oh, Ms. Oshige!
What're you doing?
Over here, over here!
Get over here, quick.
O-Okay!
Oh, my.
Everyone's watching.
It won't do a person who's going to be
a singer any good to act like that.
Right.
A talking stuffed toy?
How's it going?
Were you able to sleep yesterday?
Yes, for the time being.
That's good.
Let's do our best today.
Right.
Okay, go on in.
Wow...
I'm overwhelmed.
Oh, sorry.
Let me introduce you.
This is Miss Full Moon, and she will
start recording from today!
Oh, I'm Full Moon.
Nice to meet you all!
We look forward
to working with you!
Hang in there, Mitsuki.
I will.
Ouch. Are you nervous?
Oh. I'm sorry, Takuto.
Don't worry, I'll be watching you.
Okay.
Ow-ow-ow.
Will she be okay?
Miss Full Moon.
This way, please.
Oh, okay!
Then, it's a promise.
No matter what,
watch me from here, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
Hey!
Yipes!
Oh! It's you guys.
You're here again.
You'll get no sympathy
if you're found out.
Enough about that.
Did you see a young girl
carrying a stuffed toy cat?
A cat?
Oh, the girl who went
into that studio earlier.
Who's Full Moon?
She's the newcomer, right?
Really?
Full Moon, eh?
It's kind of quiet, isn't it?
It's been soundproofed to
not pick up any excess noise.
Is that so?
Is the position of the microphone
okay like this?
Oh, this is fine...I think.
Then, please wait a moment.
So this is where
I'm going to sing.
Takuto.
Excuse me.
We're going to
test the microphone.
Could you give us a sound?
Oh, umm...
Umm, can you hear me?
Yes, we can.
It's okay.
Oh, Mr. Takasu.
Hi.
How's it going?
I'm managing...
For now, let's sing "Myself" once.
Okay.
Okay, sound, please.
Let's see.
First, put on the headphones.
Headphones?
Listen to the music with
the headphones and sing along with that.
Oh, is that so?
This is the real deal, isn't it?
She's an interesting kid.
I'm sorry.
It's her first time, after all.
Well, she's new,
so let's take our time.
Thank you very much.
This looks like it's going
to take a while.
Why do I...
...like you...so much?
Your voice echoes and
sounds almost sad...
Up to now—
Oh, hold on a minute!
When you start singing
the peak of the song,
express the feelings you had
when you wrote this, honestly.
Honestly?
Right.
Don't try to sing well.
Sing with your genuine feelings.
All right...
Okay, it's about time to record.
Ah...
Kitty-cat!
Oh, Takuto?
What? A date now?
Sure. I'll go, I'll go!
Where are you going to take me?
What? Really?
Oh, Takuto.
So you loved me that much, huh?!
Me? Of course, I do, too.
Won't it turn out like
that for once?
Uh-oh.
At this rate I won't be able
to go outside!
What? Takuto?
It looks like you're still a little nervous.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, we have some adjustments to make.
So we'll take a break.
Okay.
Are you thirsty Mitsuki?
How about some coffee?
Ms. Oshige, do you know where
the stuffed toy cat that was here is?
Stuffed toy?
Yes.
What're you doing?
Oh, it's all of the Guitar Fighters.
Um, as a matter of fact...
Are you the new girl?
Yeah. You're Full Moon, right?
How old are you?
Umm...
I-I'm looking for a stuffed toy cat.
Do you know where it is?
A stuffed toy cat?
Beats me.
Oh. Come to think of it, Nanami
might've had something like that earlier.
Really?
Where did that girl go?
Where?
Maybe she already went home.
What?!
Do you know where her house is?
I don't know that much.
I see.
Takuto.
Hm? Where am I?
Oh. You woke up, kitty-cat?
Whoa.
Talk to Nanami!
Come on.
- Come on.
- Ow-ow-ow!
Idiot. That hurt!
You talked.
Give me a break.
See ya.
What?! Kitty-cat?
Where are you? Where'd you go?
Kitty-cat's vanished.
Give me a break!
Kitty-cat!
Now I won't be able
to get back to her.
Where is that Takuto?
What should I do?
When you want me at your side,
blow on this whistle and call me.
I'll rush over.
What? There's no sound?
She's calling.
Kitty-cat, don't talk to yourself.
Talk with Nanami.
Say something.
Ow-ow-ow! What're you doing?!
Oh, you talked.
Are you happy I talked?!
Yeah, I'm happy.
If you're happy,
then is it okay if I go?
Sorry, but I'm busy.
No.
Why?!
Cuz' kitty-cat's my friend.
Don't make me into
your friend without asking.
Oh, this'll happen if you say
things like that.
Ow-ow!
Okay! Okay! Just stop it!
Then, let's play together.
Jeez, she's worse than Meroko.
I'm bothered by terrible kitchen grease.
- I'm bored...
- In times like that, use...
- Oh. They still haven't come home.
- the scrubbing brush of the new century!
No matter how—
Come on. Who turned on the TV?
Oh... It wasn't me.
Hey, you're not even
going to let me watch TV?
By the way, what's Mitsuki up to,
Mrs. Tanaka?
Yes. I'll go check
the detached room right away.
Give me a break!
That girl did well, putting up with this
for as long as she has.
What'll happen if I can't find Takuto?
Sure enough, this whistle is broken!
I can hear it!
Takuto!
Hi.
Takuto...
Jeez, what in the world...
Hey, kitty-cat.
Don't move around without asking.
Oh!
Can you give that toy back to me?
No. It's mine, you see.
But, that's really mine.
No, it's mine.
Takuto.
I don't get it, either.
So your name's Takuto, kitty-cat?
Say, Takuto.
You're Nanami's friend, right?
You took me away while I was sleeping
without asking
and you're calling me your friend?
While you were sleeping?
That's terrible, Takuto.
Didn't you say you'd be listening?
Oh, you were still practicing
at that time, right?
I was awake
when you started recordi—
Speaking of which,
what about the recording?
When I called earlier,
they said they were still making
preparations and that it was okay.
Hey, don't talk to
my Takuto all friendly like that.
You know Nanami, Takuto is mine.
Then, show me proof.
I don't have proof... But he's mine.
You're Full Moon the singer, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Shouldn't you be getting back
to the studio pretty soon?
I can't sing
if you don't give me back Takuto.
Talking like a kid.
But...
Where are you going?
My house.
I see.
This is my house.
What?
Let's go inside, okay Takuto?
Takuto, what should
we do to play?
Nanami, shouldn't you be getting home?
It's okay.
Your mom and dad will be worried.
No, they won't.
Why?
I don't have a mom and dad.
Huh?!
You don't have a mom or dad?
Yup.
So you're all alone?
Nanami.
All right!
Takuto, let's go.
This is fun!
Let's go one more time.
Come to think of it,
when Eichi left, I also...
All right! All right!
Here we go!
Is that fun, Nanami?
Yeah, it is.
I see...
So you were lonesome, right?
No, I wasn't.
You're lying.
You were lonesome,
so you took Takuto away, right?
Then, if I say that I'm lonesome,
it's okay if I don't give Takuto back?
What?
Is it okay if I stay with
Takuto forever?
Well...
Just kidding.
What?
Everything I said was a lie.
What?!
My mom and dad are over there.
S-Say what?
Wait, Nanami.
See? That's my mom and dad.
You're not going to say
that's a lie too, are you?
Really?
Oh.
Nanami.
You're total is 933 yen.
Okay. Out of 1000 yen.
I wonder what I should have.
If you have a mom,
why doesn't she make food for you?
She's busy, you see.
Is that really your mom and dad?
Oh, I'll have this.
Yup, that's really them.
But they didn't say anything
even when you came into the store.
It's always like that.
Always?
Every day.
You eat by yourself every day
in that way?
That's right.
Every day?
This makes no sense.
If they're your real mom and dad,
why don't they say anything?
Why?
If it were a real family, you'd say,
"I'm home," when you come home...
and they'd say, "Welcome home"
isn't it true?
If I had a mom and dad,
I'd also want them to say
"Welcome home" after I said "I'm home."
You HAVE a mom and dad.
Why?!
She's...
Nanami.
I want them to do that, too...
I want to talk a lot with mom and dad!
But...they're always busy.
I... I...
Nanami!
Mom!
Mom, Mom!
We're sorry, Nanami...
I'm sorry we didn't look after you.
We're sorry.
Forgive us.
Nanami...
Dad!
I'm happy for you, Nanami.
Here... I'm sorry I took Takuto
without asking.
Good grief...
I was wondering what would happen.
Nanami, how about going to
the recording session together?
What?
And not in secret this time.
Yeah!
Nice.
Her honest feelings are coming out.
Yes.
By the way, who's that kid?
I'm Full Moon's first fan!
What?
Well, it's okay, isn't it?
Clothes ready! Makeup ready!
Takuto, what are we going to do?
Will she be able to sing all right?!
What are you getting excited about?
It's not like you're gonna sing or anything!
That's true, but it's her debut day!
Meroko's worried.
Well, we did everything we could,
all we have to do is sit back
and watch what happens.
Or...maybe she'll get
into trouble again?!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Full Moon Debuts!"
- Look forward to it!