Bl-Blue...
Fumizuki Academy is a new school that has implemented unique, first-in-the-world educational systems.
Please begin.
One of these systems is the Summoned Being Exam War.
These are battles between students from different classes that utilizes "summoned beings," made possible by the most advanced technology.
Another is the division of classes based upon exam scores.
The Placement Exam is given out after the end of the first year.
According to their scores, the students are assigned to one of six classes, from Class A, the best, to Class F, the worst.
So this is the Placement Exam, eh? It really is difficult, but I can do this!
Himeji-san!
Are you all right, Himeji-san? Get a hold of yourself!
Leaving in the middle of the exam will result in a zero. No objections, right?
Wait, Sensei!
What's the problem, Yoshii-kun?
She can't help it!
Yoshii-kun!
You're late, Yoshii!
Ugh! Iron Man.
I'm not Iron Man! Address me as Nishimura-sensei!
Here, you're the last one.
The results of the Placement Exam.
From today onwards, that will be your class.
I got it.
Yoshii, I'll tell you something.
Over the past year that I've been watching over you,
I have had suspicions about whether or not you were an idiot.
However, after seeing the exam score, I completely realized my mistake.
I'm so sorry, Yoshii,
for doubting you. I was wrong.
You... really are, without a doubt, a complete idiot.
Sign: Stamp - Try harder next time!
Fumizuki Academy is a new school that has implemented unique, first-in-the-world educational systems.
What the heck? Class F? Isn't that the worst one?
And I was so confident that I did well on the Placement Exam...
I was sure that I got at least one in every ten questions.
Fumizuki Academy is a new school that is outfitted with the newest and most exuberant equipment.
Whoa! System desks and reclining chairs!
And they even have individual laptops?!
An open bar? Doesn't that mean they can eat snacks whenever they want? Class A is like Heaven!
Tatami. Cushion. Small tea table.
This is Class F's setup?
Fumizuki Academy is a very harsh school.
If one wants to have a decent learning environment, then one must get good grades.
This is the fate of the students who attend the academy!
Damn... This is the so-called social stratification.
Yoshii-kun, hurry up and take your seat.
I got it. Where do I sit?
Just choose any of the empty ones.
The seats aren't even assigned?
Sign: Surprised
Um, Sensei, my seat cushion doesn't have any cotton left.
Please bear with it.
Sensei, the wind blowing from the broken window is very cold.
Sensei, one of the tea table's legs snapped.
Please bear with it.
Bear your sister!
I'm just joking.
TL Note: It's a bottle of wood glue.
Fumizuki Academy really is harsh!
Um... I am Class F's homeroom teacher, Fukuhara.
Students, let's have a great year.
I'll go grab some tools. Everyone, have a self-study session.
What an unbearable classroom.
So I have to live with this for a year, eh...
How humiliating.
If you're unsatisfied, then go get better scores on the Placement Exam.
Yuuji? You're in Class F too?
There are others, too!
Hello. Hello. I'm also in Class F.
Shimada-san! I see, of course Shimada-san is in Class F.
Are you trying to say that I'm an idiot?
Rage Meter
Ow, Ow, Ow! Since you're so flat... My ears are rubbing against your ribs... It hurts so much more than normal!
I can... I can almost see it. Almost.
I'm a returning exchange student. I just wasn't able to read the word problems.
Just as lively as always.
Eh? Hideyoshi?
I'm also in Class F. Nice to see you again.
You, as well.
But... it really is the class of the people with the lowest scores.
From looking around, it seems to just be a bunch of incompetent people.
You're one of them.
But how great. The only girl is a beautiful one like Hideyoshi.
I'm a guy.
I'm a girl...
You just don't understand.
The so-called girls are kind and caring.
People who have an aura around them that can heal others—
Shimada-san is rough, violent, scary, and flat.
Ah, my joints are going to dislocate! The pain!
Um, sorry I'm late.
I'm late because I stopped by the nurse's office.
Himeji-san...
Yoshii-kun.
Why is she in this class?
All right!
Yoshii-kun.
What is it, Himeji-san?
Doesn't that hurt?
Ah! My spine's already been bent pretty far! It's dangerous! Please spare me. If you bend anymore—
I can see it... I can see it...
Ah! If you continue, it'll snap!
Ninja Pervert! Pull yourself together!
Don't talk now! I'll go and get the doctor right this instant!
Aqua blue...
Ninja Pervert!
How great, there's another girl in here.
There are no assigned seats, so sit wherever you want.
Ninja Pervert! Be strong, I'll save you!
All right. Thank you.
Someone save him!
Doctor! Where is the doctor?!
Um... Is that seat empty?
Eh? Yeah, it is. Please sit there.
So, Himeji-san was also assigned to Class F.
Let's work hard together, Yoshii-kun.
Your health still hasn't improved?
Yeah, I'm still a little sick.
Crappy, wind-leaking class room. Thin as hell cushions.
Dust-and-mold-covered tatami.
It's a pretty good environment, if you like living in the dark.
So? What is it?
I've been thinking about it.
Isn't school supposed to reflect the real world?
There shouldn't be this kind of class segregation!
But we, being at the bottom, will be considered failures no matter what.
Therefore, we should properly challenge our opponents.
After we gain power and are in a position to talk, then we'll announce this problem to soci—
In other words, you want to raise the quality of the class's setup for Himeji-san, right?
I didn't want to say it like that because it's embarrassing!
Why did you just say it so directly?!
Why not? To be honest, I was thinking about doing the same thing.
You too?
Yup. I want to show the world that grades don't mean everything.
Furthermore, we have a winning chance.
Want to start a war, Akihisa?
Yup. Let's do it, the Summoned Being Exam War.
Summoned Being Exam War
Everyone, listen up!
As the Class F representative, I'd like to propose something.
I want to start a Summoned Being Exam War.
What?
A Summoned Being Exam War? Don't tell me—
Fumizuki Academy has a battle system called the Summoned Being Exam War, or Summoned Being War for short.
Under the supervision of teachers,
students can call forth Summoned Beings,
whose attack abilities are based off of the scores that the students last received on the chosen subject.
Through this Summoned Being Exam War, if a class defeats another higher-ranking class, they can swap classroom setups with the loser.
Fellow students! Aren't you unsatisfied with this ghetto classroom?!
Very unsatisfied!
So, if we become victorious,
we'll be able to get the high-class setup that Class A has.
We are stuck at the bottom.
The very bottom of this academy!
We are the ones who nobody even glances at, the trash amongst the lowest of the low.
In other words, we don't have anything to lose!
We can only go up!
In addition, we have this guy on our side!
Eh?
The guy here, Yoshii Akihisa, is actually the Probate!
Sign: Probate
Probate?!
That's so cool!
This is the first time I've seen him!
I'm in despair!
It's really nothing.
What is it, Himeji?
Is being the Probate amazing?
Yeah it is, not everyone can be one.
It's a special accommodation given to those problem children who not only have bad scores but also lack academic abilities.
A euphemism for idiot.
In other words, a piece of trash.
Eh?! That really is amazing.
Ah! I want to hide in a hole!
If we can stand victorious in the war, then we can say goodbye to this shitty classroom.
How about it, guys? Want to go for it?!
First, we'll go for the slightly higher Class E.
Akihisa, go be the Class F ambassador and declare war on Class E.
What? Me?
Don't people who declare war from the weaker side usually get treated badly?
That only happens in movies and novels.
No one's going to do preposterous things to the highly respected ambassadors.
But...
Akihisa, this is an important mission that only you can complete.
Just pretend you got tricked and go.
I really did get tricked!
So it did happen.
You were expecting this?
If I didn't even postulate this, I couldn't be a representative.
At least look guilty about it!
Well, there's no backing off now, Akihisa.
Be prepared for it.
Isn't this what you wanted?
Yep, let them come any time!
Oh? Are the sophomores this year already starting Summoned Being Exam Wars in the first semester?
Interesting. Allow it!
Yes, madam.
Well then, what will happen?
Show me, eh?
Sign: Please provide approval for the Summoned Being Exam War under the rules of the school regulated "Summoned Being Exam War for class facility take over and recapture."
We will base the battle around Hasegawa-sensei.
As he walks towards Class E during 5th period, capture him.
Speaking of Hasegawa-sensei, he teaches mathematics, right?
If it's math, I'm very good at it.
Then we'll use Shimada's math skills as the primary attack force.
Himeji-san, what about your math?
It's not my weak point.
Then Himeji-san can fight too.
No, she can't.
Why?
The Summoned Being's attack power is based off of the most recent exam scores.
Our most recent exam was the...
Placement Exam.
Because I left in the middle of the exam, I received a zero on it.
But during the Summoned Being War, one can take a Recovery Exam.
Recovery Exam
If it's accepted, Himeji can enter in the middle of the war.
Yes sir.
Good luck.
Yes.
We've captured Hasegawa-sensei!
The war starts now! All students, prepare for battle!
Sign: CLASS F
Seriously. For a bunch of idiots, they sure are arrogant.
Let's head out, everyone!
Sign: CLASS E
Beat the crap out of Class F!
Shimada Minami, heading out!
Kinoshita Hideyoshi, joining in!
Tsuchiya Kouta, also participating.
Battle allowed!
Summoned Being,
summon!
Summon!
Why was I the only one with a transformation sequence?
They're coming!
Please be careful, you can't just jump in and rush past.
If you want to go through, then you must defeat us.
Mikami Yoshiko, taking you on!
Summon!
This guy...
Finishing attack!
That's my line!
No way...
If it's math, I won't lose to Class E.
Those who died, gather at the infirmary!
That's...
Iron Man.
Summon War Axiom
Zero points
According to the rules of the Summoned Being Exam War, those who have lost all their points or have "died" will receive make up work!
Make up work
Save me! I don't want the hellish make-up work!
Want to pass through here? Then you must defeat us!
Is that so? Then, I'll do just that.
Summon!
Let's do this!
Please start when you're ready.
What's your strategy, Yuuji?
There's no strategy.
Eh?
We're just fighting with them head on and locking ourselves in here to keep them from advancing.
And if I get defeated, we lose.
We won't get pushed back, will we?
No good! They're pushing us back!
Class E's scores are still better than Class F's. If we fight them straight on, losing is just a matter of when.
No way!
But they're still just Class E, so the difference in strength isn't that big.
As long as we keep trying to block their advance, we'll make time.
And that extra time is the key to our victory!
My points!
At this rate, we'll lose.
You leave first. Go recover your points.
Okay!
I want to take the Recovery Exam!
The score you get on this exam will be transferred to your Summoned Being next time it is summoned.
This will also apply to lower scores.
Do you understand?
I understand.
What subject?
Please give me mathematics.
I need to answer as many questions as I can and increase my points.
I'm almost out!
Ninja Pervert!
Strategic retreat!
This battle's victory is mine!
Oh no!
Charge!
The defensive line has been broken, right?
This is not good, Yuuji!
If they're just formulas, then I can solve them without needing to read Japanese. Piece of cake.
Ah! Kanji!
I'll skip to the next question.
Those who have fallen, report to the infirmary!
What are we going to do, Yuuji!
Is it over already?
It seems like this is as far as you go, Class F rep.
For the Class E representative to have come personally... How relaxed...
Declaring war so early in the semester... Are you dumb?
We just went through the Placement Exam. The difference between our classes is still the difference in those scores.
Did you think you had a winning chance?
Who knows?
Is that so? It's because you don't understand this that you're stuck in that stupid Class F.
Yuuji, without strategies, we really can't win against the higher level classes.
Oh... speaking of which, I still have a plan.
Do you know why I kept you here?
Is that so?
Don't tell me... that guy is...
Precisely. He is Yoshii Akihisa, the Probate.
Akihisa, show them your true strength!
I guess it's inevitable. In the end, it still comes down to me and my skills.
Summon!
The Probate's Summoned Being has a special power.
In order to help teachers with hard labor as punishment, it can touch solid objects.
In addition, if the Summoned Being gets hurt, the one who summoned it feels pain as well.
See, very interesting, eh?
Is that all?!
Fine with me.
First, we'll roast that useless fish.
Summon!
I won't lose that easily! Let's go!
Ah! My head hurts! It hurts!
I expected nothing less from the Class E rep. Not bad.
He really is an absolutely useless guard.
No, he's already done enough.
Well then, let me personally finish you off, class rep to class rep.
Prepare yourself! I, representative Nakabayashi Hiromi from Class E, declare a duel with Sakamoto Yuuji—
Please wait!
Himeji Mizuki, joining battle!
Calling forth Summoned Being.
Summon!
Here I come!
What is with that score?!
She took out our entire class?!
Why is someone this strong in Class F?
You finally came.
Himeji-san!
Himeji Mizuki... Don't tell me you're...
Yoshii.
Shimada-san.
This child really is brilliant.
As expected of someone who was prospected to go to Class A.
That's Himeji-san's score?
The exams in Fumizuki Academy only have a limit on time—there are as many questions as you can answer.
The more you can answer, the higher the score you can get.
Then the strategy was...
Buy her time to take the exam!
I've never heard about someone like you in Class F!
Sorry, but here I come!
No way!
And so, this Summoned Being Exam War concludes with the victory of Class F.
And so, this Summoned Being Exam War
concludes with the victory of Class
Hurray! You're amazing, Himeji-san!
This is all thanks to Himeji-san's power.
It's not really just me, but thank you.
Now we can exchange classrooms and equipments with Class E.
We will have better conditions, though just by a little bit.
No. We're not exchanging.
Eh?
We'll stay with the setup we have now.
It's a nice proposal, right? Class E Rep.
But why?
Why not?! Yuuji, we finally won—
Did you guys finally finish?
What's wrong? Hideyoshi, that uniform...
Oh! Did your true self finally awaken?
Akihisa, I'm right here.
There are two Hideyoshis?
That's my sister.
Hideyoshi is my twin brother.
I am the second year Class A ambassador, Kinoshita Yuuko.
We of Class A hereby declare war on Class F.
Why is Class A declaring war on us?!
We won't go easy just because you guys are the worst class.
We intend on completely destroying you guys.
The second question.
Please provide the English name of the plant whose underground root stalk is sometimes used for food and is called "yuri" in Japanese.
Yam! Potato! Sweet Potato!
Please pay attention to the question and not focus on the "food" part.
Lilies and Roses and Physical Education
This is going to show up on the test.