When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright and
sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
All right, I'm going to do my best!
Okay, I keep this up and I
can finish this large pizza!
Wait, that's not it!
I have to get recharged and
prepare for tomorrow's exam!
Hayate, I wonder what you're eating tonight.
To the butler-in-debt, it was a wish
that was never to come true again.
Student ID
It wasn't a dream.
I can go to school again.
And I owe it all to Maria
for recommending me.
M-Maria?
So...
Please go here and study hard.
Student ID
What?!
Th-This is from Hakuou Academy...
My student ID?!
Please watch me, Maria!
I will also strive to live up to
your expectations, without fail!
All right!
I'm going to attend Hakuou Academy
and become a first-rate butler!
No, no. Even if you go to school,
it's not like that'll turn you
into a first-rate butler.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
I shall patiently teach you what
it is to be a first-rate butler.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Samurai, the Way of the Warrior, Van Damme in Action
You seem awfully happy, Hayate.
Whoa! I didn't know you
stayed the night, Hinagiku!
G-Good morning.
Morning.
But what's the matter?
You seem to be in an awfully foul mood...
You have to ask?!
Really! You suddenly disappeared
like that yesterday evening,
you showed no signs of coming
back late into the night,
and you were absolutely nowhere to be found.
And after all that, you don't think
you caused anyone to worry?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry! I really am sorry!
So, judging by your behavior,
you got accepted?
Oh, yes, thank you.
Then I'll forgive you for the time being.
I'm going home now,
but be sure to say hello
if you see me at school.
What? Oh, all right. Roger that.
Good.
We'll be students at the same school...
So, you've been holding your
student ID since last night?
Yes! I slept with it in
my hands all night long!
I swear! How adorable can you get?!
I guess it made you really happy.
Yes!
You know those people who
burst into song in musicals?
I think I know what that
urge feels like now!
You don't need to get how that feels!
There aren't any character songs
for a scene like this anyway.
Or rather, a musical anime would
be tough production-wise.
Right...
Oh, that reminds me, what
should I do about a uniform?
Uniform?
Yes. Hakuou's students wear uniforms, right?
Staying in my butler uniform would be...
You shouldn't need one.
What?
Indeed. And it will be easier to
tell you apart that way, too.
Don't worry. There are other
butlers at the school, too.
Besides, the others will respect
you more in your butler uniform.
What?
But the bigger question is whether
we'll be in the same class or not.
What?!
Indeed.
What are you saying? I'll be in high school.
You're still 13 years old,
so you're in middle school.
Oh, right, you don't know, do you?
Huh? Know what?
I've skipped grades, so I'm in high school.
What?! You're in high school?!
Don't be so surprised.
That's... But, it's like that
4-panel comic series...
Ah-ah! Don't say any more than that!
But how is it possible? You're so little!
Don't call me little!
B-But... really?
Darn it! You're one skeptical bastard!
Fine, take a look at this!
Ta-da!
Student ID
Th-This is...!
You look so grumpy in the photo.
That's not the jab you should be making!
Wow! That really is a high school ID!
I told you so from the start, didn't I?!
Hakuou has butlers, people
who've skipped grades,
and all kinds of other
students, so it's quite fun.
Wow, I had no idea.
Wait, I had to work hard
to make you believe me,
but I guess you implicitly
believe what Maria says.
Oh, no, I didn't really mean it like that.
Honestly! Taking me for a fool!
I may not look it, but my grades are...
In that case, I hope we
end up in the same class.
Y-Yeah...
Oh, I can't wait for it to be Monday!
And so, to accommodate length issues,
maybe we'll just skip forward
all the way to Monday morning.
Wow...
See that? There's nothing here when
you come this early in the morning.
We're not doing this again after today.
That's my school.
I know that already.
Oh, do you? Had you already found out?
Are you okay?
Well, it's fine if you're just happy.
But you certainly are amazing. Skipping
grades to be in high school.
It's not especially amazing.
I'm not the only one who's skipped grades.
A couple students to it every year.
What?
Besides, the record holder for
skipping grades at this school
enrolled at age 10 and graduated at age 13.
What?!
On top of that, she served as student
body president two terms in a row
and her grades were at the top of her
class for all 3 years by a wide margin.
A formidable student with 3 of the silver
watches awarded to the top achiever.
I see. I guess behemoths like
that really exist in this world.
There is a behemoth like
that, really close to you.
Oh, dear, have I caught a cold?
Anyway, students who skip
grades or transfer in
or have their tuition waived
as scholarship students...
They have a duty to contribute to
the school's record, reputation,
and rate of college enrollment.
If students like that get bad grades,
they inevitably face flunking or
other harsh punishments sometimes.
Th-They do?!
Come to think of it,
the student council people
said something similar, too.
I was in high spirits,
just by getting accepted,
but this is still a prestigious school.
I transferred in with borderline grades.
Will I really be able to cut it?
But knowing you, you'll be fine.
You're capable of anything, after all.
What's wrong, Hayate?
In battle, you must always be
reading two or three moves ahead.
By Char Aznable.
Waking up early can certainly pay off.
You get to meet interesting people.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
If I make the jab that he's the most
interesting person here, would I lose?
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Probably.
Or rather, was there a point to the
saying that he quoted earlier?
Himuro, is that enough with the flowers?
Thank you, Little Master Taiga.
Himuro thanked me!
Um...
That outfit... You're a butler as well?
Uh, yes, I'm a butler of the
Sanzenin household. My name is...
Sanzenin?
Oh, so you're the one...
Which means...
Wow, he's really pretty.
Hey, what are you trying to do to Hayate?!
Yes, that's right.
As I recall, if someone can make
this young lady apologize in tears,
that person gets to inherit the
Sanzenin family fortune...
I won't let you lay a hand on the Miss!
I will protect her!
Hayate!
Well, to be honest, I have my source
of funds called Little Master Taiga,
so I'm not really interested.
Source of funds?!
It's going to be stolen from you
if you're not paying attention.
Huh?
W-Wait, that's my string tie!
How did you do that?!
A foolish question.
It's obvious, isn't it?
It's because I'm a first-rate butler.
A first-rate... butler...?
People don't wear butler uniforms
at this school just for show.
We shall be on our way now, Little Master.
Oh, okay!
Incredible!
So that's the pinnacle of what I
want to be, a first-rate butler!
Well, not that I understand how
that's related to being a butler...
Butlers are incredible, aren't they, Miss?!
I don't really care, but you
never got your string tie back.
Oh, shoot!
Wait, he's gone already!
So this is... This is what it
is to be a first-rate butler!
No, that was out-and-out theft.
Or rather, don't force me to take
jabs at your monologues, too.
Suke, Kaku, teach them a lesson.
I'll make coffee for you any time.
I'm so sorry, Maria.
Honestly! What did you go to school for?
There.
This time, please go to school properly
without losing your string tie.
O-Of course! You can count on me!
Are you sure about that?
I can't breathe! I can't breathe, Maria!
Hey, we're going to be late!
I wouldn't mind it one bit if
you decide not to go, you know!
Oh, I'm going! I'm going!
Then I'll see you two later.
Yes, we'll be going then!
Come, Miss!
Hey, you stupid! Quit it!
This is embarrassing!
Quiet down!
Starting today, we're going to have
a new friend joining our class!
Is it a transfer student, Katsy?
Is it a boy? Or a girl?
It's a boy, more or less.
What do you mean, "more or less"?
Me! Katsy, is this boy a cool guy?
What? You want to know if he's cool?
I-It makes me nervous if they're
going to talk about stuff like that.
I bet Ayasaki's nervous.
All right! I'll take this chance
to soften up the crowd for him,
and to make up for earlier.
The transfer student is really cute!
What?!
He's kind of like
if you boil down Kimutaku and
Tackey's DNA with Joe Odagiri
and add Orly and Brad Pitt to the mix!
Just hearing his voice
will make you feel faint!
The sound effect for a sidelong
glance from him is like "BAM"!
And he's sort of like Golgo for girls.
Not to mention, he's a butler
for the Sanzenin family!
He's practically a genius
and his athletic abilities
are incredible, too!
Huh? A butler for the Sanzenin family?
And so...!
Transfer student, please come on in!
Uh, hello.
Is that Hayata?
Wait, I thought he didn't pass
the transfer admission test.
Well, a lot happened...
Oh, their focus on me hurts...
Aww. So the cool transfer
student was Hayata.
Well, it's true that he's
not exactly ugly, but...
We're talking about some awfully
poor-looking Orlys and Brad Pitts.
Okay, Ayasaki, come introduce yourself.
What?!
I-It's easy for you to give
me this satisfied look,
as if to say, "I warmed
up the crowd for you!"...
So this is adversity!
This classroom is so cold, like it
got hit with the Crackle spell,
and to think I have to introduce myself!
It can't be helped.
I can't very well bring shame to the Miss.
The boy named Hayate Ayasaki has worked
among adults from a tender age.
And so...
Nice to meet you.
This kind of sales-pitch smile
is one of his greatest fortes.
As Miss Katsura just mentioned in her
introduction, I am Hayate Ayasaki.
As a butler of the Sanzenin household,
I have the honor of serving Miss
Nagi, who is also in this class.
Miss Katsura's earlier introduction
was a little exaggerated
and I myself am not a
particularly astute student,
but I hope that I can have fun
learning alongside all of you.
So, I look forward to
getting to know everyone.
There, I've repaid my debt!
Ah, but school really is such fun, isn't it?
What? You think so?
Aren't you having fun, Miss?
There are a lot of people here.
I want to live as quietly and
inconspicuously as possible,
and spend the majority of
my days on manga and games.
That's called a useless member of society.
The reason I skipped grades
was also because I didn't want to
go to school for 12 whole years.
Th-That's really hardcore.
But I am happy that I get to go
to school like this with you.
What?
I suppose I have Maria to
thank for that as well.
And I have you to thank, too.
If you hadn't laid the groundwork for this,
I would not be here today.
Thank you very much, Miss.
No, uh, right...
Getting to be with you, I also...
You still like the unpopular spots,
the same as ever, don't you?
H-Hinagiku, you...!
Oh, Hinagiku, hello.
Hello.
But what are you doing out here?
A little something came up, so I
thought I'd drop by the clubroom.
This is a shortcut.
Wow, you're the student body president,
and you still participate in
extracurricular activities!
What's the use if you
can't juggle that much?
Come to think of it,
don't you participate in any
extracurricular activities, Miss?
Huh? Why?
Well, I do believe the best
part of going to school
is participating in extracurricular
activities with your friends.
Y-You fool! I have no need
for such things anymore!
Oh, but you're still a
registered member, you know.
Hinagiku!
Um, what registered member?
She's in the same club as I am.
Y-You fool! Th-That was just
a one-day trial membership!
You treated it as a darned
application without my permission!
So, what club?
The kendo team.
The kendo team?!
When I started high school,
there was a time when I thought
that the acute societal withdrawal
might be problematic if it continued...
Kendo Team
So, based on what I saw during the
new student recruitment activities,
I thought about getting
into some kind of sport.
Because she was really cool.
But why did she quit?
Beats me. Ask her.
Well, because...
Both the protective gear and
the bamboo sword were heavy
and I couldn't move very well.
That's why you should use
the children's sizes
instead of the same equipment as me.
Like hell I'm using children's equipment!
But you quit just because of that?
Yes, I quit just because of that.
Because I knew right away.
That even if I practiced the same sport,
it was unlikely that I'd ever be like her.
So there was a time when the Miss
tried a sport on her own initiative.
But if I leave the Miss to her own devices,
she's going to end up a deadbeat
slacker or an internet game addict.
I'm thinking finding employment
might mean an admission of defeat.
All right, Miss!
How about you come take a peek at the
kendo team with me after school?!
Huh?
Wow, so this is the kendo team.
Of course. Like hell this could be
the manga club or the anime club.
Be pure, righteous, and beautiful
But I feel like there aren't
that many people...
Well, it's not a popular club
to begin with at this school.
You look good in your uniform, Hinagiku.
What?
What?!
W-Why, thank you.
Then, shall we get the
introductions out of the way
and get you practicing
with us a bit, Hayate?
That guy just...
...addressed Miss Katsura as "Hinagiku"!
A-And she called him "Hayate"?!
But Hinagiku, what about my protective gear?
Can't you do without, Hayate?
B-But Hinagiku...
"Hinagiku"! "Hayate"! "Hinagiku"! "Hayate"!
Then I'll get permission
from our advisor first.
Miss Katsura.
There's no need to let a guy like
him practice kendo with us.
Azumamiya...
You there, butler.
Fight me!
What?!
If you lose to me, never come here again!
Even if he wins, it's not
like we'll come again.
Hey!
If I lose here, the Miss will
never practice kendo...
No, I doubt she'll attempt
any other sport, either.
In which case, I can't lose!
I understand! I will accept your challenge!
Hayate?
Oh, a flurry of petals!
This is getting interesting.
Becoming a sword for your mistress...
Quite a fine approach to take.
Oh, you're the Prince of Ties!
Please give me back the string tie!
Thank you for the interesting
nickname. But no, thank you.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
But I wonder if the Little Master
Azumamiya is up to fighting him.
What?
Take a look.
H-His swordsman's chi
is striking the petals!
Hiten...
Don't!
And due to copyright issues,
don't say any more either!
I see, so it means there's
no need for me to hold back.
You said your name was Hayate, was it?!
Y-Yes.
I, Kotaro Azumamiya, have
judged you to be an opponent,
whom I must spend the rest
of my life to defeat!
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
The mystery kendo team member, who
has suddenly declared a rivalry,
Kotaro Azumamiya.
How powerful might he actually be?
The story has suddenly taken a
classic school drama turn of events
and next time, he will finally
fight his destined rival.
Hold on a second!
When did I ever say that I would fight?!
Nonohara!
Come, Nonohara!
Nonohara?
He's my butler.
Your opponent...
...will be this combat
butler, Kaede Nonohara!
C-Combat butler?!
Um, it seems next time,
he'll be fighting this guy.
Himuro, is that enough with the flowers?
Thank you, Little Master Taiga.
Um, could I ask the non-members to leave?
What did this guy show up for?
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Hey, there, I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I'm Hinagiku Katsura.
Hinagiku, when did you get here?
What's this, Hinagiku?
What are you here for?
I'm going to be in this segment
for a while, too, now.
Well, speaking of you, Hinagiku,
it seems you're #1 in popularity in
a certain weekly manga magazine.
Truly impressive!
Oh, Hayate, flattery won't
get you anything, you know.
No, no, you excel both
academically and athletically.
I wish the Miss would learn a
thing or two from you, too.
Hayate, it's time already!
What are you so angry for, Miss?
Good grief.
Preview
So, there you have it. Hello,
I am Kaede Nonohara.
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
I serve as a butler for
the Azumamiya family.
Now, Nonohara, defeat him right this minute!
Certainly.
Safety Shutter!
Hayate!
We butlers are not tools
to be used by our masters.
It is not as if we must
merely do as we are told.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Even in Defeat, Kendo Rage".
Hayate, I have faith in you.
That there's no way you'll lose
against a butler like him!
Even in Defeat, Kendo Rage
Wipe away the tears beneath the mask.