Oh, are you here to see Kamijo?
Y-Yeah.
I'm sorry, but he's in the Rehabilitation Room now.
He has a ton of examinations today.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Thank you.
It's so nice of her to come to see him.
She's helped a lot. He's a hard patient to treat.
I hoped he finds her encouraging.
Before his accident, he was a very talented violin player.
Even if he's able to walk again, his fingers...
He won't be able to play an instrument again.
Why did it have to be Kyosuke?
My fingers all work perfectly, but they can't do anything.
Why couldn't it have been me instead?
What would Kyosuke think if I wished for him to be healthy again?
He'll just say thank you.
Or... maybe I want him to say something more than that?
I'm such a bad girl.
Looking back on it, I was clueless.
I didn't know about miracles or the price you had to pay for them.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 4     Both miracles and magic exist
All done.
Madoka.
You'll be late if you don't eat your breakfast soon.
Wats wong, Sis?
D-Does it taste yucky?
No, it's delicious. Extremely delicious.
I'm thankful that I'm alive and
can taste Dad's delicious food.
Oh man, Yuka was so dumb. She still
didn't get it even after he hinted at it.
And then she was like, "What? Did I say something strange again?"
I was trying so hard not to laugh.
Sayaka, about yesterday...
Sorry, let's not talk about it now. Later.
Well, the appropriate age for childbirth may be grounded in medical science, but that doesn't mean
you should calculate backwards from it to determine a woman's marriageable age.
Thus, a woman over the age of 30 has the unquestionable right to love and get married.
And that's why you should use the present
progressive form here instead of the past present tense.
I feel like I'm in a foreign country.
Until yesterday, nothing ever
changed about Hitomi or school...
But now I feel like I'm surrounded by strangers.
Nobody knows.
We know about Mami and the witches, but the other people don't.
It feels like we're living in a different world with totally different people.
Sayaka...
The world changed a long time ago.
We should've discovered this earlier.
Madoka, even now, do you still want to become a Puella Magi?
I see...
It's normal to feel that way.
It's hard. I know.
Now I'm just asking too much of myself.
But I can't do it.
I can hardly breathe when I think about her horrible death.
I'm afraid!
I can't do it.
Mami was so nice.
She did that to teach us the resolve you need to fight.
Hey Kyubey! What's gonna happen to this town?
Who's gonna take over Mami's responsibility to protect everyone from the witches?
This place has been Mami's territory for a long time,
but the other Puella Magi won't wait long when there's a vacancy.
Someone else will come here to hunt witches pretty soon.
But they'll only come here for the Grief Seeds, won't they? Like that transfer student?
You're right. It's rare to find someone like Mami.
They usually think about their losses and gains pretty carefully.
Everyone wants to get paid.
So that means...
But I suppose only Puella Magi themselves
should have the right to criticize each other.
I understand how you two feel.
It's a shame, but hey, I can't force you.
I guess it's time to say goodbye.
I have to find someone who wants to make a contract with me.
I'm sorry, Kyubey.
I am too. I apologize for getting you both involved.
Our time together was short but enjoyable. Thank you, Madoka.
I'm sorry.
Mami
Red Tea Life
A tea magazine for modern adults
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being so weak.
Homura?
You're putting too much blame on yourself, Madoka Kaname.
No one can blame you for anything.
I won't allow someone like that to exist.
It seems that you have accepted my advice.
Yeah.
If I had just listened to you earlier...
It wouldn't have changed Mami Tomoe's fate.
But you were able to change your own fate.
I'm glad I was able to save another person.
I-It sounds like you've been doing this for a while, Homura. But you seem different compared to Mami.
I suppose that may be true. I won't deny it.
So you've seen quite a few people die like how Mami did yesterday?
Yes.
How many?
Too many to count.
Has her apartment always been like that?
Mami Tomoe doesn't have any close relatives.
It's going to take a very long time for someone to declare her missing.
No one will realize that she's dead?
There's nothing we can do about it.
If you die on the other side,
your body doesn't turn up here.
She'll always be considered missing.
That's how the life of a Puella Magi ends.
That's terrible...
She's been fighting for us all by herself.
I can't believe that no one would even notice.
That just... makes me feel so sad.
We obtained this power by signing a contract.
We're not fighting for anyone else.
We're fighting for our own wishes.
It's normal to not get noticed or remembered.
I'll remember her.
I'll never forget Mami.
Never!
Really?
Your words must make Mami Tomoe very happy.
It makes me jealous.
You too, Homura! I'll never forget about you either!
I'll never forget how you saved me yesterday!
Homura...?
You're too kind.
Keep in mind.
Kindness can bring you even bigger troubles.
What are you listening to?
The Girl with the Flaxen Hair.
Ah, that's Debussy!
It's a beautiful piece.
Uhm, no one thinks that someone like me would be interested in classical music.
People get really surprised when I know the name of a classical piece.
They find it so unexpected and they respect me more.
You taught me all about it, Kyosuke.
If you hadn't, I would've never listened to this kind of music.
Sayaka...
Yeah?
Are you trying to torture me, Sayaka?
Why do you even try to make me listen to music now?
Are you trying to be mean to me?
I thought you liked music...
I don't want to listen to music ever again!
How can I just listen to something that I can never play?
I... I...
I can't move my fingers. I can't even feel the pain!
What am I going to do with this hand?!
Don't worry! There must be some way you can recover!
Don't give up. You can do it.
I was told to give up.
I was told to give up on playing.
My teacher told me that in person.
He said that modern medical technology isn't good enough to heal me.
My hand won't be able to move ever again.
It'd take a miracle or some kind of magic to heal me.
Both exist.
Both miracles and magic exist!
You could've been Mami's friend if you talked with her, Homura.
What did you have against her?
What?
Is that Hitomi?
Hitomi!
Do you have something to study today?
What!? She's got the same mark...
Hitomi! Hey, Hitomi!
Ah, Ms. Kaname, how do you do?
W-What's wrong with you!? Where are you going?
I'm off to a land far better than this one.
Hitomi...
Ah, right, Ms. Kaname. Please come with me.
Why yes! That's wonderful.
What should I do? I can't believe that she...
I could call Homura...
Oh, I can't! I don't have her number!
Right. I'm useless.
I can't even run such a small factory.
I don't have a place in this world now.
Be careful, Madoka.
If you use the wrong one, you'll cause a serious problem.
Your whole family could wind up dead.
Please don't make that mistake.
No! You can't do that!
Don't interfere. This is a holy ceremony.
But... that's dangerous! Everyone here will get killed!
Exactly. We are going to a wonderful world together.
Do you not see how beautiful that is?
Your body is just holding you back.
You'll understand soon, Ms. Kaname.
Get away from me!
W-What should I do? What should I do!?
N-No! Please!
No! Someone, help me!
Is this how I'm going to pay for my sins?
Because I was such a coward. Because I lied.
I have to pay.
Sayaka!?
This is my finishing strike!
Ah, my bad, my bad. I almost missed it.
Sayaka... Why are you dressed like that?
Well, I guess I had a change of heart.
Don't worry.
I may be a rookie, but I did a pretty good job back there, didn't I?
But...
You're...
You're late, transfer student!
I really didn't expect you to come.
Well, I heard that Mami was done for.
But it wasn't an easy trip.
What the hell is going on? It sounds like the story's changed.
Sorry, but a new Puella Magi has already taken this area.
She made the contract with me just a few minutes ago.
What? Seriously? Friggin' annoying.
But I'm not just going to let some rookie chick take this perfect area right from under my nose.
What are you going to do, Kyoko?
What do you think?
Let me put it easily.
All I need to do is defeat her...
Right?
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Kamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate God Himself
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Jin Kobayashi
I started dancing!
Puella Magi Sayaka will do her best to keep the peace in the City of Mitakihara!
Episode 5     There's no way I would regret it