What do we do now, Rider?
What now, mad dog?
Tokiomi...
I'll... kill you!
Saber!
We aren't making much progress.
If only we could use Saber's left arm...
Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
Hey, Saber!
This isn't working.
Withdraw!
Don't be ridiculous.
We must stop him here!
But we've exhausted our options.
Fall back for now.
I have an idea.
Listen, everyone.
Regardless of whatever plan we go with, we must first buy some time.
I shall draw him into Ionian Hetairoi.
However, even the combined forces of all my fierce warriors won't be able to destroy that.
Restraining him within the Reality Marble is the most we can do.
What then?
No idea.
Huh?
If I take in a thing of that magnitude,
the Reality Marble will only last a few minutes.
You must find a way within that time.
Heroic Spirits...
I want you to find a path to victory.
Hey, boy.
You stay here too.
Hey...
Once I activate the field, I won't know what transpires outside.
Boy, focus your mind and
call for me if anything happens.
I will dispatch a messenger.
Saber! Lancer!
I'll leave the rest to you.
Very well.
Such pointless struggling.
Mom!
What?
How about diving headfirst
into that mass of filth, mongrel?
After all that talk...
This is all you have up your sleeve?
Is he trying to kill himself?
Kariya.
Think of this as my gift to you.
Intensive Einäscherung.
I-I'll kill... you...
Tokiomi!
Zouken...
What now?
He's buying us time, but if we can't use it to come up with anything, we'll be right back where we started.
Hey, Einzbern...
Got any ideas?
Hey!
Well, um...
How does this work?
Iri?
No, I'm...
I mean...
I see.
You must be Rider's Master.
Perfect.
I wanted to talk to you too.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter.
Caster's disappearance was
the work of your Servant, yes?
That's right, I guess.
Question.
When Rider releases his Reality Marble, can he position its contents at a particular location?
To a degree.
Within a hundred meters or so, but it's possible.
Rider should be able to control where it will materialize.
Very well.
I'll wait for the right moment and fire a signal flare then.
Release Caster right under it.
Can you do that?
I can... I think.
Probably.
One more thing.
I need you to relay a message to Lancer.
Tell him Saber's left arm holds
an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Well, he had a message for you.
Something about Saber's left arm
being an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm...
Is that true, Saber?
Can it destroy Caster's monster with a single strike?
It can.
However, Lancer.
The weight of my sword is the weight of my pride.
The wound from my battle with you is an honor, not a fetter.
The aid of Diarmuid O'Dyna as a substitute
for my left arm is worth ten thousand men.
Well, Saber.
I cannot forgive Caster's actions.
He affirms the despair of those around him and finds joy in spreading terror.
By the vows I swore as a knight, I cannot abide such evil.
Lancer, you mustn't!
Is it Saber who must win this fight? Is it Lancer?
No, it is neither.
What must triumph here is the knight's path of chivalry that we champion.
Is that not so, Heroic Spirit Arturia?
Lancer...
I rest my hopes for victory
upon your blade, King of Knights.
I'm counting on you, Saber.
I accept, Lancer.
Upon my sword, I promise you victory!
That's from the legend of King Arthur...
Saber!
Berserker?
What is he...?
You dare turn your back on me, mongrel?
You insult me!
What?!
Saber!
What's the matter with Berserker?!
Just when I had finally regained the use of my left arm...
A soul naturally seeks pleasure, consciously or not.
You ordered Assassin to investigate him to such a degree
that you could understand those "complicated circumstances".
And this was all due to your unconscious interest.
It's still too soon.
That shaking...
It's a sign Rider's Reality
Marble can't hold on much longer.
Rider...
I am Mithrenes, of the Hetairoi.
I have come as the king's ears.
I-I want him to wait for the signal, and then release
Caster from the Reality Marble at the indicated point.
Can he do that?
It's possible, but we're running out of time.
Our forces within the Reality Marble cannot restrain that sea monster much longer.
I know!
I know that!
Damn it!
Damn that Berserker.
Can't we do something about him?
I will go.
Lancer...
That's enough, mad warrior!
It's all or nothing!
Archer...
That's it!
Right under that!
As you wish.
Honestly...
What took so long?
Now, Saber. Show me.
I shall judge the true worth of
your brilliance as a Heroic Spirit.
The light...
Her sword shines, a dream that all warriors
scattered in battle, past, present and future,
hold and mournfully exalt as
their final moments approach.
She carries their will as her pride, bidding them to remain steadfast in their loyalty.
Now, the undefeated king sings aloud the
name of the miracle she holds in her hands.
Its name is...
Excalibur!
This light...
There's no doubt.
This was the brilliance that blessed Jeanne and me with joy and bliss...
What...
...have I...
Did you see that, King of Conquerors?
That was Saber's brilliance.
Do you still refuse to accept her,
having witnessed light of such magnitude?
That light comes from her having taken all her people's hopes upon herself.
Its brightness is what makes it tragic.
Especially when you consider the one bearing that burden is just a dreaming little girl.
The girl never had a happy childhood, never fell in love,
but was cursed by her ideals and ended up this way.
It is too painful to look upon.
Isn't that what makes her so beautiful?
Her dreams were too much for her.
I imagine they destroyed the dreamer herself in the end.
The tears of lamentation she shed during her final
moments must have been quite sweet to the taste.
You and I just can't see eye to eye, Babylonian King of Heroes.
Oh?
So you finally realized?
Then what will you do, Rider?
Will you let your steel give shape to your rage?
I would like that very much,
but I have exerted myself a little too
much tonight to face an opponent like you.
Of course, I would have to fight back
should you refuse to allow me passage.
I don't mind.
You may flee, King of Conquerors.
It wouldn't satisfy me to destroy you
at anything less than your full strength.
So, you're wounded yourself from
being shot down by that black thing.
I repay provocation with death.
We'll decide this next time, King of Heroes.
Our battle shall be the one that
determines the winner of this Grail War.
I wouldn't be so sure.
I have yet to decide whether only one individual is worthy of receiving my treasure, Rider.
She is a fool who reaches for
dreams beyond human attainment.
I, Gilgamesh, am the only one in this Heaven and
Earth with the right to love her in her destruction.
Ephemeral and brilliant one, fall to my embrace.
That is my decision.
Episode 15
Golden Brilliance
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
I am Diarmuid O'Dyna,
first spear of the Knights of Fianna.
I am glad to have met you!
Splendid!
I, Arturia Pendragon,
King of Britain, accept your challenge.
Come!
Next Episode
Terminus of Honor
Here I come!