This is Minami from last year, right?
She truly is the academy's princess!
She's simply splendid!
Goodness, you're making me blush.
Minami!
Bonjour.
Minami, what's this from?
The Noble Party, right?
Mom told me about it.
Party?
Yes, it's a ball held every year.
It's a formal attire affair.
All the girls wear dresses, too.
Well, this is a high class prep school.
A party with dresses...
My happiness is in full bloom!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Not in a Million Years?!
Haruka Makes a Dress!
Wow!
It's simply splendid!
This is some high quality fabric.
It's what I wore last year.
I embroidered it myself.
Wow.
I only made its embroidery, but some
students made their dresses from scratch.
Made it from scratch? That's far out.
I think I'd wear one of my mom's.
I want to...
I want to make a dress, too!
I want to go to a party in a dress I sewed myself!
Haruka, do you know how to sew?
Not at all!
You'd better give it up.
You'd be drawing the design,
cutting the cloth, and sewing it together...
entirely on your own.
But I want to try!
Worry not!
We can ask the Lesson Pad!
That's right!
Bonjour, tout le monde!
Je am la professeure royal, Madame Siamour!
Bonjour!
Madame Siamour, teach me how to make a dress!
My, aren't vous excited.
Well then, let us commençons le lesson de dressmaking!
Wow!
There are so many dresses!
To begin, you can define a dress by its collar, sleeves,
and skirt line, as they have the most influence on the overall design.
Oh, I see!
Now use these dresses as a reference for ta own design!
These are all so splendid that I can't deci—
Watch out!
I'm sorry...
Good grief.
You'll never settle on a design like that.
But it's a chance to get closer to being a Grand Princess!
Right, a princess...
Come to think of it, Haruka, what kind of dress does your favorite princess wear?
My favorite...
The Princess of Flowers...
Ah!
I'm done!
Let's see.
Here!
Uh huh...
That should suffice.
Let's allons au la prochain scène!
Now choisis your material.
Okay!
Pink totally fits you best.
Really?
Go pink!
I guess I will!
Now stand still.
Right!
Good!
Be precise.
Got it!
Here goes!
This dress...
is gonna bloom!
It's crooked...
Non non, vous must calm down.
Right...
You got this, Haruharu!
That will do for today.
Bonne journée!
It's crooked again...
Need a break?
Thanks!
It smells great!
It's pretty neat that you're making your own dress.
How are you getting yours?
My mother's sewing one for me.
It's a bit out of my league.
I can't wait to see what your mother makes!
Me too!
Speaking of dresses...
rumor has it that there's a trio of girls in dresses who defeat monsters around the school.
Are you okay?
Yeah!
Well, I'm going to bed.
Good luck with your dress!
Thanks, Yui!
"Her dress is very wonderful, so she is
looking forward to the party very much."
Good!
Ouch...
Now, turn in the homework I assigned last week.
Huh?
Oh no...
Miss Haruno...
Teacher, I...
If you forgot your homework...
then you're getting an extra
ten pages of work this week!
Okay...
Japanese Quiz
Haruno, you're retaking this.
Miss Haruno!
Please learn to play this song properly, okay?
Okay...
Haruka.
Give up on making your dress.
B-But why?
You aren't keeping up with your studies.
Your dress may have outer beauty, but it means nothing if its wearer doesn't have the inner beauty to match.
It takes more than appearances to be a princess.
Think about what you lack.
Okay...
Minamin's scary...
Right, Haruharu?
Huh?
Minami got mad at me...
It's not like you to get all glum.
Geez...
Times like these call for something sweet!
Oh yeah!
Did you know that Marble Doughnuts has a limited edition coconut honey flavor?
With some almonds and cream on top, it's to die for!
Okay, I've got work today, but after that—
All right!
I'll do it!
Do what?
I'll make a gorgeous dress and study like crazy!
What's gotten into you, Haruharu?
I'm going right back to my room to study!
Thanks, Kirara!
Uh, sure.
Why'd she cheer up all of a sudden?
I'll do my best!
Why?
Short style!
Still at it, Haruharu?
Oh, Kirara. Done with work?
Yeah...
Anyway, you've gotta be tired, so I brought these!
Doughnuts!
So, how's the dress coming along?
It's almost finished.
Looks like school and sewing has you burning the midnight oil.
I commend your dedication!
I think I'll really make it in time for the Noble Party!
Let's all have some tea!
Thanks, Perf.
Oh no!
Hold on!
I'll wipe it down!
A wash wouldn't get this out...
Haruka, I'm really, really, really sorry!
It's okay, Perf.
I still have some cloth left.
If I sew this part again, it'll be fine.
Okay, I'll help too.
I think we can make it in time if we work together!
Thanks, Kirara,
but I'll do this by myself.
It's a step toward becoming a princess,
so I want to see this through on my own.
It's my dream, after all!
Your dream?
You can dream all you want, but there's
no way you can finish in time by yourself!
Besides, you look exhausted...
But I want to try!
Look, you'll never make it in time!
The party's tomorrow!
Don't worry, Kirara!
All right, time for the home stretch!
'Kay, I'm bored.
There's gotta be something fun to...
I've gotta finish these in time for the party!
A saccharine cake with a saccharine dream.
I'll sour it for you, 'kay?
I've baked the perfect cake!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
Geez, that stubborn girl...
She had a celebrity begging to help her!
Bonjour. How is she?
She's something, all right.
She's gotta fix a huge part of her dress,
but she said she wanted to do it herself and turned me away!
She'll never finish alone...
I see.
That's all you have to say?
Yes.
She said she'd do it herself, correct?
If so, I think we should let her.
Minamin, that's cold!
Do you want her to fail?
Of course I don't.
Then why?
Because I believe Haruka can do it.
She can't!
She can.
Because Haruka holds her dream dear to her heart.
Dreams again?
Dreams are fine, but get real! She's too short on time!
She won't make it!
Bad news!
There's a Dyspairvil!
Talk about bad timing!
I'll tell Haruka!
Wait!
Don't tell Haruharu.
Is that okay, Minamin?
Yes, it is.
Dyspairvil...
Let's go!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
...shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
There you are, Princess Precures.
Get 'em, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
I've gotta fight in Haruharu's stead!
Stop right there!
Haruka!
Haruharu?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Are you okay?
Mostly!
You're late, Cure Flora.
Dyspairvil!
Why are you here?
You can let us handle this one!
Vil!
How? She was barely conscious before!
I want to be a princess.
To make that dream come true, I'll sew, study, and fight...
with everything I've got!
I'll realize my dream with these two hands!
She can.
Because Haruka holds her dream dear to her heart.
To show my appreciation to Mermaid for teaching me just how far I have to go to reach my dream...
You two knew all along, but I...
And to show my appreciation to Twinkle for worrying so much about me...
Huh?
I'll give it my all!
Dyspair! Dyspair! Vil!
Because I want to!
Flora...
'Kay, you're way too chatty today.
Can it, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair... vil!
Flora!
Dyspair!
A dream, 'kay?
I'll make it wither and die, 'kay?
Oh no you won't!
Nobody can break Flora's dream!
I'm sure... no, I know...
that Flora will make a gorgeous dress!
Dyspair!
Flora!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
What?
Mermaid!
Right!
Dyspairvil...
Flora!
Right!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Dance, O flowers!
Precure!
Floral Tourbillon!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
That was fun, 'kay?
I'll play with you Princess Precures some other time.
Open!
The door to your dream!
I'm looking forward to your cake!
Are you okay?
Mostly...
Geez.
I'm done!
Haruharu!
Your work paid off.
Ah, très bon travail!
I'm amazed that you really finished in time!
Thanks for the help, Kirara.
Huh?
I didn't do anything, though.
You totally did!
You worried for me and cheered for me!
And look how happy you are for me!
I-I'm not really...
Indeed, Kirara is quite thoughtful.
Wait, Minamin, you too?
I just thought it'd be nice if
Haruharu could finish her dress...
So, uh...
Kirara, your face is beet red!
Come on!
Don't gang up on me!
It's not like I did it for Haruharu or anything!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Simply splendid!
With all the dresses and dancing, it's like I'm in a fairy tale!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Curtain Rises!
The Noble Party of My Dreams!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Kagawa Prefecture - Kae (Age 6)
Osaka Prefecture - Kokone (Age 4)