Go on and read it.
The "Love Lab News."
Love Lab News
For those who want to love
Characters
Mayu: A girl in her second year of middle school who's worried about being chubby. Conscious of her weight, she goes
jogging every day.
Yuki: Mayu's best friend.
Yuki's concerned that Mayu seems to be a bit down in the dumps recently. She's not paying any attention in class either.
Looks like she has something on her mind. Yuki decides to ask her what's going on.
"You've not been your usual self lately. What's wrong?"
Mayu finds it hard to speak up at first, but eventually tells Yuki all about it. She says she'd recently become friends with
the guy she's been in love with for the longest time, and that she's wondering if she should confess to him. This news
delights Yuki as if it were about herself.
"I'm so happy for you! Go for it!"
She cheers Mayu on, but her expression clouds over. That's when it hits Yuki.
"Wait, are you scared of confessing?"
Mayu nods.
"I'm so chubby. I can't get a boyfriend like this."
But Yuki replies to that with a smile on her face.
"Guys actually like girls with a little meat on their bones! Besides, you always work so hard. I'm sure they find you cute."
Those words made Mayu cry tears of joy.
To be continued.
"Mayu nods.
'I'm so chubby. I can't get a boyfriend like this.'
But Yuki replies to that with a smile on her face."
Wait, is this a reply to the chubby girls love advice request we got?
Momo wrote it in the form of a story.
Mayu and Yuki are fictional characters.
Nobody'll think they actually exist in the real world.
Besides, you always work so hard.
Are you suggesting we let you give out advice in the form of stories?
This way, we can get away
with it even if people find out.
Also, it'd be bad if you got too many requests,
I'm sure they find you cute.
so I think we should put up a new box for the newspaper.
You're the best, Yuki!
You messed with us so many times, so where's this coming from?
We wanted you to recognize
our abilities and achievements.
That's all there was to it, really.
And if possible, we wanted to be promoted to a club again.
Plus a large increase in budget!
See? There was more to it!
I really can't trust you.
You guys are taking too much of a risk here. It doesn't add up.
If the school finds out about this,
we could pin all the blame on you guys, you know?
You can make us your scapegoat if that happens.
Thank you, Maki.
You went and spoke to the organizers for us, didn't you?
You asked them to allow associations to
participate in the summer newspaper contest.
We get to participate thanks to you!
Maki, you...
I was gonna tell you about it eventually.
You did so much for us,
so it's only fair that we repay you in kind.
A reporter who can't take responsibility for her own articles is no reporter at all!
Most importantly, you can't keep something so fun all to yourself.
We want to be your accomplices.
And if possible, we want to be promoted to a club again.
Plus a large increase in budget!
Enough of that!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
What do you think?
I hate to admit it, but it's a good idea.
It'll take a load off our shoulders.
I'm in agreement!
Please Be My Friend Forever
What about you, Maki?
We can't make a half-assed decision.
The student council's reputation is on the line here.
Yeah.
We need to do lots more...
love research and turn our findings into articles!
Looks like you've made your decision already!
I'm gonna go run!
Why?!
It's outdoor practice for making long, black hair flutter in a way boys like!
I feel so alone!
Well, you're the only one with long, black hair.
Oh, all right.
We'll watch you from the window.
Yeah, the flutter's looking good!
This makes me feel alone too!
Why are you so wound up?
It's my first time.
This is the first time I'm sharing a secret with a
bunch of people and starting something with them.
Maki...
So I just can't sit still.
Our love research is finally taking shape.
We need to be more thorough from now on!
I'm counting on you, Master Riko.
I-I'm gonna go run!
Why?
This is bad!
I'd better do something soon!
Why not just tell her that you were never popular in your entire life?
Don't go destroying my future chances!
You should confess and apologize before it's too late.
What am I even supposed to say this late in the game?
That's for you to come up with.
You're so cold-hearted!
I don't care! Stop acting like a spoiled brat!
Pwease help me, Sayo!
Sayo!
She just misunderstood that I had loads of love experience.
I'm not deceiving her because I want to.
Maki's a precious friend of mine.
I'm here to pay you back for hurting my friend!
It's not like I'm trying to be useful to her out of guilt!
What the hell are you on about?!
You called her "Natsuo"!
What are you talking about?
Isn't her name Natsuo Maki?
Huh?
It's Maki Natsuo?!
But you call her Maki!
Oh, come on. You should've at least asked her what her name was.
Dammit.
I usually don't make this kind of dumbass mistake,
but dealing with her always throws me off my game.
Jan...
You like Maki, don't you?
Why would you take it that way?!
Try thinking back on what you said.
Me? Like that weird-ass girl? You've gotta be kidding me.
Say what?!
Yeah, she may be weird, but you're one to talk!
Maki's a really innocent and nice girl!
That's why...
Are you a love expert?!
Oh, right. You're a love expert.
Please, Master!
That's why...
If you wanna say something, then spit it out.
Makes you look dumb otherwise.
Oh, come on!
I...
wanna say it too.
All right!
I'll tell her tomorrow!
I'm attending that cram school starting next week.
My lies will be exposed in no time if she starts coming to cram school.
I've gotta silence them somehow...
No!
I've gotta 'fess up and apologize!
Maki, to tell you the truth—
I'm counting on you to help me
at cram school too, Master Riko.
I've got cram school today, so I'm gonna go.
You goddamn coward!
Oh, I need to go submit the paperwork too.
Let's go together.
I should confess before we get there.
I'll wait for a pause in conversation, and then...
Taking to you was so much fun,
it feels like we got here in the blink of an eye.
You goddamn ultra-coward!
Headmaster's Office
I'll go submit the paperwork.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
I need to silence Nagi and Jan before Maki runs into them.
Excuse me.
Uh...
What was her name again?
Er...
I need to act normal even with a guy here.
Hello, Riko-loving childhood friend of Riko who got rejected by her!
Hey! We're pretending that never happened!
I'd never fall in love with a girl like that!
What?
You shouldn't erase your memories just because Riko's out of your league!
I'm telling you that's not it!
Nagi! Jan!
Are the two of them not here yet?
Where's Mr. Irikimi?
Looks like he's gone off somewhere.
I need to see him too.
Why don't you take a seat and wait?
Okay.
Is she not doubting Riko's lies at all?
I guess I'll try asking her.
Huh? Hang on, I'm currently all alone with a guy behind closed doors!
Um...
Huh?
U-Uh...
Er...
Wow, this wall makes a pretty nice sound!
Oh, I'm a wall nerd!
Don't mind me.
I-I see.
Anyway...
What a folksy feel! Très bien!
Even I, a curtain nerd, have to bow down to this!
She's a real cutie,
but she's also a real weirdo!
Are you not good at dealing with guys or something?
'Sup, Satch!
You're as cute as ever today.
You're so cute, Satoshi!
You're like one of the gals, Nagi.
Let us give you a makeover!
This feels so fresh and new!
You don't seem to have much
in common with girls like Riko.
How did you come to know her?
Sh-She helped me out when I was in trouble.
So I wanted to be friends with her.
I know I cause her a lot of trouble,
and she always seems annoyed,
but she's extremely nice and really cool!
Yeah, she is a bit of a busybody,
or well, a good friend.
Exactly.
So I can understand why you fell for her.
How'd we get on that topic?!
Huh? Am I wrong?
In the first place, Riko has never been pop—
Come again?
Jeez, where are they?
Hey, Riko.
Nagi!
I need you to do me a favor.
Remember my friend who came here the other day?
I met her just now.
She's starting next week, right?
Then let me get straight to the point—
What?!
I told her all about your past.
Oh, you did?
Then I guess it's too late to ask you for a favor.
Wait, what?!
You're awful.
How could you lie to such a nice girl?
I need to apologize.
I need to apologize to Maki.
I'm sorry, Maki! I'm so sorry!
Wait!
I was just kidding.
I didn't tell her anything.
You goddamn liar!
Look who's talking!
If she's that important to you,
hurry up and set her straight already.
What if she finds out from someone else?
Y-Yeah.
You really didn't tell her?
I thought about it.
But she has so much faith in you.
Nagi, you're such a nice guy.
I'm sorry I can't remember your confession!
You don't have to!
I'm sorry.
I'm late because I had student council wor—
Masaomi, this is Maki Natsuo.
She'll be coming here starting next week.
I'm Maki.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Shit, I should've confirmed her name right at the beginning.
I can't believe how stupid I was.
You like Maki, don't you?
Damn Kurahashi.
Screw that.
You're in the student council too, Jan?
I'm also—
What?
Nothing!
Since you're here already, why don't you sit in for class?
O-Okay!
But...
Seriously, what?!
I'll go home!
Why is he being so hostile?
Go ahead and sit in.
Huh?
This class is pretty difficult,
so you'll need to make all kinds of preparations.
Then I'll sit in for a while.
Huh?
Is he a nice guy after all?
Preparations to switch cram schools since you won't be able to keep up.
This guy isn't scary because he's a boy.
He's just a bad guy through and through!
How much has your tutor taught you, Maki?
What? You got this far already?
Huh?
I heard you were an excellent student,
but this is amazing.
We haven't gotten this far yet.
I'm really glad to have another
excellent student join our ranks.
I've still got a long way to go.
I need to make a bunch of preparations.
Oh, right.
I hear you're friends with Riko?
Yes.
You're also good friends with her, right, Masaomi?
Excuse me?!
You took so much care to help her study for the middle school entrance exams.
Because you told me to!
You look like you're having so
much fun when you're with Riko.
Stop stating your opinions like they're facts!
But you looked so lively!
Livid
No, I was livid!
Why are you being so stubborn?
You're not listening to me at all, are you?!
Delu
sion
Th-This...
Delu
sion
For someone reason, this reeks of love!
Delu
sion
Jan's a loner because of his all too twisted personality.
Riko acts really friendly with him too.
Aw, Jan. Why're you being so shy?
K-K-Kurariko.
He'd inevitably fall for her.
But Riko was really popular.
Come on, guys. Cut it out.
The sorrow twisted his personality even further,
which brings us to today!
Fine, I got it.
Let me go get some study material for Maki.
I bet you didn't get it!
What's with that expression of sympathy which just screams, "I completely understand"?
Adults don't understand the trials and tribulations of us youth.
I don't understand it at all either.
Well, I've got a faint idea about what you're thinking, so let me say this:
Kurahashi's nothing to me.
Riko's really attractive, isn't she?
And she's popular, to boot.
Popular?
Kurahashi?
What nonsense.
Huh?
But it's not nonsense.
As if that horrible girl could ever be popular.
Says the guy who loved her!
What are you saying?!
Kurahashi's an insensitive fool!
There's nothing to like about her!
How dare you insult my precious friend.
Did your feelings turn sour because she rejected you?
Don't yell at me based on some delusion of yours!
Do you always make people deal with your stupid assumptions?
What?
Kurahashi probably has a rough time with you too.
I just hope you two being "friends" isn't
another of one of your misunderstandings.
Crap.
I went too far.
You can read people like an open book, right?
Wh-What?
You realized how I felt,
so you said things that would hurt me more.
I can breathe easy now.
Now that I know what you're like,
I don't have to believe anything you say.
You're wasting your smarts by using it like that.
I remembered that I have something to do.
If you'll excuse me.
H-Hey...
Maki!
Thank goodness. I've been looking all—
Riko...
Huh?
Riko!
What the?
I hate Jan.
What'd he do this time?!
He said you weren't popular and called you a horrible girl.
He also said you were having a rough time dealing with my stupid assumptions.
That you actually hate me, and our being friends is also...
Why would I hate you?
If I did, I would've quit the
student council a long time ago.
Riko...
So you're gonna cry after all?!
But...
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see ya.
I didn't manage to tell her this time either!
After school
Racking my brains over it isn't gonna help.
I've got no choice but to apologize...
as soon as I meet Maki!
Maki!
I have something to tell you!
Me too, Master Riko.
Wh-What is it, Ms. Maki?
It's about the underground newspaper thing.
The newspaper association will need a
room to themselves to do this in secret.
So I'm thinking of lending them the student council's storage room.
Won't treating them that favorably make people suspicious?
That's why I'm thinking of asking them to make a special edition containing student council announcements.
We'll put up a front that they're
helping with our activities, huh?
Yes.
That way, it won't seem strange for us to lend
them our storage room or visit them frequently.
And then we'll be completely
free to conduct love research!
It'd be nice if you showed a little restraint.
All that's left is to figure out a way to
make readers aware of what we're doing.
It'll be curtains for us if they carelessly let the teachers see the underground newspaper.
Let's have them shoulder an equal amount of risk, then.
What?
We don't need to do anything special.
Just make them write their name and class on the newspaper when handing it over.
To ensure that they won't expose it, no matter what.
So we'll turn the readers into our accomplices too?
Will they really accept?
They will.
Fuji Girls' is too peaceful a school.
There are a lot of people here who want to break bad just a little bit.
W-Well, yeah.
You're right.
There's no way those people would let fun things such as big secrets and love advice slip from their grasp.
Maybe I started doing love research because...
I wanted to break free from being a super talented student and break bad just a little bit too.
Stop casually boasting!
"Just a little bit," my ass!
I am now well and truly excited!
If we start doing this,
the lies I've told will no longer stay in this circle of friends.
Wait, I'm not saying it's okay if they stay in here.
Riko, I'm getting more and more excited!
Let's go on a run!
That's more like it!
Why?
I'm amazed she can go along with all that.
Sometimes, I forget that Riko has loads of love experience.
Me too.
I mean, she always talks like she's one of us.
She doesn't boast or show off either.
And...
what if her having lots of experience was all a lie?
What?
Hey, that would be awful.
Maki has so much faith in her
because she has all that experience.
Why would you ask us that, Sayo?
No reason in particular.
Here.
Thanks.
We also did love research about handkerchiefs, didn't we?
Oh yeah, that happened too.
We did lots of love research, didn't we?
Though it's hard to keep up with you sometimes.
You say that, but you always go along with me.
I love that about you.
Every day has been fun since I met you.
Please be my friend forever.
Oh my god! I went and said it!
I need to confess right now.
I have to tell her the truth!
Say, Maki.
Huh?
There's something I've wanted to tell you all along.
Something I couldn't tell you.
Well, uh...
My being a love expert,
or having loads of love experience...
is actually...
all a lie.
In truth, I'm just like you.
A c...
C...
A complete beginner!
How would you feel if that was the case?
You freakin' loser!
Wait, no!
Kurahashi!
There you go with your flashy hairband again!
To the counseling office with you!
I'd finally managed to tell her...
Oh, Riko!
Hey, Mika.
I see you guys are doing something fun.
Love advice, eh?
H-How?
How?
I used to be in the newspaper club.
The prez just told me about it and asked me to help out.
Huh?!
But, you know, are things gonna be okay?
You? Giving out love advice?
You have zero experience.
W-Well, yeah,
but we're conducting proper research.
Especially Maki. She has a strong sense of duty,
so she doesn't half-ass things—
Oh, hey, Prez Maki.
This is bad!
D-Did she hear us?!
M-Maki, did you hear all that?
"Strong sense of duty"? Oh, please!
You'll get me all excited if you praise me that much!
I'm gonna run to the student council's office!
Again?
Here I go!
Later.
Wait for me!
Thank god.
Thank god she didn't hear that!
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
The final episode, huh?
It went by so fast.
Yes.
It's been ten years since I found a wonderful boyfriend thanks to our love research.
It hasn't been that long!
My big brother's moved beyond trying to find himself too.
That'd be great, if it were true!
I never thought my slapsticks would be marketed as merchandise!
Suzu, don't run with the joke!
If you want a second season that badly, you'll have to pay me 80% more.
Holding That Hand
Don't make me play the straight man until the very end!