If there really is a giant monster out there,
do you think they'll authorize us to attack?
If this was a monster movie, I guarantee
we'd be the first to get killed off.
You know, curtain raisers to set things
up till the main character shows up.
Uh, that's not even funny, sir.
Whatever it is, we'll find out soon enough.
Didn't work, it's just restoring itself.
What incredible regenerating power.
It's all they can do to keep it from coming ashore.
Well, at this rate,
I'll never get through to Caster.
Awesome, so awesome.
That is so totally awesome, big guy!
The Lord has come.
The Lord has come!
It's terrible, how could this have happened?
In the long and winding history of the Holy Grail Wars,
a foul up like this is unprecedented.
According to our observers' reports,
even though the Mion River area is blanketed in mist,
a large number of onlookers
have already begun to gather there.
I fear we can no longer handle this by ourselves.
We must petition the Mage's Association for assistance.
What is Tokiomi doing right now?
My master left for the scene with Archer
immediately after Caster's monster appeared.
In that case, I will see to
the arrangements for the cover up.
Go to Tokiomi immediately and
assist him in any way you can.
I understand, Father.
This sight has begun to turn my stomach.
Mongrels though they may be, they are
still figures of at least some slight renown.
Yet here they are working together with all
their might to finish off that disgusting thing.
Surely there are limits to which one may sink.
Do you not agree with that, Tokiomi?
We must destroy that monster
before there are any more witnesses to the battle.
The honor of the Tohsaka family is at stake.
My king, that monster is a
vermin that is ravaging your garden.
I humbly beseech you to slay it yourself.
Dealing with pests is the job of a gardener,
or is your intent to mock my Noble Phantasms,
putting them on the level of a gardener's hoe, Tokiomi.
I would never dream of such a thing,
but as you can see, Majesty, this
creature is beyond the ability of the others.
It's the perfect opportunity
to demonstrate your true might.
I beg you, please take action.
Hm.
It can't be.
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I've grown weary of watching that disgusting creature.
No, King of Heroes, wait, I beg you.
Tokiomi, I sacrificed four swords
thinking it might duty towards you.
Having been defiled by touching that filthy
thing, I have no interest in retrieving them.
Do not presume upon my generosity.
You are the only heroic spirit alive
able to defeat that thing.
Given its regenerative abilities, the sole way
to defeat it is to annihilate it in one strike.
Only your Sword of Dissociation is
capable of accomplishing that so‐-
You fool!
You dare suggest that I draw forth Ea here!
Don't forget your place, I should have your head
for being so impertinent to your king!
I could use a Command Seal, but if I did, it
would shatter my relationship with the King of Heroes.
Father Risei and I had originally
arranged for this Caster hunting expedition
so that I could recover the Command Seal I lost.
How could my plan be backfiring so badly?
Damn.
What the hell is that?
There's a weird light hovering in the sky at six o'clock.
It's not a helicopter.
Is it a UFO or something?
Control to Diablo One,
we need a situation report.
The situation is,
uh, well...
Diablo Two, gonna go down to get a closer look.
Wait, Kobayashi!
Diablo Two, get back here!
Official inspection from up close
will tell us what that thing is.
Kobayashi.
Kobayashi!
A fearsome creature indeed.
It... it ate it.
Control to Diablo One.
What's going on over there?
Report!
Eyes, it has eyes.
It's absolutely covered with eyes!
Eyes, what do you mean it has eyes?
Shit, that thing wants to eat me too.
Captain Ogi.
Diablo One engaging.
Wait, Ogi, engaging what?
I'll kill it before it gets me.
This is for Kobayashi.
I'm gonna pump you with missiles, ya bastard.
Berserker?
Oh man, what's he doing here?
You fool, stay down!
Now he decides to join us?
Isn't that...
Ah, so that mad dog has turned up again.
This should be amusing.
My king, allow me to deal with his master.
Very well, merely toy with him.
Then good luck to us both, Your Majesty.
Dogs like you belong prostrated on the ground.
Yet you dare to climb into my sky.
Don't put on airs, you mongrel!
Such impertinence.
How amusing.
I've not played a game like this in quite some time.
For a lowly animal, you're providing me
with no shortage of entertainment.
I hardly recognize you,
Kariya Matou.
Though you turned your back on
magecraft, you still desired the Grail.
To think you'd slink back in such a sorry state.
The very sight of you is enough to invite whispers
that the Matou family has fallen from grace.
Tokiomi Tohsaka, answer me a question.
Why did you hand your daughter Sakura over to Zouken?
What?
You really think that's what you
should be worrying about at this moment?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
Do you even need to ask?
I did it because I wished to give
my beloved daughter a happy future.
You what?
All mages who have two children eventually suffer for it.
The family's secret arts can be passed to only one child.
They suffer over the issue that one of
them must be cast down into the common masses.
The simple fact is that my
wife is superior breeding stock.
Both Rin and Sakura were born with equally
rare natural gifts and magical abilities.
And so both my daughters were in need of the
protection and nurturing attention of a mage family.
For the future of one daughter I must waste
the vast potential lurking deep inside the other?
What father would wish such a
woeful tragedy upon his children?
Common masses.
The memory of his children and their mother on that day.
This heartless man is writing it
off as something for the common masses.
If I was to preserve the hopes I
had for both sisters' abilities,
my only option would be to send one away.
That is why the Matou family's offer was such a godsend.
If she were to be adopted by a mage family,
it would give her that much
greater chance of reaching the root.
A mage is someone who is born with great power,
and before he knows it, he will
attain even greater heights of power.
Even before a mage embraces his destiny,
his responsibility to do so is in his blood.
That is what it means to be born the child of a mage.
If I fail, it falls to my daughter, Rin,
and even if Rin fails in her quest, then Sakura
may yet fulfill the dream of the Tohsaka family.
You bastard, you want them to fight each other?
Sister against sister?
Even if such a development were to come to pass,
it is still best for the future of my descendents.
What?
Glory will go to the victor,
and to the loser, honor to the family of her forbearers.
The best outcome I could possibly hope for.
You bastard, you're insane!
It is a waste of time to try to explain it to you.
You don't comprehend magecraft's grandeur,
and even turned your back and walked away from it.
A lowly traitor.
Screw you, bastard!
I'll make all you bastards pay.
You filthy rotten mages.
I'll kill you all.
Zouken and you.
Every last one of you.
I'll kill you all.
When you turned down the family leadership,
the Matou's magic secrets were passed on to Sakura.
In spite of the fact that I really should be thanking you
for my Sakura's future,
you are one man that I simply cannot abide.
The weakness revealed by shirking of your obligations,
the deficient character revealed
by your lack of indebtedness to it.
You, Kariya Matou, are a disgrace.
Having crossed paths with you again I
have no choice but to put you to death.
Don't talk so high and mighty, you inhuman bastard.
You're mistaken, shouldering one's
responsibilities is the first requisite of being human.
It is those who fail to do so...
...that are subhuman dogs.
Kariya.
Hear me now, bugs. Devour this bastard.
Eat him alive!
Oh yeah, go get 'em, Bluebeard!
Crush 'em down, tear 'em apart!
This place is God's toy box!
Saber!
I am much obliged, Saber.
I'll never be bored again as long as I live.
I won't have to go through all
the trouble of murdering people.
They'll die in droves without me lifting a finger.
They'll be flattened, chopped to bits, smashed, eaten.
They'll die and die and die left and right.
I'll be able to see one kind of guts and
gore after another that I've never seen before.
All day, every day, all around
the world, everywhere I look!
It'll be nonstop, never‐end...
It stopped moving.
Hm?
What the... hey, what happened?
Huh?
That's so pretty.
Now I get it.
No wonder I never realized it before.
Oh man, talk about not being able
to see the forest for the trees.
It was in me.
I was looking for my own guts.
I didn't have to go searching for it.
It was hiding right there all along.
Ryuunosuke!
I finally found you.
I've been looking for you my whole life.
What the hell, man?
If you were inside me all along,
I wish you would've
just told me so in the first place.
Ryuunosuke, my master.
How could you die and leave me here all alone?
But never you fear, dear Ryuunosuke,
for I, Gilles de Rais, will fulfill
the solemn promise I made to you.
Ryuunosuke, watch closely! Behold my offering to you!
I shall give you the greatest "cool!" ever!
I just put down the man I believe to be Caster's master.
It looks like I was right about him.
While all the other servants are being distracted
by the monster, shall I eliminate the next target?
Wait, Maiya, that's no ordinary monster.
It's a creature with limitless regenerative ability.
It's still possible that it could
reach the shore before it dissipates.
If it does and begins to feed, it's all over.
Caster will have a new source of
mana to maintain his physical form.
If that happens, the damage will spread even further,
and there's a risk that the Holy
Grail War itself will break down.
Exactly.
But how do we kill an indestructible monster?
The only way is to annihilate it in a single strike.
To do that, its entire body will have to be incinerated.
Leaving nothing, not even the smallest scrap of flesh.
Anti‐Personnel Noble Phantasms won't suffice.
An Anti‐Fortress one is needed.
Saber possesses just such an Anti‐Fortress Noble Phantasm.
However, because of Lancer's curse,
she can't use it.
We'll just have to wait and see
exactly what they can really accomplish
with their so‐called chivalric spirit.
Oh, this brilliant light!
You prolonged the inevitable.
The invincible king is about to
cry out the true name of the miracle.
It is too painful to look upon.
Is he trying to kill himself?
We must stop its advance!
I'm counting on you, Saber.