Street No. 07
"The Naito Flight of Love"
And Yet the Town Moves
Naito
Dental Clinic
Seaside
We will compare love to foreign foods.
Love is like spaghetti with meat sauce.
It is very average but each person has their own taste.
Love is like rice enveloped in an omelet.
You can't be distracted by the beautiful egg on the
surface and neglect the chicken fried rice on the inside.
Love is like curry.
The more you let it mature with time,
the more the flavor increases in depth.
That's a dirty picture.
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
FRESH FISH SANADA
1st Place: Type A
If you travel far, the distance
between you and the person
you admire may shrink!
Lucky Item:
A sash
Your fortune according to your blood type!
Today's first place is blood type A!
If you travel far, the distance between you
and the person you admire may shrink!
Keh. Where am I supposed to travel to on a weekday?
I'm off.
To make snarky comments to the TV first thing
in the morning means you're getting old.
Don't be listening in on me, Baldy.
How dare you call your parent bald!
Also, having crab for breakfast, are you kidding me?!
You should consider yourself fortunate
to have crab this early in the morning.
What part of having crab with your bread is fortunate?!
This is what you really call Kani-pan!
Note: In Japanese, "kani" means "crab" and "pan" means "bread."
Bus Route
Whoa! It's Arashiyama. What's up with that awful face?
Morning...
You're usually just barely tardy,
but today you're awfully early.
Oh.
Yesterday, I was counted tardy by a hair.
Because the bus stopped at every red light, I was late!
Of course it would!
Maybe... I should give up...
Arashiyama! Let's not give up and run!
Wajima...
Misawa...
Here.
Mori...
Yamakawa...
Here.
Wajima...
Here!
Go sit down.
Safe!
The tardy Arashiyama can stand in the hallway
while we have homeroom.
That's not fair!
List of Surnames *Maruko, Ota City, Tokyo*
Arashiyama
Wajima is the only one safe
just because of her last name?!
A difference in the order of attendance
is Heaven and Hell?!
If I were "Warashiyama" then I would've been
called last and I would've been safe...
Sob sob...
Sob. Struggle. Pfft.
Or something like that!
If you don't take standing there seriously,
I will mark you as absent.
Whoa!
Is that why you're up so early today?
That's a good mindset.
That's not it.
I stayed up all night and finished reading it.
Another mystery novel, huh.
I'll lend it to you.
Hmm. So, who's the culprit?
Some woman named Misuzu.
I'll give it back to you.
Oh!
Aww, that's beside the point!
Just read the book, it's interesting!
She's just like a bad drunk.
1/4 INTENT TO KILL
Thank you, God! Thank you!
Next Stop:
Next Stop:        Oya High School
Next stop is Oya High School...
How merciless! Is there no God or Buddha in this world?!
This extreme bliss...
I have to put an end to it with my very own index finger.
How cruel...!
Oh!
1st Place: Type A
If you travel far, the distance
between you and the person
you admire may shrink!
Lucky Item:
A sash
Your fortune according to your blood type!
Today's first place is blood type A! A, A...
If you travel far, the distance
Next Stop: between you and the person
you admire may shrink!
If you travel far, the distance between you and the
person you admire may shrink! May shrink! May...
If I get off here, I'm not a man!
Just as I am, I'm going to go as far
as I can go and rendezvous!
Where is this?
It's the last stop, so they say.
In one day, I gained 2 kilos, poko.
Are you kidding?! First period has already started.
I'm sorry... Um... I... f-fell asleep too...
Don't busses go around and around the same route?
I thought so too, but that wasn't the case.
There are so many things we don't know about the world.
The returning bus will arrive in about 20 minutes.
At the earliest, we'll get back to school
during second period.
It's so nice out.
We don't have gym today, do we?
It's such a waste to be inside the classroom all day.
Yamanoue
Garage
Coffee
Daimyo
Shall we just stay out here and play hooky?
What do you think?
Really?
Eh?
After eating barbecue, ramen would
sit heavily in your stomach, poko.
Wow, it's a town I don't know!
She switches over quickly.
Man, there are people living
even in places you'd never see.
Somehow I'm relieved and at the same time
a bit disappointed; it's a strange feeling.
Right?
Right.
Okay, Sanada! Let's go exploring!
You look so happy.
Oh, sorry, I have siblings who are much younger
than me, so it's a habit for me to hold hands.
Did you not like it?
Not at all! Not even a single bit did I dislike it!
But...!
To hold just anyone's hand is a bit of a concern,
considering you're a high school girl...
No, I at least choose the person.
Hiroyuki Sanada Ultimate Victory
Arashiyama
CONGRATULATIONS
I, Hiroyuki Sanada! I have successfully been chosen!
Sanada Ultimate Victory
Arashiyama
CONGRATULATIONS
party
I sincerely thank you for your warm support!
Hiroyuki                  Ultimate Victory
CONGRATULATIONS
Hiroyuki Sanada Ultimate Victory
5 seconds elapsed
20 seconds elapsed
35 seconds elapsed
My mind can't take it!
I bet the remainder of my life's
happiness meter is depleting fast!
Oh, it's a river.
It's the Tama River!
Do you think we can get home
by walking alongside the river?
Yeah, if we kept walking until our legs felt like sticks.
I skipped school...
What are you saying so late in the game?
Don't you think it's okay to do this once in a while?
That's true! Aside from studying,
there are other important things, right?
Right?
Oh, but what if I'm summoned tomorrow?
I'm your accomplice. If you are summoned,
I'll get summoned with you.
Uh-huh.
The last time we hung out together,
how many years ago was that?
I wonder.
When we were little, we used to hang out more often.
Wh-why do you think we stopped hanging out...?
What?
You don't remember?!
Huh?
It was you!
Who wants to hang out with a girl, stupid!
Let's go!
You said that!
I may have said it.
I'm terribly sorry.
Well, it's okay. But I did want to say it some day.
FRESH FISH SANADA
I'm home.
So that I won't forget how moved I was today,
I shall start writing a journal.
Um... today...
Today I was with Arashiyama...
We skipped school and hung out.
TODAY I WAS WITH ARASHIYAMA...
WE SKIPPED SCHOOL AND HUNG OUT.
Oh? Was that all?
In order to develop my strength in writing,
I should read a novel...
I already know who the culprit is, though.
Hiroto Shimabe
1/4 Intent to Kill
We will compare love to beverages.
Love is like a good cup of coffee.
Slightly bitter, it gives a sleepless night in exchange
for a sense of dependency and comfort.
Arashiyama, rei-co...
Note: Slang abbreviation for "iced coffee" (冷コー). Sounds like a female name.
The ingredients for which are: misinterpretation
and getting ideas stuck in your head.
Who are you calling Reiko!
Did you even forget the name of your childhood friend?!
Huh?! Wait, calm down, Arashiyama!
Rei-co is—
Grrr! So who is she?!
Sanada, I am surprised to hear you use
a classical way of saying things.
Huh?
Get out!
Even I did some bad stuff in the past, poko.
I can't sleep.
It must be because of that.
It's a bit early, but I'll go pee then go to bed.
Gyahhhh! A ghost!
Even when you're surprised,
you're considerate to not be loud.
Wow, I admire that.
Oh, it's you, Takeru.
What are you doing up this late at night?
Children should go to bed at 9 and wake up at 6.
I can't sleep.
If I could sleep, I wouldn't come to your room.
What's that supposed to mean?!
It's partly your fault, too.
4 hours ago
Hey, do you have any bottles about this big?
I need it for crafts.
Here! To replenish your nutrients when you
experience bodily fatigue! Napovitan C!
NAPOVITAN
C
DRINK
But I wanted empty bottles...
It was a very intense taste but
I didn't want to waste it, so I drank it all.
I'm not sleepy at all yet...
Even for me it only takes half a bottle,
but at your age you drank the whole thing?
But thanks to that, my castle came out perfect.
Well, aren't you hopeless.
Why don't we go for a walk for about
30 minutes to use up that excess energy?
Is it okay?! No it's not! Isn't it not okay?
He seems so excited...
Well, for a child it's midnight, but for me
it's just the beginning of the evening.
I'll lend you my chest, poko.
Why are we going out the back door?
The front door makes a rolling noise,
and so Mom would find us out.
What's with the backpack?
It's preparation for my journey.
At night, the enemies are stronger.
What are you talking about? Your game?
The one good thing about this town
is how low the crime rate is.
Oh? Seaside's lights are on. Are they still open?
Oh, don't go near it during the night.
See, it becomes a place where
middle-aged rebels gather.
Takeru, never grow up to be like that!
But, they seem to be having fun.
Grr...
I'm going to grow up to be a lawyer
and I'll defend you, just like Mom asked.
You won't need to!
Carbonated fizzy fizzy dibon carboxide, poko.
Wow! The shopping district is mostly closed.
Now, where should we go?
He's still up. I'll call him up to be our bodyguard.
FRESH FISH SANADA
Oh, did I forget my cellphone?
Sis...
Oh! Is there something useful in there?!
There's a lot of junk in there...
SS!
Es... es? Here.
And what am I supposed to do with this?
This isn't it? I can't seem to find anything
that fits the description of SS...
Man, I'll take it out myself.
SS is short for sling shot!
How should I know, you moron?! Call it a slingshot, idiot.
Hm, but because of the season, I only have 2 DDs left!
DD... Donguri Dan...
Note: Donguri Dan = Acorn Ammo
This time I figured it out by context.
Elementary school kids are so dumb.
Missed! Oh, my precious acorn...
Isn't it supposed to be called "DD"...?
If you pull on it too hard, it'll break!
I've been hearing voices for a while now...
Which one of you bastards did this?!
I'm gonna kill you, damn it!
Yikes...
I meant for him to be our protection,
but now we'll need protection from him!
If we apologize honestly, I think he'll forgive us.
I couldn't possibly think those eyes belong to someone
who'd listen to what anyone is saying.
Because Sanada probably thinks of you as...
No... it's okay.
What?
No, it's nothing.
To Sanada... I'll apologize a year from now.
Beware of
Perverts!
Raising your
voice and crime
prevention
alarms work
Takeru, aren't you hungry?
Eh? Oh yeah... now that you mention it,
I kind of think so...
Beware of
Perverts!
Raising your
voice and crime
prevention
alarms work
In front of the station...
No, I think I'm teaching him too many bad tricks already...
In front of the station, there's a food stand
that serves ramen.
What?! So late at night?!
Again, he looks so happy.
I'm so sleepy, I'm dizzy, poko.
Now that I'm faced with it, will I gain weight?
I should be fine if I split it, my tummy says!
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
Hey Hotori! What are you doing so late at night?
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
Did you just say some nonsense?! Huh, Mister?!
Shhh!
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
No, I didn't, I didn't.
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
"Hosaki menma was boiling
and it got so late at night," I said...
"Hosaki menma was boiling"...
"Hotori-chan what are you doing"...
That's too big a stretch!
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
Must've been hearing things. Is that so? Good...
Thought I was going to finally have to arrest her.
Why's he letting him eat ramen?!
He should just give the police
a bit of fish cake and kick him out!
Until the day I arrest you, don't get caught!
Any counter-comments or disagreements?
What? Am I Lupin?!
Big Sister seems mortified!
I don't hear any. I guess she's really not here.
Ramen
Line of Daimyos
I can't shake the feeling that one day
she's really going to get arrested...
Note: A reference to the theme of a very well-known children's anime,
Doraemon: "My head is teka teka (shiny)"
My head is poko-poko!
Takeru... I may have to have you defend me after all...
Green Mart
In the end, the only place that automatically
just lets people in is the convenience store.
Plastic Bottles             Glass Bottles   Cans                          Paper & Plastic
No wonder young people hang out here.
Green Mart
Convenience
Liquor  Tobacco
It's pitch black outside of the convenience store!
Again, he's being surprised by something very odd.
Well, it makes sense; after dinner,
you don't go outside anymore, do you?
This midnight notification is brought to you
by Cameras by Yamamura.
Shoujo Gaho
Takeru!
Midnight has struck, and so it is May 1st now.
Nighthead Radio. Your DJ is Amigo Kirihara,
and I will continue to bring you more music!
Huh... midnight, as in zero hour?
Oh. Yeah.
Zero hour... zero hour...
Zero means nothing is there
but zero hour exists... Scary...
It was April 30th until just a little while ago,
and now it's become May 1st.
You just now crossed the border of yesterday into today.
What was tomorrow just a little while ago became today,
and what was today became yesterday...
That's right.
You have witnessed the way the world works.
When was the first time I saw the border of the days?
I should've remembered it better.
Your shoes... You'll need to put them back
at the front entrance or else you'll get found out.
Oh yeah.
It was colder outside than I thought.
Your body lost some heat, so go soak
in the bath before you go to sleep.
Put the towel on there, and...
Will you be able to sleep?
Probably.
Big Sister, at night sometimes you go out, don't you?
Huh? Why?
The way you're being careful not to be found out
is all too well rehearsed.
Today isn't the first time, is it?
You may be better at being a prosecutor
than an attorney.
Um... I learned who the culprit is, poko.
We will compare love to snacks.
Oh! I thought up a trick that would let me
commit the perfect crime!
Love is like a banana.
That familiarity and those rich nutrients
make it a staple in daily life.
I would use a frozen banana to beat the
victim to death then eat the banana.
Then all that remains is just the banana peel.
A weapon would never be found,
and I can make it look like the victim accidentally
slipped and use that as the camouflage!
I'd be able to fool even the police...
A banana that was used as a weapon...
I would never want to eat that.
Oh! I wouldn't, either!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
The time is the 21st century!
Finally a modern convenience that is the fully
automatic laundry dryer has been invented.
Even if you forget to hang your laundry out to dry,
a dream world in which your laundry
won't smell like a wet rag is now here!
However!
It won't automatically fold and put away your laundry,
so there is still a long way to go
before it can be called truly, fully automatic!
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Eight,
"Fully-Automatic Band Music."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 08 "FULLY-AUTOMATIC BAND MUSIC"
We turn nihilistically round and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside