Come on, get up!
You stayed up all night again, didn't you?
Because I know for sure that your light was on until 2:30.
Ryuuji...from the hole in my ear...
...grains of rice...grains of rice...are dripping into glistening stea-steamed...
I brought your breakfast.
I'll go heat it up now while you go wash your face.
Breakfast...?
Alright.
Now I just need to do the dishes and the laundry.
Really...what a barren room.
Huh?  Cardboard boxes?
What's this?
A photo album?
This is...
What the hell are you looking at?!
Oh, Taiga, thi-?!
Yes, those are pictures of Kitamura-kun.  Do you have a problem with that?!
Even if you do, I won't tolerate it.
This...is Kitamura?
I-I-I can't help it!
For some reason they always turn out blurry.
Kitamura-kun makes me kind of...
Want me to take some for you?
Huh?
Photos...?
I will.
I mean I'm not that great, but at least it'd be better tha-
Wait a second!
How many frames do I get?
Ah, what kind of photos should I take?
A pensive side shot...during softball practice?
Oh, I can't forget a shot of him eating his lunch!
I've been telling you, I'll take as many as you want me to!
Even if you tell me as many as I want, there's always a limit!
Then take more than ten thousand times ten to the sixty-fourth power!
Good morning!
Ah!
Hey, morning.
You're late today.
Yeah, I stopped by the student office first today, so...
Ohaa!
'Ohaa' is an obsolete pop culture greeting like 'wazzaap'.
That's old.  That's too old, Taiga.
No, n-no, th-that was nothi-
Aisaka.
Ohaa!
Well then, I'm off first.
Ohaa...!
O-Ohaa?!
Hey...hey, did you get it?
Get what?
The "Ohaa," of course!
That was so spontaneous, how do you expect me to get that?
You good for nothing mongrel.
You know what...
Maruo, look at this for a second.
Hey, hey!  This Reader's Choice model looks just like you, Maruo.
Hey you guys, it's almost time to gather up.
Stop your pointless chatter and hurry out to the school grounds.
He's so hard to catch.
Even though he's the Vice President...he's still too stiff.
I want a reaction at least.
Yeah.
Kitamura is quite popular among the female students.
What, catching Maruo?!
I will ball you up with this one hand.
Maruo sounds like 'maru', the Japanese circular symbol that approximates a period.
Everyone!  Line up!
I've been hearing that a lot of you brats have been forgetting your student notebooks!
There's more evidence of this.
At last week's book-bag check, the student rule enforcer reported...uh...how many?
Fifty-nine students.
Ah...school-wide, fifty-six students forgot their-
Oh, whoops...I mean fifty-nine students.
Anyway, screw the details.  Forgetting your student notebooks is the same as forgetting our school pride!
Do you understand?!
Yes!
Good.
You're one to talk.
Telling us we forgot when you yourself forgot something.
Aisaka...
You, the puny one over there, you said something?
You forget to tell us to return to ease.
Huh?
At ease!
Oh, my mistake...
Everyone, at ease!
Who does she think she is, making us line up even though we're high schoolers?
And all the time droning on with her pointless, mundane speech.
Is that too much to ask for?
You're just putting your hands on your hips.
What?!
Hey, Aisaka...
This is good.  So you want to start something this morning?
You too, President, take it easy...
What do you think you understand?!
We're not having back or labor pains, so why should we put our hands on our hips?
Don't be so ri-
Aisaka!
A-Aisaka...
Can you please restrain yourself here?
Sorry, President!
Please continue your announcement.
Oh, okay.
What?  What just happened?
Did she just attack the president?
That girl...
A...mm...za...whoo...dos...desu...dooes?
She looks totally depressed.
No...she's excited?
Y-Ysu...wansu...knowsu...hemuserufu...
Okay, Haruta-kun, that's enough.
Um, who's next?   How about...Aisaka-san?
You're in high spirits today.
Then, why don't we have you read enthusiastically.
Oh, just kidding!
Haruta-kun!
This is impossible!
Go ahead and read with lots of enthusiasm!
Listen to me...
Hey, here's your lunch.
No, I've got no appetite.
I argued with the student body president and inconvenienced Kitamura-kun.
But...he restrained me by my underarms.
It's an underarm carnival...
Taiga?
But I still want to apologize!
Don't worry about that.
The student body president is not the type of person to care about those things.
Oh, lunch.
Do you mind if I join?
Oh, good, good!  Sounds like a great plan!
I'll join in too!
This sort of thing is great once in a while, isn't it?
Yeah!
Ah, I'm starving.
Itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu.
Today's side dish...today's side dish...I wonder what it is?
H-How did this happen?
Oh, it's fried chicken!
Taiga!  That's too obvious...
Oh Taiga, your lunch has a lot of side dishes!
Crap!
Our lunches are the-
Aisaka, you've been bringing a lot of lunches these days.
Did you make them yourself?
Ah...uh...he...
What?
Takasu does?
N-No, it's not like that.
Hey, you know how Kushieda was doing a side job as a cell phone decorator?
Well, I make lunches for some spending money.
Oh, I see.
I'd like to try one of Takasu's lunches someday.
Me too!
That lunch will be brownish and have an aura of refined masculinity.
It will be very stimulating.
U-Uh, right.
Well then, I guess I'll make some for everyone next time.
Kitamura-senpai, Kushieda-senpai.
We need to start soon.
Goodness, it's the softball manager.
Oh, we have a meeting.
Sorry guys, you can start without us.
Uh, sure.
That didn't go well.
Not well at all...
Kitamura-kun...Kitamura-kun...
Taiga?
Is it really okay if you just frankly tell Kitamura that I make your lunches?
Even when people finally realize that there's nothing going on between us...
What will I do?!
Calm down!
Why do you always act weird in front of Kitamura?
Listen, just be more careful from now on.
Hmm?  What?
If there's something you want to say, swallow first.
Hey, there's no meat in today's lunch.
If you want meat every day, then go to a family who does that and become their kid.
Wow, this much mildew in a public facility...
The roots are deep.
However...
...your luck ran out as soon as I found you.
Taka-chan, let's finish up for the day.
Okay!
I'll finish up the rest.  You can take off.
Okay, then.  Thanks.
Hey you, black enemy!  What's wrong, already old?
Alright!  Just for you, I'm going to use one of Takasu Ryuu's forty-eight secret tricks, the mildew-killing buster.
Ryuuji, what are you mumbling to yourself about?
Hurry up and come with me, you slow and stupid dog!
Wha-  Taiga, you're in the boy's bathro-
Who cares?!  Hurry up!
Hey...
What is it this time, Taiga?
What are you doing?
Oh...it's just Kitamura.
Hurry, hurry up!  Take it!
This kid...
Now, now!  Hurry!
Alright.
So, the shutter is...?
Now!  Do it now!
Hold on a second.  Let me change the settings...
Ah, just give it to me!
Oh, I get it.
So this is how those pictures became blurry.
Amazing, Kitamura-kun!  That's good just like that.
Goooooo!
Hey!
Hey, he's waving like crazy.
Shut up...
Klutz.
Welcome to Sudohbucks!
Manager, one Americana order!
One Americana coming up!
I'm surprised this place hasn't gotten sued yet.
Still, did you really need to print them all?
Hey, you're drooling all over them!
Heh...lots of Kitamura-kuns...it's a Kitamura carnival.
What are you doing?!
You shouldn't be carrying a knife since you get mad so easily.
I just want to help...you mongrel.
Huh?
You took pictures for me, so...
No it's really okay.  Plus, tomorrow I need to air out your futon.
If you keep making bad excuses, I'll cut you!
Cut me?  You...
Aren't you going to bring lunches...for Minori and K-Kitamura-kun?
Alright then.  Can you peel potatoes?
Don't make fun of me!
I can do something simple like that.  I'm not that helpless.
You just take the skin off, right?
Hand cooked food for Kitamura...
That's right,
Kushieda is going to be eating my cooking, so I should put some effort into this as well.
What are you do-
What?!
What?  See, the skin is nicely taken off,
and this way you can never cut your hand.
Uh...well, true...
Wow, rice balls for dinner?
It's just like a picnic!
These rice balls are so small and cute!
I made those!
What?  Aren't you a genius, Taiga-chan!
Well something like this is a safe bet no matter how much you practice,
and it doesn't require any peeling.
As I told you before, talk after you swallow.
Delicious!
It tastes like Taiga-chan's hands!
Here, I poured you some tea.
If you don't properly store those in a album, they're going to get damaged.
You're annoying, aren't you...
What?
Just as someone was offering to laminate pictures of the person you like.
You can do something like that?
Hm...well, yeah.
Alright!  Well then wait a moment.
Um...
As long as you protect it, no matter how much you fall or drop it into water, it would be fine.
Taiga, is something wrong?
N-Nothing at all.
Well, you don't have to pick just one.
Two or three...
You're noisy, aren't you?!
Just wait!  I'm trying to choose right now!
W-What...right now?
I just...
I'm going home.
Huh?  Why so suddenly?
I can't sit here and choose in peace, so I'm gonna go do it at home.
Hey, Taiga!  Wait!
What's with her?
I want photos too...of Kushieda.
Look, look at this!
I-Is this a yellow dead squid, or...no, is it slime?
Amazing, isn't it?!
I made pudding in a bucket!
T-This is...what do you call it...
A mental browser crasher.
Note: Kushieda is obviously rather twisted.
Pudding made in a bucket...where women's desires thrive!
But still, there was a lot and it didn't go so well.
The smoothness and the jiggly-ness became one,
and that was-
Hey!  You ladies over there.
Look, look at my prized bucket "Yu-Gi-Oh" cards.
Oh, this is a picture of Kushieda.
The smoothness and the jiggly-ness became one,
and that was mysterious, sort of the beauty of harmony...
A bit different from what I was hoping for,
but it will do.
Hmm...huh?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's just you.
You're still choosing?
Just be quiet.
What's with that attitude?
Just like yesterday when you left suddenly.
I've been telling you if you can't decide I'll do as many as you need.
What was that for?
If you're so persistent, then why don't you choose for me?
Well, then I'll leave it up to you.
Should I even choose from these?
That Taiga...
Are those Aisaka's?
Yeah, something like that.
They're pictures of me, aren't they?
N-No, you see these...are....well how should I say...?
Oh, speaking of which, I totally forgot.
I left one in here too.
So nostalgic.
W-Why do you have a picture?
Before, the photography club sold these.
And one of those-
No!  Never mind that, why do you have a picture of Taiga?
I liked Aisaka and I left it in there.
That's all.
Well a second after I confessed to her, I was rejected.
Oh, I've said too much.  Keep it a secret from everyone, okay?
What...?
Hey Takasu, what's wrong?
Takasu?
What the hell is that about?!
What a crazy thing you did.
That's too bad.
I was so surprised when he told me he liked me that I rejected him.
But...but...afterwards I kept thinking about it.
And after that I...I like...fell in love with him!
It was right about here...
Aisaka!  I like your straightforward personality that isn't afraid to show anger!
I'm in love!
Kitamura...
It was a weird confession, wasn't it?
You couldn't really tell if it was praise or insult.
But, I was happy.  It was good to know that there was someone who needed me just the way I am.
I wonder why, but I visualized the room that Taiga lives in.
I had all of those pictures, but I didn't have any I wanted.
I want that face.
The face of Kitamura-kun confessing to me...once again.
W-What's wrong with you?!  You're making me say all this stuff, you perverted dog!
You're saying it's my fault now?!
Well, who else's fault would it be?!
To be needed by someone... I wonder what kind of meaning that holds for Taiga.
Still, she really is clumsy, isn't she?
If she was going to fall for him later, she shouldn't have given an answer so quickly.
Right, Inko-chan?
And there's Kitamura too.
If he fell for her once, he needs to take responsibility and go out with her.
Oh-oh-ah-I-I-I-I-
You think so too, Inko-chan?
I...I...
That's right, tell 'em Inko-chan!
I-I-It's alright, isnt it?
All of a sudden, the naturally beautiful girl Kawashima Ami appears.
All I can say is, girls are scary!
What's that, Ami-chan?