Do it!
“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
I ran away. My legs froze, and I couldn't move.
The past indiscriminately follows you around.
How did you...
I just met the slasher...
And now... Cheers!
Hurry!
You don't want to join the Dollars, do you?
No, of course not.
You can't run away from your past, Masaomi.
Stop!
Opening Theme
"Complication"
ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
Lyrics by SHiNNOSUKE
Written and arranged
by ROOKiEZ is PUNK'D
(DefSTAR RECORDS)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
Rise of the Yellow Sky
A great person once said, "The world is fictional."
Or may have said so.
Even if they haven't, someone else must have said something similar.
Hey, welcome!
Long time, no see! You're here!
It's cheap! I give you free, President Kadota!
Who's the company president now?
Bring us five of your cheapest nigiri.
Yes, sir.
So what is it you want from us?
Mr. Head-of-the-Kokinzoku.
To us, the fictional world is a playground that's just as crucial as the real world is.
We value fiction and reality equally, so it's not like we dislike reality.
You understand what it means when the head of the Kokinzoku wants to talk to members of the Dollars, right?
Well, all right. Let me just say that we don't know much,
and that even some of us have been done in by the slasher.
I'd feel a lot better if you could clear up that misunderstanding for us, Kida.
Well...
Hey!
You drink tea. Catechin is good.
Hot!
Are you okay, President Kadota?
"If your mind is clear, even a fire feels cool."
No be angry. Tsk, tsk.
You really understand Japanese, don't you?
Or rather, you sure know how to hold a hot teacup.
Well, you guys might be the only ones who think that way, Kadota-san.
Isn't the Dollars a gang with no horizontal or vertical hierarchy?
For all you know, there could be a faction of the Dollars that is masquerading as the slasher.
They'd know that if they stabbed their fellow members as well, nobody would suspect them.
I see. Well, your logic is sound anyway.
So, what's their motive?
What's the point of a group of people attacking the Kokinzoku disguised as the slasher, if they're not after money or fame?
If I knew that, things would be easy,
and it's possible that they have a personal grudge.
Personal grudge?
I never heard of the Kokinzoku ever rubbing shoulders with the Dollars.
Who are the Dollars?
Blue Squares.
Kida.
They haven't forgotten what that gang did to us,
and we may have settled the matter back then,
but the resentment never went away.
That's what I think.
Is that why you've come to me?
Well, you know, don't you Kadota-san?
Tell me who the Dollars' boss is.
If I can, I want to find out how many of your old friends...
of the Blue Squares, are with—
Oh my, Kida-kun. You mustn't get reality and fantasy all mixed up, now.
The Blue Squares never existed.
Isn't that right?
And Saki?!
Are you telling me Saki was abducted by nonexistent people, and even now is in the—
That's right. Your ex-girlfriend was taken by nonexistent people.
What about it?
Karisawa-san, I'm getting really mad!
You're already really mad, aren't you?
Besides, Yumacchi was mad long before you were. So we're even.
Just like you're mad about your girlfriend, Kida-kun,
there are people who are angry that one of the Dollars is suspected of being the slasher.
If you don't call us even based on that, then don't come talk to us.
Although, you do owe us one.
If you, who ran away, are trying to bring up the past with Dotachin, who rescued Saki,
then we'll treat the past as a mere product of delusion, and relegate it to another world.
If you value reality and fiction equally,
then you should treat the reality you don't want as fiction.
That's how we do things.
That's not right, Karisawa-san.
It isn't?
Assuming the Blue Squares actually existed, they were the first to be ruined.
I'm just opposed to being treated exclusively as the bad guys because of it.
Is that so?
How embarrassing! I just made a complete fool out of myself!
I'm... sorry.
No, no. It's all our fault.
We're sorry about what happened to Saki.
No, you guys aren't the ones who should be apologizing.
Even if you were still bitter about it, I wouldn't mind.
We were the ones who did that to a middle schooler like you.
Well, Kadota-san, you don't have to...
No matter how hard you try to get rid of it, the fact remains that you were involved.
And, if you'll let me say it, I don't know who our boss is, nor do I plan to find out.
Also, I'll say this one more time...
The slasher and the Dollars have nothing to do with one another,
and we have no reason to quarrel with the Kokinzoku.
Is that right?
Well actually, I think there is one person who knows the Dollars' boss.
Who is it?
Hold on. What will you do if you find out? Tell me first.
If that person told you the name of our boss,
would you go out to tea with him and have a nice chat?
Or would you have the Kokinzoku abduct him?
I just want to track down the slasher.
Is this what all of the Kokinzoku want?
If you could manage the Kokinzoku like you used to,
I'd trust you and even help you myself.
However, things have changed while you were gone.
Don't say you haven't noticed.
I still think they–
the Kokinzoku– are my comrades.
Even you don't know what to do.
Even if the Dollars were to blame,
that shouldn't make any difference to you, should it?
Fights between rivaling gangs...
You hate them, so you...
Ran away.
However, sometimes the past you've chased away comes back in a twisted form.
However, this time it's not just the Kokinzoku and its allies.
Someone close to me, who has no ties with the Kokinzoku or my past, was kidnapped.
I can't forgive that.
And that's your...
Right. It's my own personal problem.
I'm just using them, the Kokinzoku, as an excuse while I try to resolve it.
If you're aware of that then I won't say anything.
I'll leave the rest to the person who knows our boss, and to our boss' orders.
However... if you guys still declare us as your enemy...
If we do... then what?
We'll accept your challenge, and fight.
Are you prepared for that?
Do you understand that simply because you're after revenge,
this is no longer a child's fight, unlike the ones people your age pick so often?
I...
All the other customers are scared.
Take your conversation out front.
It's ready!
Five Kremlin onigiri cakes, yes, President?
You argue? That because you're hungry.
Eat sushi, fill your belly, fill your dreams,
this is human belly dream factory,
yes?
Thank you, Simon.
I-Itadakimasu.
Scary! The shop owner's scary!
Hey. Doesn't that count as attempted murder?
Yeah, a butcher knife really stabs deep, don't you think?
See you later, Kida.
Once again, don't have foolish thoughts.
Still, that owner guy is dangerous!
If I'd been a few inches to the right, I'd be done for!
Sorry, but I thought he was really cool!
Me too!
I can totally see him facing off with the main character of a cooking
manga, getting all mad, like: "A butcher's knife is not a child's toy!"
Maybe he's a former martial arts master for the Russian army who was fighting the Mafia, hiding himself among us...
running a sushi shop in order to disguise himself to the world.
If that were the case, he wouldn't open a shop with a name like Russian Sushi.
Horada... Horada...
What's that, Kadota?
A new incantation?
Dotachin used: "Horata horata!"
Is that a binding or a summoning spell?
Maybe it's a lightning attack.
Kida was saying it back there.
Well, he was saying something like,
"Even if we track down the Dollars, we won't find the slasher."
I... no,
we don't think so.
What?
There's a rumor that the black biker is one of the Dollars.
Why do you bring up the black biker?
Last night, we saw something unbelievable.
I see.
The black biker helped someone with a Japanese sword to escape,
so she could be the slasher's accomplice...
Also, a guy named Horada said he was beaten by the black biker before.
Horada? Horada...
Then it's, "Horado Hora!"
What's wrong? You've been thinking for a while.
It's nothing big, I think...
That's right. I could be wrong.
About what?
Nothing. I just thought one of the people I used to know had that name.
It would make sense for a portion of the Dollars to ally themselves with the black biker and go after the Kokinzoku.
Hey, Yumacchi. Doesn't this all sound weird to you?
What about it?
Didn't the slasher try to take out the black biker before?
Togusa even hit her with his car.
And finally, she was crushed by Shizu-chan, so...
However, the truth remains that fifty incidents occurred during the same evening... Yet, even then...
Either way, the slasher isn't going to show up.
Those people picked a fight with Heiwajima Shizuo.
I think you know how that ended.
Still...
Here's the number of the guy who knows the Dollars' leader.
The rest is up to you.
You don't look too happy.
You'll scare off the other customers looking like that.
Now finish eating and leave with a smile on your face.
Thank you very much.
No good, fighting.
You people are plenty happy, so don't take people's happiness away.
You should try to understand them.
Hey, I recently memorized this.
"Pitiful people are no-good catfish."
I think it's, "By doing good for others, you also do good for yourself."
Kida, boy, are you a catfish?
This sure is good.
How boring. It's simply dull having nothing to do.
Mind if I hit you?
Go ahead. That's why I'm paying you.
What's this chocolate you sent to the Awakusu Club?
There was a pistol inside. What about it?
Well, look.
About half a year ago, someone stole some pistols from the Awakusu Club and ran off, right?
Yeah, the guy that disgusting Dullahan was chasing.
Yeah. Celty got most of those guns back without any problem,
but one of them went missing.
Which is why...
I thought you'd call sooner or later.
He's bluffing?
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah. I'll be there soon then.
The only one who really can't run away from your past is yourself.
Someone important once said, "The world is a symbol."
Or probably said so.
Even if they haven't, someone else must have said something similar.
What a nostalgic expression.
It's just like your old face.
Even though you were in middle school, you looked just like an adult.
Let me be daring and greet you, filled with nostalgia about those times.
Welcome back.
I know what you want to ask me.
Well, I could've answered you on the phone,
but I didn't think it would've made for light conversation.
I hear your friend got stabbed.
What was her name? Sonohara Anri, was it?
It looks like you need her more than you do the kids from the Kokinzoku.
Once upon a time,
a boy who was inspired by manga and dramas, created a gang called the Kokinzoku.
The Kokinzoku started a fight with another gang who wore the color blue as their emblem, and gave him a dilemma.
Then a genius tactician gallantly appeared.
Hey. Why are they all girls?
However, he wasn't Zhuge Liang, but more like Cao Cao?
One group, who was cornered during the fight, kidnapped the boy's favorite princess,
and the boy ran to rescue her, but became frightened along the way...
If this girl you like got involved in the Kokinzoku's battle and sustained a heavy injury...
I see, I see.
It would be just like what happened to Saki-chan.
You must be thinking something like this.
"Sure, I loved Saki."
"However, I was too scared to save her."
"Was my love for her false?"
"Was it just her body that I was after?"
"Did I even love her as much as I thought I did?"
He's popping them off like bubbles.
Eventually you came to wish that it was true.
If so, you'd be able to put your life on the line for the woman you really love.
She's the test case, is she?
This Sonohara Anri girl.
If that's what you think, Izaya-san, then fine.
Either way, I only want to accomplish it.
Your revenge on the slasher?
Or the destruction of the Dollars?
Depending on your answer, Izaya-san, it could be both.
Nice preparation.
I understand. This is so you can move on.
And so, I'll gladly tell you all the facts, the truth,
and the helpless reality you want to know about.
Originally, those three were different,
but this is one of those times when they're all one and the same.
By the way, how's Mikado-kun?
Come on. You introduced me to him this spring, didn't you?
Your friend, Ryugamine Mikado-kun.
Why are you bringing up Mikado right now?
Well, I just think he's also getting really worried about things.
He has nothing to do with this.
I haven't talked to him about the Kokinzoku,
and he's shy like always, but he's doing just fine.
He lives every day like he's having fun.
Are you jealous of him for living such a peaceful life?
I told you, he has nothing to do with this.
What if he did?
Oh. I see, I see. He's well, is he?
Celebrating his life, even though he's the reason his friend is anguished.
Wait a minute!
What do you mean, Izaya-san?
You know what I mean.
The Dollars' boss is your best friend in the whole world,
Ryugamine Mikado.
Of course, you may be the only one who thinks he's your best friend.
Reality is always a burden.
We recreated the world to get away from this troublesome reality.
We built walls, separated the important stuff from the garbage,
put all the stuff we like on our side,
and threw everything else out.
After we did, everything was surprisingly peaceful.
You can make a whole world of cute people, tsunderes, and boys' love!
What a discovery!
It's the only good way to bridge the gap between fiction and reality.
Did you know?
Apparently, the Dollars and Kokinzoku just went at it again.
Again?
Scary, isn't it?
But it was just another small fight, right?
Well, I heard that this time they directly attacked the Kokinzoku's hideout.
How daring.
Hey.
That black rider–
She teamed up with the slasher and attacked the Kokinzoku's secret base or something.
What's wrong, Setton-san?
Once again...
Even though it's you, Kanra-san, it's hard to believe.
It sounds like nonsense.
What are you talking about, guys?
We're talking about anime.
No we're not, Setton-san.
We're talking about the new SFX movie, Saika-san.
Oh, I see.
Even you, Tanaka Taro-san...
It looks interesting.
This year, they changed producers twice and changed all their script writers too.
I'll have to go see it, then.
By the way,
it's all a lie, no matter what they say.
What is?
I hear the Shogun of the Kokinzoku and the boss of the Dollars are talking about a direct confrontation.
Really?
Masaomi!
You left without stopping by our class. What's wrong?
Well, you know.
And you skipped yesterday...
You look well today.
Kida-kun...
There you are!
Takiguchi.
Ryugamine, did you tell someone I'm with the Dollars?
You too, Kida!
What do you mean?
You don't know?
The Dollars and Kokinzoku are in a dispute.
Today, some guy was going around asking about me.
I haven't told anybody.
Me neither.
Good, then. I'll see you!
Bye!
I have to go, too.
Let's go together.
I have some business.
My vehement fan girls won't leave me alone. You understand.
Well, bye.
Masaomi.
Listen up. I'm forbidding any brawls.
If you're provoked, let it go.
But, Shogun...
Don't give the enemy a reason to take advantage of you.
If the slasher is one of the Dollars, then get some evidence first.
Shogun. You said you'd talk to someone about the Dollars' boss.
Did you find anything?
No.
Some of us can't bear to let them get away with what they did two days ago.
If they lose their patience...
Then I'll be prepared.
Wait! Hey!
What's wrong?
Let me tell you why this happened to you.
It's because you have no color.
You think you're safe without any color?
Guess again!
In the real world, nobody's gonna save someone who doesn't wear colors.
An organization with no bonds...
That's something you don't find anywhere but on the Internet!
We must exterminate it from reality!
We, the Kokinzoku!
Sometimes, reality sinks to the level of a crappy sequel.
Masaomi?
Takiguchi was...
...beaten by the Kokinzoku.
Takiguchi-kun?
I'm gonna go see him.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time:
Lost at Sea
Durarara
Why didn't I quit back then?
What do I know about the Dollars?
If I stay this way, my life won't change.
However...
Next time: Lost at Sea