Hurts, doesn't it?
Magi carry the pain of that Crest for their entire lives.
Your dad really gave you the perfect name.
Your origin lies in severing and binding, kid.
It's a little different from destroying and regenerating.
If you cut a thread and tie it back together,
the thickness will be different where the knot is, right?
In that sense, it carries the
meaning of irreversible change.
"Kiritsugu", written with the
characters for "cut" and "tie".
I have the perfect Mystic Code for you.
I've powdered some of your ribs and put a bit of it in here.
Your origin will materialize in anything that this hits.
If you fire at your target with their Magic Circuits active, it will cut, then tie the circuits improperly.
One shot will incapacitate almost any Mage.
You have sixty-six of them in total.
Use them sparingly.
Natalia, can you hear me?
Just a little longer.
Roger.
Natalia, now.
In the end...
After leaving the island, I spent the next several years
with Natalia Kaminski, the woman who took me from there.
That meant choosing the same path as Natalia.
That is, the path of a hunter.
Natalia did not belong to any organization.
She was a total freelancer, in it only for the money.
The Mage's Association and the Holy Church.
The strife between those two large
organizations kept her business booming.
Since that day, I've witnessed many
tragedies like the one at Alimango Island.
I learned that similar tragedies
occurred all over the world every day.
Are you trying to become a champion of justice?
Was there no meaning to it?
I thought I killed my father to keep
more deaths like this from happening.
Killing one man won't change anything.
Kill every last person like this bunch in the world.
If you could do that, it might be possible.
I was kidding. Don't take it seriously.
No matter what happens, do what you must to survive.
That's the rule I set for myself regarding this business.
No matter what happens,
prioritize your life above all else.
If you try to save others but end up
dying yourself, it'll all be for naught.
I know it's not possible to save everyone.
I just want to save as many as I can.
Do what you want.
Yet another tricky target.
Do you know him?
Odd Vorzak, a Mage.
He's a Dead Apostle that uses his bee
familiars to increase his number of Ghouls.
The Mage's Association is offering a huge bounty for him.
You know a lot about him.
He causes a lot of destruction.
He completely upended the last town he visited.
A town...
Natalia, can I have one?
What was the legal smoking age in your country again?
I won't stop you, but they aren't good for you.
Where's he headed?
A flight from Paris to New York that leaves in four days.
Vorzak will be on board.
I'll take this flight.
I missed Vorzak once.
You've gotta clean up your own mess, right?
So even you fail sometimes?
That's how tough he is.
What should I do?
Most likely, he has allies in New York.
I want you to get rid of them.
You'll fight Vorzak alone?
He can't carry his bees into the passenger cabin.
No worries about missing him this time.
You talk too much, kid.
Kid, do you copy?
Okay, loud and clear.
Good luck to both of us.
That was easier than I expected.
The less that's required to
neutralize him, the better, Natalia.
All right, Kiritsugu.
What about the preparations to carry
his body out of the passenger cabin?
I've secured a vehicle.
Now we just need a doctor to carry the sick patient out.
As long as you're fine with me having no license.
Hey!
Natalia, what's wrong?
Ghouls!
We have a problem.
He was keeping the bees inside his own body?
Natalia, get out.
How many feet above the ground am I?
Unfortunately, I didn't prepare to skydive—
This isn't good.
Looks like the cockpit's down.
There's no other way.
Natalia, you can't...
I'm going home.
I'm going home alive, carrying Vorzak's body.
For that to happen, I need to
do something about this plane.
Anything you want to say?
Yeah...
Natalia, you can do this.
That will do.
Prepare a nice, warm bed for me, and wait.
Can you hear me, kid?
You didn't fall asleep, did you?
Loud and clear, Natalia.
It's a rough morning, since we've both been up all night.
If you had gone to sleep in a bed
last night, I'd strangle you to death.
Now, there's good news and bad news.
Which do you want first?
Don't you always start with the good news?
Okay.
First, the good news.
For the moment, I'm alive.
The plane is also undamaged.
I managed to get to the cockpit fairly easily,
though repairing the comms array wasn't so easy.
I think I can pilot it, assuming it works similar to a Cessna.
Have you contacted the control tower?
I have.
They initially thought it was some joke.
They said they'll escort me courteously.
And the bad news?
I'm the only one who hasn't been bitten.
Three hundred passengers and crew.
They've all become Ghouls now.
The cockpit door is all that separates
me from an airborne horde of the dead.
Spooky, right?
Given all that, do you think you can make it back alive?
Well, the door's pretty tough.
They're scratching at it as we speak,
but they won't get through.
It's the landing that worries me.
I don't know if I can handle something this big.
I'm sure you'll be able to manage it.
Were those words of encouragement?
Good to hear them.
I can handle the landing,
but what do I do with these monsters?
No need to worry about that.
I have it all worked out, Natalia.
Good to know.
Fifty minutes to the airport.
Too long to spend praying.
Kid, talk to me for a while.
Sure, no problem.
You put me in a real dilemma when you
said you wanted to help me with my work.
It didn't look like I could say
anything to change your mind.
Did I show that little promise as a student?
No, the opposite.
You had too much potential.
Far too much...
What do you mean?
The ability to separate your feelings as you pull the trigger takes most killers years to develop.
You had it from the start.
It's a hell of a gift.
But choosing your calling based solely on your
talents won't always guarantee you happiness.
If you act only on what you should do
without heed for what you want to do,
you're nothing more than a machine, a phenomenon.
It's not how a human being should live.
I always thought of you as a much colder person.
What are you talking about? Am I not?
Have I ever pampered you, even once?
You're right.
You've always been strict on me,
and you never held back.
You did everything you could to teach me.
Normally, it's the father's job to train up a boy.
Well, you know...
In your case, I'm sort of the one who
deprived you of your chance for that.
Well, anyway, I did feel pretty bad about it.
This was the only way of life I could teach you.
So you consider yourself my dad?
Don't confuse my gender, punk.
At least call me "mother".
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I've spent a long time alone in this bloodstained business.
So long that I even forgot I was all alone.
Well...
It's been pretty entertaining in its own way.
Having something like a family, that is.
Me too.
I really did think of you as a mother.
I was happy not to be alone.
Come on, Kiritsugu.
Quit saying stuff that'll embarrass
us the next time we see each other.
Geez...
You're throwing me off.
I land in twenty minutes or so.
If I screw up when the time comes because
I'm laughing over old memories, I'll end up dead.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I'm getting too old for this.
Maybe I screwed up so badly because
playing family made me lower my guard.
If so, it's probably about time.
Maybe I'll retire.
If you quit your job, what would you do then?
If I'm out of a job...
The only thing left for me would be to play the mother's part.
You really are...
...family to me.
Did you see that, Shirley?
I killed again.
I killed her, just like my dad.
I didn't mess up, like I did with you.
I saved a lot of people.
If Natalia had landed successfully,
there's no telling how many people might've died.
Her sacrifice prevented that...
That's why...
That's why, Shirley...
I...
Shut up! Shut up!
You bastard!
Hey, Kerry.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I...
Twinkling quietly, the stars are scattered across the sky
Lost prayers fill the heavens and earth
Episode 19
Where Justice is Found
Unblossomed futures gleam on the slender branches
Still reluctant, I let the buds fall
Look, the time is ripe
A plump, golden fruit
For simply plucking it with these hands
Will cause the world to end
The whiteness of the falling, unblemished snow
Will disappear once it learns of warmth
A beautiful dream was enough to tear you to pieces
The truth and kindness behind those cold eyes
Twinkling quietly, the stars fill the sky of prayers
Until your screams bring this dream to an end
Who are you?
What a bad joke.
How does the life you've stolen from Sakura feel?
By my Command Spell, I order my puppet...
You look like your old self.
This is a battle I chose to fight.
You know, I really am happy.
Next Episode
Return of the Assassin