There will be strong north winds tomorrow,
and towards the Pacific,
--I should take in the laundry and dry it inside.
--scattered rain is expected.
--The temperature is two degrees
--Grandma, I'm home!
--colder than previous years...
Oh, welcome home.
I'm going to borrow Bro's PC, okay?
Oh my.
Oh, come on! Hurry it up!
I'm not good at using PCs!
Let's see...
"Kominato Ruko"
"Folder" "Inbox" "Drafts" "Sent Mail"
"Folder" "Inbox (1)" "Drafts" "Sent Mail"
"Date and Time"
This...
No way!
Is she trying to gather
all the Selectors together to battle?
It's really close by...
The truth rests solely on
the front/back of a card
It has not yet been solved
Upon the dazzling, dizzying stage,
destroy those entangled emotions
as many times as it takes to satisfy you
What should the tomorrows
wandering after fate's beckoning
choose and discard so that
they can become one?
I can't afford to disclose my reproachable hand
The days spent draining
the already-dry sea of regret
desire within limited words forgiveness
for the unplanned smile
I don't mind forgetting reality
I don't want to know anything now
Okay?
Isn't it around here?
Yup.
Ruko?
Here?
When that's finished,
it means that a big pillar
is going to fit in that alley, right?
Ru?
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
Ru...
Um, Ruko?
If something's bothering you,
or you've got something on your mind...
just say it.
Yuzuki...
Am I... scary, after all?
Like, how people can't
tell what I'm thinking?
Huh?
No, that's not what I was trying to say!
You try to figure things out yourself,
and hold them inside.
Oh, wait... I was like that too.
Um, well, sorry!
But, see this?
We are friends, you know?
Yuzuki, why...
Why are you so kind?
Huh?
Wh-What are you saying? That feels weird.
Why are you so strong?
Ru?
If I...
...could only be like that.
Yuzuki...
Tama...
I'll...
...battle Iona-san.
Wh-What are you saying?!
You said you weren't going to battle!
Yup...
but...
But...
...I have a wish now!
I...
I want to save Yuzuki...
...Tama...
...everyone who became LRIGs.
I want everyone to be returned to their world!
That's my wish.
No matter what I have to sacrifice,
that's my one and only wish!
Ru...
I appreciate your feelings,
but that can't be done.
Why?
I said before...
Eternal Girls were originally LRIGs.
And, just like me, LRIGs
were originally ordinary girls.
Things which can't possibly be made true
by a normal girl can't come true.
There are some wishes
that can never come true, right?
For example, like going to the future.
Exactly.
But, that is not something I determine.
What?
The wishes at stake in the Selector battles...
Most wishes are not
too hard to make come true.
Common sense...
Self-protection...
Such aspects prevent wishes from coming true.
But...
...an LRIG must not be
bound to such aspects.
Continuing to refuse the Selector's wish
only means you will
never return to the outside.
An LRIG seeking to return...
rely upon wishes having the
potential of coming to fruition.
For that wish to come true,
--any underhanded deed may be taken.
--But...!
That is the very reason for
the ritual of acknowledgement.
A final trigger is needed.
Now, together with me.
I accept...
I... accept!
...the laws of the Selector.
And...
--...now, a new Eternal Girl will be born!
Once an Eternal Girl,
she is obligated to fulfill the wish made.
With the wish accepted,
and the contract completed, all is final.
If the wish is not made true,
the Eternal Girl
will disappear.
Remember what Hanayo-san said before?
That Hitoe's memory can't be restored?
That's because Hanayo-san
determined that can't happen.
W-Wait, then what about my wish?
I have no clue how LRIGs get out of the card.
Maybe that girl knows.
But, I don't know how to go back to her.
Maybe it could be done...
--What?
Tama, not sure, but...
...I feel like...
...there's a way to make
the LRIGs return to normal.
What do you mean?
I don't know!
But, Tama feel like it could be done...
I feel like there's a way...
Tama...
Maybe...
That's stupid!
It was all for nothing!
There was no need for us
to go through all these battles.
A wish that anyone could fulfill with effort.
Risking it on cards,
disappearing, and more... is absurd!
There are exceptions.
Not all Eternal Girls
are normal girls.
Among them...
...may be a special girl
who holds mysterious powers.
What do you mean, "mysterious powers"?
That's just ridiculous!
You being an LRIG now...
...still deny matters of mysteries?
It's about time.
Morning has arrived for you to be
an LRIG card, to meet your Selector.
W-Wait! Who are you...?!
I will always be here.
Here, in the rift of the world
of the cards, and of reality.
Now then,
good morning.
Something's different about
Tama from the other LRIGs.
Maybe she's this "special girl"
that she was talking about.
Th-Then my wish can...!
No good.
Huh?
Did you forget?
If your wish comes true,
you're going to be an LRIG!
B-But...
if my wish is to release
all the LRIGs from their cards,
I may not become a card.
Who knows?!
You could become
the only one sealed as a sacrifice...
or worse could happen!
But... But!
Let's think a bit more, Ruko.
We may meet again,
and we could talk like this, too...
But...
as for those who aren't Selectors,
like your grandma,
you may not meet them again.
Hitoe?
That's... my LRIG, yes?
Hitoe, um...
Please give me back my LRIG.
Hitoe?!
Hitoe! Listen to me!
U-Um... Hitoe? I...
I have nothing to speak to you about.
Hitoe...
Wait!
Hitoe?
I will participate in Urazoe Iona's fan event.
If you want to talk to me,
we can do it on the battlefield.
If my wish comes true...
Grandma...
I'm home--
Oh my, it's you...
She's doing fine.
She made friends too.
Yes, right.
What...? Now, stop.
That was awhile back already.
There's no point blaming yourself.
But...
stop acting as if you're a mother, too.
You just couldn't become a parent.
"Miyako"
You weren't meant to be one.
Moreover...
Ruko isn't as adult-like
or as childish as you think.
Yes, right... I'll call you.
Okay then...
Ru-chan? Dinner is ready.
Mom?
I have a wish now.
A wish?
When... I was a kid...
Mom and Dad always used to fight.
It was really sad.
I knew Dad and Mom
wanted to be close together.
But, seeing them fight was so sad.
I figured wanting to be
close made things painful.
With Grandma and Big Bro,
I figured I didn't need anyone else.
But...
Ru-chan? You said something
about "for your friends," right?
Is your wish about that?
Is it something bad?
It's not bad!
Then is it good?
I think it's good. It has to be...
Ru-chan, you're Grandma's treasure.
If Ru-chan thinks it's good,
then that's something wonderful for me, too.
Do what you need to do.
Wishes do come true.
Especially a wish from a kind girl like Ru-chan.
Grandma...
Oh, what a huge baby I have here.
Ru...?
Are you really going to battle?
Yup.
We can battle Iona-san again, Tama.
--I bet you can't wait!
--Tama doesn't want to battle.
Huh?
Grandma said that because she doesn't know!
If she knew, she would say no for sure!
Tama wants to be Ru's LRIG!
I want to be with Ru forever!
Tama and Grandma don't want
to be away from you ever!
Tama... I'm sure it'll be okay.
But, Yuzuki said that she doesn't know!
When my wish comes true...
...and I don't become
an LRIG and stay as myself,
then...
let's always be together.
Tama, you can be with me.
We'll have breakfast together...
We'll go to school together...
We'll be friends with Yuzuki and Hitoe...
It's closed now, but during summer
the candy store at the corner
sells really good ice cream.
Together we'll buy some... and go home.
So, please...
Tama...
don't like.
No...
But still...
Tama...
I...
have to go.
Be careful, Ru-chan.
Okay.
Will you be back by dinner?
Dinner...
I want to have potato gratin!
With plenty of bacon.
Yup!
I'm going now.
I made a decision, so I need to go.
Everyone knows
that there are only Selectors here.
Everyone, welcome to the fan event--
No--
Welcome to the Selectors-only WIXOSS Party.
This building is owned by my father.
Construction is off today.
No one will get in our way.
We are doing battle for our wishes.
But... the number of wins
required for our wishes is unknown.
Our conditions are not clear.
I believe everyone is frustrated by this.
But, with this many Selectors
gathered to do battle,
some are bound to reach their conditions.
Today, a number of Eternal Girls will be born.
A number... of Eternal Girls?
But, with the wins, many others will lose.
I have no intention
of having random battles
to lose rights to be an Eternal Girl.
The battles will be conducted as a tournament.
If you lose, you will be
removed from this battle.
This is to prevent
unnecessary casualties.
And whichever Selector
makes it to the end,
I will have fight me in battle.
Twelfth floor, number four?
Are you all ready? Now then...
...let the battle begin.
Open!
Tama, Grow!
Gothic Boundary!
I'm sorry!
I'll win all of this
and save you and everyone!
Summon, Mitsurugi!
This is the final blow, Tama!
Tama?
Tama...?
Tama needs to agree with me
or else my wish won't come true.
I'm sorry, Tama!
"Akane" "Naruse" "Kominato" "Konaka"
I still...
need to keep battling.
It looks like we meet again.
You're willing to talk now, right?
On the battlefield.
--Open!
I don't sense any Eternal Girls being born.
Yes...
But, it looks like some Selectors
have lost their third battle.
I'm going to go there.
To that white room.
Where she's waiting.
I bounce Sevieria, and attack!
Yuzuki, Grow.
Banish Mikagami.
Hitoe...
She's a lot better now!
Splitting Conviction.
Tama... I'm sorry!
Yuzuki, attack. Banish Square.
Hitoe...
This...
isn't right.
About what?
Back when you and Yuzuki battled...
it was a lot different!
Ruko...
When we were playing WIXOSS
together, it was really fun.
But, I didn't think that was enough back then.
I wanted to battle more seriously.
Ruko...
But, the thought that we can't
have battles like that anymore...
anymore...
I knew it.
Hitoe...
still has memories of us.
Yuzuki?
Hitoe, listen to me.
Us three, we used to be friends.
What?!
Yuzuki!
Does it hurt? I'm sorry.
But I want you to remember!
Y-Yuzuki, Hitoe is suffering...!
Ruko! Do you want Hitoe to stay like this?!
Being controlled by Selector battles...
And just when we finally became friends...
I want to have a battle
like how we played before!
I want to battle as friends!
Stop... Stop...!
Hitoe! Please remember!
Your wish already came true!
You don't need to rely
on the cards! It's already true!
No... No, no!
Hitoe, do your best!
Let's again--
--Just shut up!
--Hitoe!
I don't want to hear any more of this!
I... I want to make my wish come true!
I told you! Your wish is already true!
--So listen--
--No!
Please... Please...!
Let me have my wish come true!
Hitoe?
Hitoe?!
That scrunchie...!
Now then... Isn't it about time?
This is...
...my final battle as Urazoe Iona.
Yes...
It was fun battling beside you, Iona.
With you,
you scum.
I'll be beside you to the very end...
Selector.
"That Choice..."