Armin...
It's nice I could be a "good person" for you.
For now, you've won your bet.
But...
...my bet...
...begins now!
We believe we've found out who the Female Titan is.
Her name is...
Annie!
I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"Mercy"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 2"
"Several days earlier"
What's takin' so long?
Where the hell are Erwin's men?
At this rate, the Military Police
escort's gonna show up before them.
Must be having a hell of
a hard time taking a shit.
You're very talkative today, Captain.
Don't be stupid.
I talk plenty.
I'm sorry.
If only I hadn't made the wrong choice then,
none of this would've happened...
I told you. No one knows
how things will turn out.
--Sorry I'm late.
--Not at all...
Guys!
U-Umm...
We believe we've found
out who the Female Titan is.
Huh?!
We will capture her this time.
We do it the day after tomorrow,
while passing through Stohess
District on our way to the capital.
This will be our first and last chance at her.
Once on the other side,
the government will take custody of Eren
and we'll have difficulty investigating
those bent on destroying the walls.
Both of which will foster
humankind's destruction.
We'll have to bet everything on this operation.
The plan is this...
While passing through Stohess,
we use Eren as bait
to lure the target into
this underground passage.
Given the target's size and strength,
if we can get her as far down as possible
we should be able to
immobilize her in her Titan form.
But, in the event that
she transforms before then...
...it'll be up to you, Eren.
Yes, Sir!
Are we certain the target will
actually be in Stohess, then?
Yes. The target is a
member of the Military Police.
The Military Police?
It was Armin who identified her.
We believe that she killed
the two Titans we caught alive...
...and that she might have trained
with you in the 104th Cadet Corps.
H-Hold on a minute!
The 104th Cadet Corps...
The name of the girl we
believe to be the Female Titan...
Y-You can't be serious...
...is Annie Leonhart.
O-Oh, no...
Damn! That ring...
She knew I was lying from the very start!
She saw the ambush coming from a mile away!
Surely there must've been a better way!
Save the regrets for later!
What should we do now?!
First, we rendezvous with
Squad 3 and get above ground.
Then we fight Annie--the
Female Titan--as per Plan B!
Eren, you'll help catch her in
your Titan form, just as we planned.
All right?!
Yeah!
Hey!
It's Squad 3!
Capture Plan A failed?!
It did!
Please switch to the backup plan!
She stomped through it?!
--We have to help them!
--Eren!
Get back!
Whoa! Hey! Mikasa!
Does she not care if she kills Eren?!
She took a gamble.
She gambled on Eren surviving
when she made that hole.
This makes her all the more formidable!
Annie's that desperate to catch Eren now!
Now what? Our escape route's been cut off.
And she'll be ready and waiting for
us if we make a run for it with ODM.
That said...
If we stay here, there's no
telling when she'll stomp on us.
I'll manage somehow!
Just like when I stopped that cannonball!
--Come here!
--Hey--!
Here goes! Stay close!
Huh?
Again?!
Dammit!
Of all the times...!
Damn, that hurts!
You can't transform without a clear goal, right?
Try to focus again! Hard!
I'm trying to!
But it's not--
Are you sure?
Could it be you still have
qualms about fighting Annie?
Eren?
After all this, don't tell me you still think
that Annie can't possibly be the Female Titan...
What did you see just now?
She killed our comrades, you know.
Do you still think it's not her?
G-Give me a break!
I'm trying here!
Annie's the Female Titan?!
What makes...
What makes you think that, Armin?
The Female Titan knew what
you looked like from the start.
Plus, she reacted to your
nickname of "suicidal maniac,"
something only our classmates would know.
The biggest reason, though,
is that I believe she killed the
test subjects Sawney and Beane.
How do you know that?
Killing them would've required real skill,
so she would've used the ODM
gear she'd become accustomed to.
Yeah, but they held that equipment inspection.
Annie's was fine.
Because she presented Marco's gear.
That's how she avoided being caught.
Huh?!
What are you saying?
What's Marco got to do with this?
I'm not sure.
Maybe you just saw wrong?
No, I definitely recognized--
Hey, kid.
We get it.
Any other evidence to share?
No, Sir.
Personally, I think Annie
and the Female Titan look alike.
Huh?! Are you crazy?!
What kind of evidence is--?!
So, basically, we're
going after her without proof.
Without proof?
You can't be serious.
Why?
What if it isn't Annie?
If it isn't Annie, then she'll
be cleared of suspicion.
I'll feel bad for causing
her trouble if that happens.
But...
If we do nothing, the government
will make a sacrificial victim out of you.
You guys are crazy, distrusting Annie...
Eren.
Does this talk about Annie ring any bells?
You fought hand-to-hand with the Female Titan;
did you see her use any
techniques only Annie uses?
You know, don't you?
You know the Female Titan is Annie.
Then you know you have to fight.
Or are there certain,
special feelings stopping you?
Huh?!
I have a plan!
Mikasa and I will exit that hole
and that entrance at the same time.
At that point, Annie will go for one of us.
When she does, run the opposite way, Eren!
Wait!
That means one of you will get killed!
If we stay here, all three of us will die!
Mikasa! Get in position!
Right! I'll take this way!
Mikasa!
Armin!
How...?
How are you guys able to fight?!
How?!
We don't have a choice.
We live in a cruel world.
Eren!
Annie! I won't let you have Eren!
I'm coming!
Open your eyes...!
Don't let the Female Titan escape!
We can't let her get away!
What's going on?!
Escort Squad! I'll hold this position!
See what's happening!
Understood!
Something's up...
First there was that big boom, and now...
Nile.
Deploy all troops immediately.
We should assume a Titan has appeared.
A-Are you crazy?!
This is Wall Sina, you know!
No Titan would show up here!
Halt! Stop right there, Jaeger!
I'm through playing dress-up!
Never call me that name again, you halfwit!
Commander! I want to help, too!
Ask Squad 4 for equipment.
Understood!
Bravado is nice and all,
but just remember to stay alive.
Yes, Sir!
Wha...?!
Erwin! What the hell was that?!
Commander! I brought it!
--Good work.
--Thank you, Sir!
Hold on, Erwin!
All able-bodied soldiers, follow me!
We're going to rendezvous
with the Capture Squad!
Erwin!
Stop!
You're committing a clear act of
treason against the royal government!
Nile. Are you as rubbish-brained as you look?
You don't seem to understand
what's happening here.
Remove your gear, Erwin!
A Titan! There's a Titan!
--What's it doing here?!
--What about the wall?!
Hey... That's a Titan, right?
Yeah? Why?
Outta the way!
Just look at 'em, not givin' a crap!
And to think that could've
been me up there too...
Man, what got into me?
Damn!
Don't try to kill her! We just need to stop her!
It's no use! She's familiar with ODM maneuvers!
I won't make this easy for you!
Eren! Say something!
Eren!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Jean! Eren's stuck under here!
Huh?! Wasn't he supposed to turn into a Titan?!
He couldn't!
I think the fact the Female Titan
is Annie is holding him back...
What?
For now, we gotta help him!
Jean! Give me a hand!
He couldn't do it?
Damn it, Eren! Quit screwing around!
I told you we'd need to count on you someday!
We're forced to put the world, humankind,
and our own lives in your hands,
and this is all you have to show for it?!
Marco didn't... Marco can't have...
Damn it!
Eren...!
It's no use! We gotta do
something about her first!
Eren...
There's something I told Jean once.
Those who can't abandon anything...
...can't change anything.
The ability to give up your humanity
when forced to rise above monsters...
I think that's something Annie can do.
Although I don't know why she does it.
But...
Whoever can do that will prevail!
Annie!
If you don't kill me this time,
your sore excuses about "your real
bet starting now" will be worthless!
Armin! This way!
Understood!
--She's coming... She's coming!
--Section Commander...
You have that crazy look in your eyes.
All right!
Personally, I thought having a
Plan C seemed like overkill.
But Commander Erwin really does know his stuff.
Now, then...
I suggest you be a
good girl and behave yourself.
You can't call any Titans to eat you this time.
But don't you worry.
I'll savor the information I pry from you instead.
She broke free?!
Looks like we didn't set enough traps!
Don't let her escape! After her!
Those who can't abandon anything...
...can't change anything!
I know.
I failed before...
...when I clung to my friends
and the bond we shared...
Think back...
I'm going... to drive them out...!
No...
Kill them!
There's no time to think
whether it's right or wrong!
Just act!
Don't try to end things all nice and neat!
Yes...
Mikasa!
We live in a cruel world!
Now what?!
Eren!
Eren...
If, by chance, I'm not me
then who's to say that you're you?
Can you pick up the pieces of your heart
that fell apart like a broken sand castle?
The voice of someone calling out
changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map
"I'm going to drive out
every last Titan from this world."
The anger that drove young
Eren to make that vow that day
now drives him to destroy everything.
"Wall"
"Assault on Stohess, Part 3"