Hello, world! We are...
Diamond Dust!
Our debut single--
DIAMOND DUST
Let's not waste time. It ain't free here after all.
We really should be looking for a bassist...
If we can find one...
Though I wouldn't mind sticking
with the three of us for now.
What?
It's just... who's the new girl speaking...?
Who knows, probably a new vocalist they found.
Not that I know her.
What about her?
I must be imagining it...
Nah, it's nothing.
5: Singing Blaze
'Sup.
Oooh, Momo-chan! How many years it's been already?
Just a couple of years.
Still the same, huh? Both you and this place.
Oh, we've changed. For the worse. I'll be bankrupt by tomorrow at this rate.
We need you, Momo-chan...
That's Momoka-san...?
Wow, what a cutie.
Shut up.
She looks just like her, huh...
Nina!
Ah- yes?
He said we can head in.
Excuse us...
It's a lot more... crammed than where we first played.
Is there even space for the drums?
This is pretty normal for a live house.
But this one's been around here for a while,
So it gets its fair share of regulars.
But that also means they won't cut us any slack.
I already asked if we could perform here, but...
What do you think?
Performing here...
Don't push yourself if you don't feel up to it.
- We can always keep practicing--
- Let's do it!!
Now, hold up...
Ah, she's really fallen for it.
To think she used to hate the thought of it...
Well, we're just talking about a 20 minute set, so...
It's not a big deal eitherway.
Lets give it a shot, then!
Here, the tickets.
Also, don't you dare sell me as a
"former Diamond Dust", you hear?
The three of us are a new band, so...
Here you go.
No more running away now.
Tickets?
NEXT DAY
We have to sell the tickets ourselves??
Sold any yet?
How??
I've only got two to go~
No way?!
You go to school, right?
It's not like your family will know.
What?
You see, I'm like... doing a concert...
You like bands?
You are...?
Yes.
Sorry, I'm more into heavy metal.
Maybe you do, but you never know!
Expand your horizons.
You sold it for FREE?
I'm building regulars here!
It's not like we're after the money here.
What matters is that people show up... right?
She won't show up.
Looks, when it comes to humans,
We don't like to waste
something we've already paid for,
But if you didn't even
pay for it, why bother?
More than anything, giving them for free
means we'll have to pay out of pocket.
- Don't tell me you really know nothing...
- About what?
We are the ones buying these tickets.
We simply resell them after.
Here's your medium bowl!
It's becoming less common these days,
but usually bands are the ones paying the establishment,
Be it for participation fees or tickets.
That way if no one shows up, it's on us,
and the house washes its hands off of it all.
But that's so unfair!
That's how capitalism works!
Don't spit at me...
Huh?
Here.
Sorry to intrude in your break~
What?
If only Momoka-san had told me that she
bought all tickets with her own money...
It's because she still sees us as kids.
Why?
Well, we are younger than her,
and we're still not working.
Oh, hey!
It's Momo-chan's friends!
Oh, why, hello!
What's that mean?
Now, where did I put it...
What's he trying to do,
give us more tickets?
No way, right?
Aha!
Here. Take this.
What is this?
Diamond Dust just got signed to this big label.
So one of the girls came
back to visit with a gift.
Invited me and all.
Can we really have this?
Well, let's just say that after they split up,
I'm not as interested in their stuff anymore.
Why did Momoka-san quit?
She didn't tell you?
No.
Not that I know the details,
But the label they signed up to
wanted them to sing more
conventional modern music.
Momo-chan was the only one who didn't want to.
If you don't mind, could you give her this ticket?
So what now? Are we giving it to her?
If we do, I feel it'll only stir trouble.
But I kinda... want to see them
with my own eyes.
So... wanna go together?
You're not the only one who's interested.
Subaru-chan...
SOME DAYS LATER
You gave me that ticket
the other day, right?
Yeah...
Do you have any left? I've got
three friends who want to come.
That will be 7500 yen.
We... have to pay?
If you don't like it, don't come.
Nina, why'd you always have to be so extreme...
Then what am I supposed to do??
Say something like: "Ah, I'm so sorry! We had some free tickets to give out, but...
Unfortunately we're super tight on cash right now!
Tell you what though, I'll do you a favor:
Instead of 3000, I'll let you have them for 2500!
- That's fraud.
- I call it hard work.
Tickets 500 to 550, please come in.
What's wrong?
Figures, sold out.
I'm lost at a crossroads that's marked on no map.
What can I even rely on, is there anything like that?
Remember. You started this.
There's no way...
It can't be...
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés.
You have no right to sing.
Huh? What happened?!
Wait! What gives? It hasn't even been five minutes and--
- Subaru-chan.
- What?
I feel I'm about to say the
foulest things I've ever said,
So stand back.
I really need to vent out all of this, so....
YOUFUCKINGPIECEOFSHIT!!
WHOTHEFUCKDOYOUTHINKYOUARE?!
EATSHITBITCH,
KILL YOURSELF!!
I only got like half of that...
Why? Why?! WHY?! WHYYY?!!!
- WHYYYYYYY?!
- Why would I know?
And it had to be Diamond Dust of all bands...
The only thing I value as
much as my life... my treasure.
Like I said, what happened?
Their new vocalist...
...I know her.
- We used to be friends, until she betrayed me.
- What?
She betrayed me!!
Girls Band Cry.
Hello, world! We are...
...Diamond Dust!
- Don't go breaking it now.
- I don't wanna see their faces.
So you went without telling me,
start acting like a sourpuss,
and won't stop bitching about this.
You know what we call that?
A pain in the ass.
You wouldn't get it.
Frankly, I couldn't care to.
What are even the chances?
What twisted miracle is this?!
Why did SHE become the
vocalist for Diamond Dust?!
While acting like such a pretentious...
I mean, she must've passed a bunch
of auditions to even make it, right?
- SO WHAT--
- Shut up already!
This is your problem.
Yes, but, I've always loved
Diamond Dust way way more
Than any person in that hall ever could!!
That's why you're a pain in the ass!
Stop acting like they belong to you.
Then what about you?!
Are you really okay with this?!
Where's the issue?
I used to be with them,
so I hope they do well.
You want them to sell well?!
You want me not to?
You're not answering my question!!
You always gotta stick
your nose in others' affairs.
I don't want to repeat myself,
but I am paying for this place by the hour.
Subaru!
Give it up.
No way we can rehearse like this.
If you're gonna argue, then let's settle it properly.
IZAKAYA
- So what now?
- Round one. Fight!
Don't make this worse than it is...
Also, showing up at an izakaya
with a school uniform is kinda...
What's the issue? Not like I'm gonna drink.
Actually, why are you always wearing your school uniform?
Saves me the choice of dressing up.
Besides, there's many advantages to
dressing like a high school girl~
You liar.
Now, don't let me steal
the spotlight. If you will.
Why are you defending them?
I already said, I'm not defending them.
You are. Please reflect on your attitude.
The current Diamond Dust is nothing like the one you created!
So what?
So isn't it weird that you're defending them?
There's nothing weird about it.
I'm not with them anymore.
They can do whatever they want.
I'm in no position to be calling the shots.
You're not listening to what I said!
I'm asking if you are okay or not with this!
I don't care.
I don't care one way or the other.
But it was your band.
You poured your soul into that band.
Don't put words in my mouth.
Then you're saying I was wrong.
I guess that in the end Diamond Dust
didn't really mean anything to you.
Shut up already!
You've only got beef
with the vocalist, right?
No!
I asked you if you're okay with
Diamond Dust as it is right now!!
Please, don't mind them~
Calm down, both of you.
Look,
Just like humans, bands evolve too. They change.
You can't just stop change.
Then why did you quit?
You quit because you didn't like
what it was becoming, right?
Because you felt that wasn't
the Diamond Dust you wanted anymore, right?
You quit because you knew you weren't wrong, right?
You quit because you hate what
those girls have become, right?
So why do you refuse to say it?
I could tell from the lyrics in your song!
That's what you wanted DD to be, right?
Please tell me you're not
happy with the current DD!!
Tell me that this isn't Diamond Dust!
Tell me--
Sigh...
Silence.
Never.
Because I love the Diamond Dust
you wanted more than anything else!
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead
What I love... is your vision of Diamond Dust.
That song changed my life!
So I don't want to see you give up like this!
This isn't even about who is right
or who is at fault anymore...
I just want you to be honest with yourself!!
Do you know what was
our goal with Diamond Dust?
What?
That we would stick together 'till the end,
even if that meant not making it as a girls band.
To always be the four of us.
It wouldn't matter what type of music we did,
as long as we were together.
So you see... it's all my fault.
"Hang in there!"
"If we make it big enough,
we'll be able to sing what we want!"
They tried to do everything to stay by my side.
And despite that... I quit.
Here's your oolong tea.
Thank you.
Nina.
Please don't mind them!
Even so...
I still like who you are.
Because I love your music.
Because the one the one that saved me... was your Diamond Dust.
You saved me.
What an idiot.
Your snot's dripping.
I know I'm an idiot.
If I wasn't an idiot, I wouldn't be here right now!
Drunkards, am I right?
Subaru-chan...
Wait... WAIT--
Sorry, I just got a bit pissed off
seeing you acting like that...
Momoka-san, I thought you said
you could hold your drink...
She drunk herself silly today.
She reeks.
Careful, you're dragging her!
- Subaru-chan, legs!
- Yes ma'am!
So?
This is just plain weird...
Momoka-san, we'll lower you down again, so...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
You think she felt happy?
No.
I don't think so.
You should pick the outfits for our concert.
It's not everyday that someone ends up
With their most hated person becoming
the vocalist of their most favorite band.
You should get something out of it.
Is that okay?
Expose all your anger, joy, and sadness.
That's the pros of being in a band!
What's that?
The promo for our concert.
"Featuring Momoka... former Diamond Dust star"??
That bastard...
But look at the upside. This is our
chance to win back all those customers
Who went to see Diamond Dust live.
Give some thought to what it is
you want to get across to them, Nina.
Of course.
Outfits, huh...
Though we really need to make them on a budget...
Three years already, huh?
Yeah we need to make sure that at our next match
We don't lose to our senpai!
Ah, Momo-chan!
'Sup.
I'm super sorry!
I told them not to put that in the
promo, but the staff just went with it...
But look at the bright side,
thanks to that we're sold out!
Eh? What? Wha-
So, what about your outfits?
Right. I hope it's to your liking.
Here you go.
Oh? You picked our outfits too?
If you don't want to, just say it.
If you don't want to, you're still wearing it.
"Bare your heart naked", right?
Heh.
Good going.
Are you Momoka?
What about it?
Sorry, but I kinda hate girl bands.
You better not kill the mood.
Look pal, it's not that--
Worry not. We'll be killing the show,
not the mood.
That so?
Nice one.
Momoka-san!
Momoka!
Momoka! I love you!
You wanna start it like that?
This pain of ours... is it even right to call it a "scar"?
We keep kicking ourselves, losing it,
But in the end we hurt
not just ourselves, but others too.
True enough.
Momoka-san... your song, I felt it in my heart.
It left a scar on it.
Telling me to never give up 'till I die.
Let's leave scars of our own!
Scream out what you truly feel.
Shout out what it is you truly want.
Your thoughts, your anger, your sadness,
even your faults, your shames,
even the past you want to shut away,
and even the regrets that
haunt your every thought...
Expose them to the world!
LET'S GOOOOOOO!!!
LIAR
QUITTER
EXPOSE YOURSELF, AND LIVE!!!
DROPOUT
What did we find
at an endlessly flowing intersection?
Superficial words, bringing each other down
A fallen shooting star
Threatens to blow it all away
In the end, nothing changed
We pretend not to see
So that our hands stay clean
In the corner of our eyes
Our dreams crumble to pieces
We pretend we don't see
We pretend we don't hear
But look, it's already gone
This city flows down a whirlpool of truths
Where should we float off to?
If we can still laugh once we land
Let's reach out for our hands
This is no dream
After our dreams turned to ashes
I finally realized
Wishes will never come true
In this ever-changing world
Where should we float off to?
What should we raise up?
Will I be able to meet the real you?
Before it all ends
Let's draw a future
With this finger right here
Next: Hymn of the Outcasts