The adamant giant, Bishamaru!
Kyoto glitters in the sunshine.
Take this, evil shadows,
who disturb the city's peace!
A devastating punch!
A thunderous kick!
But do not ever forget
its righteous controller!
It's gone!
CapitaL CraZe
What's gone?
Shouko, flustered scientist
My controller, of course!
Out
of
Service
Out
of
Service
How is your day, Shouko?
Couldn't be worse.
Call the Four Divines.
Are you looking for something again?
The Four
Divines
have
appeared!
Azure Dragon Azu
White Tiger Snow
Vermillion Bird Veve
Black Tortoise Jetty
We'll bring it back to you.
Thanks, guys.
What is it?
A replacement.
It should be the same with a new OS.
Dumbass.
I told you to put a GPS tracker on it...
Why would I? No way I'd lose it.
It's gone...
I remember I had it yesterday around noon.
Yesterday around noon...
Thanks for the food!
Awesome!
Keep your mouth shut when you eat.
Elbows off the table!
More soup!
Get it yours—
I think you've got a customer.
We're not at home!
Hand over the three dumbasses.
Look, it's Shouko.
Look, it's the gamer.
Look, it's the geek.
Shut up!
Where's my controller?
Huh?
Don't play dumb!
What's wrong?
I've got no idea what you're talking about! Do you have a concussion?
You dumbass!
Take your crap outside!
The Kurama temple is undergoing an unscheduled security inspection.
The Kurama again?
Kurama Temple Notice
Inspection Ahead
What is it this time?
We respectfully ask for your cooperation.
Inspection Ahead
I repeat.
Inspection
for 1 hour
and no more!
The chaos in the human district is always irritating,
but today it seems like a veritable maelstrom.
Yase!
The Kurama temple must have a lot of free time on its hands,
considering how many of you are simply wreaking havoc on the city.
Not nearly as much time as you!
Are you organizing another tea party?
Isn't that lovely?
I'd love to be a loaded and loved shut-in myself.
That bird!
I'll get back to you, Yase!
Get back here!
Left at the next intersection, and then—
Gotcha!
Ushiwaka
I-It's not mine!
Goddammit! Where's my controller?!
Hello? Is this the March restaurant?
No, it was a pleasure.
Incidentally, I have a question...
Bar
Saba Av
Cheers!
Damn! Thanks, guys!
Great job!
Especially you, Fushimi! Impressive!
I knew you were the type to get things done!
How did you do it, by the way?
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Eat
Sleep
Get mad
Cry
Bar
Saba Avenue
Don't tell her.
She'll just get mad.
Get up and dance!
Controller!
Good thing I put the GPS tracker in after all.