#12 The Bonds
(Bifrost) To Tomorrow
Nuh-uh.
That won't work at all.
Don't worry.
We'll find your mom for you.
Compa!
Ge-Ge!
Nep-Nep's fighting.
Yes.
I'm gonna go help her—
What are you saying?
Helping little girls evacuate comes first!
I agree, Nepgear.
Histy! Iffy!
I'm glad to see you're okay.
Yeah, we're all right.
We should lead the people away from the city.
Got it.
Everyone!
Please hurry and evacuate in that direction.
Sis...
Please wait just a little bit longer.
Only 1 hour of games per day!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
Blaze Break!
Like I said, it doesn't matter how many times you attack me. It's useless.
That lightning certainly is powerful,
but I shouldn't be taking this much damage.
Something's not right.
Mom!
That's good.
Ge-Ge?
What's wrong?
It just feels like the Share Energy within me is disappearing.
Negear, you should probably deactivate HDD.
I don't know why,
but our Share reserves are dropping rapidly.
Now, then.
Let's charge up the Pong Laser nice and good again!
What should we target this time?
There are a lot of people there, so it'll do.
Stop it!
Don't wanna.
Lock on.
No, Lady Neptune is...
Lady Neptune!
Oh no!
We're done for!
What should we do?
I don't wanna die!
We'll be fine, everyone.
Calm down.
I'm sure Sis will save us!
But she's been defeated!
It's all over for us!
Nepgear!
You mustn't!
We still don't have enough Share Energy.
What's with the gloomy look?
Rainy Ratnapura!
Is this your so-called event?
A bit tacky, don't you think?
Noire!
Vert too!
You came?
I simply came here as 5pb's chauffeur.
Hi!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Nepgear.
Uni!
5pb!
Thank you, Uni.
No problem.
I'll go join Sis and the others, then.
Okay!
Please do my part as well.
Is that 5pb?
What's she doing here?
Listen, everyone!
There's nothing to worry about.
Let's believe in our goddesses!
My, she certainly did dredge up something rather absurd.
Who exactly is she?
She's apparently the CPU of Tari, the superpower of old.
But I can't imagine how a nation that collapsed so long ago got its hands on so much Share Energy.
Look there.
Eden was using a similar device.
It's a machine that creates Share Energy.
In that case,
we should start by destroying it, should we not?
I'll take care of the woman.
I have to say, four-on-one's a bit annoying.
My powers are draining away...
What's... going on?
What did you do?
I'm losing my Share Energy!
Wait, is that thing...
a device that steals Shares?!
Exactly.
Oh, the laser should be fully charged by now.
Can I push the big red button, then?
No, don't!
I'm still gonna do it, though.
Fire!
Ice Sanctuary!
What?
Attack from under the laser, and she can't hit you with her lightning.
Right?
Blanc!
Rom! Ram!
We did it, Rom!
We're the best!
Yeah, Ram. The best!
I can feel the Share Energy.
Histy.
Go ahead.
Thanks, Blanc.
I calmed down and thought about it.
I realized that everything made sense if Eden's machine could steal Shares.
Way to go, Blanc.
But you went and kept the best part all to yourself.
No fair.
Sis!
Let's begin.
Now it's our turn.
You're too late!
I've already taken enough Share Energy to destroy the world.
"Destroy"?
Didn't you want this nation for yourself?
Are you retarded?
I couldn't care less about that!
What I really want...
is to lay waste to everything.
Why?
Aren't you a CPU too?
Yeah, I am.
Yet all they did was bitch and whine.
They never obeyed me!
"They"?
Tari cracked down on citizens that showed any discontent toward their CPU.
That made people lose faith in her,
and the nation eventually lost its Shares and collapsed.
The so-called "Great Tari Crash."
Sounds like she reaped what she sowed.
You're wrong!
They stole my nation from me.
This time, I'll be the one doing the stealing!
Recharge!
I feel so sorry for you.
You never had any friends, did you?
I'll offer you my sympathy,
but you can never have our world!
The world lies shattered into pieces
But I don't need to pick up all the fragments
I'm going with maximum output for the next one.
There's only one that matters to me
Your petty magic won't be able to stop this!
My true love is all I need find
Vert.
Noire.
Blanc.
Within the moonlit darkness
Uni.
Rom.
Ram.
I stand alone, with my heart of stone
Nepgear.
Lend me your strength!
Singing a song for the future
I bet you're just gonna try and destroy the Pong Laser.
My words don't take shape
But music doesn't have any rights or wrongs
Wonder if you can pull it off before it finishes charging.
It simply forms an irreplaceable bond
I'll get stronger just by staying here
I'll send ya flying there at the speed of light!
For this is where I met you
Where are you even aiming?
The moment my faint voice
Reaches people's hearts
Eat this!
It will give them courage
That doesn't even tickle!
To overcome anything
I play my heart out
Take care of this, Sis!
My hard beat cannot be stopped
Not on my watch!
May my song reach the ends of the earth
It's all pointless!
Go, Neptune!
The moment my faint voice
Reaches people's hearts
It will give them courage
To overcome anything
That's charged enough!
May my song echo across the world
If you've got it out, I can cut it off!
You piece of shit!
Fire!
Victory Slash!
My continent...
Give it up.
What you desire will never come to pass.
Time to throw in the towel.
Did you think that sinking my continent
was all you needed to do to win?
If I unleashed the energy I have left,
I could send half the world flying, you know?
Indeed.
The hatred is surprisingly strong in this one.
However...
In the end, hatred is all it is.
It doesn't matter if we use up all our Share Energy.
There's only one job we goddesses have.
Right,
Nepgear?
Yeah, yeah, play hero all you want...
in the afterlife!
Girls...
I'll go too.
I can still do this!
I can blow them up, at least!
And then I'll crush the world to bits and piec—
I'm afraid we have a problem.
This world is gonna be mine someday.
Say what?
Who're you?
All good, old hag.
Off to the dark abyss of despair with you!
N-No!
My powers!
We finally got an anti-crystal back,
but should we really have used it for this, old hag?
Let's say I decided it on a whim.
The "whimsical" trait only works for characters under twenty.
Wait!
Did you just help us?
Don't be stupid.
I will always and forever be your enemy.
Oh, okay.
But just for today, let me express my gratitude.
Thank you,
Bar Whore!
Who're you calling a bar whore?!
A Few Months Later
Thanks to your efforts, we recovered our Shares
and stand here today to celebrate the completion of the new Planeptower.
Have your Shares remained stable since then?
Of course.
We merely had them stolen by Tari.
We hadn't lost the trust of our people.
No problems here, either.
Good to hear.
Let's begin the ceremony, then.
Sis!
You gotta say it.
You gotta.
Hey, Neptune.
How should I put this?
Uh...
Back then...
Are you talking about the time you attacked me?
I'm sorry.
I felt like you'd taken advantage of our treaty of friendship,
and all I could see was red.
Frankly speaking, it was kinda fun fighting you all-out for the first time in a while.
So I came up with an idea.
What idea?
I'll tell you later.
It's all thanks to your faith that we were able to complete the new Planeptower.
The city of Planeptune is
recovering by the day, too.
As this nation's CPU,
I'm grateful to you all.
Thank you so very much.
Oh, and one more thing.
I'd like to take this opportunity to make an announcement.
And that is...
One moment, please.
Yeah, I gotta do it in this form!
Well...
I, Neptune, Planeptune's CPU,
on this day,
declare the treaty of friendship null and void!
What?!
There's no need for that old thing anymore.
We're true buddies now!
Don't you agree, Noire, Vert, Blanc?
I suppose.
You want to compete fair and square from now on, I take it?
I guess even you can be clever once in a while.
Then how about we hold an exhibition match right now?
Let's do this!
My heart's all aflutter.
I've come to this universe of countless stars
Hey, wait for me!
To start our search for the ultimate game
I'm the protagonist here!
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
Uni!
Rom!
What are you getting so serious for?
Ram!
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Count me in.
We're gonna show them we're the best.
Let's start a New Game+
Yeah, the best.
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Looks like things are going to get chaotic once again.
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
See you later