Get up.
You stayed up late again, didn't you?
I know for a fact your lights
were still on at 2:30 a.m.!
Rice is... Rice is pouring
out of Ryuji's ear...
A-All white and shiny...
Freshly-cooked...
I brought your breakfast.
Wash your face while I warm it up.
Breakfast...
Okay...
That just leaves dishes and laundry...
Seriously...
This room is so empty.
A cardboard box?
What's this?
A photo album?
This is...
What are you looking at?
Hey, Taiga! These are—
Yeah, that's right. Pictures of Kitamura-kun.
You got a problem with that?
Not that I care if you do.
These are all supposed to be Kitamura?
I-I can't help it!
For some reason, I always start to shake
wh-whenever I try to take his picture.
Want me to take some for you?
I could take pictures.
I'm not especially talented, but
they'll turn out better than the—
Hold on a sec!
H-How many are you willing to take?
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
The Look You Had
What kind of pictures do I want?
A profile shot while he's deep in thought...
Something during softball practice...
Oh, don't forget about when
he's eating lunch!
I told you I'll take as many
as you want, didn't I?
But I'm sure you'll draw
the line somewhere!
Or are you going to take an infinite
number of pictures for me?
Good morning!
Hey.
Good morning.
You're late today.
- I stopped by the student council office.
- M-Mo-...Mo—
Mornin'!
Lame.
Oh-so-lame, Taiga.
Sh-Shoot!
That wasn't what I meant to do...
Um, well...
Aisaka.
Mornin'!
Well...
I'm off.
Mornin'!
M-Mornin'?
Hey! Hey!
Did you get that?
Get what?
A picture of him going "mornin'!" of course!
It came out of nowhere.
How was I supposed to take a picture?
Useless mongrel...
Seriously?
Maruo, come look at this.
Hey, hey!
This model looks exactly like you!
Now, girls.
It's almost time for the morning assembly.
Cut the chitchat and move
along to the schoolyard.
Aw, he's such a bore.
He doesn't have to be so serious
just because he's vice president.
I was hoping for some kind of reaction.
Totally.
Kitamura is surprisingly
popular with the girls.
You want a reaction?
I'll give you a reaction...
Line up, people!
Hey, maggots.
Seems a bunch of you have been
forgetting your student handbooks!
We've even got proof.
According to the disciplinary committee's
report, last week's check yielded...
Uh, how many were there?
Fifty-nine.
Uh, forty-nine students forgot
to carry their handbooks.
Oops, I messed up.
Fifty-nine students.
Well, the details aren't important.
In any case, forgetting your
student handbook at home...
is akin to forgetting your
pride as Ohashi students!
Got that, maggots!?
Yes!
Should you really be criticizing others?
You're pretty forgetful, yourself.
A-Aisaka?
You say something, squirt?
You forgot the "at ease" part.
At ease!
Oh, my bad.
At ease, people!
Jeez...
Making high school students
stand at attention...
and forcing them to stay that
way while they listen to you.
What's so hard?
You're just putting your hands on your hips.
What did you say!?
Whoa, Aisaka...
Nice.
Working up a morning sweat there?
Please stay calm, President!
What do you know!?
We have to stand here like fools when we
don't suffer from back or labor pain!
- Have you no shame!?
- Aisaka!
A-Aisaka, would you kindly restrain yourself?
Sorry about that, President.
Please continue with the morning assembly.
Y-Yeah...
What was that?
The Palm-top Tiger snapped
at the president!
That fool...
It's so easy to tell she's depressed about it.
Wait, is she happy?
Yes, okay.
Haruta-kun, that's enough.
Um, next up is...
Aisaka-san?
You're in a good mood today.
In that case, let's have you
read to us, nice and loud!
E-Except that was just a joke!
Haruta-kun!
Yuri-chan, does that even
make any sense!?
Knock us out!
Hey, listen to me, please!
Here's your lunch.
No thanks. Not hungry.
I fought with the student council president
and caused problems for Kitamura-kun...
But...
He held me up by my armpits...
Armpit Carnival...
Ta-Taiga?
But! I want to apologize!
You don't need to worry about it.
Our student council president doesn't
get hung up on little things.
Oh, you brought a lunch?
Mind if I join you?
Oh! I like the sound of that!
Count me in on the fun.
It's not a bad idea to do something
like this on occasion.
You know it!
Man, I'm hungry.
Thanks for the grub!
Thanks for the food.
Wonder what I'm having...
Wonder what I'm having...today!
- H-How did this happen?
- Ooh! Fried chicken!
- Taiga! You're too tense!
- Ready and...chicken fry!
Ooh!
Taiga's got quite the spread!
Shoot!
Our lunches are...
Aisaka, you've been bringing
your own lunch lately.
Do you make it yourself?
Um...
What? Takasu made it?
U-Uh, it's no big deal!
It's just...
It's like how Kushieda decorates
cell phones on the side.
I figured I could sell lunches
to make some extra cash.
Oh, really?
I'd like to try a Takasu lunch creation.
Oh, me too!
That lunch is oozing with a brown elegance.
Fascinating!
Th-Then I'll make enough
for everyone tomorrow...
Kitamura-senpai! Kushieda-senpai!
Um, we need to get going.
Oh, it's the softball team manager.
Ah, the meeting.
Sorry. Go ahead and eat without us.
R-Right...
- That was a close call...
- I got to talk with Kitamura-kun...
- Too close for comfort...
- With Kitamura-kun...
- Taiga?
Hello?
You're okay with letting Kitamura
know that I made your lunch!?
And I finally convinced everyone that
there's nothing between us...
What do we do!? What do we do!?
- What do we do!?
- Calm down!
Man...
Why do you get so worked up
whenever Kitamura's involved?
Listen to me.
You need to be more careful from now on.
What's that?
Don't talk with your mouth full. Swallow first.
Hey...
You didn't put any meat in my lunch today.
If you want meat all the time, go find
a household that can afford it.
I knew the mold in a public
facility would be tough!
It's deep in there.
But!
Your luck ran out the day I found you.
Taka-chan, let's call it a day.
Right!
I'll finish the rest, so you can get going.
Oh?
Lucky me.
All yours, then.
You vile devil!
What, ready to surrender?
Okay, I'll use one of the
48 Takasu Housework Skills,
- the Takasu Moldbuster, to finish you off!
- Ryuji!
Why are you mumbling to yourself?
Hurry it up, stupid dog!
What!? Taiga!
You do realize this is the men's roo—
- Just hurry up!
- H-Hey!
What is it, Taiga?
What are you—!?
Oh, I see.
Kitamura.
C'mon!
Hurry!
Snap some pictures!
Seriously...
C'mon!
Now's the perfect time!
Hurry!
I got it.
Pretty sure the shutter button's...
Now! Go now!
Hold on, I'm setting it up.
Oh, jeez! Forget it!
Hand it over!
Now I understand...
This is what led to that mass
production of blurry pictures.
You're amazing, Kitamura-kun...
That's it...
Whoa!
Go!
Hey!
Hey, he's waving like a madman.
You're annoying...
Klutz.
Welcome to Sudoh-bucks!
Boss, Americano and Napolitan spaghetti!
Napolitan, comin' right up!
Why hasn't this place been sued yet?
Oh well...
Was there a point to getting those printed?
Hey, you're drooling all over everything!
Kitamura-kun everywhere...
Kitamura Carnival...
Whoa!
What are you doing!?
That's going too far, even for our
short-tempered generation!
I'm helping out, you mongrel.
Since you took pictures for me.
No, it's okay.
I'd like to be able to hang
up the sheets tomorrow.
Any more lip and I'll cut you up!
Cut me up, huh...?
Anyway, you're making extra
lunches for tomorrow, right?
For Minorin and...
Ki-Kitamura-kun...
All right. Do you know
how to peel potatoes?
D-Don't underestimate me, boy!
Of course I can.
Just peel this, right? Jeez...
Cooking for Kitamura, huh...?
That's right...
I've been given a chance
to make food for Kushieda.
I should get psyched up...
Hey!
What are you doing?
Whoa!?
What? I got rid of the skin, didn't I?
And there wasn't any danger
of cutting my fingers!
Uh, well, I guess...
Yay! Rice balls for dinner?
It's like we're on a picnic!
And this one's so little and adorable!
That's the one I made!
Get out! Are you a genius!?
Well, no need to worry if
you practice on these.
There's no peeling involved.
I told you to finish eating before you talk.
It's so good!
I can taste Taiga-chan's hands!
Here. I made tea.
You should put them in an album
before they get damaged.
Stop nagging like an in-law...
What's that supposed to mean?
And here I was going to laminate
your favorite picture for you.
You can do that?
Yep, sure can.
H-Hold on!
Um...
A little processing and it won't matter if you
trip over yourself, or drop them in water.
Taiga?
Something wrong?
N-No!
You don't have to limit yourself
to one, you know.
Pick two or three.
Shut up!
Just wait!
I'm trying to decide!
Wh-What's your problem?
I was just—
I'm leaving.
Now what's wrong!?
I can't make my decision in peace
here, so I'm going home.
Hey! Taiga!
Hold on!
What's up with her?
I'd sure like to have pictures...
of Kushieda.
- Take a look at this!
- Whoa!
Th-This is...
A dead, pale, yellow squid...
No, wait, is that slime?
Incredible, isn't it?
I made a bucket of pudding!
Th-This is pudding?
It's certainly managed to blow my mind...
A bucket of pudding!
The ultimate victual to sate
a woman's desires!
The size really gave me trouble, though.
The melt-in-your-mouth parts and the
jiggly parts mixed together, making...
Oh!
Hello there, ladies!
Have a look-see...at my valiant
contest with a bucket!
Um...
This is...
A picture of Kushieda...
The melt-in-your-mouth parts and the
jiggly parts mixed together, making...
Not exactly what I had in mind...
But this works.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Huh? What?
Oh, it's just you.
You still haven't decided?
Man, shove it.
What's wrong with you?
You just took off yesterday too.
I told you I'd laminate more than
one, if you can't decide.
What was that for?
If you can't stop bugging me, you decide.
I'm leaving it up to you.
How am I supposed to choose?
Frickin' Taiga...
Do those belong to Aisaka?
Yeah, sure do.
Pictures of me.
U-Uh, this is, well...
How do I put it...?
That reminds me...
I'd completely forgotten that
I still have this in here.
Student Handbook
What!?
Sure brings me back...
Wh-Why do you have this picture?
Oh, the photography club used to sell them.
So I bought one.
That's not what I mean!
Why are you carrying a picture
of Taiga around!?
Because I was in love with her.
That's all.
She shot me down a second after
I told her how I felt, though.
Well, cat's out of the bag now.
Don't tell anybody else about this.
- Wha—
- Takasu, what's wrong?
- Hey, Takasu?
What the hell!?
What a waste...
It wasn't my fault.
H-He said he was in love with me...
and I was so surprised, I turned him down.
But I noticed him more, after that...
And then I just...
just fell in love, somehow!
It happened right at this very spot.
Aisaka!
I love that straightforward personality!
Your refusal to conceal your rage!
You've won my heart!
Kitamura...
Funny way to confess your feelings, right?
I mean, was it a compliment or an insult?
But you know...
I was happy.
I felt vindicated, because someone
appreciated me for who I really am.
Because someone understood me...
For some reason...
Taiga's apartment came
to mind, all of a sudden.
I have so many pictures, but none
of them have what I want.
I wanted it again—the look he had
when he told me how he felt...
Wh-Why are you making me say such
humiliating things, you sick mutt!?
You're blaming me!?
Who else is there!?
I wonder what feeling appreciated...
means to Taiga, exactly.
No matter what, she's one hell of a klutz.
If you were gonna fall for him later on,
you should've held off on giving him an answer.
Isn't that right, Inko-chan?
Same goes for Kitamura.
If you were in love with her at one point,
you should man up and go out with her.
I-I-...
- Oh? You agree, Inko-chan?
- I-I-...I-I...
- Yeah! Tell them off!
- I-I-I...I-I...
I—
It ain't bad.
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
A pretty airhead, Kawashima Ami,
makes a sudden appearance.
For now, all I can say is...
Women are scary!
Huh? What's that mean?
I don't get it!