Th-This is...
Initiating docking procedures.
Roger.
Elevating from six to nine
on the Torino Scale!
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
The course suddenly shifted?
I see.
Then we must now discuss
the best course of action.
Should I go now?
All right.
Master, for some reason the
Hero Association wants me to come in.
I will be back later.
Okay.
Maybe you're getting fired?
THE ULTIMATE DISCIPLE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
CITY Z HERO ASSOCIATION BUILDING
Ah, you would be Genos?
My name is Bang.
Nice to meet you.
Bang, Class S rank 3,
also known as "Silver Fang."
His skill is the real deal.
The Association called me in.
Everyone's at Headquarters.
This little branch office is empty just now.
All of the S-class heroes
got the call to come here,
but we're the only ones who showed up.
Why is that?
Too far away, or perhaps they're busy.
Of course, some of the more
cold-blooded ones simply don't bother.
After all, we're called up only
when there's some impossible problem
they want us to take care of.
Today's no exception.
The threat level is Dragon,
the highest setting possible.
Thirty-five minutes from now,
a huge meteor will strike City Z.
They are asking if nearby S-class
heroes can do anything about it.
A meteor?
Apparently, its trajectory suddenly changed.
That means the end for us.
The impact will wipe out City Z.
I'm afraid there's nothing
we can do this time.
You should consider evacuating
your loved ones as well.
Do the citizens know?
I was told they would estimate the impact area
and issue evacuation orders thirty minutes before it hits.
Attention! This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
Panic is sure to ensue.
And you, old fellow?
"Old fellow," is it?
Call me Bang.
You are not evacuating?
My dojo has been in
my family for generations.
I cannot abandon it.
"Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock."
Heard of it?
He left…
Emergency evacuation warning.
The threat level is Dragon.
Evacuate immediately.
Twenty-one more minutes
until meteor impact.
It's huge…
No way we can escape that.
So many people have
given up hope of survival.
It is not just City Z that is in danger.
The neighboring cities will also be affected.
It is too late to evacuate.
I did not expect to be testing
this prototype so soon!
Let me see if an attack from my incineration
cannon at full power will do the trick.
Master Saitama lives here too.
I cannot possibly evacuate without him.
Is that…
You are Bofoi, correct?
And you are the new boy, Genos.
Come to stop the meteor?
Yes.
Class S, rank 7.
A hero who uses intense firepower to obliterate
his opponents along with everything in their vicinity.
Does he also live in City Z?
Or did he rush here, putting his life at risk?
Bofoi. I need your help.
I refuse.
Why?
I only came to field test my new weapon.
The meteor is a perfect target.
A test?
If that meteor hits, you too will die.
I will not.
What?
What you are talking to right now
is a remotely-controlled drone.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but my life's not at stake here.
Also, I am not Bofoi. I am "Metal Knight."
Heroes call each other by
their hero names, not real names.
Everyone knows that.
Looks like it's time to end our little chat.
All right!
Firing missiles!
Metal Knight?
I cannot fire with his missiles in the way.
Amazing.
Such destructive power.
This hero is dangerous.
I must be wary.
Not quite potent enough, eh?
Thirty-three seconds left until impact.
To fire my incineration cannon at full power,
I need five seconds to
charge it with my body's energy.
But the target is already close.
And even if I do take it out, what then?
The meteor may break apart
and still cause a disaster.
But will my weapons even be
powerful enough to stop it?
Even Metal Knight's
countless missiles had no effect.
First off, be calm.
I see you've lost your composure.
You're far too young
to be worried about failure.
When your back's up against
the wall, just muddle through.
The outcome won't change.
So that's what is best.
Muddling through is best…
He is right.
If the outcome will not change…
then I how can I die without giving it my all?
Bang, get down!
Oh.
I will no longer think about failure or repercussions!
I will just pour everything I have…
into one last shot!
Dammit, it is not working!
No! I think I see the meteor being pushed back.
Really?
Oh, no. It was just my imagination.
You senile old man!
So this is where I'll meet my end.
Nine more seconds.
Get out of here, Bang.
Old man, take care of Genos.
Wh-Who are you?
I'm a hero.
Master?!
You're not…
gonna fall…
on my town!
He shattered it!
Unbelievable!
But…
It's collapsing…
It's not just this building.
The destruction is spreading
through the whole city.
Guess that settles that.
Three Days Later
Although City Z was able
to avoid total destruction,
the city was still devastated,
with the effects of the meteor
fragments visible everywhere.
If only the Hero Association had called
you to help instead of me, Master.
If you had worked with Metal Knight,
the damage could have been minimized.
But that Metal Knight guy
wasn't interested in helping, right?
So stop worrying about it.
I think we kept the damage to a minimum.
After all, no one died.
He is right.
Master's punch killed the meteor's momentum.
Theoretically, the shockwaves from the meteor
would have annihilated everything.
Stopping it was nothing short of a miracle.
I would not be surprised if people
talk about Master for years to come,
praising him as a man of courage.
But Master has no idea.
Some of the public is even making him out to be
the bad guy for causing the partial destruction of City Z.
No, I should not mention it.
By the way,
do you think we moved up in ranking?
Yes, we did.
I went from rank seventeen
to rank sixteen in the S class.
Metal Knight also moved up
from rank seven to rank six.
Master, you shot up from rank three-hundred
forty-two to rank five in the C class.
Rank five?!
From three-hundred forty-two to five?
What the hell?!
That's crazy!
Not at all.
Your performance was worthy
of A-class or even S-class status.
After all, the threat level was Dragon.
Yeah?
If there had been no damage,
I am sure you would surely
be rank five of Class S.
Smashing the meteor alone
was worthy of A-class status.
But I think the Hero Association assumed
that Metal Knight and I played a big role.
By the way, they always report threat levels
as "demon" or "tiger" or whatever.
Does all that mean anything?
It does…
Tiger
Tiger: A crisis threatening massive loss of life.
Demon: A crisis threatening to halt
the functioning of an entire city,
Demon
or its destruction.
Dragon
Dragon: A crisis threatening
the destruction of multiple cities.
God
God: A crisis threatening human extinction.
Wow… I had no idea.
I believe heroes often consider threat levels
when deciding to respond or not.
But I guess they don't matter to you.
Well, of course not.
If the heroes run away, who's left to help?
What are you doing?
I must record your words.
Anyway, it wasn't all that much
for such a huge jump in rank…
All right.
I'll be out for a bit.
You are going out, Master?
I will come with you.
You stay here.
If something happens,
you'll get all the credit again.
This place is in ruins...
Oh.
My favorite supermarket got smashed.
And the crappy apartment building
I got kicked out of is…
Just fine… Damn.
Hey.
You cheating bastard.
Uh, who are you?
You know damn well I'm Tank-top Tiger!
Brother!
It's that guy!
Seriously, who is this guy?
You called me, little bro?
Brother!
The hero Tank-top Black Hole…
is here!
So you're the fraud who takes credit for work done
by S-class heroes in order to advance in the rankings?
What the—
No one could move up to rank five
so quickly without cheating.
What do you guys want?
Huh? Isn't that obvious?
To beat you up so bad
you'll never be able to—
Hang on, little bro.
Bastards like him don't learn
from that kind of lesson.
Let's make him really pay with
the most brutal method there is.
Are you the one?!
The jerk-off responsible for
destroying this city?!
I get it!
There are tons of people
in this city who are angry with him.
Unbelievable!
How can you show your face?!
I see what he's doing.
He's going to use their anger…
Do you feel nothing at the
sight of this devastation?
…to break his spirit!
You're gloating,
thinking you've actually saved these people!
Why else would you be
walking around so shamelessly?
Thanks to your screw up,
these citizens have nowhere to go!
If you were gonna fail this hard,
why'd you butt in?!
The other heroes would have
done a way better job!
And yet you still wanna play hero,
even after causing such a huge disaster?
Look at this place!
All this destruction is your doing!
That's right.
I-It's your fault!
They took the bait.
You hear that?
The heart-wrenching cry
of someone who lost his home!
Look at them all,
victims of your thoughtless actions!
That's right!
Yeah, you tell him!
Haven't you even thought
to take responsibility?
Yeah!
You're inhuman!
Give up being a hero!
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up!
Go on, get outta here!
Get lost!
Give it up!
Beat it!
Scram!
Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
We got him.
His pride should be shattered by now.
That's what he gets for cheating…
That idiot!
CITY Z FORUM – IS IT TRUE A C-CLASS HERO DESTROYED THE TOWN?
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up!
Is this what you call mob mentality?
They're all chanting in unison.
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Saitama…
Without a doubt, you saved this city.
Yet look how the city treats you.
This is reality, though.
You're strong,
the strongest man I've ever seen.
That's why I refrain from saying anything.
I'd hate to see you rotting away in this industry.
Resigning is also an option.
Time to finish him off!
Hey!
He's getting ready to fight!
Huh? What are you talking—
No way!
You're gonna take out your frustration on these
people here, just like you destroyed their city?!
Do you just kill everyone you don't like?
I won't let you do that!
We, the Tank-top Brothers,
will not stand by and let you resort to violence!
If you're a hero,
then fight us fair and square!
So they're out to crush a rookie
and perform a publicity stunt at the same time.
I'd say they've gotten a little greedy.
No wonder they can't rise above B-class status.
Yeah!
Go, Tank-top!
Do it!
Tank-top Tiger,
who fights like a true tiger, and...
Tank-top Black Hole, who crushes all
with a grip strength of 2,800 psi!
We brothers will punish all who stray
from the path of the hero!
Huh?
Damn it!
I'll rip you apart!
I give up! I give up!
You're crushing my hand!
Huh?
You're kidding, right?
I give up for real. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for lying!
No, you weren't lying.
I'm the one who smashed the meteor!
Anyone with a complaint, let's hear it.
Speak up!
Because of you, my brand new car was—
You can shut up!
Why would I give a crap
about your problems?
Tell it to the meteor, jackass!
Listen up!
I don't do this hero-thing for admiration!
I do it because I want to!
So if you wanna blame me, go ahead!
You baldies!
You're the baldy…
What'd you say?!
Master.
Oh, it's you, Genos.
Hang on.
These guys—
Let's go home,
Master.
Oh yeah?
Dammit.
That guy's face is burned into my brain.
I'm gonna remember this.
Master.
I have never met any person
as incredible as you, Master Saitama.
What brought that on?
You're creeping me out.
Even if the public doesn't appreciate you,
I will still follow you.
You don't have to butter me up. Really.
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
I heard one of the C-class
heroes is pretty amazing.
C-class?
The guy who says he smashed the meteor, right?
That's just a rumor.
Going after weak guys,
then calling yourself a hero?
Just shows that there's no hero
you can really count on.
Next
Time
The
Deep Sea
King
My name is Bofoi.
You all may know me better as Metal Knight.
Next time on One-Punch Man episode eight,
"The Deep Sea King."
Oh, the king of the sea, eh? Pretty cocky.
Wonder what he's like…