Let me get this straight, Fuku-chan...
Chocolate that you just melt and reshape isn't homemade.
That's why you won't take it.
That's what you're saying, right?
Well, put simply, yes.
I see.
Fine!
If that's what you want...
Remember this!
Next year, I'll make a masterpiece that even you'll accept, and then cram it right into your face!
Kaburaya Middle School
The Homemade Chocolates Case
Making chocolate from cocoa beans is just way too hard!
It looks like it.
But I'm not giving up.
I just need to make the best homemade chocolate ever.
If Fuku-chan still complains, I'll lock him up somewhere and read this book to him.
If that's not good enough, I'll shove my chocolate right down his throat!
Mayaka-san...
I've got your back!
Hey, now...
If there's anything I can help you with, just tell me!
Oh, right!
Do you know any stores that sell ingredients for making candy?
Let's see...
There should be a store that sells ingredients for professionals near the shopping district.
I can take you there if you'd like.
Really?
Yes!
Yay!
Make sure you keep this...
...a secret, right?
Then how about this Sunday?
Have they forgotten I'm here?
Okay, sounds good.
Oh, Oreki.
Make sure you don't say anything either.
Sure.
If you do...
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
Yeah, I won't.
Could you stop glaring at me like that?
Isn't this Satoshi's?
Hey, Houtarou!
You passed at just the right time.
How about it? A game for old times' sake?
I guess I'm in no hurry to get home...
I haven't been here since middle school.
Same for me.
I'll go with Viper 2.
You go with Raiden, right?
He's the only one I can use.
I thought he'd go straight to the defensive.
Was Satoshi this kind of player?
No.
This isn't like him.
Back in middle school, Satoshi was obsessed with winning.
He did whatever it took to win.
And if he lost, he'd get all pissed off.
He was a sore loser.
We're changing machines and going again!
Is this a trap?
Man, that was a good game.
That was great joystick handling.
Very nice, Houtarou.
Hey...
At the end there, why'd you just charge in like that?
Robot battles are all about close combat.
Don't you think so?
That's right.
This is Satoshi now.
He's changed since middle school.
This is no good!
I'm already nervous!
I'm sure he'll accept it.
I hope so.
By the way, Chii-chan...
Is there anyone you like?
Um...
I...
So itchy...
I present to you one bar of chocolate.
From Oreki Tomoe.
With warm and tender pity.
Good morning, Oreki-san.
Morning.
So how did it go with Ibara's chocolate?
She finished making it.
But it was quite a struggle to the end.
We tried all sorts of chocolates.
I'll bet you finished them all in a flash.
That's not nice, Oreki-san.
Sorry.
But the result was a masterpiece.
That must be what it means to put your heart into it.
Isn't it wonderful?
So, what's she going to do with it?
Well, she apparently has to go to the Manga Society today,
so she said she would leave it in the club room.
It's unfortunate.
Satoshi would probably prefer it that way, though.
Oreki-san, today is Valentine's Day...
But in my family, we don't give presents to people whom we're truly close to...
So that's why...
Even for Valentine's Day...
Wait a second...
Does that mean...
What does that mean?
They said it's going to snow.
Seriously? I didn't bring my umbrella...
We'll going to be late.
Y-Yeah.
Shall we go?
Geography
Prep. Room
Dear Fuku-chan,
Please accept my
Valentine's Day
chocolate.
Mayaka
Houtarou!
Going to the club room?
No.
I'll wait for the sleet to stop or snow to start in the library.
The club room's too cold.
You going to the club room?
Yeah, I am.
Ibara's apparently at the Manga Society, so she won't be there.
Word sure spreads fast.
Did Chitanda-san tell you?
Well, guess I'll head up now.
Satoshi.
Good luck.
With what? Come on.
Geography
Prep. Room
Huh?
Library
Oreki-san.
Chitanda?
Have you seen Fukube-san?
He didn't go to the room yet?
Not yet...
I thought something might have happened...
I saw him half an hour ago.
He said he'd be going to the club room.
Okay. I'll wait a little longer.
Fukube-san...
What's taking you?
Oreki-san!
Wait!
It's terrible!
The sleet stopped, and I'm about to go home.
Sorry, but can this wait until tomorrow?
Hey.
I'm sorry, but at least hear me out!
It's my fault.
I left the club room door open.
I've done something horrible to Mayaka-san...
Satoshi.
What happened?
Well, you see...
The chocolate!
Mayaka-san's chocolate was stolen!
Fine, I'll help.
I don't want to have to face Ibara if she hears her chocolate got stolen.
I'm not into horror, after all.
The Hannya
Sutra
Risshun
When the air of spring starts to rise.
Hyouka
Oreki-san, we can't use the west stairs to the fourth floor right now.
Just waxed.
No entry.
Let's take the east stairs.
Hey, do you have a second?
Is this level?
Looks crooked.
Trapezoidal?
One side's too low now.
Oh, shoot.
It was right here.
It was in a clear, vinyl bag.
It was shaped like a heart, about this big.
That's pretty big.
It was here before I went looking for Fukube-san.
When did you get back to the club room?
Just past five.
It's because I didn't lock the door for those 15 minutes...
You don't need to feel bad about it, Chitanda-san.
It's my fault for being so late.
Have you told Ibara about this?
Not yet.
It might not seem right, but I want to try finding it before telling her.
It's not anywhere in the room?
Right.
Fukube-san and I looked through the room and around the building.
Satoshi, too?
We met by the stairs.
We entered the room together.
I see.
When did the Crafts guys get there?
Crafts guy?
The guy with the glasses.
The person from the Crafts Club?
He was just starting to put up the poster when I went to look for Fukube-san.
Great.
If he was there the whole time, then he knows who came and went.
I see!
Wait.
What if he's the culprit?
Not a chance.
What kind of culprit would just stand around putting up a poster after the fact?
True...
People who passed here?
Yes.
I remember.
Three, in total.
Three?
What kind of people were they?
Did they have any particular characteristics?
One.
Two.
Three?
In other words, the culprit is still on the fourth floor.
Satoshi, what clubs are on the fourth floor?
I think they were the Classics Club, Light Music Club, Astronomy Club, and the Philosophy Club.
But I think the Astronomy Club and us are the only two that haven't gone home.
This is a rare sight.
You're not usually this into stuff.
What if the sleet starts up again?
Oh, shush.
So we might be able to find it?
But why would anyone do this?
That's the real question.
Let's try checking the possibilities first.
Electives Room 5
Coming!
Oh?
The Classics Club?
Give back the chocolate!
There's something we'd like to ask you, Senpai.
Oh?
What's that?
Well—
You see, some Valentine's Day chocolate was stolen from our club room.
We're looking for any witnesses.
Chocolate?
What's that, a love thief?
Did you see anyone between 4:45 and 5:00?
Well, we were partying pretty hard here...
I don't remember when, but at various times Nakayama, Yoshiwara, and Oda left the room I think.
Three out of five?
Did anyone go home?
No.
Is Oda-san that girl?
That's Nakayama.
I'm sorry Mr. Detective, but no one here took your chocolate.
Hey, guys!
Anyone here catch a glimpse of anything like chocolate?
Senpai, could you not kick me while I'm down like that?
Wish I could say I have!
Yeah, not happening to you!
You hear?
Is that all?
Thank you very much, Senpai.
Sorry we were rather rude.
Well, whatever.
Okay, back to the party!
Took you long enough, Senpai!
Sawakiguchi-san was angry.
Of course.
But we need to find Mayaka-san's chocolate!
Houtarou...
Let's just go back to the club room for now.
I want to bring this to a close.
Besides that staircase, is there any other way to get to the fourth floor?
Only the other staircase that's being waxed.
But there were no traces of anyone using that one.
I see.
Did you check the girls' bathroom?
I'll go check now!
Do you really think it's going to be there?
No, not a chance.
Not a chance? Then—
Satoshi.
I've more or less figured it out.
Be quiet for a bit.
Okay.
It wasn't there...
Then there's only one remaining possibility.
Oh?
Why's everyone here?
Um, Mayaka—
So what did you think?
How was my chocolate?
Straight to the point, huh?
Ibara—
I'm sorry, Mayaka-san!
I left the room without locking it, and someone stole your chocolate while I was gone...
I'm sorry!
I see...
It got stolen...
Mayaka-san...
I—
Don't worry about it!
It's nothing you need to apologize about.
It does sting a little, though...
I'm going home now.
Don't worry about it, Chii-chan, really!
Please move.
What are you going to do?
I may need to take some drastic measures, but I will find Mayaka-san's chocolate.
If I don't, there's no way I'll be able to face her tomorrow!
It's not your fault.
I can't forgive myself!
This was supposed to be a happy day for her!
I can't say I know how you feel.
I don't feel things as strongly as you.
But leave this to me.
I have something in mind.
But I can't do it with you around.
Do you know who did it?
Yeah.
Nakayama from the Astronomy Club.
Ibara's chocolate was pretty big, right?
Which means you couldn't hide it in a guy's uniform.
You'd look really awkward trying to move.
But it's possible in a girls' uniform.
You could tie it to your leg and hide it under your skirt.
I'll find Ibara's chocolate and give it to Satoshi before the day ends.
Leave this matter to me and go home.
Alright.
I'll trust you on this.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Satoshi.
Lend me your bag for a second.
I'm giving you Ibara's chocolate now.
Now I've fulfilled my promise to Chitanda.
The one who stole Ibara's chocolate was you.
Well done, Houtarou.
The moment I heard that her chocolate had been stolen,
it occurred to me that Satoshi would be the only person who'd do that.
But I was only sure when the Crafts member talked to us.
Satoshi said that one side was too low now.
He wouldn't have said that unless he had been there previously and said to lower the right side.
I'm guessing he hid in the boys' bathroom on the third floor and waited for Chitanda to pass,
then took the chocolate from the empty clubroom.
But it was larger than he thought.
He couldn't fit it in his bag, and there weren't any other bags that would fit it in the room.
He couldn't risk running into Chitanda while just holding it.
And so, he decided to...
Did you hesitate at all before you broke it?
Now we're even.
Even?
In April last year, you helped me distract Chitanda with the story of the Silk Spider Society.
Oh, I remember that.
But that didn't hurt anyone.
Except you.
I assume you have a good explanation for this.
If this was your idea of a joke...
If it was?
I'd have to hit you.
For both Chitanda and Ibara. Hard.
I don't think I'd like that.
I'd rather not say, but I guess I have to.
Do you think I'm the obsessive type?
Yeah. I'd call you a hobbyist.
That's not quite right.
A hobbyist devotes themselves to one specific area with the intent of being better than anyone else.
And you're different?
Yeah.
I won't ever be the best at anything.
Or rather, you might say...
I've stopped trying to be.
I'm guessing you noticed something different about me at the arcade, too.
About how I wasn't obsessed with winning.
Yeah.
In the past, I used to be obsessed with winning, so I tried to win all the time.
It was boring.
Even if I did win, it was boring. It was more than I could handle.
How can it be interesting unless you win in an interesting way?
One day I got tired of it.
I became obsessed with not being obsessed about anything.
And since then my life's been really fun.
Every day is a happy day.
But there was one problem.
Mayaka.
She's a great girl, really.
There's no one else like her.
For her to love me is like a dream come true.
Then—
However,
can I really let myself get obsessed with her?
I want to be with Mayaka, no question about it.
But I don't want to obsess over her.
I guess I'm just being selfish.
I'm not even thinking about how she feels.
So egotistical, right?
It's not like I want to make light of her feelings.
But if I leave my comfort bubble and accept her, I might go back to the way I used to be.
And that scares me.
That's why you didn't accept it?
Yeah. And so, we reach today.
I still haven't found my answer.
I couldn't think of any other way to not accept the chocolate that I couldn't accept.
But you hurt Chitanda in the process.
I guess my plans don't go as smoothly as yours.
Both Mayaka and I never stopped to consider Chitanda.
Mayaka-san!
Please wait!
Chii-chan...
I—
I'm sorry, Chii-chan!
I knew all along who stole my chocolate!
After Valentine's Day last year, I told Fuku-chan that I'd wait until he gave me an answer.
Today was supposed to be the day he gave it.
Then your chocolate...
Fuku-chan probably already has it.
I... see...
I'm sorry that I ended up hiding it from you.
Don't worry about it!
It's my fault for making such a fuss about it.
So when Oreki-san said someone from the Astronomy Club took it...
I'm sure he was just lying to cover for Fuku-chan.
I see.
But how could Fukube-san be so mean as to pretend they were stolen?
I know, right?!
Yes!
It pisses me off so much!
But what pisses me off the most is that I still love him!
Alright, Chii-chan! Let's go stuff ourselves with cake!
Okay!
Well, Houtarou, that's the whole story.
What now?
It's not like I can tell Chitanda any of that...
No way.
I'd rather be punched.
So, have you found your answer yet?
I think I'll have an answer soon.
I see.
You're good at what you do, but you need to work on how you do it.
Sorry. In the end, I didn't really understand you at all.
But I can't really say that to him.
Yeah, I managed to get the chocolate to Satoshi.
I see. That's good to hear.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
Oreki-san, thank you for everything you did today.
Sure.
Mayaka
Hello?
Hey.
There's something I need to tell you...
Bitter.
joukyou wa hikagaku teki ni
The case seems so irrational
kanjou no monta-ju
A montage of emotions
dare ga dare wo yonderu
Just who's calling who right now?
furimukeba nigeteku shisen kanjiru
When I turn around, you always look away (I can feel it)
ki no sei ja tsurenai yo
It's not my imagination
antena wa sainou tte iu desho
Intuition is a talent, too, you know
datte (datte) shiritai (kimi wa chigau no)
I mean (I mean) I want to know (Don't you want to?)
seishun ondosa ima no uchi tadashite ageru yo
I'll make sure you see your youth the same way as I see it right now
ashita kaiketsu suru nara ima demo yokunai
If we can solve it tomorrow, then why not solve it today?
kimi no misuteri-
You are a mystery
toite mitai
Detective I'll try to be
shougen no himitsumeita senaka sagase (kyou mo)
Looking for the person who makes me feel this way (Again today)
kimi wa fantaji-
You are a fantasy
hikareteiku yo zurui
You draw me in to see
fukuranda koukishin
I want to launch an investigation
torikku wa nai no ni
Even though a trick there won't be
ki ni naru yo
I'm so curious
kyoumibukai
This case interests me
doushite
Why is that?
Next time: Chicks on a Detour.
Chicks on a Detour