When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Thank you for having me.
You are welcome.
Please come visit again.
Say, Isumi, what do you say
to being lost for one more night?
What? But...
I need you!
If we become separated now,
there's a chance we may never
meet again in this lifetime!
If you only came to school,
we could see each other.
She has friends to invite her
to school like that, and yet...
I have to do something so that
the Miss can enjoy going to school!
Hayate!
Yes?
What do you suppose is the meaning of life?
What? Um...
D-Do I need to answer that immediately?
No, but I think the testament of your life
is not something
that is given to you by others.
Having been born a human being,
I think there must be a way
of life that's more true to myself.
Um, is this going to take long?
Well, there you have it.
While she's coming up
with excuses like that, it'll be tough...
Even when urgently needing
to go to the bathroom,
you listen to what the Miss has to say.
That is yet another part of a butler's duties!
Hey, no filming allowed within the residence!
Ow!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Please do not, by any means,
watch this alone.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
That's just not cool!
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Elohim Essaim.
Mr. Cow, Mr. Cow! What is it, Mr. Frog?
Good morning, Miss! It's Hayate!
What is it? It's so early...
Miss!
Hey, you dummy! What
are you doing all of a sudden?!
I will help you change!
Since it would be a shame
to only accompany you to school!
Don't be ridiculous!
How could I do something embarrassing
like change in front of you?!
Accompany me to school?
Yes!
Starting today, I shall be
escorting you to and from school!
You think a trick like that
will make me go to school?!
*This is within the grounds of the Sanzenin estate.
W-Well, no need to go to school.
It would be fine to just go
somewhere to have fun like this.
What are you saying?
A student's duty is to study.
Please attend every day and study hard.
*This is within the grounds of Hakuou Academy.
I will see you later, Miss.
Why?!
If I go to school, we become
separated for the duration,
so why do you want me
to go to school so much?!
There are some who can't go to school
anymore, even if they want to, so...
S-Sorry...
Then I shall come
for you again after school.
With the Miss away at school,
we really get some peace
and quiet here at the estate.
If the tiger would refrain from talking,
I think we'd have even more peace and quiet.
The butler-in-debt sure is coldhearted.
Or rather, don't you need to be in school?
You were technically in high school
before you came here, right?
Well, yes, but...
I must be the Miss's butler here
for another 40 years to repay my debt,
so given that, going to school just seems...
So I've got another eternity of lectures
that remind me of crappy games.
Nagi, wait.
Why doesn't the blackboard have
the ability to skip forward?
It's because they continue to adhere
to such old-fashioned systems
that education in Japan is never going to...
Wh-What are you...?!
You must not go that way.
What?
That is not the school building.
R-Right.
It's so rare for you to know
when we're going in the wrong direction.
I guess you don't attend
school every day for nothing.
That is not the reason, but I can tell...
Winner!
Sinner
I-It was one letter off...
Hey, I'm home!
Oh? That's strange...
What is the matter?
It seems she forgot a notebook at school.
What?!
See that?!
This is what happens when
I make a rare excursion to school!
It is because you go to school
so infrequently that this happens.
I will go get it!
You have dedicated yourself
to studying all day today!
We cannot allow the fruit of that labor
to languish in a deserted classroom!
Well, it's not that important...
And it's quite late already...
All right, I'm off!
How do I get into school at night?
Suspicious individual sighted!
Wait. Oh?
You're that suspicious individual
from some time ago,
who's also a Sanzenin family butler,
who also saved my life...
Um...
I'm Hayate Ayasaki.
As I recall, you are a teacher here...
Yukiji Katsura.
Or rather, what're you doing here?
I was dodging your blow from behind.
Oh.
What are you doing out in the street?
Oh, me?
I'm on so-called night duty.
You know, night duty.
Your hard work is much appreciated!
This is perfect. Miss Nagi apparently
forgot something here and...
What?
I'm sorry to ask this, but might
I borrow the key to the classroom?
What?!
Th-The key to the classroom?!
You mean, you're coming
to the night duty room?!
Yes! I don't want you
to trouble yourself, after all.
Uh, wait, I'll go get it for you.
Night Duty Room
No, I will go myself.
If you just open the door...!
This night duty room is rather bursting
with the lifestyle sensibilities
of a woman in her mid-20s, isn't it?
I-It's not that bad!
I already culled a lot of my
personal belongings, you know.
Could it be that you live here?
I-I-It can't be helped, right?!
I can't afford rent
and the bath in the night duty room
is cleaner and bigger!
Oh wait, you're an outsider!
I don't have to take this from you!
Oh? What do we have here?
Oh.
Katsy's bringing a man back
with her to the night duty room!
And it's a younger guy to boot!
Scandal exposed! You'll be fired for sure!
Anything but that! My salary!
You've got the wrong idea!
Wait, that look of poverty...
I feel like I've seen it before...
I-I'm a butler of the Sanzenin family.
My name is Hayate Ayasaki.
Oh!
You trespassed on school grounds!
And after making a pass
at the student body president,
you took a kick to the face
and got rejected!
And as revenge,
you tried to kidnap and confine her
to the student council office,
but your plot was foiled by Yukiji!
That butler of the Sanzenin family!
I feel like some rather erroneous
embellishments have been added to the story...
You're just imagining things.
So anyway, I'm the student council committee chairman, Izumi Segawa.
Nice to meet you!
Likewise, vice chairman, Miki Hanabishi.
Disciplinary committee member, Risa Asakaze.
Student council?
Then, these people
are Miss Katsura's friends?
What are you doing here?
Um, um... Hayata?
I'm "Hayate".
I came to pick up something Miss Nagi forgot.
I see. Incidentally, we are here to study
for our midterms, Hayata.
Indeed we are, Hayata.
Fine, just call me "Hayata".
But meeting for a study group
so late at night at school...
You really are studious.
If we truly were studious,
we wouldn't be meeting
for a study group, Hayata.
But I thought Hakuou
is a prestigious school...
It's just that a portion
of our students are super smart.
They're the ones who transfer
and skip grades, after all.
But fundamentally, except
under extreme circumstances,
our system of automatic
advancement won't flunk you.
The school covers grades 1-12!
Students like us, who've
been here since grade school,
are stupid, as it should be!
So that we're on the verge of flunking
due to extreme circumstances!
Beat that!
So that's why I'm tutoring them.
The way Katsy teaches makes
things so easy to understand!
Oh, please!
It's a good example of how good athletes
don't always make good coaches.
Right, right.
Wait, was that a compliment?
Relax. I was mocking you.
Don't you mock your teacher!
Looks like a lot of fun.
Here.
The classroom key.
Return it when you're done, okay, Hayata?
Miss Katsura, you know what
my real name is, don't you?
But you know, you sure
aren't a boy for nothing!
Going to the classroom
in the West Building so late at night!
What?
I know!
Yeah, yeah.
Um, surely, you don't mean...
Well, it is an old school.
There are apparently a lot of appearances.
What?!
Don't bring back any curses
or anything with you!
Even if Sadako or Kayako
or Jason or Freddy show up,
beat them up, okay?
Right...
Just because they don't have to go...
Besides, it's the school building
they attend on a daily basis.
There's no way any such things will appear...
Come on! Isn't this way different than
when I was here last?!
W-Well, since I'm here anyway, I guess I'll go in...
From this red door...
Old School Building Do Not Enter
How would you like some squid? (Ika wa ikaga)
I'll have lots, thanks.
(Gattsuri itadaki-masu)
Whoa...
My cell?!
Oh, right, I got one from Maria.
Yes, hello?
Hey, Hayate, how are you doing?
I'm in the school building right now.
To what do I owe this sudden phone call?
Oh, no, sorry!
But you know, school at night can be dangerous in various ways, so well...
I got worried.
Thank you very much.
R-Right. I'm relieved, though.
I thought you were alone,
but I hear lots of other people around you,
so I guess you're there
with a bunch of people.
What?
You hear people?
Yes, I hear a lot of chatter
in the background.
But it's not like this is a test of courage.
I don't think it's necessary for them
to be screaming like that.
Well, good luck.
Miss?! Miss?!
No Signal
Do it over from somewhere
with a good signal.
In fact, do over your whole life.
I-I better hurry to the classroom.
It's taking him a while to come back...
Well, at night, classrooms hold
alluring recorders and P.E. clothes
that are distracting for adolescent boys.
He may be a butler, but he's still a boy.
He's probably ransacking Hina's desk right
about now and has her recorder...
You seem to be having an awful lot of fun.
What in the world might you be talking about?
Whoa, Miss Student Body President...
Hina, when did you get here?
I made a special effort to bring you snacks,
but are you working seriously?
Not to worry.
We are seriously discussing
the perverted actions of adolescent boys.
Huh?
In conclusion, your recorder must be
in Hayata's possession right about now.
That's right!
Get serious and study! Study!
Hey, maybe Hayata's mistakenly
wandered into the old school building.
The old school building?
Oh, that's a distinct possibility!
This is terrible. That place is...
Wh-What?
What?! Hakuou Academy
is haunted by evil spirits?!
Yes, I hear they appear
in the old school building.
Well, knowing that school, I'm sure
they'll hire a ghost sweeper or something.
What are we going to do?!
If Hayate mistakenly goes in there...
Hayate, respond! Hayate!
No Signal
You have no signal.
What?
Hayate of the Sanzenin family
went to that old school building?!
No, we're just saying it's possible.
We don't know that he's
actually wandered in there...
I'll go look for him.
It's dangerous, Hina!
An outsider may be in danger
on school grounds!
I can't just ignore that.
There may be ghosts and stuff.
Don't worry. Ghosts and stuff
don't bother me at all.
That's Hina for you.
I know she's my little sister,
but it's too bad that she's a girl,
considering how tough she is.
Yup, yup.
I know what I said, but...
A-Anyway, I better hurry up and find Hayate.
Come to think of it,
why's it so bright in here...?
That scream just now...
My cell...
I thought ghosts and stuff
do not bother you.
Like there's a girl who wouldn't
be bothered by those things!
They say will-o'-the-wisps
are a scientific phenomenon called plasma.
There's nothing logical
about what scares you!
Then here is the final question.
Who is it that has been
asking you these questions?
S-Someone...
Someone!
Are you all right?!
Oh? You're Miss Katsura,
the student body president.
M-Miss Katsura?!
Thank you for saving me, but...
Don't go wandering
into scary places like this!
I see, so this is the old school building.
No wonder things didn't seem quite right...
What happened earlier is to be kept
strictly secret, all right, Hayate?
Pardon?
If you tell anyone that I was scared
like that, I'll hit you for real!
I feel like you already hit me
for real earlier...
Never mind that. Let us hurry up
and get out of here.
What are you saying, Hayate?
Huh?
You think I'd ever go home after being beaten?!
No, but I need to get the Miss's notebook...
Overruled!
I'm going to identify who that
bastard was, no matter what!
Oh, wait... Miss Katsura!
Call me Hinagiku!
Please wait, Miss Katsura!
It will not do to leave things as they are.
Miss Katsura really
is the same as Miss Nagi.
She absolutely hates to lose.
It's getting kind of hot in here.
Wow, are you self-conscious
that you're alone with
a girl at school at night?
I-I'm not self-conscious
about someone like you.
Someone like me?
You're too unguarded to begin with!
You should learn to be
a bit more modest around boys!
Being easygoing like that, who knows
what someone might do to you...
I'm fine with that.
Huh?
If it's you, Hayate,
you can do anything to me.
What?! M-Miss Katsura?!
If I played a joke like that,
would boys think I was being serious?
Thank you for the warning.
I'll be careful in the future...
...around boys like you.
I thought she hated to lose
about as much as the Miss,
but I was wrong.
She hates to lose even more than the Miss!
That's the doll that I defeated earlier!
What?! No way!
Ta-da!
L-Leave, you humans!
Leave, or I-I will eat you guys!
Don't underestimate Hinagiku Katsura,
the student body president of Hakuou Academy!
I-It is unfair to execute a sneak attack!
A-At any rate, my dear Hayate...
Huh?
Please hurry up and leave this...
I mean. L-Leave!
The humiliation you made me suffer earlier...
I'll return the favor a hundred times over!
Why you!
I-I will curse you!
"My dear Hayate"...?
I don't understand the situation at all,
but could this really be a simple
scare tactic to get us out of here?
Miss Katsura, let's forget about
that terrifying monster and leave!
Call me Hinagiku!
At any rate, I'm defeating this bastard!
Please!
"We can't go until you've magnificently
defeated that terrifying doll?!"
Don't say such a thing! Let us leave!
It'll be fine, Hayate.
If I fight him without fear,
he's not that tough...
I-I am tough!
I am real strong,
so I will defeat you humans!
You may have changed your appearance,
but you're no match for me...
You got me!
But I haven't done anything yet...
Uh-oh.
W-Well, that was incredible, Miss Katsura!
You defeated the ghost
with just your fighting spirit!
Huh? Huh?!
That must be what they call "chi"! "Chi"!
It's what the masters use!
You must have used it without realizing it!
Man, you're incredible, Miss Katsura!
I'm not sure I'm convinced...
Come now. The evil spirit has been
defeated, so let us hurry and...
Huh?
You're going to get Nagi's notebook, right?
What?
Let's hurry.
Y-Yes, Miss Katsura.
Call me Hinagiku.
Yes, Hinagiku.
It seems they have finally left.
Yes.
Now, let us defeat the real evil spirit.
Yes, ma'am!
Hayate!
I was so worried! You didn't get
possessed by evil spirits, did you?!
I am fine.
School really is a nice thing to have.
School life is a distant thing for him now.
What is the butler-in-debt thinking?
And this is where in the next episode,
a terrible incident happens
that no one could ever have anticipated!
We all will fight against a state of emergency!
Or rather, we have no choice but to fight it!
Study!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Sign: Butler Report
I'm counting on you, courage.
I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Today, we've brought Maria
on for a guest appearance.
Hello, I'm Maria.
Man, this song is so soothing.
That's Maria for you!
Thank you very much, Hayate.
What's this, Hayate?! Getting all spoony!
Oh, my.
All right, I think I'll train hard
to become a soothing ladylike girl, too!
No, you are best as you are now, Miss!
Really? If you say so...
Bye-bye!
Preview
Say, Maria, I recall seeing this
scene several times before...
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
The next episode takes place
during the same time as Episode 8.
Which means we get to see
cat-ear Hayate from another angle!
That is not all.
It seems it is a completely
original story made just for anime.
Ooh! That makes me feel
both worry and anticipation.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Strangest Hyperdeflation Ever.
"Play Your Games
and Don't Build Up a Backlog".
Mr. Hero, please get fished up already!
The Strangest Hyperdeflation Ever.
Play Your Games and Don't Build Up a Backlog
Rawr! I'm currently intensely fired up!