Romero...
Romero, let me bring you there...
The place you longed for.
A place where no one can catch up with us.
At a speed fast enough to brush off the past...
...to reach there.
I can't believe you've got work this late.
For my work it doesn't matter what time it is.
Getting tired of becoming an assassin?
Nope.
This might take a while.
You can go to bed.
No, I'll stay up.
I picked up a broken video cassette recorder during the day.
I want to try to fix it.
Just buy a new one.
That's such a waste.
Maybe it can still be used.
It can still be used, huh?
That's right.
Come back soon.
Yeah.
Promise.
Yeah, I promise.
I don't want to leave you...
I want to stay by your side forever.
If I can still return to the way I once was...
...it's time to quit.
Whether I choose to stop or to run...
Whatever I pick, the organization will...
You're late, Lizzie.
Lizzie?
All right, don't move.
I'm sorry.
I'm always giving you trouble.
I've heard about it, brat.
You're that Phantom guy.
No wonder my young men were finished off so easily.
Don't play dumb.
I've got solid proof.
Look.
That picture... who...
Was it her?
So?
Not gonna defend yourself?
Mr. Godoh, it's a misunderstanding.
That picture...
Listen to me before you embarrass yourself.
I know your higher-ups ordered you to do it.
We just want to know the inside story.
The one behind all three attacks against us was Claudia.
Is that right?
Are you fuckin' stupid?
How much effort do you think Claudia put in to get you guys into Inferno?!
Although I like loyal people,
that woman doesn't deserve so much loyalty from you guys.
She tricked us.
Both you guys and us.
Shut the fuck up...
Hey, Miss...
It isn't our first time meeting at this place.
What?
Don't you remember?
That was such a memorable night.
Yeah, it's almost been a year.
A year?
Which organization are they from?!
The lading...
We did it!
It's too early to say that, bro.
Just get the hell out of here!
I see. So it was you guys.
You teamed up with Scythe...
I don't know anyone named Scythe.
The one who planned it was Claudia.
No way!
When we were about to hit a dead end...
That woman came to us out of the blue and offered a deal.
She allowed us to steal 500 kg of cocaine.
She prepared everything beforehand, including backup.
She even asked us, "Do you want to have some 'fun' in Los Angeles?"
Why did she do it?!
The condition was that after things were settled,
the Godoh Group would join Inferno through her.
At first we didn't understand,
but after finding out her situation, we did.
She wants an organization within Inferno that can watch her back.
If she's always alone,
she won't have a chance to shine.
That thing about how we used to get cargo from other places is bullshit.
The market we have now was created in the course of one year.
Using the cocaine we stole from you as capital.
Then Claudia sold out Scythe...?
Yeah, there was a retard who got screwed from that.
Is it him? The Scythe you're talking about.
It's me.
There's been a sudden change of plans. Scythe betrayed the organization.
He made Phantom attack Inferno's lading.
The organization is looking for those two with all their might.
They haven't found either of them though.
At that time...
A way to prove your innocence and get Ein back.
You know how to use this, don't you?
It was all because of her...
Scythe!
Because of that, we were hurt and shed tears.
Judging by your looks, it seems like you remembered something.
Is it true, Phantom?!
Seems like even the great Phantom was deceived by a woman.
However, there's a sequel to the story.
That bitch wants to kill Shiga and me in the end,
and control the Godoh Group by herself.
On one hand, she's finishing us off in order to seal our mouths.
On the other, she's using the confusion that's caused to remove her rivals.
Even I can't believe how scheming she is.
This is the truth.
Get it? She used us as stepping stones.
I don't give a shit about Inferno anymore.
My name won't be Godoh Daisuke if I don't do anything after being deceived like this!
I don't believe this! I don't fuckin' believe this!
You fucking bastards!
Die!
Shit! Where?!
Where are you?!
It's that one.
Get on, Phantom!
You go on first.
Phantom!
Elen...
Impossible... you're still alive?
But why?
Why, Elen?!
Why are you doing this?!
Don't call me Elen.
I am Ein.
Right now and in the past.
I've just been Ein.
Hurry up and escape.
Inferno will come and kill you soon.
Once and for all.
Inferno will?
Elen!
Wait!
I am Ein.
Right now and in the past.
It's him, huh?
It's that bastard...
Scythe Master!
Beautiful.
The Godoh Group, Claudia McCunnen,
and Inferno's Issac Wisemel.
Stirring up a three-sided struggle of fear and doubt.
Sending the ones who tricked you before to hell one by one.
No, that's not all.
The truth behind it was sent to Inferno through my guidance.
They'll take action soon.
They'll kill the traitor, Claudia McCunnen...
and her trusted subordinate, Phantom.
The organization is going to kill me? If so...
Cal!
I see.
You passed the entrance exam.
Congratulations, Mio.
I wanted to tell you right away.
Am I interfering with your work?
Don't worry about that.
But foreign trading is tiring, right?
Yeah, it is.
I need to leave Japan the day after tomorrow to deliver stuff.
Do you want any gifts?
No, it's fine since you always buy them.
Besides, if I receive too much from you, mom will find out.
I see...
That's true.
My friends are waiting for me.
Have fun.
See you again.
Okay!
Although she was kept apart from the main family,
the same blood of me and the boss flows inside Mio.
The blood of the Godoh's demons.
If someone tries to take advantage of that,
Mio won't be able to protect herself since she doesn't know anything.
No matter that her standpoint or surname changed,
she's still my little sister.
My precious little sister.
Shiga, this is going to be a huge deal.
If I can't make it back alive,
then...
I know, bro.
I, Shiga, will watch over Mio-san's future until the end.
I'm sorry, Shiga.
I got shot in the stomach and shoulder, huh?
This is no big deal.
I've survived after catching at least twice as many bullets.
The Asura realm is my way.
Yo.
Who's left?
They're all dead.
Really? So in the end,
the only ones left are you and me again.
It's always like this.
Regardless of what hell it is,
you're always there to rush in with me.
With my courage and your intelligence, no matter when...
What's wrong?
Nothing much.
So what about Claudia?
Inferno is going to finish that woman off.
Forget that. The problem is with us, the Godoh Group.
Inferno won't let us, the group that was under that woman, go so easily.
War is about to begin.
Inferno, so what?
They tricked us, so it's payback time.
We need to teach them a lesson, right Shiga?
We'll kill them all!
There's no need for that.
As long as one person dies, everything will be settled.
Shiga...
I guess you won't believe me no matter what I say now.
Bro, I truly love you from the bottom of my heart.
Shiga...
Shiga!
Killing the traitors proves the Godoh Group's sincerity.
I'll help you out with joining Inferno.
Mr. Shiga, now the Godoh Group is safe.
Giuseppe, I can barely hold back my urge to shoot you.
Are you going to shoot me?
Seems like we'll get along well.
We can become good friends, Mr. Shiga.
Clau... Where are you, Clau?!
Where are you?! Where the hell are you?!
At least give me an excuse, Claudia McCunnen!
Run, Reiji.
Live on!
Any pursuers?
Cal...
Cal!
You're still not bored of it?
Of course not.
Do you like that song that much?
I do.
Because it was given to me by the person I love most.
I thought I had nothing...
What normal people usually have, I don't.
That's why I thought I'd never be able to get it.
Thanks, Reiji.
I want to stay by your side forever.
Cal...
CAL!!
If this world isn't an endless hell...
...it must be because you're here alive.