There we go, nice and clean again.
Why the extra effort? Did someone say they were stopping by?
Not really, but he still might come. Mr. Moriaki, that is.
Oh? I thought you lost all hope and gave up.
Today's love horoscope on TV predicted that this is the week
that you'll become more intimate with your fated someone.
Channel 6's did, anyway.
Channel 6's?
I flip through the channels and watch all the different ones.
The last one I watched is my true fortune, though.
Like the other day, the first one I saw predicted "poor luck".
So I tried other channels, but it just kept getting worse.
Flipped to the last one, and it was the worst of all 13 signs!
13? I thought there were only 12.
If it's in 13th place, I can't simply put my faith in "poor luck".
If I were 12th, it'd tell me,
"you're a persevering romantic Taurus."
But 13th place predicted, "Aries can get
things done, but can also be inconsiderate".
That fits you perfectly!
Goodness, I wish I could be as carefree as you are every day.
Hee-hee, is it that obvious?
I bet my "intimate encounter" with my fated someone means Mr. Moriaki!
Couldn't your "fated someone" mean someone else?
Like your arch-nemesis, rival, or natural enemy, and stuff.
Why would a love horoscope mention my natural enemy?
Hey, here comes your intimate encounter with Mr. Moriaki.
Where!?
Notice
Hotori Arashiyama
Stay after class for
supplementary math lessons
Natsuhiko
Moriaki
Extra lessons!?
Good for you, your fortune was accurate.
Nanairo no Tasogare Oritekite
A rainbow-colored dusk surrounds us,
Kaze wa Nandaka Suzushige
and the breeze is nice and cool.
Doyoubi no Yoru wa Nigiyaka
It's a party every Saturday night.
Kurai Kimochi Sae Sugu ni Harete
It brings a smile to anyone blue.
Minna Ukiuki ukiuki
Everyone's happy.
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Down Town e Kuridasou
So let's go downtown!
Ukiuki
Let's be happy.
Formulas of Love (From Vol.1 Chapter 9)
Formulas.
Formulas are equations that use variables to prove a certain value for a single set of data.
Said values are referred to as solutions.
Here, before my very eyes, sits my second natural enemy.
I recall my first natural enemy was my 2nd grade homeroom teacher.
When we read books, we all form our own unique opinions, right?
The charm of literature is that there are as many answers as there are people who read.
On the other hand, for math, there is only one correct answer for a problem.
That's what makes math so interesting.
I get it! I think I like math!
Division
Uh-oh... we're not done yet, but we can't divide any further!
What do you think we should do here?
She's right! What do we do?
We can't do anything about the leftovers, so we write "remainder 5" here.
T-Teacher!
What's the matter, Moriaki?
Umm, well, is it okay to just leave it unfinished like that?
You're right, it is kind of troubling.
But there's nothing we can do about it.
How would you handle it, Moriaki?
I don't know...
But teacher, you always say not to leave leftovers at lunch,
so is it okay to have leftovers in division?
He's right!
I agree with Moriaki!
Thank goodness! I said that out of desperation, but everyone seems to agree with me!
That's true, it's bad to stop when there's still some left.
But if you have a persimmon in your lunch, you leave the seeds, right?
The remainder in division is just like those seeds.
Sit down already, Moriaki.
Hehe stoopid! You eat persimmon seeds?
You're the stupid one here!
This experience would end up having a major effect on my life.
This eventually led me to becoming a math teacher.
My homeroom teacher became my first natural enemy.
And now, in front of me sits the second.
Umm, by any chance, am I the only one getting supplemental lessons?
Supplementary
Math
Lessons
The only person to get a zero on both the test and  the exam is you, Hotori Arashiyama.
Oh, really? All right then...
Well, it's not so bad!
Just think of it as a date!
My stomach's beginning to turn earlier than I expected!
Hotori Arashiyama.
As a teacher, I hold good morals in the highest regard.
Of course, I'm concerned about my students to a point,
but I'm sure you know how I would respond to that comment.
Yeah, I think I've got it.
Very good. Now pay attention to me.
When I was grading the tests...
Next one is... Arashiyama.
It happens every time.
As soon as I get to your test, my stomach begins to hurt.
For the equation
if
find the value of b
Despite the fact that you clearly gave up halfway, you still wrote the answer anyway.
Naturally, the answer was completely wrong.
Just the mere sight of it made me sick to my stomach.
Before I could even consider the answer, seeing that bastardized square root gave me a splitting headache.
And worst of all...
If you don't know the answer then JUST LEAVE IT BLANK!
Just when I thought I had finally found a part of your test to circle,
it ended up being a zero in the score box instead.
Grading your tests is without a doubt chipping away at my life.
This is obviously the work of a serial exam murderer!
Oh my god!
You sure have a passion for melodrama.
But to make matters worse, you're doing perfectly fine in all your other classes.
I can only assume that you're doing this out of spite.
But math's got nothing to do with being a detective.
Detective?
Right now, I'm but an ordinary high school girl.
But someday, I will become a genius high school detective!
Someday? How long do you plan on being in high school?
At any rate, if you keep this up, you won't move onto the next grade.
So your dream might just come true.
A 20-something year old high school detective is not outside the bounds of reason.
And thus we're having these supplementary lessons.
Now, solve this problem.
Good...
Mr. Moriaki!
Wow, that was fast.
How would you move a sphere of one
meter in diameter into this house?
Door
Sphere
What's the meaning of this?
Do you know how to get that sphere into the house?
Everything you need to solve it is already written here.
Of course!
The sphere has a diameter of one meter from every angle.
While the rectangular door's parallel sides make a constant one meter width.
Thus, the sphere cannot pass through a door this narrow.
It's impossible.
The answer is simple.
The sphere doesn't pass through the door.
The house was built around it!
This kind of outside the box thinking is critical in life.
So for math too, if you give the answer first, it's easier to understand.
I like corm.
Maid Cafe Seaside
You, cracking open a textbook, Hotori? What gives?
That's a rare sight. Did hell freeze over or something?
Already has. At this rate, I'll be an eternal high schooler.
Wow, I'm kinda jealous.
Moriaki's furious at me!
Of course he'd be if you showed him a silly riddle like this.
You know how he's overly serious.
Just how serious he is, however,
can only be explained in a story I heard from an upperclassman.
Years ago, there was a student in love with him.
She was a pure, charming young girl with a passion for literature.
That's just like me!
We're exactly alike!
Huh!?
One day, this girl poured her heart into a letter,
and handed it to Mr. Moriaki.
The next day, she received his reply.
What did it say? I wanna hear!
Wait, don't, I'm scared!
My heart's all aflutter!
Only a single equation was written.
(Boy + Girl) / morals = 0
Love between a teacher and student was not morally acceptable.
And so she was ignored.
The girl made such a fuss over it that it eventually reached the principal's ears.
Here's  where your characters overlap.
Principal's Office
But the principal...
Mr. Moriaki is a moral beacon in this age of illicit school conduct!
...was moved to tears instead.
They say that it hangs in his office to this day.
And they all lived happily ever after.
What part of that is happy!?
You won't change his mind, so just let it go.
If you don't buckle down and study, you really will be held back.
They're alike.
My two natural enemies almost overlap!
Speaking in riddles completely unrelated to math and making me look like a fool.
It's almost as if their faces resemble each other.
Could it be that the adult Hotori Arashiyama went back in time to be my homeroom teacher?
No, don't be silly.
I don't believe in that sci-fi hocus-pocus nonsense.
I'm such a kidder...
Done!
Lemme see. I'll check your answers.
Morals < Love
What the heck is this?
My answer to his equation.
I'll show him this at the next extra lesson.
Yup, you're not moving up this year.
Formulas.
The values of the variables within, are referred to as solutions.
There are also cases when there is no correct answer.
Results of what
she "showed" him:
_____________
Morals < Love
Cursian Roulette From Vol.3 Chapter 25
Here's your coffee, Mr. Moriaki.
Thank you.
And some for you, Mr. Kameda.
'Preciate it. Pardon me.
Way back, they used to say that when you pour the milk in,
it would float to the surface and spell your soulmate's initials.
I never took you for a romantic, Mr. Kameda.
Never, huh...
If you squint your eyes, it kinda looks like it says N.M.
As in Natsuhiko Moriaki, that is.
Interesting. Mine looks like pi.
He totally blew me off!
That's not even an initial.
I suppose it means I'm fond of pi.
Well, I wouldn't say I'm not.
What about you, Mr. Kameda?
If I don't see god's initials in mine, then I'm in trouble.
Curse.
What happened? It just collapsed all of a sudden.
The height lever must be out of whack.
I'm stumped. It falls every time I put some weight on it.
The desk next to me is open. How about you switch chairs?
I think I'll do that.
This is a bad omen, I think.
The work of that "curse" initial maybe?
Don't say stuff like that, Ms. Nishi. It's not even an initial.
Dear, come quick! Hotori's putting some weird goop on her face!
She said she's just putting on lotion so the air doesn't dry out her face.
Our little girl's growing up, huh?
I wonder. She can't tell the difference
between lipstick and glue stick, so I'm not so sure.
What? What happened!?
My eyes! My eyes!
My face burns, and it stings really bad!
Jeez! What did you put on?
King
of Hair
Yeah, the bottles look similar, so you must have mistaken it.
Dad, you jerk!
Why are you using hair tonic when you aren't even bald!?
It's thanks to that stuff that I still have hair!
It's hurting my eyes! I can't open them, so I'm gonna skip school today.
Don't be ridiculous!
...and that's why I was late today.
You've got some imagination. Your excuses never cease to amaze me.
Well, they say truth is stranger than fiction.
Grown up men sure have it tough, having to put that burny stingy stuff on every day.
How's your hair holding out, sir?
Still there, no thanks to you.
If I start losing hair because of stress, it'll be your responsibility.
A shotgun wedding!
You sure aren't the type who thinks before they speak.
I'm going to begin class, so have a seat.
We'll continue this later. See me after class!
Well, those kinds of things do happen.
I brushed my teeth with face soap before.
You're such a klutz!
You're the last person I wanna hear that from!
Sure stepped on a landmine there.
I told my story right after yours, so what's with the attitude?
I mean, normally after that nasty
taste, you'd be sure not to do it again.
It's not like you've never done that yourself.
Notice
Hotori Arashiyama
Concerning your tardiness
Natsuhiko
Moriaki
Hey, what the hell!?
Called out for tardiness? What are you, a middle-schooler?
So he was serious about staying after class.
Well, Moriaki's a stickler for rules, you know.
As for how extreme he is, there's this story-
I know. The love letter.
Tattsun told me about it before.
Love between a teacher and
student was not morally acceptable.
Well, the story doesn't end there.
There's more?
5 or 6 years passed, and believe it or not, she began working here as a teacher!
But there's still no sign that the feeling is mutual.
It's important to know when to give up.
My, what lovely weather!
Better get home before dark, yes indeed.
I tried to act natural and sneak by, but you caught me!
That was so unnatural that I
remembered the notice I wrote for you.
I got work soon, so make it quick.
That depends on your behavior.
I just had thoughts unbecoming of a teacher!
Thoughts of sweet revenge for the daily torture Arashiyama puts me through!
If I made her sit on that broken chair, she'd be in for a surprise.
Such genius!
I never knew I had such a sharp sense of humor!
What happened, Ms. Nishi?
Sorry, I just spilled some coffee, but I just finished cleaning it up.
Oh, I see.
I have no idea which one's the sinking chair!
It's regrettable, but I'm afraid the
"Spook Arashiyama Plan" is on hold.
Wait a minute!
Which chair should I sit in?
Standard Lecturing Style
according to level of offense
Minor
Minor offense lecture style.
Infraction
Mid-level offense lecture style.
Serious
Infraction
Serious Infraction lecture style.
How should I approach this?
Which chair should I sit in?
What if my chair collapses and goes ka-thud ?
My dignity will collapse along with it!
Which one's the busted chair?
I can't tell from just pushing on them.
If I had known this would happen, I'd have marked it this morning!
Just skip the lecture today!
Are you just going to run from your responsibilities?
Okay. I'm going to sit now.
Sure, go ahead.
Damn, she's not getting the hint!
I just realized that pi looks kind of like death!
How ominous!
Just relax! Things like that aren't real!
The only truth here is the 33.33% chance this is the busted chair!
What are you doing, sir?
N-Nothing at all.
Okay, Arashiyama. I'm going to sit down, so you sit down too.
Well, okay then.
No hard feelings, okay?
You're acting strange, sir. Babbling about 33.33% and stuff.
W-Well, you see...
Basically, in the span of a month, you're late 33% of the time. Yes.
It's not that  often!
Twice a week at most.
Arashiyama, math aside, you can't even do basic arithmetic?
Um, 6 school days each week...
...and I'm late 2 out of those 6...
Agh! Weren't we talking about tardiness?
Why are you trying to turn this into math class?
My class is on the level of mere arithmetic...
No! I've avoided the collapsing chair, so I can't allow myself to collapse either!
For her sake too, I've got to let her have it!
Be stern, like a proper teacher!
As of now, the chance of us teachers retaining our dignity are zero.
Spaghetti, not pasta.
Today's love horoscope for Taurus is...
Sis, you're watching horoscopes again ?
Hey, shut up!
Watch out for romantic troubles.
Poor luck...
Today's horoscope for Taurus
predicts bad luck with your studies.
Don't doze off in the middle of your test, 'kay?
Poor luck again.
Here's today's 13 horoscopes!
Aries' luck with money is at its worst today!
No, no, this one's no good either.
...and that's why I'm late today.
Turn it off!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Hi Fu Hi Fu Mi Yo
Living for rock!
Taikutsu wa Rock Damashii Tazusaete
Living alone, blasting my music.
Hitori Kurashi no Bakuon Jinsei
With chubby, blowfish cheeks,
Tennen no Chouchin Fugu Hoppeta de
chaos follows me throughout the city.
Machi wo Chaos ni Kyou mo Makikomu
Being bipolar is a sign of intelligence,
Tsundere wa Intelligence no Akashi Nari
but my beloved has yet to confess to me.
Kyou mo kare ni wa naze ka kokurezu
We devote our beings to table tennis,
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
so we build our endurance by playing the drums.
Kitaeru Tame ni Drum Tatakou
Despite what we do, it's all for fun.
Konna Band Demo Yarase ja Nee
With these folks, it's hardly rock.
Konna Member Rock ja Nee
We aren't trying to start a folk dance here,
Mezashiteru no wa Ondo ja Nee
and we aren't trying to reach nirvana.
Tadoritsuku no wa Nehan ja Nee
We're the Maids, yeah!
Warera wa Maids Yeah!
We come on stage in our maid outfits.
Maid Sugata de Sanjou Sanjou
The Maids have taken over, yeah!
Kokora wa Maids Yeah!
We show up at the scene of every crime.
Jiken Genba wa Sanjou Sanjou
We are the invincible Maids, yeah!
Muteki no Maids Yeah!
If you're constipated, you'll be in pain giving birth.
Benpi wa Nanzan Kanchou Kanchou
We're pure, proper, and respectful!
Kiyoku Tadashiku Isagiyoku
Seaside's the best maid cafe around!
Shisaido wa zessan eigyouchuu
Thank you very maid for coming!
And the Town Still Turns
Next Episode
Hey Koh, don't you think Tattsun's kinda weird?
Yeah, she is a bit, that's for sure.
How should I put it, it's kind of weird.
It's weird since depending on the meaning, it's not actually weird.
It's just kind of weirdly weird
when you force it into a sentence.
That's just weird.
What's so weird about me?
You can't just tell me?
It's weird.
Cafe Seaside
Next time: The Amazingly Strange Toshiko Tatsuno.
The world still turns when it feels like it.