When her grandmother objects
to her going to America,
Mitsuki decides to leave home
without saying anything.
But when she finds out that her grandmother
used to go to a music school,
she is motivated to
try to persuade her again.
She ended up going
without getting permission,
but I think her feelings
got through to her grandmother.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
In any case, it's hard to believe
your grandmother gave you her permission.
On the other hand,
she didn't say anything to us.
Grandma...
Eichi went off to America
like this two years ago too.
Eichi, I'm coming now.
Wow!
Wow! I'm really here in America.
More importantly, how are we gonna
find her? With this many people...
Welcome to America!
Ms. Kazumi!
Welcome, Mitsuki!
I'm proud of you for coming all this way!
Anything to see Eichi!
That's right.
- No one can get in the way of my dream!
Oh, Ms. Kazumi,
let me introduce you.
This is Dr. Wakaoji
and Ms. Oshige.
I'm Wakaoji. Nice to meet you
I'm Oshige.
I'm Kazumi Franklin.
Very nice of you to come.
Thank you for having us.
It is an honor to meet you.
Of course,
there's no one to greet us.
That's the way it goes.
Oh, Takuto!
Don't, Nick!
Oh? So that baby is yours,
Ms. Kazumi?
That's right. This is my son Nick
and my husband Jim.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Franklin.
Nice to meet you, Mitsuki.
Huh?
Nevada...you said?
Yes, there's someone in a town
at the edge of Lake Roslyn there
who knows Mr. and Mrs. Sakurai.
It's about ten hours
by car from here.
What?! It's that far?!
It's that way.
Oh, okay.
I'm coming to see you, Eichi.
But Ms. Kazumi,
how did you find out?
I have a bit of
an information network.
What?!
Is that a shady and mysterious group?
Or perhaps a shady psychic?
I think it'll be all right if you see that person,
but do you want me to go with you?
Knowing that much is the same as
finding him. We'll be all right on our own.
I see.
Well, here's that person's address.
If you need anything, please contact me.
Yes.
So it's Eichi...
I wonder why I'm starting to
acknowledge Eichi's existence now.
I had no real sense of him
when we were in Japan.
Eichi, I've finally come
all the way here.
We're here!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Oh, I'm envious!
What's up with that?
Remember, she's said before, she likes
rooms with a view of the ocean.
But it's the same Pacific Ocean.
In that sense, I guess Japan
and America are connected.
Come to think of it,
Eichi once said that the Pacific Ocean
is exactly the same size as the moon.
Huh?
So the moon was once
in the Pacific Ocean?!
I don't know about that.
Maybe the lost Mu continent was the moon?
If so, that's incredible!
There's no chance of that!
Grandma...
Please listen to
my songs someday.
Mitsuki, you can only see
one face of the moon from Earth.
Even such a beautiful moon has marks
on the other side from meteors falling on it.
Continuing to shine
despite the scars.
When I first met you, Mitsuki,
I thought it was a perfect name for you.
Ms. Kazumi...
Mitsuki, do you remember
this photograph?
What?
I-I remember it.
Oh? Mitsuki doesn't look happy
at all in the photograph.
I know.
I don't know what happened
at the Christmas party,
but she sulked the whole time.
Did you have a fight
with Eichi or something?
Let me see,
I forget what happened.
Oh, you don't remember?
I remember.
On the night of
the Christmas party.
Your hands are warm, Eichi.
Mitsuki...
There'll come a day
when we'll be separated.
That won't happen!
We'll always be together.
Isn't that right?
I don't know. But if and when that happens,
I'm afraid you'll forget me and leave.
That's why I want you to always
let me be near you like this.
Mitsuki...I really like you.
Now everyone,
look at the camera.
- Okay!
Okay, everyone smile!
One, two...
It was after that...when I was told that
Eichi would be going to America.
Oh, Nick!
You shouldn't be so rough!
Please, I'm asking you.
Here, I'll lift you way high up.
Actually...
He was lost...and when I took
him to where he wanted to go,
he asked to take me out
to dinner to thank me.
But I didn't know that you were
fluent in English, Ms. Kazumi.
No, Jim was fluent in Japanese.
Oh...
But I was surprised.
As soon as our meal ended,
he asked me to go out with him.
I couldn't help but ask you.
It was love at first sight.
But of course I couldn't
give my answer right there.
Y-Yeah.
Mitsuki...I really like you.
Of course.
So I later replied with a video letter.
Oh, that was when...
I was happy when I
received the video letter.
I thought it was
the happiest day of my life.
I didn't even know I'd
soon be apart from Eichi.
I just kept running away...
simply because I was embarrassed.
So you've at least heard of them,
right, Mitsuki?
The musical actress Eleanor Pain
and the vocalist Steel of
the hard rock band THEM.
Yeah.
Apparently their throats were fixed
through Dr. Lon Herberd's surgeries.
Is that so?
Thanks for waiting, you two.
This is Dr. Lon Herberd.
Hello.
What do you think?
I think your measures to stop the progress
with medication were appropriate.
However, surgery will
be needed in due course.
But it may be difficult from a stamina
standpoint given this girl's age.
Her mentality is also
an important element.
The best choice would be for you,
a person she absolutely trusts,
to perform the surgery in your hospital where
there'd be no communication difficulties.
I understand.
If your hospital expresses a reluctance to
bring in the equipment, we could do it here.
Thank you very much.
- Tony, how does your throat feel?
- I'll do my best to convince them so
- It's all right, Mom.
- the operation can take place in Japan.
The doctor also told me to let
my throat gradually get used to it.
Really? I'm so glad. At one point,
I didn't know what would happen.
Not that again.
- That child was the same as you,
- You're such a worrier.
but he's recovered to that point.
I want you to get well like that too.
Herberd... Herberd...
Nothing.
W-Well, it is work.
What? You don't need
to tell me that. I know.
Oh... I see.
If that's the case, then...
Looks like they're done.
So, next we have to go make
an appearance at AAS Broadcasting.
I need to transform her.
I thought he was criticizing me,
but it was only my imagination.
Oh, this is throwing me off.
So now our work is done.
Yes.
Meroko!
What's the matter?
Oh, I guess there's
no use worrying.
Come on, let's go sightseeing!
Let's go!
Let's do that!
Yeah!
All right!
Wow!
Watch out!
It's your first time, right?
Yes.
I'll hold your hand.
Thank you.
- Hi!
Maybe it's the nice weather,
but she looks healthy too.
We Death Spirits really don't fit in
on the West Coast, huh, Meroko?
Meroko?
So it's only me that doesn't fit in.
There!
Go Mitsuki!
I did it!
Yay!
Maybe I shouldn't have
come to America.
She looks like
she's having fun.
That's understandable.
She is closer to Eichi.
So what is it that
I want to do?
She's a human and
I'm a Death Spirit.
Even if I could share my feelings,
what would happen?
I can't make her happy.
More importantly,
she likes Eichi.
There's no need for me.
I fully understand this,
but why can't I tear myself away?
That was fun!
It really was!
Welcome back!
- We're home!
Oh, New Year's pine decorations?
Tomorrow is New Year's.
So we do this as a Japanese custom.
That's right, let's all eat noodles
to ring in the New Year tonight!
Really?
Here, eat up!
- Thank you!
- This looks great!
I never thought I'd come
all the way to America
and be able to eat noodles
to welcome in the New Year.
Right? Eat as much as you'd like.
Thank you.
Even when I knew Eichi
was going to America,
I still couldn't say
anything to him.
So this is where you were.
You don't need to pick it up.
What?!
Mitsuki, sorry for making you worry.
Please forget about me.
You don't need to worry anymore.
Y-You're mistaken! I...
Wait, Eichi!
The pendant!
The same Eichi that said he was afraid
of being forgotten told me to forget him.
I made such a nice person say
something to push me away.
I realized that I liked Eichi as I cried,
thinking about how much he thought of me.
I found it!
After that, I was somehow
able to talk to Eichi,
but ultimately, the day to say goodbye came
before I was able to tell him I liked him.
I won't forget any of you.
Take care.
- Bye bye!
- Take care!
Take care, Eichi!
No! No!
Don't go, Eichi.
Don't cry, Mitsuki.
America isn't that far away.
But...
So let's make a promise that we'll
be closer to achieving our dreams
than we are now
when we next meet.
I wanna be an astronomer.
And you wanna be a singer.
He may have
understood my feelings,
but in the end, I wasn't able
to tell him that liked him.
W-What?
New Year's Eve bells even in America?
No, those are church bells.
But this time I'll say it.
That I really like you, Eichi.
She's so stupid! Being in America
has made her so careless!
What's wrong, Takuto?!
Mitsuki lost the pendant
she's always wearing!
You mean, the precious pendant
that Eichi gave her?
Jeez, I can't believe it.
I'm gonna go help her find it.
Takuto! Wait up!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Stolen Pendant."
- Look forward to it!