Full Moon has a show at
a university's school festival.
But there are some weirdos
among the students
that put her in some
dangerous situations!
Takuto thinks fast and
turns into his human form
to act as Mitsuki's bodyguard,
so nothing goes wrong, but...
Why are you always all about Mitsuki?!
You're mine, Takuto!
So, I wonder what's
going to happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Good job today!
- Good job!
Oh, here she comes!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Are all you done?
Let's hurry and go here!
I heard it's famous for
its super spicy ramen!
I would rather go to this Taiyaki place.
Sure, I can't eat unless
you go with me anyway.
Oh yeah! How about
going to both places!
How about it, Takuto?
Okay, okay.
Go to both places?
Say, I haven't seen Madoka lately.
Madoka? Who's that?
Oh no, did you forget her?
That one that competed with Full Moon
to release a CD... Madoka Wakamatsu.
Oh, right, right!
I wonder what she's up to?
We haven't heard anything about her.
Maybe she's retiring.
Maybe.
Retiring?
Huh? Madoka Wakamatsu?
Yes, I wonder what she's
been doing since then.
Is it bothering you?
Well...yes.
I understand how you feel, but it's not
something you should be worried about.
Even if something
like that happened.
I'm a bit shocked that Ms. Oshige
said such a cold thing.
Really? I think that's logical.
Even you're saying that?
Well, it won't do much to worry, right?
Well... That's true, but...
Yeah. Why are you even
worrying about her
after she did all sorts of
mean things to you?
Yeah, you're right.
But...
I can't stop worrying about
what happened to her.
Oh, over there!
Wow, it's so crowded!
They must really be good!
Don't they look like they
are from the industry?
I can't take this anymore!
Wait, Madoka!
Wait!
Madoka!
You have to go back, Madoka.
But I can't stand spicy things!
I can't eat that!
I don't know what
your previous manager was like,
but I won't let you be so selfish!
Whatever!
Ms. Sasaki would've never
made me do this kind of job!
She took better care
of me as a talent!
Madoka...
Well, at least she hasn't retired.
Looks like she has
a new manager as well.
She's reporting, huh?
No fair! She gets to eat
that super spicy ramen for free!
Ms. Imamura,
we are going to take a break now.
All right.
I'm very sorry.
What are you doing?
Did you come to eat ramen?
Huh? Oh...
Or, I don't suppose you're
Madoka Wakamatsu's fan?
No, you can't be, right?
That ex-idol on the downgrade.
D-Downgrade?
You can call it going downhill too.
Listen, Madoka.
Ms. Sasaki didn't care about you.
She was just spoiling you.
Understood? Now go back to work.
I can't take this anymore.
What?
I quit!
Madoka?!
I don't want to be doing
these kinds of worthless jobs.
Don't say such nonsense!
Bye.
Madoka!
Come back, Madoka.
No.
I don't want to do it anymore,
so I won't go back!
Where do you think you're going?
Goodbye!
Madoka, you are coming back here!
Do you hear me?
You are coming back!
What the heck?
Can't at least one person
come running after me?
What is it?!
What do you want from me?
U-Umm...
Hey, are you okay?
You shouldn't have
pushed yourself that much.
I-I'm all right.
Hey...
Are you all right?
Are you not feeling well?
Wow, the pizza is so red.
Didn't she say she
couldn't stand spicy food?
Here, eat, eat!
Yeah.
So huge.
Oh, any normal idol would eat that.
Really?!
Is that so?
Oh yeah, you didn't know?
How nice!
I didn't know that.
Why are you being so clueless?
You're an idol too, aren't you?
Oh, that's right.
- Did you say something?
- Oh, no!
You're a bit strange.
So, what were you talking about?
What?
You were talking with the staff, right?
At the ramen shop.
So, what were you talking about?
Well... Umm... That's...
I don't suppose you're
Madoka Wakamatsu's fan?
No, you can't be, right?
That ex-idol on the downgrade.
What?
You can call it
going downhill too.
I can't tell her such
a horrible thing.
No, nothing out of the ordinary.
I'll determine if it's out
of the ordinary or not.
So just tell me!
Umm...
We were just saying what
a wonderful person you are, Madoka.
Oh, really? Of course.
Some people can actually see that.
And you?
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh?"
Aren't you my fan?
Tell her no. Just tell her clearly.
Yeah, or else this woman
will get carried away again.
Don't hesitate to tell me the truth.
Yes...that's right.
Hey, don't be idiotic now.
Yeah, women like her only take things
the way they want to!
Yeah! I knew it!
You see?
So, you must be like,
"oh my god,"
after meeting your idol
Madoka Wakamatsu, right?
Miss, I'm so sorry!
Sorry.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's delicious!
That's an outfit I wore for
a role when I as a kid.
I'm glad it fits.
Thank you so much for this.
No, no problem.
But that was terrible.
Yes.
You're the one who drenched her!
Oh? A message?
Who could it be?
Madoka, it's your mother.
How are you?
You haven't called in so long,
I started worrying. How is work going?
We got a bunch of persimmons,
so I'll send some to you.
I'll send some to
your new manager as well.
Please call me sometime.
Hello. Delivery!
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
Wow, so many persimmons!
Wanna try them?
Sure.
Thank you!
These persimmons your mother
sent are so delicious.
Really?
Madoka...
Hmm?
What are you going to do now?
Dashing out in the middle of work...
It's just that,
I want to become an idol.
I wanna wear pretty dresses
and have the spotlight on me.
And have many fans,
and people who copy me.
And I wanna always have
the attention of the media.
After running away from the workplace,
what the heck is she talking about?
She thinks being a singer is easy.
Recently, I've been thinking maybe
it's better to be an actress than a singer.
What do you think?
Wouldn't I make a great actress?
She thinks being
an actress is easy too!
How audacious of her!
So singing...
So you aren't going to sing anymore?
I'm done singing.
Oh, Gu!
You know Gu?
Oh, no, I've only seen you
holding him in a magazine.
Huh? What?
Does he see us?
That can't be.
You really are my fan, aren't you?
No!
- I'm impressed. Make yourself at home.
- Hey! Meroko!
Y-Yes.
Gu!
Can you be quiet please?
I'm saved.
What a shrewd pig.
These videos are so valuable now!
Madoka... You're so beautiful.
Oh? R-Really?
It's a little embarrassing
when people remind me.
What are you doing?!
Madoka?
Yeah! This is the song that I competed
against Full Moon with and lost.
Doesn't it amuse you to hear it?
But...
Sorry for raising my voice.
Oh, yeah, you must be thirsty, right?
I'll go buy something.
Madoka!
Takuto!
Sorry, I have to go after Madoka.
Wait!
Meroko is going after her.
Read this before you go.
What's this?
"September 18th.
A new song. Such a wonderful song."
"I'm so lucky to be able to
sing this as my debut song."
Takuto, is this...
"I want to study a lot of things to
get a better image for this song."
Mr. Takasu disapproved of
my performance today.
But Mr. Takasu is
my most reliable producer.
He scolds me because he cares about me.
I have to meet his expectations.
November 30th.
I can't hit the high notes well.
I should've done my vocal
exercises more thoroughly.
I'm regretting that.
Madoka, you cared about
"Eternal Snow" so much.
I'm so frustrated.
So frustrated! So frustrated.
What do I do?
Just what can I do?
Now, everything is over.
What?
Is it funny...that I'm crying?
Why don't you sing "Eternal Snow"?
I want to sing it too!
But I can't anymore!
After all, I've lost.
I lost to myself!
I didn't lose to Full Moon.
That's right.
You can't believe in me,
can you?
Well...
I believed in you.
I believed in your power.
Madoka... Please sing.
You said a moment ago that
you wanted to sing, right?
I want to hear your song too!
My song?
I think...
that everyone
has a unique song.
2There's a song for Full Moon.
But I think that there's also
a song that only you can sing.
I want to hear your song.
You better think again
why you want to sing.
That's all I can say.
That's what he meant.
I have a feeling that once I hear your song,
I'll like you even more!
What a statement.
But who on earth are you?
I'm one of your fans.
I see.
But there might be no place
to go back to anymore.
That's not true!
There must be lots of people
waiting for you!
You think so?
Yes!
Everybody is waiting for you!
I'm sure they're waiting! I'm sure.
It's so late,
I'm sure no one is still waiting.
Ms. Imamura?
Ms. Imamura!
Madoka?
You came back.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I'm so glad you came back.
Ms. Imamura...
Yes?
I want to sing!
I was waiting for you to say that.
You had been running away.
You were scared of singing.
But it won't do you any good to run away.
That's why I was strict with you,
believing that one day,
you would tell me
that you wanted to sing.
I had no idea. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Now, let's go to Mr. Takasu's,
shall we?
Mr. Takasu must be
waiting for you too.
Yes!
And today's show's director is...
Oh, Madoka!
Madoka! Good morning!
I've been wanting to
tell you this for a while.
Yes?
All this time, I thought of you as
an inept idol with just a pretty face.
Huh?
But maybe you are pretty
talented as a singer.
That's what I started
to think recently!
But I will not lose to you,
no matter what!
What was that?
Well, I guess that's
her way of greeting you.
Greeting me?
It means she acknowledges you!
She's so insincere.
Though, who am I to say this?
Madoka...
Oh no, Takuto! Looks like Mitsuki's illness
has suddenly gotten worse!
What?! Have you
contacted that doctor?!
Well... Just when we need Dr. Wakaoji,
we can't get a hold of him!
Jeez! Where is he
at such a critical time?!
If we don't do something,
they will force her to get the operation!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Illness Advances."
- Look forward to it!