It's officially begun. The 57th Recon Mission!
Scouts, move out!
After setting forth to establish a route to Shiganshina,
the Scout Regiment encountered a Female Titan
seemingly possessed of sharp, cold-hearted intelligence.
We're not dealing with an Abnormal,
this thing's showing intelligence!
It's a human being wrapped in a Titan body!
As soldier upon soldier fell to this new foe, the
regiment retreated into a forest of massive trees.
Though to what purpose, no one appeared to know.
If the Levi Squad can't stop this thing, then who can?
Those men need us!
The choice is yours.
You can trust yourself,
or you can trust the people willing
to put their lives on the line for you.
I'm with you!
Fire!
Oh, that's right.
While we're on that subject, let me ask.
You're okay with me cuttin' your
limbs off at the joints, right?
I'm mean, they'll grow back?
I'm talking about your actual body.
Don't want you dead just yet.
Timing wouldn't work.
Think about it. The enemy was prepared
to make sacrifices. Enormous ones.
So committed to maintaining her secret, she would
rather let herself be cannibalized than exposed.
All hands, withdraw!
Redeploy the formation!
Return to Calaneth District!
Erwin. Why bother having him replenish?
There's no time.
We saw the Female Titan get eaten.
Did we actually see the person
inside suffer the same fate? I didn't.
You mean?
Yes. Your hypothesis is correct. This isn't over.
We're dealing with someone like Eren.
Someone who regenerates in and out of Titan form.
Suppose that person equipped
themselves with ODM gear in advance.
Suppose further that they're also
disguised in one of our uniforms?
What would their next move be?
Captain Levi?
Wait, that... That's not... Oh shit!
Gunther!
How do you ferret out the enemy...
when they're one of your own?
When the Colossal Titan breached the
wall and disappeared, theoretically,
whoever was inside had with ODM gear.
They would have used it in
escape before the steam cleared.
It's possible the same thing happened here.
I don't see how, sir.
Based on Eren's condition when he emerged from Titan form,
I think it's safe to assume that
something like that is highly unlikely.
His equipment was broken.
Parts of his uniform were missing.
More importantly, Eren was so spent he couldn't
even stand on his own two feet without assistance.
The Female Titan's ability to summon reinforcements
was unlike anything we've encountered before.
Our failure to anticipate that
factor cost us the operation.
Evidently, there are different
levels of mastery to the Titan ability.
We were naive to think that a mere
novice like Eren would set the standard.
If we're to stop this enemy, it's clear now
that we'll need to broaden our way of thinking.
So if we're goin' home, that means
the operation's a success, right?
Hopefully so.
If that is the case, then that might mean they've
already discovered the Female Titan's identity.
I wouldn't mind knowin' that myself.
Still, I'm impressed with the commander.
How'd he know she'd come after us
once we took Eren beyond the Wall?
Think about it. During the Trost invasion,
did it strike you as odd the way the Titans
suddenly halted their advance midway through?
Huh?
They must have intended some purpose
when they destroyed the front gate,
but they never made a move on the inner gate.
Nor did they interfere with
Eren when he sealed the breach.
Perhaps, something happened which made
them re-evaluate their plan entirely.
And what would that be?
Something drew their focus
away from the Wall's destruction.
Something that forced them to call off the attack.
You mean Eren's transformation?
That's the most logical conclusion.
Wait, but then that would mean...
It means they were there.
Whoever called off the attack saw Eren transform.
It means the enemy is one of us!
Gunther!
Go kid! C'mon!
Keep moving!
We... We're just leaving him?
Who is that?
Keep 'em away from Eren!
Damn it! Hey, Eld. What're we doin', huh?
There isn't time to get the horses.
Make for HQ at full speed!
Is that the Female Titan? Or did she have an accomplice?
Damn! Whoever it is, they're gonna
pay! Even if it's the last thing I do!
The Female Titan? No. That can't be right!
I thought we caught her!
We have to consider that if the enemy
was still able-bodied when they escaped,
then it's entirely possible they
can make the Titan reappear as well.
I hate being right!
No time to lose! Move it!
She's coming for us!
Damn you!
Not again! I'll kill you! I swear I will!
No! Don't!
We've got this! The three of us can handle her!
You get back to base! Go! Now!
This enemy forces us to rethink everything we've learned.
What seems the most logical strategy
might prove to be the worst course of action.
Mark my words. The time will come
when risking everything is the only choice left to us.
I can fight her, too!
Just go! This is our best course of
action! We can not afford to put you at risk!
Have you learned nothing? After
all this, you still doubt our skills?
Is that true, Eren?
I thought you had faith in us. That you trusted us!
And unless we can take that risk, humanity can never win.
I have faith in the Levi Squad!
Good luck!
We've blinded her! That should give us at
least a minute before she can regenerate!
We'll finish her well before then!
To hell with capturing you!
We're gonna kill you!
We're gonna carve you up!
We'll make you pay, bitch!
Covering your neck isn't gonna save you!
We'll just keep slicing those
shoulders 'til your arms are worthless.
Trust me, we know what we're doing. No mercy!
We'll cut you to ribbons!
Lop off your arms!
Send you to hell!
They're down!
Now go for the neck!
Take out the muscles supporting her head!
Let's chop our way to the nape!
They... They've got her totally overwhelmed!
They're so good. They pulled off a
coordinated attack without even saying a word!
It must be the trust they have in each other as teammates.
That's how they've survived this long.
It's how they're able to stay
strong even after losing Gunther.
Gotta keep going!
I have to have faith that the right
choice is to keep moving without looking back!
I've got to trust in them. I understand that, now!
Truth is, I don't know which is better.
I never have. Should I go out on my own?
Or should I put myself in the hands of my comrades?
Either way, there's no guarantee.
Say goodbye to your nape...!
Eld!
How? She can see again? That's impossible!
It hasn't even been thirty seconds.
Only one eye? She channeled her energy into one
eye to grow it back quicker? How can she do that?
Petra! Pull yourself together!
Petra!
Now...
die!
What the hell? My blades weren't able to...
I'm gonna...
kill you!
That's Eren!
Hang on a second! Mikasa!
That roaring. This isn't good.
I made the wrong decision when you came after us.
I made the choice to trust my teammates.
And it got them all killed!
I should never have left it to them.
I should have fought her from the very start!
I-It's all my fault.
I should have killed her!
I should've...
I should've changed into a Titan then.
No. Even earlier than that.
I should've fought back!
And with Captain Levi there.
We would've beaten her.
We could've captured this monster!
I wouldn't blame you.
Do as your conscience dictates.
It was... It was my choice.
And because of that choice,
my squad-mates are dead.
All of them, gone. And I'm to blame.
No. More than anything, this is your fault!
I'm going to rip you to shreds.
Once my hands heal.
I'll tear you apart. Piece by piece.
Then I'll devour you!
A...
Eren, no!
N-No. Wait, I...
Eren.
Please, you can't leave me.
Give him back.
Do you hear me? Give him back!
Give him back!
My blades didn't even break the skin.
He's still alive. He's still alive.
And I'm coming for him.
Just hang on, Eren!
I know you're in there.
And after I kill her, I'll carve out her insides,
and pull you out again. I swear I will.
Just hang on a little longer.
Don't give up, Eren.
Never give up!
Get back here!
What?
We'll stay back for now.
Maintain current distance.
She's slowed down a bit.
That fight wore her out, too.
It looked like she may have bitten the entire nape off.
It's unlikely Eren survived.
"He's still alive. Give him back."
After watching helplessly as Eren was taken away,
Mikasa fights alongside Levi, humanity's greatest soldier,
in a battle against the Female Titan.