WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the seiyuu for 佐倉杏子 (Sakura Kyouko):
野中藍 (Nonaka Ai) - affectionately called あいぽん (Aipon).
Okay! Well then, Mahou Shoujo☆Madoka Magika, um, episode 5 There's No Way I'd Have Anything Like a Regret,
commentary shall begin now! Um, sending us off with the role of Madoka, it's Yuuki Aoi and—
Yes!
Yes.
With the role of Akemi Homura, Saitou Chiwa, and—
With the role of Sakura Kyouko, it's Nonaka Ai!
Yaaay! *clapclapclap*
Ahh, hurray!
I look forward to working with you!
yay yay ya~y
Man, Ao-chan. Somehow your tension is really high.
Kyoukoooo～♥
I'm weak against her, I love Kyouko too much.
Ahhh, is that so?
Did you always like her?
I want to marry Kyouko.
(lol)
You want to marry Kyouko?
I want to marry Kyouko.
Kyouko-tan would be difficult to marry, she'd always just be eating.
That's right!
Right, right, right.
I will conform to that!
Ne?
Even though she eats that much, she's not fat.
I see that in high status!
Ohh~
That kind of stomach.
That stomach has room.
Sayaka-tan's "There's no way I'd have anything like a regret!" is like that!
Ahhh.
I'd say.
And that is how you start to become a mahou shoujo.
Right? Yeah, that's right. Right.
It's rather desecrating, though...
And then Black Kyubey. That's what I'd call his face.
Well, since Aipon has finally come for the first time, I would like to ask a little bit!
Mm!
Yes!
That's right, ne.
First of all, a discussion about auditions.
Ah, that's right.
Chat about auditions?
Yup, yup.
When I took these auditions, I was given a script for all of the characters, then...
I was told "Please pick two roles that you'd like to take."
So it was the same for everyone?
Right.
That's right!
For me, Madoka was already decided, then I could do ones that I pleased.
Eh? Ehhhhhhh?
Ohhh.
For me, I was doing things completely different from Homura.
Eh?
Other than Homura, there was Beh-san.
(lol) Beh-san.
Ah, Beh-san?
Beh-san was decided on.
Oh!
Is that right?
That Beh-san over there.
(lol)
Hoeeeeeeeeeh~?
Then, Urobuchi-san was like "Please try a bit of Homura,"
mm
And from there it was decided I would venture into Homura, but...
Mm, right?
(lol)
Ah, that's right, the fact that they let you pick 2 characters you'd like is amazing!
Then, I really thought this anime would be just like its opening,
Ohhh, that was thought!
since I completely thought that, it was like...
"For this heroine, it'd definitely be cute if a newcomer got her instead of me."
I thought I would take a different role.
So my choices were Kyouko-san and Mami-san.
Ehhh? So Kyouko was your own choice?
That's right.
So that's right～!
Speaking of Kyouko, we recently did episode 4's commentary, right?
Ah, that's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
During that time, everyone was like "I wonder who Kyouko is~!" throughout all of episodes 1, 2, and 3. We didn't know.
Ne~?
Then when I heard Aipon, it was like "Wow, amazing, she's so fun!"
Ne?
Huh? From episode 4?
In episode 4, she's at the very end.
Yup, from episode 4.
I see.
In Episode 3, Mami-sama is still...
That's right, Mami-sama is.
Ah, there's Hitomi!
There's Hitomi!!!
I'd say she's the most wicked girl!
Mmm, you know?
Wicked girl. Really.
Hitomi, ne~
From a girl's standpoint, you know.
Mmm—Mmm.
From a guy's standpoint, she's really cute, I think.
Yeah, from a guy's standpoint, surely.
Ojou-sama - high-class proper young lady.
She's like an ojou-sama or something.
Right, right, right, she's very ojou-sama, you know.
Right.
Mmm...
Somehow, at the very beginning, there was a conversation like "Hitomi is an awful woman!"
Then, "But I wasn't expecting that!"
Then, "But I   wasn't expecting! that!"
Then when everyone heard the final outcome, "Mm. Yup. Most scary."
Mm.
I'd say. (lol)
This girl is scary, scary!
Scary, huh? She's really a witch.
Right, that young lady, is, you know!
In one meaning, she's the biggest witch!
A witch!
Witch... scary, scary, scary.
Even though she never became a mahou shoujo, she's still a witch. Amazing.
Ne?
So there are people like that in the world too.
That's right.
Then I wonder if the people with hopes will become happy?
Wahh~ they're a victim!
That's right, those fall through...
Everything will probably go downhill, huh?
It has a sort of "mistake" feeling.
Yeah, it has that feeling.
That's right, "Reality is cruel to nice people."
The winners are those kinds of girls, huh?
She's the starter? (lol)
Ah... well that's about Hitomi-san.
So, the one you got was... Kyouko.
Right, I was surprised, myself!
But she's nice, isn't she? Kyouko. I love her too!
Nice! Super nice!
Yup. She was a shock, Kyouko~
Somehow, it's like another new approach, isn't it?
ヤンキー(yankee) - Delinquent youth.
Different from the normal English definitions.
Ne? When I read the script, she seemed a little bit yankee-ish.
A middle/high school student... with a kind of yankee senpai feel.
She puts on an air that's a bit like that, right? It's cute.
Ne!
Right, right, right.
昭和(Shouwa) refers to the Shouwa era (1926–1989)
This is referring to her speech style.
Somehow, her lines are like "bad" influenced... fairly Shouwa-ish.
Right, right... somehow, she's a bit teyandee style.
てやんでえ(teyandee) - This is a short hand of
何を言ってやんでぇ(Nani wo Itteyandee, 'what are you saying', in an Edo style)
Typical traits of and Edo style are straightforwardness, cheerfulness, and assertiveness.
Right, right... somehow, she's a bit teyandee style.
Right, right... somehow, she's a bit teyandee style (lol)
江戸っ子(Edokko) - This refers to a child in the 江戸(edo) style.
Very edokko.
Right, right, right.
I think it's somehow extremely nice, though.
Me too.
Did you have any directions when you began acting?
"Don't come off as scary"
You wouldn't be! Aipon, really...
When it started, if it was like a bad person came on,
umm, I guess that wasn't good with the sound director, so they thought "Nonaka would be fine, right?"
Ah, that's right.
I was told something like that afterwards.
That's right, it was said, it was said.
I kind of "pulled back" my voice, or sort of... made it "loose."
I thought "This is fine, I think."
Mmm, I see.
Certainly, because of Nonaka-san's voice, and Nonaka-san's acting, I'd say it felt like Kyouko wasn't really a super bad person.
Yes.
That style, I somehow REALLY love it.
I completely love that.
Right?
She's a straightforward girl, isn't she~?
Right!
In order to bring forth the righteousness inside of her, she fought her absolute hardest, and then that happened...
It's really heartrending, and I super love it♥
(lol)
Super love it, ahh...
Since Aipon comes, it's like really, Aipon... talks so much that I feel bad for her!
(lol)
That's right.
(lol) Really...(lol)
and it's true here too, you're constantly like "Heeh heeh hoo!"
(lol) even if you say that...
It's got an image that seems straining.
SUPER straining (lol)
(lol)
She has a few episodes!
Starting from episode 5, you know.
Ne?
You know she really talks a lot, since she has that long monologue...
Presenting that kind of thing is actually really difficult, isn't it?
Of course, it was very well acted, so it was great, but as far as mental strain...
"I'm glad I got a character that doesn't talk too much!"
(lol)
Somehow, Kyouko is... extremely nice, ne? Mmm.
You know, around this point, Madoka still hadn't really developed any connections with Kyouko, right?
During that big story, when she talked for a long time, I became like a regular Kyouko fan.
♥ Kyouko-tan (*´Д`)HaaHaa
There's finally some light shed on your past!
(lol)
Finally...
"I see, so that's why you eat!"
Really, right?
Right, right, right.
Ne~
Ne? There's never any establishment of the time setting...
Well, it gives off a feeling like it's in the very near future.
The very near future.
But somehow, the story explaining Kyouko's past doesn't feel like it was from this age.
It seemed a bit like a disparate society, though...
Ne?
I'd say "So there's a bit like that, too."
It seems like capitalism has moved forward a bit.
Ne...?
Ahhh...
Ah, it's come, it's come.
Kyouko is cute, Kyouko.
wahhhh~
It's got a sort of... atmosphere that feels like things have degenerated, doesn't it?
This kind of "sense of space"... everything is so wide!
I see.
You could say it's mysterious, or it's like... a very mysteriously wonderful sense of space...
Ah, it's decadent.
(lol)
A–A bit.
Isn't that a bit dangerous, can he really properly hold that?
"Well, regarding that, whatever"
(lol)
But in this way, this time, Sayaka... to have a bit of discussion about Sayaka thus far,
"In order to save someone else, my own self..."
Well, I don't want to say it, it actually happens just after this...
Somehow, right... a lot unwraps, but...
It's a wish for another person's sake, you know?
mmm...
Hmm...
Then, um... Actually, Kyouko has a wish like that as well. But, if it was you, Aipon...
What kind of wish do you think you'd get?
Heeee~?
Well right now, we know the true QB, so I think everyone would say "No wish."
"I'll take no wish."
But thinking about it at around this time, if you were told you could have a single wish...
Ehhhhhhhhhhh!?
This is amazing.
You know, lately it's something I've thought about while taking a bath...
What is it, really in the end I guess I should use it for my own sake!
If you had a wish in the same class as world peace...
"There's indecision, huh...", right?
But really if you have a wish for yourself...
Down the line...
"There's no way... that I'd have something like a regret."
She said it, she said it!
Ahh~!
She said it! It hurts coming from Kyouko!
What a piercing painful feeling!
It's piercing pain!
Looking at Sayaka-chan now, she doesn't seem sad... she seems very happy...
Then looking back after...
"I think I might not make a wish for another person's sake."
Mmmm↑
It somehow really makes you think, doesn't it? This piece of work.
Mm.
ahhh
It's come, it's come.
Ah, there it is.
She's eating again.
Right here... there have been retouches, huh?
IT'S TRUE!
This is the first entry, huh?
Right, this is her first entrance?
It's not, right?
Ah... it's time...
Huh?
C'mon, when she says "It's fine if I beat her" is her first entry.
Ah!
That's right.
rightrightrightrightrightright
That's right! With QB.
At the very end.
Ah, I see.
At the very end of 4, QB is like "What are you gonna do?" and she's like "I can beat her up," or something.
Huh? Compared to this, that's...
That's her first—
Wait, I'm wrong, I'm wrong. (lol)
First entrance is in 4. Right, right, right.
I see I see
There's a mysterious sense of space here too, huh?
Ne?
Just what is this place?
There's no one around... but there's a viewing platform.
Mm.
It's nice you know, somehow... you always want to eat whatever the food that Kyouko is eating, don't you?
We talk about this during after recording too, though.
(lol)
Right, right.
But looking at it, it all looks delicious.
It made me really want to eat pocky and stuff.
Ah!
What?
Ahh...
It's fine, right? Since it's delicious.
If it's delicious, you know? If it's delicious then I want to eat it. Ne?
Mm.
Right, right.
Right.
Around this part, conversations between these two are a little bit rare, aren't they?
Ah, that's right, ne.
Right, right, right.
Mmm.
And in this "sense of space" the two are talking.
This space is like a family restaurant.
Madoka properly ordered, and has that kind of sweet-looking drink, but Homura is plain, huh?
"Coffee" it seems.
Yeah, it's like she just requested that kind of thing.
This kind of settei is interesting, ne?
Interesting...
Ah, it's coffee?
Right, right, right.
Something like that.
Like tea.
And then it feels like she probably doesn't drink any of it all.
And then it feels like she probably  sdoesn't drink~ any of it all.
(lol)
Mm.
Ah—
Ah, it's opened, what's inside?
She finally opened it.
What is it? What is it?
(lol) That place shrouded in mystery.
(lol)
She got a bit mad just now, right? "Quit talking like that!"
Right, M–Madoka's outbreak... Every now and then, that will happen.
(lol)
We've talked about this before, but you know...
Madoka's "ready to run away" part, is very much grounded in reality.
Reality.
That's right.
I think that's right, yes.
When you look into the depths of this story, every girl has really dishonest parts to them, don't they?
Mmm!
Mm.
She's basically a good girl, but also has that feeling like "You can fight!"
Ah, that's right, ne.
Right.
That's right.
But then she doesn't fight, right? I think.
Somehow she's the one who gives them the most sympathy, but then she's the one I'd want the least as a girlfriend. (lol)
In the end I do think that my own character is the cutest,
but, what is it...
"Marrying Kyouko would be nice, huh?"
(lol)
That's right, Kyouko seems the most down to earth. The best to single out, I think.
Husband would be fine. (lol)
Husband would be fine?
Husband would be fine.
You really love her, huh? Always saying it.
Suuuuuuper love.
Really~ Thank you~
Truly...
She has the finest balance, huh? Kyouko, that is.
Ne?
Compared to how they moved forward on their own before, when Kyouko comes,
it really brings out and moves forward a kind of passionate feeling in all the characters.
I think that's really nice, really cool.
Mmm, extremely, you know. Somehow ne, um...
Actually, before recording this, we already did episode 6's commentary...
Ohh, this commentary?
Commentary, you know.
Yeah!
Mm, mm.
Then, in Episode 6, the series director Miyamoto-san is our guest. Miyamoto-san said this there, but,
Miyamoto-san is.
Oh! Yes.
since Kyouko is a very "high-temperature (feverish)" character...
Mmm~
That's why somehow, her conversations have a lot of movement...
And then somehow, gradually everyone, you know... gradually everyone's temperature changes.
Right.
Everyone who was a bright character gradually cries more and more.
Gradually things fall.
Right.
(lol) Right, ne.
So in one meaning, since Kyouko comes, everything blooms.
Ne?
But Kyouko overcame that and is able to properly support herself, that's sort of...
Ah~
Strong, isn't she? In the sense of growing up.
Right, strong!
A bit like an adult.
Ahh, right.
Almost a bit nee-chan ish.
Mm, it has that feeling.
Ne?
The feeling of an onee-san you can rely on.
She's relieving, and yet... uwaah~
Ah, it's come, it's come, again.
Here it comes—
QB is... Mouuu~
Ah, cute QB!
There it is!!!
QB (lol)... Somehow, it's like QB has ears coming out of his ears.
Right, right, right, ears are in his ears. (lol)
He has ear hair.
Ear hair (lol)
Right, those ear hairs are what do the work to make a Soul Gem.
That's there, isn't it...
Ieaaaaaaaaaaaa~
(lol)
Fuwa, ahh~
QB sitting around acting cute is a bit like "Mmm", isn't it?
(lol)
Somehow, one-by-one he just grabs onto them, and you think "Fuu..."
Ne?
That's sort of like a familiar.
Right, Sayaka-tan tries her hardest, too. Ah!
Right, from your viewpoint, Aipon, Kyouko is probably your favorite, but are there any other characters you like?
Ehhh, a character I like?
Really, Mami-san.
I like that, what is it, "Senpai Mahou Shoujo" kind of girl.
Mami-saaaan~
Mmmmm.
She gives off an air like "She really is cool!"
I get that!
That's right.
Mami's fighting style is too cool!
Super cool!
Mmmm.
Kyouko's is cool too.
Ahh, it's long.
It can extend and retract. In various ways, it feels a bit like a nunchaku.
It's dangerous, though!
Right.
(lol)
It has that kind of feeling. That fighting style is nice, ne?
It's cool, ne? Makes for good action scenes, ne.
I think that it is cool.
Mami-san's fighting style feels extremely mahou shoujo, but Kyouko feels more, what is it—
Warrior-like!
Right, warrior-like! You could say it's a fighting style that requires proper practice!
Ah, cool.
That's why she can take in so many calories!
Ah, ah!
Moves around so much! (lol)
That's right, and she dances and stuff. Like in the next episode.
Right, right, right.
That's what she does next. Yeah.
Ah, right.
She might do a lot more!
That's why she's not fat!
Right!
Enviable, isn't it?
How nice.
Then there's the magic.
Magic, is it?
(lol)
In reality—
She's one to use magic, right.
I see. (!?)
I see.
Mm.
That's right. She does various things.
This might be the first time I'm a little jealous of a mahou shoujo.
No, don't do it, don't do it!
(lol) don't do it, don't do it!
This is no good!
Don't make a contract!
(lol)
You know, in this piece of work... Ao-chan keeps getting tempted, like right here, there's enough of it.
Ah, like this.
It kind of moves forward a little bit, getting heavier and heavier, right?
Eh, that's right.
Yes~
So Aipon, were there any things you were cautious of other than your general acting style?
I...
Um...
have no idea how much Kyouko knows before this point, right?
Her development, and the various things with QB... For Kyouko, it's completely...
Compared to Madoka and Sayaka, she's probably bit more of a senpai, like, closer to the extent of Mami-san...
If you think about "How much does she know?", it's unexpected.
Then there's her time at peace...
Did you hear anything about that?
I completely didn't know.
Ahhh.
Ahhhhh
It was like realizing after looking at the script.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is Ao-chan.
I did that.
"VRRRRRM VRRRRM"
Eh? Is that so?
(lol)
Actually, I did.
Ah, the transformation scene!
Ahh!
ｷﾀ━━(＾∀＾)━━ ・・・
It's kind of sexy, ne?
It's sort of uplifting, ne?
Mmm.
Ne?
Cool.
This sword is so—this sword!
So cool.
The two of them have a very slightly similar fighting style, don't they? Sayaka and Kyouko.
Mahou shoujo—
Ne!
You could say they're both kind of like a "magical warrior"-type.
Ne?
Sayaka uses a sword though, yeah...
I see. I suppose it's because they're close-quarters-combat style?
Ah, they can do long distance though. Right.
Reall—
ｷﾀ━━━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━━━ !!!!!
There she is!!
Help—
UWaaaah!
There she is~
It extends!
extends
Right, at first she has this kind of feeling.
She has a fairly goal-oriented style of thinking around here, doesn't she?
Ne?
Mm. Then somehow you think, "She might shift into a good person...?" It has that sort of feeling around here.
That's right.
She has the air of a "stray cat." That's another major kyun! point.
Like a loner.
Right, right, right.
Ahhhh.
A feeling of strength...
Right, right.
That's really cool.
And then for me, actually, I like her clothing.
Ne~!?
Ohhh~
It's cute.
Super cute!
Mm.
Somehow at the bunkasai (culture festival) there was a conversation like "What if everyone cosplayed as a mahou shoujo?"
There was?
Wear a dress, a dress!
For me it was QB.
QB!?
QB???
In that case you should have just not gone to school!
Right, it'll become "real Madoka."
Madoka totally wouldn't do that.
What about the opening?
We put Mami-san in the opening~
( ｀・ω・´ )どや～
どや(doya) - "How's that?"
2ch slang. This AA is called a "doya face": ( ｀・ω・´ )
Yuuki Aoi hosts a radio show with seiyuu/friend 早見沙織(Hayami Saori) by the name of
あおい・さおりの新番組(｀・ω・´) - Aoi・Saori's new program, Doya?
(lol)
As for QB, you can be him by wearing white tights on your entire body.
Ehhh really?
You just need white stuff for QB.
As for size, you fit perfectly!
That's right.
(lol)
Small, huh?
Someone went like that.
(lol) I don't get it.
Ah, it came.
Super cool~
Kyoukoooooo~♥
Uwaah~
The retouches are nice, huh?
Ne?
Mm.
Uwaaah~
Right, amazingly nice.
She bit it!
Right, right.
It's taiyaki~!
This time she's eating almost the entire time.
Almost all~
Mou, that's right, ne.
It's like "To what extent will you eat?"
(lol)
Right, that's right~
"Is she eating in this cut!?"
Just now it was in her mouth, but then it disappeared!
Did she finish eating it? (lol)
Right, right, right.
Amazing, right, each time she has something different to eat.
Ne?
Right, right.
That's a part that differs, you know?
The, what is it... moisture between each type of food differs, so...
For when talking while eating...
When you're constantly shoving various things in your mouth, that makes it difficult, so...
It's qu—
THAT HAND!
Eh?
That QB is...
Uwahh~ scary!
(lol)
No, no, no!
Don't want.
(lol)
That's right, they're talking about Mami after all this.
Ahh~ uwaaa~ kaa~
I really love that!
Mm, so cool!
You know, Sayaka-chan's "SHUN!" part...
Mm.
The magic circle she makes is cool.
Presently... uwahh~!
Uwahh~
This fight is amazingly cool.
This fight is amazingly cool!
Fighting and such, scary!
She says "Annoying" and "You're a fool."
Ne? Since I haven't really heard Aipon say that kind of thing before...
Ne~!?
Is that another fresh style?
Ahh, it feels really fresh.
This is nice, huh?
Ah, there it is~
Cool...
After that, nothing left but killing ya, y'know!
It cameeee
so wicked~
Ahhh, so cute~ Kyouko-chan...
Super cool.
And then...!
I won't lose...
Mou.
Mmm.
Somehow this here is kind of shounen-style feeling.
Ne!
Ahhhh~
That feeling!
Fuwa!
You know the action really properly portrays both of them well, too...
It's super cool, but it's also like "Eh? These are mahou shoujo?"
(lol)
That's right.
Right, right, in this fight.
There are no kira-kira attacks anywhere.
Right, right.
None~
Even though they're magic users, you know (lol)
That's right, isn't it?
That's what you think when watching this scene, you know~
They don't overly implement their magical tools.
Really, everyone has a very different concept of "magic" here, it's fun to watch.
Ne?
Usually magic is full to the brim with an image of "BAAANG!"
There's simple magic too, though.
Ah, it came!
It came, so cute~
It   came~ so cute~
Cute evil beast.
Cuuute~
Right.
Cool, huh?
Uwaaaah.
It really is true for us too... All of it, entirely, when watching in after recording is like "Whoa!"
Ahh
That's right!
And watching it again is COMPLETELY different.
And watching it again is COMPLETELY different!
Mmm.
It's coming, it's coming.
yup
She can do this too~
Right.
Mm.
She came!
The number one most popular character, really by a bit.
Uwaaah!
Right.
She only enters for a little bit, but she's the number one!
(lol)
Another cool and nice part about Kyouko...
When Homura-chan makes her entry here, Kyouko's surprised face is another amazing "Kyun!" point.
Mou, anyways, you like her.
I like her too much!
I can't bear it.♥
Over.
Yaa~
Finally!
Ohhh~
Right!
We pretty much completely just watched it, but that's true for us in the past too, with this commentary.
This part, huh?
That's right, isn't it?
I wanna watch it, you know~
I was a bit too fully loaded, Kyouko is so cute~
Ne? That's right.
Well then, this is the ending.
That's right, ne?
For you, Aipon, regarding Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika, what sort of piece of work do you think it is?
Yes.
Mmm.
Well, everything was betrayed.
I thought it'd be cute, you know. During auditions.
(lol)
Mmm!
And then, Kyouko is an unusual character.
I said "Oh, I was really selected? Thank you very much!"
Ohh.
That was the feeling, huh?
It was wonderful to do this, huh?
Ne~?
Well, here it's only episode 5, but we've already done episode 6, so we're perfectly halfway done.
That's right!
Ahhhh~
Mm.
Starting from here, well... this is the halfway point, so this is the peak at the moment, right, everyone?
Is that wrong?
From here we're going to start heading towards the peak.
Right.
It'll keep going up, right?
That's right.
There'll be hopes, and then more hopes, and then some hopes will be answered, and a really tall hurdle...
Then down with a ↓pyuun↓
With the pyuun, everyone's thoughts will be BEATEN.
Beaten up!
I really hope that everyone continues to listen from here!
That's right, um...
Yes~
Yes!
We're done,
Yuuki Aoi, and—Yup, then Saitou Chiwa, and—It's Nonaka Ai!
Okay, then, next time:
Okay, then, next time!
Episode 6!
We look forward to seeing you in episode 6 too!
Thank you very much, Aipon.
Thank you very much!