It's true that any kind of wish can be granted, right?
It's all right. Your prayer can undoubtedly be accomplished.
Well then... it's okay, right?
Yeah. Do it.
Now...
Go ahead and accept it.
That is your fate.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 5
There's No Way I'd Have Something Like a Regret
Ah, how improper.
I beg your pardon.
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Lack of sleep?
Yes. Last night, I was at the hospital and with the police until late into the evening...
Ehh? Did something happen?
Somehow, I was sleepwalking or something...
And there were a lot of people with the same type of symptoms.
When I regained consciousness, everyone was lying in the same place.
What's up with that?
Doctor-sama said it was a mass hallucination or something.
And today, I need to have a detailed examination after school as a result.
Such a bother.
If that's the case, it would have been fine to take a break from school!
That wouldn't do! Then, it'd seem as if I was truly ill.
It would create more and more worry for the people at home.
As expected of an honor student!
Admirable!
I haven't felt this good in a long time!
Refreshing, refreshing!
Sayaka-chan... aren't you scared?
Hmm? That is, I'm a little scared, but...
Well, the one from yesterday was an easy victory, after all.
If by some chance... Madoka and Hitomi.
The possibility that I may have lost two of my friends simultaneously...
That outcome is much scarier, you know.
So...
I wonder what to call it... confidence?
A feeling of relief?
I kind of feel like praising myself a little bit, you know.
Well...
I'm soaring high, you know!
Because from now on, Mitakihara City's peace...
will be passionately protected by this "Magical Girl Sayaka-chan" here, after all!
You don't have any regrets or anything at all?
Well, right... If I had to name a regret...
Hesitating would be my regret, I guess.
If I was going to do it regardless, I'd say I should have made up my mind a little bit sooner.
The witch at that time...
If we had both fought it together... for all I know, that may have prevented Mami-san's death.
I...
Hey now, you're thinking of something weird, aren't you?
I... If I had...
I can say these things since it's after I've become one.
The key point is that I did it regardless.
You know, this means that as long as it was possible, I would have become a magical girl.
Sayaka-chan...
I found... something to wish for.
It appears I had something that I didn't mind risking my life to fight for.
The fact that I was so slow to realize it...
Frustrates me a little, that's all.
So, it's fine if you don't feel weak or anything like that.
It means you don't have to end up becoming a magical girl, Madoka.
And it means nothing more than simply that.
Yeah...
Well now... I need to get going soon, then.
Do you have something to do?
Well, a bit, you know.
I see... you haven't been discharged yet, then.
The rehabilitation for my legs still hasn't been completed.
I need to be able to properly walk first, after all...
As for my hand, they say that they have absolutely no idea why it just healed...
That's why they're going to closely examine it for a little while longer.
Kyousuke, how's your self-confidence?
Does any part of your body feel strange?
No... it's so normal, you could call it scary.
It's like everything after the accident was just a bad dream.
I wonder, "Why am I lying in this bed?"
Exactly like you said, Sayaka... This is a miracle, isn't it?
What's wrong?
Sayaka, I said awful things to you, didn't I?
No matter how depressed how I was, I shouldn't have.
It's fine if you don't remember anything weird!
After all, it's natural for you to be overjoyed right now, Kyousuke!
Don't make a face like that.
Yeah.
Somehow, this doesn't feel real.
Well... don't overdo it either, okay?
It's about time, I think.
Kyousuke, let's go breathe a bit of the outside air.
What business do we have at a place like the roof?
It's fine, it's fine.
Everybody!
The real celebration is when you're discharged, but...
Your hands healed before your legs, you know.
T–That's...
You told me to dispose of it, but...
No matter what, I couldn't throw it away.
I...
Now... please try it out. You don't have to be afraid.
Mami-san...
My wish... has been granted!
There's no way I'd have something like a regret.
I'm... right now... the absolute happiest I can be!
That's this town's new magical girl, huh?
Do you really intend to conspire against her?
I mean, isn't it too easy?
I'll insta-kill that kind of person.
Or what?
Got a problem? You.
Everything is not limited to being as you plan.
Since there's one more magical girl in this city, you know.
What kind of person is that one?
I don't quite understand that myself.
Hah?
What do you mean?
Even they became a magical girl after forming a contract with you, right?
You could say that's right, or you could say that's wrong.
That girl is a guaranteed irregular.
Even I can't predict what kind of actions she'll make.
Hah! Isn't that perfect?
After all, I dunno about too much boredom.
Gotta have a little fun too, y'know...
What did you want to discuss?
Um, well, it's just about Sayaka-chan, but...
T–That girl, you know... vehemently makes an assumption, is really stubborn, and then—
She gets into fights with people fairly quickly...
But you know, she's a really good girl!
She's kind, and has courage.
If she's thinking in another person's interest, she'll really keep at it...
For a magical girl, that's fatal, you know.
Is that... so?
Extreme kindness is connected to naïveté.
Reckless courage becomes negligence.
And... no matter how much dedication you have, there's nothing like a reward.
If you don't understand that, you aren't fit to be a magical girl.
That's why Tomoe Mami lost her life.
Stop talking like that!
Right... even though Sayaka-chan herself says that she's fine...
Still, when I think about the possibility of something similar to that time with Mami-san occurring,
I... what should I do?
So you're worried about Miki Sayaka, then.
I... can't give Sayaka-chan strength anymore, so...
That's why I want to ask it of you, Homura-chan.
Please get along with Sayaka-chan.
Don't fight with her like you did those times with Mami-san!
During the times when you attack witches too, it should be much safer if everyone cooperates by fighting together, you know!
I don't want to tell lies.
I don't want to make promises I'm unable to keep, either.
Therefore... give up on Miki Sayaka.
Why...
That girl shouldn't have contracted.
Certainly, it was my miss.
Instead of just you, I should have kept precise observation on her as well.
In that case—
But, after admitting responsibility, let me say something.
Right now, it's a miss that cannot be redeemed by any means.
It's the same thing as how someone who has died is unable to return.
Once you become a magical girl,
there's nothing like hope for salvation anymore.
That contract means giving up on everything in exchange for just a single hope, after all.
So, you've also given up, Homura-chan?
On yourself, and the other girls too... everything?
Yes.
I won't make an excuse by saying this is atonement or something.
I will continue my fight, regardless of what kind of sins I have to commit.
I wasted your time, didn't I?
I am sorry.
Are you nervous?
I guess.
I'm done for if I make a single mistake, after all.
Madoka?
Sayaka-chan, from here on, are you...
Yup. I'm going on patrol to search for bad witches!
Since this is another duty of an ally of justice, you know.
Will you be fine... all by yourself?
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Even Mami-san had to go and do this.
As her kouhai, this is expected of me.
Um, you know... I... can't do anything,
and even though I understand that I'll just get in your way...
Still...
It's fine if it's only while I'm not a burden,
until then, if we go together—
Aren't you trying too hard?
S–Sorry...
It's no good, right? I understand that I'm just a bother...
No, I'm really happy!
Hey, did you figure it out?
My hands started shaking earlier... and they haven't stopped.
Pitiful, isn't it?
Even though I'm already a magical girl, it's like I'm disheartened when I'm alone.
Sayaka-chan...
You aren't anything like a nuisance. I'm really happy.
Just being with someone is really heartening.
I feel like I have the strength of a hundred people.
I...
I'll protect you without fail.
So be at ease, and follow behind me.
Let's beat those witches together, like we've done up until now!
Yeah.
You're aware of the danger, right?
Since I'm an idiot, I might do something reckless if I'm alone.
When I take to heart that even Madoka is here, I believe that alone will make me more cautious.
I see.
Yeah, it's fine if you've thought about it.
Kyubey...
(You've also had your own thoughts about this, right, Madoka?)
(I understand your feelings of wanting to protect Sayaka.)
(In reality, just by staying next to her,)
(you possess a single trump card that's ready to be used in the worst-case scenario, don't you?)
(I...)
(You don't have to say anything right now.)
(Sayaka will surely object to it too, I believe.)
(Just... if there comes a time when you've made up your mind, then my preparations will always be in order, okay?)
(Yeah.)
It's here.
This barrier probably isn't a witch's, but instead belongs to a familiar.
I can't get comfortable.
I'm still a beginner, after all.
Unpreparedness is a forbidden thing.
I understand that!
That's...
It's running away!
Leave it to me!
Hold it, hold it. What are you girls doing, exactly?
It'll get away!
Can't you tell by looking?
That's not a witch, it's a familiar.
It's not carrying a Grief Seed, is it?
But, if you leave it alone, won't it kill someone?
That's why, like...
You have to wait for it eat four or five people and become a witch.
'Cause that way it'll conceive a proper Grief Seed, y'know.
What're you going to do when you strangle a chicken before it lays eggs, huh?
Are you saying we should watch as the people attacked by witches helplessly die!?
Aren't you, like, having some kind of major misunderstanding?
Do you know about the food chain?
You learned it in school, yeah?
Weak humans are eaten by witches.
Those witches are eaten by us.
This is an obvious rule, right?
'Cause it just goes in order of strength, after all.
That's...
You're...
I don't think it's possible, but...
For the sake of forcing a joke so flashy as "helping other people in the name of justice"...
That couldn't be the reason a contract was formed with that thing, right? You.
If it was, what would you say!?
Hey now, could you stop?
When you stick your neck into my work, half just for fun, y'know... it seriously pisses me off.
Sayaka-chan!
Hmph! Newbie...
Cool your head a little bit.
That's strange.
Full recovery should take about 3 months after that, but...
Sayaka-chan's fine?
That's because she became a magical girl with a prayer for healing.
Her damage resilience is higher than other people's.
Who'd... to someone like you...
Since there are people like you... Mami-san is...
Annoying.
Super annoying!
Actually, what? I don't want to hear you talking like that in the first place, y'know.
In front of your senpai.
Silence!
We aren't messing around by dancing, y'know! Fool!
Sayaka-chan!
Madoka, it's dangerous if you get any closer!
If you don't understand when I tell you,
and you're an idiot that doesn't understand when I beat it into you, either...
After that, nothing left but killing ya, y'know!
I won't lose...
You think I'd lose!?
Why...?
Hey, why?
She isn't a witch, so why do fellow allies have to fight?
Nothing can be done.
Neither of them wants to do anything like surrender.
Please, Kyubey! Make them stop!
Such a thing shouldn't be happening!
I can't do anything.
But...
If you want to stop them by force no matter what, then it's not like there aren't any methods.
No one besides another magical girl can thrust themselves into this battle.
But if it's you, you have those qualifications.
If that's what you truly desire, you know.
That's right...
If I contract...
This is the end!
I...
That is now unnecessary.
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl for the purpose of beating witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch. She's a magical girl just like you!
Episode 6
Something Like This Is Definitely Strange
Something like this is definitely strange.