Mom... Mom!
Mizuki! Mizuki!
Dad!
Is... Is Mom okay?!
I only just heard, and I came as soon as I could.
Mizuki...
Mom...
Grandma!
Is Mom okay?!
You said she was brought in after taking a turn for the worse?
Darling.
Should you... Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Fine? Then...
It's good news, actually.
I'm pregnant.
Oh, you're pregnant!
Oh, you're just pregna—
Whaaaaaaaaat?!
Really?
Is it a girl?! A boy?! Which is it?!
I don't know, but Tsubomi,
you're going to be their big sister!
Me...
Their big sister...
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Tsubomi!
Why'd you dash off like that? We were worried.
Oh, I'm sorry!
But the thing is...
My mom's pregnant!
That's a surprise!
Yeah.
I've got super-eyes!
Your puns are worse than ever, Dad!
So anyway, she's going to stay with Tsubomi's grandma for a while.
I keep telling him I'll be fine here.
I mean, we have the shop to consider.
No way! You need to take it easy now!
I'll help look after the shop, don't worry!
I do worry, though.
I'm in middle school now, Mom! I can handle it!
Put a little faith in Tsubomi, okay?
All right. Do me proud, Tsubomi.
Have a safe trip!
It's Sunday tomorrow.
I've gotta give it my all!
Our Family's Growing!
I'm Going to be a Big Sister!
Here goes!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Don't get yourself all flustered, dear.
Oh, you made breakfast this morning, Tsubomi?
Oooh!
This looks great!
I like them a little charred.
Tsubomi cooked the rice too.
Some nice and fluffy rice is just what I wanted!
Let's see!
Delicious!
Thanks for the food!
I'll be off, then!
Bye, dear.
Bye, Dad!
Right, I'd better get moving as well.
Okay!
Oh?
It appears we have some guests.
You guys!
Let us help too!
Being a florist sounds like it'd be fun!
I'd love you to!
Do you clean out here every day?
Yes.
The flowers drop petals and leaves, and soil always ends up all over, so the mess piles up very quickly.
We're cleaning too!
We're helping!
You want these lined up in front of the shop?
I'll help too!
All right, thanks.
Being a florist is hard work, huh?
It is, but my mom always told me, if you love flowers, no other job can even compare.
And I totally agree!
It warms my heart to see our flowers
bring happiness and smiles to people.
We'd better open up shop.
Okay!
If one clears the mind, even fire
itself can be made to cool the body.
By freeing my mind of worldly thoughts,
I can rid myself of the very sensation of pain.
I will free my mind.
I will empty my heart and cleave
through their HeartCatch Orchestra!
Precure! Today, our long feud comes to an end!
If you want flowers for your girlfriend, you've gotta go with white cyclamens!
They represent purity.
Okay...
So give her a card that says what they mean along with them!
What kind of flowers are you looking for?
What flowers do you like?
Me? Um...
Because it's you I want to give them to!
We're so daring!
Sure are.
If you want to commemorate a new construction,
may I recommend long-lasting preserved flowers?
That does sound good.
Yuri's amazing!
Tsubomi!
Can you give me a hand?
I was always happy to do all the heavy lifting, but Mizuki was always pushing herself.
She'd overwork herself, and I'd always be worrying over her.
Dad.
You're both still really in love, aren't you?
Yeah, we really are!
But it's not just her I love.
It's you and your grandmother too.
Being surrounded by my family is what keeps me going.
Tsubomi!
There's a customer here who wants a wedding bouquet.
What should we do?
Mom always did the bouquets.
Well, you used to help her with them, didn't you? Go on.
Okay then!
Welcome!
I'm certain we'll be able to create a bouquet that meets your needs.
Could you tell me a little about the happy couple?
That bouquet giving you trouble?
I don't know what flowers to
use or what design to go with.
I'm at a total loss!
Why not ask your mother for advice?
Okay!
Their parents had been against them getting
married up until now, so they never actually wed.
But they have two children together, and their parents finally gave their blessing.
So they're finally getting married.
So their children will be part of their wedding, then?
I can't think of a greater happiness.
Yeah, you're right!
It's a celebration for their whole family, not just for the two of them!
What's wrong?
Their eldest daughter, Kasumi,
seemed kinda sad about it, though.
I see...
So you're wondering what kind of
bouquet you should make for them?
Yes.
What do you think, Mom?
It's not just about the happy couple, but Kasumi as well.
I think their bouquet needs to bring happiness to their entire family.
I know you can do it, Tsubomi.
What's important is that you pour your
own feelings into creating their bouquet.
Thanks, Mom!
I'll call again if anything else comes up.
Good luck, Tsubomi!
Dad!
Can we go and talk to Kasumi about the bouquet?
Say, Dad.
Can you tell me about when I was born?
Sure.
The day you were born, it had rained the whole day.
You were there crying your eyes out,
but your mother and I, and all the rest of the family, were overcome with joy.
When the rain finally stopped, we saw the sunlight reflecting off the budding trees outside the window.
Your mother said that soon, those buds would become beautiful flowers.
And those flowers will bring joy to everyone.
Hence your name, Tsubomi. It means "buds."
So that's why you named me Tsubomi.
We'll have to think of a good
name for your new sibling too!
Yeah!
"I have arrived, my princess!"
"Who are you?"
"I am the prince of the western lands!"
"Hello!"
The flower lady?
You're playing princesses?
It's a story I came up with!
Can we talk for a bit, Kasumi?
I want to ask about the bouquet.
I don't care about the bouquet.
It has nothing to do with me.
Where are your mom and dad, Kasumi?
Are you playing out here alone?
Mommy and Daddy are busy running the shop.
And even if they're not...
Ever since my little sister was born, she's been all they care about.
They don't even remember I exist.
Kasumi,
your mom and dad haven't forgotten about you.
I don't think so either.
Oh, I know!
Will you help me design their wedding bouquet, Kasumi?
Me?
Yeah! Let's make a bouquet
that'll make everyone happy!
Your dad, your mom, you, and your little sister!
But it was my little sister...
that stole my parents from me!
Kasumi!
The Flower of your Heart has weakened nicely.
Who're you?!
I am Kumojacky, a commander of the Desert Apostles!
I shall take the Flower of your Heart and use it to defeat those meddling Precure!
Flower of the Heart, show yourself!
You're up, Desertrian!
Kasumi! Where are you?!
Kasumi!
A Desertrian?!
Kasumi's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen!
Don't worry, Kasumi! I'll save you!
Seed of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
My dad...
And my mom!
Don't care about me anymore!
They hate me now!
That's not true!
No parent would ever hate their child!
Every child is born from their parents' love!
That's why their children bring them happiness!
Children... bring happiness?
I'm going to have a new brother or sister soon.
And I'm so excited I can hardly wait!
Remember that feeling!
I know you were dying to meet your sister too, Kasumi!
I wanted... a sister?
I wanted... to meet my sister...
I know you love your sister dearly, don't you, Kasumi?!
Yeah... I do...
It seems I must take the field.
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
Love and family are pointless concepts!
All that matters is victory and defeat, and on which side you fall!
You're just using Kasumi's love for her family as a weapon,
and I've had it up to here with this!
Shut up and fight!
I'll start by destroying you!
Blossom!
You came!
Here we go!
Your pathetic attacks won't be enough to stop me!
This is revenge for Sasorina!
Transform into Super Precure!
HeartCatch Mirage!
Come on, everyone!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
I'll show you the results of my training!
If one clears the mind, even fire
itself can be made to cool the body!
Kasumi.
I'm sorry we've been neglecting you.
It's okay.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
I'm the big sis around here,
so I've gotta be strong for her!
I can learn a lot from you!
I'm going to be a big sis soon!
So I can look up to you for advice, Kasumi!
I know!
Miss Tsubomi, let me help make the bouquet too!
Sure!
We'll make it together!
In the language of flowers,
a convallaria means "blessed tidings."
It looks like Kasumi's family has a
lot of happiness to look forward to!
Yeah, I think so too!
And Tsubomi's does too!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
That's a beautiful bouquet, Tsubomi!
Kasumi and I made it using her entire family's birth flowers,
and a wish that their family will always stick together.
I see.
I'm gonna work really hard to be the best big sister I can be!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
Christmas is in the air!
So why the heck's a Desertrian gotta show up now?!
I wish Santa had come instead.
I think we have a much better visitor this Christmas.
Who could be better than Santa?!
The one we all look up to. The beautiful, wonderful legend who we all love!
HeartCatch Precure:
A Christmas Miracle!
We Got to See Cure Flower!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!