Alarm
Slide to Stop
I believed I had to go on being your ideal.
Day after day after day...
That's how I tightened the bonds restraining me.
For that purpose I will become strong, emerge victorious from the Selector battles, and discard you.
So you changed your alarm tone, Kou?
Yeah.
Does that mean she's your new favorite?
Yes. Isn't her voice just lovely?
Voice Recorder
Have no doubt.
I will discard Suzu for my own benefit.
I can hear desperation dripping
from her voice. How adorable.
That's the entire reason I'm here.
It's almost unbearable just how unaware she is.
That doesn't matter to me.
I'm ridding myself of Suzuko for my own sake.
If only she'd show some consideration,
teasing and inciting me every day.
That's a nice personality you've got going for you.
Can you blame me?
What's life without a little fun?
This shitty world deserves nothing else.
I can't say I disagree.
Born into memories everything is given life
born memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Pull me from this maze of fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Dive into memories, if only I could see you
dive memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurikaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Darkness
Longing and Loss
Um... I use Crisis Chance to play Datemasa on the field, and then... Rise with Odanobu!
Decided.
This match is your victory.
Huh, really?
Unique. You've made this fighting style devoid of preconceived tactics your own.
It breaks your opponent's rhythm.
Did you just praise me?
Naturally, or so I intended.
Awesome!
That makes me so happy! Thank you!
Forthright. I was merely providing analysis of my observations.
I certainly underestimated Suzuko-san.
How reliable she's grown to be since we first met.
Whatever could have caused this change?
Suzuko is just trying to protect what she holds dear.
Her memories, I presume.
Hanna-sama appears to be just as attached,
but I cannot see the value of them.
You're out of time.
Now you have only one coin remaining.
What's going on in this photo?
Tell me, Dona.
Shou-chan, you should battle soon.
Then, I'm sure...
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Satomi Kou
Party A
henceforth
Party B
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Shirai Shouhei
Satomi Kou
henceforth
Party A
Party B
henceforth
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
Morikawa... I...
Don't worry. I'll go with you.
Master, here is today's offering.
Gratitude. Could these be...
Muff Muff chocolate muffins!
And this scent... could they contain banana?
Tasting.
I will put them to the test.
Refined! Chocolate banana is divine!
Thank goodness.
I actually baked those myself.
Sorry, I was running out of pocket change.
But it's my mom's secret recipe, so I was
confident they'd turn out good.
Did you bake these with your mother?
No, my mom passed away from illness when I was young.
I... see.
My mom had always been frail.
Still, she found the strength
to teach me how to cook.
Eventually, that became too hard for her.
For a while after that, all I could do was cry,
at least until Chii-chan comforted me.
She promised that we'd be together forever.
Confession.
I have also experienced the loss of a family member.
Seven years prior, my younger brother Yuuto
vanished from before my eyes.
Hanna-chan, let's play over there!
Yuuto, you're running too far ahead!
Yuuto?
That poor boy...
They say he fell from an apartment building under construction.
Why wasn't I with Yuuto?
Why can't I remember anything?
Why...
Hanna? Your friends are here to check up on you.
Refuse.
I don't want to see them.
I heard this
.was popular.
..Why not play it
...with friends?
........From Onee-chan
I am the LRIG of the Beginning.
Now registering your memories.
Rules. That is when I learned.
Desire. Were I to win, I could gain the piece of the puzzle I seek.
Contradiction. I must admit that I'm
a bit fearful of regaining all of my memories.
However, I must get them back at any cost.
Hello!
You must be Shirai-kun.
Who's this?
He's Satomi, the Bookmaker.
Also Chinatsu-chan's employer, for full disclosure.
Your employer?
Chinatsu-chan came asking me for a job.
She'd never—
More importantly, about his contract.
Oh, right!
I heard you went all the way with Chinatsu-chan!
In your battle.
I'm so jealous. Say, how did it feel?
While you were in the act with her.
Damn you!
Whoops, that's my fault. I should've expected this.
You must want to keep the girl you like all to yourself.
Stop that.
Shirai-kun!
What are you doing?
Didn't you want a contract?
What are you thinking?!
Something must be wrong with you
to agree to work for him.
Aren't you just forcing yourself to do this?
I'm the one who asked him for it.
You never would've done something like this in the past!
This has nothing to do with you!
I can't just leave you alone. Your words are what saved me.
You taught me that my time wasn't wasted,
and that I shouldn't just forget.
There's also that girl.
Suzuko-chan cares for you too!
So you want to restrain me too?
Morikawa?
I'm different.
I've changed.
Poor, pathetic Chii-chan.
All alone, with nobody who can understand her.
Satomi Kou
Shirai Shouhei
I'm just trying to move forward.
Satomi Kou
Shirai Shouhei
Why is it that everyone treats me
like I'm doing something bad?
It's okay. I know everything about you, Chii-chan.
Shou-chan.
Was signing that contract the right choice?
Just now...
she was trembling.
For beginners
To go well with tea
Easy! Happy!
Sweets
What are you planning on making?
Mistaken! I am not considering how to repay her at all.
I haven't mentioned a single word about that.
Is your battle class on hiatus today?
Postponed. Suzuko-san said she had business to attend to.
Hence your current aimless wandering.
Misunderstanding.
I am not—
Worthwhile.
At Suzuko-san's current level,
she makes for a worthy opponent for practice.
Someone sounds motivated.
Naturally. I have four coins.
My wish will be granted with one more win.
Then I have some good news for you, Hanna-sama.
I sense a Selector.
Here's today's collection.
Thanks.
Later. See ya after the next set.
Chii-chan, Chii-chan!
What? I told you not to talk to me in public.
You forgot about Shirai-kun's contract.
Why didn't you hand it over?
I have no reason to tell you.
Are you trying to keep him out of this?
That can't be right. Chii-chan would never back down on any decision she made.
You're no longer that weak—
No! I'm not—
Then prove it to me.
And in front of her.
Her?
Chii-chan.
Pardon! Are you a Selector?
I request a match.
Are you available?
Wait!
I resolved not to throw away our memories together!
I'll win every battle it takes to do that!
Do whatever you want.
I'll become strong!
I'll become strong enough not to ever rely on you again!
Then you won't have to get rid of your memories, right?
Suzu...
Light is such a funny thing.
It holds the power to either erase or grace whomever it shines on.
But you've already made up your mind.
Tell her.
I won't change.
If you won't disappear, then I'll just erase you.
You and my memories both.
Sumida Sou
I found her.
I can't take much more...
There's no point in edging. Guess I'll
have this one relieve me tonight.
Answer me.
Why are you investigating the Selector battles?
Sudden. Why ask that?
Tell me.
Demand. If you wish to know, then battle me.
Fine, I understand.
Introduction. My name is Mikage Hanna.
I'm Kiyoi.
Mizushima Kiyoi.
Is this really the right place?
And why is my opponent a secret?
Forget that shit. Do you even realize the position you're in right now, Onii-chan?
I have only one coin remaining and nowhere to run.
If you get it, then fight like your life depends on it!
Yeah, I still haven't figured anything out.
I won't let it end here.
They're here!
Sup, Narumi-oniichan.
Oh, it's just you, Satomi-san.
What brings you—
Onii-chan, he's a Selector!
There you have it.
Nice to meet you.
It couldn't be that my opponent...
Kou-san, you kept it a secret the whole time,
so you've gotta explain it to him.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Well, you might as well just spill the beans on his little sister.
Sure, you mean my battle with Aya-chan?
Your battle with Aya?
Don't tell me...
You know something about Aya!
Don't you?!
Let's continue this during our battle.
I feel like going buck wild tonight.
Suzuko.
I'm fine. I won't hesitate any longer.
Excuse me.
Are you a Selector?
If you want to battle, bring it on.
Open!
Piruluk, Grow.
Destruct Through.
Nanashi-chan!
I can still go on.
Powerful.
I admit that you are in control of this battle.
However, I cannot afford to lose!
I play a SIGNI and bet a coin!
Blind.
Turn End!
Kiyoi.
Yes. Coin Bet.
Peeping.
Level 4.
Lingering attachment to her lost memories.
Excessive curiosity towards the Selector battles.
Transparent. You read my mind?
Yes, I have seen countless wishes and witnessed the resolute emotions behind them.
As well as the sins that were committed to fulfill them.
You still don't understand these battles.
No, you still can turn your back on them.
Mikage Hanna, you mustn't proceed any further.
Listen, Ril.
I'll become even stronger.
Now then, it's my turn.
Hold on! Tell me about your battle with Aya!
I've been looking for the truth!
Ask all you want, but what is there really to explain?
After we battled, she just up and disappeared.
Disappeared?
Disap...pear...
Onii-chan, we're in the middle of a battle!
Did you... did you erase her?
What did you do to Aya?!
"What", you ask... would you like me to recreate the battle I had with Aya-chan?
Right, now it's coming back to me. She had terrible draws at first, so I got to sneak in a bunch of attacks.
Let me show you, Onii-chan.
I summon Antares and draw a card.
Attack.
Defend!
Fuck! If you're gonna defend, then do it—
Shut up!
Don't talk back to me!
I love it! Aya-chan couldn't defend for her life either!
It was you...
You took Aya...
I won't forgive you. I'll never forgive you, Satomi!
He took the bait.
Grow!
Summon Comrus, and use a trap—
There aren't any?!
What are you thinking, fuckwit?!
Bravo! No wonder you're siblings.
Even I'm surprised at how all your moves are carbon copies of hers.
It was worth replicating it.
Coin Bet!
Holograph!
Team Aaya takes the stage!
Thanks for the love!
Good, keep it coming! Onii-chan's deepest desires
were turned into a move right in front of me!
Grow.
Oh man, which one should I request?
That one.
Aaya!
Bingo! I'm so glad I didn't miss!
Otherwise it wouldn't be the same as when we broke through Aya-chan's coin ability in one strike.
You both have the mental fortitude of a newborn.
Damn it, what are you saying about my sister?!
Oh please, don't get the wrong idea about me.
I was but a LRIG back then.
A LRIG?
Yes! I was only following the orders of a human like you.
He was the owner of my body back then, though.
Whoa, aren't you telling him too much?
It's fine. Narumi-oniichan will be following in the footsteps of Aya-chan soon enough.
Right, he's going to disappear soon.
Hey, excuse me! You're supposed
to be begging for your life!
Aya-chan had broken down into tears by now.
She was crying "Save me, Onii-chan!"
Hey, get a grip!
I'm so glad I could let Onii-chan know.
Though he didn't make it in time for her.
Turn End.
Out Dust!
Whoops, now he's lost it. Moridra.
I'm pretty much spent after letting it all out,
so how about we put an end to this now?
What's the point in asking?
He can't get it up anymore.
Aya...
I just can't get enough of you humans' reactions.
Not to worry. I'll make sure Narumi-oniichan reaches his climax as thanks for helping me relieve myself.
Coin Bet.
Joker.
Convert Garnet Star into Kosaki.
We'll say our goodbyes with the same card that erased Aya-chan.
You changed it? That's cheating!
Super Nova.
Bye-bye, Onii-chan.
Defeat.
And with no room for argument.
It would be best for you to stop investigating the Selector battles.
You can't see the depths of the abyss.
It will consume you if you dive in.
Doubt. Why are you telling me this?
Who are...
Battles really are the best.
So, how does it feel to take your first breath in this world?
It's nauseating.
And besides, Aaya never asked to get a boy's body!
Don't be like that.
I'd rather kill myself than see this face
in the mirror every morning.
If you really hate it that much, you could always decide to get back in the fight, like I did.
If you get one of these, that is.
Though to tell you the truth,
this world isn't all that bad.
If you don't like the flavor, then just add your own spice.
How do I do that?
For example, you could join me in returning my gratitude.
Your gratitude?
Yeah, the greatest and worst we can do
for the humans who used us at their will.
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
Someone pulls back their tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no ga
But I can no longer remember who
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru
I'll teach you about this twisted world.
You don't need to see that guy anymore.
Play a SIGNI, and full attack.
Will that really be everything?
What is your reason to fight?
This is farewell, Hanna-sama.
Next time: Truth / End and Beginning.
Truth
End and Beginning