I need to kill...
...or be killed!
Are you awake?
You don't need to be scared.
I won't attack you anymore.
You're...
If you're asking about my name, I don't know it.
If you want something to call me, call me Ein.
That's what I'm being called all the time.
Ein...
Why did you attack me?
To prove your talent.
Talent?
You were born with a talent.
A talent to kill.
A talent to survive.
Talents needed for an assassin.
No way...
That doesn't make any sense.
On what grounds you can say....
Weren't you trying to kill me?
In that situation...
normally people would just panic and get themselves killed.
But you weren't like that.
You acted before knowing about your situation, thus you survived.
Zwei.
Zwei?
That's your name.
No...
Don't call me by a weird name!
I do have a proper name...
My...
...name.
You don't have it anymore.
Thinking about it is useless.
What is that supposed to mean?
Your memories were erased.
By Inferno.
Wonderful.
The journalist that has been found dead by gunshots,
Your Phantom is excellent, Scythe Master.
...is believed to have been involved in the syndicate's plot.
It is an honor, Mr. McGwire.
No one would believe they were the work of a kid.
Correct.
That is why she was granted the title "Phantom".
You have achieved something great.
Because you have created a ghost
that shouldn't belong anywhere in this world.
Not at all.
This is all because I have full support from Miss McCunnen.
You have a good subordinate, don't you Claudia?
By the way, the disposal of that journalist took quite some time, didn't it?
No, not at all.
The disposal was seen by someone, right?
By some ordinary traveller.
I don't know where you heard such a thing,
but the witness has been disposed of.
The body has also been taken care of.
I see. Wonderful.
Did you use Phantom too?
Yes.
You were supposed to have been killed.
To erase any proof completely.
But Master realized your talent,
and thought it was such a waste to kill you.
Master?
Scythe Master.
My Master.
Master took away your memories,
and prepared a new life for you.
As one of Inferno.
A life as an assassin.
Assassin? Me?
You are my clone.
You have become "Zwei".
Don't talk nonsense!
Why should I...
...kill?
Refusing is fine.
But if you do...
I will have you killed, just as you should have been.
Here and now.
You'll need to be reborn if you want to keep living.
You have already become an existence that cannot live without killing.
I...
...don't want to die.
This is a dream.
This is all just a bad dream.
If that can put you at ease, then that's fine.
Just consider it all a dream.
However...
It'll be a long dream.
Change into that!
You will be sticking with me all the time from now on.
You will follow my orders.
Understand?
Let's begin.
Zwei's results are proceeding smoothly.
He received the steady training obediently.
He's quite easy to handle.
Faced by such a hard training everyday
would make merely having ideas painful.
Yes, that is the basis of training.
I will present you with results that will not fail your expectation,
Miss McCunnen.
Do you think I expect anything?
My pawns are yours as well.
It's all an offering for Inferno.
This is how you hold it.
Don't place your finger on the trigger.
Use both of your hands, not your shoulder.
And give some pressure on your finger.
This is the scope,
this is the point view.
Look at the point view through the scope to aim.
When you take the stance, straighten your right arm,
and bend your left arm to stabilize the gun.
But where you need to put your strength
isn't in the whole arms, but your hand instead.
Don't panic when you pull the trigger.
Squeeze it softly.
Shoot!
Keep shooting the remaining five.
You need to hit every one of them from this distance.
If you can do that, next is your speed.
Your target is six rounds in four seconds.
Concentrate on hitting your target for now.
Still too slow!
It seems that you can hit every time,
but at this rate, you'll be killed even before
you had the chance to take down your enemy.
Again...
...and again.
I'm digesting every given task without a single complaint.
If I do that...
without thinking anything...
if I do that...
I can be at ease.
Forgetting lots of doubts.
My daily life...
...is disappearing.
I'm heading out. Do the usual menu.
Heading out?
A job.
Let's go, Phantom.
Yes, Master.
Master?
He's Scythe Master.
A sniping mission after a long time.
Well, it'll be easy for you.
The target will be in 700 yards of distance.
I have prepared a Remington .308 with scope.
The weather at the location is cloudy with a bit of wind.
The forecast said there will be no change until tomorrow morning.
The details are in there.
Any questions?
No.
Very well.
By the way, how's Zwei doing?
He has completed the basic course.
He will begin the next phase of training tomorrow.
I should prepare an actual trial in the near future, huh?
Don't mind me, keep going.
Should I call this our first meeting?
I'm Claudia McCunnen.
Is there anything else about me that you're wondering beside my name?
Nothing.
But, you do want to know about Inferno,
the organization that took you in, right?
You don't answer me, so I assume your answer is yes.
Inferno is...
Yes,
a group that are trying to create a different kind of order in an orderless world.
Or so...
If you picture gangs and mafias as countries,
Inferno is like their UN.
Inferno is striving for the union of the crime world.
That dream-like story might not have been more than a joke not too long ago.
But the one who is making it true...
...is Phantom.
That's right.
Your instructor.
Phantom's power is absolute.
That she exists only to kill the target...
...is Inferno's ultimate asset.
The organizations that resist it would recieve the ultimate fear.
She is the perfect assassin.
But...
In the end, she is just someone who is being used by the organization.
Phantom and I.
We can only live like slaves.
Indeed, we are giving you only one way of life.
But you're not slaves.
You have freedom.
It's your speed.
Speed?
Even in the pre-determined course,
as long as you have will and effort,
you can take off to wherever you want.
You might even able to stand in the organization's court.
How you'll surpass it is only up to you.
Don't ever think of yourself as a slave again.
As long as you think of yourself that way...
...you're giving the victory to those who want to beat you.
I wanted to have a longer conversation with you,
but there's this job I can't miss.
Good bye, Zwei.
Cars are to be driven.
Unlike dolls.
Even in the pre-determined course, as long as you have will and effort...
...you can take off to wherever you want.
Will...
Effort...
I have forgotten about those words.
Ein.
What is it?
Today's mission.
Did you kill someone?
Yes.
Why did you...
...become an assassin?
I don't know.
I haven't been told who I was before.
Isn't that...
Yes, just like you.
My memories were erased.
And I became an assassin.
But what of it?
I can keep living to this moment.
That's all I need.
An assassin...
the past, and the future...
We don't have either.
But...
the woman named Claudia...
Claudia?
She dropped by this afternoon.
She said we're not slaves.
That we have freedom.
If you want to believe in that, then so be it.
But sooner or later, you will feel nothing.
Because there is no other way to bear this way of life.
In time, you will be like that.
You will understand after you actually kill someone.
Pulling the trigger is easy.
If the targets...
...are only bricks.
But...
Shoot!
Zwei.
Zwei...
This is the continuation of the dream.
A never-ending dream until you die.