Fionn mac Cumhaill, hero of Aillen and
leader of the knights of Fianna,
is now formally betrothed to
my daughter Gráinne.
My loyal subjects, let us celebrate!
That striking man with the mole
beneath his eye...
What is his name?
He is a knight of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Diarmuid...
Traitor...
You will pay, Diarmuid!
Take me from here...
Let us run, together.
Rejoice, Gráinne!
Fionn has accepted our love!
You thought I'd forgiven you
for stealing Gráinne away?
A dream?
That dream was...
It was Diarmuid's legend.
My Servant's memories?
Where am I?
You're awake.
Sola-Ui...
What is this?
What am I doing here?
You remember nothing, do you?
I...
I was shot.
I remember defending myself with
Volumen Hydragram, but...
What's happened to me?
Apparently, every Magic Circuit in
your body has shorted out.
It's a miracle you weren't
killed instantly.
I was able to save your
internal organs, but that's all.
Your Magic Circuits were destroyed.
You'll never cast a spell again.
I... I...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too early to give up.
We haven't been defeated yet.
Sola-Ui...
If the Holy Grail can truly grant
wishes with its omnipotence,
full restoration of your body is sure
to be well within its ability.
We merely need to win.
If we are victorious
and claim the Grail,
everything will return to normal.
So... My dear Kayneth?
Please give me your Command Spells...
I'll stand in for you, as Lancer's Master,
to bring you the Holy Grail.
N-No!
Don't you trust me?
The woman who would marry into
the Archibald family?
I do, but...
Sola-Ui,
do you believe that Lancer
will swear his allegiance to you
instead of me?
Yes.
He is a Heroic Spirit who responded
to the Holy Grail's invitation.
He desires the Grail, just as we do.
I'd expect even a change in Masters
would be acceptable,
if it will bring him closer to his goal.
Sola-Ui!
Lancer isn't as admirable as he seems!
Why would you say a thing like that?
When I asked him of his wish,
he told me, "I have no interest
in the Holy Grail."
A Servant who cares nothing
for the Grail is impossible.
He is hiding his true intentions.
But whatever he's trying to conceal,
so long as I have these Command Spells,
he must obey.
Kayneth...
I won't give them up...
Kayneth, you don't seem to realize...
That we must win, no matter the cost.
You see, Kayneth...
My spiritual healing ability
cannot forcefully remove those
Command Spells from you.
Only through your willing agreement
may I take them without resistance.
If you continue to categorically refuse,
I'll have no choice
but to remove your right arm.
So?
Irisviel?
Don't worry.
Magical healing takes quite
a toll on the target.
It will be a while before she
regains consciousness.
Could you keep an eye
on her for me?
Are you going to report to Kiritsugu?
I'm sure he's worried, too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
Please tell Kiritsugu something...
Please urge him to prioritize
Caster's elimination.
Saber...
If he's allowed free reign,
more innocent children
will be murdered.
Kiritsugu?
How long until we can use Maiya?
She won't be able to move for a day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stand by here.
I'm going to finish off Kayneth.
Wait, Kiritsugu!
Did Saber argue that we
should deal with Caster immediately?
Huh?
I thought so.
Are you mad at Saber for
letting Lancer go?
Iri...
Saving a few children,
or even a few dozen,
is not our priority.
Saber trusted Lancer not to kill me,
but what if he had betrayed his word?
Our Holy Grail War would
have ended there.
Don't tell her where I'm going, either.
Lancer?
Please come out here.
Lady Sola-Ui, how is Lord Kayneth's condition?
It's very serious...
I've done all I can for him, but...
Don't blame yourself!
It's Kayneth's fault!
All it means is that he couldn't
handle the Grail War.
No, but...
He simply isn't a suitable Master
for you, Diarmuid.
Kayneth has retired from this War,
transferring his authority,
as Master, to me!
I've sworn my fealty as a knight
to Lord Kayneth.
Lady Sola-Ui, I cannot agree to that.
What?
But as a Servant,
is it not my mana that maintains
your physical form?
And I even have his
Command Spells now!
Before I am a Servant, I am a knight.
I can only serve one lord.
So I'm not worthy to be your Master?
That isn't what I'm saying...
Look me in the eye when
you address me!
Lancer...
Fight with me, and protect me!
Support me, and we'll claim
the Holy Grail together!
I cannot.
If Lord Kayneth has truly withdrawn,
I shall no longer seek the Grail.
A miracle is his only chance
to be healed!
And the Grail is the single way to
bring about that miracle.
If you feel regret over his condition...
If you would restore Lord El-Melloi
to his former stature...
Then you must deliver the Grail
to your Master!
Lady Sola-Ui,
you, as Lord Kayneth's partner,
seek the Grail solely to save him?
Correct?
Y-Yes...
Of course!
Then will you swear to it?
You have no other motive?
I swear...
As Kayneth El-Melloi's wife,
I shall bring the Grail to him.
She has the same look in her eyes
that Gráinne did.
I bear no grudge against anyone.
However,
fate has truly treated me unkindly.
In this era, my wish is but to
tread the path of loyalty I was
unable to hold to before.
I do not wish to repeat that pain.
But...
Er...
Quite a drinker, eh?
Ah, many thanks!
You should have told us you were
bringing a guest!
Oh, I wouldn't have it any
other way, ma'am.
A simple, home-cooked meal is the greatest form hospitality.
Such flattery!
I told you...
to dematerialize...
when you come and go!
But then I wouldn't have been
able to carry this.
To do so, I also obtained
this fine pair of pants.
Besides, boy, you were the one
who ordered me to go.
And why should the King of Conquerors
need to fetch water from a
common country river?
Because it's more useful than sitting around,
stuffing your face and watching TV.
What's this?
Pretend alchemy?
Not pretend alchemy.
It's actual alchemy, dummy.
So what's that?
Spell casting residue.
Basically, the traces of magic
that remain in the water.
It indicates that someone
was using magic near the river's mouth.
If we follow this trail,
we might find some clues.
Boy, did you know from the start
that you'd find something
like that in the water?
Of course not.
But the river cuts right through
the city center.
It was the obvious place to start.
Rider.
Did you notice anything between
these two points?
Like a drainage pipe or an
irrigation channel?
Yeah!
I saw a large one around there.
That's it.
If we follow it, it'll probably take us
straight to Caster's laboratory.
Boy, could you actually be
an incredibly talented mage?
This isn't the method a talented
mage would use.
It's probably the simplest possible way.
You're mocking me, aren't you?
Certainly not!
It's a much greater accomplishment
to achieve your ends through simple means.
rather than starting with a grand plan.
As your Servant, I'm filled with pride!
Okay...
If we can but locate him,
victory will be ours.
What say we go and give him
a good thrashing, boy?
Hold on.
We're fighting Caster, remember?
I know.
You don't know!
He'll have every advantage
when it comes to defending his territory.
What kind of idiot would just
charge straight in?
Listen...
In war, control over territory may
shift at any moment.
If you do not strike at your opponents
the moment you locate them,
you will regret your inaction if they escape.
Why are you so pumped up today?
Why do you think?
My Master has finally accomplished
something worthwhile.
As his Servant,
it spurs me further onward,
to go forth and retrieve
the enemy's head!
Do not give up when
we've yet to start.
At any rate, what say you
to simply venturing in?
It may pay off in ways you
cannot yet conceive.
Here it is!
See, this pays off already!
Bah...
Unfortunately, Caster's not at home.
Is this some kind of water storage?
Ah, boy...
I think it's better if you don't see this.
Are you kidding me?
If Caster isn't here,
we should at least look for clues
to where he went,
or we'll never find him.
That may be so, but don't do it.
This is too much for you.
Shut up.
I did try to warn you.
Shut up!
Damn it, don't make fun of me...
Damn it...
This is no time for stoicism, fool.
Well, this is right...
I'd pummel any man who
could look upon this
without flinching.
Pummeling who exactly?
You, yourself,
appear perfectly calm!
Trust me...
This is no time to be emotional.
It's because my Master is in danger!
Assassin?
That's impossible!
Assassin's already dead.
There isn't time for surprise, boy.
H-How?
The how of it matters not to us.
There is one thing we know for sure.
Any who believed Assassin was dead
has been gravely fooled...
They ran...
Didn't they?
Do not relax your guard.
Two have fallen, but at least two remain.
And we have no means to
know how many more
Assassins there may be.
This location favors their strengths.
We should withdraw immediately.
Should we really just leave it like this?
We may learn something by investigating,
But leave it.
If we destroy the place,
it should at least set Caster back.
With his lair in ruins,
Caster will have nowhere to run or hide.
He'll be forced into the open.
It won't be long before we can
be finished with them.
I get it...
Knock it off!
Let us leave, boy.
Don't dwell on it, Kirei.
It's doubly unfortunate that
Assassin was revealed
before we uncovered Rider's
final attack.
But we've learned
that Rider's Master is no more
than a third-rate mage.
Which is why, had they not been seen...
You would have had more options?
Yes.
Naturally, planning is paramount,
but you must always retain your
confidence and elegance.
Even battles should be fought with dignity.
But I had no idea he'd be so insufferable.
Another chance to see Rider's final
Noble Phantasm will come.
Have Assassin take extra precautions,
but continue to observe him.
Understood, my mentor.
Episode 9:
Master and Servant
Did I expend too much mana at once?
There's gotta be some way I can help!
She couldn't have gone to Fuyuki...
Here is the Matou family magic.
The party's just about to start.
I can't do anything!
Next Time:
Rin's Adventure