Yo-heave-ho!
It's fall.
After the Typhoon
Virtual and Real Images
So Kureha-chan, your dad used to ride a tank!
Right. He helped more than 1,000 civilians and soldiers,
out of the completely surrounded town of Waldenburg,
with only six Millpad Type-2s!
He was the hero of the legendary evacuation!
He's great!
Isn't he?
And my dad, who was honorably wounded during the war,
met my mom, a combat medic, when he was in the hospital.
Then, their child is...
Kureha-chan!
Right.
So you mean I'm a potato!?
Wow. The potatoes are great.
Thanks to Kana-chan's hard work.
Then, I guess we can even give a gift to the people in town.
And, Klaus-san should also be coming later.
Let's bring them as gifts.
So he's gonna be here?
Kureha-chan, you really like Klaus, right?
I-It's not "like". It's respect.
Rio-senpai...
Wow, she can even do this too.
As expected from Rio-senpai!
The wind is coming!
It looks like the weather is breaking.
Let's get back as soon as possible.
Yes.
Noël-chan too.
Huh?
Think about it. Doesn't Rio-senpai look weird?
How so?
The trumpet...
That's so great, right? Really cool.
It feels like she's really depressed...
She's always quiet, isn't she?
But...
Right. Dinner!
That was so delicious!
Tempura.
Mmm. The potatoes were so crispy.
No. I didn't mean that!
Here you go, Rio. Eat it while it's still hot.
Ah. Thank you.
Tastes good?
Mmm.
Really? Good.
She even munched on those green peppers!
I can't believe Rio-senpai would do that!
Right.
No matter how small the amount is, she would always find it and definitely flick it away.
How can Rio-senpai...
That is probably the most important thing...
Is this... Klaus-san?
Yes. That's my treasure.
The Wolf of the Desert, Miracle Klaus.
The Wolf Head tattoo on his left chest stands for the unity and pride of platoon 481.
He's so hot.
I won't give that to you!
Don't worry too much, alright?
The platoon leader too, she's just worrying too much about us.
Cause it's Rio-senpai!
She is cool, attractive and beautiful.
Right. She must have overcome it, and become able to eat them, even though they're green peppers.
Kureha-chan. You really like Rio-senpai.
Because senpai is my idol.
That's true for me too...
Well, Noël-chan, what do you think?
Dangerous!
Noël-chan is already fast asleep.
I guess we have to leave her as she is. I can lend her part of my bed.
Kanata, take that part.
Umm.
You forgot to put out the fire for the bath.
Sorry. I wasn't paying attention.
You always try hard to beat things but slip-up in trivial places. That's your charming point.
But, it's been too much recently.
Sorry.
Are you regretting receiving that phone call from your dad?
There's just no other choice.
I will cover up your oversights.
Please, at least be a great senpai in front of those girls.
Is that the wind?
It's not.
Sorry for disturbing you this late.
Here's a high priority parcel.
Who's the recipient?
Staff Sergeant Kazumiya Rio of platoon 1121.
Please take it.
Major, anyway, please come in first.
In such weather, you won't be able to go anywhere else.
Even though you are the Wolf of the Desert.
I told you not to call me that anymore.
I'm sorry.
As an apology, would you like to have some hot tea and a bath?
Thank you for your hard work, completing your mission in this typhoon.
Er... I'm sorry that this is all we have left from yesterday's dinner,
but please enjoy it.
You could have woken me up for Klaus-san's arrival.
Mmm.
It tastes great!
It's delicious even though it's already cold.
And the green pepper was well cultivated.
Oh really!?
I did the plucking and frying.
Oh? It seems that Kureha will be a good wife.
A new newspaper?
Right. The Major brought it to us.
How's the cease-fire agreement going?
There are still a lot of arguments in the negotiations.
Neither side is going to give way.
If Princess Iliya were still alive, things might be completely different...
Iliya...? Princess...?
Don't you know her?
She's the hero of Vingt, King Arkadia's first princess.
The Goddess of Victory of the Helvetian Army.
She is the Goddess of Tankers similar to Major Klaus, the Wolf of Desert!
Kureha, that's...
You're all here? There's an emergency.
Rio! Rio!
What's happening?
A child's been missing from Yumina's place since this morning.
Please give her a hand.
What?!
Who's missing, Yumina-san?
Seiya-san.
The water level of the river has risen a lot...
The farmers downstream won't have finished their harvesting yet.
Everything will be destroyed.
I'm not familiar with the city. Please help me, Kureha.
Yes Sir!
I'm really sorry. I should have kept an eye on him.
It's one of the army's duties to search and rescue during disasters. Just leave it to us.
Let's go.
Yes Ma'am!
Seiya-kun... Seiya-kun... Seiya...
Seiya! Seiya-kun...
That's extraordinary! The water is so...
If he fell into the water...
Seiya!
Seiya-kun...
What's up?
You!
You know something, don't you?
You came out because you know where he is, right?
Tell us where Seiya is!
At the farm...
Farm?!
Eggplant... Yumina-oneechan loves that the most...
So, some time ago, we gathered our pocket money and bought some...
Seiya must be...
Where is it?
You fool...
What are you doing?!
Why are you out here in a typhoon?!
I'm going to protect the eggplants!
What are you talking about?! That's ridiculous!
We're risking our lives to save you!
You came by yourselves. I didn't ask you to save me!
What?! Do you hear what you're saying?!
Listen, orphans should be more sensible than those with parents by their side.
If you make trouble for others, they will look down on you.
Not only you, but also Yumina.
They will do the same to your onee-chan as well.
Kureha...
I am an orphan too... So I understand...
Right. Let's go back as soon as possible.
But...
What are you hesitating for?
Well... Just wait a minute.
Things cultivated with your heart are sometimes as valuable as your life.
It's ready to be eaten at such size.
Right. It tastes great after pickling.
Thanks a lot, Ojisan!
Major...
Seiya-kun has started climbing up.
Please go ahead, Major.
Well...
N-No, you take the lead. I'll follow you.
Yes sir!
It seems that both of them are fine.
But... They cannot climb up anymore.
Things are... getting worse.
Thank you very much.
Although things are getting worse, I believe there must be a way out.
You're wrong...
What are you saying?
Nope...
Listen! Don't be afraid!
You are now with the Miracle Klaus!
Yes sir!
The river bank is collapsing!
A consequence...?
Damn it. That's why I hate children.
Naughty kids should be tied up and watched carefully!
Rio! How can you say something like that?!
Those kids look up to you all the time!
I'm sorry... A slip of my tongue...
B-But there must be a way out, right?
Klaus-san is said to be a man of miracles...
You are wrong.
He is neither the Wolf of the Desert nor the Miracle Klaus.
It's just that they have the same name and a similar figure.
Kureha mistook that when they first met.
Klaus is not good with conversation.
He has been looking for a chance to tell her the truth but there hasn't been one yet.
How can this happen...
Anyway, he is an experienced communicator...
And a passionate gunner with little experience.
We have to find a way to rescue them from that place.
Rope... Pass to them...
There's no place for them to stand.
We're too far away to pass the rope to them.
If there is a method to pass them the rope...
There is one.
When I first met Klaus-san...
I thought that my father would have been like this if he were still alive.
People think that I know a lot about my father.
But, it's all second-hand information. I don't actually know much.
He had already passed away before I was aware.
Kureha...
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
"Left... Mind the left side above you...?"
Takemicaduchi!
Stop!
Noël-chan, how is it?
Half done. Activation status of Anchor Coil.
Target system, parts B7 through F5 are activated.
Starting to aim.
It's possible!
Anchor Coil Gunner, prepare to fire.
Kanata, go!
Yes Ma'am!
It's coming!
I'll be protecting you in place of your deceased father!
Yes... Major.
Good. Fire!
Come!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Pull it back! Quickly!
Hey... Kureha...
We're safe now... And I think it's time to tell you...
I...
You really are the person I longed for!
The blue sky after a typhoon...
So after all, you kept silent?
To be frank, I was really amazed...
That you could really do that.
Looking at a person trusting me,
I thought that death is not as awful as breaking Kureha's dream.
And that's why I did it...
In the end, I'm still a coward.
That's not true.
Klaus-san was really great!
Listen, girl.
Most of the time, what you hear about a person is completely different from your own feelings for him or her.
You'll never have a clear image of a man if you look at him through glasses filled with expectations.
Someday when you're the one being stared at, you'll understand the hardship in it.
Can you keep it a secret until Kureha-chan discovers it herself?
Can you tell Kureha for me...
That this wound has been the most glorious one of my life?
Departure: Time of First Snow
Next Time :
Departure
Time of First Snow