"Keep Out"
Chiyori-san...
Chiyori-san.
Ah, she's awake!
Wh-Who are you?!
Huh? Well, um...
Is this like some sort of religious soliciting?!
Or an offer for a pyramid scheme?!
Chiyori's got no money!
Um!
If you'd like... could you be friends with us?
Huh?
--This has got to be a trick!
--N-No...
--Like, there's no way anyone would
--You've got it wrong. We really want to...
--want to be friends with Chiyori!
They're gonna strip me of everything I've got!
Sorry about that...
I'm sorry... I guess she didn't trust us.
She just got confused being suddenly
approached in a friendly manner.
She'll probably say something like, "I want to
be your friend-y," when you meet her again.
Th-That's embarrassing me...
Huh?
Well, when that happens,
please be friendly with her.
Here... I go!
Wha...?!
And... Out!
Th-That's how you get out of the card?!
Well then, take care!
Um...
Huh?
Eldora...
Eldora's so kind,
doing all that for Chiyori-san...
It's not only Eldora.
Yuzuki went through a lot for me, too.
Stop it...
Plus, it isn't only me, too...
At first, I thought I was tricked, but...
...all the LRIGs are like any other girl.
I'm sure they're all hurt...
Midoriko...
I'm sure all the girls in the
Selector battles are hurt.
No.
Mayu is the only one
different from any other girl.
That's why she longs for other girls...
...and tries to break those very girls' wishes.
Ruko.
Take me...
...to Urith.
Taken and granted,
ideals are repetitious games that slip through
My daily life is so shot with holes
that I can barely stand
Empty theories without conclusions
Dance steps along invisible rules
The final bell holding together
the crumbling day rings
In the scene I imagine
you're there
with a smile
No forgiveness? No desires?
And still
We cry "OPEN"
A future to get back and a world to destroy
A wish to open. GOT IT?
Now cross
I wish you don't cry
The future of light and dark,
let's believe in the "future"
so that they overlap to gain color again
Come on in.
This place will be given to me as my room...
We fought against Ruko in this very building.
She was... very beautiful.
On the other hand, you really are lacking.
The likes of you can't kill anyone.
What...?
You remember what you said?
Her wish... Her life...
You reaped them away from her...
You really are simple, aren't you?
That girl--
I don't care.
I really don't care whether
she's alive or not...
It's just that I was different back then...
Why...?!
This...
...isn't my face...
What are you saying?
You're just back to what
you looked like before.
You're more unsightly than everyone there is.
You're filthy from the bottom of your soul...
She said I was filthy from
the bottom of my soul...
That soul...
You reached your hands deep
within my very soul to save me.
You seek to see things
of beauty being broken.
You seek to see them being
dirtied and driven to corruption.
With me already in filth...
...I was merely a pawn to you,
so that you could battle Ruko.
How surprising.
I thought you were a bit more stupid, but...
...it looks like you know yourself pretty well.
So, now you want revenge, right?
What kind of revenge do you seek,
beating me in a Selector battle?
Do you want to see me in ruin,
just like what you sought against Iona?
Or... maybe you want to
scar this face just like yours.
I'm gonna...
...heal your scar...
That scar will be a pure and beautiful
scar inflicted on you by my love.
That scar will also be healed
by my strong love for you.
I'll be an LRIG...
...and once I return to being human...
...I'll first find you, and then scar you.
Then I'll battle again for
my wish to heal your scar.
I'll be an LRIG, then a human,
then an LRIG again...
...and every single time,
from now and beyond...
...your body will...
...with Aoi Akira's love...
Aoi Akira's love...
...will go through you!
Aoi Akira is going to continue
circulating through your body!
Your body will never forget me!
You're quite interesting...
Okay, let's battle...
Tama and I are starving...
Ru...
I'm sorry...
In the last battle...
...when the dark entered my stomach,
a thought came to Tama's mind.
If that wish could come true...
...Tama would do anything...
...even if...
...I made someone cry.
Here I go, you piece of shit...!
You want to see Iona?
Yes, we really need to speak with her.
Hey, aren't you girls Iona and Akira's friends?
You were here before, right?
Y-Yes!
I guess you haven't heard
what happened to Iona.
I can't believe Urith is
hospitalized from an accident...
I wonder what happened...
I'm getting bad vibes from it.
Maybe Tama got invol--Wha...?!
What's the matter, Yuzuki?
A battlefield opened up somewhere!
What?
Wh-Who's battling?
Maybe...
Iona, can you tell what's going on?
It's very... unstable.
It's as if the battle itself is...
refusing to be seen.
Could it be...?!
Da...
Damn it...!
Tama... Grow.
Ru, don't come to Tama...
Don't see Tama like this...
That shop had a good selection of singles.
Yes...
Yuzuki!
That was close...
Ah, how about we get a drink?
Yuzuki?
Yuzuki, you've been acting strange recently.
You said something similar before.
That I've been acting strange recently.
Huh?
Since when have I acted strange?
A week ago? Two weeks ago?
Yuzuki...
Between the previous me and current me,
which do you like better?
What's the matter? Yuzuki?
I'm...
I think it's this way.
Tama!
Ah, wait! I got an email!
Huh? From who?
I don't know the sender...
"If you want to meet Urazoe Iona...
...head here."
Urith...
Urith!
Uri...?
Tama... Give me back Tama!
Ta... ma...?
That email was very literal...
Huh?
This girl isn't Urith.
She's Urazoe Iona.
What...?
That means this is the real Urazoe Iona-san,
and not someone using her body?
Lrig...
It's been a while hasn't it, Lrig?
So... I see you look just like me now.
Huh?
Lrig...?
That's what I called her by.
LRIG.
Lrig? That's your name?
That's not quite true, but I don't
have a name, so that will do.
Such a strange girl...
What's your wish?
Wish?
Let me see...
I guess... I don't want to
be Urazoe Iona anymore.
Back then...
...everyone around me had expectations...
...of me as the successor to the Urazoe Family,
and as an up-and-coming model.
I had very little room to myself.
Lrig didn't really speak much...
...and I didn't ask her much, either.
Amid all the involvement I had
with others, it was a bit relaxing...
I battled alongside Lrig...
...and then...
...an Eternal Girl was born.
I went to Mayu, and found out
all of what happened.
Do you understand now what
Selector battles are about?
Are you upset?
But, all you need to do is to become an LRIG
and drag a Selector into battle, then...
It doesn't matter.
My wish to not be Urazoe Iona came true.
There's no reason for me to battle anymore.
So... you don't care about being human again?
Everything will end...
Are you okay with that?
Yes, I'm fine.
What...? That's wrong...
What?
That's absolutely wrong!
Say that this is terrible...
Say that you want to be
human again no matter what!
Wail and scream with tears!
Otherwise, that's absolutely
and completely wrong!
And then... I became an LRIG.
I was an LRIG for two other Selectors...
...but I didn't coerce
my Selectors into battle.
But...
...if you think about how your wish can
come true, you start wanting to battle.
But, the Selectors I was with
weren't suited to doing battle.
They lost their battles and
their wishes were reversed...
I think that girl, Mayu, didn't like me.
That's why I think she purposely
assigned me as an LRIG to weaker girls.
That's not...
I didn't think much about
myself and of others, but...
...with all the tears I've seen,
it became hard to bear...
That's when I felt my real body...
...Urazoe Iona, become hollow.
Hollow...?
I immediately thought to myself
that I needed to go back.
If no one resided within Urazoe Iona's body,
everything would truly end.
I see. Urith was using Iona-san's body, so...
...Urith's wish came true,
and an Eternal Girl was born!
That's why...
Wait! But, why hollow?
If Urith became an LRIG,
then Tama should be human, right?
And, in Iona-san's body!
Right, Iona?
Tama... refused.
Refused...?
Why didn't you become Urazoe Iona?
It's wrong that you remain an LRIG, right?
But...
I sensed your feelings, Tama.
A feeling of wanting to eat ice cream
together with Ru under the summer sun.
Tama... is originally a card.
I'm not a human...
So, if Tama wanted to be human...
...someone else may become sad and lonely.
Stop making excuses!
I told you I sensed your feelings.
Tama, you also thought...
...that you were fine even if you
had to make someone cry, right?!
I didn't want...
...the bad Tama to be seen.
But, I sensed...
I sensed Ru doing her best looking for Tama.
But, Ru can't find Tama...
She'll never find me...
...because the bad Tama isn't
the Tama that Ru knows...
That's why, even if Tama
became human, Ru can't find me...
Tama can't be friends with Ru...
That's why Tama broke
the promise with Ru...!
I...
I want... everyone who became LRIGs...
...to be returned to their world!
That's my... one and only wish!
Tama...
...needs to make Ru's wish come true.
Thank you for accompanying me.
I'll take my leave here.
Okay, until next time.
I know it's weird for me to say this, but...
...don't get involved in
Selector battles ever again, okay?
Yes...
Ah, anything to say, Iona?
Take care.
Lrig, you seem a lot different now
from when you were with me.
Thank you...
...and, I'm sorry.
Tama is with Mayu...
Yup.
Just when we were thinking of
meeting Mayu to speak with her...
There goes that plan.
Why?
I think the only thing that
changed was the order.
Our plan was to get a wish
while Tama and Mayu are with us.
But now, I just need to win Selector battles,
and become an LRIG to go
to the white window room.
To where Mayu and Tama are at.
There I'll speak with Mayu,
and once she understands--
No! That's too dangerous!
Like I said, it's only the order that changed.
What are you saying?!
It isn't that simple...!
I'll be with her, so it will be fine.
I'll protect Ru.
Iona...
Ah...!
That's not correct!
Huh?
We were saying "Iona" all along,
but that's not her correct name!
Oh, that's right...
I'm fine being called "Iona."
Oh, no!
Let's think of a new name for her!
Okay?
Nice! Let's get thinking!
Um...
Is there any word that you like?
Kind of like how Chiyori was saying she wanted
to be an LRIG named "Elizabethan Collar,"
or something.
Like...
Snow...
I liked... snow...
Back in the room where I was with Mayu...
Shut up...
Shut up... Shut up!
Many sounds were heard from the outside,
even when I didn't want to hear them.
But, when it snowed...
The snow got rid of all the sounds.
It hid all things.
Cold, yet kind...
...snow...
How about "Yuki," since it means "snow"?
Yuki is perfect! It has
that girly, pretty touch to it!
Yup! It even has that "cool"
factor to it that matches!
--Yup. That'll make things a lot clearer.
--Yuki...
I'm... Yuki...
I mean, it'll be confusing calling her
"Iona" when Urazoe Iona's around.
Aah! I forgot to ask Iona-san...
...about the sender who
told us where Iona-san was.
That's right!
Wow, that was stupid of us...
What's the sender's address?
Um, well... "shadow-prince"...?
Anyone know of any "shadow-prince"?
Shadow... prince...
Life...
A city of mazes with no exit
Shiro...
I understand...
A city of mazes with no exit
and the sound of bells ringing
Kuro is a bad girl, and Shiro is a good girl.
I do...
But...
Leave the "now" handed to me
...Shiro is more spiteful.
Spite... ful...?
Leave the "now" handed to me
Yes.
as I begin to walk in the morning
You're cheerful, happy, and kind...
In a world where light and dark intersect
Girls like you find happiness
and leave Mayu behind!
In a world where light and dark intersect
catharsis begins to awake
That's why I had Shiro closed away!
I swore in my shaking heart
I should have known better to have
let Shiro go to the outside world!
I swore in my shaking heart
that I won't lose anyone anymore...!
No!
Ru!
that I won't lose anyone anymore...!
Ruuu...!
Even if my tears flow tomorrow
I'll run through the wind
Release myself towards the future I selected
Kazuki, did you forget something?
to regain it
I won't give up on my wish
"This Warmth Is at Its Limit"
I accept...
You're so stupid...
Now...
...your wish won't come true...
...a new...
Now, let's begin...
Ru... please...
"That Locked Window"
That Locked Window.