After setting forth to establish a route to Shiganshina,
the Scout Regiment encountered a Female Titan
seemingly possessed of sharp,
cold-hearted intelligence.
As soldier upon soldier fell to this new foe, the
regiment retreated into a forest of massive trees.
Though to what purpose, no one appeared to know.
If the Levi Squad can't stop this thing, then who can?
Those men need us!
Another one!
Damn it, he didn't have to die!
The choice is yours. You can trust yourself,
or you can trust the people willing
to put their lives on the line for you.
I'm with you!
Fire!
Wait, what?
They're going to take her alive? Seriously?
So what do you think of us now, Eren?
We managed to outsmart the damn thing!
Let this be a lesson to you, greenhorn.
Don't ever underestimate the Scouts!
Never again! Agreed?
Agreed!
She's not putting up much of a fight.
That's no reason to let our guard down.
Good work, leading her here.
I'm more than a little impressed.
We couldn't have without the rear
contingent whose lives bought us time.
This belongs to them.
I don't intend to ever forget that.
That so?
Yes.
Because of their sacrifices,
we can expose whoever this really is.
Ten to one they're in there
pissing themselves right about now.
An Abnormal? No, she's more
like... more like the Colossal Titan!
Wait, so does that mean Commander Erwin was...?
Hey! Snap out of it, runt!
You can puzzle it all out later.
Right now we need you focused on pushing ahead.
Right!
Not quite yet, Levi. A little more insurance.
Second and third waves!
Fire!
All reserves!
They, uh... They've figured out how to climb.
I can see that. Well, if they make it up this
far we can always go up a little further, I suppose.
Anyway. I doubt we'll be here much longer.
I suspect the order to withdraw will be coming any minute.
What makes you say that? Those explosions just now?
I hope everything's alright in there.
Me, too.
Mikasa. You think that's cannon fire or what?
I mean, nothing else makes that kind of racket, right?
If that's the case, why didn't
we see them bring any cannons in?
What the hell's with all the noise? Seriously.
Gimme a hand here, Bertholdt.
You happen see what tree Christa scuttled up?
Sorry. I don't have a clue.
Nothing makes sense anymore.
What are we even doing here?
I just wanna go home.
Whaddya say we get outta the way?
Ugly bastard is really gettin' the hang of it.
At this rate, he's gonna try his
hand at buildin' a damn tree house.
The alarming thing is that this shows that they can learn.
Not a pleasant thought. Of course, they
probably all develop at different rates.
Hey, Armin. They want us keeping
these Titans outta the forest right?
I think I just figured out why.
We're here to lure that Female Titan into a trap.
C'mon. What else could it be?
It's like you said.
There's a person inside it steerin' the thing.
Commander Erwin wants to find out who.
So that was the plan from the start?
We weren't flying by the seat of our pants?
Look, I'm not complaining. I get keeping it from me.
But, come on! Keeping you guys in the dark?
You'd think you'd earned a
little more trust than that, right?
Damn, you're annoying.
I hope you're not suggesting the captain kept the
plan from us because he thinks we're a liability!
I'm sorry, but I am!
There's just no other way it makes sense!
Enough of this!
Petra! Knock the teeth out of his skull!
Look, I hate to say it, but he's got a point.
Huh?
For being as supposedly instrumental to the plan
as we were, the captain didn't give us much to go on.
So, what?
That means he doesn't trust us. Kind of a big deal.
C'mon, you guys. Think about it.
Maybe Eren isn't the only one who can change.
Maybe someone in the regiment's a Titan spy.
It's the only way all the pieces fit. You with me?
Yeah. Best explanation.
A spy? Are you sure about that?
Well, no. But I'm sure the commander believes it.
He'd have to. And I'll wager you anything the only people
in the know on this were the
survivors from five years ago.
Of course. That's got to be it.
I concur whole-heartedly. Hear that, Snivel-drop?
There was a good reason.
Right. Yes. A perfectly good reason.
It adds up.
After all, in their position, it's the best way of
narrowing down the list of
suspects to a manageable number.
Shiganshina's probably when the spy got in.
So, you think this person's
responsible for killing Sawney and Beane?
Possibly. In fact, after it happened,
the commander asked me this odd question.
What is it you think you see?
Who do you think the real enemy is here?
So that's what he meant. Of course.
If we'd known the answer to that question, he
probably would've let us in on what was happening today.
Though, there again, I really
don't think any of us could've.
Speak for yourself, my friend. I knew.
I just decided to keep my own counsel.
Doubtless you appreciate the reason for my silence.
Which would be?
Oh, come now. Surely you all know? Dear
oh dear. Perhaps I've said too much already.
Well, one day, when you've
reached my level of expertise...
Look, we all get that you like
to pretend you're Captain Levi.
But that's not how he sounds.
If we pull this off, we might
learn what the Titans are all about.
But, even for that...
was it worth letting so many people die?
You think the commander was
wrong to leave us out of the loop?
Well he certainly wasn't in the right.
Why put so many of our lives at risk
just because one of us can't be trusted?
Hell, we could've smoked out the spy.
Maybe saved some good people.
No. He did what was necessary.
Are you seriously trying to defend him?
Do you know how many of us died so
the commander could play intrigue?
Of course I do. All I'm saying
is it's easy to judge in hindsight. At the time, though,
there was no way to know how things would turn out.
He's a commander, not a soothsayer.
He had to act on what he had. Period.
He had to choose: a handful of us, or all of us?
What would you have done?
He made a decision. He sacrificed a
hundred lives for the good of mankind.
Eren, I can understand why you still have your doubts,
but in time you'll come to realize, just like we all did,
why Erwin Smith was entrusted to lead
the Scouts and carry humanity's hope.
Or why even someone as cagey
as Captain Levi can trust him.
Indeed. Live long enough and
you'll understand the weight of it.
I may be naive but,
there's one thing I know beyond all doubt.
Genuine harbingers of change must be able to
do what others won't dare. Sacrifice their heart.
Accept the burden of doing the unspeakable.
Whether we like to admit it or not, the fact is this:
To rise above monsters, we have to abandon our humanity.
That's the irony, really.
If you can't let it go, it's not worth holding on to.
Fire!
Poor thing.
Can't so much as bat an eyelash, can we?
Must be terribly frustrating.
Get used to it, my dear.
Heh. Biology can often times be a curse.
Case in point, the more your wounds
heal, the stiffer your joints become.
Now what in the world is the hold-up
on the extraction of our esteemed guest?
It won't get any easier.
Strike while the iron is hot, I say!
An impressive ability. So she can harden
her skin to protect portions of her body.
Similar to the one who rushed Wall Maria.
The Armored Titan, I believe they called him.
The question is, how many blade strikes
would it take to finally chip our way through?
Too many, in any event. Time is short.
Yes, sir?
Prepare an artillery round. I want her hands blown off.
With all due respect, Commander,
there's a risk if we use the cannons.
The hands will get blown off, but
whatever's beneath them will too, sir.
A fine point, soldier.
Which is why you'll aim carefully
and sever them at the wrists.
On my signal I want an all-out salvo.
Yes, sir!
Knock knock. We know you're in there.
Why don't you make this easy and
come on out. Stop wasting our time.
Seriously, what can you hope to gain by stalling?
If you're thinking we'll let you go, we won't.
If you're thinking about trying to escape, don't.
All you should be thinking about
are the good men you killed today.
Not that you would.
That's not your style, is it? Remorse.
You enjoy killing.
Which means we have something in common.
'Course, I enjoy killing Titans.
But it's a start. I'm sure we
can still find some middle ground.
Oh, that's right.
While we're on that subject, let me ask.
You're okay with me cuttin' your
limbs off at the joints, right?
I mean, they'll grow back.
I'm talking about your actual body.
Don't want you dead just yet.
Timing wouldn't work.
Nicely done. I almost lost my composure.
Were those like, death throes or something?
They're coming. I can smell them.
From what direction?
From every direction. Fast. Dozens.
What the hell is this? They... They're all going in!
Why're they ignoring us all've a sudden?
Oh no.
You... You tellin' me they're all Abnormals?
Who cares? Concentrate on pushing 'em back!
Engage!
What's going on over there?
Wait! Please!
I know that sound. It used to haunt my sleep.
I'd hear it from the forest in the dead of night.
Believe me, nothing in the world
screams like that except a dying animal.
It's the sound of a creature who knows
it's got absolutely nothing to lose.
It's alright, I know to be careful.
That is not the right attitude to have!
You can't just be careful, you have to be terrified!
Have you ever seen me terrified of anything?
No! And I'm tellin' ya this'd
be a good time to try it out!
Right.
I have to give her credit.
The girl's instincts are usually dead-on.
Especially right before all hell breaks lose.
Eren's in the center rank, I think.
That's what Armin said.
Faster on the artillery, gentlemen!
Here they are. First wave's closing
from the east, and coming in fast!
Wagon defense squad! Intercept, now!
What's going on? Damn things passed right by us!
Three Titans have broken through!
Captain Levi!
Hey! What did you do?
You called up some friends, didn't you?
It ignored us and went straight for her?
The enemy is bearing down from all directions!
All hands, commence combat!
Defend the Female Titan at all costs!
No!
All hands, withdraw!
Redeploy the formation!
Return to Calaneth District!
We've been bested.
Oh, don't give me that crap.
Not now. Not yet.
Think about it. The enemy was prepared
to make sacrifices. Enormous ones.
So committed to maintaining her secret, she would
rather let herself be cannibalized than exposed.
That whole song and dance in the courtroom,
and this is what we've got to show for it.
We scurry back now with our tail between our
legs, Eren's right back in chains, or worse.
We'll jump off that bridge when we come to it.
Right now our only concern is getting
back without sustaining further casualties.
However we can.
This steam isn't helping matters.
Smoke signals aren't likely to cut through the murk.
I'll gather up my squad.
Not yet, Levi.
First replenish your blades and your fuel.
I can deal with what I've got.
We're running against the clock as it is. Why?
Because I said. That's an order.
Whatever you say, sir.
I trust you implicitly.
Withdraw? I guess we're done here.
We return to HQ on horseback.
Understood.
Hold on. You tellin' me it's over?
Ah! Thank god!
I don't like this. Eren...
That's our cue.
Alright, let's saddle up! We're going home!
Chop-chop, runt. One would think you'd be beside yourself
to get an eyeful of who's driving that gargantuan harpy.
You really think they found out who it is?
Of course, all thanks to you!
I didn't do anything.
You learned to trust the fellow members of your squad.
That's big. The sort of thing that turns
out well for everyone involved, actually.
A lesser man in your dilemma probably would've buckled.
Then where would we be?
Oh, please.
Why don't you stroke his forehead while you're at it.
We'd be exactly where we are now, without of
course having had to endure his incessant whining.
Don't wait for me to decorate your
path in pink and white rose petals.
Survive the journey home and I
might be persuaded to respect you.
The mission isn't over.
Not 'til we're though the gates.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir. I completely understand.
Oruo! Petra!
I gotta hand it to ya both. For someone who wet
themselves first time out, you've come a long way.
I thought we agreed never to speak of it again!
Whoa. Seriously?
Relax. Incidentally, I've never
once pissed myself in battle.
How dare you! I have the highest kill-count
of anyone on the damn squad! Argh! Imbecile!
You wanna hide that stain behind
your kill-counts, be my guest.
Shut your hole!
So did it, like, rain down on everyone midair, or what?
Enough! No one cares who pissed who's pants!
Focus on the job at hand!
For the record, my shorts've always been dry.
Huh?
Must be a signal from the captain himself.
Stow the chatter 'til we're home.
We'll rendezvous with Levi shortly.
Erwin. Why bother having him replenish?
There's no time.
We saw the Female Titan get eaten.
Did we actually see the person
inside suffer the same fate?
I didn't.
You mean...?
Yes. Your hypothesis is correct. This isn't over.
We're dealing with someone like Eren.
Someone who regenerates in and out of Titan form.
Suppose that person equipped
themselves with ODM gear in advance.
Suppose further that they're also
disguised in one of our uniforms?
What would their next move be?
Captain Levi?
Wait, that... That's not... Oh shit!
Gunther! You okay? What happened?
Talk to me!
How do you ferret out the enemy...
when they're one of your own?
Erwin's plan has backfired.
The dreaded Female Titan comes for Eren yet again.
But between her and her quarry
stands a team of expert Titan slayers.
The Special Operations Squad.