Irisviel...
I've lost him.
If I can't see him,
I'll sense his presence.
The chariot.
I've found you, Rider!
Rider, look.
Is someone chasing us?
Oh, so it's Saber.
Saves us the trouble of searching for her.
By the way, boy,
are those motorcycle
contraptions usually so fast?
She's on a motorcycle?
No, that's impossible.
But with Saber's Riding skill,
it could become possible.
Now, this is fun.
If that's the game,
I'll have to respond in kind.
We're landing?
Change of plans.
We'll settle our feud with a race.
Fine...
Just don't do anything stupid!
Fear not.
Nothing in Heaven or on Earth can stop me!
This isn't good.
This machine has almost reached its limit.
If I push it any more...
But I'm so close.
Invisible Air!
No way...
She's gaining on us!
She'll catch up if we don't do something!
To ride a simple machine so fast...
Wonderful.
However, this is a chariot.
It is not suited to a polite footrace.
I believe the expression is "eat my dust," Saber!
Excellent!
That is what makes you
the revered King of Knights.
A true flower of the battlefield!
Don't mock me, King of Conquerors!
Rider!
Have at you!
Irisviel isn't there?
How...
I know I saw Rider.
But then, where is Irisviel?
You thought to fool me by
pretending to be a Servant?
Rider's Master doesn't have the intelligence
gathering skills necessary to find our location.
And Tohsaka was in no position
to have tried anything.
So by process of elimination,
it had to have been the Matou
who kidnapped Irisviel.
Answer me.
Where is Irisviel?
I-I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Then, where is Matou Kariya?
Kariya?
I've no idea where that idiot is!
I don't know!
I swear I don't know anything!
He was with some guy who said he's
an observer sent by the Church.
They left this morning!
An observer?
Kotomine Kirei.
I never guessed the real Rider would appear.
A happy turn of events.
Luck seems to favor your side in battle,
Matou Kariya.
Father,
was this little trick
really worth burning two Command Spells?
Rest easy, Kariya.
Now, hold out your hand.
As long as you cooperate with me,
you are free to use your
Command Spells as you like.
Even still...
That ability to transform...
Such a Noble Phantasm is almost wasted
on the Berserker class.
There are tales of him taking on
the guises of other heroes
in his quests for victory.
So that is his limit, even when
compelled by Command Spells.
His obsession with Saber is quite remarkable.
That's enough.
Leave us, Berserker.
This woman...
Is she really the Grail's vessel?
Technically, she is its contents.
Worry not, Kariya.
I shall relinquish the Holy Grail to you.
You have yet another promise
to keep before that, Father.
Oh, that?
That is not a problem.
Come to the Fuyuki church at midnight tonight.
You'll have your chance to face Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Don't forget, Kariya.
Tonight, at midnight.
And your wish will come true.
Now, then...
We're alone.
I don't know who you are,
but it's time you showed yourself.
So you noticed me?
Of course, you are an experienced Executor.
Matou Zouken?
Indeed.
Hey, Rider...
Are we really gonna charge from here?
At this distance?
Head-on?
The sword of light she used at the river
requires a moment before its activation.
That's when we'll strike.
Why take such a crazy risk?
Precisely because it is crazy.
If she loses after all this,
she will be utterly defeated.
Perhaps she may
be convinced to join my ranks yet.
And you desire that so much?
On the battlefield, she is like
a star sitting upon the world.
But only by joining my army,
will she learn to truly shine.
He never cared
for his enemy's territory or treasure.
He wished to rule their very souls,
but without humiliating or destroying them.
That's what made him
the King of Conquerors.
All right, Rider.
Just win, however you must.
Boy, you've finally begun to
understand conquest, haven't you?
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let's go...
Via Expugnatio!
Wind!
Excalibur!
What business do you have here, Matou Zouken?
Let's see...
Basically, I've been waiting to
see what cunning trap
you'd use to break Kariya.
You would stand by and watch the
Matou lose their chance for victory?
The sight of Kariya in agony...
It just never gets old.
Victory for the Matou,
or a pathetic death for Kariya?
Such a difficult call.
Do you take such pleasure
in seeing your own son's suffering?
I thought you'd be certain to understand.
What?
You have the same smell as I do.
A creature drawn to the
rotten meat known as Kariya...
A maggot.
Oh, you've scared me.
Inexperienced or not,
you're still the Church's dog.
A man risks his life simply jesting with you.
One day, I'll see you again, kid.
Until then, be sure to nourish your true nature,
so that it may match my own.
Rider...
Sorry, boy.
I screwed up.
Rider, Ionioi Hetairoi!
I'm only willing to expend the chariot on Saber.
But still...
She's gone.
A motorcycle, eh?
Quite marvelous.
That's what you say after being defeated?
Hey, Rider...
How do we get back to town?
Well...
We'll have to walk.
I was afraid of that.
How many more days do I have?
How many more times can I fight?
I'm not done yet.
I'm not...
Tohsaka Tokiomi...
You thought you'd killed me, Tokiomi?
In your dreams.
I'll keep getting up
until I've made you pay!
Tohsaka...
What?
Kariya-kun?
Aoi-san?
No, it wasn't me!
He...
Are you satisfied, Kariya-kun?
The Matou family is guaranteed
to win the Holy Grail now.
I...
Why?
Was taking Sakura from me not enough?
You had to kill my husband
right in front of me, too?
Why?
He...
It's all his fault!
If it weren't for him...
Everyone would've been happy!
You and Sakura-chan...
You could've been happy!
Shut your mouth!
What would you
know about it?
You...
You've never even
loved anyone!
I did love someone.
Someone warm and kind.
I wanted to make her happier than anyone else.
I would've given my life for you.
That's the only reason I've
been able to endure this pain.
I've endured...
Endured, endured, endured, endured
endured, endured, endured...
Endured everything!
Don't you dare deny it all.
I won't forgive that!
Lies, lies, lies...
I definitely have someone...
There is someone I love!
Who was I fighting for?
Whose fault is this?
If I'm going to die,
I may as well...
What an awful play.
But for a first script, it wasn't a bad effort.
Well, Kirei?
Your impressions?
The taste of wine...
It's more intoxicating than I remember.
I'd say you're finally learning what it means
to broaden your horizons.
If the flavor will be this intoxicating,
I would very much like
to taste it again.
Episode 21:
Knight on a Two-Wheeled Steed
By my Command Spell, I order you...
Open your eyes, and look!
Tonight, I shall not hold back.
I must make it quick.
How are he and I different?
What are we, if not lost?!
Who am I?
Next Time:
All the Evil in the World