I'll have another coffee, please.
Um...
Actually, I...
I have a request!
A request?
Yes.
To be honest, this is something I should solve on my own,
so I have no right to ask you for help...
But please, just hear me out first!
If that's all I need to do, yeah.
Hyouka
Thank you!
Inheritors of the Classics Club and Its Circumstances
It's about my uncle. His name was Sekitani Jun.
Please help me remember what he told me!
I don't really get it.
Oh, sorry. I skipped a few details.
I'll explain things from the start.
My uncle went to India seven years ago, and nobody has heard from him since then.
Japanese man missing
Japanese man goes missing
When I was little, I was very attached to him.
He would answer any question I asked, no matter how crazy it was.
It was as if there was nothing he didn't know about.
When I was in kindergarten, I heard that he was in the Classics Club,
and I became interested in it as well.
I think it's because "Classics" sounded similar to the "candy sticks" I loved at home.
That's a really bad pun.
One day, I asked him about the Classics Club.
That was the one and only question he avoided answering.
He avoided it?
Yes. I threw a huge tantrum, and eventually he relented.
When I heard his answer, I...
You what?
I cried.
I don't know if it was because it was scary or because it was depressing, but I cried my eyes out.
You cried...
What's more, I remember my mother came running in surprise,
but my uncle didn't even try to calm me down.
It was such a big shock that I can't remember anything else.
But back when I entered junior high, I couldn't stop thinking about it.
Why did he try to dodge the question?
Why didn't he try to calm me down?
Since then,
I've done everything I could do.
Though we drifted apart from the Sekitanis, I still tried to stay in touch as much as possible.
But no matter what I do, I can't remember what it was!
So, when I started at Kamiyama High, I felt like the Classics Club was my last hope.
That's the "personal thing" you were talking about?
But I didn't know that the Classics Club was on the verge of being disbanded.
I asked the teachers, but none of them remember
what happened 45 years ago, when my uncle attended the school.
So? Why did you come to me?
Well...
Because you can solve mysteries that I can't even fathom!
Like the locked door, the library book,
and the secret club!
I just know that you'll be able to lead me to the truth!
You really shouldn't overestimate me.
That was just dumb luck.
Then let me count on that luck!
I don't want to.
You could say that this mystery
is at the core of Chitanda Eru's very life.
Do you really think a low-energy person like me would want to be responsible?
You've gotta be kidding me.
So why just me?
Surely there are other people you could talk to as well.
Many hands make light work, right?
Just ask all your friends to help.
Oreki...
I'm not the kind of person who just goes around revealing her past to everyone.
This isn't...
something I can discuss with just anyone.
Sorry.
I know I'm really asking a lot of you.
I know I shouldn't be getting you mixed up in my past.
But...
You might not be as friendly as my uncle, but you answer my questions too!
Please accept my deepest apologies for being unfriendly.
I think I might've seen something of my uncle in you.
High school lasts for three years, right?
That's more than enough time to investigate this.
I want to remember my uncle,
before he's dead.
Before he's dead?
Yes.
If someone goes missing for seven years,
they're considered legally dead.
I see.
My uncle's family wants closure as well.
They're of modest means, but they've planned a funeral.
So...
So I wanted to find out what he told me back then...
And prepare myself for the funeral, as well.
I'm sorry.
It's not like you have anything better to do, right?
I can't take on this responsibility for you.
So I can't say that I'll take on your request.
But I'll keep all this in mind,
and if I hear anything that might point you in the right direction,
I'll let you know.
If you have any trouble interpreting the clues,
I can assist you with that.
Okay.
If you can agree to those terms, I'll help you.
Thank you very much!
I'm sure you'll be able to help me!
Yeah.
Though people say high school life is colorful,
it isn't all fun and games.
For example, we have exams.
At Kamiyama High, midterms have begun.
All club activities are put on hold during the exams,
and needless to say, that includes the Classics Club as well.
We didn't do much to begin with, though,
so not a lot has changed.
Library
We probably could've kept meeting in the clubroom as usual,
but with no key available we didn't have much choice.
First Semester  Midterm Exam         Schedule
period
Contemp. Lit.     Contemp. Soc.          English I               Math A
Contemp. Lit.     Math I           World History B      Compr. Sci
Classics
First Semester Midterm Examinations
Day Two, Period Two
Mathematics I
First Semester Midterm Examinations
Day Three, Period Two
World History B
First Semester Midterm Examinations
Day Four, Period Two
Comprehensive Science
Okay, pens down!
Finally, the midterms are over... Jeez.
First Semester  Midterm Exam         Schedule
period
Contemp. Lit.     Contemp. Soc.          English I               Math A
Contemp. Lit.     Math I           World History B      Compr. Sci
Classics
Greetings.
I am writing to you from Istanbul.
A few things went wrong when I arrived, so I'm currently stuck in the Japanese consulate and haven't seen much of the city yet.
What did you do this time?
I'm really enjoying this trip!
I'm sure that ten years from now, I'll be able to look back on these days without regret.
By the way, how's the Classics Club?
Has anyone else joined?
There's one other thing on my mind, so I thought I'd better mention it.
Will you be making an anthology?
The Classics Club used to release an anthology every year at the culture fair.
Are you still doing that?
If so, you might be wondering what you need to do.
The Classics Club's prior anthologies aren't kept in the library.
You should be able to find them in the clubroom.
There's this unused medicine safe.
The back issues are in there.
It's not locked.
When I arrive in Pristina, I'll give you a call.
Greetings, Oreki Tomoe.
A medicine safe?
You couldn't have chosen a better time to tell me...
Full Grain
As all things brim with life, the world dresses in green.
Hyouka
Earth Sci. Prep. Room
Really?
Yep.
I brought the letter with me, too.
So it's in a medicine safe, is it?
It's not here, though.
That's right! I haven't seen anything like that here!
B-But then what about the anthologies? The anthologies?
Chill out, Chi.
"Chi"?
Chitanda, all she said was that the medicine safe is in the clubroom.
My sister graduated two years ago.
The clubroom has changed since then.
I see! So that's what happened!
So, do you know which room it was two years ago?
I asked our club advisor.
Apparently, it was the biology prep room.
Wow, you really did your homework!
I just took the most efficient approach.
Such enthusiasm!
Not even close.
I don't know the meaning of the word "enthusiasm".
Then, let's go!
By the way, what about Fukube?
That sew-and-sew?
He was going on about taking a sneak peek at some summer fashion thing...
Oreki!
Huh? It's locked.
Is anyone in there?
Oh, sorry.
I'd locked the door.
Are you interested in joining the News Poster Club?
Not exactly.
Is this the News Poster Club's room, then?
Yeah, pretty much.
That smell... Cologne?
Or rather... Air freshener?
So, how can I help you?
I'm the president of the Classics Club, Chitanda Eru.
You're Tougaito from Class 3-E, right?
How do you know my name?
I remember seeing you last year at the Manninbashis'.
At the Manninbashis'?
Wait a moment, would you happen to be one of the Chitandas from Kanda?
Yes. You've been a great help to my father.
Ah, please, the feeling's mutual...
I see, a Chitanda.
Why's he so tense?
So, how can I help you?
Right! We heard the Classics Club's old anthologies were being kept here in the biology prep room.
Biology Prep. Room
This used to be the Classics Club's room, right?
Oh... Oh, right. I think it was when I was a first-year student, yeah.
So...
So would you happen to know anything about the anthologies?
No... No.
I see. Thank you very much.
Hold on!
Sorry, but they have to be in here somewhere!
Please, let us look for them!
Sorry, but like I just said, they're not here.
But...
Well, let's be off.
Wait!
Don't you think it's weird?
I do.
Then stick around!
I'm sorry, but you'll have to look somewhere else.
But we heard that they were here!
If we can't find them here, we'll have to search the entire school!
The entire school? That's out of the question.
Please let us in!
Just for a minute!
Please.
I'd prefer not to let outsiders in.
No offense, but this is a classroom first and a clubroom second!
And you are?
Ibara Mayaka from the Classics Club.
Very well.
You can take a look inside.
Just don't make a mess.
One day, one article!
Where are the other club members?
They're on break today.
I was just thinking about what to put in the June issue.
It's called the Kami High Monthly.
It has quite a history. We're nearing the 500th issue, in fact.
Looks like it's not here either.
I see. That's too bad...
What should we do,
Oreki?
Tougaito,
did anything get moved around when you switched clubrooms?
Now that you mention it, we had to carry a few cardboard boxes.
Cardboard boxes?
Yeah.
Which means...
The tricky part would be getting to it, though.
Let's give this guy a good shake and see what falls out.
We're sorry, but there's so much stuff in this room
that it'd take ages for us to look through it all.
I'd like to ask our club advisor
to help us give it a more thorough search.
Is that okay?
No.
I told you not to make a mess.
But this is the only lead we have!
We'll take full responsibility for returning everything to the way it—
I said no!
But...
I'm busy!
I don't care about your thorough search!
Your anthologies aren't here!
You got that? Get outta here!
Bingo.
We're after what's in the medicine safe.
What?!
The anthologies are supposedly in there.
That's all we need. No skin off your back, right?
Either way, we have things we need to do in the library right now,
so if you should happen to find the anthologies after we've left,
we'd be grateful if you could bring them to the earth science prep room.
It isn't locked.
Y-You...
What do you think you're...
What do I think?
Very well.
If I find them, I'll bring them to you.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Hey, first-year.
You haven't introduced yourself yet.
Oreki Houtarou.
I apologize.
Hey, Oreki.
Why are we waiting here?
To save energy.
Oh, come on.
By the way, Chitanda.
What is Tougaito's family famous for?
Well...
They're quite well-known in the field of junior high school education.
Many people from their family work in education, in fact.
I see.
It's been five minutes.
Shall we head back?
Earth Sci. Prep. Room
Look what we have here.
Hyouka
No 28
Kami
yama
High
School
Classics
Club
It's the anthologies!
Hey, Oreki, what just happened?
Did you do something?
Just a bit of blackmail.
Blackmail?
Ibara,
Is targeted!
can you keep a secret?
Huh?
If you tell me not to talk about it, I won't.
I see.
Then, let's start from the beginning.
When Tougaito came out of that room, he was clearly wary of us.
That's true.
How about inside the room?
The windows were open and he had the fan turned on,
but from that position the papers on the desk were almost blown away.
He wanted to air out the room.
Exactly.
But why did he want to air out the room?
Or rather,
why would he lock the door and set up an infrared sen—
Wait a moment!
What are you talking about? What infrared sensor?
There were these tiny boxes on the corridor walls that I hadn't seen before.
And if that gadget with an antenna in the room was the receiver,
then it must have been set up to alert him when someone passed by.
How did you figure that out?
Just a guess based on the situation.
But why would he take so much care to start airing out the room
as soon as someone passed by?
To clear out a smell?
Most likely.
He also smelled of air freshener.
What smell would he want to cover up that badly?
Tobacco, right?
The heir of a family famous in the field of education
couldn't allow anyone to find him smoking illegally.
I see.
Though, if Chitanda didn't have a cold, she would've smelled it right away.
But wait,
where were the anthologies, then?
In the medicine safe, of course.
O-re-ki!
I-I'm not making fun of you.
The medicine safe was under that home-made table.
I guess he must've been hiding his smokes and lighter in there too.
That's why he panicked when I suggested
getting a teacher involved in the search.
You're really weird.
Come on,
I'm as average as they come.
Hey guys!
I'm a sunflower!
Satoshi,
we found the old anthologies.
Whoa, really?
So that's how they look!
This one's forty years old, so does that mean it was written by hand?
What's wrong, Chitanda?
Nah, they probably printed it with a mimeograph.
Or in other words, a cyclostyle. It was invented in the late 19th century..
What's wrong?
I doubt the school would have had a photocopier during the 1970s.
Oreki...
Look, this one was photocopied...
Come here...
I see...
This is it.
"Hyouka".
Issue number two.
This is what I found back then.
I brought it to my uncle
and asked him what it was.
You remembered?
Please read it.
Hyouka
There is something in here that has to do with my uncle.
Something happened 45 years ago in the Classics Club.
"And so, this year the culture fair has come once again.
One year has passed since Sekitani left us.
The year that he began as a hero and finished as a legend.
The battles he fought, the sacrifices he made,
and the smiles he shared
will all be carried along by the river of time, into the distant past.
But that is how it should be.
It is not something meant to be remembered.
It was nothing even close to an epic.
And as it loses all subjectivity,
it all becomes part of the classics, as per the rules of historic perspective.
One day we too will just be classic literature on someone's shelf.
October 13, 1964. Kooriyama Youko."
The year before that was 45 years ago.
Which means that the Sekitani mentioned there was my uncle.
Sekitani
Whatever it was that he told me, it was related to the Classics Club as well.
Then it's all right now, I guess?
But I can't remember what it was!
It's...
It's so close!
What did he tell me that day?
What happened to my uncle 45 years ago?
Then why don't you investigate it?
It says right there that it shouldn't be remembered!
What if I find out something I never wanted to know?
There are things in the world best left forgotten, right?
Even things from 45 years ago?
Does that matter?
It does.
As it says here:
"It all becomes part of the classics, as per the rules of historic perspective."
It's already in the past..
If you want to look into it further, this article refers to the previous year.
So why not just check the first issue—
Hey, what's going on?!
The first issue is the only one that's missing!
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time:
Past Days of the Classics Club and Its Glory.
Past Days of the Classics Club and Its Glory