The fairy had been turned into a shard, but the world of illusion,
located in places of Negi’s memories has not disappeared, and has not come back to the real world!
There’s some other magic power different from a fairy’s that’s pullin’ the strings here.
You guys be careful.
Please make sure you don’t touch or move anything.
Okay!
Ane-san!
Asuna-san!
YOU RETARD!
No time to be laughing.
by Hakase
Scary!
He looks pretty strong!
When it comes to opponents, it’s no-holds-barred, aru!
Then don’t leave us out.
Don’t push it!
Please don’t! These are monsters you’re dealing with!
Alright!
Takahata-sensei!
Takamichi!
La
lac
Spiritus!
Where are we?
We've teleported from the castle.
Eva-chan, you’re so cool!
Desu!
That was nothing.
Takamichi…
Ah, I-I’m fine.
Takahata-sensei…
Hmph! Clumsy…
To think you were hit by your own arrow. You fail as a mage.
What are you doing?
Takahata-sensei risked his own life and body for us; what’s with you!?
Apologize this instant!
I saved you, so what’s your problem!?
What’re you doing!?
In any case, you're the one who opened that weird door!
Zip it! It’s only obvious that you’d open a door if it looked weird!
Please stop it, you two!
Stop it…
STOP IT RIGHT NOW!
Negi-kun…
I-I’m sorry… for raising my voice…
That looks painful…
Well?
It’s pretty deep. You should let it rest.
Takamichi… it’s all my fault.
If only I didn’t turn into this, then I’d be able to help you with my magic!
Negi-sensei…
OH YEAH! Yeah, it just might work!
Aniki! You might be able to turn back into a human!
Really, Chamo-kun?
I can’t say anything about it until we try, but...
there’s a possibility.
What is it?
What should we do?
Spill!
Tell us, Chamo-kun!
Provisional contracts.
Provisional… contracts?
You mean us?
Yeah, everyone in Class A should make a provisional contract with Aniki!
And when everyone becomes his partner, the fact that you saw him use magic will be nullified!
Will that be easy enough?
Isn’t that too easy?
I guess so, huh?
Yeah, Chamo-kun…
But still, we may not have a 0% chance, de gozaru.
Kaede-san…
I think so, too, Negi-kun.
Shichimi-kun, what do you have to say about it?
It’s never happened before, so I can’t say much about it, mya.
Basically, it's worth the try, right?
Takamichi…
Well, if I have to exchange a provisional contract with Negi-sensei, I wouldn’t mind.
How do you exchange a provisional contract?
Tell me.
Um, that’s… uh…
That’s so easy! You just gotta kiss him is all!
Eh?
Yup, gotta kiss him!
Kiss?
Yup! Kiss!
KISS!?
Oh? Was it something I said?
Of course it was.
A kiss with… Negi-sensei?
My, how wonderful!
Um, can’t you get Negi-sensei to return to normal for just a second?
I don’t think that’s possible.
I’m sorry, Iinchou-san.
I’m just a chupacabra.
Negi-sensei! No, don’t think that!
Whether or not you’re a chupacabra, Negi-sensei is still Negi-sensei!
It’s too late to fake it now…
Alright, let’s give this a shot, then!
Let’s exchange those contracts! Come on!
You guys…
What’s wrong?
Well, a kiss is um…
Agreed.
Aru.
Come on, you guys! Don’t you want Aniki to return to normal!?
Of course we want to, but…
A kiss is…
Yeah…
No way!
Jose.
And it goes something like that.
You guys… You’re right. I apologize for saying something that can’t happen.
Chamo-kun, let’s think of an alternative.
Aniki…
A pursuer?
Motsu.
I have come back ashamed, in a good way.
Oh well, I guess that’s it.
IT’S BACK!!
Negi!
Asuna!
Asuna-san!
Negi-kun!
It’s no use!
My power…
Stubborn scoundrels.
La
lac
Spiritus!
Now!
Run now!
But, Negi-sensei’s-!
Do you think this is the right time to say that!?
We gotta run away. Hurry!
Run away~
Go now! I’ll be fine!
Negi…
Hurry!
Asuna, let’s go!
I’ll come back to save you for sure!
Asuna-san…
Negi!!
Asuna-san!!
Negi!
Thus, Negi is captured!
Amenhotep.
The fighting spirit, the spirit, I say!
F-Fighting spirit?
So kisses are all about that, aru?
Of course not!
What are you talking about, Asuna-san!?
A kiss is like a fighting spirit, Iinchou!
Idiot.
Asuna, I also don’t think that’s what it’s about.
What are you saying, Konoka?
I’m trying as hard as I can to persuade them so they’ll exchange provisional contracts, so don’t butt in on it!
Okay, but there’s no fighting spirit in kissing.
Well then, what am I supposed to say?
You got an alternative to this?
I do.
Leave it to me.
Guys, about that kiss.
It’s love.
“Love”??
LOVE!?
“Love”… that’s really bold. Actually, it’s too bold, Kono-chan.
Brats, all of ‘em.
Pasta.
On the other hand, here too.
Basically, you’ll turn into an adult!
Desu!
Turn into...
and adult?
Quick to take the bait.
Seems like they’ll be able to make the provisional contracts, de gozaru.
That’s why you guys...
gotta exchange a contract and become adults, too, desu!
Question!
What is it, Chizuru?
So where on your body have you matured?
Ah! I wanna know, I wanna know!
Gack!
Um… uh…
here…
Ochazuke.
And here as well.
Yes, for example…
The thin rays of sunshine through the morning fog, and the birds of the forests are all presenting their blessings to me.
What’s she talking about?
Chirp, chirp, chirp! Good morning, little birdie!
Is this going to go well?
In this scenario, it would if we had a miracle.
Will there be a miracle!?
Oneechan.
It’s so roomy! Amazing!
Oh that’s right; this is your first time coming here, Anya.
Eh? You’ve been here before, Negi?
Yeah, I’ve been here with Oneechan once before.
In this castle, they say even Her Majesty has stopped by in the past...
And at that time, all of Wales’ nobles had gathered, and a grand ball was held in this big room, and…
I know that much!
I remember now!
This is the second time I’ve been here!
Really, Anya?
Yes, the second time! I remember now!
This is really her first time. She says it because she’s in front of you.
Ah, I see.
What’d you say?
No, nothing.
What!? Why are you laughing!?
I told you, it’s nothing!
You’re doing it again!
Why are you laughing, Negi!?
Uh, well…
What is it!? Tell me right now!!
Um… it’s nothing!
Hey, wait up, Negi!
I told you to wait up!
Wait up, dang it!
Xiao Long Bao.
Konoka-san, it’s for love, right?
Yup, it’s for love, Iinchou!
It’s for love? Ah, love…
I’m coming for you, Negi.
Do not move.
If you value your life, pose as Sumo-sans do.
Dosuko~i!
Yes, like that, "Dosuko~i!"...
Hey, hey, don’t do it for real, Ane-san?
Dosuko~i!
Dosuko... huh!
Chamo-kun!
Heh. Surprised?
You guys!
So you came after all!
Yup! It’s for love!
You’re pretty obedient, Ane-san!
You were all, “Dosuko~i”!
Just die!!
World of Illusion Animal Abuse!
We’re pretty far up!
I’m dizzy.
Oh well, this means that we have no other choice.
We can’t backtrack or anything…
You got no choice but to do it!
Yeah!
They’re strong...
despite that they can’t even use a single magic spell.
Alright, we’re goin’ in!
YEAH!!
They’re all a bunch of idiots.
A doll.
Get him, Chachamaru!
Yes, Master.
Alright!
Spiritus!
Negi!
Asuna-san!
Alright, let’s get to those provisional contracts!
Provisional contracts? Does that mean you’re all okay with it?
That’s how it turned out.
It’s for love, Negi-kun!
It’s for… love?
So it seems.
The castle’s-!
This isn’t good!
Aiyah! The way out!
What do we do?
Okay, if it winds down to this…
So you had that in mind?
Well, what’s “that” then?
Don’t tell me we’re gonna-!
Exchange the contracts from the sky, Negi!
Got it!
Aww, how unreasonable!
Don’t worry about it. When the time comes, Evangeline will do something about it.
That all depends on my mood.
Alright, I’m gonna jump!
W-Wait a second, saying that is easier said than-!
We’ve got no choice, aru!
It looks like it!
Here it goes!
Alright, who’s first?
Me, of course! Please excuse me, Negi-sensei.
Okay, NEXT!
Hey, wait!
Next is Kuu Laozi, aru!
Go on, Maki-chan!
W-Wait, my heart isn’t-!
Everyone! Go!
Whoa! You can see Sayo-chan now!
Eh? Really!?
Whoo hoo! Yay for provisional contracts!
I’m so happy!
Who’s she?
You did it, Aniki!
And with that I say, “Provisional Contracts, All Complete!”
Welcome back.
Asuna-san!
Welcome back~
You guys… thank you so much!
What’s wrong, Iinchou?
I have failed!
If only I kissed last, I’d be able to kiss Negi-sensei’s face, but no, I had to kiss the chupacabra Negi-sensei.
No matter how much I regret it, it still won’t be enough!
I-Iinchou-san…
Then why don’t you just kiss him again?
Well, um…
The castle-!
Takamichi!
No, it’s not me.
Don’t look at me!
Black Rose Baron…
You…
Why?
So you’re not an enemy?
That, I cannot answer.
But aside from that, hurry.
Nodoka-san!
O-okay!
Partner: Miyazaki Nodoka. Show me the power within you!
Contract, Activate!
Please God; give me a Rare Card…
Alright! A Rare Card!
Nodoka-san! Please find out how to erase this world of illusion!
Okay.
I got it!
There are two ways.
The first is to erase the fairy.
The second is to-
An incantation, huh?
At the axis where Light and Shadow join,
the reflected dream has told all till the end…
Turn back into the mountain of dust;
your path shall be the great land!
Tel
ma
Amoris!
We’re back.
We’ve come back.
Alright! We’re back!
Baron…
Hey, wait a minute!
Over there!
N-no way!
T-the school…
At that moment, Negi has exchanged provisional contracts and turned back to normal,
but another problem awaited Negi and company!
Exactly where will these plot twists continue? Sit back and wait till next time!
The title “sniper” probably came from a bird that was very good at escaping…
Next Time: “There’s a Rising Commotion as to How Everyone Will Get Along in Unexpected Situations,” by Mana.
“How Will Everyone Get Along?” by Zazie.
“15 Points,” by Mana.
A Magnificent Success!
The Baka Rangers Side Story: Go Go Baka Pink!