Rider...
Why break through the shutter, you fool?
Couldn't you just dematerialize,
the way you did when you entered?
If I'd dematerialized,
I couldn't have carried these out.
Don't get so worked up.
You make it sound like I'm some sort of thief.
If you're not a thief,
then what are you?
There's a big difference.
A common burglar simply sneaks away,
under cover of darkness,
but he who departs the battlefield
singing a song of victory
is a conqueror!
Fine, whatever...  Just go!
Go on, get lost!  Get out of here!
Okay, then I entrust the items
into your care.
Don't drop them, okay?
Why did things turn out like this?!
T-The summoning went perfectly.
How did I end up doing this?
World Atlas
Homer's
Odyssey
What do we need these books for, anyway?
To prepare for war, as I said.
You cannot enter battle
without a map of the terrain.
Hey, boy...  Where are
Macedonia and Persia?
Don't address me like that!
I'm your Master―
I am aware that you are my Master...
Did I not form a pact with you?
Anyway...
I asked you where my former kingdom lies.
Around here, I guess.
It's so small!
To think, that's all the land I worked so hard to rule.
Incredible...  My heart thunders!
Now, boy, where on this map
are we right now?
Over here.
Ah, the other side of the
great round continent.
Invigorating!
It's settled.  My compass of war
has decided our course.
Compass?
We'll start by going halfway around the world.
We head west...  Due west!
And we conquer every country
that falls in our path!
And when I make my triumphant
return to Macedonia,
I'll hold a great celebration,
in honor of my resurrection.
Does it not inflame your heart?
Have you forgotten why you're here?
To fight for the Holy Grail!
The Grail!
Right, I must question you about that.
How do you intend to use the Grail, boy?
W-Where did that come from?
What concern is it of yours, anyway?
If your goal is also to rule the world,
that would make us enemies.
There is no room for two rulers.
Rule the world?
A-All I...
All I want is to be treated fairly.
I want to force those Clock Tower idiots
to acknowledge my talent,
and change their methods.
You think too small!
Small, narrow, and pointless.
The grand dream you fight for
amounts to nothing but others' validation?
And you are my Master?
I'm utterly disgusted!
If having others respect you
is truly of such importance...
...you should ask the Grail to make you taller
by another thirty centimeters.
This lowly Servant...
I'll show you!
I'll use a Command Spell.
You will obey the rules of the Grail,
Lord of Asia, Iskandar!
Calm down, Waver.
A Master receives only three Command Spells
to force his Servant's obedience.
If I use all three,
I won't be able to control him anymore.
All I care about is getting the Holy Grail.
After that, you're free to do whatever you—
Enough!
I'll get you the damned Grail.
You seem pretty sure of yourself,
but do you actually have a plan?
You wish to see what I am capable of?
O-Of course I do.
Prove to me that I can count on you!
With this strike, I, Iskandar,
Lord of Asia, claim this land!
A gift, originally given to King Gordias,
from Zeus himself.
This must be the reason
I was summoned as a Rider.
If you desire the Grail,
locate some of the other Heroic Spirits.
Until then, I shall stare
at those maps, attempting to
stave off boredom.
Now, are you satisfied?
Okay, I'll be first today, for sure.
Found one.
No way!  Where, where?
I couldn't have missed it!
The day's first walnut bud.
I'm on the board first.
I-I'm not gonna lose!
Oh, there's one!
I found one, too.
Your dad found his second.
Hey, that isn't a walnut, is it?
Actually, it's called a wingnut.
It's a cousin to the walnut.
So it still counts as a walnut bud, see?
No fair!
No fair, no fair, no fair!
You're cheating, Kiritsugu!
I have to.  It's my only shot at winning.
If you keep cheating,
I won't play with you anymore, Kiritsugu!
Oh, I don't want that!
I apologize.  I'm sorry...
Promise you won't cheat again?
I promise.
Okay.
Then we'll play again.
The champion will answer
your challenge anytime.
I am honored...
my princess.
Whee!  I'm up high!
What are you looking at, Saber?
I was watching your daughter and Kiritsugu
playing in the woods.
Does it surprise you?
I was under the impression
that my Master was a
cold, ruthless man.
I can't blame you.
If this is my Kiritsugu's true nature,
I fear he may be disappointed to be my Master.
There is nothing funny about that, Irisviel!
I apologize.
Actually, I wondered if you were still
upset over what happened
at the summoning.
A little.
I understand that I had pretended to be a man,
but there was no reason for you both
to be as shocked as you were.
I know, but there was no helping it.
The stories about you, about King Arthur,
are known worldwide.
Perhaps Kiritsugu...
thought less of me,
upon learning that I am a woman.
He'd never think that.
But...
Yes.
He was upset, but over another matter.
What was it?
I think, maybe...
He was angered by the
people around you.
The ones who cruelly forced a young girl
to become a king.
They had no choice.
When I drew the sword from the stone,
I accepted my destiny.
Perhaps your resignation to
your fate bothered him
all the more.
I have no need for his sentiment.
He hasn't the right
to say anything about the choices made
by those of my era, including me.
That is why he has kept his silence.
He fears Emiya Kiritsugu and the hero Arturia
can never see eye-to-eye.
He may have already given up on trying.
Both Kiritsugu and you wish to use
the Holy Grail's power
to save the world, correct?
Yes, although in my case,
I merely parrot his wish.
I would use the Holy Grail
for the same purpose.
I wish to save Britain, the homeland
I was unable to protect alone.
I believe that you and Kiritsugu are
fighting for a noble cause.
You should take pride in it.
Fill, fill, fill, fill...
Repeat it four times...
Or was it five?
As each is fulfilled, so must it be destroyed...
Right?
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill.
Next, a report on the Fuyuki City serial murders.
Okay!
There we go, five times.
All right?
Police are reporting
that in each of the three known incidents,
designs resembling magic sigils drawn with the victim's blood were found at the scene.
Guess I've made a bit of a scene...
We will interview a criminal psychologist about what these magic sigils might mean―
Do you believe in demons, kiddo?
The newspapers and magazines say
I'm a demon.
But if demons really exist, calling me one
would be pretty rude, don't you think?
On that note, let just say...
What's up?
I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke, a demon!
Or maybe I shouldn't have said my name.
So, I found this...
It was hidden in my family's storehouse.
Might be some kind of ancient document.
Turns out my ancestors
were researching how to summon demons.
So obviously, I've gotta find out for myself
whether demons really exist.
Now, on the off-chance I actually
summon a demon,
I'd be a total jackass if all I had to offer
was a cup of tea and a
hearty handshake, right?
That's where you come in, kiddo.
If a demon does show up,
let him kill you, okay?
How would a real live demon kill his victim?
This is a critical experiment!
Ow...
What's this?
I ask you...
What summoner has called me, sought me,
drew the Caster class to this object?
I ask your name.  Tell me...
Who are you?
Um...
I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke.
I do odd jobs,
and my hobby is serial killing.
I prefer kids and young women.
Very well.  The pact is made.
I, too, have a wish to ask of
the Holy Grail that you seek.
We will hunt down that sacred chalice,
and we will claim it for ourselves.
Holy Grail?
Whatever.  How about grabbing a drink?
Or are you hungry?
Whoa!  Is that human skin?
There's no need to be scared, child.
Can you stand?
Now, child...
You can leave through that door.
I trust you'll be okay alone?
Yeah.
Hey, what's...
Fear is best when it is fresh.
Scare a victim over and over,
and their emotions will slowly,
but surely, shut down.
True terror must be constantly reinvented.
It is the very moment at which
hope becomes despair...
Does this please you?
The taste of fresh fear and death...
Coooool!
That was awesome!
You are so cool!
Okay!
I dunno what that Holy Grail deal is,
but I'm with you, man!
Let's paint the town red!
Show me more of your awesome killing style!
I've gotta see more!
Your name is Ryuunosuke, correct?
I feel blessed to have been
summoned by a Master
who understands me as you do.
Finally, I can hope my wish will be granted.
Oh, yeah...  You haven't told me your name.
My name?
Let me think...
What name would be suitable for me in this era?
For the time being,
you may call me Bluebeard.
I heard from the Church
that the seventh Servant,
Caster, has appeared.
The final Servant has been
summoned, and so it begins.
Indeed.
Let us not waste time.
I'd like you to go to the Tohsaka manor.
And?
With your abilities, the magic barrier
that fortifies the Tohsaka manor
should be next to nothing.
Are you certain?
I thought you and Tohsaka Tokiomi were allies.
Do not concern yourself with that.
You have nothing to fear,
even should you end up facing Archer.
I have nothing to fear from Archer,
one of the three knight classes, as you say.
Do not fail me.
Your first mission is the assassination of Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Disgraceful.
You dirty little worm.
Who said you could raise your head?
I have...
nothing to fear
from him?
You're not even fit to look at me.
A worm should die as it lives,
crawling in the dirt.
Episode 2
The Fake First Shot
The fourth Holy Grail War is beginning.
What a hopeless sneak attack.
Where did she go?
Now I'm getting pumped!
You did well to make it here.
Secure the victory!
I shall.
Next Time
Fuyuki City