Hey.
Here, this...
As always, thank you truly.
Sayaka, you're a natural at finding rare CDs, you know.
That sort of thing is just good luck. Definitely.
This person's performances are truly amazing.
Do you want to listen too, Sayaka?
I–Is it okay?
Honestly, I want to listen through speakers, but...
this is a hospital, you know.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 3
Nothing Is Scary Anymore
★ Tiro・Finale!! ★
Man... Mami-san really is cool, you know!
Sheesh... this isn't a show, though.
I don't want you to forget to be aware of how dangerous this is.
Yes!
It didn't drop a Grief Seed, did it?
Because that was a familiar that split off from a witch.
They don't carry Grief Seeds.
It wasn't a witch, then...
Somehow... we keep failing at this part, don't we?
Even a familiar can't be left alone, though.
Since when they mature, they'll grow into a witch like the one from which they originally separated.
Come, let's go.
Did you two find anything to wish for?
You, Madoka?
Well, it's that kind of thing, you know.
Especially if you're told to think of something immediately.
Mami-san, what kind of wish did you ask for?
No, um... I don't have to hear it no matter what...
In my case...
I simply did not have room to consider it.
That doesn't mean I regret it.
I think my current way of life... is greatly preferable to dying in that place.
But you know, I want girls with room for a proper choice to think about precisely what they want.
Because that's something I couldn't do... right?
Hey, Mami-san...
If your wish isn't for your own benefit, is it forbidden?
Eh?
For example... this is just an example scenario, okay?
If there's a person who's troubled to a greater extent than someone like myself,
and my wish was used for that person's benefit...
Is this about Kamijou-kun?
D–Didn't I say it was just an example scenario!?
It isn't particularly necessary for the person who's contracting to be the target of the wish, you know.
It isn't an unprecedented situation, either.
But what you're saying isn't too admirable.
If you're granting another person's wish, then that's all the more reason to think clearly about your own desires.
Miki-san... do you want his dream to be fulfilled?
Or do you want to be the one who fulfills his dream?
Mami-san...
They seem the same, but are completely different.
These things.
I think saying it like that was a bit cruel.
I'm sorry, but I had to say it now while I had the chance.
Since if you move forward while mistaken about that, you will surely regret it.
That's right.
My thoughts were naïve.
Sorry.
In the end... this really is a difficult thing, isn't it?
You shouldn't decide in a hurry.
For me, the sooner the better, though.
That's no good.
Girls hate guys who rush them.
In the end, this really isn't something simple, is it?
I am not allowed to rush you from my position.
Giving advice is also a violation of the rules.
I wonder if it's not good to simply want to become one...
Madoka, do you long for the power itself?
No, that isn't it...
I wonder if it is, though...
I am slow, and I have no redeeming qualities.
So if I could become someone like Mami-san, who's cool and wonderful...
That alone would bring me enough happiness, or something.
Madoka, if you became a magical girl, you'd be far stronger than Mami.
Of course, it's also based on what kind of wish you make when contracting, but...
Madoka, measuring the size of the Soul Gem you might produce is impossible, even for me.
This is my first time meeting a girl that holds such a natural gift.
Sheesh, what're you saying? That's a lie, right?
No—
Madoka, are you awake?
Yeah, what's wrong?
I'm ho—
Again?
Really, already...
W–Water...
That bamboo screen baldy...
If you want to drink, then pour one for yourself!
I'll tear it off, with a comb!
Thank you.
Should I make hot cocoa?
It'll be completely clean.
You listening?
Yeah, please.
Why does Mama like her job so much, I wonder?
A dream from long ago to work at that company, or something... didn't exist, did it?
Hmm... Mama doesn't like her job, she likes persevering.
Eh?
I think there are a lot of displeasing and tough things, but...
The feeling of satisfaction you get after overcoming those things is the greatest treasure for Mama.
So, working at a company wasn't her dream, you know.
Nevertheless, Mama is trying to live in her own ideal way.
Dreams can be fulfilled in that way too.
The very way you live can become your dream?
I think how you feel about it is up to each individual person, but...
As for me... I love that part about Mama.
I can respect it, and take pride in it.
She's a wonderful person, you know.
Yeah.
You understand, right?
You have involved ordinary, unrelated people in danger.
The two girls were chosen by Kyubey.
They're not unrelated anymore.
You are guiding both of them to become magical girls.
That's the reason you're not amused?
Yeah, it's bothersome.
Especially Kaname Madoka.
I see... You've noticed it as well, then?
That girl's characteristics.
That girl alone... I cannot allow her to form a contract.
Because an opponent stronger than yourself will be a nuisance?
That's the way a bullied child thinks, you know.
I don't want to fight with you, though.
If that's so, make an extensive effort to see that we never meet again.
I think tonight will surely be the last time that this will end with just a discussion.
Yo. Sorry for the wait.
Huh? You couldn't meet with Kamijou-kun?
Somehow, it looks like today's circumstances were bad, you know.
Even though I came especially for him... Pretty rude, isn't it?
What's wrong?
Over there... there's something...
It's a Grief Seed!
It's about to hatch!
Unbelievable! Why in a place like this?
This is bad. We have to escape quickly!
A barrier will be completed soon!
That labyrinth again?
Madoka, have you asked Mami-san for her cell phone number?
No.
This is bad.
Madoka, go ahead of me and retrieve Mami-san.
I'll watch over this thing until it's finished.
That's...!
Too absurd!
There is still time before the witch inside emerges,
but when the barrier closes, you won't be able to come outside!
I'm not sure if Mami's help will make it here in time...
When that barrier is completed, you'll end up losing this thing's whereabouts, right?
I can't leave it alone... in a place like this.
Madoka, go on ahead of us and come back.
I'll stay close to Sayaka.
If Mami comes this far, then she'll understand my position via telepathy.
If Sayaka and I stay here and watch over the Grief Seed, we'll know the shortest path through the barrier,
and then we'll be able to guide Mami.
Thank you, Kyubey.
I'll... bring Mami-san back here immediately, then!
Is it scary, Sayaka?
That's, well... of course, right?
All you need to do is decide on a wish,
and I can turn you into a magical girl right here and now, though...
Operating
Yeah.
If the time comes, I might have to rely on you.
But right now, I won't.
It's something really important to me, so...
If I do it, I don't want to make a decision with half-hearted feelings.
Here, right?
(Kyubey, what's the situation?)
(We're still all right.)
(There aren't any signs that it will hatch immediately.)
(Sayaka-chan, are you okay?)
(I'm fine, I'm fine.)
(Bored enough to fall asleep.)
(Actually, it'd be worse if you stimulated the egg by carelessly using large magical powers.)
(Since you don't need to hurry, could you come as quietly as possible?)
(Understood.)
I'm glad we made it in time.
I want to get mad at you for being too rash in doing this, but...
This time, you made the right decision.
With this, any worries about letting the witch get away are—
I stated it before, right?
That I don't want to see you again.
I'll cut down the game this time.
You two need to withdraw.
That just won't do.
We must go meet with Miki-san and Kyubey.
I guarantee the safety of those two.
You think I'd trust you?
I–Idiot...
This isn't the time to be doing such a thing...
Of course, I do not intend to injure you, but...
If you struggle too much, no guarantees.
The witch this time presents a different situation than those guys so far...
If you behave, I'll give you a proper release on the way back.
Let's go, Kaname-san.
Okay.
Wai—
Um... Mami-san?
What is it?
For a wish, I've been thinking about various things in my own way, but...
Have you decided?
Yes. But, um...
Perhaps you'll get mad at me for thinking about it too lightly, Mami-san.
What kind of dream do you intend to have fulfilled?
For me... ever since long ago, I've never taken pride in anything like an academic subject, or had a special talent I could boast about.
Before this, I always thought that I'd surely go on forever without helping anyone else, merely being a bother.
I disliked that, yet I couldn't help it.
But I met you, Mami-san, and you showed me what it means to fight for the sake of helping other people.
When I was told that even I could do the same thing...
That made me happier than anything else.
So for me... if I become a magical girl, that will fulfill my wish!
When even someone like me can help other people,
if I can live with my chest held high...
Then that's my number one dream.
It's difficult, you know.
You get injured.
You won't have free time to fall in love or play around.
But, Mami-san, who perseveres in spite of that...
I aspire to be like you!
I'm not someone you should aspire to be...
I'm only forcing myself to put on an appearance...
Even though I'm scared and I can barely handle it, I can't go to anyone for consultation.
I can do nothing but cry alone.
It isn't a pleasant thing... to be something like a magical girl.
Mami-san, you're not alone or anything anymore.
That's right... that's right, isn't it?
Will you really fight together with me from now on?
Will you stay by my side?
Yes, if someone like me is okay.
You beat me, didn't you?
I still have a way to go before I can behave like a proper senpai, huh...
In the end, I'm a useless girl after all.
Mami-san...
But you know... since it's a lot of trouble, you should think of something for your wish.
Trouble... is it? As I thought.
A contract is a contract after all, so think of it as an opportunity to get something.
Like billionaire status, or a wonderful boyfriend.
Anything would be fine, wouldn't it?
No, that's...
Then, I'll tell you what.
If you still haven't decided on a wish after this witch is beaten,
then at that time, we'll ask Kyubey to treat us to a cake.
C–Cake?
That's right. An extravagant celebration cake of the largest size!
And then, we'll have a party with everyone.
In commemoration of Kaname-san and me becoming a magical girl combo!
I'll get a cake for being a magical girl?
If you don't like it, then properly think of something yourself!
(Mami!)
Operating
(The Grief Seed has started to move...)
(It's started to hatch. Hurry!)
Okay, understood.
I'll finish it this very day with a swift attack!
That's...!
My body feels light.
This is the first time I've fought with such a happy feeling...
Nothing is scary anymore!
I'm... not someone who's alone!
Sorry for the wait.
Ah, you made it in time...
Be careful!
It's coming!
Sorry for attacking you at a troublesome time, but I'm going to decide this at once!
Take this!
Hurray!
★ Tiro・Finale!! ★
It can't be...
You two, contract with me immediately!
Madoka! Sayaka!
Decide on your wishes!
Hurry!
That will not be necessary.
The one who'll kill this thing... is me!
That was a narrow escape from death, you two.
Burn that into your eyes.
That is what it means to become a magical girl.
Return that.
Return it!
That... that...
belongs to Mami-san!
Didn't I say to return it!? To Mami-san!
That's right. This is an item for the benefit of magical girls.
You two don't have the qualifications to touch it.
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Mami-san was a truly kind person.
In order to teach us a lesson about what kind of mental preparation is necessary to fight for an objective...
That person has...
Episode 4
Miracles and Magic Do Exist
Miracles and magic do exist.