WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is the seiyuu for 巴マミ(Tomoe Mami):
水橋かおり(Mizuhashi Kaori) - affectionately called ミズハス(Mizuhasu).
All right, well then, let's start. Um...
Um... Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika... Um...
Um...  Mahou Shoujo! Madoka Magika... Um..
(lol)
Episode 3, Nothing Is Scary Anymore commentary host, l–let me introduce myself,
with the role of Kaname Madoka, I'm Yuuki Aoi.
And...
Yes (lol), with the role of Akemi Homura (lol), I'm Saitou Chiwa.
With this kind of feeling, let's take off!
Ah, yes!
This time's guest is... (lol)
(lol)
Um...
With the role of Tomoe Mami, I'm Mizuhashi Kaori, yoroshiku.
Yes, looking forward to working with you.
Yees, looking forward to working with you.
This is more lax than I thought!
It's fine.
Yes!
Um, we got everything done at the last moment, and it was like "Can I leave the rest to you?"
Thankfully~ (lol)
Yes!
I look forward to working with you.
You said you'll introduce yourself as a host!
Because I got a message from the office saying to do it that way.
(lol)
Gotta do it~
No, no, no.
Well, there are a lot of doki-doki scenes now...
Yes.
and finally! Mami-sama!
Mami-samaaa!!! That's right!
(lol)
It's already Mami-sama now.
Thank you very much.
I don't really get why, though (lol)
Ah, right. The commentary this time needs one little warning.
Yes, yes.
(ﾟДﾟ; ) Ho っ!
For those who might've thought to listen to the commentary before the original story on this volume...
Ah, that's right.
Yes.
Mm!
Stop this. Right now.
(lol)
Please watch the original story.
Yes.
This part isn't much of a spoiler, but...
Yeah.
We might be saying some fairly sad things.
Yes.
That's right.
You might not understand why we're so gloomy.
So if you watch it first, you won't be given too many spoilers, or anything.
Yes.
Won't be given!
So how much will they get?
Yes
From here on out it gets amazing, I think.
Ne!
(lol)
That's right, ne.
Um, but... the previous volume had commentary by us too,
Yes, yes.
That was really, really fun, too.
Yes.
Right.
Yes...
Follow the title, you "Mahou Shoujo" Madoka Magika...
(lol)
Why isn't there any fun going on from here? Why is that? (lol)
mmmmm...
The cause is probably... that we're sitting in the middle of it all right now.
Yes.
(lol)
Right.
Part of it is because of our roles.
Our roles.
The opening is really cute, isn't it?
Our roles are.
(lol) Ri–(lol) Right
There are afros and stuff, aren't there?
(lol) Yeah.
It's like "When will those kind of scenes come?"
Right, when will that scene with her in the underwear happen?
(lol)
They aren't there, are they?
What's with this, the part with the highest number of happy dreams is right here! The opening.
Right!
There's enough fun right here. (lol)
Right here, it's like Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆Magika is a lot of fun.
That's right.
But there's really... Mami-san's... yeah.
Yes.
Well, "that."
(lol) Really...
Whenever I do commentary, the display it's on is so awesome.
I really understand what you mean.
You may or may not know this, but,
Yeah?
I don't have a digital TV connected or anything, just an antenna set.
Seriously?
I'm not able to see it on air.
Ahh.
Ahhh.
That's right.
Note: 白パケ(shiropake - white package) is a term that refers to media which is done being edited, however final touches (for example, multiple audio tracks or closed captions/subtitles/credits) have not yet been inserted.
So, when I receive the thing called the  shiropake, or something like the broadcast version...
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yes, yes
That sort of thing before the commercial version... I'm just really late to seeing it.
Ohh.
That's why, you know... I haven't properly caught up in watching it, and I want to "inspect" it seriously.
I'll unintentionally be inspecting it seriously.
Well, it's pretty–Ah, she's come! Mami-san!
She's come!
So cool, huh?
Super cool!
Biiiig gun, isn't it?
ξ(✿ ＞ ◡❛)ξ ▄︻▇▇〓〓     Finale!!
That's a gun, isn't it.
It's a gun.
Mami-sama fights with a gun.
Yes, yes.
Right.
And such an amazingly cool fighting style...
Big, huh?
It's kinda like the appearance of an Italian soldier.
Cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bat.
It's a smashing bat (lol)
(lol)
A golden bat.
Cool. So, I'd like to have a conversation with Mami-san since she is here,
Yes
Yes, yes.
You took auditions?
That's right.
There were a lot of people who were possible to use, but...
She... dies...
Ah, that was no good.
Ma—
Ma–Ma–Mamirareta.
マミられた(mamirareta) is a play on 食べられた(taberareta - eaten).
マミる(mamiru) from 食べる(taberu - eat) is a joke from 2ch/nicodou.
Yuuki Aoi uses a lot of netslang/etc in her speech.
It's fine, because we're lax.
D–Di–Dies
Lax! Right right.
Did you know she dies?
I had heard it, so I knew.
UUUU, is that so?
Somehow, it was established from the settei.
Mmm.
Everythi—
Why does everyone know? I didn't know anything!
Really?
(lol)
I just found out today that I was the only one who didn't know any details about that!
Really? Really?
Yeah, it was kind of all there from the outset, you know.
That's right, som—
What happens to all of the characters, and the full feeling of the main outline...
Right, right right.
mmmm
I knew what would happen and about where it would be. From the beginning.
I knew, and furthermore... somehow, they were very unusual auditions, weren't they?
That's right, ne.
Selection. They let you select.
That! That is true.
Right, right, right.
(lol) It was like "Are things like that all right"?
"There are a lot of characters, so pick one that you find special, or one that you'd like to do yourself."
Right. Yeah.
Ne!
That's right.
That's right, isn't it?
"Do as many as you'd like," and I particularly said Mami-san...
and...
"Is that okay?" but they had already left (lol)
It was your own choice?
Yes, my own choice. That's right.
Ooooooo
Ah, is that right?
Ne... In the end, Ma–"Mami-san" is kind of...
for "Mami" to be a mahou shoujo's name,
somehow, it really has that sort of image to it.
Yeah.
Ahhh!
I get that, I get that.
魔法の天使 クリィミーマミ (Mahou no Tenshi Creamy Mami) is an anime series from the 1980s.
It kind of has a "cream" feeling. (lol)
Right, right, right, right, right.
And so is エスパー魔美 (Esper Mami).
It's kind of like an Esper-san.
Esper (lol)
Somehow that's (lol), in my head "Mami" is a really mahou shoujo name.
I see, that's true!
It's true!
It piqued my interest, somehow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm, mm.
"I don't do too many onee-san type characters, so won't it be kind of fun?" is what I said.
It was that kind of self-choice.
I did some other roles, as well...
انا ذاهب الى التخلي عن هذا ال
Kyousuke-kun, and...
and one more, just who could it be!?
Who do you think it could be?
(lol)
Who could it be...
Eh? It couldn't be that white thing?
Yes, um...
White thing! The white thing that is here right now.
Yeah.
Yes, um... the QB-san that everyone loves.
I knew it! (lol)
Eh? I took it too. (lol)
I took it too!
(lol)
Looks like QB-san was a competition.
That's right.
Everyone—Everyone loves QB.
In my case, I was told I'm too stupid.
(lol)
My head is too inferior.
But well, when it actually started, I thought "Yup, this is too hard, impossible."
(*´Д`) *pant pant pant*
I was also a bit like "This seems kind of intellectual"
Right, it felt a bit like "Can I read this?"
I was too naïve!
(lol)
Ahhhh~
They said "You're too cute."
I was seriously like, BECOME A MAHOU SHOUJO!
(lol)
It's like "Do magic!"
Like "Just do magic"
It's like "Kaan"
If "This character is really smart",
well then, I might not be cut out for it.
(lol) Really...
Well, um, after properly reading the scenario, QB is... Ne.
I didn't understand the kind of position he gave off.
Right, I wasn't expecting that kind of individuality.
Right, he has a kind of cute feel.
Cute~ Cute~ Cute~
Yeah, right, right.
He doesn't say "KYUU!" or anything.
I thought that might be the case, too...
He doesn't really say anything like that, though.
Ah, this was inserted!
This was used quite a few times.
Ao-cha—
The drawing in the notebook?
That thing...
It's great, isn't it?
The person inside did a person outside's...
External use.
Foreign consumption.
(lol)
Is that right, is that so~
That's right.
I see!
I'd say "So there's stuff like that"
Yes, yes, yes.
So, during the auditions, there weren't really any "Yeah, that's OK" in one try, you were always asked to "try this" or something.
Yes.
Yeah, they said that a lot.
"Try like this, or like this." and "What if you did it more like this?"
There was a lot—There was a lot like that.
I see.
Yes.
I didn't do that many other main girls.
Ahhh.
I don't portray their image.
Ahhh~
I thought that might be the case, though.
How long would they have lived for?
The first real thing we did was probably the same for all of us, which was to record introduction lines for the homepage.
mm mm mm
Ah, right, right, right, right.
That's right, ne.
In CM breaks—Ah, no, wrong—They came out in the dialogue of the anime.
in CMs—
No, that's wrong, they probably came out before this work started—during the breaks for other works.
Right.
Ah, yes, yes, yes. That happens often.
During the time of another work.
They came out one-by-one there, about 2 months before Madoka started.
That's right, ne.
Mmm...
And then those lines were uploaded to the homepage, with some other lines, certainly.
Yes.
That's right.
That's right...
At tha—That was certainly done—At that tim—
We tightened those up.
Oh! Really?
What people see on the PC is their first impression, so isn't it important? You have to do it right.
Ah, I've also been at that for a super long time.
Yeah, you can get comprehension of situations by doing that.
Ne? You can.
It's a lot of fun, though.
Mmm.
Mm.
I'm happy I was employed for this.
Yeah, that's what I first thought too.
Ne!
This is a bit different, but your impression of a line changes a lot when it comes out in the story compared to just seeing/hearing it...
When it comes out in the story, it's like "Ah, she said this line!"
She said it!!! (lol)
It's here? (lol)
You think "So it's here!?"
Right, right.
And then there's the title, you know. This one's.
Ahhhhh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
All the episode subtitles are said. Mmm.
She says it.
"Nothing is scary anymore."
ahhh~
(lol)
Ahhh why was she Mamirareta'd (´；ω；`)
Really, now...
That's right, after episode 3 was over...
Really, tension raised inside of us, and you'd say "Getting cocky is dangerous."
Yes.
Dangerous. (lol)
マミるぞ(Mamiruzo) - from 食べるぞ(To eat)
In this context, she's screaming it as if to say "You'll be eaten!"
You end up saying ＼Mamiruzo!／＼Mamiruzo!／, you know.
Mamiraretta! It's dangerous, it's dangerous!
When something like that happens, it puts up a flag, doesn't it?
That's right.
(lol) Dejected.
Somehow, "Mamirareru" became pretty popular among the public.
2ch
Mou!
(lol)
This is a bit scary, you know...
It's like "I want to Mamirareso my part-time job" (lol)
All the way until the end, my... "friendly terms" or, what would you say, with Mami-san...
If it wasn't obvious, she's referring to Homura as herself here.
This will happen often in seiyuu commentary.
Relatively speaking, we don't really talk to each other. So this scene is a bit meaningful, huh? For these two. Meaningful scene.
We're on unfriendly terms...
That's right...
Mm.
That's why I want to do stuff where we get along...
Ah...
There's a little bit of that in the conversation earlier...
Ah!
The drama CD that comes with this.
Right!
The drama CD that comes with this—
Eh? This? Eh? The previous volume's?
Ah, no, the one that came with the previous volume,
Previous volume. Mmm.
On that drama CD... well, it's a drama CD where Homura talks quite a bit.
Mm.
Right, that's true, isn't it?
Mm, mm.
I wanted more relatively normal conversations, like then.
Yeah, that's right! There aren't any!
Mm.
If they were able to have a proper senpai-kouhai relationship, I think it would have been really nice.
yeah, yeah.
Mm.
They'd click.
Like going about their hobbies relatively carefree.
Yeah.
Laid-back style.
Those two just drinking tea together. (lol)
So Kaori-san, when you did this piece of work...
What do you perceive as this piece of work's charms?
Ehh, you can't say that in a single word, ne. There's too much.
What should I say, what is...
In the end, from the position of an actress...
There are an amazing number of lines that are like "I want to say this line!", really.
That's probably the number one most amazing thing, firstly. So that's there...
Then, you know...
Ume-sensei's designs...
and an Urobuchi-san script...
When I heard about that, it was like "Wow, I really want to do that."
Isn't that everyone's first thought? Kind of like "I really want to do this."
That's right.
And you just don't know what it'll be like.
Right~!
You really don't know.
Ne!
Really. That's one quality of an original.
That's right.
Usually you can read the source material and find out what kind of feeling it has, but...
This is an original work, so...
That's right, an original work, you know.
That's right...
Mmmm.
That's right, so we weren't informed about all that much.
That's right.
If you hear, you have to force a （･▽･）ニヤ(smile)
(lol)
We were told about the really basic things, but...
There are things we didn't know, so it's always like "What will happen after this!?"
The small things, that is.
We weren't told that.
Actors also have a lot of that sort of "want to know" passion.
Even now, we don't know the very end.
That's right.
Isn't that right?
Right now we have a grasp on things until the end of episode eleven, but...
(lol)
We don't know episode twelve!
Don't know!
All of the characters were at an equal standpoint. (lol)
Seriously, you know...
That's right.
That may be true...
After knowing, it's like "Ah, that thing from that time is this."
Ah, it's this?
It's this.
Ah, it's this.
uwaaaa
Truly lovely... Inu Curry-san's...
So it's this world?
Ne!
Inu Curry-san.
Somehow, this sort of thing is a bit scary, but I really love it.
Ne~ I get it.
Right, right.
Right—right—right, this is another charm.
That's right.
mmm
It really sort of pulls you in, huh?
Ne?
You can really see it.
Mmmm
Right.
Can see it...
Concerning these, there might be a lot of people who want to know how they were made, but...
barriers
We don't know either, you know.
That's right.
Yes.
(lol)
In reality.
This is a pretty intense conversation right here.
Dangerous!
(lol) Dangerous.
Nee~
Ah, right, other than Mami, were there any characters that piqued your interest?
Piqued interest...
You know, after this point, Sayaka had really, really, really, piqued my interest.
That's...
I see. Right, right, that's right.
She piqued my interest.
Ao-chan and I are making a face like this.
(lol)
You can't see it, but it's this kind of face.
(ﾟДﾟ;) (ﾟДﾟ;)
(lol) like you're saying "AHHH"
B–But for us too, it's like "After this, how will it turn out?"
What are Madoka's circumstances going to be like...
That's right.
It's her.
(lol)
AHHHHHHHHHHHH
her!
لدي عشرة يو متعب
Ahh~
No one will be condemned anymore.
That's right.
Mmm.
もう何も怖くない(mou nanimo kowakunai, "nothing is scary anymore") = Episode title.
もう誰も責められない(mou daremo semerarenai, "nobody will be condemned anymore") = Joke.
"Nobody will be condemned anymore."
Sounds like a title.
(lol) Subtitle.
(lol) Really, you know...
In this story, everyone really gives it their all.
Right...
There isn't really anyone who's like "Man, this person really sucks."
None~
There are none!
There's no one that's just like "This person is bad."
Ne!
Right, right
Everyone kind of... has their own circumstances, you can listen to everyone, huh?
Yeah, everyone gives it their all, and everyone is thinking with good intentions.
Excluding Beh-san.↓
Ah, well, Beh-san is doing his own job.
Beh-san might be the one bearing the most, huh?
Right.
Beh-san seems like the kind of person who'd be a realist.
In a way, Beh-san is the most real.
"Beh-san", "Beh-san" (lol)
Beh-san, umm...
(lol) So he had that nickname? (lol)
Inkyuubee-san.
Really, now...
Beh-sama, that is.
Beh-sama.
Ne~
He has no bad intentions.
No bad intentions!
His intentions aren't even a little bit bad.
Is that normal? (lol)
The way everything is entwined, this kind of... "social ill will" it holds is amazing,
it makes me think the head of this piece of work must have been entirely full of ill will.
Right, you feel a lot of pain...
It's tough, huh?
It's tough when no one is particularly bad.
Ne~
It's comforting to be able to say someone is at fault...
That's right...
Like "That guy is bad!"
Mmm!
Without that, what do you do?
There isn't that.
Yeah, really...
It sucks if they cry.
It hurts if anyone cries...
mmm...
Somehow, earlier today, just a bit before this, I was taking an interview by myself...
Yes.
mmm
This is a topic which has sort of piqued my interest...
Yes, yes, yes.
You know, men and women both understand feelings for this show rather well.
Eh? That's right!
Ehhh~
Regarding feelings on the story overall, it generally doesn't change... it's just,
when you think about the characters individually, men and women really—
Ah... you mean what they'll approve and won't approve?
Right. At the moment, there's nobody here but girls, so we can all understand the pain that these girls are holding, right?
Ahhh.
That's right, huh?
That's right, isn't it~
Right. So, in actuality, none of these girls simply have a "pure heart",
mmm.
mmm...
That's right, isn't it~
As a protagonist, Madoka is a really good girl, but in the end, she's the character who runs away from everything the most.
That's right, you know.
But personally, I understand that.
mmm...
And, Mami-san too, she fights while persevering, but understands that she herself is weak.
mmmm.....
This part right here is perfect for this discussion, but
that "I'm weak, so I will fight" is a feeling that I hold myself, and that's a part which girls can relate to.
mmm...
And through a man's eyes, somehow, seeing a group of such courageous and praiseworthy girls fight while persevering,
mm?
is a part that sticks with them.
Ahhh.
Right.
Certainly, from a girl's perspective, you can relate to any of the characters a little bit.
That's right.
And, this straightforwardness and toughness that everyone holds, a girl can understand that too.
mmm...
mmmm
Right, if you look at Mami-san... she's all alone after the accident, isn't she?
She's constantly doing this heartbreaking work... and probably has no friends.
mmmm.
I believe she has no one on her wavelength to talk to, you know.
This is never established in the settei, so I'm not exactly sure, but...
Possibly, after that accident, she transferred by herself, and was truly alone...
Then when she's left with absolutely no friends... Madoka could possibly... be a friend that she makes.
This scene is perfect timing.
But, that means... she knows about, and will be lured into, the underground work that Mami-san is currently doing.
If you put thought into it, you think "that's a bad idea" though...
But somehow, one way or another, I understand those feelings.
I understand them!
Completely understand them.
And then, how she doesn't immediately say "Let's do it together,"
and instead is like "Wait just a bit," but you feel like it's probably-definitely going to happen...
That kind of... "weakness" and "strength" co-existence is painful!
I really understand it.
It isn't particularly deceitful of her...
Right, right, right, right, right
Right, right, right.
She lays out the entire situation, and says the choice is up to you... but you know...
That's right.
Right.
When you see them delay things a little bit, that gives off a really human feeling, and it leaves an amazing impression.
Ne~
These lines are, you know~
that's right...
Mou... so wonderful...
Ne~
Right...
Somehow, these lights... since there's something floating upwards, it sort of lifts you up, really.
It's got emotion.
Ne!☆
They have proper meaning to them, don't they?
It's so wonderful...
This cheerfulness... it's the beginning of getting cocky!
أي فكرة عما تقول يوكي الهيئة لكنها لطيف جدا
(lol)
When there's a sorrowful conversation, you're like "waah!", and after crying, you find that the meaning was cheerful...
NE~!
Right–right–right
Wouldn't you say it points to a suitable time for something to happen?
Right.
When the material is expressly more comforting or the like, when it "raises up," during those times, you know something is up.
Mmm!
Mm.
Don't you think it really feels like that?
Right–right–right–right–right.
That's right.
Wait, wait just a second please (lol)
During a sad time, she's just like "How's a sweet cake?"
Right, right, right.
She really has that girlish way of thinking.
Comfort being a weakness really hurts, you know...
Mmm, right...
That's why what happens after this is so... mmm... ne~?
That's right... (´；ω；｀)
Right, right.
Mou, tension is rising so heavily today!
So dangerous.
Ahhh, be careful Mami-san~
I thought she was being careful!
(lol)
I really thought she was!
Really thought!
Everyone else continues the story forward, and ...
Well, after this, tension rises pretty quickly for a certain character...
So after this, for everyone, it's like "Be careful, be careful!"
"BE CAREFUL!"
You're very cool!
It's so cool to fight inside of a cake.
Her fighting style is amazing, isn't it?
Her fighting style is  amazing!, isn't it?
Kawa-Kowai! It's somehow nice.
Mmmm.
Mm.
Cute, but a little bit scary.
Right, right, right.
Ne~!
And then, a little bit cool!
Yeah!
Mmm!
Somehow, it's extremely nice...
Ah, so precious.
Once again, I kind of...
I love this pleasantness that Mami-san displays.
Thank you very much.
mmm...
Amazing...
Truly wonderful.
And then, this style of running!
Right? That's...
"Girl's running."
ahhhh~
When they enter this room, there's a bright color inserted, isn't there?
ahhhh~ That's right.
Cute, isn't it?
kawaii...
And then he's there.
He is! (lol)
Him! Beh-san is (lol) right in the middle of them.
(lol)
Beh-san is 2525(smiling)
Actually, I... really like the witch this time.
Yes.
Really!
Cute!
Mmm.
This little one is cute.
This little one is... kawa-kowa.
'Cause, you know.
She got this cutie!
It's a bit pitiable, isn't it?
It's pitiable!
Mm.
Ah, it's coming.
ｷﾀ━━━━(´Д`)━━━━ ・・・・・
Somehow, on the last volume, we were supposed to ask Kitamura Eri-chan this too, but,
if you were to become a mahou shoujo, what would you make Beh-san do?
I'd definitely stay silent. (lol)
(lol)
That's right.
So, what kind of wish would you get?
What kind of wish...
should I pick...
What would be good...
While watching this scene, you're...
(lol)
Amazing.
I don't want to worry too much! Not too much, you know?
(lol)
I thought this is a part we shouldn't touch on!
ahh...
Ah... ah.
this...
That's right.
We're touching on this part!
Just watching it normally!
To be frank, this is a little...
scary, scary
Umm...
ai, ai.
The question before we saw this violence...
yah.
yah!
Yes.
Wh–Wh–Wh–What do you think?
When everything is smooth, you aren't really thinking of what could happen to you.
Ah, you mean how Mami was feeling?
Yeah. But, somehow, when I read the scenario, I was thinking "What should I do for this?" ...
Since I haven't really done too many characters that die.
I was thinking what should I do about that, but the way she dies is portrayed in a relatively "real" manner.
When she dies, she doesn't say "Ugh!" or anything like that.
Since there's nothing like that, I was thinking "What do I do?"
So then it was like, "Until the last moment, normal is fine."
mmmm
mmm
That's kinda piti–
pitiable.
She was full of hope until the very end.
Right...
Until just a moment ago, she was conversing normally, then suddenly... you know.
Ne.
Somehow, it kind of brings it a bit closer to you, too.
That kind of also makes you wonder, "Will she be okay?"
Yeah.
Before, it was about your wish.
As for a wish, I'd kinda... always be like "What should I do?"
Isn't it fine if you just don't have a wish?
ahhh.
Actually, it'd be like "I'll just make myself a mahou shoujo, so please forget about me."
Ah, that isn't a wish.
(lol)
"Please forget about me" isn't a wish.
It's not. (lol)
This is scary, isn't it!?
Nope, I'm fine! "Nothing" would be okay!
"DON'T WANT THIS", I'd say.
Mou, ne...
scary...
Beh-san is scary~!
Ah, this makes me want to cry.
But, you know,
I wonder if you can just wish to deny it?
But, somehow it'd be granted with a really unpleasant feeling.
Mm.
You'd have to constantly be on the lookout for Beh-san after that.
And then, 90 curses.
Ah, you'd be cursed, cursed!
You'd be cursed.
Ne~
Ah, it's here... this feeling, you know...
hsssss
Ne? Really. It's become this kind of atmosphere.
This kind of atmos—Can't do anything, everything is too heavy.
For an after recording workplace, you aren't supposed to have this kind of atmosphere, but instead–
Right.
YAAAAAY!
(lol)
Ahaha~!
Great job everyone!
That kind of atmosphere.
Yes.
Right.
Well, up to this point, what is it, the characters are all depicted as a bit... refreshing.
That's right.
That is true.
Yup, yup.
And then, the true character comes out... in this ending.
Mm.
Yes...
That's right, from here on out, it's this ending.
Fr–Fr–From here.
Well, they don't put this ending on episode 1.
Mmm.
(lol)
But, by episode 3, it's now this ending. (lol)
That's right.
(lol)
Man, just have to put on a "Hahaha!"
I really like this song!
I love it, too!
Ne? It's cool.
Kalafina-san is the best.
And the silhouettes, too, you know...
Ne. Ah, Mami-san's silhouette is...
A bit in suffering, right?
Ne?
(lol)
I really think that the way these girls look from behind is amazing.
I always really really like it.
Somehow...
It looks like they're thinking about a lot. The girls' appearances from behind.
That's right.
Like, this silhouette perfectly gives off that kind of feeling, seeing it from the back.
That's right, ne.
Makes you think "I wonder what her face is like right now?"
Mmmm.
mmm.
We're almost done with this piece of work, but...
Yes!
How was it?
...
Fun.
(lol)
I think this single word is nice.
But a lot of various stuff happened!
Yes.
When you rewatch this piece of work, you definitely discover a lot of things.
No matter how many times you watch it.
First off, one-hundred times!
Yeah! (lol)
Yeah.
You can't run away from QB-san!
Can't run away!
Okay, really...
Thank you very much!
Um, next time: Episode 4.
Next time is episode 4, Urobuchi-san!
(ﾟДﾟ; ) Ho っ!
Watch it, please!