Oh, are you here to see Kamijo?
Yeah...
Sorry, we had to move up his examination, so he's seeing the rehabilitation counselor right now.
Oh... Thanks.
She comes to see him a lot.
I'm thankful. He's such a difficult patient.
Maybe she'll finally cheer him up.
Before his accident, he was a violin prodigy.
But now, even though he can walk again, his fingers...
He'll never play the violin again.
Why Kyosuke?
My fingers aren't good for anything, no matter what I do with them.
So why Kyosuke, and not me?
If I wished for his recovery, what would he think?
Would he just thank me? Or... something more?
I'm horrible.
Thinking back, I realize that at that point I understood nothing.
Of what it meant to wish for a miracle... Or what it would cost.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 4 There are miracles and magic
What is that, a mole? Ah, got it.
Madoka.
Hurry up and eat, you're gonna be late.
What's wrong, sis?
You don't like it?
No... It's really, really tasty...
Just being alive and able to eat your cooking...
Can you believe Yuka? She still hasn't picked up on it!
What? You think I said something weird again?
I'm already laughing my head off, why are you so serious!?
Sayaka, about yesterday...
Sorry, I don't want to talk about it right now. Maybe later.
--totally into someone different!
There's certainly a medical basis for an ideal age to reproduce,
but you mustn't judge someone's chance of marriage based on that!
For example, of course women over 30 still have a chance to find their true love.
So you should use use the progressive rather than the perfect--
I feel almost like I'm in a strange land...
Everyone here at school hasn't changed a bit from yesterday,
but they're like total strangers now.
None of them know.
About the witches, about Mami...
We know, and they don't.
So we live different lives, in a different world.
Sayaka...
We'd already changed long before.
We should have realized sooner.
Madoka, do you still want to become a magical girl?
You're right.
Of course not.
I know it's no fair, but I'm just too afraid.
I just can't...
Just remembering it makes me too scared to even breathe...
I'm scared! I don't want to!
Mami was so kind.
Showing us what we must be prepared for if we're to fight, she—
What's going to happen to this city, Kyubey?
Will someone take up Mami's task of protecting us from the witches?
This has been Mami's territory for a long time, but the other magical girls won't ignore an opening.
Another girl will be here soon to hunt witches.
Won't it just be someone like that transfer student, here to gather Grief Seeds?
There aren't many like Mami. Most just think of their own gain.
Everyone has their desires.
Then...
But only those who share in the fate of a magical girl have the right to blame them.
I understand how you feel.
Unfortunately, I can't force you to become magical girls.
I guess this is goodbye. I need to find a girl who needs to contract with me.
Sorry, Kyubey.
I'm sorry I involved you in it.
We only knew each other for a short time, but thanks, Madoka. I enjoyed it.
Sorry...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I'm so weak!
Homura!?
Madoka Kaname. You're being too hard on yourself.
Nobody can blame you for what you've done.
I won't forgive anyone who does.
I see you heeded my warning.
If I had only listened to you earlier...
That would not have changed Mami Tomoe's fate.
But it changed yours.
I'm happy I was able to save at least one person.
Homura, you...
You seem like an old pro in a different way than Mami.
Perhaps. I can't argue with that.
You must have seen people die like she did yesterday so many times...
Yes.
How many?
I no longer keep count.
I wonder if her room will just stay like that.
Only distant relatives survive Mami Tomoe.
They won't receive notice of her disappearance for quite some time.
No one realizes she's gone?
Of course. If you die over there, you don't leave a corpse.
In this world, she'll eternally be "missing".
That's how magical girls die.
That's terrible!
She fought alone for our sakes for so long...
No one realizing she's gone is so lonely!
That contract is what gives us our power.
It's not for anyone else.
We fight for our own wish.
Even if we're ignored, even if we're forgotten... That's part of the contract.
I'll remember her.
I'll never forget Mami.
Ever!
I see. I'm sure that would make her happy.
I'm jealous.
You too, Homura! I'll never forget you!
I'll never forget how you saved me yesterday!
Homura?
You're too kind.
Don't forget. That kindness may yet bring upon you greater tragedy.
What are you listening to?
The Girl with the Flaxen Hair .
Oh, Debussy, right? That's a great song.
I guess everyone thinks I don't really look like the kind of girl who'd listen to classical music,
so they're always so shocked when I come up with the name of a piece or something!
It's so unexpected that they get all impressed.
It's because you taught me, Kyosuke.
Without you, I think I could've gone my whole life without listening to this music.
Sayaka, you're...
What?
Are you mocking me?
Why do you keep making me listen to music?
Are you just harassing me?
But you love music!
I don't want to hear another note!
I can't stand listening to music I'll never play!
I... I...
I can't move my fingers! I can't even feel pain!
With this treatment...
Don't worry! You'll get better somehow!
As long as you don't give up, someday--
They told me to give up.
They told me to give up on playing.
My maestro told me himself that it's impossible with modern medicine.
My hand will never move again.
Not without a miracle or magic or something.
Those exist!
There are miracles and magic.
Homura seems like a friendly enough person now that we've talked.
I wonder why she was always fighting with Mami?
Huh? Hitomi?
Hitomi!
How did practice go!?
It's just like what that woman had!
Hitomi!
Hey! Hitomi!
Oh, Kaname! Good evening!
What's wrong? Where are you going?
Where? Well...
I'm going to a better place.
Hitomi...
I know! You should come too!
Yes, it'll be fabulous!
What do I do!?
This is--
If I call Homura--
Oh no! I don't know her number!
That's right.
I'm trash.
This little workshop isn't enough to satisfy me at all.
There's no place for me in this world.
Listen, Madoka.
If you use these wrong, bad things happen.
Bad enough to send the whole family straight to heaven.
Make sure you never do that.
No! Don't do that!
You mustn't interrupt the holy rites.
But that's dangerous!
Everyone here will die!
Yes! We're all going on a journey to a wonderful new world!
Don't you understand how great that will be?
Our living bodies only hold us back!
You'll understand very soon now.
Let me go!
What do I do!?
No!
No! Somebody, save me!
Somebody!
This must be punishment.
It has to be.
Punishment for being such a crybaby and a liar.
I'm... Being punished...
Stop...
Sayaka!
This is the end!
Sorry it took me so long. You looked like you were really in trouble.
Sayaka... Your outfit...
I kinda had a change of heart.
It's fine. Did great for my first time, huh?
But...
You...
Hey, the new girl's finally here!
I didn't expect you  to show up.
I heard Mami bit it.
But then I come all the way out here and you've got a totally different story?
Sorry. There's a new magical girl here now.
She just agreed to her contract.
Really? Jeez, that's lame.
Some rookie setting up shop in turf like this ticks me off.
What are you planning, Kyoko?
Isn't it obvious? I just need to knock her off.
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes will
(Go beyond the time)
There is but one dream, of a world rushing toward its doom
(Will it be destroyed?)
Swallow your hesitation! What do you desire?
Chasing these greedy desires, will the future fade away?
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even the darkness
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a plucked laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
Illustration: Jin Kobayashi
This is my chance to shine!
I, Magical Girl Sayaka, will protect the peace of Mitakihara City!
Episode 5 Absolutely no regrets
Absolutely no regrets.