You got it!
Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
It now trembles within my chest
Mou kuru ki ga shita
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne to
So happy for them
Everyone's out partying late at night.
In that case, you must be punished.
What's going on...?
Kanade.
Hey, what's going on?!
Tenshi isn't harmless anymore?
No... that's not Kanade at all.
As long as we weren't resisting...
Kanade never turned her sword against us.
Damn you!
Yurippe!  What should we do?
Everyone, surround her.
Huh?  What are you giving orders for?
Concentrated fire!
If she doesn't have distortion on, we can win!
Hey! Lemme go!
Roger!
Yuri!  Pull back!
Fire!
Damn it!
Sign: "No Unauthorized Entry After Hours"
Medical Offices (After Hours) School Infirmary
Is Kanade alright?
That was a really deep wound, right?
She's the same as us.
Even a fatal wound will heal automatically.
How can there be two of the same person?
Has this world really become that crazy?
There's a reason.
What is it?
Do you remember when we infiltrated Tenshi-area?
Yeah...
She had software on her computer that would develop "skills", right?
There was one on there that we'd never seen before.
She must have used that skill.  Harmonics.
Harmonics?
What kind of power is it?
Weren't you looking at the screen?
It's a skill that splits one's body into two.
A doppelgänger.
Like a clone?
At any rate...
It's a skill that Tenshi herself created using software, correct?
It sure didn't seem like she was in control anymore...
That thing was different than her.  More warlike.
Why?
Kanade only uses her powers to protect herself.
Even the swords were used that way.
They were just used to deflect our bullets.
Honestly.  You're a pretty incompetent group.
Otonashi-san being the exception, of course.
Because it's composed of idiots.
Let me tell you one possibility.
The reason her other self sprang forth is that...
she wanted to call forth a powerful attack.
From back then, huh?
I see.
It's still just following the order of the main body.
Yeah, but...
Kanade has never wanted to attack before.
I don't really care,
but you sure are sticking up for her a lot.
That's because...
I feel bad for her.
Well, whatever.
So, what's our current problem then?
Is it how we're gonna fight Tenshi's clone?
Are you stupid?  It's how we're gonna erase it.
What'd you say?
But... if she created it on purpose...
What are you doing?!
Lemme go!
there must be a way to erase it on purpose, as well.
Can't we just wait until she wakes?
Hold on.
If she summoned it on purpose, would it really do this to her?
Most likely, she summoned it unconsciously.
That's why she was unable to erase it.
Even if they had to extinguish each other, that's all she could do.
Hey now, wait a second.
That thing isn't gonna disappear?
It's gonna be hanging around this world from now on?
For now, we're being allowed to remain at large.
But starting tomorrow, we probably won't be forgiven.
If we start to act outside the boundaries of "exemplary behavior"...
it'll quickly turn into a blood-stained battle just like yesterday.
Even though she's not even the Student Council President anymore?
Yes.
Her desire to correct our behavior is still absolutely present.
Only now she's enforcing it in a more warlike manner.
It's the worst possible situation.
We don't even have enough time to organize our resistance.
Can you buy me some time?
How shall we do that?
Go to class, and pretend to pay attention.
Make sure you don't actually concentrate on the teacher, though.
If you really take the classes seriously, you'll disappear.
You don't want to be discovered by Tenshi's clone...
So just immerse yourself in your own separate activities.
And separately, try to hold out.
May nobody disappear.  I pray we'll meet again.
Sign: Study Notebook
Yeah, I already know that she splits into two.
Girls Dorm - Tenshi Area
I wanna know how to make it disappear.
Hmm?
Angel Player?
This is the software manual, right?
Damn it.  It's all in English!
Even under normal circumstances, I don't have much time.
Um...
Oh!  It popped up.
Is this its range?
That's useless.
Huh?
What's this?
Yes!  This is it!
If this order is given, it should disappear on its own.
Alright, what are the conditions, then?
Ugh.  I don't get it.
Maybe I should just bust the computer up.
Who am I kidding?
That won't make it disappear.
Damn it!  I'll just write it into the program I understand!
Just disappear!
Wait time, 10 seconds!
How's that?!
Waiting 10 seconds is kinda long...
Why can't I do it under 10 seconds?
Good.  It looks like that worked.
What's this?
There's more!
Howling?
Did the clone create this?
Should I delete it?
No... I've been pretty careful so far.
I need to keep my editing to a minimum...
That should do it.
Now we just need her to use Harmonics again.
Then Absorb will start up, and her clone should go back to her main body.
We screwed up.
Maybe she went out someplace.
No, she wouldn't have.
Kanade made a promise.
She promised to stay with us.
She promised that?
Y-Yeah...
Judging by this destruction, it looks like she was abducted.
You!  What have you done?
"You?"...
I just wrote something into the program.
If that girl uses her power again, a supplemental power will be invoked.
Then the clone should return to her main body.
You were able to do that?
I was mostly guessing, but yeah.
But, the enemy moved faster than we expected.
If she hides her main body, we can't destroy her.
What should we do?
We have to find her.
While avoiding the notice of that monstrous Tenshi?
If only we could have gotten away with just faking it in class.
How well can you pull off a diversion?
Me?  A diversion?
Why'd you join GirlDeMo?
Cause I looked up to Iwasawa-san...
GirlDeMo is supposed to be a diversion!
No, no, no, no.  I can't just distract someone that scary!
Do it!
Who do you think you are?!
I'm your Senpai!  I should be getting mad here!
Senpai, huh?!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Um.  I might pee my pants during the concert, but...
I'll try my best!
I appreciate your determination but, we might not need you.
First, let's do what we can.
This is a directive for all members.
Gather information on Tenshi's whereabouts!
Hey! Yo! Check this out!
It's a moonwalk!  It's a moonwalk!
Headspin!
Gym. - Interior
According to the information gathered on short notice...
there's a high probability that she's being confined in the Guild.
In that case, it would have to be the newer one.
The one we blew up?
Yes.
With all the traps.
Very dangerous.
And very far from here.
We're going down there again?
Last time we were all nearly wiped out.
Hmph.  Are you guys scared or something?
You know, you were the first to die last time...
For everyone's sakes, I'll keep singing, even if I start to pee.
I'll show you how brave I am!
Using a diversionary tactic against that thing won't do any good.
Got it?  No distraction this time.  We're gonna do this openly.
While fighting Tenshi?
That's right.
Are we clear?  The operation is to descend to the destroyed Guild...
and safely recover the original Tenshi.
Operation... start!
UTW Presents:
Looks like last time's traps haven't been reset.  Lucky~
Passage Connecting to Guild - B4
Um...if Tenshi shows up I think I'm gonna pee my pants either way.
I don't care.
You should care!
She appeared already, huh?
Fire!
Damn it.
She's fast!
We've still got handguns!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Fire at will!
This might go faster than expected.
What?
What's going on here?!
Is that the original?
No!
That's another clone!
Why is there another?!
At any rate, the enemies are multiplying.
It's not really a big deal, but man, he was done in right off the bat again, huh?
Damn it.  Fire!
What do we do about the one behind us?
No time to worry about that!
We need to get the enemy right in front of us.
You all seem pretty busy.
Yurippe, we're gonna run out of ammo.
We don't have a chance.
I'm gonna make us an exit.
Follow me!
Here we go!
Yuri!
10 more seconds!
If you don't make it you'll be left behind!
Now there's two of that ferocious Tenshi.
Passage Connecting to Guild - B5
This is even worse than the last time we came down here.
Why are there two now?
The clones can use Hand Sonic and Distortion.
So it's no surprise they can use Harmonics as well.
Honestly, you certainly are a feeble-minded bunch.
Otonashi-san being the exception, of course.
Shall I explain the problem for you?
By all means...
There's two problems.
The first is how many clones have been created?
If clones can make clones...
there's no limit to how many there may be.
So it's not just two?
It could be ten or twenty or more?
But wait a sec.
Yuri appended that ability, right?
The clones should be returning to the main body?
Can't we just wait for them to disappear?
That's the second problem.
What if she'd already made a number of copies before the ability was appended?
But...that's...
Hmph.  Peasants.
You've finally realized it?
Well, Otonashi-san is a sublime nobleman, of course.
If it knew that we were going to be coming here...
and began to mass-produce clones...
and stationed them around the Guild...
That would mean this is a...
Trap.
Yes.
For us.
There's already two behind us.
They won't disappear.
You fools have no chance of victory.
And there could be swarms of them that await us.
So we're trapped.
We can't resupply our weapons, either.
All we can do is wait for them to get us.
What could their goal possibly be?
Ultimately, it must be to make us completely obedient.
That's her mission.
So that we'll just silently disappear?!
It's a good plan for taking us out in one clean sweep.
Let's go.
There's another one.
Passage Connecting to Guild - B10
Number 3, huh?
Don't waste your bullets.
What are you planning?
Matsushita-godan!
Go!
Go while I'm still conscious!
Stop trying to sound like the hero on the brink of death!
Hurry!
Let's go while we still can!
Endure it, Matsushita-godan!
The rest is up... to you...
Everyone...
Let's not waste Matsushita-kun's sacrifice.
Passage Connecting to Guild - B11
Thanks to him we understand now.
Making the first move is the best way to deal with her.
Tenshi's body is tiny, so it's best to restrict her movement.
No matter how ridiculously strong she might be,
a judo hold should work.
The Judo lessons Matsushita-kun gave us should come in handy now.
So basically...
we can sacrifice one of ourselves for each clone we encounter.
Is that correct?
Sacrifice ourselves?
If we can save the original...
then we can save those who sacrifice themselves as well.
Let's hurry.
Number 4!
It's my turn.
Get chance and luck!
TK!
What's with this scenario looking like the end of a shounen manga?!
Forget it.  We're going!
This body of mine...
The time to show it to you has come.
Takamatsu!
Heh.  Like this would scare me.
Fujimaki!
How foolish.
How fooliiiiiiish!
Shiina!
You understand now.
You're a clown.
Look.
Over there in that dark corner.
There's a lonely little girl there.
Ah.  Oh no, he's right!
I'll make you laugh!
Ooyama!
You're a monster.
Otonashi-san, that's not it at all.
Hear me out. I just misspoke!
I'll go next, okay?
Hey... somebody say something.
Well... I don't know his name though.
Let's go.
Passage Connecting to Guild - B15
How many does this make now?
Who knows?
I'm not even counting anymore.
This time I'll go.
Hold on.
It's my turn.
You hang on until the end.
Why?
That girl is waiting for you.
I have this feeling she is.
That's why you've gotta keep going.
Got it?
Also, if by some chance-
If you're going, then go already!
Wait for me, Senpai!
Do you love him or hate him?
We've arrived.
The explosion site of the Guild.
Ground Zero - Inside Guild
We're all gonna go to the bottom at once.
Otonashi-kun and Yui will look for the original Tenshi.
When you find her, get her to use Harmonics immediately.
It would be better for me to fight.
Didn't you listen to Hinata-kun?  That girl is waiting for you.
Well then I'll fight!
You're too puny, it's not even worth considering.
At least consider it!
Alright, we're going.
I'm super-strong!
I hope this will turn out to be our final operation.
Yeah.
Ahh.  Wait for me!
Huh?  Where's Yui?
I kinda felt like I heard a really short scream...
Did she fall prey to Tenshi?
Poor thing.
We'll save you soon.
Once again, we're the only ones left.
Yeah.
Just like last time.
Is this the last one now?
I sure hope so.
Hey, don't just stand there, go find the original.
Oh... yeah!
I thought so.
Damn.
She's tough.
Cover your ears!
Guard Skill: Howling.
What is this?!
My ears!
You're not... injured?
Huh?  What was that?
My ears are plugged, so I can't really hear you!
Come on, give it up.
If you really want, I'll use my other knife to slit your throat.
She's there!
Kanade!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Everyone from the SSS put their lives on the line to come save you.
I see.
That's right, Kanade.
I'm sorry to push you like this, but I need you to use an ability for me.
It's Harmonics.
If you use that, it'll help everyone.
I see.  Understood.
If you use it, will your body be alright?
If it's only once...
Guard Skill: Harmonics.
It looks like you changed the program, huh?
Yeah.  You'll all return to her body now.
All those cold-hearted copies of me?
What do you mean?
Even clones have consciousness.
They won't just disappear.
They'll be assimilated.
All the copies that attacked you will return to this one's body.
For her to take all that consciousness in at one time...
It won't be easy on her.
It's time.
Wait!
Damn it!
Please be okay!
Kanade!
Itsumo hitori de aruiteta
I've always walked alone
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turned around, everyone was far away
Soredemo atashi wa aruita
Even so, I walked on
Sore ga tsuyosa datta
That's what it was to be strong
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetter: Nikon
Timer: Klipper
Typesetter: ar
Editor/QC: Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c290] What's going to happen to us?
[c12] This is the first time Tenshi has ever been in that condition.
[c28] But we can only withstand that for a short while.
[c23] There's about a 1% chance, huh?
[c276] You want to help me strip?
[c93] What is this?
[c147] Somebody hit that guy!
[c83] We're going to help. Definitely!
[c143] Nobody's gonna help anyway!
[c239] Am I gonna disappear?
[c34] Who is God supporting?
[c160] Go back!
[c209] Otonashi.
[c221] I... remember everything.