No way! That's a convenience store trash can...!
Anyway, don't go near a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo.
I'm not good at dealing with Shizu-chan
because he doesn't listen to words or reason.
Didn't I tell you never to come to Ikebukuro again?!
Shizuo! Fighting isn't good.
Shut up!
Huh? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
It's gotta be him...
Heiwajima Shizuo!
I got fired without any warning!
They told me to leave the dorm as well!
I didn't get any severance pay, so I can't even afford food or rent!
The government won't do anything to help!
Yes, it's the government! It's all the government's fault!
Shut up...
So you go into debt over a hostess?
That's love!
Mint and I truly love each other!
Huh?
Shut up...
We can only meet at the club and I don't even know her cell number...
But we are truly in love!
Disgusting!
You only see each other at the club...
You don't even know her cell number...!
Shizuo!
I'll say this right off...
What about that...
Is true...
Love!?
I hate violence.
Did you know?
There's a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo who's
been going completely out of control recently.
Huh?
Is Heiwajima Shizuo that guy who wears a bartender's uniform?
Yeah.
They say he's always been scary, but apparently he's even worse now.
People are saying Ikebukuro's turned into a battlefield!
I've seen him before...
And Heiwajima Shizuo is indeed scary.
I wonder...
I don't think you should judge someone based solely on rumors.
Oh, Setton. Is Heiwajima your friend?
Maybe...you're the same as him?
I'm scared! Someone save me!!!
It's not like that!
Man, I can't collect money from anyone if you keep beating them up.
Sorry.
It reeks...
They said he hasn't been back for two or three days.
This has been happening a lot recently...
Maybe it's because of those fabled human traffickers?
It reeks...
Hey, people were injured!
I heard it was The Slasher.
It just happened!
I saw it! He ran that way.
Man...
Ikebukuro's in an uproar again.
It reeks...
Yeah, the whole town reeks!
What the hell is this smell!?
Ugh, This is annoying!
Hi Shizuo, Tom!
Hey, Simon.
Shizuo...?
Sorry, he's been in a bad mood recently.
Oh, Shizuo...he in puberty?
It's more like his rebellious stage.
Rebalance...?
Hey, it's been a while.
He got another leading role, huh?
That Hanejima Yuhei, I mean Heiwajima Kasuka, is quite the star.
You must be proud of your younger brother, Mr. Heiwajima Shizuo.
I'm sorry, let me introduce myself.
He doesn't just look good, he's also a good actor, right?
Ah, what was the name of his first film, again?
Ah, that's it.
Vampire Ninjas: Carmilla the Joker.
I knew he'd hit it big when I saw him then.
He performed all of his own stunts too, didn't he?
I'd like you to tell me whether or not you helped train him.
Shizuo!
I hate violence.
That's no lie.
I wasn't always like this.
The first time was when I fought with my little brother Kasuka.
I snapped over something trivial, lifted
up the fridge and tried to throw it at him.
It's not that I thought about lifting it.
I just couldn't go without lifting it.
And then...
Hey, Shizuo, your butt sounds like a shamisen!
Idiot!
I couldn't control myself.
I wasn't angry; my body just moved on its own.
And whenever that happened...
People can do crazy things in extreme situations, right?
That must be what you always use, Shizuo!
The brain saves that power by destroying a person's muscles and bones when they reach their limit!
But your brain makes that power explode!
It could be the mystery of life: an astonishing event like no other!
Hey, can you let me examine your body just on—
Owowowowow!
That hurts!
That hurts, Shizuo!
I didn't understand the details.
It's going to break!
Anyway, I couldn't control it.
My ulna!
I'd break my body and whatever was around me.
My right ulna!
That I understood.
And then...
I stopped trying to control it.
There was no reason to try in the first place if I couldn't do it.
My body was going to break.
Like I care!
My body broke countless times and got stronger with every break.
As Shinra would say...
Ugh, how annoying!
Anyway, I continued to get stronger!
But...
Hey, you...
You're always injured, aren't you?
Are you alright?
Wait a second.
Here.
Drink some milk so you can grow stronger.
Here. You, too.
Thanks.
I went too far.
And when I came to, I'd...
Good morning!
Why'd it turn out like this?
I was raised in a normal home.
I didn't suffer any trauma.
Yet...
Kasuka.
What?
Aren't you...afraid of me?
Not really.
It happened when I entered Raira.
It's our opening anniversary!
Everything's on special!
Our store's been around forever!
It seems like we were fated to go to the same high school.
Shut up.
How's your body holding up?
That's right, let me examine you to commemorate our reunion!
No good?
Then how about you let me draw some blood?
Celty!
Where'd you go yesterday?
I was worried because you didn't come home.
Were you looking for your head again?
You say that, but I bet you met a nice guy—
Celty...
Stop poking my solar plexus.
Oh, Celty, let me introduce you...
An odd feeling came over me...
He's my friend, Heiwajima Shizuo.
I don't know how to say it, but...
Shizuo, Celty lives with me, or I should say she's my future—
She...
What a horrible memory.
That's right, that was about the same time I met that pest.
And that person...is Orihara Izaya!
I...
This is Orihara Izaya from my middle school.
...I hated him from the first time I saw him.
Well, he's not that good a person...maybe I should say he's a horrible person.
You're so mean, Shinra.
No, I didn't mean it in a bad way.
I don't like him.
Huh?
Oh?
That's too bad.
I think I could have some fun with you.
Shut up.
Don't say that, Shizuo.
See...this is fun, isn't it?
The day we met...we tried to fight to the death.
I didn't have a reason why. I just didn't like him.
But...
Are you alright?!
He's fine.
He's built strong.
Is he...really alright?
He's fine.
Nice work.
Yeah...
I failed.
Oh, what a coincidence.
Izaya's here, too.
Hey, why aren't you injured?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
The next day was an annoying one.
Guys I had never seen before were fighting me one after another.
I hadn't done anything.
I was just living peacefully.
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit! Dammit! What a pain!
How annoying! Annoying! Annoying! Annoying! Annoying! Annoying!
Hmph. I know.
Bastard!
It was Izaya.
Izaya was pulling all the strings behind the scenes.
And when I found that out...
IIIzaaayaaa!
If only I'd killed him then...
Dammit!
After graduating from Raira...
How is it?
Do I look good?
The idiot kept on living like that...
And that pest was doing something with the yakuza.
Anyway, it was quiet for a while.
But I still...
Acted that way...
Welcome.
Hey, did you see?!
No way!
That's the actor...
Hanejima Yuhei!
Yo, Kasuka.
What's up?
Bartender uniforms?
I don't think you should change jobs.
I bought a lot for you...so you can continue doing what you do.
Thanks.
Well, I'll try my best.
But...
Dammit!
Izaya!
I got framed by that pest...
...and he disappeared from Ikebukuro.
They soon found out I was innocent and released me.
Yet...
I'm sorry...I didn't keep my promise.
Oh, if it isn't Shizuo!
Tom was a class ahead of me in middle school.
He asked me to help him collect debts from people.
To sum it up, I'm his bodyguard.
I didn't like it at first.
Tom would say...
"You don't have to raise your hand to her like that."
"By the way, Heiwajima Shizuo's with me."
"No one can stand in his way."
...stuff like that, but Kasuka got busy
ever since then and I hadn't seen him since.
I wonder if he's mad at me...
Hmm?
Yuhei!
Yuhei, this way, please!
I didn't understand why...
...but I felt better.
And I'm still working with Tom.
Repayment deadline?
I don't understand difficult stuff like that.
We march to our own beat.
Exactly. School, society, everyone's to blame.
They're the heart of darkness.
C'mon...
I said I don't understand.
Get outta here.
I'm just doing my job.
What? What's with the stare?
Hey, why're you wearing that?!
You idiot, he's a butler.
You guys...
You don't know who Shizuo is?
Who's that?
Some famous person?
Is that true, butler?
I spit it all out!
Would you be so kind as to bring me another one, butler?
You certainly do march to your own beat if
you're in Ikebukuro and don't know about Shizuo.
My clothes...
The clothes my brother gave me...
Even so, I really don't like violence.
I want to become stronger.
...Strong enough to control my rage.
I feel much better after talking with you.
Really? That's great.
I'd been irritated this whole time. I didn't know why, though.
Yeah, I heard about that and was worried about you.
Really? Sorry to make you worry about me.
Hm?
Pffft. Shut up.
See you.
Even though I want to put distance between
strangers and myself, I can't stand being alone.
That's why I always try to connect with people like Tom or Kasuka.
She's a lot like me.
She must have someone as well...
Yo.
Huh?
Shizuo!
Yo.
Are you done with puberty?
Then eat sushi. Sushi's good.
It's great!
Some other time.
Izaya!
That's it! I thought it reeked here!
Your...!
What is he doing?
What is he planning to do in this city now?
Dammit!
IIIzaaayaaa!
I have a dream.
It's the same dream over and over again.
I'm asleep when it's awake,
and it's asleep when I'm awake.
Next Time: Fleeting Dreams.