What on Earth?!
Look over there!
It's closing in!
Who's available?
We've received word that Lightning Max
and Smile Man are on their way.
Get me that threat level assessment!
As you can see, the city is being
leveled by huge explosions.
The scale of the damage
left by the monster is unprecedented.
The Heroes Association is currently analyzing the threat level—
Huge Explosion in City A
I guess I'll go.
Justice
Enforcement
Daddy! Mommy!
And who do we have here?
Just a guy who's a hero for fun.
What kind...
of half-assed backstory is that?
I was formed from the constant stream of pollution
with which you humans have suffused the earth.
I am Vaccine Man!
The Earth is a single living organism.
You humans are nothing but disease-causing
bacteria eating away at her lifeforce.
In order to obliterate humans
and their evil civilization,
the Earth has given birth to me!
And you say you do this for fun? For fun?
How dare you confront me,
Mother Earth's apostle, for that inane reason?!
I shouldn't have expected
anything more from a hu—
Not again... It's over in one punch.
Damn it!
Three Years Earlier
A monster!
Run for it!
Huh?
You sure you don't want to run away?
I bet you're a newly employed
salaryman already tired of work.
I am Crablante. I ate too much crab
and transformed into this!
Why aren't you running?
Do you want to die?
Is that it?
Well, not quite.
I'm not a salaryman. I'm unemployed.
Right now, I'm looking for a job.
I had another interview today
and failed spectacularly.
I couldn't care less right now.
So I really don't feel like running even though
the mighty Crablante is right in front of me.
So if I don't run, what'll you do to me?
Your eyes are lifeless, just like mine.
In lieu of our similarities, I'll let you go.
Besides, right now...
I'm hunting different prey!
A big-chinned brat...
And when I find him,
I'm gonna rip his arms off!
What're you looking at?
A big-chinned brat...
If he's caught, he's dead!
Hey, kid. Were you messing
with a big crab monster?
Huh?
He was asleep in the park,
so I drew some nipples on him with my marker.
It's definitely him.
He has no idea what he's done.
What do I do? I could still help.
But man, he's pretty ugly.
It's none of my business.
I should just walk away.
Right. I mean, who really cares?
I found you!
What the hell am I doing?
Huh?
Kid, he's after you! Get outta here!
Don't worry about me. Just go!
B-But...
My soccer ball...
Your ball?!
Hey, what's the big idea?
Don't tell me you're gonna
protect that stinkin' brat!
Come on, you're gonna kill him
over some harmless prank?
Think it over, man!
I've already mutilated lots of people.
Whoever makes fun of
the way I look pays the price.
No exceptions.
And that brat drew nipples on my body.
With a permanent marker too!
With these claws, I can't even
grab a towel to wipe it off!
Get in my way, and I'll make sure
you never go job hunting again!
It just came to me.
You look exactly like a villain
from this cartoon I used to watch!
Die.
Hold it right there.
In this age of declining birth rates,
I can't just let you kill a kid.
That's right.
When I was a little boy,
I wanted to be a hero.
Not a salaryman,
but a hero who could send rotten villains
like you flying with one punch.
Screw looking for a job!
Bring it on!
Some hero you are!
You're pathetic!
You don't stand a chance against me.
This is where...
you die!
Has it really been three years since then?
After that day,
I trained so hard I went bald.
I've become so powerful,
no one can beat me.
I'm the hero I dreamed of becoming.
So what is this? What's wrong?
Why does my heart feel so empty?
482 yen, please.
Okay.
Oh, hang on.
I have 82 yen.
Incredible...
This is incredible, little brother!
I never thought it would work so well.
Yes, it's more than I'd ever imagined, big brother.
My goal was to become stronger
than any other man in the world.
The strongest man.
That was my dream.
Finally, I have completed
the ultimate steroid, "Biceps King"!
Little brother, drink this and you will
obtain the power you've been seeking!
What? Drink that?
Indeed! I added strawberry flavoring,
to make it go down easier.
Brother...
Yes, this will do!
My brains and your brawn!
By combining the greatest of minds
and the strongest of bodies,
we brothers will conquer
the Earth and rule as kings!
I-Incredible!
Well done, little brother.
Thousands have perished!
Now, on to the next town
to destroy it as well!
This! This is it, big brother.
This is what I was looking for.
To be the strongest man.
This is an emergency evacuation warning.
A giant creature has appeared in City D.
The creature is currently moving towards City B.
All residents of the area,
please evacuate immediately.
I repeat, the giant creature
is currently heading for—
Yes, that's right! Scatter like rats!
Get them!
I'm the strongest man.
I'm the strongest man. I'm the strongest man.
What do you think, brother?
Yeah, how's it feel being the strongest?
What?!
There's someone on your shoulder!
Put some pants on.
That guy on your shoulder! Kill him!
Brother!
How did this happen?!
I just wanted to be strong!
And I finally am the strongest man, and yet...
I don't know who you are,
but it's your fault my brother is dead!
The strongest!
Behold our brotherly power!
I am the strongest.
So what if I am?
I feel empty.
Right?
Having overwhelming strength is...
pretty boring.
Oops.
City B Destroyed
There's no sign that the evils
of the world are disappearing.
It's still the same as before I became a hero.
In other words, you could say
that I haven't made a difference.
I'm not necessarily sad about that.
But something's been bothering me lately.
As the days pass,
my emotions grow more distant.
Fear, tension, joy, anger...
I don't feel any of them anymore.
In exchange for power,
have I maybe given up
something essential to being human?
Vroom, vroom?
No sense hiding if you saw me.
I'm Super Custom YO649Z Mk. II!
I love building custom cars so much,
I decked myself out.
I used to feel all kinds of emotions
whirling inside me when I fought.
Fear, panic, anger...
I'm a custom car-loving monster!
If you're thinking of getting in my way,
I'll put a shine on
that big headlight of yours!
But now, all I need is one punch to end it.
Guess I'll have eggs over rice tonight.
Every day I come home
uninjured and wash my gloves.
When I'm out fighting monsters,
I never feel as if my heart's really in it.
I mean, I just do the hero-thing as a hobby.
In other words,
as long as I enjoy doing it,
that's all I care about.
My house?!
He's tough!
What the hell are you?
"What" am I? How rude.
We are the true Earthlings.
We?
I believe you call us "Subterraneans."
We suffer from overpopulation.
Therefore, we must now colonize the surface.
However, I have been informed that there
are many people on the surface too.
As it stands, you are in our way.
That is why we have
decided to exterminate you all.
Since the start of our invasion,
we have eliminated seventy
percent of the surface dwellers.
This is a battle for survival.
I hope you can understand that.
However, this is unexpected.
We've never encountered a surface dweller
whom our punches would not kill.
I could say the same about you.
It's been too long since I've come
across such worthy opponents,
Subterraneans!
We are Earthlings!
But how?!
You bastard!
Die!
It's over.
What was that surface dweller?
I'm...
just a guy who's a hero for fun.
I do not lose!
And the surface...
is under my protection!
Big talk for a race of vermin!
What is this feeling?
This wild throbbing in my heart?!
This rush! This tension!
It'd been so long, I'd forgotten...
the exhilaration of a real fight!
It's coming back to me.
This is it.
Well, well...
Looks like you've been taking
good care of my children.
This is it!
I, the Subterranean King, will take you on.
This is the feeling I've been looking for!
The surface is ours!
You surface dwellers must die!
I am the Subterranean King!
Surface dwellers, prepare yourselves for—
All right, bring it on!
Sorry
I've become too strong.
The Strongest Man
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved is so strong, and still I worry
He only shows his weakness to me
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
The Lone
Cyborg
How'd you like seeing me
get ripped apart this week?
Now it's time for me, the mighty Crablante,
to tell you what happens next week.
Huh? There are no visuals?
Well, next week this guy appears
in City Z where Saitama lives!
What now? Time's up?
Well, next week will be
episode two, "The Lone Cyborg."
I hope you all—