Aw, we'll be in Japan tomorrow.
Misato said she'd be there
by noon to pick me up.
Oh, Misato is the person who was sent
to Germany before you, Mr. Kaji.
I don't like her that much.
She's always putting up a front.
Darn, we'll be going
our separate ways for a while.
This sucks.
When we get to Japan, I'm sure there will
be lots of new boyfriends waiting for you.
And from what I hear,
the Third Children is a boy.
I'm not interested in some dumb kid!
The only person I like is you, Mr. Kaji.
I'm flattered that you think that.
If you asked me, Kaji-senpai.
I'd say okay nonstop!
To kiss me! Or even to go past that!
Sorry, you're still just a kid, Asuka.
You need to grow up a little more
before you get into that stuff.
You're no fun!
I'm already grown up enough!
I'm an adult!
An adult! An adult!
So please look at me!
What had been hypothetical
has become a reality.
How ironic. The advocate
for the experiment became the guinea pig.
So that contact experiment
was the direct cause, then?
It seems the end result of her contact
was her total mental breakdown...
How cruel... She committed suicide,
leaving such a young daughter behind.
Actually, that might not have
been the only factor.
Asuka, honey?
Mommy made your favorite today.
Don't be fussy,
or that girl there will laugh at you.
She's like that every day. She talks
to the doll, thinking it's her daughter.
Maybe it's her way of expressing
feelings of guilt.
She was so wrapped up in her research
that she had little time for our daughter.
You have my sympathies, Mr. Langley.
Those two look like a matching set
of dolls, mother and daughter.
No, maybe there isn't much of a difference
between humans and dolls.
Dolls are something that humans
make in their own image.
If there really is a God,
maybe we're nothing more than his dolls.
You hardly sound like a practitioner
of modern medicine.
I'm a doctor, but I'm first
and foremost a human.
And a woman.
You're being such a brave girl, Asuka.
But you don't have to hold it in.
That's okay, I'm not going to cry.
I'll think for myself.
Asuka, can you hear me?
Your synch rate is down by eight.
Keep all extraneous thoughts
from your mind.
I'm trying to!
Asuka's synch rate has been
dropping steadily lately.
This is the last thing we need
on top of everything else.
Let's shift our priority toward
repairing Rei's Unit 00.
We don't have the resources to repair
both at the same time right now.
Mitosis process in Unit 02's left arm
has met target values.
Necrosis currently below 0.05%.
Apoptosis progress shows green.
Unit 00 morphogenesis system
holding at current levels.
Please connect all receptors
to Signal Two.
The Eva Series, born of Adam...
We can't defeat the Angels
without using the very thing
that caused the Second Impact.
If our survival is on the line, we'll use
even something that almost destroyed us.
That's humanity for you.
Maybe I really do hate the Evas.
-They killed my father...
-Ms. Katsuragi!
Construction has begun on Eva units
up through Unit 13?
At seven locations around the world?
This intel comes through Shanghai.
The source is reliable.
But why the rush for mass production now?
Two Evas have been lost, and another
two are currently badly damaged.
Maybe it's a push to bolster our reserves
as part of the Phase Two Buildup.
I'm not so sure.
We've been cannibalizing parts
from Units Five and Six in Germany.
There's been a lot of money
moving around lately.
Yeah, they've doubled our budget
at this stage of the game.
I wonder if that's a sign that
the top brass are feeling desperate.
It's obvious that the Council
is nervous about something.
Are they expecting a simultaneous
attack by multiple Angels,
instead of the individual attacks
we've had so far?
Plausible... But that doesn't explain
why they're keeping it under wraps.
They're after something else.
The number you are trying to reach
is not in service at this time.
That's strange.
My calls aren't getting through.
I wonder if he headed off somewhere again.
A train is now arriving on track two.
For your safety,
please wait behind the white line.
He spent a whole month absorbed
into his Eva not too long ago.
Look at those two, back together
like nothing ever happened.
Yeah, I know I lost.
To the likes of you!
We're together for the first time in ages,
but you can cut the tension with a knife.
Thanks, I'm done.
-Asuka.
-No way!
It's just Kaji calling you again,
so you should get it.
That won't happen.
Goodness, I'm ever so sorry
to make Shinji the Mighty
stoop to such a menial chore!
Hello?
What the hell? He always acts so polite.
It's an international call from Germany.
For you. It's your mother.
It's for me? From Mom?
Give me that!
[speaking German]
When Asuka talks in a different language,
she seems like a different person.
Her mother...
[speaking German]
Wow, that was a long call.
It was just your basic family interaction.
A family conversation... I'm jealous.
It only looks that way.
It's all just superficial stuff.
She's not even my real mother.
I don't hate her or anything.
I just get a bit uncomfortable around her.
Why the hell do I have to talk to you
about this stuff?!
-Sorry.
-Ha!
If I'm getting pity from the likes of you,
I may as well hang it up!
This is gross.
I'm not getting into the same water
that Misato and Idiot Shinji bathed in.
I'm not going to use the same
washing machine that washed
Misato and Idiot Shinji's underwear.
I'm not going to sit on the same toilet
that Misato and Idiot Shinji used.
I'm not going to breathe the same air
that Misato and Idiot Shinji breathed.
I hate Misato! I hate Shinji!
And I hate the First even more!
I hate Dad! I hate Mom!
But I hate myself the most!
I'm sick of this! I can't take it anymore!
Why do I have to put up with this?! Why?!
Synch graph indicates a drop of 12.8.
This is barely enough for activation.
These numbers are terrible.
They're even worse than yesterday's.
Asuka isn't feeling too hot today.
She's on her period.
Synch rates aren't affected by
superficial physiological states.
The problem is deeper down.
In her subconscious.
I guess we might have no choice
but to change Unit 02's core.
Asuka, you can come out now.
No.8 power system restoration
will begin at...
Asuka's pride is in shambles.
It's hardly a surprise,
not after a defeat like that.
Actually, the fact that she feels like
she lost to Shinji is even worse.
Maybe this won't work anymore.
Us three living together.
Have things gone critical? Your fun times
playing house are at an end?
I don't have to take that crap from a lady
who drowns her loneliness with cats.
I'm sorry. I'm on edge, I guess.
Why do I have to go through this
just because I'm a girl?
Even though I never want to have kids!
Loop Route No.7 is closed
due to an accident.
Please use Route 12 as a detour.
You're saying I'm closing myself off?!
I have mental walls?
Yes. The Evas have a heart.
-Those dolls have a heart?!
-Deep down, you know that.
Ha! If you started a conversation with me,
Hell must have frozen over!
What, does me not being able to pilot
my Eva make you that happy?
Don't worry! If an Angel comes,
Shinji the Mighty will defeat it!
We don't need to lift a finger!
The only one they need is Shinji!
First it was Shinji, and now even
a clockwork doll like you is pitying me!
I really must have lost my edge!
I'm not a doll.
Like hell you're not!
All you do is follow orders!
If Commander Ikari told you to die,
you'd do it, wouldn't you?!
I would.
I knew it, you are a doll!
I've hated how you act like a puppet
since the day I met you!
I hate all of you! Every last one of you!
Shinji's out again today.
Ayanami being absent
is nothing new, though.
But Asuka is also gone.
And Suzuhara can't be discharged yet.
I guess they have bigger problems
than school to worry about.
Eva-02 signals nominal.
VA attachment and fusion status green.
Propagation range is as predicted.
Finally pieced you back together, huh?
Even after you lost like that?
You're my doll, so just keep quiet
and do exactly as you're told, got it?
Why does a weapon need a heart, anyway?
It just gets in the way.
Anyway, just obey my commands,
and we won't have a problem!
I feel like an idiot.
All personnel,
condition one battle stations!
Prepare for anti-air intercept!
An Angel? Another one is here?
Visual confirmation of Angel.
This is at maximum magnification.
Weird, it's not moving out of orbit.
It's maintaining a fixed distance from us.
So is it waiting for the right time
to come down,
or can it destroy us from up there?
It's hard to tell what to do.
Either way, there's nothing we can do
unless the target
comes into our attack range.
The Evas can't intercept
a target in orbit.
Rei's status?
She and Unit 00 are both fine. Good to go.
Roger that. Unit 00, launch!
Prepare for super-long-range sniping!
Unit 02 and Asuka, prepare to launch
as backup in support role!
Me? Backup?! Support Unit 00?
That's right. Provide cover from the rear.
Like hell I will...
Eva-02, launching!
Asuka!
It's okay. Let's let her take point.
Major Katsuragi!
In other words, if she fails, she's out.
So, one last chance?
Let's start thinking about
a replacement for Unit 02's pilot.
Yes, ma'am.
Um, we're not deploying Unit 01?
It's been grounded.
Strict orders from Commander Ikari.
It's no surprise, after what happened...
NERV INSPECTION DIVISION
If you blow this,
they'll probably take you off Unit 02.
No screw-ups this time, Asuka.
Target still outside
effective firing range.
Get your butt down here, damn it!
This is so annoying!
ALERT
A directed energy weapon?!
No thermal energy readings!
Psychograph is going haywire!
Psychological contamination beginning!
An Angel psychological attack?
Impossible, it can read a human mind?
You god damn bastard!
-Positron projectile dissipated!
-It's no use, it's out of range!
I need an analysis of that ray!
It's an energy wave
in the visible spectrum.
It's similar to an A.T. Field,
but details are unclear.
-Asuka's status?!
-In danger!
Psychological contamination
now in Y region!
No!
Stay out... Stay out of my head!
It hurts!
No!
Don't look into my mind!
I'm begging you! Stop raping my mind!
-Asuka!
-Psychograph at critical!
Her neural pathways
are being torn to pieces.
It's too risky to put more stress on them.
Asuka, fall back!
Never!
That's an order, Asuka! Withdraw!
No! Absolutely not!
I'd rather die than retreat now!
Asuka!
Accelerator synchronization start.
Voltage climbing. Approaching threshold.
Forced convergence device, activate.
Correction for Earth's rotation
and gravity, 0.03.
Chamber interior pressure at maximum.
Final safeties disengaged!
All systems ready to fire!
No-go! At this range,
there's just not enough energy
to punch through its A.T. Field!
But the power output's already at maximum!
We can't go any higher!
Unit 02's psychograph barely registering!
The LCL's psychological firewall?
Ineffective! Catalyst
also having no effect!
Life support has top priority.
-Prevent flow reversal from the Eva.
-Yes, ma'am!
It's as if that ray is scanning for
Asuka's mental wavelength...
I don't believe it. Is this Angel trying
to understand the human mind?
Why am I crying?
I promised myself I wouldn't cry anymore.
What's the matter, Asuka?
That was a present from your new mommy.
Didn't you like it?
I don't want it.
Then what do you want?
I'm not a baby!
I'm going to grow up fast!
I don't need dumb stuffed animals!
So, please, look at me!
Mommy! Please, don't stop being my mommy!
Come die with me...
Mommy! Please, Mommy! Don't kill me!
No! I'm not your doll, Mommy!
I'll think for myself and live by myself!
I don't need a mommy or a daddy!
I can live by myself!
No! Stop making me remember all that!
I finally forgot it,
so don't dig it up again!
I don't need those
horrible things anymore!
Please, stop it! Stop!
Please, Asuka honey...
Please die with me.
Sure, I'll die with you, Mommy.
So please don't stop being my mommy!
Okay, Mommy?
"Mommy"? I don't know any Mommy.
Who are you?
I'm Asuka Langley Soryu. Nice to meet you!
Are you an idiot or something?
Here's my chance!
So please look at me!
No! That's not who I am!
I'm Asuka Langley Soryu. Nice to meet you!
Are you an idiot or something?
Here's my chance!
So please look at me!
No! That's not who I am!
I'm Asuka Langley Soryu. Nice to meet you!
Are you an idiot or something?
Here's my chance!
So please look at me!
No! That's not who I am!
I'm Asuka Langley Soryu. Nice to meet you!
Are you an idiot or something?
Here's my chance!
So please look at me!
No! That's not who I am!
I'm Asuka Langley Soryu. Nice to meet you!
Are you an idiot or something?
Here's my chance!
So please look at me!
No! That's not who I am!
Help me! Help me, Mr. Kaji!
Sorry, you're still just a kid, Asuka.
What the hell are you doing there?!
You just stand there! You won't help me!
You won't even hold me!
Nobody does! Nobody! Nobody!
So, please, look at me!
Are you lonely?
No!
Get away from me!
I'm going to live on my own!
Tell me, do you like me?
I won't depend on anyone else!
Do you really like me?
I can live on my own just fine!
You're full of it.
No!
My mind... It's been defiled.
Mr. Kaji, I've been defiled...
What should I do? I'm dirty now...
-Unit 02 has ceased operation!
-Life support showing abnormalities!
Pilot is entering danger zone!
No change in target status.
Relative distance still unchanged.
Chances of target moving into
Unit 00's firing range, 0.02%.
Do we airlift Unit 00
and fire at it from the sky?
No, that won't work.
If it fires during our approach,
it's all over.
I'll go in Unit 01!
Absolutely not! This type of Angel
corrupts the pilot's psyche!
We must avoid any situation
where Unit 01 might be compromised.
I just need to make sure
I don't get hit, right?
That may not be enough.
But if we don't do something,
Asuka's gonna--
So be it. Rei, go down into
the Dogma and use the Spear.
The Spear of Longinus? Ikari, that will--
It's the only way to defeat an Angel in
orbit, where our A.T. Fields can't reach.
Do it!
But what about the risk of contact between
Adam and an Eva causing the Third Impact?!
It's far too dangerous!
Commander Ikari, don't do this!
So, it's a lie. A deception.
The Second Impact wasn't caused
by contact with an Angel.
Opening Central Dogma
levels 10 through 15.
Unit 00 now passing Malebolge No.6.
Now opening levels 16 through 20.
So this won't cause the Third Impact?
Then what was the cause
of the Second Impact?
Ikari, isn't it too early for this?
The Council has begun
mass production of the Eva series.
This is our chance, Fuyutsuki.
Even so...
We can't turn back the hands of the clock.
But we can force them forward.
The old men won't stand for this.
We have to complete everything
before Seele can act.
It would be unwise
to lose Unit 02. Not yet.
Using the Spear of Longinus without
Seele's permission will cause trouble.
It's enough that a reason to exists.
Anything beyond that is trivial.
A reason? What you want is a pretext.
Unit 02's pilot's brainwaves down to 0.06!
Life support now at critical!
Unit 00 now passing level two.
Exiting to the surface.
That's the Spear of Longinus?
Unit 00 in throwing position!
Target acquired! Corrections complete!
Beginning countdown! T minus 10!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two! One!
Zero!
Target obliterated!
-Eva-02 has been released!
-What about the Spear of Longinus?
It's exceeded first cosmic velocity.
It's currently heading for lunar orbit.
Retrieval is next to impossible, then...
Yes, sir. We currently have no means of
retrieving a mass of that magnitude.
Unit 02 operational.
Graphs are back to normal values.
Recover Unit 02 to Cage No.2.
Please use Route 67.
How's Asuka?
Pilot's vitals confirmed.
Quarantine measures due to
contamination have been lifted.
I see.
I'm glad you're okay, Asuka.
Screw you! I'm not even close to okay!
Why did I have to be saved
by her of all people?!
Someone like her saved me!
If it meant being saved by her,
I wish I had died instead!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate all of you!
I hate you all!
TO BE CONTINUED
NEXT EPISODE
Latched onto by an Angel,
Unit 00 and its pilot are violated.
However, even as her body
and soul are being corrupted,
she never loses her sense of self.
But to save Shinji from the Angel,
Rei wishes for her own death.
Transforming into light and heat
along with Tokyo-3, she vanishes...
leaving behind nothing
but memories in people's souls.
Next episode! "Tears"!
Translator: Dan Kanemitsu
Subtitle Editor: David Fleming