Hi, everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can, okay?
Well, well, well.
Have any of you ever told the
person you love how you feel?
"I love you." Like that.
Oh, it makes you so shy, doesn't it?
Actually, Mr. Policeman says
he's decided to propose to Miss Kate!
That Mr. Policeman. He may look a little scary,
but even he gets nervous
when push comes to shove.
Have courage! It's all about guts! Right, Ken?
Huh, you look kinda down...
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
What if I told you to become my partner?
Hey... Let me go!
Are you the one?
Mr. Leon, please stop it!
Are you the one who can become my partner?
Sophie! Sophie!
Mr. Leon...
Sophie... I'm so glad...
Mr. Leon has another side to him.
It's different than the
cold side he always shows.
It's warm...
And sad...
But Mr. Leon is someone who fights.
I've decided not to fight onstage anymore.
So I can't become his partner.
The path I'm trying to walk is different
from Mr. Leon's and from Miss Layla's.
It's mine and mine alone.
Someday when I can get back to the stage,
my goal is a stage with no battling,
where the audience and
the performers are all smiling.
That's the kind of
Kaleido Stage I want to create.
"Mr. Policeman's Amazing Proposal."
Here she is.
I'm so nervous.
I thought you would be.
I figured something like this would
happen, so I brought something!
Jonathan, get it out!
What's that thing?
"The Perfect Dating Manual:
100 Ways To Captivate Her Heart!"
If you don't want to have
Sora stolen from you by Leon,
then captivate her, even if
you have to use that book. Got it?
Captivate?
Don't worry, that looks good on you.
Hearing that doesn't make me happy.
Plus, if she sees me in this and
thinks I've teamed up with Anna...
That would be fun too.
When she's in trouble, that's your chance.
While you tenderly take care of her,
take advantage of her confusion
and invite her out on a date.
Then take her to a nice, extravagant lunch.
Then her heart is totally unguarded.
Hey guys, let's set high hopes!
No, Ken can't hope for much.
What?
At least make Sora feel better.
But...
Thanks for always helping me, Ken!
He is not my boyfriend
or anything at all like that!
What was it you wanted to talk about, again?
Ken, I didn't see you there!
Men need to have guts!
Women need to have guts too!
In this world, it's about guts!
So get out there!
Sora! What's wrong? Did you hit
your head anywhere or anything?!
When she's in trouble, that's your chance.
This isn't the time for that.
Are you all right, Sora?
Oh, Ken!
I wasn't looking where I was
walking and I bumped into you.
You weren't looking?
Actually, what are you doing here?
Are you going on a hospital visit too?
No, it doesn't look like it.
Oh, no, I was waiting for you.
I was wondering if maybe
you'd have lunch with me.
Me?
Could Ken be trying to cheer me up?
Wearing that silly suit, even?
Come to think of it, I've done
nothing lately but worry everyone.
Okay, in that case I'll have so
much fun that I'll surprise Ken!
Thank you, Ken! I was just getting hungry.
Really?
Yeah, let's go!
Yeah!
That outfit looks good on you.
Really?
Really! Are you going to team up with Anna?
I'm going to go change now.
They left.
Was that a success?
It's hard to tell.
Let's follow them.
Right.
It's a really good restaurant.
And the view from the terrace is great.
I was just there last week
with a friend from middle school.
Yeah, if we turn at this corner...
There's a... laundromat that's been shut down...
Um...
If we turn that corner on the other end...
...there's a bowling alley
that's been shut down,
and if we turn this corner up here...
...there's the ocean.
And we ended up here because...
there are complex reasons...
Maybe the map in that book is wrong?
It can't be! Papa got Mama by using that book!
How many years ago was that?
That was before I was born,
so I can't really tell you.
Oh, Ken's started to do something!
He's turning to the manual for help...
At times like this...
In unexpected situations,
make the appropriate decision!
If the restaurant you're
going to has been closed down,
remember whether there's
another restaurant you know close by!
With the power of love
that we call the fighting spirit!
Huh?
Sora? Sora!
Sora?! Sora?!
Maybe this job was too much for Ken.
Sora?!
Ken!
Sora!
There's a hot dog stand over there!
So, want to have hot dogs then?
I don't see a terrace, but
there's a good view of the ocean.
Really?
This is good!
And there's a great view.
When the weather's nice,
hanging out outside is the best, isn't it?
Thanks for inviting me, Ken.
Yu'h wegkome.
What's the point of me
getting cheered up by her?!
Life is so good!
I am a man, after all.
I have to take the lead!
It really is nice weather, isn't it?
Yeah, it feels good.
Nice weather...
I just need a little more courage...
Oh, it's Mr. Policeman.
Mr. Policeman!
Sora... Sora!
Mr. Policeman, don't take dangerous
shortcuts when you're in a hurry!
Sora, I'm begging you! Please help me!
Mr. Policeman?
You're going to propose to Miss Kate?
Yeah. Making a romantic
proposal by my thirtieth birthday
has been my dream ever since I was a kid.
But...
When you think "What if I ask
her and she dodges the question?"
you get so you just can't say the words.
So you understand me?!
Yes, I feel your pain as if it were mine!
So, when is your thirtieth
birthday, Mr. Policeman?
The truth is, it's today.
Today?
For real?
For real.
Then you have to hurry
up and go see Miss Kate!
But she's on vacation from the
hospital and she's not at home.
Here I've got the day off too,
and I can't even see her.
Maybe this just means that
dreams are better off staying dreams.
Mr. Policeman...
"Dreams are better off staying dreams."
No, we have dreams so they can come true!
We do whatever we can to make that happen!
Mr. Policeman.
Let's go, Mr. Policeman.
Let's go make your dream come true.
Sora...
Come on, hurry!
Yeah!
That's kind of a strange turn of events.
But it's okay, because it
looks like Sora's feeling better!
First of all, we have to find Miss Kate.
I wonder if we can find her.
Sometimes if your timing is bad,
otherwise easy things go badly.
Maybe it's hopeless after all.
Come on, don't be pessimistic!
The chance will definitely come!
You have to believe that!
That's right!
It's just like Sora says!
What good will it do for me to lose heart?
The chance will come for sure!
Hey, isn't that Miss Kate?
Hi, Kate.
Were you waiting long, Roberto?
It looks like I've got no chance of winning.
That's not true.
With men,
it's really not about looks or brains or money...
Yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah!
...it's about warmth and sincerity!
And Miss Kate knows
all about your good points!
Anyway, I'll go find out.
Sora, what do you mean, "find out"?
She left.
If this is a dream that won't be
fulfilled, maybe I'd rather wake up.
I'm sick of this.
That's what I'd like to say!
How long are we going to keep doing this?
Oh, I like the way you're doing it now.
How about laughing with your
feelings bursting out like that?
Do you remember how
the audience looked at you
when you were on the
stage with Leon and Sora?
No.
This is going to take longer than I thought.
This is supposed to be special training?
Is this a new kind of performance?
Maybe it's a TV shoot?
Or just some weirdoes?
Might be best not to make eye contact.
This is getting more and more complicated.
Let's be careful not to let
them find out who we are.
If anyone finds out,
I won't be able to go to school.
Oh, Roberto's only a colleague.
He just went shopping with me today, that's all.
Oh, I see.
But why do you ask?
You see, I had something I wanted to ask you...
It's because I didn't eat a whole meal before...
My, my.
Say, let's go eat.
Today's payday, so I'll treat you.
I'm going to go to the bank
for a second, so come with me.
Oh, I have to tell
Mr. Policeman he can rest easy.
I don't understand what she's trying to say.
My unease only grows.
Let's go.
Right.
Why's it doing that at this time of day?
I've got a bad feeling.
Sora!
What is it? What's going on?
It couldn't be a bank robbery, could it?
No way.
Hand over the money quietly!
Don't underestimate me.
I'm the unluckiest man in the world!
Kate!
Jerry?
Mr. Policeman! Ken!
Policeman? Really?!
Really. Now, let go of Kate.
You've got to be kidding!
Dammit, my first bank robbery
ever and there's a policeman?!
I really am the unluckiest man in the world!
You guys! Now you get that
I'm telling the truth, don't you?
I'm serious!
Everybody on the second floor,
you come down here too!
Hey, you, tie the policeman up with this!
What? Me?
Yeah, hurry up!
Yes, sir.
Tie him tightly. I'm gonna
check up on you afterwards.
If there's not enough rope,
there's plenty more in my bag.
Preparation is the one thing I'm good at.
My grandma always praised me for it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Policeman.
If we pull any stupid tricks,
you'll be in danger.
You can tie it tightly.
It's a patrol car.
You're kidding!
If you guys contact the police you'll be sorry!
Aw, man, am I closing the barn door too late?
Even if they don't report everything,
the inside of this bank is set up
so it can be constantly monitored.
Really?!
I didn't know that.
That's just what you'd expect from me.
I really am the unluckiest man in the world.
Looks like it really is a bank robbery.
Sora...
Attention, criminal! Release the
hostages quietly and come out!
Everything that happens in there
is being watched on our monitors!
It looks like all of the hostages are safe.
If you stop now, your crimes are still light.
You might be dissatisfied about
some things in this world, but so are we!
Well?
Can you see?
Yeah.
Do you know how little pocket money
Sort of.
my wife lets me have each day?
It's really...
There they are!
It's not a number I can say in front of people!
Sora and Ken are both okay!
Jeez.
The world's full of phonies!
I'm always at a disadvantage.
But I was supposed to
stop feeling like that today.
I wanted money to make my dream come true.
It doesn't have to be a fortune.
My dream's a small one.
Go to a country with a low
cost of living and no phonies,
meet a woman who
doesn't call me a blockhead,
and get hold of a little bit of happiness.
Why doesn't a tiny dream
like that come true?! Huh?!
Is it me?! Is it my fault?!
What do you think?
I'm not sure.
Do you have a dream?
Yes...
Does it look like it'll come true?
It'll come true. I'll make it come true.
You're pretty sure of yourself.
What kind of a dream is it?
To create a Kaleido Stage
where everyone can smile!
Kaleido Stage?
Are you one of the Kaleido Stage cast?
That's just a phony show!
Phony?!
What do you mean by phony?
The Kaleido Stage isn't phony!
So you're from Kaleido Stage too?
I'm not gonna get taken in by phonies anymore!
I'm going to doubt everything that's
unbelievable and live life on the winning side.
I don't believe anything
I don't see with my own eyes.
I've been reborn as a man with a heart of steel!
I'll show you, then.
Show me what?
Wait, Sora!
Hey, Sora...
I'll give you a performance here and now.
Here and now?
Sora, now's not the time for that!
He's right, Sora.
I'm talking to this girl about dreams right now!
Don't butt in!
You said your dream was to
make everyone smile, didn't you?
Yes.
Then make me smile.
Me, the man with the steel heart.
All right.
Whoa! That's amazing!
I'm borrowing your rope.
Uh, go ahead.
Now then, please sit back
and watch through to the end.
Okay.
...and what do you think my
daughter's boyfriend called me?
Hey, what's this?
What is it?
Sora is...
...doing a show.
I wanna see! I wanna see!
So Mia, which bank is it?
I have to hurry or it'll be over!
Hey, come to think of it...
Is that a smile?
You're done?
Come in.
I thought you'd be here!
You've been coming here every
day lately, so I figured you might be!
What do you want?
Mia called me and said Sora's
doing a police drama at a bank
and it's on TV and they're shooting right now!
Come on, wanna go watch?
I can't tell what she's talking about.
Well, if we go we'll figure it out.
There's no point in doing
any more today anyway.
Please wait! I'll keep trying! Miss Layla...
Let's go.
All right.
You come too, May!
Oh, I'm so sorry, thank you so
much for driving me there too!
That really wasn't my intention
when I told you about it, I swear!
Oh, no, the more the merrier.
Although it's a bit cramped.
Right now, this is my stage.
For the people who are watching me,
and for that man, I'll give it my all!
Sora!
Oh, wow!
It's really not rigged?
Everyone's made me remember
what it feels like to be the audience.
More than the amazing performances,
it was the way everyone onstage
looked like they had so much fun
that was the biggest reason
I fell in love with Kaleido Stage.
After I understood that my mom
and dad weren't ever coming back,
somehow before I knew it I was
always thinking about Kaleido Stage.
That was because I felt
like if I went to Kaleido Stage,
I could have fun again like I did that time.
She'll fall!
You just smiled, didn't you.
Looks like Sora won this one.
Looks like it.
Do you know why Sora worked so hard for you?
Naturally, one reason was to
prove that Kaleido Stage isn't phony.
But the other one was that Sora
wants you to get your smile back.
No, not just you.
She wants all the people
who watch her show to smile,
and all the people who
perform onstage with her too.
You know, I want to create a Kaleido Stage
where the audience and
the cast can all have fun.
I like it when people smile.
Sure, that's a tough dream to make
happen, but Sora thinks she can do it.
That's why she works so hard.
For her dream, huh?
That's why I've decided to try
working a little for my dream too.
You too?
I'm going to propose to that woman.
My dream's as small as yours, huh?
Mine isn't a dream.
I was just a loser looking for place to escape to.
Start all over again.
Yeah, that's what I'll do.
Then...
Hold it. I'll leave by myself.
I'm not the one you really have to catch, right?
Hey! You can stop, I get it.
I take back what I said
about it being phony. I'm sorry.
You mean...
It was fun. Thanks.
Next time, please come to
see the show at Kaleido Stage!
Sure.
It's over already? What a shame.
But still, it was a good show.
That was great, Sora! Yay Sora!
Sora!
Sora's as great as ever.
It hurts, but her moves were definitely good.
And she wasn't even onstage...
What does Sora have that I don't have?
Oh, thank you, thank you.
It feels like back when we were kids, huh?
Wonder Kate rescued Crybaby Jerry
all the time when he got bullied.
I built up my body because
I didn't like the way I was then, but...
Jerry, your good point is your kindness.
Kate...
What?
I want to put you under eternal arrest!
Happy thirtieth birthday!
I'll arrest you too.
Kate!
It looks like right now, the stage is
still the only thing that captivates Sora.
What Sagittarius wants...
A stage with no battling,
colored only by smiles.
It's an extremely foolish dream.
It's foolish, and therefore
it's a path no one dares to walk.
What awaits at the end is either applause...
or scorn.
One of those two.
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation, I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
What is this feeling springing up inside of me?
And so! In the end,
everyone's smiles really are the best!
Whatever it is Sora's got that I don't...
It hurts, but I'll find out what that is for sure!
A great performance with
May at Mr. Kenneth's event!
And... here goes, Rosetta!
Okay, Teacher!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Launching An Amazing Smile!"
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...