It's finally time to publish my new and improved art!
Finally settling things with Nidou-san, eh?
Are you confident?
Yes I am.  Absolutely.
Even if Nidou-san's book is really amazing?
Of course.
That's a little troublesome.
Even if Hoshi-kun won't buy one?
That's more than a little troublesome.
Well, I'm rooting for you.
That devil!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
oshitari? hiitari?
Pushing? Pulling?
sakusen!! doushiyou?!
Which strategy should I use?
oh! what a night! tomaranai
Oh, what a night! Don't let it end,
risou to mousou bousou BATORU
This out of control battle of dream and delusion
mekuru meku sekai jinsei kore deai
This amazing world!  For life to encounter this..
ikenai? demo mitai nee motto motto
I shouldn't, but I want to see!  It'll make me more and
doki doki doki doki doki doki doki doki
More and more and more and more and
shichaundeshou?
More excited, won’t it?
iijan iijan iijan iijan isshoumon no yuujou
It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! It's fine! Lifelong friendship!
HIIROO mitai ja nai kedo guttokichaimasu
He doesn't look like a hero, but he'll come running to
kimi boku dare? sore are kare dare de mo OK! donna basho de mo
You, Me, Who? This, that, him, whoever, OK! Wherever we are!
minna to ireba saikou no hoshi nan desu
If we’re together it’s the best planet ever!
Chance to get up!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get up! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimero
Just decide!
Chance to get dream!! (Yeah&Yeah)
Chance to get dream! Yeah, yeah!
Just kimena
Just decide!
I can't get used to this packed train.
It's even more crowded than usual, too.
Ah, I'm so sorry!  Are you oka-
Nidou-san?
Eh? Najimi-san?
Ah, Tsuyuri-san, good morning.
Good morning.
I'm looking forward to watching you two compete.
It's not a competition, I'll just be selling at my own pace.
M-me too!
Oh?  I thought you were starting the battle by stomping her foot.
I would never do something cheap like that!
S-something like that doesn't faze me.
I said it wasn't on purpose.
Ara?  Have a seat, Najimi-san.
No thank you.
You should take it.
Well, I plan to finish selling by noon.
I'll be able to sit down on the train home before it gets crowded again.
I'm still young, so I'll be alright.
There it is!
Hey, you're late, Nidou-san!
I didn't think you were participating today, Najimi-san.
Umm, excuse me...
Please don't run inside the hall.
I-I'm sorry.
Please make sure.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Justice! We're half sold out.
Justice?
Ah, sorry, Sora. I was just thinking.
Is something bothering you?
Wanna talk to me about it?
Yes, it's about Najimi's new book.
Oh, so you've seen it.
About that...
Well? Are you speechless from amazement?
No, it's just...
Disappointment beyond words.
All the faces are from the same angle.
That's not all.
Not once do you draw the body.
I'm amazed that you two noticed.
It'd be difficult not to notice.
This upcoming Comic Festival is my match against Nidou-san.
So I have to make a higher quality manga.
I see.  Najimi can only draw faces from this angle.
So you're betting everything on this.
Yep, not a bad strategy, eh?
Well, maybe you can fool two or three people...
Alright!
Two or three is enough for you, eh?
That probably won't do well.
Then let's finish selling and cheer Najimi on.
Eh?
Geez, Justice always acts like he's Najimi's dad!
Sora!
Justice!
Thank you, Sora.
Jus-ti-ce~!
Thank you very much.
Whew, it got busy there for a sec.
H-how are you doing?
Totally awesome.
Just our enthusiasm...
Hey, do you want to check out my new volume?
Well, aren't you just full of confidence?
The cover looks pretty good, but...
I-it's what's on the inside that counts.
So good!
So the first of the two or three people was right next to her.
In such a short period of time...
Unbelievable.
Just accept the truth before you.
Nidou-san, don't be fooled.
That manga only has faces from a single angle.
But it's really good...
Right?
No, no. It means she can't draw anything else.
I see! You perfected the one thing you can draw.
So smart!
That's kinda wrong too, but...
This manga also doesn't have bodies.
It's an ero-manga, but it's not erotic.
So don't worry, who knows who will win the competition.
W-well, how's your new volume, Nidou-san?
May I look?
No... That's...
No, Tsuyuri-san told me to cater to girls.
It's not like I like to draw that kind of stuff.
It went smoothly while I was drawing it but...
How should I say this?
T-tsuyuri, have you seen this?
I haven't seen the printed version yet.
I'm not good at drawing yet, I know.
But I think mine is more erotic than yours, Najimi-san.
Yes, definitely.
R-really?
Yes, it's too erotic to be sold.
You're going too far now.
No, but you forgot to put a mosaic on this stuff.
Well, at least you noticed before you sold any...
Right?
Nidou-san, I fixed all these with a marker.
Now you can sell them.
Tsuyuri-san!
We're back to where we started.
Yeah...
Now that they're censored, no problem.
It was perverted beyond imagination.
You're an awfully dirty girl.
What are you doing?
Hi, Najimi-san.
Tsuyuri-san, Kaneru-san, too, you're all here.
Huh?  You know her?
Thanks for the other day.
Have you gotten Justice-san's new book?
No... I haven't gotten it yet.
That's no good!
You have to go straight to the person you like.
Yes, that's why... I'm here.
Oh!  He doesn't have to go buy them, he gets them straight from Justice-san.
I should mind my own business.
Ah, Hoshi-san, this is my book.
I think it'll suit your tastes.
You like it right? Hoshi-san.
I-i'm not sure if it's what I like...
but it's pretty well drawn.
You tried really hard, I'd like to buy one.
Yes!  Thank you very much.
Hoshi-kun is my fan, you know.
This is my new book.
Right.  Wow, you've gotten so much better.
I can't wait to see inside.
Would you buy like three, if you want?
What happened?
Isn't it great?  I tried really hard.
You normally put in so much effort despite your lack of skill.
This book just seems like you're afraid of failure.
The manga of yours I love...
Isn't like this!
Hoshi-kun...
Hmm...  so he did like Najimi's manga.
He's your fan, but he only bought my book.
I guess some people know a better book when they see one.
I'd like to buy this.
Thank you very much!
I'd like to buy one!
How much is it?
I'd like one, too.
Me too.
Thank you very much!
I'd like one, too.
Najimi, how are things going?
Sell any?
I sold five!
Yay!
Alright, congratulations.
Wow.
Keep up this pace for next time.
I-I guess!
Cheer up, it may only be one, but you sold your manga.
Besides, winning and losing don't really matter.
But your fan bought the one I sold.
I think the one he bought is worth more than the five you sold.
One is one!
Just accept your loss.
But you said that winning and losing doesn't matter.
Kaneru-chan.
Najimi...
Hmm?
How do you feel about winning?
Well, it kinda hurt when my only fan didn't buy one...
But I guess I need to draw better.
What?
I wonder what happened to actually making money.
Of course that's my number one concern!
I need to draw better in order to make money.
I see.
Yeah.
Father, Mother! Najimi isn't going to go crazy for doujin works!
I'll make you feel better.
What are you talking about?
Najimi, I can see it all.
fushigi itsu no ma ni ka
It's strange
hajime no ippo fumidaseba
Before I noticed
maru de yosou gai de
After taking the first step, despite my predictions
iya mo iya mo suki ni naru
It might be icky, but I'm starting to like it,
hontou no watashi ga mezamechatta!?
Has the real me woken up?
mufufu miryoku kamo ne
Hah ha ha! It might be charming,
jinsei kake masshigura
To live life fast and free.
sora wa PINKU iro de
The sky has turned pink,
BURUMA mo BYUtto tonde iku
Even bloomers fly through the air,
mitaiken na ERIA saa susumou!!
An area I haven't experienced! Now, forward!
yume miru otome wa SUI SUI CHAO!
Girls who dream can do anything smoothly,
kewashii michi mo hiraoyogi
Swim through even the hardest path,
mizutamamoyou no ashita ni naare
Get used to a polka dot future,
dakara ganbaccha Oh!
So then, let's give it our all!
Thank you for your patience.
Next time, we'll bring you swimsuits and someone fresh out of the bath.
We'll be waiting.