How do I look?
Yeah, looks good...
...I think.
Umm...
I'll pick something else.
Come on. Hurry up!
Time is limited, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, it's this way! Are you even looking at the map?
I am!
Oh! I'm gonna go take a look in that store real quick!
All right.
Can I borrow your wallet?
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Nice to meet you.
Are you going to carry that around with you?
Yup!
Come on, I know a good place around here.
Let's sit over there.
I'll pay for that.
Idiot.
You didn't have to order this much.
No, it was my fault after all.
Please help yourself.
Thanks.
Mm, this is good!
Are you two students?
Yeah, we are.
Today's a weekday.
Skipping school, eh?
It's the anniversary of our school's founding.
A school-sponsored party is boring, anyway.
Yeah, I used to skip those too.
See?
Sorry.
You have ice cream on your face.
You are so careless, Wallace.
Let's go.
Do you have a clear understanding of the mall structure now?
I crammed it into my head.
How many security cameras are on Main Street?
Sixty-eight.
There are a lot of blind spots, but they won't make our mission any easier.
Don't get involved with other people so thoughtlessly.
Sorry about that.
Let's go back to discuss the mission.
The luggage should be arriving right about now.
Roger.
Zwei.
Your acting...
...sucks.
Since we've obtained Zwei, Phantom has been able to perform missions more efficiently.
They're an ideal pairing.
They look like a bunch of useless brats,
but I'll praise them since they helped us advance into the east coast five months earlier than we planned.
The highest of honors.
However, don't you find it dangerous?
That we're continuously using Phantom like this.
I wholeheartedly agree with you.
I believe that the wise thing to do would be to carefully postpone the plan.
This may be rude of me, but if you trust me and Phantom, I'd like you to allow the plan to be carried out.
To be absolutely sure, I will head to the site myself.
Oh? You're pretty fired up, aren't you?
Very well.
I'll leave it to your Phantom.
I am eternally grateful.
The fake name that was given to me was Wallace Yang.
He's a student living in Los Angeles.
It's the same name as the first man I killed.
Ever since I killed him, I've been working all this time...
...the work of killing people...
...together with her.
I...
Don Lucio.
The boss of a Dallas mafia family.
He tries to stay inside his mansion, which has strict security.
But there will be an exception in three days.
He'll go to that mall to buy a birthday present for his granddaughter.
That's...
This is for us.
The target arrives at the scene around three o'clock tomorrow afternoon.
We'll take up positions in the ideal locations before that.
Where do you think the ideal locations are?
You decide.
Another test?
That's what Master ordered.
We'll mingle with the shoppers and approach the target.
People won't suspect us.
But we can't shoot him inside the mall.
Why?
It's too wide open.
There'll probably be a lot of guards, too.
They've also gained control of the security cameras.
We should attack him somewhere inconspicuous and with fewer guards.
And where would that be?
There's only one answer.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
That's...
That's enough.
That's the right answer.
Let's go back now.
Yeah.
What's up?
I've confirmed the target. But I've been marked.
There are two tracers on me. Help me fool them.
Come to the fountain in front of the elevator. Quickly.
How long do you think I've waited?!
Geez! I've already gone and looked around by myself!
Sorry...
I don't want to hear your excuses.
So, how are you going to make up for wasting my time today?
Well...
Depending on your answer, I might be going home.
Fine, fine. I'll carry everything you buy today.
Will you pay for dinner, too?
Sure.
I've already found all the stores.
You saved me the trouble.
It's your fault, Wallace.
I said sorry, didn't I?
The target is at an antique store in the south mall.
His car will be sent to the south exit to pick him up.
Are we going to proceed?
Thank you very much.
I think this one looks good on you.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'll attack, so cover me.
Roger that.
The moment the target and his guards relax...
Now we bring this to an end.
Well done, you two.
What is it?
Nothing.
No, nothing.
Nothing...
I'm honored that you went through the trouble to come and greet me.
It's natural for a superior to show her appreciation to her subordinate.
You did a good job. I appreciate it.
Not at all.
That boy transformed, didn't he?
Are you satisfied?
Yeah, I guess...
Is something the matter?
No.
Where are those two?
I'll have them return via a passenger flight after taking care of the equipment.
Are you interested?
Not really.
I see...
Maybe she's tired from waiting?
Oh, you're the person from yesterday...
Taking a trip?
We took a trip here. Now we're heading back.
I see. Did you have a good trip?
Yes... it was great.
Good. It'd be nice if we could see each other again.
Well then!
Bye.
That was...
...good acting.
Two dogs in a doghouse, just waiting to be given a task...
That's... what we are now.
And... again...
Something wrong?
Nothing.
Don't worry about it.
What Master said was right.
Within three months, he ran through the path that took me two years.
He is... who I used to be...
He is... another me...
I'm afraid...
...of the truth...
...I might see who I really am...
Your eyes...
...scare me...
We get rid of our emotions and pull the trigger.
We take others' happiness away.