With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Catch!
That's Kaidou White Beach.
Over there is Grand Hotel Kaidou,
which is right next to the Kaidou Aquarium.
We're in the Ocean View Kaidou right now.
They're all part of this resort that the Kaidou family built to help people enjoy the sea.
You guys made all of this?!
This entire beach belongs to the Kaidou family.
I come here every summer.
Whoah...
The Kaidou Group is a global corporation
and an industry leader in numerous fields.
You didn't know?
I had no idea!
I knew Minami was a big shot, but I didn't know how big!
I can't take credit for this.
That goes to the one managing this resort, my brother.
That ship belongs to one of my brother's companies.
My brother manages the resorts and
serves as the president for ten companies.
Ten? Like, whole companies?!
He may be young for a president, but he's a hard worker.
I just do what I can.
Hi there, allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Kaidou Wataru.
Brother!
That boy...
...is her brother!
A Vow to the Sea!
Minami's Dear Treasure!
Haruka, what's wrong?
N-Nothing!
I mean, I can swim...
but I've never swam in water deeper than my feet...
Don't worry, just take it slow.
It's not scary if you relax.
This takes me back!
Huh?
Minami couldn't swim a bit when we were kids!
She'd always cry to me about how scary the sea was!
Really?
Oh?
Th-That's ancient history!
I started from when I couldn't swim at all,
so Haruka should be fine.
But...
I love this place, so I want you to see it too.
Okay!
Wow! It's so pretty!
I know!
Tina!
It's a dolphin!
It's been forever! How are you?
I missed you too!
Is that dolphin your pet?
No, it's a wild one, but it's been
Minami's friend since she was a kid.
Being friends with a dolphin sounds splendid!
That's our princess of the sea!
Sea Appreciation
Festival
The Kaidou group first found its footing on this land.
We'd like to extend our deepest gratitude...
to the sea for nurturing us and to you all for supporting us.
But let's not get too mushy, now!
Today is a day for playing in the sea and savoring its bounty!
Let's all have a good time!
This is some tasty bounty!
Long time no see, Minami.
Same to you. How have you been?
Just dandy! Thanks to your brother, my shop's been in the black!
You all can have a fruit platter on the house.
Thank you very much!
Wow, bon appétit!
Haruharu, don't overeat!
Teehee!
Kid Pres, the cavalry's here!
Oh, what a catch! I see you haven't lost your touch.
Darn right!
Wataru, have some fresh octopus sashimi!
Oh, that looks great! Don't mind if I do!
Your brother's pretty popular.
He's a president, but still down to earth, so I can see why.
My brother does more than just manage the companies our father left him.
He tries to treasure their people above all else.
He always says it's people that make a company.
You're planning to join a Kaidou Group company too, right?
Yes. I plan to manage and lead as a member of the Kaidou family.
To do that, I have to be the best I can be.
I need to move people's hearts the way my brother can.
I think you already can.
After all, I learned to love the sea thanks to you!
Did you? That's good to hear!
Princess Twilight's Key desires despair.
It's been a snoozefest lately, so let's make it a game, 'kay?
We'll see who can make a Dyspairvil that pleases Princess Twilight first.
Only if you ain't chicken, 'kay?
I'll do naught but accept!
Sweet.
There's naught but to use me!
Use me, 'kay?
Did I really say that?
Yeah, I could've sworn you did.
The second you learned to swim,
you shouted that you'd be a dolphin!
Well, I recall you saying that you'd be a whale when you grew up.
Because whales are the kings of the sea.
I meant that I wanted to become stronger.
I need to be as strong as the whales that swim across the world.
Work's been... hard, right?
No job is a walk in the park.
I get worn out at times,
but I come here when that happens.
I've been around the world, but I like it here.
Looking at this sea soothes my soul.
That's why I always want to protect this sea.
Yes, I feel the same.
Besides, seeing the smile on my dear sister's face always cheers me up!
Goodness, we're not children...
Why does my chest ache?
Shut! Lock!
Right!
Later, slowpoke!
You cheater!
Work's calling, so I should get back.
Sorry, we'll talk later!
Sure!
Don't worry, I'm still here.
Who are you?
Show me your dream, 'kay?
I'll use the sea to bring people together!
I'm gonna throw that dream in the cage of despair, 'kay?
Lock your dream!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspairvil!
Brother!
I'm stuffed!
Relaxing on the beach after a feast is simply bliss!
I love the beach!
It's so soothing!
Haruka!
Kanata?!
Sir Kanata!
What brings you here?
I feel the presence of a new Dress Up Key.
It's very close by.
Really?
What was that?
Dyspair!
Now let's get this game started!
Tina, swim away!
You dare use my brother?!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dys! Pair! Vil!
Mermaid!
Girls!
He used your brother!
Haruharu, let's go!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Dyspairvil!
Flora!
Dyspaaaairvil!
Dyspair!
I may be fashionably late,
but I've naught but to defeat you!
There's another Dyspairvil?
What will you do, Princess Precures?
Heart Arrange!
Dys...
Dyspairvil!
Mermaid!
Are you all right?
Yeah, thanks!
Twinkle!
I can fight underwater, so leave the sea Dyspairvil to me.
Okay!
Dyspair!
Tina, take everyone with you and hide deep in a cave!
I'm counting on you.
I need to be as strong as the whales that swim across the world.
I won't let you get away with warping my brother's love for the sea!
Vil!
Dyspair...
Twinkle!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair!
Flora!
Dyspairvil!
Flora! Twinkle!
Excellent! There is naught but to drag them into the sea!
Yes, give in to despair.
Dreams are but bubbles that vanish into the ether.
Dyspairvil!
Good job, Dyspairvil.
Keep it up and bring these seas to ruin!
Dyspair!
Dyspairvil!
I'm... saved?
Tina!
Hang on, Tina!
Dyspairvil!
Look out!
Where am I?
Did you save me?
Thank you!
Hey, Dolphin, what's your name?
Maybe... Tina?
Tina, nice to meet you!
Tina!
Are you okay? Hang on!
You saved me once again?
And yet I couldn't...
Tina!
No, don't close your eyes!
Everyone...
Could it be...
What is that light?
This bubble is shielding us!
Tina!
This is a new Dress Up Key!
I see... These bubbles...
allow me to feel the wills of every being in the ocean!
They've tasked me with saving the ocean and granted me a great power to do it!
Wait here, everyone!
For all of you living in this ocean...
and for my brother's love of these seas...
I'll defeat anyone who threatens you!
Dyspair!
Mermaid!
Viiiiil!
What is that power?
Is that...
It's a new Key! The Miracle Dress Up Key!
This is more than just a Key!
It carries the wills of every being in the ocean!
You dared to use my brother's love for the sea to ruin its beauty!
Neither the Key nor I will let you get away!
A new Dress Up Key...
I cannot leave it in your possession!
Lock, procure that Key.
Right!
Get goin' Dyspairvil, 'kay?
Dyspair!
You won't take my Key, but you will take this!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Now!
Dyspairvil!
Gah! Oh no!
Flora! Twinkle!
Okay!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Rose!
Ice!
Luna!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Lumière!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
I had assumed she, like Flora, was a false princess unworthy of the slightest attention...
but I'll remember your name, Cure Mermaid.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Brother... thank goodness you're safe.
Hey, Wataru!
Let's play together!
Sure, I'll play along!
I was worried about how they'd cope, but it doesn't look like anyone remembers what happened.
That's for the best as long as they all enjoy the sea.
But they still remember.
All the fish got together to show how happy they are!
Looks like everyone in the ocean saw what Mermaid did for them.
Tina...
I protected this sea.
I'm glad you're all safe.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Kirara, you're finally sharing the stage with your mom!
Mrs. Stella is like a princess of the modeling world!
It must be splendid to have someone like her as a mom!
Well, Mom's not the most mature...
Are you nervous?
What? No, I'm totally not!
Go! Princess Precure:
As Bright As the Stars!
The Runway of Kirara's Dreams!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hiroshima Prefecture - Riko (Age 6)
Hyougo Prefecture - Yuri (Age 7)