"White Room" "Large Window" "Mayu"
Ta... Tama?!
Taken and granted,
ideals are repetitious games that slip through
My daily life is so shot with holes
that I can barely stand
Empty theories without conclusions
Dance steps along invisible rules
The final bell holding together
the crumbling day rings
In the scene I imagine
you're there
with a smile
No forgiveness? No desires?
And still
We cry "OPEN"
A future to get back and a world to destroy
A wish to open. GOT IT?
Now cross
I wish you don't cry
The future of light and dark,
let's believe in the "future"
so that they overlap to gain color again
Tama...
Tama-chan...
Why...?
I see now...
Tama...
Thank goodness, you were okay...
Tama!
But... why is Tama-chan there?
Well, that too, but...
...why is Urith a Selector?
Isn't she supposed to fulfill your wish?!
My wish is,
to a certain extent, already fulfilled...
But...
Then why battle now?
You know something, don't you?
Even about Tama...
Not at all...
Really.
That's just like her.
Such tasteless play...
Poor Tama.
But it's scary! She'll be hurt again.
I go first.
Grow.
Battle staaart!
Please go easy, okay?
Tama! Don't!
Can you please not speak to her?
Tama is my LRIG.
Wish Crisis!
Yaaargh! So strong!
Seriously?! Is it happening?!
Finally happening?!
My rival appears?!
All righty! This is getting exciting!
This isn't anything to be happy about...
Chorizo In The Fantasy!
Say the name of the move properly!
Cloth Crash Flash!
Yahoo!
So strong!
Seriously?!
Owww!
It's so one-sided...
At this rate, Chiyori's going to lose.
Tama...
Stop... Tama!
Ru...
There's no need to listen to her.
She threw you away.
N-No! Ru was...!
Get Bound.
No...
It... It's coming!
It seems Tama is fine without you.
Look at how vividly she's enjoying herself.
Nothing changed about her
ever since she was your LRIG.
Tama...
Not me...
Ru, you're...
...the only one for me.
No...
Tama... You're not having fun, are you?
--What?
--Eldora, Grow! And now, Kozame!
Ru... I'm sorry...
Tama...
Tama was a bad girl.
That's why I went bye-bye from Ru, right?
Baroque Defense.
Sh... Shiira!
Attack!
Or, maybe not.
Aw, c'mon, do it.
That's not something you say
when they're prepped, y'know?
This isn't fun...
Why...?
Battle was so fun before.
It was fun doing it with Ru.
It's not fun because I'm with Urith...?
Salvage!
N-No!
Tama isn't... having fun battling?
Tama...
Sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Tama!
When I was battling Iona-san,
I didn't think I could return.
I thought I was going to become an LRIG.
Tama, Yuzuki, Hitoe, and all the other
girls who turned into LRIGs...
If everyone could be saved,
I thought that would be okay.
But... that was wrong.
Ruko...
I was lonely.
I was lonely without you, Tama.
Tama was... lonely too...
It's my fault.
It's because I didn't talk
about my true feelings.
It's because I made you worried, Tama.
I'm sorry...
I should have talked more to you, Tama.
Talked so that you would understand!
Because Tama, you're my...
You're my precious friend!
Ruko...
Friend...
Huh?
And... what the heck are you crying for?
Because! Tama and Ru were friends!
Them now battling as enemies is so cliché!
So cliché!
Of course I'm gonna cry... I love clichés!
I can get my satisfaction just with clichés!
I really don't think this is the time
to be saying things like that...
What?
Huh?
With the next attack, we're going to lose...
Then...
Ru...
Tama...
Such a horrible girl.
Doing it with me, and yet
thinking of someone else...
What a turn-off...
Let's finish this!
Arc Aura!
Tama?
Tama...
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Give me back Tama!
If you want her back...
...battle me.
No!
Ru, don't battle! Never!
I can't wait for our battle.
You too... Iona.
See you again, scum...
Tama!
Ru...!
Ruko... are you all right?
Yup, I'm okay.
I know Tama is okay now,
and that she feels the same way as me.
Sorry I made both of you
worried, Hitoe, Yuzuki.
What a nice turn of events!
A torn friendship and a rival appears!
Like, so exciting!
Chiyori-san?
Like, you're still here?
Cool, and cool! So super!
That aside...
Hey, you!
We told her at length not to battle...
Don't you care about what's
going to happen to Chiyori?
Now, now. I talked about
it in depth too, you know?
I talked about it, but...
Let's see...
Here it is!
Lookie!
Huh?
What's that?
Chorizo De Ibéricoña The Second!
Huh?
Chorizo? As in the sausage?
Boop-boop!
It's Chiyori's name when I become an LRIG!
Huh?!
You see? She just became even more excited.
But... you lost to me.
And you lost to Urith...
So you lost twice already?
That isn't good!
But, but, I already won three times!
My wish could come true
at any moment, y'know?
If you lose again,
your wish is going to be reversed!
The heroine in the novel loses twice too,
but ends up beating her rival!
And then before she knows it,
she's at White Garden...
White... Garden?
Yup! A hyper-dimensional white void!
White?
Could it be...
...that white room I was at
when I became an LRIG?
Wait! Does a room appear in that novel?!
Wha...?! I gave you a copy of the novel.
Didn't you read it?
Ah, um... Not really...
What's this about?
Chiyori-san? Do you mind
letting us read that novel?
WIXOSS...
The Wings of Lament Mark
the Dreams of the Ruined Land...
"Futase Fumio"
Futase Fumio...
In a future not far from now,
mysterious beings called "LRIG"
appear throughout the world.
LRIGs connect themselves to
young girls with special powers
and are able to make their wishes come true.
In order for the wish to come true,
they need to defeat other LRIGs
and gather the WIXOSS factors from them.
A young girl meets an LRIG
and is drawn into the battle for wishes.
This young girl, who won her battles,
ends up in the time labyrinth, White Garden.
White Garden? This is the
white windowed room, right?
The word "Selector" doesn't appear,
but this all sounds so similar...
It's written to sound cool, but...
Yessy! She finally appears!
The Dark Lord of Atonement, Cocoon!
Gotcha!
The ruler of White Garden!
The almighty being that holds
dominion over all the WIXOSS battles!
Is she like, a last boss?
I can't believe it ends here...
The suspense! Hurry with the next volume!
Um...
Cocoon...?
Hm?
Isn't that English for "mayu"?
Ah...
Mayu!
White room... Mayu...
That's...
That's it!
She must know something!
Futase Fumio...
It says here that she originally
announced her novel over the Internet.
What she wrote as a pastime caught
the attention of a person working at a publisher.
The first book was published, and...
...she wrote the second book,
but the series stopped there?
Looks like it.
Could she be a Selector?
But... why would she glamorize it in her works?
Yeah. If she knows about the white room,
she should know what would happen
if someone continued battling.
I want to meet her.
Huh?
We could find out a lot of things if we ask her.
A lot, as in?
About Mayu...
...and about Tama.
Yuzuki, you said something about
how Tama could be a "special girl," right?
Not all Eternal Girls are normal girls.
Among them may be a special girl
who holds mysterious powers.
Tama, not sure, but I feel like...
...there's a way to make the LRIGs return to normal.
That's what Tama said.
I want to save Tama.
I want to save everyone!
Ah, come to think of it, where's Chiyori-san?
--Yaaargh!
--Huh?
There. Six wins in a row for Grandma.
Urrh... You're too strong...
If you don't try harder,
you're not going to get any.
Could you be the Sorcerer of Blood?!
The Danger Zone of WIXOSS!
Queen of Innocent!
Who knows?
I'll tell you if you win, Chiyori-chan.
Oh?
How about you two join us?
Uh... maybe later.
"Ruko"
Ah! See?
Here's the novel's website.
"Futase Fumio" "Official Website"
It's still active.
"Futase Fumio-sama...
Excuse us for our sudden e-mail.
We read your novel, Sensei.
We'll be very upfront.
We're Selectors...
Sensei, are you aware of Selectors?
If so, please allow us
an opportunity to speak with you.
Kominato Ruko. Uemura Hitoe."
Does that sound okay?
Yup.
"Send"
See ya laters!
We'll contact you when we get a reply!
Be sure to come with us, okay?
Absolutely!
Will we... get a reply?
There are a lot of things we don't know.
Like how Akira-san and Urith-san
became Selectors again.
Yup...
It's no coincidence that Tama
became Urith's LRIG, right?
Huh?
Yuzuki... came to me, too.
Mayu...
Maybe it's her doing...
Yup. It has to be.
But, why? Why would she do such a thing?
Right?! It just makes everyone confused!
What are you saying?
Why are you girls battling?
All the while confused
by incomprehensible rules.
You're all just being played by her.
Selectors and LRIGs...
are all just dolls to her.
All she's doing is playing with her dolls.
Playing with dolls?
She's enjoying seeing
the dolls battle each other.
That's all there is to this...
If that's true...
I won't forgive her!
I'll be going now.
Okay.
Um, you know...
There was a lot that happened,
but I'm happy you got to see Tama.
Tama pairs up best next to you, Ruko.
Yup.
Let's do our best so that Tama-chan
can come back to you, Ruko.
Hitoe...
Yuzuki...
Thanks.
See you!
--Good night.
Disgusting...
Huh?
Those two are... unpleasant.
Disgusting...
What?
Akira, it's Iona-san.
How has Akira-san been?
She calmed down quite a bit,
all because of you. Thank you.
Not at all.
Say, Akira?
That girl... Please, come on in.
Excuse me.
Can you help me again?
Yes...
I will...
I'll do anything...
So cute...
Akira...
Truly disgusting...
That smile...
"Regarding Selectors"
"Futase Fumio"
This is Futase Fumio-sensei's residence?
That's what it said in the e-mail...
I... I can't take this!
Nervous! Nervous! Super nervous!
So sorry here! She's surprisingly timid.
Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle!
Hello... I sent an e-mail yesterday. Kominato...
H-Hello...
Um, excuse me.
Hello?
What should we do?
"White Room" "Large Window" "Mayu"
White room...
Mayu...
Large window...
White room...
Mayu...
Large window...
White room...
--Hello...?
--Mayu...
--Are you... Futase Fumio-sensei?
--Large room...
Yes...
I'm... Futase Fumio.
"Those Wild Delusions"
Life...
A city of mazes with no exit
and the sound of bells ringing
I do...
Leave the "now" handed to me
as I begin to walk in the morning
In a world where light and dark intersect
catharsis begins to awake
I swore in my shaking heart
that I won't lose anyone anymore...!
Even if my tears flow tomorrow
I'll run through the wind
Release myself towards the future I selected
to regain it
I won't give up on my wish
...don't you know more than
what's written in the novel?
If you can defeat me in battle,
I'll tell you everything that I know.
How much do you think she knows?
What's with that form?
"This Impatience Is an Awakening"
This Impatience Is an Awakening.