That's right!
When we played classical music to our shiitake mushrooms, they grew really big!
Really?
Apparently, they'll also grow well if you use a lightning generator to run electricity through them.
Electricity?
Yeah.
When they get shocked by a strong current, it triggers their survival mechanisms to produce more spores.
Just stop talking and do your homework.
A helicopter?
That reminds me...
Ogi liked helicopters, didn't he?
Mazui Presents
fukuzatsu ni
kamaeta kyou ga
Every day is set
in stone, and we
iki wo nonde sumashiteru
Just hold our breaths and live them through
mi ni oboe arun
I'm sure you know just what
darou
I mean
kimi wa dou shitai
What do you really want to do?
nani mo nakatta soburi de
Pretending like nothing happened to you
kabau itami wa mou
The pain inside just builds up
kokorodzuyoi kurai ni
It makes me feel all the more sure
sekasunda
And urges me to go on
Catching on
Catchingon
tsukande
koboshite
Falling through
fukanzen na
bokutachi ga
We've yet to learn
just who we are
hikatte mienai
They're so bright,
we can't see
mirai no jibun wo tsukureru nara
If we can decide the kind of person that we want to be
mezameru mama hashire
When you wake up, just start running
shinkirou wo oikoshite
Breaking through all the illusions there
kawaritai mama hashire
When you want to change, just start running
jiyuu na iwakan de
And feel yourself break free
todokisou na kagayaki to ima wo erandeikou
I hope you choose this moment and the light that shines before you
toutatsuten wa shiranai fukai asai
We don't know where we might go, so deep or short
kokyuu wo kasanete
Just take another breath
Ogi-san?
Are the Mountains Sunny?
Ogi Takahiro-san from class 2-B?
Who?
The one in class 2-B?
You don't know the Ogi I'm talking about.
He was our English teacher in middle school.
You remember, right Satoshi?
Of course I do.
I didn't know he liked helicopters, though.
I thought everyone knew.
But you remember, right Ibara?
Dunno.
That's weird...
How could I know, but these guys don't?
All three of us went to Kaguraya Middle School,
and Ibara was in every single one of my classes.
She should definitely know.
Is there something about that Ogi-san you're talking about?
It's not important, but...
Don't you remember, Ibara?
At one point, a helicopter flew over the school.
That happened a lot of times.
One of those times, he suddenly stopped in the middle of
class, walked over to the window, and stared at the sky.
He watched the helicopter until we couldn't see it anymore.
Then he laughed and made some excuse like,
"I like helicopters" or something and resumed class.
I kind of remember after hearing the whole story...
Yeah, that happened.
Was that Ogi?
Yeah, it was.
Good. So it wasn't just me.
That doesn't sound right.
What do you mean? It definitely happened.
One time, a squadron of JSDF helicopters flew over us.
It was quite a spectacle, but I don't remember Ogi-sensei reacting to that at all.
A squadron?
In formation.
How did you know they were JSDF?
There aren't any other organizations who would fly helicopters in formation like that.
And you're sure Ogi was around for that?
I'm pretty sure.
I remember looking up "AGM" in my English dictionary after seeing them.
AGM?
What's that?
It stands for Air-to-Ground Missile, if I remember correctly.
Ogi would probably run outside and do a little dance of joy if that happened.
I don't think he'd go quite that far.
It was just an example.
So, it was Ogi-sensei who was obsessed with helicopters...
I think that happened that pretty soon after we started middle school.
Now that you mention it, I do remember thinking he was pretty weird at first.
But like Fuku-chan said, I don't remember him reacting to them after that one time.
Three years ago...
My memory's a little hazy.
But now that I think about it, I don't remember any other times he did that, either.
But there were stories about Ogi with more punch than that one.
Like the one about him being immortal.
Don't just make stuff up.
I didn't make this one up!
Ogi-sensei told me this one himself.
He told me...
...well, I don't really believe it myself,
and I don't know if you'll believe it,
but I do think it's possible...
Just tell us the story.
According to him, he's been struck by lightning three times.
Lightning? Real lightning?
Yep.
Thunder!
Thunder, too? It's amazing he survived...
It hit me like thunder!
It looks like Chitanda's learning how to deal with Satoshi, too.
Apparently he was never hit directly, but he didn't get away unharmed.
One time, he got knocked out.
And he's got burns from them, too.
I see.
But he survived. He must be very happy to be alive.
I guess.
Actually, I don't remember seeing any obvious scars.
Lightning...
Three times?
Is that even possible?
It's not like Kamiyama is known for lightning storms or anything.
And yet, Ogi says he's been struck three times?
I don't think Satoshi's making this up, either.
If anything, he's probably just embellishing the story a bit.
So then, was Ogi making it up?
It certainly doesn't sound true...
Wait...
Satoshi, the public library has old newspapers, right?
Yeah.
A few, at least.
Our library has some, too.
They're all articles about this school, though.
That's not what I'm after.
I'm leaving.
I'm dropping by the public library. Want to come?
Houtarou... actually wants to do something?
No.
I'm just a bit, you know...
...curious.
Houtarou...
Are you really Houtarou?!
The energy-conserving Oreki Houtarou?
Is some alien controlling your mind?
Or did Chitanda-san infect you with something?
Stop that!
Oreki, I think you should go home...
Dress warm and go to bed early.
I'm sure you'll feel better by morning.
Well, excuse me!
I didn't know it was that strange for me to want to do something!
Whatever, let's make it quick.
Oreki-san!
What?
You're curious, aren't you?
I guess.
You're going to go look into this, right?
I might not find anything, you know!
I'm curious!
Wha...
About what?
What in the world could have possibly piqued your curiosity, of all things?
I'm curious!
This girl is pretty rude...
Satoshi said he couldn't come because he had homework.
Ibara might have been helpful since she's a librarian, but she doesn't owe me any favors, so I didn't ask.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Shall we go then?
Go on ahead.
This bike can handle a passenger, you know?
No way.
That's not happening either.
It's fine, go ahead.
Alright then.
Chitanda.
Yes?
If they can search newspaper archives, find out anything you can about a man named Ogi Masakiyo.
The kanji reads "a small tree, true and pure".
Got it.
See you in a bit!
Kanro
When the cold, dark air rises,
But the dew has yet to freeze.
Hyouka
According to Sis, who's been to the Kamikakiuchi Range a few times,
the 3km tall mountains that make up the range block atmospheric currents,
resulting in completely different climates on each side.
I shouldn't make Chitanda wait too long.
Kamiyama
Public
Library
Oreki-san!
I found some information about Ogi-sensei.
"Kamikakiuchi Trail Restoration Work Continues."
It looks like Ogi-sensei enjoyed climbing mountains.
"Restoration work on the Abumidake Trail began on the 26th, sponsored by the Kamiyama Climbing Club."
"Eleven volunteers participated in garbage collection along the trail."
"Kamiyama Climbing Club President Ogi Masakiyo-san (39 years old) said,"
"Due to the recent popularity of mountain climbing, many new folks aren't aware of the rules."
"I want everyone to understand that the rules are there to protect you from possible life-threatening dangers."
I thought so.
What is it?
Nothing.
Did you search all the newspaper archives?
We can go ask at the counter on the second floor.
I hope I'm not right about this.
Excuse me, we'd like to search for a newspaper article.
Sure. What are you looking for?
An article from three years ago, in April or May.
Are there any keywords for this search?
Go with "stranded".
There are twelve articles.
Any other filters?
Could I see those titles?
Go ahead.
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Preventing Accidents in Kamikakiuchi: A Manual
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Preventing Accidents in Kamikakiuchi: A Manual
Eight Dead, Two in Coma After
Being Stranded in North America
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Preventing Accidents in Kamikakiuchi: A Manual
Eight Dead, Two in Coma After
Being Stranded in North America
Eight Climbers Missing, Stranded on Mountain
Hikers Aged 60-70 Stranded
Five Dead in Alaska
Seven Doctors Stranded
Seven Years After Being Stranded
11 Stranded, 2 Dead in Kamikakiuchi, All-Time Record
Rescue Helicopter Saves Saves Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Man Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
Preventing Accidents in Kamikakiuchi: A Manual
Eight Dead, Two in Coma After
Being Stranded in North America
Eight Climbers Missing, Stranded on Mountain
Found it.
Difficulties Rescuing Stranded in Kamikakiuchi
It's from May 9th.
Excuse me, could we see this article?
Looks like Chitanda's figured it out too.
Maruta-san, could you help with this?
What is it?
We're looking for an article from a newspaper from May 9th, three years ago.
Three years ago?
Let me go grab it.
Thank you very much.
It'll probably take me about half an hour to dig it out.
Is that okay?
That's perfectly fine.
I'll let you know when I've found it.
Thank you very much.
Oreki-san, why don't we have a look around since we're here?
Sure.
A special on Taira no Kiyomori?
The cover is so pretty!
This article says that Taira no Kiyomori was the son of a Shirakawa princess.
I've read some theories that say that.
Wow, that's quite impressive.
Miyajima? It's the Itsukushima Shrine.
I'd love to go there one day.
Exciting! Vegetable School
Look at all the cabbages!
Such a wonderful green color!
And look at all these tomatoes!
They look so delicious...
That reminds me, Oreki-san...
We have a lot of shiitake mushrooms this year.
Would you like some?
Look!
Books on insects!
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Honeybee Diary
The Life of a Bee
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
Dung Beetles!
Dung Beetles
Written and Illustrated by Dr. Fabre
They're so cute!
Why would you pick up that one?
Is there anything you'd like to see, Oreki-san?
Let's see...
That's quite a grand castle.
Your house is pretty grand, too.
My house isn't all that big.
I think it's just a little bigger than normal.
I don't understand what your idea of "normal" is.
Were you able to find it?
The papers from around then are in this file.
You should be able to find it in here.
Thank you very much.
Wow, it's heavy.
There are a lot in here.
There!
A newspaper from May 9!
May 9
I think this is the day Ogi said he liked helicopters.
Found it.
Kamiyama Mountaineering Team, Two Members Stranded
What does this mean?
Simply put, Ogi didn't like helicopters.
He was struck by lightning three times.
That's probably the truth.
But there's no reason why a normal English teacher would get struck by lightning so often.
I suppose that's true...
That's when it came to me.
Maybe Ogi often went places where lightning would strike.
And that would be the mountains?
Did you think this might be the case?
Kind of.
I thought Ogi might have been a mountain climber as well as an English teacher.
So I came here to confirm it.
Why did Ogi want to see the helicopter that day?
Because there was something special about a helicopter on that day.
Ogi was waiting anxiously for a helicopter to fly that day.
What do you mean?
Or more accurately, Ogi wanted a helicopter to fly that day.
That's why he had to see it for himself when he heard it.
An English teacher wanting a helicopter to fly doesn't mean a thing.
But if a mountain climber wants to see a helicopter fly, that's a whole other story.
Kamiyama City is next to a 3000 meter tall range of mountains,
the Kamikakiuchi Range.
A mountain climber in this city wanted a helicopter to fly.
Maybe they were filming or transporting materials.
If not...
If not?
Then a rescue team.
A rescue team?
This article says that the weather was bad on the 8th, so helicopters couldn't fly.
Right.
Ogi was only interested in police helicopters flying.
He was interested in the weather conditions around the Kamikakiuchi Range.
If the mountains are sunny, helicopters can fly.
If the mountains are sunny, survival rates change.
I wonder how Ogi-sensei felt.
I don't know how he felt,
but I think he was smiling.
We looked through newspapers from the days that followed.
The two who were stranded were eventually found, dead.
A police helicopter found them.
Um...
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Why were you curious?
Is it that weird for me to want to look into something?
Yes, it is.
It didn't really seem like something you would do.
Well, I guess.
Usually, if I don't have to do it, I won't.
No, that's not it.
She totally tossed aside my eternal motto...
You do a lot of things for a lot of people.
You've helped me countless times.
Now that's a misunderstanding.
But you never do anything for yourself.
Why did you want to look into this today?
I'm sorry, but I'm really curious.
When Satoshi said that thing about lightning, I had a bad feeling.
I remember you mentioning that.
I wanted to know if what I thought was true..
That's why I wanted to look into it.
So then I thought of the library.
If it were an investigation that would have taken a week, I wouldn't have done it.
But just flipping through a few old newspapers isn't too much.
Plus, you were there to help.
And I'd need to be careful if it were true.
Careful?
Under circumstances like that, I can't really just say "Ogi liked helicopters" and leave it at that.
That would just be insensitive.
That's why I'd need to be careful.
Was that hard to understand?
I guess it's less of being "insensitive" and more of
"Not knowing how someone feels."
Though, I'll probably never meet Ogi again, so it's not like I'd need to know how he feels.
Oreki-san!
That's... very...
I don't know how to say it.
What's she trying to say?
Well, whatever.
If she doesn't know how to say it, it's not like I can get it out of her.
That's it for today.
Thanks for helping me.
You're very welcome.
I'm glad I could see a different side of you today.
Enough of that, already!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, good-bye.
By the time Chitanda gets home,
it'll be completely dark out.
She's the one who wanted to come with me.
I didn't ask her to.
But I guess I owe her one.
This time.
joukyou wa hikagaku teki ni
The case seems so irrational
kanjou no monta-ju
A montage of emotions
dare ga dare wo yonderu
Just who's calling who right now?
furimukeba nigeteku shisen kanjiru
When I turn around I don't feel watched anymore
ki no sei ja tsurenai yo
I know it's not just my imagination
antena wa sainou da yuusha
A heroine's antenna is her talent
datte (datte) shiritai (kimi wa chigau no)
I mean (I mean) I want to know (Don't you want to?)
seishun ondosa ima no uchi tadashite ageru yo
I'll fix the difference in how we view our youths right now
ashita kaiketsu suru nara ima demo yokunai
If it'll be fixed tomorrow, then why not fix it right now?
kimi no misuteri-
You are a mystery
toite mitai
Detective I'll try to be
shougen no himitsumeita senaka sagase (kyou mo)
Looking for the person who makes this happen to me (Again today)
kimi wa fantaji-
You are a fantasy
hikareteyukuyo tsumui
You pull me in to see
fukuranda koukishin
I want to launch an investigation
torikku wa nai no ni
Even though there isn't a trick
ki ni naru yo
I'm curious
kyoumibukai
I'm so interested
doushite
Why is that?
Next time: Anyone Who Knows.
Anyone Who Knows