What's this? It's all squirmy...
What's this? An alien umbilical cord?
I'm sure it was you who put it in,
so you eat it!
No.
Young ones, you mustn't waste food.
Ozu, you put chocolate in these wrapped ones, didn't you?
Hanuki-san, you put in beer, didn't you?
You caught me? But it deepens the flavor, don't you think?
It's already so deep that
I can't tell what tastes like what.
I'm sorry, but may I open the curtain for a bit?
If you insist...
Impressive, as always, Master.
Speaking of which,
what kind of training is this?
No one knows what the future holds in life.
We must take that endless bit of darkness
and turn it to our advantage.
This is practical training for doing just that.
When you drink it in the dark,
it's not like beer at all.
Hanuki-san is a mysterious dental hygienist who comes and goes under Master Higuchi.
She lives on ethyl alcohol and castellas,
and she has a habit of getting drunk and licking people's faces.
If you go drinking with Hanuki-san, you'd better be prepared for an endless night of hell.
Yeehaw!
I was once freely dragged all around Kiyamachi,
and when I came to, I was collapsed
near the Ebisugawa Power Plant all alone...
And Ozu was a person without
even a single redeeming quality.
He could eat three helpings of people's misfortune.
Although he was only fifteen minutes faster than me, he's Master Higuchi's first disciple,
Arrogant
Selfish
and he takes glory in this meaningless lifestyle.
Lazy
The Devil
Why didn't Akashi-san come?
It seems she has a report she can't get out of.
I have a report I can't
get out of too, you know!
Indeed, after neglecting my studies,
and surrounded by these worthless faces, spending all day "training" for things,
I have made a complete mess of
my first two years of college life.
I have a question that must be put to the person responsible for this!
Where is the one responsible?
Will the responsible party come forward!
Then I was a brand-spanking-new freshman university student,
and countless doors to that rose-colored campus life lay open before me.
However, at that time,
I had a bad premonition.
Disciples Wanted
Because I could not envision those suspicious looking fliers leading to some glorious future.
I must not reach out for these fliers!
In fact, I felt I should get as far away as possible!
However, I was not able to escape.
Disciples Wanted
With clairvoyance to pick out
fair maidens from the crowds of Gion
Disciples Wanted
and devil's ears that let not even the sound of
cherry blossoms falling into the canals slip past,
I am Higuchi Seitarou!
Come, ye youths of limitless possibility!
Yes, Master!
My bad premonition was right on the mark.
I had held a position of not
opening up my heart to anyone,
but as Master Higuchi lived in Yuusuisou,
the same boarding house as I, we hit it off,
and the fact I was just old enough to drink helped immediately.
"Myself" is over 20 years old.
Ozu did not imbibe.
And before long, the walls came down
and I was enjoying myself.
And as a result of our heated
arguments over boobs until dawn...
The question is not whether it is a real breast.
What matters is whether you believe it.
Switch, on!
One, two, three!
I ended up becoming his second disciple.
Of course, that was the only time
our master ever treated us to alcohol.
Being the disciple of Higuchi Seitarou.
I'm still not clear as to what I'm
a disciple in even after these two years.
And if you looked under the cover,
Master Higuchi was no hermit master or anything,
but just some eighth-year student.
Like how animals that live long lives
feel somewhat uncanny,
our master had this mysterious air about him unlike normal people.
He wears the same yukata and tall geta everywhere he goes all-year round,
and he knows 100 places
to cool off in the summer.
He can't speak anything other than Japanese,
but he can converse cordially with people in any country,
and there are times he perceives things
that normal people do not.
His body is light and incredible.
That being the case,
he doesn't participate in anything,
only focusing intently on living life day-to-day.
It was a frighteningly, gentlemanly manner, perhaps the pinnacle of buffoonery.
However, he had a weakness.
He has library fines.
Our master was being targeted by a secret
collection organization known as the Library Police.
Helping him escape from them was our duty as his disciples.
The fiend!
Besides the Library Police, Master also had
an ongoing battle with a man named Jougasaki.
What color?
Pink.
Master called this battle the
"Masochistic Proxy-Proxy War."
And as the name implies,
it was a "war" of the tiniest,
pettiest, most stupid things you could imagine.
It seems that five years ago,
there was some deep strife between the two which caused the opening shots to be fired.
And we, as his disciples, were
wrapped up in this pointless struggle.
Glued
For example, when we had
twenty plates of sushi delivered,
he'd invite over a bunch of
exchange students for a sushi party,
and Ozu and I would split the bill.
In short, it was always us who got the short end of the stick.
I wondered if wasting my precious youth helping with this stuff was a good thing,
but each day and the next,
I worked hard to pay him back.
Kaori! K-Kaori!
Jougasaki is a perverted man
the same year as Master Higuchi
and the head of the movie circle,
but it's still uncertain what grudge
they have between them.
The journey is over.
Goal
What's this?
In the chaos just after the war in the Pacific,
med students who stole the techniques behind Nishio Market's Kamenoko scrubbing brushes
created a mystical cleaning weapon
from the fibers of a special Taiwanese palm.
The tips of the fiber both stiff and supple,
it seems like it uses the Van der Waals force
to bind dirt particles.
Put under pressure by detergent makers
for fear of losing sales,
its power to clean was considered too great a threat, and it was banished to the depths of history.
However, it seems like someone continues to make them even now, in secret.
I wish to obtain one of these
mystical Kamenoko scrubbing brushes.
Demachi Futaba Mame-mochi
This is another part of your training.
Shougoin
Nama
Yatsuhashi
Nishimura
Eisei-Boro
Our master had required many things prior to this,
and we were always supplying him.
Ox-drawn cart of
ancient pine
Ueda Sweets Factory
Conpa-Rusk
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
Ueda Sweets Factory
Conpa-Rusk
Ueno Liquor Shop
Tsubame Sauce
Ueda Sweets Factory
Conpa-Rusk
Ueno Liquor Shop
Tsubame Sauce
Ueda Sweets Factory
Conpa-Rusk
Ueno Liquor Shop
Tsubame Sauce
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
Ueno Liquor Shop
Tsubame Sauce
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
Ueno Liquor Shop
Tsubame Sauce
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
Nishiri Senmai-zuke
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
This is the final test.
Remembrance of
Kamesuehiro
Please do whatever you can
to get it by tomorrow at noon.
If you don't, you're expelled.
Perhaps he thought of
cleaning his 4.5-tatami room,
but as you probably figured,
I will be the one who ends up doing it.
The Master's room was so dirty.
One glance and a lady of sheltered upbringing
would surely swoon. It's a disaster.
Never heard of it.
I wouldn't be surprised
if it were some life-form
You don't plan to
buy anything?
Are you makin'
fun of me, idiot?
that secretly evolved and had never previously existed on the Earth's surface
Hey, bring the salt!
Coming all the way to the Sanjou Bridge,
as it is lunch time, I see chicken 'n onions lined up,
and I thought to shoot fireworks at them.
However, I had a feeling
like I'd already done that,
which made my uneasiness all the more indescribable.
When I came to, I had moved to Kiyamachi,
and despite it still being midday, an old
fortune teller was spreading out her eerie aura.
The fortunes of this creature must surely be spot on.
You're back?
What do you mean, I'm back?
You are dissatisfied.
Because you have fiercely earnest talent.
I tip my hat to the old woman's insight.
Anyway, I feel there's an opportunity
you can't let slip away.
Grab the opportunity that is
dangling in front of your eyes.
That'll be 4,000 yen.
This is getting more and more abridged.
Our master made us do all kinds of meaningless things in the name of "training,"
and most of them made no sense.
I thought countless number of times
"Why am I doing this?",
and I couldn't help but think
"If only I hadn't met the Master."
Why shouldn't I just expel myself?
Senpai!
Akashi-san is a first-year in the engineering department like Ozu, and she's a younger disciple.
A mystical Kamenoko scrubbing brush?
I don't even know if it actually exists.
You mustn't give up so easily.
Let us search!
The old man I asked before,
who was like a boiled octopus,
acted nice like he'd just found
Princess Kaguya in a bamboo shoot.
The man who runs a general store in
West Kinichiba might know something.
Perhaps the owner of the general store
facing Bukkouji Road.
The man who runs the old book store over there might know something.
The used utensil shop in
Shinkyougoku might know.
Akashi-san was quite skilled at information gathering
and narrowed down the location
of the scrubbing brush.
And then...
Excuse me!
We're searching for the mystical Kamenoko scrubbing brush.
Um...
Do you know anything about the mystical—
Where did you hear of that?
From Master Higuchi.
Wait a moment.
Th-That's...
Um, how much for it?
Perhaps I will ask for 100,000 yen.
Hell if I'm buying that.
No scrubbing brush is worth 100,000 yen.
It's not something you'd wash in a sink of
a 4.5-tatami boarding house covered in sludge.
Enough. I give up on the scrubbing brush.
I'm finally expelled.
That master is not going to cut the thread so trivially.
I will ask him as well.
If I can become a circle with you...
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
At the
public
bath
Th-That's...
Farewell triangle, I'll come back sometime, square
Circle X triangle... Always a dead space
The world tends to 4 sides, 4 faces, 5 sides, 6 sides, turkey
Search for the circle...
To learn how not to become a circle...
It might be nowhere
It might be somewhere
You don't know either... on this Kamo River
Search for the circle...
Search for the circle
While I was listening to my master's song,
I suddenly had a feeling like
he would be going somewhere far away.
Higuchi-kun and Jougasaki-kun were here earlier.
It had been a long time since they'd met.
Jougasaki-san's pretty cool, isn't he?
Really?
I don't think Higuchi-kun is all that different myself.
I can't believe that.
Jougasaki-kun hasn't had any friends
other than Higuchi-kun since long ago.
You know, I think that Higuchi-kun is going to make you his successor.
I've already been expelled.
And I don't think I'm suited to
living in such a shrewd manner.
It all began when two high-school seniors were rivals in love.
It's said that it was a drinking contest
with unrefined saké,
but the details are already
lost to the depths of history.
And so this battle dragged on for a long time,
and they refused to let it drop
without coming to a conclusion.
So thinking in utter desperation,
it became a Proxy War.
They forgot the reason why the battle began,
and without regard to changes in society, they passed it down through successors.
Technically, it's called the Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War.
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
The Masochistic Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-Proxy-
Proxy-Proxy-Proxy War
Why are we talking about this?
You're taking it over, you see.
When I came back, there was
a mysterious bag left in my room
Th-This is...
Funds for continuing the Proxy War?
I didn't know what was what anymore.
It was precisely the amount of money needed to buy that scrubbing brush!
Should I take the Eizan Electric up to Kurama
and hide out as Ushiwakamaru?
Or should I take the Kyoto-Osaka and head around
Naniwa with some raven-haired maidens?
This was called a Mochiguman,
and Akashi-san had once told me she had lost it.
It seems they come in
sets of five and she lost one.
Grab the opportunity that is
dangling in front of your eyes.
A Dream Date with Akashi- san
I will let myself be expelled!
With this 100,000 yen,
I should return to the life I deserve!
You've done well.
With this, you have cleared the final test!
Perhaps I did everything the Master said these past two years just to see this smile.
There is a ceremony now.
Come with me, you.
Master, I have something important to...
A duel on the Kamo Bridge.
The Proxy-Proxy War will continue with you.
Please, wait!
Ah, you two.
I'll be the witness.
Okay then, let's go.
And so the cannons were readied
for the decisive battle.
Jougasaki came walking from the west side.
The two soon met in the
center of the Kamo Bridge.
Oh, Akashi-san?
Greetings.
We meet again.
How are you feeling?
Thanks to you, I'm fit and healthy.
So you're one of Higuchi's?
Yes. I became his disciple last fall.
And isn't that my disciple, Ozu?
Yep.
He's my proxy, the one who will succeed me.
You might have thought he was your disciple,
but he was actually my spy, you see.
Did I fool you?
Ya got me.
Sorry 'bout that, Master.
That is unprecedented in the history of the Masochistic Proxy-Proxy War.
Your name will be etched into history.
Things sure dragged out for a long time.
Was it five years? Or more?
I've forgotten. It's been
a battle of so many years.
Ozu was active in all fields, and despite
filming a hit piece on Jougasaki,
it seems he also dyed
Master Higuchi's yukata pink
and played the part of
a meaningless double agent.
So this guy is your proxy?
Yes.
Thank you.
Wait a second!
Well then, let's do it.
Yeah.
Get it over with already!
The battle started with such a flat phrase.
In a moment's breath, the two clashed!
Let's do it!
Fine by me!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Okay, it's over!
Jougasaki-kun won,
so Ozu-kun goes first next!
The weight has finally been lifted off my shoulders.
What are you going to do now?
I'm leaving on a journey.
Hey, Hanuki.
Higuchi is spouting some nonsense.
For now, I plan on circling the globe once.
Will you come with me, Hanuki?
You can speak English, right?
Don't be crazy. This is foolish.
You have money?
I have the prize money
from the Shimanami Cup.
You, sorry about this,
but please clean up the room with this.
And so my master disappeared with the wind.
Want to go out for a drink?
Oh, you're finally in the mood?
You're the one who spends
all that money on your love doll.
Where did you learn about that?
From Ozu-kun. He tells me everything.
Why that little...
What's his real story anyway?
No!
I thought I might rather
jump into the Kamo River.
Or maybe run away from Kyoto to
Cape Muroto and obtain enlightenment.
I look forward to our time together.
Th-This is...
I apologize if you were supposed to bat first.
Let's continue to play nice and dirty.
The first shot of the Proxy-Proxy War
had been fired.
Being caught by Master Higuchi in front of that clock tower
was definitely a turning point of my fate.
If I had joined some other circle, I would have surely spent quite a different two years.
Clearly, meeting Ozu
was my greatest mistake.