Thanks to your mind-reading powers, you never have to worry about your grades. Cute trick.
I do my own work!
Do you really?
Can you definitively say that you found these answers on your own?
Are you absolutely sure that no one else's thoughts got into your head?
It's not impossible... But...
Lay off!
Don't pick on Kotoura just because you failed your finals!
Barely Avoided Failing
Second
in Her Class
First
in His Class
Failed Most Exams:
Bound for Remedial Classes
Plain Old
Good Grades
Guess I won't let you come with me to my grandfather's house for summer vacation.
I'm sorry!
Please, please don't go until my remedial classes are over!
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
Summer Vacation!
Summer vacation is here.
I never really cared about it before,
but this summer, I'm kind of excited.
Don't cry, Moritani. I was just kidding.
R-Really?
Of course. You wouldn't want to be all alone for summer vacation, would you?
Puke-o-ura
Bleaurgh~
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
You stink, Puke-o-ura!
Get out of here!
Bleaurgh
Please forgive me!
Please don't worry about it anymore.
Your grandfather's house is where we went to find you not long ago, right?
It was such a gorgeous place!
Don't get your hopes up too much.
It's close to the beach and the mountains,
but there's really not much to do there.
The beach? Sounds good to me!
Oh, ho. The beach, is it?
With finals out of the way, it's time to splurge on a new swimsuit!
That sounds great! Let's go right now!
A bathing suit...
But it really won't be a bother if we come with you?
Of course not. I really want to get to know you guys better,
so please do join me.
I see. We'd be glad to then.
Great!
Bikinis. Boobs. Butts. Bikinis. Boobs. Butts.
Bikinis. Boobs. Butts. Bikinis. Boobs...
Lechers can't come.
I'm sorry! Please let me come!
Why are you giggling?
Did you see a girl in a swimsuit out there?!
We're not even that close to the beach.
How is it even possible to get this excited about bathing suits anyway?
But the one I'm most hyped for is yours, y'know.
Wh-What are you talking about?
This is supposed to be a trip.
Don't waste your time reading. Have some fun with us.
I was having fun, actually...
Oh, yeah!
I went swimsuit shopping with the girls the other day,
but it seems my size has changed.
So you've gained weight again?
What do you mean, "again?!"
I'm not getting fat! I'm having a growth spurt!
Figures. It's four to a pair of seats, so someone has to get left out.
Do you feel nothing when you see this heaving bosom?!
Take a damn look!
Sto-o-op!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Jiggle-joggle! Jiggle-joggle! Hey! Hey!
Last time I came this way, I was alone too.
Moritani.
Kotoura?
Want a nice cool mandarin?
Yes, I do!
It's so cold! And sweet!
I've got candy too.
It's delicious!
What in the heck is wrong with you?!
Sto-o-op!
Just look at these gazongas! Jiggle-joggle!
Guess I'll take a nap.
He should be here to pick us up.
Hey! Good of you to drop by!
You're late, Grandfather.
Sorry. These darned Japanese streets are so narrow.
Head Priest, I see you came too.
Zenzou invited me along.
You've traveled a long way.
There's not much here, but make yourselves at home.
We appreciate it.
So, how's it going? Have you kissed her yet?
Only a matter of time, O Grandfather of mine!
Grandfather! Please!
And I believe you're a new face.
Y-Yes. We haven't been introduced.
Nice to meet you. I'm Moritani Hiyori.
Ah, Moritani, eh?
Oh yeah. This is apropos of nothing,
but I hear you youngsters live in a pretty dangerous town.
Why, it seems the streets are positively littered with random acts of violence after dark!
Gulp.
Come to think of it, wasn't there a martial arts dojo there?
I think it was called Mori... Mori... Ah, I've forgotten.
One gets so forgetful in one's dotage.
H-He knows.
Don't be so mean to her.
It's okay, Moritani.
Kotoura!
Oh, we've already arrived?
Okay, everyone. Hurry on out.
Um, Grandfather, what is this place?
I've only heard this from the head priest, but aren't you kids interested in psychic powers?
No, really it's just our preside—
Of course we are! We comprise the ESP Society!
Wait, does that mean...?
Yes.
This building only seems to be an abandoned hospital.
In reality, it used to be a secret
government lab studying espers.
But then!
One day, a horrible psychic accident destroyed the lab,
together with everyone inside!
I see. This truly is a case for the ESP Society.
Most intriguing!
Uh, hang on, you don't mean...
L-Let's just let it go! Okay?
Man, he's easy to read.
Really, Grandfather, why did you bring us to a place like...
Huh?!
Hey! Grandfather!
You are suspiciously well-prepared, President Mifune.
It's merely my duty as President of the ESP Society.
It feels like something could pop out at us any second.
Lemme outta here! I wanna go home!
Kotoura! I-I can't breathe! Will you let go?
You again?
Really seriously please let go of me, Kotoura.
Okay? Okay?
No! Don't abandon me!
I'm begging you, Kotoura! Please get off me!
Yuriko, you know this isn't really a psychic research lab, right?
Of course I do.
What?!
Then what are we even doing in here?
Well, obviously, we're enjoying ourselves watching Kotoura go into freakout mode.
You brute!
I thought as much.
B-But even if it isn't a psychic
research lab, it's still a hospital.
Isn't there still a chance it's haunted?
Don't be silly.
Ghost sightings are all cases of the
human mind playing tricks on people.
So you believe in psychic powers, but not ghosts?
Well, I've never seen any.
But it'd be nice if there were some around.
Maybe we'd get to encounter some psychic ghosts.
Th-That sounds absolutely awful!
Don't worry. We've got a real psychic on our side.
All I can do is read minds!
What hope do I have against a ghost?
I just heard a spooky voice!
This is an old building.
It was only the wind.
There it is again!
It's saying, "hold me tight... hold me tight..." in the most depraved tones!
Relax. You're just hearing Manabe's thoughts.
A g-g-g-ghost!
In a bathing suit!
Hey there, handsome!
Relax. That's just his dumb fantasy.
I don't understand how you can even do that in a place like this!
Never underestimate me!
My lust can conquer any situation!
I can't take it any more!
Manabe?
Wh-What the hell is that thing?
How should I know?
It's a chupacabra.
The name is Spanish for "sucker of goat blood."
It's an Unidentified Mysterious Animal, or UMA.
And what do UMAs have to do with psychic powers?
More of them!
Now this is what a psychic research lab should be!
We've got the Jersey Devil, Mothman, and even the Yeti!
I wish that "Hey there, handsome!" girl would show up, too!
"Hey there, handsome!"
Welcome to Harukaland!
Harukaland?
This is the first time Haruka has brought friends home.
I threw together this theme park to commemorate the occasion.
Take a look behind you!
Sign: "Terror! Abandoned Hospital
Do you have the guts to check in here...?"
Wasn't the haunted hospital fun?
I did tell him to tone it down.
S-Stupid old man.
Grandfather, you jerk!
Wait! Wait!
Mama, please don't go!
Don't leave me!
Mama!
If only you had never been born.
Oh, yeah. I'm back at the house.
Good morning, Kotoura!
Manabe. Good morning.
You're already up? It's still pretty early.
Yeah, for some reason I always wake up super-early over summer vacation.
Yay! I'm gonna catch me some beetles!
He's just like a little boy.
But man, your family's house is ginormous!
I've been exploring it all morning!
Such an innocent little boy.
Sexy, sexy, sexy, sexy...
Found it!
I found the treasure!
If you sneak into my room, you will die.
Lecher.
Gah! My visions of manly splendor were leaking out again?
Wait, is that where your room was?
Th-This room is...
Wh-What are you doing?
Let's play, Kotoura!
Huh?
It's our first summer vacation together.
It'd be a waste if we didn't enjoy it to the max!
Yeah.
What should we do?
Wanna go back to that Harukaland from last night?
Absolutely never again!
Ohh! The beach!
You sure took your time finding it.
Grandfather. What are you doing here?
Is it that strange for me to come to the Kotoura family's private beach?
No, but...
First a theme park, now a private beach?
They may be rich, but...
Just don't think about it too hard.
Stooop!
They invited us here.
It's only polite to enjoy ourselves.
I-I guess you're right.
Kotoura! Let's hit the water already!
Over here!
Here! Here!
Hey! Jiggle-joggle!
Mine jiggle-joggle, too!
It would appear, sir, that my psychic powers have awakened.
What a mysterious coincidence. Mine, too.
I can read Kotoura's mind.
Another strange concurrence. I can, too.
So what do you think of my new swimsuit?
Come on, Manabe. Gimme a compliment.
Mmm. Be careful to avoid sunburn.
Welp, I'll be hanging out over here.
Alas for my pallid skin.
Upsadaisy.
Gghnaargh!
You don't have anything else to say?!
Let's split, Moritani!
Yeah!
And for all that...
Tee-hee! Hee-tee!
ain't the beach great?!
Beaches are just the best.
Hey! You're still wearing your shirt!
How improper, Haruka!
There, it's off!
Hey! Kotoura!
This feels so nice.
Kotoura! Come play with me.
Hiss!
K-Kotoura?
She's like a stray cat. She won't let me play with her.
She's just being shy. Don't you think it's kind of cute?
Better than being an insensitive asshole who doesn't react at all.
What should I do? At this rate,
I won't get to ogle her swimsuit.
Uh. I won't get to play with her.
I'd guess she's picking up on those ulterior motives.
He's talking to President Mifune about something.
I can just hear him:
"Your breasts are so jiggly-joggly! Hurr hurr hurr!"
or something like that.
Stupid Manabe.
I'll have lots of fun without you.
Huh?
What's up? Getting hungry?
Yeah. Let's have lunch.
Hey! Come on back! Kotoura!
Aww, look how hard she's waving.
Wait.
Kotoura!
She's caught in a riptide!
Manabe, use the boat!
M-Manabe...
Kotoura!
Up you go!
M-Manabe...
I was so scared!
I thought I'd never make it back!
Well, yeah! That's what you get for going off alone!
Yeah.
It's dangerous, so stick by me.
Okay.
Watching you two is just exhausting.
And so, luncheon is served.
I've been waiting for this!
All that worrying's made me even hungrier.
Grandfather, what do you mean by "luncheon?"
I called in a top chef. Something wrong with that?
N-No, of course not.
Mind if I head on in?
Kotoura...
Man up, boy. That was the perfect chance,
and you didn't do a thing! You miserable weakling!
I stand ashamed! Next time, I swear!
I even made a lunch for him.
But it seems I'll never get the chance to give him one of my lunches.
Oh, did you make this yourself?
I'll take it off your hands.
M-Manabe? But...
I'd rather have this.
Delish! Your cooking is seriously awesome, Kotoura!
They're having a much nicer meal inside.
You don't have to do this for my sake.
I've been dying to eat one of Kotoura's homemade lunches!
It's good! So damn good!
What is it?
N-Nothing.
Yeah?
This is so good!
I'm glad I came to the beach.
It's just not summer without some fireworks.
Whoa! Don't point that thing at other people!
Muroto! You're the vice-president! Do something about her!
I. Love these.
Stop following me!
I told you to stay away!
Are these puny fireworks really enough for you?
I had some really spectacular ones prepared just for you.
I appreciate the thought but please, just go home!
I even had them specially made.
U-Um.
Manabe, President Mifune, Muroto, Moritani.
I, um...
Thank you.
I never knew summer vacation could be so much fun.
Silly.
Summer vacation has only just begun.
Come on, Kotoura. Join us!
I told you not to point that at other people!
Sorry, but the black snakes are mine. All mine.
Kotoura.
Yeah.
All right! I'm gonna make this the best summer vacation ever!
Truly a natural-born klutz.
Are you okay, Kotoura?
I'm fine!
Flat as a board
Flat at first sight
Flat as a pancake
If my breasts had been only one size bigger
maybe everything would have worked out differently for us
Taking it slow is just a part of my shyness
I'm not having second thoughts or anything
My thighs and no further!
No need to be uneasy when we hold hands
I'm happy, but
all those fantasies leaking from your brain are like an earthquake warning
I may be flat, but
That's also fine, right?
Love is all we need
But, but, but
I know
I can feel your eyes roaming about
I was acting strong
That's also fine, right?
Who cares about size?
But, but, but
When there are bigger breasts around
Don't look at them and don't compare us!
Flat as a tack
Flat at first sight
J-Jiggle joggle!
As if.
Kotoura...
No! Don't give me that look of pity!
It's okay, Kotoura! You're...
silky smooth!
Silence, you lustful lecher!
Episode 7
In This World, I...