We will now begin the 57th expedition beyond the Walls!
Onward!
The Recon Corps left to find a route to Shiganshina,
but encountered a female-form Titan,
a transformed human like Eren.
That's no abnormal.
It's a human in the body of a Titan!
As soldiers died one after another,
the column headed into a nearby forest of giant trees,
though none of the troops knew the reason.
If the Levi Squad doesn't stop it, who else will?
Decide.
Will you trust only in your own strength?
Or will you put your faith in the Recon Corps, including myself?
I'll keep going!
Fire!
Oh, right...
I wanted to ask you something.
Is it okay if we cut off your hands and legs?
They'll grow back, right?
I'm talking about your limbs, not the Titan's.
We need you alive, after all...
Our enemies are prepared to sacrifice everything.
I never expected the enemy to destroy itself along with the evidence
by inciting other Titans to devour its flesh.
Retreat, men!
Back into formation!
Return to Karanes!
Erwin...
Why did you order Levi to resupply?
There's no time to waste.
The female-form Titan was eaten.
But did you see the person inside get eaten?
I didn't.
You can't mean—
Yes...
If your original hypothesis was correct,
they can still move to a degree after regaining human form.
If they'd prepared 3D Maneuver Gear in advance...
The person inside the female-form Titan is wearing our uniform right now.
Captain Levi?
No, it's not!
Who are you?!
Günther!
The enemy is now camouflaged as one of our troops.
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
This is a victory for us!
Jetzt, hier ist ein Sieg
Our fame starts here!
Dies ist der erste Gloria
O, my friend!
O mein Freund!
Let us celebrate this victory for the next battle!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
"I died for naught" — I won't let it end like that for you
muimi na shi de atta to iwasenai
until I am the last one standing
saigo no hitori ni naru made
The enemy is cruel... We will kill—
Der Feind ist grausam... Wir bringen...
The enemy is colossal... We will jump—
Der Feind ist riesig... Wir springen...
In our hands we hold blades of glory
ryoute ni wa Gloria
and sing in the name of victory
utau no wa Sieg
We bear the wings of freedom on our backs
senaka ni wa Flügel der Freiheit
Swearing iron determination upon our hearts,
nigirishimeta ketsui wo hidarimune ni
we slash apart the circle of idiocy
kirisaku no wa Ringe der Torheit
and soar through the sky
soukyuu wo mau
with our wings of freedom
Flügel der Freiheit
Crushing Blow
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 5)
When the Colossal Titan vanished,
whoever was inside must've been wearing 3D Maneuver Gear,
permitting them to escape into the steam.
Don't you think the same thing could've happened here?
But up until now,
based on what we saw when Eren emerged from the Titan's body,
we've believed that such a feat was impossible.
His equipment was destroyed, and his uniform was gone.
Not only that, Eren was so weak that he couldn't even stand up without help.
The female-form Titan was able to summon the other Titans with its cry.
We were unable to predict this, and so the operation failed.
If a Titan's abilities vary based upon experience,
then it was a error to base our assumptions off of a total novice like Eren.
If we're going to outwit our enemy, we'll need to think outside the box.
If we're withdrawing, does that mean the mission was a success?
If so, then we may already know who was inside the female-form Titan.
I'd like to see who it is.
But why was the Commander so certain
that the enemy would come after Eren if he ventured beyond the Walls?
Maybe it's because, for whatever reason,
they suddenly halted their advance in the midst of their last onslaught.
Despite having managed to break through Trost's outer gate,
they didn't even try to reach the inner Wall gate.
And when Eren sealed the gate, they let him succeed.
That might mean that they have bigger concerns now.
Bigger concerns?
Something more important to them than breaching the Walls.
Some unexpected occurrence.
Eren's transformation into a Titan?!
I think that's the only answer.
That means—
Wait...
Someone who was there, who saw Eren transform,
is a Titan.
Günther!
Eren, don't stop!
Keep going!
But Günther—
Who's there?
Protect Eren!
Damn it, what do we do?
Eld, where should we go?
We don't have time to reach the horses!
Head for headquarters as fast as possible!
Is it the female-form Titan? Or is there more than one?
Damn it!
How dare you?!
Come at me!
I'll take you down, no matter what!
The female-form Titan?
Impossible! How?
Didn't we capture it?!
If the enemy has some way to retain its strength,
it may also be able to transform once more.
I knew it!
It's coming!
The female-form Titan!
Damn it!
How dare you?!
This time, I'll defeat you!
No!
The three of us will kill the female-form Titan.
You will continue to head straight to headquarters at top speed!
Here's what I have gleaned from this battle so far:
If we only focus on making the smart moves,
we will never get the best of our opponents.
When necessary, we must be willing to take big risks,
and we must be prepared to lose everything.
I'll fight, too!
No!
This is the best move.
Your power is too risky!
What? Do you doubt us?
Is that it, Eren?
Do you find it that hard to believe in us?
Unless we change how we fight,
mankind cannot win!
I have faith that my squad will be victorious.
Good luck!
We took out its vision.
For at least a minute, it'll be completely blind!
Kill it during that time!
Screw capturing it!
Kill it now!
You'll die here in disgrace!
Make this Titan bitch pay!
We won't let your eyes regenerate!
We'll shear off so much muscle around your shoulders,
you won't even be able to lift your arms!
Slice it all off!
Make its arms...
...fall!
They're down!
Now for the neck!
Cut through the muscles that support its neck!
Then we can strike its weak point!
They're so strong.
They forced the female-form Titan entirely onto the defensive.
How can they coordinate such synchronized attacks without even speaking?
I suppose it's only possible because they trust one another.
They've overcome many hardships that way.
That's why they're so strong, even right after losing Günther.
I'll keep going...
If I keep going forward and believe in them, without turning back, then...
I'm sure that's the right answer.
I finally understand!
I don't know...
I never have.
I can believe in my own abilities,
or the choices of my trusted comrades.
But no one ever knows how things will turn out.
Strike her neck now!
Eld!
H-How?
There's no way it can see!
It hasn't even been thirty seconds.
Just one eye?
It prioritized one eye to accelerate the regeneration...
Is that even possible?
Petra!
We need to regroup!
Petra, hurry!
Hey...
Die!
How?
My blade can't pierce it...
I...
I will...
I'll kill it!
Eren?
Wait, what? Mikasa?
That voice...
Don't tell me...
Currently Disclosable Information
Recon Corps Horses (pt1)
The horses of the Recon Corps
were bred specifically for them,
and stand around 160 cm,
weighing between 450 and 500 kg.
Currently Disclosable Information
Recon Corps Horses (pt 2)
Their top speed is between 75 and 80 km/h,
and they can maintain speeds of 35 km/h.
Horses are about the only way to escape a Titan.
I made the wrong decision.
I wanted to believe in my comrades...
Because of that, they all died!
If only I'd believed in myself and fought from the start...
If I'd just killed it at the beginning!
Back then,
if I'd transformed into a Titan...
No...
Even before that,
if I'd fought...
Captain Levi was there too.
We would have won.
We could've actually captured it.
You're not mistaken.
If you want to, do it.
I...
I made a decision.
And it killed everyone.
It's my fault they died.
But despite all that...
You're still to blame!
I'll tear you apart.
Once my hand recovers,
I'll rip you to bits...
Tear you to shreds...
I'll utterly eviscerate you...
And then devour you!
Eren!
Wait, Eren...
Don't go.
Give...
Give Eren...
Give Eren back!
Give him back!
Give me him back!
Why won't my blades cut through?
I know that
he's still alive...
I know that Eren's alive!
No matter where she goes, I'll kill her,
rip her wide open,
and dig you out of that filth.
I'm sorry, Eren...
Just wait a little longer.
Wait!
Wh-What are you—
Fall back for now.
Maintain this distance.
It may be tired.
It doesn't appear to be going particularly fast.
He seems to have been bitten right out of the neck.
Is Eren dead?
tatoeba ore ga ore ja nai to shite
If we suppose that I am not me
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
Once your sand-like shell breaks and your heart crumbles?
dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitai da
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
I broke out of the deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We used to feel like living corpses
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
But now we're breaking out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
"Eren is alive."
"Give Eren back."
The female-form Titan took Eren from Mikasa before her very eyes.
Mikasa joins forces with humanity's strongest fighter, Levi,
to challenge the female-form Titan in battle.
The Defeated
57th Expedition Beyond the Walls (pt 6)