[Citizen 1] Wh-What's going on?
[Citizen 2] Is the
city under attack?
[Citizen 3] I don't know.
[Citizen 4] I heard
the Flame Alchemist
turned enemy of the state.
[Citizen 5] Are you
sure about that?
[Citizen 4] Well,
that's the rumor.
Hey! You got a radio in here?
Quick! Turn it on to
Radio Capital! Hurry!
The public news station?
Yeah. You aren't gonna
believe what's going on.
There's never anything
good on that station.
Just turn it on!
Before the military shuts
down the broadcast! Come on!
[Broadcaster] Do I understand
you correctly, Mrs. Bradley?
The "Mrs. Bradley"?
[Bradley's Wife] That's
right. Our own military...
They attempted
to have me killed.
You mean, someone
gave out that order?
They actually pointed
their guns at you?
They did. They specifically
said to shoot me
and Colonel Mustang's
men. It was awful.
[Broadcaster] Fuhrer Bradley
went east to preside over
a military exercise and has
yet to return to Central.
[Bradley's Wife] That's correct.
[Broadcaster] So then,
it would seem that an official
took advantage of his absence
in order to stage a coup.
[Bradley's Wife]
That I do not know.
Is that really Mrs. Bradley?
I've heard her speak before.
That's her, alright.
[Broadcaster] I imagine
you must be relieved
that your son is traveling
with his father.
[Bradley's Wife] I haven't
been able to contact my son.
[Broadcaster] You haven't?
You're kidding!
[Bradley's Wife sobs]
That poor woman.
I sure hope little
Selim's alright.
[Broadcaster] Please try to
remain calm, Mrs. Bradley.
[Customer 1] A coup d'état?
[Customer 2] They're
fools if they think
they can run this country
without Bradley.
[Bradley's Wife sobs]
If... If Colonel Mustang
hadn't saved me...
I'm certain they
would've killed me.
[Broadcaster] I see. it sounds
as though Colonel Mustang
was expecting this coup d'état.
Did he say Mustang?
[Broadcaster] If it's not
too difficult, do you think
you could describe the exact
details of your rescue for us?
Okay.
She doesn't know
Selim's a Homunculus?
Don't you think that
someone should tell her?
How can we? We still
haven't even told her
that Fuhrer Bradley is missing.
[Bradley's Wife]
But that's when--
[Broadcaster and
Bradley's wife gasp]
There's something we haven't
told Mrs. Bradley yet...
but she needs to hear it.
The Fuhrer was
returning to Central...
But his train was blown up.
[Bradley's Wife gasps]
I'm sorry, but we
have yet to find him.
[Bradley's Wife
gasps, exhales]
[Broadcaster] Mrs. Bradley!
Is she still conscious?
Uh... Well, uh--
Mrs. Bradley fainted.
She's understandably
a little overwhelmed
by the news we all just
received. And about that...
What exactly did you
mean when you said
that you have yet
to find the Fuhrer?
Well you should
know this first...
The Colonel's suspected the
senior staff of foul play.
And he's expected them to
make a move for some time now.
So with the Fuhrer's train
having been bombed...
And the orders given to
assassinate Mrs. Bradley...
His suspicions were confirmed.
We know for a fact.
Someone's attempting
to overthrow the government.
[Cremin] Listen, you fool!
I want that
broadcast shut down!
Do you have any idea the
damage that this is causing?!
I only wish it was that
easy, sir... but I can't.
They've taken the
whole studio hostage...
We're sitting here with
guns pointed at our heads...
We're lucky that
we're still alive.
The only reason they
haven't shot any of us
is because we're
following their orders.
Put Mustang on the phone!
I want to speak to
that traitor directly!
Uh, Mustang? He's, um...
Uh...
Ah! Ahh! Don't shoot!
Nooo! Don't shoot me!
I'm sorry!
[sound of phone
being hung up]
[busy signal]
[Cremin snarls]
[laughter]
How was my performance?
You should win an award!
Back to it! Don't
stop broadcasting!
Right!
There's no way
I'm gonna abandon
the story of the century!
[Broadcaster]
To continue with our story,
we now have an
exclusive message
from one of Colonel
Mustang's men.
So Colonel Mustang isn't
behind the uprising?
[Ross] Those of us giving our
support to Colonel Mustang...
We may be few in number...
[Brosh] That.. voice...
[Ross] But that won't stop us
from protecting the
legacy of the Fuhrer.
We'll do everything we can
to stop these traitors
in the name of justice.
[Brosh sighs joyfully]
[Grumman laughs]
Brilliant play, Mustang.
Taking advantage
of the Fuhrer's absence
and using his influence
any way you like
to suit your needs.
And invoking the name
of justice at that.
Let's keep our fingers crossed
that the public accepts it.
[Breda] You sounded like a pro.
And that last bit, about
"justice"... Nice touch.
Well, of course.
Everyone's willing
to fight for justice.
So I said it.
That's right. And in this war,
it belongs to us.
[indistinct murmurring]
[Man 1] Does anyone
know what's going on?
Mustang's men say that they're
trying to prevent an uprising.
Are you sure
he's not behind it?
[Ishvalan 1] Roy Mustang
is telling the truth.
We've just arrived in
Central from East Amestris.
We witnessed the wreckage
of the Fuhrer's train
with our own eyes. It is true.
The leader of your
country is missing...
And no one has even
informed you yet?
Our Fuhrer could be
dead for all we know.
Why would they keep all of us
in the dark about such a thing?
The military must be
staging a coup d'état!
[Citizen 8] But
who's behind it?!
[Citizen 9] If they
storm the radio station
and kill Mrs. Bradley...
Then we'll know it's
the senior staff.
[Citizen 11] Selim!
What about little Selim?!
[Citizen 12] Do you think
he's been taken prisoner?
[Citizen 13] I just
hope he's safe.
[concerned murmurs]
[Unidentified Citizen]
Mrs. Bradley...
[Gate Captain] What is the
garrison doing down there?!
[Subordinate 1] Well,
sir, the enemy seems
to possess more firepower
than we expected.
They're putting up
a strong offense.
Hmph. No excuse!
They're on foot.
I doubt they have
that much firepower!
[Subordinate 2] We have a
transmission from the garrison!
You should hear this.
You're late checking in!
I want a detailed
rundown. Now go ahead.
[Garrison Soldier]
The... The Briggs soldiers!
Th-They actually have a--
Ah...! Hey, what's happening?!
[Gate Captain growls]
Sir? Is everything okay?
I mean, we aren't going to
lose the main gate
to them, are we, sir?
Of course not!
Ridiculous!
That's impossible!
They'd need a tank to
breach the main gate.
Huh?
What?!
[fighting sounds]
Maybe I could lend you
a hand... Fullmetal?
Colonel?!
[Gerso gurgles, Darius grunts]
You just manage
to make new friends
everywhere you go... Hm?
[Scar grunts]
Is that Scar?
I can't help but
think of the last time
we were here, Lieutenant.
As I recall, you were
crying over me.
Shame I don't get to see that
softer side of you more often.
The last thing I'm gonna do
is start crying for you now.
Water makes you useless.
Save your banter for later!
Kill these things!
Hey, don't you dare
give me orders!
He's right! Just start
shooting at these white guys.
No, save your ammo!
Bullets won't even
slow 'em down!
[Dummy roars]
Not again! How else
do we kill them?
They're Homunculi?
No... They aren't
healing themselves.
But they're not dying, either.
They've got to be powered
by Philosopher's Stones.
[Ed yells]
[fighting sounds]
[Ed pants]
[Dummies scream in agony]
[Gerso and Darius]
Uh... Huh?
[Ed shudders]
They were the enemy.
It had to be done.
[Ed shudders, exhales]
[May pants]
[Envy] Stop scampering
around, dammit!
[May] He obviously doesn't
want me to go this way.
And the chi is stronger
down here. I knew it!
[Envy grunts, yells]
[May cries, struggles]
[May grunts]
[Envy cries out]
[Envy yells]
[May cries]
[pipes creak]
[Gerso] Is that May?
[Envy coughs]
Envy?!
Eh? Not you guys...
[Envy growls]
[May grunts]
You damn fool! Why didn't
you go back to Xing?!
But I.. I thought...
I just wanted to...
[Scar] Forget it. Don't cry.
[May] Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
Bleh. Typical whiny humans.
You're making my stomach turn.
[Envy sighs]
I gotta admit, you guys really
made a serious mess down here.
So, we've got the
Fullmetal Alchemist
and the Flame Alchemist...
And there's even Scar...
And I've got a serious grudge
with you filthy chimera.
So, then... Who gets the
pleasure of being first to die?
[Roy] You're Envy, right?
[Envy] Hm?
You're the Homunculus who can
change his appearance at will.
Wow! You've heard
of me! I'm flattered!
Nice to meet you, Colonel.
Hold on. You're teaming up
with him, Scar? You do know
that he helped reduce
Ishval to a hell on earth?
I'm aware of that.
What?! You're friends now?
You guys are no fun at all!
What happened to trying to
crush each other's windpipes?
Look at the two of you!
You obviously wanna
kill each other, so do it!
[Roy sighs] We aren't
going to be the pawns
in your sick little
game anymore.
Really? And what
about your sick games?
Don't kid yourself, Mustang.
You know humans love to watch
other people suffer while
making fools of themselves.
I mean, why else
would you constantly
be at war with each other?
Hm. There really is
nothing quite like
watching fools dig
their own graves.
[Envy whistles]
Especially when that fool
is an arrogant Homunculus
who's too stupid to
see what he's doing.
[Envy] Hm...
[Roy] I've humored
you long enough.
So how about you answer
a question of mine?
I want you to tell me
who killed Maes Hughes.
[Ed gasps]
And I want the truth... Homunculus.
Maria Ross did. Isn't that
why you burned her to death?
[Roy] Shut up.
I know that she didn't kill him.
Huh? You mean to tell me
that you scorched an innocent
girl to a pile of ashes?
Nicely done, you monster!
Wow. Must've been fun
telling her family...
Did you cry when you told them?
Or did you sit back quietly
and endure their outrage?
Quit running your
mouth, you idiot.
I'm sick of you Homunculi
giving me the runaround
when I ask you this question.
Tell me the truth or I'll
burn it out of you...
You worthless scum.
[Envy groans]
Tell me who's responsible
for his murder.
[Envy laughs]
[Envy] Congratulations,
Colonel Mustang.
You've finally hunted
down your culprit.
[Roy and Hawkeye grunt]
[Envy giggles]
You're saying that
you killed Hughes?
I doubt a moron like you
could pull that off.
[Envy] Moron? Tell me who
the real moron is here.
Because I don't think it's me.
[Ed gasps]
I prefer to use that
term for someone
who falls for a
cheap trick like this.
[Roy gasps]
Ha ha! You should see your face!
Ah, you're not gonna
believe this...
But that was the same look on
Hughes' face when I shot him!
The utter shock...
The dumb confusion...
You could see every
emotion he felt
as his own wife shot him.
Ah... It... was.. great!
[Ed seethes]
[Roy] That's enough.
You were stupid
enough to confess...
and even more stupid to boast.
Everything you've said is
fuel on your funeral pyre.
So then... I think
I'll begin...
by burning out your tongue.
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Stand down, all of you.
I'm dealing with him on my own.
This one is mine
and mine alone...
Well. You heard him.
Let's keep moving and
find this Father guy. Ah!
[Envy] I don't remember giving
you permission to leave.
I still owe you some pain
and misery for what you did--
[Envy screams]
Keep your eyes on me, Envy.
Our conversation is the only
one that should concern you.
[Envy grunts]
[Roy] It's kind of
interesting how quickly
the tongue can be rendered
to a bubbling grease...
It's surprising how easy
it burns... Isn't it?
Lieutenant.. You really
think the two of you--
[Hawkeye] Edward. Just go.
We can handle this one.
Are you sure?
The Lieutenant said go, Elric.
You've got more important
matters to deal with.
He's right, Ed. Now let's go.
[Ed] Hold on!
Damn it!
[Darius] The Colonel's
gonna be fine.
You saw that back there.
This won't even be
a challenge for him.
That's not exactly what
I'm worried about.
Huh? Then what's the problem?
[Envy] So... You've
been rather dogged
in your pursuit
of Hughes' killer.
You're a true friend
to the very end...
[Envy yells, roars]
Keep your distance, Lieutenant.
Out of respect for your
tireless quest for vengeance,
I'll give you the fight
you're looking for.
I'm not exactly capable of
treading lightly in this body.
So you better give
it all you've--
[Envy roars in pain]
What's it like having the fluid
inside of your eyes boil?
I'd imagine it
might sting a little.
Damn you!
[Roy snaps, Envy screams]
[Roy] I can't believe you'd
give me a bigger target.
Did you think that
size would increase
your chance of winning?
You idiot. Stand up, monster!
Go on and regenerate yourself.
You'll suffer a thousand
deaths before I'm done.
[Envy] That's right.
How could I forget?
He's the one who
incinerated Lust to death.
[Envy growls]
[Roy] You coward!
[Hawkeye] Colonel!
[Roy] You wait here,
Lieutenant!
I'm going to take
care of him myself!
[May] This way.
It's gotta be this way.
This place is creepy.
These tubes are like veins.
And the further we get,
the more it feels like I've
got a bad case of heartburn.
I'm not surprised.
I've got it too.
There's a strong mass
of rancid chi ahead.
Rancid chi?
You know how you can
feel a crowd's fear
before a disaster? It's like
that, but it's far worse.
I don't really understand...
but it sure is scarin'
the hell outta' me.
[Gerso] This is the last place
I'd want to run into
that Father guy.
Scar. I need to talk to you.
It's about the Flame
Alchemist, isn't it?
It wasn't that long ago
that I was a monster.
I understand the burning desire
for revenge all too well.
The way he's headed...
He will destroy himself
in the flames of hatred...
And it's doubtful that
he will ever recover.
[Ed gasps]
[Envy screams]
[Roy] Show yourself, Envy!
Damn it!
[Roy] Come out now.
Otherwise, I'm gonna
ignite your bone marrow.
Roy! What's up?
[Envy] Stupid human!
He won't kill his friend!
[Roy growls, snaps]
[Envy screams]
What's wrong with you?!
You didn't even hesitate to
incinerate your best friend!
Maes Hughes is dead.
That's a fact.
And you invoke his image?
You must be a glutton
for punishment. Hya!
[Envy screams]
Damn! I'll show you
real punishment!
[Roy snaps, Envy screams]
[Envy] Again?! My eyes!
They're gone!
[Roy] So I'm curious.
Were you trying to get close
so I wouldn't use heavy fire?
No one told you that I
can do pinpoint aiming?
Too bad for you...
Because I can!
[Roy snaps, Envy screams]
Colonel... I'm sorry,
but I can't wait.
[Envy screams, writhes]
Tch. You're not getting away.
[Envy chuckles]
[footsteps]
I told you to stay
behind, Lieutenant.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't
just sit there, sir.
Where's Envy?
He outran me. This place
is like a labyrinth.
Well, you might as well help me
kill him now that you're here.
Stay right by my
side, Lieutenant.
[Roy] Hm?
[Narrator] The years that pass
between the moment of birth
and the moment of death
are the true materials
that construct a human being.
Time must accumulate to create
a genuine and robust self,
but the person is only complete
in their final moment.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 54:
"Beyond the Inferno."
Look closely at yourself.
Examine what's in your heart.