Here, Bro.
Come on, eat it.
Well, Bro?
Isn't it good?
Yeah.
It's great.
Hagino.
It seems like...
I won't be seeing you yet.
I want to spend more time with them, you see.
The serpent Ishihara continues his wretched attacks.
However, in the jaws of death,
Sakuragi desperately clings to life.
So he's finally dead.
Well, I'm not surprised.
He's had nothing to eat or drink for ten days.
Well, what a pity.
You only had six days to go.
Six more days and you would've been out of here.
Sucks for you.
Just... six more days.
What the hell's going on?!
It's been ten days, but he looks like he's better! Not worse!
Really?
That's quite peculiar.
Just... six more days.
Mr. Ishihara, please prepare a water hose.
A water hose?
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
We'll have to be a little rough.
You want me to strangle him with the hose?!
What are you saying?
Of course not.
It's best to keep his body free of injuries.
Just trust me.
No matter what, Sakuragi won't leave this place alive.
Hello?!
Doctor?!
Mr. Ishihara, I'll tell you the details later.
Fucking Ishihara!
Minakami!
Calm down!
Minakami, no!
You're still not healed.
Let me go!
I'm gonna beat the crap out of Ishihara!
No!
Leave this to Mr. Kumagai.
No way in hell I will!
Even if you go back...
you won't be able to do anything.
You'll only cause more trouble for Sakuragi.
Bro...
Turtle brought Bro a rice ball?
Yeah.
Since then, I've been bringing him food behind Mr. Ishihara's back.
Sakuragi will be out in six days.
He'll hold out somehow.
That true?
You're really bringing him food?
Yeah.
So don't worry.
And I'd like you to hear this as well.
Okay.
I'll put Minakami back in the facility tomorrow.
What do you mean?
He's still not healed.
If he stays here...
Minakami will also become a victim of harassment.
What... do you mean?
It's not just Mr. Ishihara.
The director of the hospital's involved as well.
Doctor Sasaki.
Are you serious?
I know it's a shock, but it's true.
No...
I don't know why,
but Doctor Sasaki's also involved in the relentless violence against Sakuragi.
No...
Minakami.
Tomorrow at noon, I'll come get you.
Let's go back to the facility.
I won't let you or Sakuragi...
or anyone else die.
I promise.
Sure, all right.
Sakuragi, can you hear me?
It's me, Kumagai.
I've brought you food.
Sakuragi?
Hey, what's wrong, Sakuragi?!
What in the...
Hold on!
I'll stop the water right now!
Hey...
Mr. Kumagai.
What the hell's going on?
Stupid Kumagai.
He said he'd come pick me up this afternoon!
It's already night.
Minakami, calm down.
I'm sure...
Mr. Kumagai has his reasons for being late.
He must.
I don't have time.
I don't have a second to lose.
Hey.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going back to the facility.
Don't be stupid!
I can't let you go outside without surveillance.
I'm sure he'll come... by tomorrow.
There's no real proof that Bro can survive until tomorrow.
Even if I have to beat you down, I will go!
Minakami...
I-Ishihara...
Hey.
Come on, Minakami.
You want to leave the hospital, right?
Isn't Mr. Kumagai coming?
Oh, right!
I figured you don't get the newspaper here,
so I brought one for you.
Mr. Kumagai...
Died?
No...
He was drunk, drove into the river, and drowned.
Serves him right.
I won't let you or Sakuragi...
or anyone else die.
I promise.
Well, that's how it is.
So I'll be in charge...
of 2-6 from now on.
My pleasure to be with you again.
Now, shall we go, Minakami?
Doctor Sasaki's waiting downstairs.
I need to take him with me.
Get ready to leave.
Um.
Before he leaves, can I change his bandages?
What?
Well, all right.
Make sure you bring him down when you're done.
Got it?
Yes.
About Mr. Kumagai's accident...
It's... some bullshit story.
Hey, nurse.
What's your name?
Setsuko.
Koike Setsuko.
Setsuko, huh?
Setsuko, you like Bro, don't you?
Why do you say that all of a sudden?
Don't try to hide it.
I can tell just from watching you.
Bro's already been in here for two years.
So I don't know if there's anyone to welcome him when he leaves this facility.
If we could, we'd do it for sure...
but we've still got more than a year inside.
So...
I want you to welcome him.
Don't worry.
We'll protect Bro.
We won't let him die.
That's a promise, Minakami.
I promise to go get him.
"I won't let Ishihara kill Bro."
"If he dies, so will all six of our hearts."
"I swear I'll save Bro."
In the morning glow, Mario swore in his heart.
Mario!
Mario?
You're back?
Wouldn't you have preferred to stay in the hospital longer?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
No way.
Ishihara and Sasaki were in this together?
Yeah.
Damn it!
That old pervert!
What's wrong, Mario?
Mr. Kumagai's dead.
What?
He's dead?
What do you mean?!
He drowned... apparently.
He was driving drunk...
and drove his car into the river.
That's ridiculous.
It's hard to believe he would drive drunk.
Something's fishy.
Yeah.
I'm absolutely certain Sasaki and Ishihara killed him.
Mario.
We don't have time anymore.
The six of us here...
All six of us... are going to get Bro out of here.
Hey, Mario...
What did you say?
At this rate, those two are going to kill Bro for sure.
We can't just sit on our butts anymore.
This... is the only option we have.
Mario, are you nuts?
Bro only has four more days in here!
Do you really think Ishihara and Sasaki will let Bro out of here alive?
If we get caught...
We'll be sent to a juvenile prison.
But...
That's our only option now.
So...
How do you plan to free him?
Well...
I figured you didn't have a plan.
All right.
I'll draw something up right now.
If I leave it to you, we'll just get fucked over.
Uncovered...
But let me say something.
This plan's just about freeing Bro.
Your safety's not guaranteed.
Bring it on.
If we can free Bro, we'll go to juvenile prison, or wherever else they send us.
Hear that?
Sorry, guys.
I'm really... sorry.
So this is where you were, Mr. Ishihara?
Doctor Sasaki.
I don't think there's a reason to stay here forever.
The water's been running for a while now.
He should've lost consciousness from the cold.
Not to mention no one will feed him anymore.
Well, let's take our time and see what happens.
Take our time?
How can you be so calm?
I've already killed someone!
I don't have time for leisure!
You're too loud, Mr. Ishihara.
I'd also like a few words with you about that.
What is it?
What do you want to say?
Who told you to kill him, you son of a bitch?
If you hadn't killed him, I could simply have transferred him to some facility far away.
If you disobey me again, you'll meet the same fate as Mr. Kumagai.
Thanks to you, we can't take direct action anymore.
We must wait patiently.
If... Sakuragi doesn't die...
Don't be ridiculous.
Didn't you see him?
He's at his limit.
He'll only last until tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning.
He'll be dead.
Sakuragi... will be dead!
Bro's escape plan... complete!
I'll tell you the details of the plan after lunch.
Wait a minute, Uncovered.
You still had some butts left?
You kept it a secret from us?
You bastard. That's a lot.
Wait...
I picked them up when I was in charge of cleaning out the the trash in the guards' room.
One for the each of us.
Here.
One for you too, Mario.
Something wrong, Mario?
This... This one's for Bro.
I'll keep watch.
So don't mind me and take a puff.
I think I'll save this too.
Me too.
All right!
Let's share Uncovered's, then.
Good idea.
Wait a minute.
I'm all out, you know?
This reminds me of when we met Bro.
We passed it around among the seven of us.
Yeah.
After Bro beat the crap out of us.
Hurry, take a puff.
He treated us like real human beings.
Let's hope that by summer, two years from now...
we'll be out on the streets.
We'll definitely get him out.
Lunch time!
Get out!
Just a little more patience, Bro.
We'll get you out for sure.
Bro taught the boys the value of friendship and love.
The six boys of 2-6 made a firm decision on his behalf.
"We'll risk it all."
The six made the choice regardless of possible loss and gain...
and prepared themselves for their war.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Begin escape plan.
We're all going outside.
We're coming, Bro.