After what happened
at the audition,
I had a falling out with Takuto
and couldn't go home.
But Mitsuki told me
she wanted me to return.
At first, the both of us
were hesitant.
But with Mitsuki's persistence and pleading,
I was able to make up with him.
We celebrated the revival
of our partnership
and set off Green Onion Ramen
fireworks and it felt really good!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
It looks like her illness
hasn't progressed.
How about it?
Can she return to work?
Certainly when you compare
it to the 12-year-old's X-ray,
symptoms are not at all visible in
the condition of the 16-year-old's.
Well, how about it?
Let's see.
If she doesn't push herself...
- What?! Yay!
- Yes!
That's great, isn't it, Mitsuki!
Yes.
Dr. Wakaoji!
I promise.
I won't push myself again!
Hm? Good.
Dr. Wakaoji, thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
At any rate, that's really great.
You can sing songs
as Full Moon again.
Yeah.
More importantly, Dr. Wakaoji
forgave me, I'm really happy!
Yeah, yeah.
What is it?
Umm... You're Takuto, right?
That's right.
Who's the rabbit next to you?
I'm Meroko!
Oh... I see.
Somehow it feels like I'm recapturing
the thread of a bad dream.
That's rude!
A bad dream, like we are spooks
and specters or something.
We are bona fide Death Spirits,
you know?!
Death Spirits...
Yes, that's it.
Oh!
Meroko, don't say that now.
Why not?
I mean, why does she know about us?
What in the world happened
while I wasn't around?!
It can't be helped, can it?
The situation required it.
It seems like we're always carried
away by the situation requiring it.
Is this okay,
Green Onion Ramen?
W-Well, you've got the official word that
you're okay as long as you're
in your current condition.
So, from now on, we have to
think of Mitsuki's body first.
Thank you, Ms. Oshige.
Work with all your might!
Yes!
The time has come
to start working again.
I have to do my best.
Oh... Good morning, Mr. Todoroki.
What? Ms. Oshige,
I haven't seen you in a while.
Starting today Full Moon is back at work.
Thanks in advance for your help.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, now that you mention it...
How are you? Are you feeling well?
Yes, sorry to have troubled you.
I hope you are,
take care of yourself.
I will.
Well... Excuse me.
Excuse me!
They say that she's in
poor physical condition
but I wonder what
it was really about.
What do you mean?
There's a rumor that
she has a boyfriend.
I've heard she doesn't deny it either.
One could say she's bold,
or maybe shameless.
Oh, is that so?
But that rumor,
who did you hear it from?
Well, that's uh...
Ms. Sasaki?
Hm?
She returns to work starting today?
Full Moon...
Yes, so it seems.
For the taping of a music show.
Hmm.
The talk of her missing
the audition in such manner
is already resounding
throughout the industry.
If she thinks she can make
a comeback that easily
she's got another thing coming.
I mean, rather, I won't let her.
Good morning!
- Oh...
- She's here.
Must be nice,
they say she has a boyfriend.
To think she can afford to cut back
on her work! What luxury.
I think she's letting her popularity
getting to her head.
Pretty conceited for a new face!
There's, like, a negative vibe.
Don't take them seriously, Mitsuki.
But...
This on the first day of her comeback.
They say his name is Eichi.
Huh?! Why do they know that much?
W-What was that about?!
Don't just keep quiet!
Say something back!
Meroko!
- Hey!
- Huh?
Good morning!
Mr. Takasu?!
Congratulations on your comeback!
What? Um...
I was really surprised when
I heard you'd collapsed!
But you're returning today? Work hard!
Mr. Takasu, thank you so much!
This bouquet is so big.
Wow... It smells so good!
Well, I thought it would
liven things up!
It's about time, shall we go?
Yeah.
Well, do your best!
Yes!
That man is unexpectedly nice.
I'm a bit surprised.
That aside...
What is it, Ms. Oshige?
Things with Eichi have become even
more of a rumor than I thought.
Yes.
I hope it doesn't become
a terrible scandal.
Huh? And how bad could that be?
That's fine.
If there's a little bit of a scandal,
then surely it will be easier
for Eichi to find Mitsuki!
That's another way to think about it.
I've always suspected it,
but you're the kind of girl to always
gain something from a mistake.
You know it!
What? That's a compliment, right?
Huh? Yeah.
Well, let's leave it at that.
And...Mr. Takasu was checking on
how she was doing.
What was that?
What's going on?!
Why does it go so well for her?
Why is she loved by everyone?!
Even though she hasn't
put in any effort!
If it were me,
it wouldn't be going this well.
I wouldn't be accepted by
those around me like she is.
I know.
After all, this world has
always been cold to me.
I wonder if she's lost.
Oh!
Oh... Thank you.
Um... Where are you going?
I want to go to my grandchild's house,
on this map.
I know this place.
I'll take you.
Good morning!
What do you mean "good morning"?!
You're late!
I'm sorry.
You're an hour late,
are you taking us for a ride?
I'm sorry!
I'll get ready right now!
There's no need for that!
We've already found
your replacement!
What?
You don't have to come anymore!
No way...
What on earth were you doing?!
Because...there was an old lady
who was lost and...
Listen! In this world, you are
the most important thing!
You won't rise to the top
by caring about someone else!
After that, they started the rumor
that I was conceited,
and my jobs were cancelled
one after the next.
Even though I did something
that was to be expected.
I can't forgive it.
Why?
Since then, I've put
in so much effort.
I did everything to
change the image
that I was conceited,
which stuck from that one time.
I always looked at the reactions
of those around me
and tried to be nice.
Even so...
Why is it always that girl?!
Mitsuki.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Miss Full Moon!
Rehearsal, please.
Oh...yes!
Well then, camera test, please.
We're starting!
5 seconds, 4, 3...
Why do I like you so much?
My tears are falling.
Because in the past
there were a lot of things I lost...
And I couldn't sing.
A distance place—
I wonder if everyone is telling
rumors about me.
...was where I belonged
Who's that?!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Stop the music!
I'm disappointed in you!
Disrupting someone's song...
Ms. Komaki!
I-I'm sorry!
If you call yourself
professional singers,
you should listen to the singing
of others with the proper respect!
- Y-Yes!
- You are absolutely right, Ms. Komaki!
And you, your song is not all there.
What happened?
Where is the power you had
when you turned on me that time?
I-I'm sorry!
And you over there!
If you have time to lurk around
in the shadows,
how about studying acting
for a little bit?
Madoka...
It seems you've been spreading
rumors for some time.
You can't stand a fair match
based on your own merits?
If so, that's the same
as losing from the start!
Madoka? Rumors?
Th-That's right! We...
We took what Madoka said at face value!
I'm sorry.
I-I think I did something
that is unforgivable.
But... I'm envious of Full Moon.
Madoka... Jealous of me?
But telling rumors in the shadows...
that wasn't my intention.
It's just, it must be nice to have
someone that you like.
I want to see what it's like to
like someone like that.
I didn't think it would be
that much of a rumor.
I'm sorry.
That wasn't my intention.
What? No...that's okay.
I'm sure that Eichi will find you.
Thank you.
I think that Madoka is
a nicer girl than I thought.
That's right!
There are times when you can't
convey what you want to convey.
I hope that's it.
What?
Meroko, what do you mean by that?
Let's see.
Oh!
Oh my... What happened?
Th-That...
Huh? Oh no!
What happened?
What, what?
Who? Who did this horrible thing?!
Oh...
Oh! Hello?
This is Oshige.
Is Yasuno the stylist there?
What? She's not?
Do you know where she went?
Huh? We have a big problem with
Full Moon's wardrobe!
Oh no! Why now, of all times,
can't I get in contact with her?!
Mitsuki?
What was that?!
It looks like we were frivolously
passing on rumors by ourselves!
And she was the one bad mouthing
Full Moon not long ago!
She talks out of both sides
of her mouth!
Now, for the first time, I understand
the scary side of this business!
That just now...
What was that about?
Uh...um...
Of course! It's just as I thought.
What? What do you mean
of course, Meroko?
Madoka's tears just now
were all an act!
What? So, do you mean
that Madoka did it?
Stop it, it's not like there's proof!
Yeah, but think about that
conversation just now.
That's the only thing I can think of!
Right now, there's no use in
saying stuff like that.
Anyway, we have to do something
about this situation.
Y-Yes, I can't catch Ms. Yasuno!
Oh no! What should I do?!
That's it!
Hey hey, this is a place to
showcase my powers, don't you think?
What?
Powers?! What's that?
Well, leave it to me.
Mero-Mero Change!
Oh my...
What? Th-This? This is a little...
What are you doing?!
What? That's strange.
One more time!
Meroko... Are you playing around?
Um... We don't have much time.
L-Leave it to me I said!
Here!
W-What?
Please! We have only 30 minutes
until the performance.
That's strange.
Hmm... How was it for
an idol's wardrobe again?
That's okay.
- Huh?
- What?
I don't know who did this to
my wardrobe or why.
But...
No matter who did it,
I don't want it to get me down.
You...
- Mitsuki!
- No!
Hey! I said hey!
Have you gone crazy?
Stop! Stop! What in the world
are you doing, Mitsuki?!
I'm sure that she's in a fluster about
not having her wardrobe about now.
Serves her right.
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes and
it sounds almost sad.
Up to now what was supporting me?
I realize, now that I'm far away.
What was supporting me?
Why do I like you?
That's too easy to answer.
Everyone, I'm really sorry to
have caused you trouble
by suddenly taking a break.
Although I might not be the best,
I'll continue to work my hardest.
Please continue to support me!
That was great!
When I watched the rehearsal
earlier I wondered how it would go.
Thank you very much!
Continue to do your best!
Yes!
The sudden change of wardrobe really
surprised me, but this is good.
As a comeback, too, it's a big success.
Thank you!
Well, it seems that there are
some strange rumors,
but don't worry about it.
It happens a lot in this world.
Yes!
Well then, take care.
Good job!
I never would have guessed
that you'd arrange and wear
your costume in that manner.
This is one little girl who always
gains something from her mistakes.
Really, at one point, I wondered
what was going to happen.
This kid's gotten tough.
Absolutely.
But you know, that Madoka
is so unforgivable!
Save your breath, Meroko.
I haven't understood the
conversation for a while.
Did something happen?
Somebody cut this girl's wardrobe
into shreds!
What? What did you say?!
I'm fine.
Don't worry, Dr. Wakaoji.
But...
I'm just fine!
These kind of things won't
get me down at all! Right?
Mitsuki, you really like
singing, don't you?
I understand.
I won't waver anymore.
Dr. Wakaoji?
I'll search for some way for you, Mitsuki,
to do without an operation.
Really?
Yes.
But don't overdo it.
There are going to be many things
you need to pay attention to
on your return to work
after a long break.
But, really, don't push yourself.
Okay!
This is bad! This is bad!
Takuto, what are we gonna do?
What are you so upset for?
Her first solo performance
has been planned
so this is no time for all of this.
The thing is that there's trouble
with that solo performance!
What happened?
Someone has cancelled the event site
where she was to perform!
But the performance is tomorrow!
What are we gonna do?
Next time on Full Moon:
"A Solo Performance - Live!"
- Look forward to it!