Since the audition for the commercial was canceled...
...she had a long break before returning to work.
But...
...there was a rumor about Full Moon  going around at the television station...
On top of that...
...at some point, someone tore apart her costume...
...and we were in a huge bind!
But even in such a bind...
...Mitsuki came up with an idea to overcome it...
...and the television program finished without a hitch.
Really...
...this girl's become so strong!
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
My first solo live concert?!
You think it might be a little too early, huh?
There's been a huge response from the fans!
That means that...
...they'll all want to go to the live concert!
Are they for real?
It's like a dream come true...
Getting to hear you say such adorable things...
There won't be much time for that now...
Things are going to be hectic from here on out.
You'll lose all of your summer vacation...
...so be ready!
Okay!
Well, regarding that...
For your first live concert...
...is there anything special you'd like to try out?
Eh?
Are you asking... me?
Yes.
Just how does Full Moon  feel about this right now...?
My feelings right now?
Isn't there something?
An image... or a keyword...
Anything's okay, so...
...just tell us.
Maybe that's asking for too much, huh?
Nope.
I'll do it!
Let me do it!
Exciting Solo Live Concert
Huh?
W-What is this?
Today...
...I'll be going over the essential parts of a live concert...
...and explaining the–
Huh?
Give it up.
Man!
I give up on this!
Same Time
What you want to tell your fans
Artist
Dreams and Reality
Love and Hope
Anyways...
...to have a good live concert...
...things like your image...
...and theme are important!
Ah... in that case...
Because...
...when it comes to time to prepare...
...things will get ugly if you have to worry about stuff like that.
That's why...
...Meroko's going to help you this time.
Artist
What you want to tell your fans
Dreams and Reality
Artist
What you want to tell your fans
Dreams and Reality
Artist
What you want to tell your fans
Dreams and Reality
Like I said, that's just...
I'm already...
...far too brilliant...
It's like I'm the number one bride for any Shinigami.
What you want to tell your fans
Artist
Dreams and Reality
That's way out there...
I understand...
Everyone else thinks so...
Um...
Meroko?
Listen to people when they're talking!
Mitsuki already knows all of that.
ll your fans
Same Time
Dreams and Reality
Love and Hope
Huh?
She does?
Well...
Dreams and Reality
Love and Hope
Then... what are you planning on doing...
...for Full Moon 's first live concert?
Yep.
It's Moon and Stars.
Moon and Stars?
Yep!
The theme of Full Moon 's first live concert...
...Moon and Stars, has been decided.
Decided?!
Takuto!
You never told me that it was already decided!
I've been trying to tell you the whole time, but you haven't been listening!
I'm heartbroken...
Thanks for being so concerned about everything, Meroko.
Actually, you see...
This live concert...
...is being broadcast to everyone around the world through the Internet.
So... surely...
Moon and Stars...
To the moon and the stars...
...I'll send my feelings for Eichi-kun...
...and sing with all my heart!
Be sure to watch, Eichi-kun!
I-I can't... I... I-I can't... I can't breathe!
For the location of Full Moon 's first live concert...
...we've decided on Bayside Hall.
We'll open at five...
It'll start at six, so make sure everyone knows.
Yes.
As for the visual effects and stage lighting...
...they were finished yesterday.
What about the musicians?
We already got the best of the best!
The backup chorus is perfect as well!
I see.
Have all the dancers been gathered?
Yep!
We've got experienced foreign dancers ready to go!
All right.
Isn't this perfect?
Damn good job...
Ah... I thought of it earlier, but...
Yep.
Everyone...
What if...
...to put together my first live concert...
...they're all working so hard...
Boss!
They're done printing!
Oh ho...
Wow!
Nice!
They're great!
Wow! It's so beautiful!
Yeah, it looks good.
All right.
With this, Moon and Stars... will be on its way!
Let's do our best!
Okay!
Yep!
This is my first live concert...
Moon and Stars!
So then...
...everything's still in the process of being set up, right?
Yep!
I'm sure it'll be a great live concert!
Everyone, please come and listen, okay?
Good luck!
Okay! I'll do my best!
Sure.
Leave it to me.
I'll come up with the perfect advertisement.
We're counting on you!
To tell the truth...
...my own kids are huge fans, Full Moon.
I'll be there with my kids to listen.
Good luck.
Okay!
Here you go.
Akiba-san, I definitely want you to come listen!
This is the greatest!
Such a great seat at your first live concert...
...I'm so moved!
Put these posters everywhere
around the store, 'kay?
Okay, okay.
Yes, ma'am.
Full Moon-oneechan!
I'm cheering for you, so...
...you have to have a cool live concert!
Got it!
You can count on me.
I'll do my best!
Takuto's going to cheer along with me!
All right!
Promise!
'kay. It's a promise!
Yeah!
Session in Progress
I
Thanks for your hard work!
Oh, good luck on your live concert!
We're rooting for you!
Okay!
Huh?
Komaki-san...
Thank you very much!
Heh...
First live concert, huh?
Everybody!
Come hear me at my first live concert, 'kay?
This is where the live concert will be held.
Wow...
It's huge!
This is just the beginning.
You'll sing on much bigger stages.
If you're scared by just this, it'll be problematic.
Um...
Can I try standing on it?
Of course.
This is your stage.
Ah!
I'm gonna give it my all!
I-I'm home...
Ah.
Geez!
Aren't you late?
Sorry...
Ah?
Oh my, already?
At least change your clothes first.
That's right.
You have to take proper care of your skin.
Hey, kid!
Wake up!
Yes sir!
First solo live concert...
Moon and Stars...
Please come listen...
My, my, my... she's sound asleep.
Man, guess it can't be helped.
Do your best!
Good night.
Come in!
Are you done?
Yep!
How is it?
Hmm...
It's good, but...
...it seems to lack that oomph.
That's right...
It feels like something's missing.
Shall we throw on some accessories, then?
In addition...
...let's try some makeup and add a little color.
Eh?
Eh? Eh?
How's this?
Well...
In that case, I'll go even farther!
Ah... ah... ah-choo!
Ah! I'm sorry!
I'll get that off right away!
Let's see...
Did I forget to bring it?
This is...
Ah!
What are you doing, Mitsuki?
Full Moon-chan?
Huh?
I'm done!
Eh?
It's Moon and Stars!
Yep. It's cute.
All right.
That's taken care of.
Let's do her costume fitting now.
It's so wonderful!
I just tried to add something extra.
Thank you, Machi-san!
So now, then..
...all that's left is the accessories...
That's right.
Then... the theme is...
Moon and Stars!
All right!
In that case, let's make this a masterpiece!
Okay!
Let's see... next comes... this one.
Ah.
Or is this one better...?
Don't fall asleep!
But I wanna go to sleep already!
You're the one who wanted to help.
Far too brilliant...
The best choice for a bride, right?
Eichi-kun...
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yep!
Mitsuki... just like the moon and the stars that shine in the sky...
...there will surely come a time where you shine as well.
I've sent my wish to the moon and the stars...
That's why I chose Moon and Stars...
Eichi-kun...
I want to shine!
In order for Eichi-kun to find me...
In order to reach everyone who's cheering for me...
It's done!
It's finished?
Nope.
I'll try this color next.
This is taking a lot longer than I expected.
Reception Office
Good.
This will work.
Everyone will fall in love with
that accessory instantly!
Yep!
T-There's a problem!
Eh?
What's wrong?
Well...
...the site's been canceled!
What?!
What do you mean?!
The live concert's tomorrow!
Someone called saying that they were a member of the Village Pro staff...
...and told them that tomorrow's live concert for Full Moon  has been put on hold.
No way!
That's complete nonsense!
Someone go tell them about this... fix it before it's too late!
Well...
...another event was scheduled immediately after...
All the posters and tickets are already out!
Anyways, divide everyone and get on the phones!
It doesn't matter where!
Just find an open place!
Okay!   Okay!
Yes... tomorrow.
I understand.
Have a nice day.
Is that so?
There's no way?
It's the day after today!
How can we find a place that fast?
Um...
What's going to happen?
Well...
If we can't find a place...
...we'll have to postpone the live concert.
Eh?!
That can't be...
I can't believe this!
That's what you deserve.
Can you help us out somehow?
Even if you say that...
I beg you!
Anyways, can you come back later?
We're already booked.
Have a nice day.
I'm begging you!
An e-mail.
I wonder who it's from.
I'm looking forward to Full Moon 's
first live concert...
Ah!
It's those high school students from before!
But...
I'm sorry...
I won't be able to do... the live concert...
Kiyone
Eh...
It's too bad that it's been postponed!
The place doesn't really matter...
We just wanted to listen to you sing.
Eh?
Acchan
It's Moon and Stars!
Under a real starry sky...
...it'd be kind of fashionable, right?
Moon and Stars...
Underneath a real starry sky...
That's right.
I can sing anywhere!
Set up the lights over there.
Make it snappy!
Okay!
If we don't hurry, we won't make it before the live concert starts!
Everyone!
The location for Full Moon 's concert has changed!
This way!
Is this the place?
In a place like this...?
Where's Full Moon ?
Okay.
Start it off.
Sorry to keep everyone waiting!
On this, the last evening of the summer...
...let's all have one last blast!
Full Moon 's first live concert!
Moon and Stars...
...is beginning!
Ah! It's Full Moon !
Wow! It's so pretty!
It looks just like the real moon and stars in the sky.
Ah... you just used your power again...
Let's sing a song!
Thank you.
I'm going to do my best!
Oh well.
Everyone!
Day by Day
Thank you for coming for my live concert today!
Please enjoy it to the end!
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I lost way too much back then.
Isn't it romantic?
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all.
It's the best she's ever been.
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Eichi-kun...
Are you watching me?
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
From wherever you are in the world?
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
On that day I could see...
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Why do I love you so?
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Doushite kimi wo suki ni nattandarou
Why is it that I've fallen in love with you?
Kantan sugite kotae ni naranai
I can't find an answer easily...
Preview
Hey, Meroko!
I heard the manager moved in to a place near her house!
What?! Is that gonna be all right?!
What's wrong? She said it was to better support her at her job.
But...
We have to keep the fact that Mitsuki is
Full Moon  a secret from her family!
See, I knew it! That housekeeper Tanaka-san found out!
Oh crap...
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Moving Panic
Look forward to it!