Hey, when did that Taika Reform thing happen?
You don't know that? We're in the
third grade now. You're such a dummy.
I haven't learned it yet, so...
There's an easy way to memorize it.
"Re-form" means "form twice."
"Re-form"?
That’s right, The Taika
Reforms re-wrote the doctrines.
Re-form, so it was in the year six two five.
"Re-form. 625."
Don't forget, okay?
I memorized it good. I'll never forget.
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
At Fumizuki Academy,
academic ability is its idea of power
and test results are its idea of justice.
What's the matter, Himeji? You
wanna talk to me about something?
Actually... there's something
I wanna ask you. Got a minute?
So that's what's going on. The
Year 2's first war in the first term
ended with Class F achieving
victory by defeating Class E.
I see... Not bad.
I imagine the beaten class is feeling gloomy
about their shabby equipment by now, huh?
Tell them to study hard and
take it back in the next war...
--Ah...
--...and that life is a battle.
Ah, well, actually... the students
decided not to exchange their equipment.
Hm? What's that mean?
Just as you'd expect from instant glue.
The repair is complete in no time!
That's good, Akihisa. So you
got better glue this time, huh?
We fought hard and won.
We deserve at least upgraded supplies.
Under normal circumstances,
she could've had a Class E desk by now.
Yuuji! Why did you turn
down the equipment exchange?!
What? You like shabby wooden desks like that?
It's obvious that they're better than
these low tables that break so easily!
"Glue -- for general use" "Alphadine"
What?
You don't study so desks
don't matter anyway, right?
It does matter! I put my lunch box
on it. I doze off on it. I scribble on it.
The desks are our important
partners during our days at school, right?!
Or rather, you and the desk are one.
Today's the last day we'll have these low tables
since Class A declared war on us.
Ah...
If we win the next war,
Class A's equipment will be ours.
This wasn't part of my plan,
but it's not a problem.
Everything is going as I planned.
Right, Himeji?
Huh? Ah... yes.
Now, let's go march into Class A.
So this is Class A...
It looks as if it's a ritzy hotel.
Humph.
This is suitable equipment for
me to spend my school days with.
Look, Yoshii! They've got free
drinks and all-you-can-eat snacks!
If you're surprised by every single thing
in here, they'll take advantage of you.
You should assume a more confident attitude.
Your words and actions don't match at all.
Oh? Isn't the war starting tomorrow?
Big Sister...
You've come to surrender already?
We're here to inspect our new equipment.
You're quite confident, aren't you?
I came to negotiate. I'd like to
request a duel between the reps.
Are you an idiot or what?
There's no way you can defeat
Year 2's top student in a duel, is there?
Are you scared? I guess you must be...
as you guys're cowards who attack
a weak class weakened even more
by the war they just finished.
You wanna do it right here right now?
Wait.
I don't mind accepting the duel.
Rep...!
But... on one condition.
The loser will do one thing the
winner says without exception.
What?!
Is that the reason for declaring war on Class F?
Don't get the wrong idea.
We, Class A, are obligated to
protect the academy's safety and dignity.
This is a punishment for idiots who
started a war at the start of the first term
when they haven't put any
efforts into their studies yet.
Okay. The loser of the duel between
the Reps will do whatever the winner says.
It won't be a duel. It'll be five versus five.
Yuuko...
I don't think our Rep will lose...
but it wouldn't hurt to be cautious.
Okay. Five versus five is fine.
In return, we'll decide
on the subjects for the war.
Okay.
The negotiation concluded successfully.
What're you gonna do, Yuuji,
after making a promise like that?!
It won't be a problem since
we're gonna be the winners.
We just got a bonus in that they'll
do whatever we tell them. That's all.
Are you really sure?
That Rep, Shouko Kirishima...
I heard a strange rumor about her.
A rumor?
She's an excellent student,
so she has both intelligence and beauty.
Although she's that pretty,
I hear guys leave her alone.
Really? She looks like the type
that'd be popular among guys.
According to the rumor,
she isn't interested in guys.
Not interested in guys...?
Don't tell me... her goal is...
N-N-N-N-N-No way! That can't be!
That's weird!
There's no way something like
that is happening around here.
Right, Shimada?
There is.
What?
A weird girl like that... sticks close to me.
I found you, honey!
Miharu?!
You're such a meanie, honey!
To think you left me to have a
tea party with these filthy pigs!
L-Let me go! Don't come close to me!
--Honey!
--Who's that?
Miharu Shimizu from Year 2, Class D.
Stop it! Let me go!
Please don't feel embarrassed, honey!
I know you actually love me.
You're shy, aren't you?
Like normal girls, I like guys!
Yoshii! Help me out here!
She's right, Shimizu. It's wrong
for a woman to love another woman!
It's true that Shimada's appearance,
personality and breast size
are all indistinguishable from a guy's...
figure-four leg lock!!
I'm a girl no matter how
you look at it, aren't I?!
That's right! I love her as a woman!
I give! I give up!
--I'm really not gonna let you off the hook today!
--Almost... Almost... Almost...
Ow, ow... Help me,
Shimada! I'll do whatever you say!
Really? Then next weekend,
I wanna have crepes at La
Veditz in front of the train station.
What?! But then my food budget will be....
Huh?!
Ahh! No. Please let me treat you!
A-And, call me Lady Minami
from now on. I'll call you Aki!
Y-Y-Y-Yes, Lady Minami!
And... And... T-T-Try saying you love me.
Yes, ma'am! I'll say it!
I won't let you!
Say it!
Almost... Almost... Almost...
--If you go any further...
--Now, say you love me!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Say you love me!
You... idiot!
Boy, that was terrible.
Ah... Himeji?
What're you writing, Himeji?
Ah! Yoshii?!
Th-That looks like a love letter.
B-But no one would write a
love letter in their classroom, right?
U-Uhm, well, this is...
It's not like that!
Oh, well, it is, but it's not!
This is a strange unhappy chain letter.
That misunderstanding presents
some major problems of its own.
Are you writing to someone in our class?
Yes...
I see... Then I'll teach you how to write
an unhappy chain letter in a correct way.
No thank you. This isn't
an unhappy chain letter.
Yes, it is.
In fact, I'm feeling unhappy right now.
It's not like that.
I see... What do you like about
this guy? He isn't that good looking.
Well, it's not about how he looks.
Ah, I do like how he looks, too!
My friends were also saying
that when handsome Yoshii and
sturdy Sakamoto are walking together,
it's picture perfect.
You've got good friends. Be nice to them.
They were also thinking you're
probably the one on the receiving end.
Break it off with them right away.
But it's not just his looks,
he's nice on the inside, too.
It's true that he looks like
he's got a strong liver and stuff.
That's what's inside the body.
Could it be you mean his personality?
Yes. He's kind and cheerful.
He always looks happy.
I've always admired him.
I see... That letter...
Y-Yes?
I hope you'll get the response you want.
Yes!
Oh, there you are. Let's
start the strategy meeting.
Hey, where're you going? Akihisa!
Don't come close to me! Don't walk with me!
What's the matter, Akihisa? What happened?
I'm not... I'm not...
on the receiving end!
Huh?
"Elites vs. Idiots"
Well then, we'll start the first round.
Why am I the round card girl?
--Round One.
--What're you saying? Who else can do it besides you?
I keep telling you guys that I'm not a girl.
Well then, players from
both classes, step forward.
We're counting on you, Shimada.
Okay then, I'm off to battle.
Let's finish this quickly.
You're no match for me anyway.
Don't underestimate me
just because I'm from Class F.
"Yuuko Kinoshita" "Minami Shimada"
Start the match.
I'm summoning my Avatar... Summon!
When it comes to math, my
scores are a match for Class B's!
Oh, how amazing. Summon!
O-Oh no...!
Of course, my scores are a
match for Class A's, though.
Winner, Yuuko Kinoshita, Class A.
It couldn't be helped.
After all, realizing that a Class B level player
can't defeat a Class A one
is too much for a brain like...
I can't breathe!
--Ahh! This might feel kinda good, though.
--Almost... Almost...
Round Two!
We'll start the second round.
Players, step forward.
Miho Satou, Class A.
All right. Akihisa, I'm counting on you.
Me?! If I lose here, we'll
be at the end of our rope.
Don't worry. I have faith in you.
Well well... Does that mean
that you want me to get serious?
Yeah. There's no point in
hiding it any longer, is there?
Show everyone your real strength!
Geez... I guess it can't be helped, huh?
Don't tell me... you are...
Yeah, up until now, I've
never been serious at all.
Then... you are...
That's right. Just as you've guessed...
I've been hiding this
until now, but I'm actually...
left-handed.
Winner, Miho Satou, Class A.
--Your dominant arm has nothing to do with test scores, does it?!
--My arm... My arm... My arm...!
--Almost... Almost... Almost...
The real fight has yet to
come. Let's get serious now!
Yuuji! I thought you had faith in me!
It's not that I had faith that you'd win.
I wanna give you my serious left-arm punch!
--Round Three!
--Well then, we'll start the third round.
Aiko Kudou, Class A. Kouta Tsuchiya, Class F.
What subject would you like to fight in?
Health and Physical Education.
I heard that you do well in
But I do quite well, too. On top of that,
unlike you, I really work up a sweat.
Work up a sweat?
Muttsulini!
"Aggressive Girl vs. Muttsulini"
How dare you hurt Muttsulini
like that! How cruel! That's dirty!
Do you wanna take his place?
But you don't look like
you do well in academics.
If Health and Physical Education
is okay, I can teach you...
Of course... I'm gonna make you sweat.
Yoshii!
Aki!
That's none of your business! He's
never going to get a chance like that!
That's right! Yoshii will
never need that sort of thing!
Why are you two saying such sad things?
Muttsulini?!
I'm fine. This is nothing.
Then, start the match.
Summon.
Summon!
She's got over 400 points?!
A practitioner and a theorist...
I'll show you which is stronger.
Bye-bye, Muttsulini!
Accelerate...
Acceleration complete.
C-Can't be... I lost...?!
Winner, Kouta Tsuchiya, Class F.
He's strong! His Health and
Physical Education score alone
is like my score for all subjects combined!
--Round Four.
--Well then, we'll start the fourth round.
Well then, I'm off to fight.
Himeji... Good luck.
Okay!
Then, I'll fight her.
Toshimitsu Kubo, huh? This is the crucial match.
Why?
He's the No. 2 student in Year 2.
Unless she attacks him in a subject
he's bad at or something, it'll be tough.
Oh no!
Well then. What subject
would you like to fight in?
Combined subjects, please.
He can't do that! We have the right to...
That's fine.
Himeji...
This is bad. In a combined subjects match,
the ranking itself shows his strength.
Then...
Start the match.
"Start"
Summon.
"Toshimitsu Kubo" "Mizuki Himeji"
An incredible score! The No. 2
student has a score that high?!
Himeji!
I'm summoning my Avatar...
Summon!
"Toshimitsu Kubo" "Mizuki Himeji"
Over 4000 points?!
That score is even a match for the top student.
When did you get such a high ability?!
I decided... that I'll do my best.
I heard the reason why our
class started Summoner Test Wars.
I like my class.
They try hard for others.
I like my class because of them...
...and because the
person I like is in this class.
So... I'll do my best, too!
Winner, Mizuki Himeji, Class F.
This is amazing, Aki! We've caught
up with them! We're two to two now.
Himeji...
So the next match will decide
the outcome of the war, huh?
--Round Five.
--Well then, we'll start the fifth round, the final round.
Now, it's my turn.
Yuuji...
Well, just wait and see.
Yuuji Sakamoto, Class F Rep.
Shouko Kirishima, Class A Rep.
Well then, what subject
would you like to fight in?
Japanese history, restricted test, please.
The test should be elementary school
level and the perfect score is 100 points.
Test match?
Not a battle between their Avatars?!
The Summoner Test War is a war
based on students' test scores, after all.
If a test is used in the battle, as
long as the attending teacher approves,
the reasons and methods are unimportant.
Understood. Then, I'll prepare the test.
Players, please meet me in the classroom.
What're you doing, Yuuji?!
If it's elementary school level, it's
just natural for both of you to get 100%!
That makes it only a tie!
No, that means even one
small mistake can lead to defeat.
Exactly. It'll be a match in attentiveness
and concentration, not academic ability.
Yuuji...
Don't worry. I do stand a chance of winning.
Once Shouko memorizes
something, she never forgets it.
Then you're at disadvantage as a
history battle depends on memorization!
No, that's the trick.
She thinks the year of
the Taika Reform was 625
because she memorized it in
the wrong way. “Re-form in 625.”
What?!
If that event makes it into the test, I can win.
Wait, Yuuji!
Hm?
The Taika Reform wasn’t in 625?!
It’s “re-four-m.” Reform in six four five!
This information is the
real deal. Trust me, Akihisa.
Yuuji...
I'll make Class A's workstations... ours!
Well then, please start.
It's finally started.
Yeah...
What happens if that question isn't in the test?
If Yuuji yields to her in attentiveness
and concentration, he'll probably lose.
But if that question is in the test...
"Q1: Who did Nobunaga Oda join
hands with in the Battle of Nagashino?"
"Q2: Who signed the Treaty of Amity and
Commerce with US Consul General Harris?"
"Q3: In what year did the
Taika Reform take place?"
There it is!
Well then, I'll announce the
results of the restricted test.
Shouko Kirishima, Class A Rep...
"Shouko Kirishima" "Yuuji Sakamoto"
97 points.
All right!
The Class A Rep missed the 100% score!
So this equipment will be ours from today on!
Yoshii!
Yeah!
Next, Yuuji Sakamoto, Class F Rep...
53 points.
Class F's low tables
turned into cardboard boxes.
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
Jugyou owari shifuku no jikan
Tatoeru no nara “Maji de Angel!”
Fui no kokuchi heiwa kowashita
Tsuishi no shirase “Jigoku da!”
Tomodachi tono warai banashi ni
“Iru wake naiyo sonna baka”
Demo hontou wa mune no oku dewa
Sakendetanda “Jibun ga! Sou deshita!”
Chuusha jou de miru “Tsukigime” no koto
Kaisha no namae dato omotteta...
Zutto...
Baka mo tooseba otoko date
Bokura no joushiki hijoushiki?
Ruuru wa muyou sa kono sekai
Yakiniku teishoku gekokujou
Miroyo!
Nishi kara nobotta ohisama ga shizunde iku
Hashire! Mou gohan da
Ouchi ni kaerou! Ouchi ni kaerou!
It's gotten worse! What was that score, Yuuji?!
That's indeed my actual academic ability.
If you can't get 100 points,
your strategy is useless, right?!
I never imagined that such an
unexpected obstacle was lurking.
Don't be your own unexpected obstacle!
Yuuji.
Hm?
Yuuji, the promise...
Promise? That he'll do whatever you tell him?
I know. Tell me what you want me to do.
T-This isn't right, Kirishima!
For a girl to go out with a girl...!
Yuuji... Go out with me.
Huh?
I thought you gave up on that.
I never give up. I'll always like you.
Can I say no?
No, you can't. Since it was a
promise, we're going out on a date now.
What?! Ah, well, wait.
What... was that about?
Well, I don't know.
Then, why was Kirishima looking at Himeji?
Maybe she was concerned
about the girl who was with Yuuji?
Uhm, I'm sorry, Himeji.
Huh?
Our classroom equipment
has gotten worse than before.
No. It's a nice classroom.
What?
I love Class F.
And...
Huh?
Well then... Shall we go have crepes, Aki?
What? Isn't that supposed to be on the weekend?
Weekend is weekend. Today is today.
No way! If you make me treat you twice,
before my parents send me money
again, then my food budget will...!
No. Yoshii'll go see a movie with me.
What?! Himeji, that's news to me!
Right! I decided it just now.
Now, hurry. We'll go have crepes!
What movie are you taking me to?
No way! Nooooo!
My budget is...!
My nutrients are...! Help! Ah, hey!
It's possible that he's a real idiot.
Yeah.
Question 3.
In household expenses,
what do you call the proportion
of income that is spent on food?
I'm having only salt and water this week.
The question is not about
the breakdown of your meals.
Next Episode! "Food Budget,
Dates and Stun Guns."
This will be on the test.