We can't do this.
Sorry. Imanity's finished.
Wh-What do you mean? After that grand entrance?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't expect it to be set in Tokyo.
I can't do anything here.
It's our home, but we're the away team.
We can't help you, so I'm sorry, but please handle this yourselves.
Is this your world, Masters?
We can't do it.
You were incredibly popular.
You were so popular that girls from all over the world chased after you.
But in your heart, there is only one woman you love.
However,
if faced with too many temptations, your love will waver.
Can you make it through all the temptations
and convey your feelings to the one you love?
Living or Dead Series Side Story:
Love or Loved 2: Hit Her With Your Bullet of Love!
Love or Loved 2:
Hit Her With Your Bullet of Love!
Killing Giant
Can you hear me?
Welcome to the world inside the game.
We'll be holding the game inside this fictional field.
Wait.
Yes?
Let me confirm something.
This is a fictional place. It doesn't really exist.
In other words, it's a virtual world you imagined for your game?
That's right. Why?
Don't scare me like that!
Damn it!
That brought all kinds of trauma back to me!
Why are you so upset?
Don't make misleading stuff like that!
Damn you, old man!
Do you have a problem with the level?
Of course I do!
Why the hell would you use this for a level?
Is this psychological warfare?
Are you trying to screw with me?
This is a science fiction level very popular with the youth of the Eastern Federation.
That is the only reason it was chosen, but don't worry.
It's a game, so to an extent, you will be safe.
That explains why I can be out in the sun.
Shiro! Calm down! This isn't Tokyo!
It only looks like it! They just made it up!
That's right. This is a game,
just like Pers*na, or Stein's G*te, or Akiba Str*p!
If we're in a game, we're fine!
Inside a game?
Okay, got it...
All right, we're okay now.
Get started.
Then, everyone, I shall explain the rules.
First, look at the box at your feet.
You'll use those guns to shoot the NPCs who chase you.
We're shooting them?
By shooting them at times,
and exploding them at times,
you will make them fall in love with you.
Isn't that G*l Gun?
The girls who fall in love with you
will give you their love power and disappear.
The ammo fired from the love-love gun is your own love power!
This is called the love-love gun?
Lame.
However, if Izuna shoots one of you, you'll turn into her love slave!
Izuna
Love
Can't you just say, "you'll join her side?"
As girls all over the world turn to look your way,
the one person you love will not!
Conveying your love power to make her fall in love with you is the goal of this game!
That ends the explanation!
So basically, I just have to reject every girl I see?
Who do I think I am?
In other words, Izuna wants the harem ending where all four of us fall for her,
but we're after her only.
That's correct.
One last note: Magic cannot be used in the virtual world, so be careful.
Well?
Do you need a further detailed explanation of the rules?
No, I'll figure them out as I play.
Let's try this.
Firing the love-love gun depletes your love power.
Defeating NPCs restores your love power.
What is going on? This is too creepy!
If an NPC touches you, your love power depletes,
and if it runs out, the NPCs will stop approaching you...
Huh? What's wrong?
But you'll run out of energy to fire your love-love gun,
and become unable to continue combat.
So what happens if you shoot an ally, old man?
You can restore love power to an ally who has run out.
You can also save companions who have been turned into Izuna's love slaves,
but the person who was shot temporarily becomes a love slave of the one—
Master!
Oh, my sister!
I had no idea such a cute, beautiful girl was so close to me this whole time.
My blindness makes me want to gouge out my eyes.
No, Brother, we're sibli—
Jibril!
I love you!
Shiro?
Are you rejecting your brother's love?
So this is the love triangle and NTR stuff I saw in my master's books!
Shiro! My beloved Shiro!
I don't even possess the emotion of love, but somehow it excites me!
Jibril, you'll be punished later.
Oh, forgive me, Lady Shiro!
I see.
When you're a love slave,
I couldn't hold back my curiosity!
you lose all functions and can't control yourself.
I found you!
You all left me on my own again!
That's horribl—
Sora! My prince!
Steph, do you understand the rules so far?
Love doesn't need rules!
Even if I don't know them, our love is eternal!
Of course you don't.
So put this here, and this here...
Oh, my...
My heart is pounding...
Now pull your index finger in.
Huh? What am I—
I'm so beau-ti-ful!
I thought so. It bounces off of things.
I'll never let myself go!
This bouncing ability is the key, Shiro.
I'm so cute!
Leave it to me.
Also, even though we're in a game,
our stamina doesn't change much from real life.
Keep your running to a minimum.
Yeah.
Okay,
let's go, you two!
Looks like it's finally getting started.
Can you see it, Fi?
Yup. Coming in loud and clear.
I'm borrowing your eyes, Kurami.
The Warbeasts must hate this magic.
It's hard to maintain this spell,
but I'm doing it for you, Kurami!
The Warbeasts...
Their physical abilities are said to approach the limits of physics itself.
Let's see how you fight a race like that.
Show me, Sora.
Hey, Izuna.
When's the last time you thought a game was fun?
Damn it!
I knew it!
That's what makes this game special!
Then I can do it!
Target: NPC's cotton panties.
Cotton max thickness: 1 millimeter.
12 o' clock.
Distance: 20050.
Firing angle: 93°.
300 meters per second.
Acceptable targeting error: within 0.5 millimeters.
But I can do it!
Fire!
What?
Damn it!
I failed!
Why?!
I give up on this race.
They're a bunch of morons.
Tell me how you're having fun, please?
If you lose, so many of your people will be unhappy,
so you have to win!
But if you win, your opponent...
Yes! Bra destroyed!
Hand bra for the win!
Of course I've never thought it was fun.
These footsteps...
Is that Shiro?
She's coming this way.
Shiro, you're mine.
I missed!
That's impossible!
What?!
This can't be happening!
I'm sure you're surprised right now, Izuna.
In the genre called FPS, where the best shooters in the world gather,
I'm not the one who holds all the records.
Shiro is.
Futile.
Her terrifying calculation abilities allow her to grasp her enemies' movements,
and her firing intervals and dodges take into account
everything from her understanding of your movement patterns to how fast you can fire,
almost verging on precognition.
It feels like your bullets are passing right through her,
and hers are tracking you like guided missiles, right?
This is insane!
I have to run!
Hi!
Welcome!
It's the Flugel...
Jibril!
A bomb to blind her.
Huh?
Oh, yeah... I can't fly!
Jibril!
I can't dodge it!
Master!
My master, please come back to me!
I see.
She can use her clothes as a shield.
What's going on?
The kings are amazing!
Imanity is winning!
Did you see that, Fi?
Yup. I saw it through your eyes.
Shiro's firing skills are amazing,
but more amazing is...
Yes. I can't believe she was able
to sense and dodge Sora's shot before it was even fired,
when he was so far away and completely silent.
This is...
This is the sixth sense of the Warbeasts, I suppose.
Don't be stupid.
That's not a sixth sense.
That's seeing the future.
Then...
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
A cheat code. They're cheating.
It's a con game!
I see. A cheat you can't prove.
If they say it's a sixth sense, there's nothing you can prove.
So they did know this game.
More than we do.
But...
Izuna!
They're in the corridor below you.
Shiro is exhausted and can't move.
Take them out now!
You don't need to tell me, please.
No matter what little tricks they may have,
there's no way they can win.
So now we're finally on the defensive.
Jeez...
I'm counting on you, Shiro.
We weren't able to finish this during the start,
so now we'll have to wing it.
Wing it?
We're trying to play a fair game against cheaters
who know the game inside and out?
That means...
Your luck just ran out, Sora!
I'm getting you back for all you've done to me, and for Lady Izuna!
You're so mean, Jibril!
Where did you go? You left me!
Bringing her was a mistake.
I won't let you go anymore!
I'm smiling?
And my heart is pounding so loud.
When's the last time you thought a game was fun?
Shut up!
Lady Shiro, what's our next strategy?
Jibril, shut up!
Master, maybe this really is impossible.
Even for Lady Shiro...
No, she can do it.
If there's something I can't do in a game, Shiro can do it.
That's always been true, and it always will be.
Brother...
Do you believe in me?
Has your brother ever doubted you?
Then, Brother...
It's
your turn now, okay?
What?
No—
Shiro!
Shiro?
It's over, isn't it?
I don't understand why Lady Shiro protected you, Master.
Yeah.
I do, so don't worry.
It's not that Shiro couldn't find the answer.
That was the answer.
It was blank.
In other words, us.
Everything, including Shiro joining the enemy's side, is Blank's power.
In other words, it's up to me to
complete the magic formula that will lead us to the promised victory.
That's right, isn't it, Shiro?
Jibril.
Fight Izuna to buy me time.
Th-That's fine, but...
You don't mind if I defeat her,
do you?
I might as well tell you...
That's a death flag, right there.
What?
Then I'll just go defeat her normally.
That makes this easier.
Where did she go?
Hello there, puppy.
I feel I'm experiencing déjà vu.
The last time I challenged the Eastern Federation and lost,
were you my opponent?
Master told me to buy time, but since I'm here...
let's have some fun.
Throw every cheat you've got at me,
and embarrass yourself to your heart's content.
No, damn it!
Going to a different area isn't going to help!
What the hell am I supposed to do, Shiro?
I need to run to the roof...
No, she's planned for that.
Either way, she'll catch up to me soon.
Wait, something's not right.
Why isn't Shiro running after me?
If she were running, she'd have any number of chances to defeat me.
Keep your running to a minimum.
Yeah.
Wasn't I the one who said that?
If I get this wrong, it's going to be rough.
But, well...
Okay, Shiro.
Your brother's just about had it.
This is a rough game for a guy
who never leaves his room.
Your brother can't make a mistake now!
Shiro,
if there's something you would never expect, it's that...
...I wouldn't try to dodge at all, right?
I love you, Brother.
I love you, too.
Now, Izuna!
That took way too long.
This is why you saved your strength and didn't run, right, Shiro?
I love you, Brother.
Impossible...
Sora just shot her. She shouldn't be able to move!
Her panties are gone!
It can't be!
Was it really only her panties that got hit?!
You finally figured it out?
Shiro was never on your side.
She let the shot hit her clothes and pretended to be under my control!
They fooled me!
But that doesn't mean anything.
It'll take more than that!
When's the last time you thought a game was fun?
This is so much fun!
With a loneliness
That no one else could see, I was crying all alone
We could never bring ourselves to smile
But the moment we met, we smiled
In the dead of the night,
we delved into our imagination
And shared all the feelings
we didn't know what to do with
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
We waved goodbye to sadness
And someday
We'll light up our empty hearts
By piecing together the fragments of expressions we find
Our own little world will never end
Like we're praying to the sky
Let's soar high into eternity
Rule Number 10
We're almost there! Give your power to Blank!
Ready!