Your call cannot be connected at the moment.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Uh... Kushieda?
It's about tonight's party...
Ryuuji, you there?
I'll call you back later.
Hey, open your window, Ryuuji!
You have to come no matter what, okay?
It'll definitely be fun! Bye!
Hey, Ryuuji!
You're so slow!
What were you doing?
No, what are you do-
Catch this.
Why did you do that out of the blue?! You're so viole-
Whatever. Just open it.
Huh?
You'll understand when you open it.
I have to get ready, so I'll come over in half an hour.
Later.
Hey!
What's going on? What's going on?
Holy Night Party
Coming!
Oh my god! You look so cute, Taiga-chan!
Ryuu-chan, come over here and check her out!
Okay...
Ryuu-chan, you look amazing.
How nice, it's the perfect size.
I-Is it okay for me to borrow these clothes from you?
You're not borrowing. They're yours now.
Mine?!
The name "R. Aisaka" is sown inside!
This is your father's, isn't it?
He just sort of left it because it didn't fit him, so it's okay.
Just take it.
Wearing his castoffs? Are you messing with me?
If you don't want it, I'll just throw it away.
These sorts of small chores really suit you.
You were the one who told me to take it.
D-D-Destroy the evidence!
How can you say something like that when you can't even say your name?
All right!
Magical Girl Ya-chan will cast some magic on you two!
Magic?
Now don't go too wild.
Once the party starts, this will smell really good mixed in with your scent.
And you, Ryuu-chan...
Here.
This is...
Is this my father's-
Nope.
A long time ago, when I ran away from home,
I took a few valuable things with me.
That means this is my grandfather's.
Correct!
S-S-Stolen goods?
Write down your name and class when you enter!
Hey, you'll a catch a cold like this.
Wow, there are a lot of people.
Just how many are here?
It doesn't matter. There's only one important thing...
There's something you have to do tonight, get it?
Y-Yeah...
Oh! Yuri-chan-sensei, you dressed up!
So the reason you're not coming to the party is because you have a date.
It's not a date.
I'm going to a course for single women about buying real estate.
Huh? Real estate?
Yeah, I'm going to buy an apartment.
Why today of all days?
Well, that's because women who date on Christmas Eve are far from being prepared.
When you find something you want, you have to get it right away!
Heh...
Um...
Anyway, I'll be leaving now. I need to worry about buying an apartment.
Everyone, try and stay out of trouble!
Okay...
Oh, my.
Oh, hello.
Thank goodness the Christmas tree was fixed.
Your grades went up too, so I'm really happy.
Thank you, Miss.
I knew you'd get rewarded for all the effort you put in.
Yeah, and you too, you'll definitely get what you want!
A fantastic single life is waiting for you!
Right, thanks.
Hey, everyone,
I'd like to thank you all for coming out tonight for this party, planned by the God of Broken Hearts!
We went through a lot of trouble,
Hey, Kitamura's clothes...
but regardless, this Christmas party is about to begin.
Stop, we'll lose if you complain.
Everyone, I truly appreciate your cooperation.
I want you all to have a wonderful time tonight!
So...
are you ready?
We're going to celebrate Christmas Eve, so...
Merry Christmas!
Oh! Drumsticks!
I know what this is!
It's called turkey, isn't it?
No, it's just normal chicken.
Did you hear her?
It's good! As expected of homebred turkey!
Yeah...
Nanako, they have cake over there!
You're kidding! Where?
The corner over there. Shall we?
Let's go!
Kihara in hot pants and Nanako-san in an innocent one piece are really hot.
Speaking of which, why is everyone all dressed up?
I look out of place. I mean, poor.
Hey, over there!
Keep your eyes on one place while walking.
The floor will get sticky if syrup spills on it!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Scary...
Takasu.
I was wondering why I didn't see you.
What are you doing here?
Well, I couldn't stand how the drinks were being handled, so...
By the way, I'm surprised you have such an expensive suit!
Wow...
Isn't that chicken grease on your hands?!
Taka-chan, don't you know?
This is called turkey!
Moreover, it's homebred turkey!
Kaoru, you're so slow!
Oh, sorry.
What were you looking at?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, right...
I haven't seen Ami-chan yet! She's here, right?
Y-Yeah, probably.
I think I caught a glimpse of her.
Seriously?! Was she hot?
Was she really hot?!
Is she not here?
And Taiga too...
Taiga, huh?
Well, Taiga isn't bad,
He's right, where did she go?
but I'm all in for Ami-chan.
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no egao
There are smiles everywhere
kimi ni todoketa PARTY NIGHT
Here's a party night from me to you
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no negai
Everyone is making their wish
kimi ni chikaunda
I promise you...
HOLY HOLY NIGHT
...a holy, holy night!
Ami-chan and Taiga?
Woah, amazing!
kotoshi no CHRISTMAS chotto tokubetsu sa
This year's Christmas is a bit special
WHITE CHRISTMAS ja nakudatte
Even though it's not a white Christmas
hoshikuzu no ILLUMINATION
The illumination of the stardust...
When exactly did they practice for this?
hora furitsumoruyo
Look, it's falling and piling up
kirakira kagayaite
It's glittering and shining
minna ga shiawase de
And everyone is happy
chikachika matataite
Flickering, and in a blink
minna ga yume wo mite
Everyone's having a dream
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no egao
There are smiles everywhere
kimi ni todoketa PARTY NIGHT
Here's a party night from me to you
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no negai
Everyone is making their wish
kimi ni chikaunda
I promise you...
HOLY HOLY NIGHT
...a holy, holy night!
From: Santa Claus
Uh... Kushieda?
It's about tonight's party...
Ryuuji, you there?
Hey, open your window, Ryuuji!
I'll call you back later.
You have to come no matter what, okay?
Hey, Ryuuji!
It'll definitely be fun! Bye!
Wow, that was awesome.
Ami-chan and Taiga were both hot, but still cute too!
Here.
Thank you.
Takasu! How long are you planning to stay there?
It was like a dream come true!
Huh? I'm sure it was different than your dreams.
Look, hot, but still cute and such are basically the same thing.
Oh? Then am I...
hot, but still cute?!
You're hot! You're really hot!
H-Hey!
You damn perverted exhibitionist.
Hey, Maruo, what are you doing?
Oh, Kihara! Do you think I'm hot, but still cute?
Huh? Um...
Isn't that sexual harassment?
Revenge!
Give me some fruit punch please.
Oh, okay.
Kawashima!
So you're here.
Yeah, somehow it turned out like this.
Hey, how was my singing?
It was amazing!
When did you practice for it?
If it wasn't kept a secret, it wouldn't be a surprise, would it?
Were you surprised?
Yeah, I was totally caught off guard.
I see, that's good.
By the way, where's Taiga?
I could tell she tried her best,
so I wanted to give her some fruit punch as a reward.
Taiga left already.
You didn't know?
O-Oh...
Seriously? You didn't notice?
She's going to Minori-chan's place.
She said she was going to get Minori to come here and then go home.
It was something about welcoming Santa, I think.
Why is she doing that?
Why is she going home?
I don't know, maybe there's something she'd rather not see.
That's why I gave you some advice.
Advice?
"I think you should stop playing this childish game of house."
"Why do you have to pretend to be daddy?"
Whatever.
Kawashima!
What the heck?
He didn't even listen to me back then.
In order to give everyone a happy and joyful Christmas,
I'm prepared to take off one or two pieces of clothing, or even take it all off.
Is that really all right?
I want to be good.
I want to be part of the happy, glittering scene on Christmas Eve...
while wearing a happy face.
Takasu, can you get me some fruit punch?
I burned too many calories.
Kitamura.
I'm going out for a bit.
Hey, Takasu!
As I thought,
something's wrong!
Is that it?
Kushieda
Really?
Are you sure about that?
Yeah.
Ryuuji is waiting for you to come.
He said he won't leave until he sees you.
He's even prepared to live at school.
I'm sorry, Minorin,
but it's not that you don't like him, right?
I understand. Because we're best friends,
there was no other choice.
Santa isn't here yet.
As I thought, it doesn't work if I'm only good around Christmas.
Actually, there's no Santa.
That's why I'll be alone this year.
I'll also be alone next year,
and forever. I'll never...
I'll never have someone to rely on...
and I'll be all alone.
No one to rely on?
What's that?
It's coming from my bedroom.
S-Santa?
H-Hang in there!
You're heavy!
Are you really Santa?
What is this?!
Hey, come here!
Look, Santa!
That's my Christmas tree!
I knew you'd approve!
Yay!
I knew this would be the best!
Amazing! Amazing!
Santa praised my Christmas tree!
This is real, right?
Wow, my dream...
My dream came true!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Thank you...
very much, Ryuuji.
D-Don't take it off, you idiot!
G-Give it back!
So tell me, where did you get this?
I borrowed it from a guy who was wearing it.
Oh, what did you do with your suit?
Well, I traded it with the guy who was wearing this.
Oh, I'll definitely get it back later.
I will.
You took it off when it was just about to begin.
You're honestly stupid.
Stupid! Stupid!
Even though I planned everything for you...
Even though you had the chance to meet Minorin!
What do you mean by stupid?
Didn't I tell you to believe in Angel Taiga?
Minorin is on her way to the party.
She's probably already there.
Come on, you can still make it if you hurry.
Huh? But...
I've already changed my clothes,
and I don't want to leave you by yourself.
What are you talking about?
I'm fine now.
A fake Santa and faking being good, it was a fun experience!
Oh, and of course, I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
If by some chance things go well with Minorin,
tomorrow's Christmas meal will be on me!
Chicken and rice! Beef and rice!
No, we can't have chicken because of Inko-chan.
Then it'll just be beef and rice.
Come on, hurry up! Get moving!
B-But...
If you're not there at that party, it'll mean I lied to Minorin, right?
Come on!
Hey, I said wai-
Santa came already, so I have to be good until the end of the year!
So just let me be good.
Getting Minorin to go to the party is my real Christmas present for you.
So please...
accept it.
Taiga-
Come on, indecisive dog!
Thanks!
He finally left.
I forgot to give this back to him.
This is so troublesome.
Huh?
Why...
Oh, I see.
I was always relying on Ryuuji.
On his kindness...
But those times have passed.
Minorin will definitely fall for Ryuuji,
and Ryuuji truly likes Minorin.
In other words, they both like each other.
Then I won't be able to...
stay by Ryuuji's side anymore.
I won't be able to walk by his side.
The one beside Ryuuji...
won't be me.
I don't...
want that.
Ryuuji...
Ryuuji!
Ryuuji... Ryuuji...
Ryuuji...
This sucks.
I didn't bring my cell phone,
and my present is still in the pocket of the suit.
What should I do?
It's a great bear, isn't it?
Yo.
Oh, yeah...
K-Kushie-
Takasu-kun.
I'm sorry, but let me speak first.
Do you still remember that?
When we were at A-min's villa during the summer,
we had a talk at night about weird things, right?
It was about UFOs and ghosts...
Y-Yeah.
You know, Takasu-kun.
About UFOs and ghosts, I really think I shouldn't see them.
I think it'd be best to not see them.
I've been thinking about it a lot recently, and this is what I decided.
I wanted to tell you that. That's why I'm here.
Kushieda...
I'm sorry for just saying what I wanted to say.
I'll be leaving first.
Seriously?
Wait, what?
Was I...
rejected?
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no egao
There are smiles everywhere
kimi ni todoketa PARTY NIGHT
Here's a party night from me to you
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no negai
Everyone is making their wish
kimi ni chikaunda
I promise you...
HOLY HOLY NIGHT
...a holy, holy night!
kotoshi no CHRISTMAS kitto tokubetsu sa
This year's Christmas is definitely special
LONELY CHRISTMAS ja tsumaranai
A lonely Christmas is too boring
egao wa ILLUMINATION
The smiles are what illuminate it
hora kazatteageru
Look, I'll decorate it for you
yurayura yurameite
It's swaying and flickering
minna de te wo tsunagi
And everyone is holding hands
pikapika kirameite
Sparkling and twinkling
minna de hoshi miage
Everyone's looking up at the stars
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no egao
There are smiles everywhere
kimi ni todoketa PARTY NIGHT
Here's a party night from me to you
saa CHRISTMAS
Now it's Christmas!
ippai no negai
Everyone is making their wish
kimi ni chikaunda
I promise you...
HOLY HOLY
...a holy, holy...
NIGHT
...night!
Next Episode Preview
Always, like this
I was rejected by Kushieda.
Whenever I close my eyes, I-
Takasu-kun, you're dreaming!
I'm already hearing her usual cheerful voice.
All right, boom!