I'm Tomoe Mami.
I'm a senior at your school,
Mitakihara Junior High.
And I'm a magical girl who formed a contract with Kyubey.
Another weird dream...
Good morning, Madoka!
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 2
I think that'd be really nice
Madoka, I heard you came home late last night.
An upperclassman from school
invited me to her house.
I'm not going to be an annoying mom
and impose a curfew and stuff,
but make sure you call home before dinner.
I'm sorry.
I guess no one else can see him.
What a beautiful room!
Wow...
I live alone, so make yourselves at home.
Though I admit you've caught me unprepared.
Mami-san, this is delicious!
It really is!
Thank you.
Since you've been chosen by Kyubey, that means you two are now involved in this.
I think we should get you
up to speed with things.
You bet!
Ask us anything at all.
Sayaka-chan, you have that backwards.
Wow, that's pretty!
This is a Soul Gem.
When Kyubey forms a contract with a girl, a Soul Gem is born.
This is what identifies us as magical girls, and the source of our power.
What do you mean by a contract?
I can grant each of you one wish.
Wait, really?
What kind of wish?
Anything you want.
I can fulfill any miracle you wish for.
So it could be gold, silver,
priceless treasures, immortality...
Maybe even a feast fit for a Chinese emperor!
I'm not too sure about that last one...
In exchange for that wish,
a Soul Gem is produced.
Those who receive one are given the responsibility of fighting witches.
Witches?
Hey, Mom.
Hm?
What if... What if someone offered to grant you any wish you wanted with magic...
What would you do—?
I'd get rid of a board member or two.
The president is also getting a bit too old for this,
so maybe I would wish for him to retire...
But he hasn't even named a successor yet...
What if you became president then, Mom?
I didn't think about that.
I'll have to work things out
with the Sales Department first.
Planning and Administration
are already my puppets.
The only problem left
is the baldy in Accounting.
I'll just pull off his toupée.
Mom, you look scary.
What's a witch?
Are they different from magical girls?
If magical girls are born from wishes,
then witches are born from curses.
Magical girls spread hope,
whereas witches spread despair.
And to make matters worse, they can't be seen by normal humans.
Doubt and suspicion, irrational rage and hatred...
They sow the seeds of catastrophe in this world.
Many inexplicable suicides and murders that occur are caused by a witch's curse.
It's a formless evil that eats away at humans from the inside.
If they're so dangerous, then how come no one knows about them?
Because witches hide within barriers
and never show themselves to people.
The labyrinth-like area you wandered into before was one.
They're pretty dangerous, actually.
Those who are swallowed up by the barriers don't usually live to tell the tale.
Mami-san, are you really fighting something that dangerous?
Yes.
Sometimes my life is in danger too.
That's why I think you two should weigh your options carefully.
Now that you've been chosen by Kyubey, you can have any wish granted.
However, doing so could lead to your death.
That's a tough decision.
To help you make up your minds,
why don't you come along
with me on a witch hunt?
Huh?
That way you can see what
it's like to fight a witch.
And afterwards, you should take the time and think about
whether having your wish
come true is worth your life.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good mor—
Good morning, Sayaka.
Is something wrong, Sayaka-san?
So we're really the only ones who can see him?
Looks like it.
Um...
Don't worry about it.
Let's go.
Looks like we can also talk to each other telepathically.
Wait, so we already have magical powers?!
No, no. I'm just using myself
to relay your thoughts.
It's pretty convenient though, isn't it?
It feels a bit strange.
Hey, what's going on with you two?
You keep staring into each other's eyes.
N-No, we've been... Um...
No, don't say it!
Are you two already close enough to
communicate through your eyes alone?!
I can't believe you've become so close
to each other after just one day.
What on Earth happened yesterday?
No, uh... you've got it all wrong.
A lot did happen last night, though.
You can't! You're both girls!
It's a love that can never be!
You forgot your bag!
Hitomi-chan's acting a bit like you today.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Is it okay for you to come with us to school like nothing's happened?
Why wouldn't it be?
I told you that the girl from yesterday transferred into this class, right?
Wasn't she trying to kill you?
I actually think the school
is the safest place for me.
Mami's here too.
Mami's a senior, so her
class is kind of far from here.
Don't worry.
I can hear everything you're saying.
Even at this distance, we can still communicate with her.
U-Uh... good morning.
I'll keep a close eye on you all, so don't worry.
Besides, I'm pretty sure she wouldn't attack any of you in public.
I hope you're right.
Damn. Speak of the devil.
So is that transfer student also an, uh... what was it? Magical girl?
Just like you, Mami-san?
Yes, she is.
She seems quite powerful too.
Wouldn't that make her one of the good guys fighting evil witches?
Why did she suddenly attack Madoka, then?
She was after me.
I imagine she was trying to stop
the creation of new magical girls.
Huh?
Why? Wouldn't it be better to have
more people fighting the same enemy?
That's not necessarily the case.
It's actually more common for us to compete with each other.
Really? Why?
There are rewards for eliminating a witch.
So, in some cases, it turns into a contest,
and magical girls may even fight over them.
So basically, she predicted that
Kyubey would try to talk to Madoka,
and that's why she's been pestering
Madoka since this morning?
That's most likely the case.
Don't worry, Madoka.
If she tries to do anything,
I'll punch her lights out!
We've even got Mami-san here.
That's right.
Miki-san's ability to protect you aside,
I'm with you, so everything will be fine.
Don't worry.
Don't put me aside!
So, as we've learned thus far,
a phrase is in the "active voice" when the subject—a person or thing—performs the action.
In contrast, a phrase is in the "passive voice" when the subject receives the action.
Passive voice is formed by an auxiliary verb with the participle of a transitive verb.
For instance, if I were to say, "He likes me," or "kare wa watashi no koto ga suki"—
Here you go.
Hey, Madoka.
Have you come up with a wish yet?
Nope. What about you?
Me neither.
I kind of thought a whole bunch
of things would pop into my mind...
I mean, there are a bunch of
things I want to have and do,
but when risking our lives
is the catch... you know?
I don't think anything I
want is worth that risk.
Yeah.
That's surprising.
Most girls answer immediately.
I guess we're just idiots.
Huh? You really think so?
Yep. Blissfully ignorant idiots.
Having a wish you'd trade your life
for shouldn't be all that uncommon.
I'm sure a lot of people in
the world have a wish like that.
So if we can't think of anything,
then it must mean we haven't
faced much misfortune.
Living such a sheltered life
has made us ignorant.
But why us... of all people?
Don't you think it's unfair?
I'm sure there are other people who'd
give anything for a chance like this.
Sayaka-chan...
Don't worry.
Picking up where you left off yesterday?
No, that's not my intention.
I had hoped to settle things before he made contact with Kaname Madoka,
but it's too late for that now.
So what will you do?
Have you two decided to
become magical girls as well?
I...
That's none of your business!
Do you remember what I told you yesterday?
Yeah...
That's fine, then.
I pray that my warning won't fall on deaf ears.
Ho... Homura-chan!
What... wish did you make
to become a magical girl?
Sorry, Hitomi.
We have a few things to do today.
Oh, something secret?
We...
I'm so jealous!
No one can come between
you two anymore, can they?
Uh, you're really misunderstanding us...
Akemi-san, wanna come to a café with us?
I have something I need to
take care of again today.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's begin our first lesson on the magical girl experience.
Are you two ready?
I'm not sure if it'll help, but I brought this!
I thought it'd be better than nothing.
Well, it's good to see you're
mentally prepared to fight.
Madoka, did you bring anything?
Huh? Oh, I have this...
Wow...
I-I figured I might as well
think about the costume.
You're enthusiastic, that's for sure.
That's great.
I can't top that.
It's reacting to the remnants of the magic used by that witch we faced yesterday.
Searching for witches basically involves a lot of walking.
All you do is follow the Soul Gem as it traces the witch's presence.
That's pretty lame.
The light hasn't changed at all.
It's been a whole day since it escaped.
There's very little left to track.
What if you had gone after it yesterday?
I might have been able to defeat it,
but it wasn't worth leaving you two behind.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Mami-san's one of the good guys!
On the other hand, that transfer
student really gets on my nerves!
I wonder if she's really that bad.
Hey, Mami-san. Do you have any idea of where the witch might be?
Witches' curses tend to cause traffic accidents and assaults.
So I prioritize major highways and entertainment districts where accidents and brawls are likely,
as well as desolate places
that are perfect for suicides.
The worst case scenario is when they haunt places like hospitals.
It's not a pretty sight when they drain
the life out of those in a weakened state.
It's reacting to some very powerful magic.
It must be close.
It has to be here!
Mami-san, look!
A witch's kiss.
I knew it.
Is she...
It's okay.
She's just unconscious.
Let's go.
You're not getting away today!
Wow.
It's nothing special, but at the very least it'll help protect you.
Make sure you stay by my side, okay?
Okay!
Stay away! Stay away!
So, are you two scared?
Th-This is nothing!
I'm scared, but...
Keep it up!
We're almost at the barrier's core!
Gertrud
Look, that's a witch.
Disgusting...
Are you going to fight that?
It's okay.
I won't lose.
Stay back.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
Mami-san!
Don't worry.
I can't just embarrass myself in front of my future protégés.
Close, but no cigar.
Tiro Finale!
She won?
Wow.
This is a Grief Seed.
It's a witch's egg.
E-Egg?
If you're lucky, sometimes
a witch will have one.
Don't worry.
It's safe in that form.
Actually, it's extremely useful.
My Soul Gem is a bit darker
than it was last night, right?
Oh. Yeah, it is.
However, by using a Grief Seed...
Take a look.
It's all clean.
See?
Now the magic I've depleted
has been replenished.
This is one of the rewards I mentioned earlier.
You should be able to use it one more time.
You can have it,
Akemi Homura-san.
It's her.
Or do you not like to share?
It was your prey.
You should keep it for yourself.
I see. So that's your answer.
That antisocial bitch!
I wish we could all just get along.
If only everyone felt that same way.
Where am I?
Wait, what was I doing?
Wh-Why was I...
Why did I do that?
It's okay. Everything's okay now.
You were just having a bad dream.
Looks like our hero saved the day.
Yeah.
It's too hard for me to come up
with a wish on such short notice,
but the sight of Mami-san pouring her
heart into saving others was really amazing.
If someone like me can really help other people,
I think that'd be really nice.
"sore ja mata ne" tte te wo futte
「それじゃ またね」って手を振って
I waved my hand, saying, "I'll see you next time"
muri ni waratte samishiku natte
無理に笑って さみしくなって…
I forced a smile, then I was lonely...
kousaten shingou
交差点 信号
Traffic lights at the intersection...
tooku no kurakushon
遠くのクラクション
The distant sound of a car honking...
shiranai dareka no waraiau koe
知らない誰かの笑い合う声
The voices of strangers laughing
kyou wa hitori de aruku
今日はひとりで歩く
Today, I walk alone
kayoinareta machi demo
通い慣れた街でも
Even though I'm used to the city,
itsumo yorimo nandaka
いつもよりもなんだか
I feel just a little smaller
jibun ga chotto chiisaku omoeru yo
自分がちょっと小さく思えるよ
than my usual self
"sore ja mata ne" tte te wo futte
「それじゃ またね」って手を振って
I wave my hand, saying, "I'll see you next time"
egao tsukutte samishiku natte
笑顔作って さみしくなって
I made a smile, then I was lonely...
honto wa mada hanashitarinai kedo
ホントはまだ話し足りないけど
Even though I want to talk even more with you...
"sore ja mata ne" tte kotoba tte
「それじゃ またね」って言葉って
Saying, "I'll see you next time,"
mata aeru tte uso wo tsuite
また会えるって嘘をついて…
Lying about seeing each other again
itsumo toori no egao de iu yo
いつも通りの笑顔で言うよ
I say, with my usual smile,
"mata ashita"
「また あした」
"See you tomorrow."
Illustrated by  Hekiru Hikawa
I'm just acting cool,
but I have no one to talk
with when I'm scared or sad...
I'm forced to cry all alone.
Being a magical girl
really isn't that great.
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
Episode 3
I'm not scared of anything anymore