NEXT Emergence
"Jazz Club - King"
Thanks for coming today, guys.
That was some great singing.
Yeah! It really moved me!
You're definitely going to be a huge star!
Yeah, no doubt about it!
Hey, guys!
Whadya say? I’m feeling a bit peckish.
Wanna go drinking?
Aww, they're leaving?
They're all pretty busy.
Bah. They're no fun.
You can come visit my place if you want.
Huh? Your home?
There's no sake, but you
can at least get something to eat.
Is it really okay for me
to suddenly visit, though?!
Quit tryin' to be polite. It doesn't suit you.
In that case...!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon, Ryuga
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
"Scam invited me to his house.
It isn't much, but it still makes me happy."
Turtle was so happy
that he was embarrassed.
I'm his younger brother, Kazuo.
I'm his younger brother, Tatsuo.
T-Twins? And they look just like Scam...
Come on in. It's a small house,
but please make yourself at home.
O-Okay.
This Maeda kid's really something!
He's smart and he has a real job, at his age!
Really? What sort of work is it?
Oh, it's, uhh... import business-related...
Oh, I see!
It was a real shock for Ryuji to bring a friend home, though.
This is the very first time!
Oh, really?
Feel free to visit us anytime, Maeda.
Okay!
Sorry, I didn't mean for
her to make so much food...
Don't worry about it.
But, why did you invite me?
She said it was the first time
you ever had a friend over.
You saw it yourself-- our mom
has to support us all by herself
"Kimono, Futon Repair"
and my brothers are still in
their first year of high school...
Basically, we're dirt-poor.
But I figured you wouldn't make fun of me--
Don't be stupid!
What's there to be embarrassed about?!
You have a great family!
You think so?
You need to hurry and get through college
so you can put your mom at ease!
I know.
I'm actually thinking of studying law...
Law? You're gonna be a lawyer?
I haven't decided on anything yet.
It's just, if anything happens to you guys,
I'll be able to help you out.
Try your hardest. For your family, too.
Well, I better go.
Anyway, Turtle...
There are reference books I need,
but they're really expensive and
I can't ask my mom to buy them...
How much?
This is all I have right now... It is enough?
Th-Thanks...
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
You can pay me back
when you're out of college.
I won't even charge interest,
because of that great meal today.
I really appreciate it!
Never mind that, just hurry
home and hit the books!
Turtle!
Come visit again!
You're welcome at our home anytime!
Yeah! I will sometime!
Having a rice bowl handed
to him as if he belonged there
filled Turtle, an atomic bomb
orphan, with a warm feeling.
"Poor or not, it's nice having a family..."
Hello!
Oh, Maeda!
Is Sca-- I mean, Ryuji here?
Huh? He isn't with you?
He left early this morning, saying
he was going to help you with work...
O-Oh, right! I guess we mixed
up where we were gonna meet!
Oh, yeah.
This is for you.
Oh, but this looks so expensive...
Don't worry about it, it's a gift.
It's my thanks for yesterday!
That idiot!
What is he up to,
lying to his mom like that?!
"Red Crane"
Hey, Ryu.
Can you really afford
to come here so often?
It's no problem!
I can get all the money I want!
Anyway, have you given
any thought to my proposition?
I can't, Ryu...
The only way I can be
free is too work off my debts...
I'm serious here
I want you, Eri! I want to be with you!
Thank you.
That makes me happy,
even if you don't mean it.
I do mean it! I'm serious!
I'm serious about how I feel about you...!
How much more do you owe?
Much more than a student
can do anything about.
Still...!
My father's business went under,
and he disappeared...
Until then, the four of us
had lived as a happy family.
We weren't burdened in any way.
I even had mediocre dreams
of finding a nice man someday,
getting married, and having kids.
Eri...
But I don't want my little sister
to have to go through this!
That's why I have to...
I'm helping my sister get through college!
I have to work hard, so I can pay off
our debts and she can get married...
Huh? Why am I talking about this?
Eri...
It must be because
you're such a nice person, Ryu...
Listen, Ryu...
You need to become
a responsible grownup.
So... you shouldn't come
to places like this anymore...
"I don't care if she's a prostitute or not.
I'll do anything for Eri.
I'd rather lose my friends
and family than lose her!"
Drunk with love, Scam was blind to all else...
What's going on? Am I just really tired?
Umm, Maeda?
Oh, hey! You're Scam's brothers!
What's up?
On your way home from school?
Don't take too long getting home now!
Did something happen?
Umm...
--Are you the one...
--...lending our brother money?
Sorry for suddenly asking
you here like this, Scam.
No, it's fine. I actually
needed to see you, anyway.
Need some more reference books, huh?
Your brothers told me...
They said you've fallen for that prostitute.
And that you've been
swiping the family's money.
Does... my mom know, too?
No, I doubt it.
Your brothers came to me
because they had no one else to turn to.
You'd never experienced
girls until just recently,
so I can't blame you
for falling head over heels.
But there are lots
of for-hire girls out there.
I can introduce you to some new ones.
It isn't like that...
It isn't like that!
I'm sorry if I offended you.
But you have
to stop worrying your family!
What would you know?
You don't have a family or a woman...
What would you know?!
Scam...
Don't get a big head and
act like you know everything!
You're a nuisance! Mind your own business!
Don't ever tell me what to do again!
I should get going.
Oh.
The money I lent you... You can keep it.
I'm sorry for butting into your business.
I guess I was wrong about you.
I always thought we were friends.
Hey Turtle.
You've been down in the dumps lately.
Did something happen?
It's nothin'...
Oh, come on in!
Oh, Turtle!
What's the matter?
Beats me. He's been like that lately.
That reminds me,
I ran into Scam the other day.
Oh, yeah? How's he doing?
He said he wants to study law.
He's gonna be a lawyer or something.
Really?! That's great!
For now, he's focusing
on getting into college.
So... how much did you lend him?
Huh? How did you know about that?
I figured as much...
Hey, what does that mean?
I'm outta here.
Hold on, Turtle. Not so fast.
Out with it. What are you talking about?
I can't believe it...
The Scam we know so well, devoted to a prostitute...
Don't tell anyone else about this.
We especially don't want
Scam's mom to find out about this.
Yeah...
Come again!
Oh, it's you.
You must really have a thing for Eri.
She's our main attraction here;
don't go giving her any strange ideas.
Ryu...
I told you you shouldn't come here anymore...
This'll be the last time, all right?
Eri...!
I love you, Eri!
I want you!
Run away with me! Leave this place!
That's crazy, Ryu.
There's no way I can run away...
I'll do whatever it takes to help you, Eri!
I'll protect you with my life! So, please...!
Eri!
All right.
2:00 next Tuesday, inside Senso Temple.
I'm allowed to leave that day because
I have routine medical checkup.
Burning with his very first love,
Scam thought, with no suspicion
whatsoever, "We love each other!"
Gains, losses, the future, friends...
He was blind to it all.
His mother, brother, and everything
appeared as a fleeting heat mirage.
Eri was all there was...
Please, Mario! I beg you!
Lend me money with no questions asked!
2000 yen!
No, even 1000 will do! Please!
I'm sorry, Scam.
I'm out of cash right now...
All right.
Sorry to bother you.
Hey.
Soldier...
Let's take a walk.
What the hell... are you doing... ?!
Y'know, Scam...
That Eri girl you're in love with...
She's one hell of a woman.
I made love to her at that whorehouse earlier.
Soldier... What did you just say...?
Sure, I'll say it as much as you want.
I had sex with that Eri girl!
Come to your sense, Scam!
Your girl is nothing but
a piece of merchandise!
Are you good-looking
enough for her to love you?!
Are you an important enough of a
person for her to really love you back?!
Soldier! What are you doing?!
If we don't open his eyes now,
his life will become a living hell...
So what...
...if Eri...
...is a piece of merchandise...?!
Of course she is!
That's the line of work she's in...
As long as they have money,
anyone can sleep with her.
But, so what, Soldier...?
So what if Eri is a prostitute?!
Eri and I are running away!
I'll do whatever it takes to help her!
If you guys are gonna try and
stop me, I'll kill you if I have to...!
Do you understand what you're saying!
You do know what'll happen
if they catch you, don't you?!
Yeah... I know...
This guy's the biggest dumbass in all of Japan...
"You can't really love someone
without being ready to risk your life!
And I love Eri!"
No one can laugh at Scam's
feelings and call them foolish.
Scam-- now risking his life-- was
changed into a man by his first love.
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
He risks his life for love.
His friends quietly see him off.
Scam abandons all and goes to Eri...