Now, we're going to raise Kaleido Star's curtain.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
you should keep your room brightly lit
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I've finally realized what
I forgot to take care of.
The reason my heart is
pounding and I can't slow it down...
Right now I'm not her senior in
the troupe, nor am I her partner.
I stand before her as a rival.
I've come back.
Give me your best shot, Sora.
My name is Layla.
Layla Hamilton, the Golden Phoenix.
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
The contest is on, Sora.
If you don't like it, step down from your role.
You said you'd practice more up until opening
day and aim to be a true Kaleido Star, correct?
If you can become one
of those just by practicing,
I won't give up.
I entrusted that dream to you because
I thought you had something that I didn't.
You still hadn't figured that out?
I've mastered the Angel's Maneuver too,
in order to do battle with you.
I trust you'll consider me a worthy opponent.
If you still decline the challenge,
you're nothing but a loser.
If you have any intent of
becoming a true Kaleido Star,
then surpass me, Sora.
Battle Miss Layla for a role?
My blood is starting to race
just thinking about it. Why?
I can't hold back the desire to challenge her.
I like the look in your eyes.
I take it you're up for the fight.
Yes!
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
"A Most Amazing and Inescapable Showdown."
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Don't you find this strange?
Huh? What do you mean?
One, two, three. One, two...
Nobody's talking about tomorrow.
Everyone's business as usual.
It's like they don't care
which one gets the lead.
Maybe they really want both of them to be.
So right now,
nobody's got any choice but to
do what they need to be doing.
No matter who ends up being the lead,
now that you've decided to do this,
give your own role all you've got!
You don't need to tell me that...
I know it'll be hard to do with
the time and budget we have, but...
This is it! It definitely has to be this!
The decision is yours.
If we're going to do it, I'll start work right away,
even if it's just tearing down the current set.
All right, let's do it.
All right! Sweet!
If you're going to do it, make it brilliant.
Sure. Leave it to me.
In order to make my debut as a clown,
I absolutely must master this...
How many times has it been?
About a thousand?
She's really staking
everything on this show, isn't she?
Miss Anna!
Dammit!
Please, stop this!
You'll die, Miss Anna!
I feel like I'll get the hang of it soon.
I think we can stop here.
Now get plenty of rest.
Right!
I thought you'd refuse her,
saying you didn't want to fight.
I am contradictory, aren't I...
But I can't hold back my feelings.
Miss Layla is the one who taught me
both the fun and the harshness of the stage.
She was always far ahead of me,
and she became a goal for me to strive for.
And now she's come
back to the stage as my rival.
For Miss Layla, who left the Kaleido
Stage because of a shoulder injury,
it must have been so painful
to master the Angel's Maneuver...
And so I want to go up
against her with all I've got.
Miss Layla is special to me!
Being able to meet Layla was your
greatest stroke of fortune, wasn't it.
Yes.
Neither Sophie nor I had such good luck.
But I was the one who tied Sophie down
and let all her possibilities go to waste.
In order to atone for that,
I continued to go out onto the stage
and I destroyed partner after partner
in order to find a true star.
I've committed so many wrongs.
If a true star is realized,
I may at least be allowed to die.
Mr. Leon!
Leo turns its fangs on Sagittarius,
its brightness increased to
almost ferocious brilliance.
Did you come all the way here
because you were worried about Sora?
Both constellations shine intensely.
Their fate is that if they collide,
one of them must disappear.
I thought I was a constellation
that had already disappeared.
But at that moment...
Ever since the moment
I realized I could still see you,
I pondered what it meant.
I did think that the role left to
me might be to guide Sora on,
yet in the end my actions
only caused Sora to take a detour.
But watching Sora regain
her brilliance, I realized...
I still haven't been allowed
to step down from this stage.
So I'll just return once more.
Like May, who made her comeback
even after Leon wrecked her shoulder,
I'll become a demon.
However, this demon may end
up destroying the true Kaleido Star.
We'll find that out tomorrow.
It's a beautiful day.
I haven't been this excited in a long time!
I'm on fire.
It's strange...
It's still a battle,
but there's none of that
pain there was at the Festival.
It's the opposite. I'm happy that I can fight!
Surpass me, Sora.
With all I've got, so there's no regrets.
But Mr. Leon is...
We have an important audition today.
Please take care not to get in the way of that.
Now, eat!
Um, but Chinese for breakfast is so...
Eat this, power up, go at
her head-on and be crushed!
Be crushed?!
I don't want you losing too pathetically.
Losing...
I'm looking forward to it.
Not just seeing Miss Layla's Angel's Maneuver,
but your Angel's Maneuver too.
May!
Now hurry up and eat already!
It's bitter...
Come on, eat this too!
And this next!
Spicy!
And this!
Hot!
And then this!
It smells...
The Angel's Maneuver is
said to require innate instinct;
I'm impressed you mastered
it to this degree of perfection.
If I couldn't do that, this
contest would be meaningless.
I wonder when it was...
What?
I've felt this feeling before.
Maybe it was the first time
I stood on the Kaleido Stage.
Or maybe it was my first
audition for a lead role...
Maybe the first time you
pulled off the Golden Phoenix.
I feel like those feelings
were all different than this.
But my heart is dancing so much at
the thought of today's performance!
Not long now, huh?
Yeah.
I wonder if the "true Kaleido Star"
you dreamed of will be born.
Nobody knows that.
Kalos.
What?
Your socks.
I love that about you.
Let's go.
This is thrilling. What do you think?
Does it look like Sora will fulfill our dreams?
I have high hopes for her.
Then I'll set very high hopes for her too.
There's a door that only those
who have kept on dreaming can open.
Yes.
Scene 32. The angel's flight.
It's finally time.
Yes.
Mr. Leon.
What?
I think Miss Sophie was happy.
You treasured her above everything else.
I think Miss Sophie must
have felt that way about you too.
I think maybe having someone you
can feel that way about is happiness.
If I were Miss Sophie,
I don't think I would want
you to suffer trying to atone.
If the stage is nothing
but pain for you, Mr. Leon,
you shouldn't go out onto it.
I'll do this audition myself.
If you're going onstage,
do it for your own sake.
For my own sake?
Let's go out there together
and get the best kind of applause.
With a real Angel's Maneuver.
The best kind of applause, with you...
I'd like to hear that.
It's about to start.
Yes.
If I keep going straight down,
I think I'll hit trapeze A-2.
I can tell.
If I keep going straight
down, I'll hit trapeze A-5.
Good.
They're both perfect.
On a technical level they're equal.
Yes.
But Sora's Odette is lively and vigorous.
Miss Layla kind of projects an air of innocence.
That's Layla for you!
To think after all this time, she's
still showing us a new side of her!
I can't tell how this battle will play out.
They're both great, aren't they?
There's a huge amount of tension in the air.
It feels like I'll start
having trouble breathing.
Good for you, Sora, coming this far.
Now clear your own path on your own power.
You're the first rival I've been able
to compete with on an equal level.
I can feel your burning
enthusiasm all through my body.
Back then, I never dreamed
a day like this would come.
The first time I saw you perform,
I was actually angry, but...
Someday, the audience
will come here just to see her.
Kalos, it's just like you foresaw.
No, actually, she probably overcame each
ordeal with more strength than you'd imagined.
Then she became my partner,
and now she's here as my rival.
Sora...
I want to win against you.
When Miss Layla's onstage, the air crackles.
Her true drive to utterly defeat me
makes me even more fired up.
If I lose my focus even a tiny bit, I'll lose.
My Angel's Maneuver
awakens everyone's angel hearts.
I have to perform my Angel's Maneuver!
Hey, I know, why don't
I try performing more freely?
I'm going to put a little ad-lib in.
Got it.
Sora's performance has changed.
The Angel's Maneuver is sure to
awaken everyone's angel hearts.
My angel heart...
The people who gave me an angel heart,
my four parents...
And Yume.
Everyone must have people
who are important to them.
Maybe our angel hearts are treasures
given to us by the people important to us.
Sora is adding ad-lib to her performance.
Interesting.
Layla is seriously trying to beat Sora.
She may be doing the Angel's Maneuver,
but that relentlessness is like a demon's.
The demon that raises an angel...
That was Layla all along?
The you who wants Sora to surpass you,
and the you who wants to win against Sora...
Which one of them is the real you?
Or are they both the real you?
What a tranquil performance...
I can hardly believe you're vying for a role.
This feeling is...
Both the stage and the
audience are wreathed in smiles.
You want to be on that
kind of stage too, right Leon?
I wonder why it is...
The atmosphere is the audience
is quickly becoming tranquil.
What in the world has happened?
Wait, isn't there something
strange about Layla's angel?
I wonder why it is...
Huh?
I just remembered my grandma.
When I was little, I used to write all kinds of
stories for my grandma and tell them to her.
I remembered how she used to smile
those times, like she was having fun.
Actually, I was remembering
the first picture book I ever wrote.
It was crap, but I remember
I gave it to a sick friend...
I wonder why it is...
I just remembered my first diabolo show.
I screwed up a little,
but someone in the first row of the audience
clapped for me and shouted "Amazing!"
I remembered telling gags for my mother
when she cried, trying to make her laugh.
She didn't think they were funny,
but I got her to smile again...
The first time I asked my
mom to teach me the trampoline,
she looked happy...
Why am I remembering this? It's got
nothing to do with skating or Kaleido Stage.
I remember teaching my little
brothers pro wrestling moves...
May Wong Devil Headhang!
After I started skating lessons,
I guess I didn't play with them much anymore...
This room is so warm.
The fervor of the audience
has completely vanished.
Is it because of Sora?
What?
I've felt this feeling before.
I remember.
It was then.
The day I made my busy mother
and father rearrange their schedules,
when I came to the
Kaleido Stage for the first time.
I was excited about what was about to happen.
That's the feeling of an audience member.
On the way here I was already
looking forward to Sora's performance.
I want to see Sora's angel.
An angel...
It looks like this battle
has been settled, Layla.
Yes, Mr. Kenneth.
Huh?
Sora.
Yes?!
They say a true prima turns
even her co-stars into spectators.
While I was competing with you,
before I knew it I found myself your audience.
I couldn't hold back my desire
to see your Angel's Maneuver.
You've finally surpassed me, haven't you?
I'm happy, Sora.
Miss Layla!
Sora, you just arrived at the
gates of true Kaleido Stardom.
From now on, many novices will come here,
drawn by their admiration of you.
When that happens, what you have
to do is take your challengers head-on
and become a wall for them to overcome.
And when the time comes,
you must fight with all
your strength and be defeated.
That was what I came to do today,
what I forgot to do before I left here.
I ended up leaving the stage
without being defeated by you.
That hindered your independence.
Sora...
Giving your challengers a battle will be
another important duty of yours from now on.
Don't forget that.
All right.
Congratulations, Sora.
Thank you.
The results of the audition have been decided.
In the days left until opening day,
all of you give everything you've got!
Yes, sir!
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
Until your wish comes true
someday, you're not alone.
I really cried a lot.
I really laughed a lot.
I was really frustrated.
I was really happy.
We're really feeling lots of gratitude
as we send you the next episode,
a success story of those in the bloom of youth!
The final episode of Kaleido Star:
"To the Amazing Promised Place."
My wings are my dream...
Everyone together now!
And on towards the sky!