THE OBSESSIVE SCIENTIST
Long ago,
there lived a brilliant young scientist.
By virtue of his astonishing genius,
he made many contributions
to human knowledge.
However, he eventually became disillusioned with the world.
Though constantly showered with praise
for the brilliance of his mind,
Professor Genus Ba
nished fro
m Scientific Society
Deranged Gene Experiments...
none of his ideas or theories ever received
any support from the scientific community.
"We should strive not to advance civilization,
but to drive forward the evolution of the human species."
That was his lifelong dream,
but not a single person
came forward to help him fulfill it.
Damn these apes!
"Dangerous ideas"? How dare they
write about me as if I were some freak!
Do they really think humans have come this far by avoiding risks?
Idiots who think they no longer need to evolve
have no right to pass on their genes!
Of course, this plan was always for my own sake.
Even if I must do it alone, I will do it!
Thereafter, he devoted himself to his research.
It was only after he turned 70 that his efforts began to yield results.
First, the scientist regained his youth.
Next, he began cloning himself.
He named his laboratory the House of Evolution,
and together with his clones,
he conducted countless experiments with animals to create new species.
Eventually, his experiments shifted to human subjects—
This is taking too long!
Huh?
What's this got to do with me?
You're just trying to act cool again.
Just get to the point, okay?
My master is a busy man.
Summarize it in 20 words or less.
I-I'm sorry.
ONE PUNCH
THREE, TWO, ONE, KILL SHOT
JOIN THE FIGHT, CERTAIN VICTORY, THE STRONGEST EVER
SANJOU, HISSHOU, SHIJOU SAIKYOU
WHAT WAS THAT? FRUSTRATION
NAN DATTEN DA? FRUSTRATION
THERE'S NO STOPPING ME
ORE WA TOMARANAI
ONE PUNCH, IT'S OVER, VICTORY AFTER VICTORY
ONE PUNCH, KANRYOU, RENSENRENSHOU
I WIN, I ALWAYS WIN, OVERWHELMINGLY
ORE WA KATSU, TSUNE NI KATSU, ASSHOU
POWER, GET POWER
RIGHT TO THE VERY LIMIT
GIRIGIRI GENKAI MADE
HERO
PEOPLE SHOWER ME WITH PRAISE
ORE O TATAERU KOE YA
BUT I DON'T DO THIS FOR THE FAME
KASSAI NANTE HOSHIKU WA NAI SA
HERO
SO I JUST FIGHT EVIL IN SECRET
DAKARA HITOSHIREZU AKU TO TATAKAU
(NOBODY KNOWS WHO HE IS)
COUNTLESS ENEMIES FILL THE SKY
SORA OOI OSHIYOSERU TEKI
BUT I WON'T TURN MY BACK AND FLEE
ORE WA SE WO MUKE WA SHINAI
HERO
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND AND I WON'T GIVE IN
NARABA YURUGINAKI KAKUGO SHITA TAME
A FIGHTING HERO
TATAKAU HERO
A SOLITARY HERO
KODOKU NA HERO
I WANNA BE THE STRONGEST HERO
I WANNA BE A SAIKYOU HERO
So, in other words,
my boss has developed
a keen interest in your body.
Too bad, I don't swing that way.
I think you misunderstood, Master.
He plans to use your body,
which surpasses human limitations,
to further his research on evolution.
If we don't do something,
I'm sure he'll try attacking us again.
We cannot let him do as he pleases.
Our next move should be a counterattack.
Sure, let's go.
Okay.
Huh?
Now?!
Yeah, there's a sale tomorrow.
Can't do it then.
Master!
This is bad.
Better tell the Doctor…
Hey, you.
Y-Yes?
I have one final question.
Was the House of Evolution developing cyborgs prior to four years ago?
How many more cyborgs are there?
Have any of them destroyed towns in the past?
I-I'm not sure,
but at the House of Evolution, I'm the only combat cyborg.
Impossible!
Our elite force, bred to exterminate
these obsolete humans, was wiped out?!
According to Armored Gorilla's report,
the two responsible are on their way here.
If they come,
all our research, everything we've
been working on, could be destroyed.
This is a serious matter.
The only option is to use our trump card.
Begin preparations to release Carnage Kabuto.
What?!
No, not him!
That's crazy!
He'll finally be released?
He's right. That might be the only way.
It's still not a good idea.
It's too dangerous.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Is this our only option?
Stay calm!
He will be our last resort.
But…
First, we'll activate all the traps on
the first floor through to the eighth.
If we're lucky, they will take care of the intruders.
I'm fully aware of what will happen to me
should we fail.
I didn't think we'd be running the whole way.
How else would we get there?
I was sure you would be capable of flight.
Humans can't fly, you know.
It's amazing that you are never late.
You are a true hero.
Actually, I'm almost never on time.
We're here.
This is the place Gorilla told us about.
So this is…
…the House of Evolution.
One, two, three, four, five, six…
Looks like it's about eight stories high.
Uh… what the hell was that?
Well…
I decided it would be most efficient
to destroy them all in one blast.
Well, that's true, but…
We could've at least seen
what they had in store for us.
That was kind of mean.
Looks like there's a basement.
S-Stop!
Hey, Carnage Kabuto.
Are you well?
It appears you've killed a bunch of my clones again.
Satisfied?
Huh?
Fool! You think this is enough to satisfy me?
You dared to imprison me deep underground.
Me! The strongest warrior in
the entire House of Evolution!
You are mentally unstable.
We couldn't control you, so we had no choice.
Control?
You moron!
I'm the culmination of all your efforts
to produce a "new human."
My intelligence and physical strength make me
incomparable to you obsolete humans!
You should be the ones obeying me.
You're wrong. You're a failure.
It's true your performance is unparalleled,
but you lack humanity.
Go ahead, kill me.
Plenty of clones could take my place.
Oh?
But I have a favor to ask first.
There's a specimen I must have.
He is extremely strong.
Only you can defeat him.
I want you to catch him for me…
…dead or alive.
This basement is huge!
I'm getting kinda fired up!
Huh?
I sense life-forms further ahead…
Master, two of them are approaching.
Oh, here we go!
There are two. Which one is it?
The one on the right…
In that case, you don't need the one on the left!
Genos?
Huh?
Hello?
I am Carnage Kabuto!
We've got a combat experimentation room.
Let's let loose in there.
You turned Genos into a piece of modern art.
Bring it on!
Pretty big, eh?
It's the biggest room in the facility.
This is where they make us fight to test our combat abilities.
Well then, let the slaughter begin.
Oh?
Still alive, huh?
You fool!
Machine Gun Blows!
He got me.
Let me…
…take him…
Your face is all cracked. Don't push yourself.
With his breath? Impossible!
Genos, you okay?
Yes…
No, you're not! Look at your head!
You've gone and gotten my hopes up.
I have always been critical of humans
and their inferior abilities.
The entire species, myself excluded,
is nothing more than dumb animals.
That realization was agonizing.
If memory serves, I was 15 when it occurred to me.
A plan to evolve the human species
and create a world where I could live contentedly.
A utopia of my own creation, just for me.
A world made up of only us, a new breed of human that will transcend humanity!
I must see it through.
Compared to my anguish back then,
the physical pain I feel now is nothing.
What's the holdup? Let's go!
Show me everything you've got.
Carnage Kabuto, a demon incarnate.
The strongest and most brutal creation
of the House of Evolution.
Let's see how you, at your
archaic stage of human development,
fare against the pinnacle of artificial evolution.
Will you be the spark for a new era of evolution?
I can't wait to find out!
Oh, I get it. I get it!
You're supposed to be strong.
Don't disappoint me now.
You're this place's ultimate weapon, right?
You're clearly not the same as the guys from this morning.
Look at you, just oozing with confidence.
Such speed!
What are you doing?
Hey.
He backed off?
Carnage Kabuto backed off?!
If I'd attacked him just now,
he would've killed me!
Who the hell is this guy?
He's leaving himself wide open,
yet all my instincts are screaming out danger!
Huh?
You bastard!
How the hell did you get so strong?!
So you wanna know too?
Okay, fine.
Genos, you listen carefully too.
He's going to tell us right now?!
The secret to his power?
I'd like to know, too.
Huh?
Who are you?
I am Genus.
Well, fine. Listen up.
It's too risky!
Is it really okay for these guys to hear it?
First of all,
you need to make sure to stick
to this intense training regimen.
Training?
Not augmentation surgery or genetic enhancement?
Training?!
What kind of…?
Listen up, Genos.
You just have to keep at it.
No matter how hard it gets.
It took me three years to get this strong.
One hundred push-ups!
One hundred sit-ups!
One hundred squats!
Then a ten-kilometer run!
Every single day!
And of course, make sure you eat three meals a day.
For breakfast, just a banana's fine.
But the most important thing is to
never use the A/C in summer
Save
money
or the heater in winter, so that you can strengthen the mind.
In the beginning, you'll wish you were dead.
You might start thinking,
"What's the harm in taking a day off?"
But for me, in order to be a strong hero,
no matter how tough it was,
even if I was spitting blood, I never stopped.
I kept doing squats even when my legs felt so heavy they refused to move.
Even when my arms started
making weird clicking noises,
I kept doing push-ups.
A year and a half later,
I started to notice a difference.
I was bald…
And I had become stronger!
In other words, you gotta train like hell
until your hair falls out.
That's the only way to become strong.
Anyone just screwing with evolution
and trying to create a "new human race"
will never make it this far.
The ability to grow and adapt
is humanity's greatest strength!
Wh-What?
Is this guy… for real?
Master…
You are so…
full of crap!
Huh?
That's just ordinary strength training!
And it's not even that intense!
Anyone could do it!
I…
I have to get stronger!
I didn't ask to study under you so I could listen to your jokes!
Master Saitama, your power…
is clearly beyond what you can achieve
by just training your body!
That's right, I want to know your—
We want to know your true secret!
Genos…
You may not believe me,
but that's really all I did.
Oh yeah?
No! Carnage Kabuto!
If you don't wanna tell us your secret, so be it.
Stop! You'll go on another rampage!
I bet you aren't stronger than me anyway!
But, since you pissed me off,
I'm gonna annihilate you.
Carnage Mode!
CARNAGE MODE
When I get like this, I lose my mind for a whole week
and my bloodthirst can't be quenched!
After I kill you, I'll head into town and
go on a killing rampage until next Saturday!
If you're such a powerful hero,
then just try and stop me!
No way… It can't be…
Master?!
Dammit. I might've made a horrible mistake.
This guy's in Carnage Mode.
He said he'll be on a rampage for a whole week.
Die, die, die, die, die, die,
Die, die, die, die, die!
He'll be like this till next Saturday?
One whole week from today…
Next Saturday…
In other words, today is Saturday too!
That means…
It's all over.
There's no one in the world that can stop him.
That means…
Today is…
Bargain day at the supermarket!
Who the hell is this guy?
God damn it!
What is he—
I believe he is upset about this.
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Saturday
Only
Gigantic Sale!
Master, the store closes at 10 PM.
It takes about four hours to get there.
If we really hurry, we can make it.
I'll make it if I hurry?
Yes!
Let's go, Genos!
Yes, Master!
I think I'm done with evolution.
It appears that the one who must change… is me.
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
When my worries keep me awake under the crescent moon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
All I can do is close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you, I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope my feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know so very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you always work
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, yet still I worry
tsuyokute shinpai
Only I ever see your weakness
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before the stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come right back home
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Yes.
The on-site investigation is underway.
Yes, that's correct.
Just like the other cases,
the site is scorched by intense flames.
Everything points to the young cyborg
being responsible for this.
Yes, understood.
Such devastating power.
Yeah.
NEXT
TIME
THE
MODERN
NINJA
THE
MODERN
NINJA
Yo, this is Carnage Kabuto.
In Japanese, my name is "Ashura Kabuto,"
written with the kanji for "shell,"
"field trip," and the Sanskrit word "Om."
Whaddaya think?
Bet you don't give a damn!
Next time, on One Punch Man : Episode 4,
"The Modern Ninja."
So that guy's finally gonna show up?