Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono ude de
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne to
So happy for them
Academy
Principal's Office
Takamatsu-kun, your report, please.
Right.
According to the Armory's reports,
our emergency ammunition stocks will be depleted soon.
Anti-Angel Operations HQ
Before conducting our next combat operation, we should refill our stocks.
We've got a new recruit as well, so we'll need new guns too, right?
Good point.
Understood!  Our next operation will be to drop into the Guild.
D-Drop?
What's wrong, Otonashi?
I guess I'm just... not good with heights.
What are you talking about?  We're not dropping from the sky.
We're descending underground.
Ohhhhh underground, huh...
UNDERGROUND?!
We call it the Guild.
It's deep underground.
We have allies there who make weapons for us.
So, it's there to keep Tenshi from finding out?
That's right.
If the Guild was seized, our source of ordinance would disappear,
and our odds of success would go way down.
Yeah?
It's me.
We're coming tonight.
Deactivate the traps for me.
Roger.  Tonight, it is.  See you then.
Alright.
We'll go with everyone here.
What about Noda-kun?
That idiot's probably just doing whatever he wants again.
Alright, let's go.
Gymnasium
Here we go...
Alright, let's get moving.
Come on, don't just stand there.  Let's go.
I... in here?
This is the entrance, huh?
It's been a while since we've gone into the Guild, huh?
Passage to the Guild B1
It sure is dark.
Whoa, someone's here!
Ahh, it's just a moron.
Otonashi, huh?  I refuse to accept you yet.
Why'd he pick here to lie in wait?
Noda-kun attaches great significance to situations.
That's a little cryptic...
I don't really want you to accept me, either.
Bastard... this time won't go the same as the-
Defensive positions!
The traps aren't deactivated?!
What's going on?
Exactly what you're seeing.
The road to the Guild is filled with anti-Angel traps.
And right now it looks like they're all activated.
And so that means...
I wonder if we forgot to deactivate them?
No way.  That's like asking to be annihilated.
No.  The Guild must have rebooted the traps on their own.
Why?
There's only one possibility.
Tenshi is here!
In here?!
Just wild heaven.
How negligent.
So wait... these Guild guys are doing this even though they know we're here?
It seems you still don't understand...
No matter what might happen, we aren't going to die.
Although, we'll certainly taste the pain of it...
I'd prefer to avoid that...
But if the Guild's location is discovered and overtaken,
our weapons, ammo, and everything else will cease to function.
After that, how would you suggest we fight against Tenshi?
The Guild's decision was correct.
Are we going to pursue Tenshi?
Even with all the traps activated?
The traps will handle Tenshi somehow... let's retreat!
The traps won't be able to do more than temporarily halt her advance.
We'll chase her.
Advance!
Passage to the Guild B3
So, then... what kind of traps are there?
All kinds, my friend.  Look forward to 'em.
Oh, no.  It's coming!
Huh?  What is?
Run!
Fool, we're crazy...
In here!  Hurry!
That was Takamatsu-kun's voice...
It got him.
Everyone but Takamatsu-kun appears unhurt.
Let's continue.
Is it really alright not to help him?
It's not like he'll die.
He'll make it out on his own, eventually.
Really?
Up you go.
Ah, thanks.
You saved me back there.
No need for thanks.
To tell the truth, I've grown to like you.
You coming onto me?
Wha- NO!
Passage to the Guild B6
Will it open?
Not at all.
Oh no, I forgot!  This is the trap that seals all the exits!
Don't forget something that important!
How foolish.
What's about to come is really dangerous!
Avoid it!
Get down!
What the?
What happens if you touch them?
You'll be split in two by the sharpest object imaginable.
Second wave coming!
What do I do?
You evade it!
Third wave coming!
What was the third wave, again?
It's an X pattern!
So what do I do with this one!?
Just do something!
Hurry and open up!
Don't look!
You don't wanna see...
What's going on?
It's open!  Let's go!
So the sacrifice this time was Matsushita-kun, huh?
With a body like that, it's no surprise.
Man needs to go on a diet.
He saw something pretty nasty.
Poor guy, right in front of him.
I'm glad that you managed to make it.
By the way, even when you're chopped up like that, you'll still recover.
Passage to the Guild B8
The trap's firing up!
Oh no, I forgot!  This one's a falling ceiling trap!
I said don't forget important stuff like that!
TK!
Hurry up.  If you go now, you can make it!
Hold on to each other and get out of here!
Thanks.
See ya!
'Preciate it.
Sorry.
Even TK sacrificed himself...
You guys sacrificed him.
Like I said, he'll be fine eventually.
No problem, no problem.
We'll make sure his sacrifice isn't in vain.
Let's go.
Passage to the Guild B9
What's wrong?
Something's...
Oh no, I forgooooooooooooot!
L-Like I said!
Don't forget stuff like that!
Too heavy...
I can't hold on...
Otonashi and I are gonna fall.
Hey!  Don't just decide things yourself!
Losing everyone here isn't a good idea.
I know that!  Hurry up everyone and climb!
Otonashi, can you make it?
I don't have much choice!
You're quite the ace.
Shut it!  I'm going up!
What are you doing?!  Don't stop, keep going!
But where do I grab?!
Wherever!  Grab wherever you want!
Hurry up...
You're gonna fall if you grab there.
I guess so.
Whoa.  What's with her... she smells so good...
No good.
I need to climb.
Hey, why are you looking at me?
I can't help it!
H-Hurry up and climb.
Yeah...
Wahhh!  You can't grab there!
Idiooooooot!
Er... um... Hinata was-
He sacrificed himself.
I see...
We're down to four, now.
You've got a lot of nerve.
Being one of the the few that remain.
Yeah, whatever.
You'll definitely be next.
UTW Presents:
Passage to the Guild B13
An inundation trap, huh?
This guy... can't even swim, huh?
The exit's this way.  Come on!
Passage to the Guild B15
Here.
Thanks.
Yuri!  Over here!
Shiina-san.
Let's go.
Huh?  What's that doing here?
That's...
The puppy's gonna get swept away!
Shiina-san!  No!
I messed up.  It was just a toyyyyyyy!
Even Shiina-san got sacrificed in one of the traps...
That was a trap for Tenshi, too?!
Wait... she couldn't tell at a glance?
Cute things are her weak point.
Wow.  That's unexpectedly cute.
But she'll be alright too, won't she?
Passage to the Guild B17
You're the only one left, huh?
Seems that way...
If we were a real unit, we'd have been completely wiped out by now.
I'm a terrible leader.
There's no helping it, right?
These are anti-Angel traps after all.
If they can't even stop us, what good are they?
Um...
Should we take a break?
Alright.  We need to dry our clothes, anyway.
I'm amazed that you're able to lead a group like that.
Why were you selected as the leader?
It's because I was the first to resist.
That's the only reason.
Against Tenshi?
Yeah.
I had siblings...
Huh?
I'm talking about what you don't have.  Memories.
The time when you were alive... before this world?
Yeah.
Including me, four siblings.
I was the eldest daughter, and had two younger sisters,
and one younger brother.
My parent's work was going well, so we were quite well-off.
We were surrounded by nature, so it was almost like living in a villa.
It was during Summer Vacation.
In the afternoon, when my parents were out, some men I'd never seen before were in the house.
Even though it was the middle of Summer, they were wearing stifling-looking balaclavas.
I knew they'd come to do something bad.
I was the eldest daughter, so I thought I definitely had to protect my siblings.
But... no way that would happen, right?
Obviously, the guys were after our valuables...
But they couldn't find them.
So, they started indiscriminately destroying
windowpanes and televisions, and getting angry.
And then, they came up with the worst thing to do to us siblings.
Little girl, you're the eldest, right?
Your parents must've told you where the valuables are, right?
Like, "if there's an earthquake, grab these and run",
Or "if robbers come, give them these and ask them to leave".
I'm sure your parents must've told you something, right?
I don't know...
I don't know anything about that!
Well then, go and look.
If we don't like what you find, we'll have to do something bad to these kids, one by one.
You've got 10 minutes apiece.
Go and find something good within 10 minutes.
I started searching the house frantically.
My head was pounding like it was about to split.
I was nauseous.  I was ready to faint.
My siblings' lives were on the line.
I had to find something!
But, I had no idea what sort of valuables they were looking for.
Ahh, it's time.  I have to hurry.  I have to hurry!
I'll bring the biggest-looking thing here.
H-Heavy.
If I can just bring this down, I'm sure it's worth a lot!
By the time the police arrived... 30 minutes had passed.
The only one alive... was me.
All alone.
It's not that I care if I'm reincarnated as a water flea, or anything.
It's just that if God exists... I want to fight him.
I mean... it's just too much.
He doesn't intervene when bad things happen...
That afternoon, I truly thought I was a responsible older sister.
But, everything I wanted to protect was taken from me in 30 minutes.
You don't find that unreasonable?
You don't find a life like that unforgivable?
You're strong, Yuri.
If I had memories like that, I'd want to just sit back and disappear.
But you're fighting, Yuri.
That's right.
Hey... can I ask you something?
What?
Why did you die, Yuri?
Ahh...
Don't be stupid.  It wasn't suicide or anything.
Someone who commited suicide wouldn't fight back like this.
And besides, there's no suicides in this world.
Now, let's go.
I'll protect you.
This is Guild?!
Guild, Final Floor
It's Yurippe!
She's here!
She's alright!
These guys make weapons here?
You managed to make your way here past all those traps, Yurippe?
We should have known you would.
More importantly, where's Tenshi?
Her advance was halted recently, but it seems she's begun to move again.
There it is, again!
She's close.
Yurippe...
We're abandoning this place.
What?
Are you serious, Yurippe?
Yeah, you're fine with not being able to make weapons anymore?
What's important isn't places or tools.
It's memories.
Have you guys forgotten that?
N-No...
What do you mean, Yuri?
In this world, nothing with a soul can be given life.
Only objects of form can be.
As long as you know the composition and structure of the object,
that's essentially all you need.
You can even make things out of mud.
However, we eventually prioritized efficiency, and all we do now is make replicas in this factory.
Chaa-san.
This guy's a high-schooler, too?
Even though in the past, we used to breath life into objects using only the shape and memory of them, right?
Well then, let's go to the Old Guild.
It's been left alone for quite some time.
There's nothing there, but...
If you're looking to create things from Earth, there's a mountain's worth.
We should be able to get back to the surface from there, as well.
What about this place?
We'll blow it up.
Otherwise, Tenshi could cross over to the Old Guild from here.
It's the only place we have left to go back to.
Even so...
She's right above us!
All you need to bring with you are your
memories and your pride as a craftsman.
That's all you need.
Am I wrong, you guys!?
Right!
Alright!  Prepare the explosives.
Let's see some teamwork!
Yeah!
There are no traps left.  Hurry!
Yuri, where are you going?
To buy us time!
Ah, so you came.  Aren't you afraid?
Even if I stayed down there, there's nothing I could do.
She's here...
Let's do it!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
She's responding too quickly!
Incredible.  She can keep up with her in close combat?
Load shell!
Is it okay to fire with her up there?
Just do it!
Here we go!  Hurry it up!
Guard Skill: Delay.
Damn it!
Otonashi-kun!
You two, get out of the way!
You guys, you get things done when you need to!
Something like that doesn't look easy to make.
Otonashi-kun, this way.
Let's do it!
All hands brace for impact...
FIRE!
Did it work?
The cannon blew up, huh?
Tch... I guess you can't make something you don't have memories of.
Don't make things you don't know how to make!
Tenshi's waking up!
You guys!
Do something with these!
Shell-squad, hurry up!
All members accounted for.
Alright.  We'll blow the Guild up.
Okay?
Do it.
Blow up!
How many years has it been?
This place really is empty...
Old Guild
What a joke.
If you tear down the walls, you'll have all the earth you need.
What a crappy nesting place.
I'm counting on you to make a new one.
Right.
Okay, let's get started, you guys!
Yeah!
Hey morons, you awake?
We tore down the Guild, and blew up Tenshi.
Hurry to the Old Guild, and let everyone know.
We'll replenish our arms as fast as we can, before Tenshi recovers.
All members, to the Old Guild.
I repeat:  Hurry up, morons.
I saved her without even thinking twice.
What am I doing?
It's just that if God exists, I want to fight him.
I mean... it's just too much.
It's too terrible.
You're really amazing.
So, this is why everyone follows you.
You truly are a leader.
Itsumo hitori de aruiteta
I've always walked alone
Furikaeru to minna wa tooku
When I turned around, everyone was far away
Soredemo atashi wa aruita
Even so, I walked on
Sore ga tsuyosa datta
That's what it was to be strong
Mou nani mo kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Sou tsubuyaite miseru
That's what I try to tell myself
Itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
Eventually, everyone will be alone
Omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
They'll continue to live only through their memories
Kodoku sae aishi waratterareru yori
Rather than try to love and laugh at this loneliness
Atashi wa tatakau n da
I will fight
Namida nante misenai n da
I will never show you my tears
UTW Staff
Translator: Ershin
Timer/Typesetting/Editor: Nikon
Timing: Tranquility
TLC/QC: Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c6] Why is the new song a ballad?
[c37] Please, call me Christ.
[c83] ... I couldn't sing the song I wanted to.
[c40] This is Tenshi's residence.
[c76] It was an incredible fever.
[c62D] What's gonna get exciting later, is... Alchemy!　Alchemy is...
[c118] No memories.
[c330] Well then, what do you think happened?
[c167] Just when I was starting to have a better opinion of you guys!
[c219] Tenshi has appeared.
[c326] The worst possible situation.
[c231] ... That's as far as you go.
[c245] ... Also, don't touch it!