Hey!
This is for you.
I really want to say thank you for everything you've done.
You're so good at finding these rare CDs, Sayaka.
Well, I think I'm just lucky.
He's such an amazing musician.
You wanna listen, Sayaka?
I-If you don't mind.
I'd rather hook up a speaker, but we're in a hospital.
Kawashita Yakusoku Wasurenai You
So that I never forget the promise we made
Me wo Toji Tashikameru
I look back on it every time I close my eyes
Oshiyoseta Yami Furiharatte Susumuyo
Then I get rid of the darkness and walk toward the future
Itsu ni Nattara Nakushita Mirai wo
There's a future I've lost
Watashi Koko de Mata Mirukoto Dekiruno
When can I hope to rediscover it here?
Afuredashita Fuan no Kage wo
Shadows and shadows of doubt overflow
Nandodemo Saite Kono Sekai Ayundeku
I sweep them all away as I continue forward
Tomedonaku Kizamareta
The endlessly ticking time
Toki wa Ima Hajimari Tsuge
marks the beginning of the era
Kawaranai Omoi wo Nose
I'll open this locked door
Tozasareta Tobira Akeyou
bearing unyielding thoughts
Mezameta Kokoro wa Hashiridashita
Awaken, my heart begins to race
Mirai wo Egaku Tame
Now I will decide my future
Muzukashii Michi de Tachidomattemo
I may stop my feet at a thorny path
Oozorawa Kireina Aosa de Itsumo Mattete Kureru
But the sky will always be there in its blue glory
Dakara Kowakunai
So I won't be afraid
Mou Nani ga Attemo Kujikenai
I'll never lose heart again
Episode 3     Nothing scares me anymore!
Tiro Finale!
Wow, Mami is so cool!
Jeez, that wasn't just for show.
Keep in mind that we're dealing with something really dangerous.
YES!
But there was no Grief Seed.
That's because it was just a familiar spirit that split from a witch.
It didn't have a Grief Seed with it.
So that wasn't a witch...
It seems like the witches keep getting away.
Even so, you can't just let their familiars go.
They can turn into the same witch they split from.
Now, let's go.
Have either of you decided what you'd like to wish for?
Have you, Madoka?
Well, this is what happens when you suddenly need to make a decision.
What was your wish, Mami?
Well, you don't have to answer me...
I...
...didn't even have the chance to choose.
Not that I regret doing this.
Dying back there would've been worse than living like this.
But if I could choose for myself, I would
want to make the decision very carefully.
Since I was unable to choose.
Mami, do we have to wish for ourselves?
What do you mean?
For example... I mean, it's just an example.
There's someone who's in much bigger trouble then I am.
Can I make a wish for that person?
Are you talking about Kamijo?
I-I said this was an example!
Well, the contracted person doesn't have to benefit from the wish.
Also, there's someone who's done that before.
But that story doesn't have a happy ending.
If you want to make someone else's dream come true,
you need to make your own wish even clearer.
Do you really want his dream to come true, Miki?
Or do you just want him to thank you for making his dream come true?
Mami...
The two may sound the same, but they're totally different.
It's kinda mean for you to say that...
I'm sorry, but I have to say it now.
If you make the wrong choice now, I'm sure you'll regret it later.
You're right. I was too naive. Sorry.
It really is a tough decision to make.
Don't stress out because you can't think of something.
Well, I do want your wishes as soon as possible.
Don't say that. Boys who tell girls to hurry up will be unpopular.
It really isn't easy.
I can't make you hurry. It's also against
the rules for me to give you suggestions.
It probably can't be as simple as wanting to become something.
Madoka, do you desire power?
No, that's not it.
How should I say it...
I'm pretty lame and I have no special talents.
I'd be satisfied if I could become a cool girl like Mami.
Madoka, if you became a Puella Magi,
you'd be so much more powerful then Mami.
What?
Of course, it would also depend on what
you wish for when you make the contract.
I can't even measure how big the Soul Gem you produce might be.
You're the most talented one I've ever met.
Gosh, what are you talking about? You can't be serious.
I am...
Madoka, are you awake?
Yeah. What's going on?
Oh, not again.
W-Water...
What a jerk. If you want something to drink, help yourself! Jeez...
Thanks. Should we make some hot chocolate?
Yes please.
Why does Mom love working so much?
It's not like she dreamed about working for that company, did she?
Hmm... It's not the work she likes, it's how hard she works.
She likes the satisfied feeling she gets
after she overcomes all of her problems.
It doesn't mean that she dreamed about working for that company.
But Mom is still living her ideal life.
Some dreams come true this way.
So her dream is her lifestyle?
I guess everybody sees her differently,
but I respect her and I'm proud of her.
She's amazing.
Don't you understand?
You're trying to get these ordinary
people involved in this dangerous game.
They were chosen by Kyubey.
They're involved.
You're guiding them to become Puella Magi.
Isn't that interesting?
No, they'll cause problems.
In particular, Madoka Kaname.
I see. It seems to me that you've noticed her talent too.
I really can't let her make the contract.
Because you believe someone more powerful
then you will be a problem for you?
That sounds like something a bullied child would say.
I don't want to fight you...
Then please try not to meet with me again.
Let tonight be the last time we speak and try to settle things.
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
What? You didn't get to see Kamijo?
Sounds like he isn't doing very well today.
It took us a while to get here. That's pretty rude.
What's going on?
Look, there's something here...
It's a Grief Seed! It's about to transform!
I can't believe this! Why would it be here?!
This is bad. We need to run away quickly!
It's about to form its magical barrier!
Will there be a maze again?
Madoka, do you have Mami's number?
No.
That's bad.
Madoka, go and get Mami right now.
I'm going to keep an eye on it.
What?!
That's ridiculous!
It'll take a while for the witch to come out of it,
but you won't be able to get out once the barrier forms.
I'm not sure if Mami can get here in time to save you...
If the maze forms, we won't be able to find out where the witch is.
I can't just leave it.
Madoka, go by yourself! I'll stay with Sayaka.
When Mami gets here, she can use telepathy to figure out where I am.
Just let me stay here with Sayaka to keep an eye on the Grief Seed.
I'll be able to guide Mami so she can find
the quickest way through the barrier.
Thank you, Kyubey.
I'll bring Mami here as soon as possible!
Are you afraid, Sayaka?
Uh, yes, definitely.
If you pick a wish, I can turn you into a Puella Magi immediately.
I will if there's an emergency.
But I can't do it now.
It's such an important decision for me to make.
I wanna try to take it very seriously.
It's here, right?
Kyubey, what's the situation?
We're still okay. It's not going to hatch soon.
Are you okay, Sayaka?
No prob, no prob.
It's probably napping.
It's probably a bad idea to use strong
magical power to stimulate the egg.
Don't rush. Can you come here without making much noise?
Yes, I will.
Thank goodness we got here in time.
You're so reckless. I was going to be mad with you,
but I think you made a smart move this time.
We don't even have to worry about the witch getting away...
I should've told you that I don't want to see you ever again.
I'll hunt this one. You two should stay out of this.
I don't think so.
We have to get Miki and Kyubey out of here.
I'll make sure that they're safe.
Do you really think that I would trust you?
Y-You fool! This isn't the time for this!
I'm not trying to hurt you,
but I can't promise that you won't get hurt.
This witch is different from the previous ones.
Be a good girl and I'll release you when we get back.
Let's go, Kaname.
Okay...
Well, Mami.
What?
I've thought about a lot of possible wishes.
So you're ready to decide?
Yes.
But I think you'll be angry with me since it's too naive.
What dream do you want to come true?
I've never done well in any subjects and I've never had any talents.
I'm pretty sure that I'd just be trouble
and wouldn't be able to help anyone.
I've never liked this, but I
couldn't do anything about it.
But you showed me how you fight to save people.
You told me that I can probably do the same thing.
That's the nicest thing I've ever heard.
That's why I believe that in order to fulfill my
dream, all I need to do is become a Puella Magi.
Even someone like me can be useful to someone else.
I want to live being proud of myself. That's my biggest dream.
It won't be easy.
You'll get injured and you won't even
have spare time to date or have fun.
But even under those conditions, you're
still trying so hard. You're my dream.
I'm not someone to dream about.
I'm just being cool by pushing myself too hard.
Even when I'm afraid or having a hard time, I can't talk to anyone.
All I can do is cry by myself.
There's nothing good about becoming a Puella Magi.
Mami, you're not alone now.
Right. You're right.
You really want to fight alongside me from now on?
Will you be by my side?
If someone like me can do it, then yes!
You got me.
I tried to act more like your mentor,
but it turned out to be something that I can't do.
Mami.
But you don't get opportunities like this everyday.
Think carefully about your wish.
Yeah, it really is rare.
A contract is still a contract. You need
to think about how you can benefit from it.
You can become a billionaire, you can get a cute boyfriend.
You can do whatever you want to do.
Well...
Then how about this.
If you still can't pick a wish before we finish the witch off,
let's just get Kyubey to treat us to a cake!
C-Cake!?
Yup. We need the biggest and most luxurious cake for celebration!
And then, we'll party with everyone!
To commemorate us forming a Puella Magi duo!
How could I become a Puella Magi just for a cake!?
If you don't like it, you'll just have
to think about it carefully yourself.
Mami!
The Grief Seed started moving!
It's gonna start right now! Hurry!
OK, I got it.
I'll finish you off with a swift attack today.
Huh!? How can you...!?
My body feels light.
I've never fought so happily before.
Nothing scares me anymore!
I'm not alone!
Sorry I'm late.
You got here in time.
Watch out! It's coming!
Sorry for ruining your great day. I'll finish you off!
Here I go!
She's got it!
Tiro Finale!
Unbelievable...
You two! Make a contract with me! Now!
Madoka! Sayaka!
You have to choose your wishes! Quickly!
You don't have to.
I'll kill it.
You two just avoided death.
Remember what you've seen.
That's what you get for becoming a Puella Magi.
Give it back.
Give it back!
That's... that's... Mami's!
Give it back to Mami!
Right. This is only for Puella Magi.
You don't have the right to touch it.
Itsuka Kimi ga Hitomi ni Tomosu
Love will ignite a light
Ai no Hikari ga
in your eyes
Toki wo Koete
It will transcend time
Horobi Isogu Sekai no Yume wo
The world dreams
Tashika ni Hitotsu
as it hurries to death
Kowasudarou
One dream will be destroyed
Tamerai mo Nomihoshite
For what do you seek,
Kimi ga Nozomu Mono wa Nani
upon ridding all hesitation?
Konna Okubukai Akogare no
Do ephemeral tomorrows verily await
Yukue ni Hakanai Ashita wa Aruno
past this profound admiration?
Kodomo no Koro ni Yume ni Miteta
If I could replicate the ancient spells
Inishie no Mahou no You ni
I dreamt of in my youth,
Kamisae Kudaku Chikara de
I would go see your smile,
Hohoemu Kimi ni Aitai
harnessing the power to obliterate God Himself
Obieru Kono Te no Naka ni wa
The funeral wreath I hold
Tomuraeta Hana no Yuuki
gives courage to my trembling hands
Omoidake ga Tayoru Subete
My heart is my only support
Hikari wo Yobisamasu Negai
I will light the darkness
Artist Santa Tsuji (nitro+)
Mami was so nice.
She did that to teach us the resolve you need to fight.
Episode 4     Both miracles and magic exist