The students have finally discovered his magic! And on top of losing his magic, Negi's been turned into an animal!
And Negi became a chupacabra at that!
And furthermore, they have once again been caught in this and were sent to the world of illusion!
It is a castle in Wales, yet another place that is nostalgic to Negi.
Who did it? And for what purpose is Negi being invited to his birth place?
What is the fate of Negi and Class 3-A!?
by Chachamaru
And there you go. That’s how it goes.
My, so that’s what it was…
So if he’s exposed,
he gets turned into an animal, aru?
That’s how it goes!
In a good way!
That’s the rule for the Magic Academy, mya!
So that’s why Negi-sensei turned into a…
Never knew that a chupacabra was an animal.
All of this is our fault, isn’t it?
Yeah… If we didn’t see it, things wouldn’t have turned out like this.
I’m sorry, Negi-bouzu.
I’m sorry!
You guys…
No, don’t say that!
It’s not your fault! It was my fault.
I was always causing trouble for Asuna-san and the others, whom I’ve exchanged provisional contracts with.
And keeping it a secret from the rest of you was also very painful.
So, now I am very relieved…
Negi-sensei…
Here ya go. It’s a bit plain, but…
I’m a-!!
Chupacabra…
Aniki!
He had a show of courage as he has caused the whole class quite some trouble!
What a horrible teacher he is!
Rice Scoop Attack!
What kind of a heartless frog are you!?
There you are,
fairy!
How cute!
Everyone! Don’t let it fool you!
He’s the bad guy!
Desu!
Doesn’t seem like it, though…
Please, stop it!
Negi!
Aren’t I the target!?
The others have nothing to do with it!
Return them this instant!
Ako?
Sakurako!
Satsuki!
I will...
destroy everything...
that’s important to you!
Ha, ha, ha!
Guys! Run away!
All of you too! Hurry!
What are you saying, de gozaru!? Negi-bouzu!
Yeah!
Desu!
We’re your partners!
That’s right!
Right.
We’ll fight together, Negi-kun!
Well, Negi, if you get it, then hurry up and activate those contracts!
I can’t.
Idiots, did you forget, Ane-sans!?
Negi-chan just got his magic certification taken away from him, mya!
So basically…
I can’t activate any provisional contracts while I’m in this state!
Leave it to me, Bouya!
Evangeline-san!
Lac
lac
Spiritus!
An ice sword!
Is Eva-chan...
a mage, too!?
No; Master is a vampire.
You don’t have to say anything unnecessary.
Vampire?
So, all those vampire events from last year…
So Eva-chan’s the culprit…
See? You guys are saying unneeded things, so the air’s feeling a bit annoying.
Saying rude things again.
Eh? There was a commotion involving a vampire?
Hello, weren’t you there to begin with!?
Eh? When?
She seems to have forgotten.
Attack!
Don’t do it, Eva-san!
Don’t hurt those three girls!
What are you talking about, you imbecile!?
Do you understand the situation we’re in!?
Yes, I do! But still, don’t do it!
Hey! Let go!!
I refuse to!
Let go of it, dammit!
Don’t do it!
Master!
Eva-san! Chachamaru-san!
Asuna-san!
What the heck are you doing, you stupid Negi!?
Let’s flee.
Agreed!
Wait!
We won’t let you get away,
Negi!
That idiot…
Ah, I hit my back.
Are you okay, Master?
That was pretty harsh, huh Evangeline?
Yo.
Takamichi.
So you’re here, too?
I suppose.
What do you mean “I suppose”!?
If you’re here, then hurry and get the hell out!
We missed the fairy!
I wanted to get out of here, but here,
if my students were to see me using magic, I’ll also be turned into an animal.
Liar. You’re not gonna turn into anything!
So you knew?
Duh.
Don’t be so mad!
Worry not; I know where the fairy’s located.
Eh?
Well now, the first group that ran away was…
Where exactly… are we?
I’m scared!
A weird place, isn’t it?
More like, can we even get out of here?
And here, we have the other group which escaped.
We got lost, aru!
Ah! Look at that!
I can’t be a mage anymore…
I’ll be a chupacabra for the rest of my life…
Hey, this isn’t the time to be moping, you know.
Get a hold of yourself.
I’m sorry.
I got you and the others mixed up in all of this…
I’m really sorry…
Be a man and stop crying!
Shh!
We’ll get caught!
Oneechan… Anya…
Negi-kun’s Oneesan?
And I’m pretty sure that Anya is Negi’s childhood friend.
We can hear the laughter, but the girls aren’t reacting.
That’s an illusion, without a doubt.
That was a close one!
Keep it down!
Negi-sensei is-!
Eh?
Negi! Don’t fall for it! That’s an illusion!
Negi-sensei!
Stop!
Oh crap!
Negi, no!
Don’t go in there!
Ah~ Negi! Don’t go there~
by Makie
Um…
We’re in a jungle, huh?
Weren’t we in a castle?
We were in the castle before we opened the door, huh?
Eh? Why?
In the meantime, we have to hurry and get out of here!
Ah, yeah, we should!
Looks like the door’s gone.
Eh? Why?
What are we gonna do, Iinchou?
Calm down! Let’s think about it in a serene manner!
First off, who was the one that suggested we enter the room?
Hmm?
It was me?
Makie-san! How could you?
Ah! I’m so sorry!
I wasn’t able to guess this kind of twist!
At any rate, this isn’t the time or place to say something like that!
No! You are responsible for everything that’s happened right now.
Do something about this right now!
If I don’t hurry and make it back to where Negi-sensei is,
I’ll worry and worry and lose weight fast!
Even if you tell me that, I can’t do anything about it!
What do you mean you can’t do anything about it!?
You give up so easily! That’s why you fail!
Eh? I… fail?
Yes, fail. You fail at being Sasaki Makie! You’re a Sasaki Makie Failure!
The animal’s voice disappeared.
W-w-what’s going on?
Dinosaur!!
Farewell, Sasaki Makie.
by Kuu Fei
Captain! Damage on the port of the vessel!
Damage is 75%!
Captain! Energy is rapidly lowering!
Whoo, I’m burnin’ up!
We must endure, aru!
Reinforcements will surely come, aru!
Hang in there, aru!
Main Defensive Armament on Stand-by!
If we take that hit, we’re over!
Absolute end!!
Just at last, our luck has run out, aru.
Here it comes!!
Is everyone okay?
Only that fighter plane declared war and struck.
Whoa, 90 points!
Yay, Yuuna!
Yay, Asakura!
Sayo-chan’s workin’ hard, too!
Y-yay… Sayo-chan…
There are some disorders in the enemy’s ranks of troops…
Captain!
Now, aru!
We’ll take ‘em out all at once, aru!
Roger!
No one in this group feels suspicious about their sudden situation.
Takeoff, aru!
Meanwhile…
It’s been a while, Negi.
I’m so happy.
You look like you’re workin’ hard there.
But I know you really wanna just go home, you crybaby Negi!
Oneechan… Anya…
Negi, do you want a scone?
Nekane-san baked them, you know. Doesn’t it bring back memories?
There, eat up!
I will. Thank you!
He seems to have disappeared.
It won’t open!
Negi-sensei’s in there-!
Despite that there’s no way Oneesan or Anya would even be here!
I think he was in so much pain that he couldn’t distinguish reality from fantasy.
It’s normal.
He just had his magic powers revoked, and he’s speaking in that form.
You’re right… it sucks…
You’re a real idiot, you know!
OPEN UP, DAMMIT!
Asuna-san, please step away from it.
It’s no good; it’s a magic door!
Negi, come out here right this instant!
Hey, Negi!
Negi, you stupid Negi!
Asuna…
Oneechan…
Hmm? What is it, Negi?
I know what you are.
You’re an illusion, aren’t you?
There’s no way… that you guys would be here.
And on top of that, despite my appearance, you’re talking to me as if nothing’s happened at all!
It’s too strange.
There’s no helping the fact that I’m the target.
I don’t have my magic powers anymore, remember?
I wasn’t able to become a mage.
Right now, I’m just a…
I’m just a… strange animal.
So please, let me out of here!
Return everyone in Class A!
Please!
That cannot be done.
Black Rose Baron…
It can’t be done…?
Why? Why can’t it be done!? Baron!
I cannot answer any further.
We’ve cornered it.
Did you know that the darkest place is under the candlestick?
Sleep!
HELP US!!
We can’t… win with this ship, aru…
The magic-!
The Black Rose Baron!
Negi!
Hey, you! What did you do to-
He just fell unconscious.
He disappeared.
Wait! Hey you!
Negi!
Asuna-san?
You… idiot.
This is strange.
What is the meaning of this?
I wonder if someone sealed the fairy already?
Seems like it.
But, someone-
Iinchou!
Kuu-chan!
You guys!
Ah! There you guys are!
Is this everyone?
Everyone.
Takahata-sensei!
Even Takamichi came, huh?
Thank goodness. It looks like everyone’s okay.
So, was it you that sealed the fairy?
Evangeline and Chachamaru-kun lent a hand as well.
So that’s what happened…
Eh? Wait a second…
Does this make Takahata-sensei a mage as well?
Yeah, in all actuality.
Ah, I’m sorry!
It was supposed to be a secret, too!
It’s alright, no big deal.
That’s because he won’t turn into a chupacabra like you if people find out.
Chupa…
Aside from that, don’t you think it’s rather strange, Negi-kun?
What a stupid guy he is.
The fairy was sealed, you know.
Don’t you think it’s weird?
That’s right! We’re still in the world of illusion!
That’s correct.
There’s some other magic power different from a fairy’s that’s pullin’ the strings here.
You guys be careful.
Everyone, please make sure you don’t touch or move anything.
Okay!
Ah! Ane-san!
Eh?
Asuna-san!
YOU RETARD!
The nightmare’s not over! Will everybody truly escape this crisis, and can they all manage to get back from the world of illusion?
And as for Negi, will his wish of reverting back to his original form be granted!?
As we continue our unexpected plot twist, sit back and wait till next time!
Once a week, Chachamaru sees me for a maintenance check.
Next Time, “Scientific Theory is Something That Doesn’t Mix With Magic, to Put it Bluntly,”
by Hakase.
And for the record, this is a crepe.
Hey, can Yamamoto do tricks?
Isn’t that impossible for him?
He’s a fish, you know.
Gimme your hand
Nah, there’s an extent to what he can’t do.