Akihisa Yoshii is an extremely picky eater.
Thanks for the food.
Salt water for an appetizer and
sugar water for the main course.
This feels kinda luxurious.
His pickiness lessens as time wears on.
Coming!
It's been quite a while, Aki.
Si... Sis?
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Why! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Seventh Period
Kiss and Bust and Ponytail
Akira Yoshii, 23 years old. Has E-cup breasts.
She's Akihisa's older sister who was studying abroad.
Sis, are you seriously going to dress like that?!
Why did you start screaming out of the blue?
You have no common sense.
Says the person who's walking around in a bathrobe...
Let me finish.
I have my reasons for dressing like this.
I'm sorry.
Did something happen?
An elegant day with Akira. Episode one.
It was a hot summer day. I made my way through the airport,
carrying a load of heavy luggage.
After boarding the train, I looked into the
window and saw myself sweating viciously.
I might be only visiting a relative, but I need to look my best.
I didn't want you to see me all sweaty, after all.
So, to get rid of my sweat, I changed into an absorbent bathrobe.
Stop! That's crazy!
Finally, I maintained my elegance as an older sister and met up with my younger brother.
That's even more crazy!
Thank goodness the train was nearly empty.
An elegant day with Akira. Episode two.
I needed a lot of room to change.
Hang on! Where exactly did you change?
An elegant day with Akira. Episode two.
Omitted
Aki, I came here for a very important reason.
I am going to monitor your daily life
and conclude if it is a good idea for you to live on your own.
When I promised to let you live alone, I had two conditions.
Don't tell me you've forgotten them.
Will you get mad if I told you I forgot?
No, I won't.
Thank god, since I totally-
I will give you a kiss instead.
I totally remember!
Moreover, a kiss so hot that it will ruin you for marriage.
I'm your brother, for crying out loud!
Don't worry, I was talking about myself.
I can't handle this!
You'll have to live with the knowledge that you deflowered your sister for the rest of your life...
I remember them, seriously. Don't do it!
Recite them.
Uhh...
Aki, close your eyes.
1: only 30 minutes of gaming each day!
2: no sexual deviance!
Oh my gosh...
Shit!
Now I can't kiss you.
That's no reason for you to look so depressed!
It's cleaner than I had expected.
Did you really think I'd leave my room messy?
Well, you are a teenager.
I thought your room would be buried under 2000 porn magazines.
I'm too poor to buy that many!
So you're saying you have at least one.
Akihisa's
allotted
points
Akihisa's
allotted
points
Akihisa's
allotted
points
Suspected sexual deviance. Minus 20 points.
What do you mean, points?
These points will decide if you're elligible to live alone or not.
I'll compare them with the score you make on your next test and make my decision then.
So, if I get an extra 20 points on my
midterms, it'll cancel out that deduction?
I'll ask you another question just in case.
You're not hiding anything else deviant, are you?
Like what? And how many points will you deduct?
Holding hands with a girl will cost you a hundred points.
If you have seen a movie with a girl, or had crepes together with her,
or had her make you lunch or waffles, that would be a grand total of 50,000 points.
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
You're a fine man.
I understand your need to explore your urges.
I never said that...
I've tried my best to let you have a little freedom.
I've prohibited sexual deviance with the opposite sex,
but I don't mind if you go after the same sex.
What the hell?! You've been
corrupted by liberal America!
The stars are beautiful.
You grades are worse than I thought.
That's my best effort.
Effort is nothing but a means to an end.
It doesn't matter how hard you try;
being proud of the fact that you tried is just putting the carriage before the horse.
You don't have to go that far...
If it bothers you that much, then go out and conquer your weakest subjects.
I'm sure you're weak at something.
Like what?
Cooking.
That has nothing to do with school.
But it's essential to living.
Say more and I will shut your mouth with a kiss.
You know, a person is nothing more than a test score...
I'm sorry.
Yuuji, show me your cellphone.
Why?
I saw on TV yesterday that evidence of affairs is usually kept in the cellphone.
Show me.
No-
That hurt!
My eyes...! My eyes are on fire!
Resistance is futile, since I will simply remove it with force.
Hey! Don't take off my pants!
The TV also said guys like to walk around with only a shirt on.
Yeah, but I never said I wanted to!
I want to see it.
Fine! You win!
I'll give it to you!
Oh.
Don't look so fucking disappointed!
Here.
You have more text messages from Yoshii than from me.
So what?
That means you're having an affair with him.
You can't be serious!
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Hey, can I stay over at your place? I don't really want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Akihisa
Can I
stay over?
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really...
want to go back to mine tonight...
Hang on, Shouko...
All right, that's settled.
Good morning, Akihisa.
What's wrong? You look more chipper than usual.
Yeah, I managed to have a
decent breakfast for a change.
Akihisa sold his comics and games in order to raise money for food.
Even if it's just for the period my sister's here...
I need to live healthily or else she'll deduct points.
Cool Biz?
Then why would I only not wear pants?
Thanks a bunch for that weird text!
What's weird about it?
Read it out loud.
Yuuji
Can I
stay over?
Yuuji
I love you.
Don't let
go anymore
Yuuji
Let's...
Hey, can I stay over at your place?
I don't really want to go back to mine tonight...
I don't even know who Aki's after anymore!
You have to wait until you're older before doing things like that!
You're filthy, Yoshii!
Hey, Yoshii.
Please go to the health office.
Is the fact that I'm studying that weird!?
Did something happen?
I mean, you're actually studying.
You've been acting different today...
No, don't worry about it.
Wow, what a lunch you've got!
Yeah, every now and then...
Wow! Who made it?
Me.
Liar.
You're lying.
I'm not lying!
This is beautiful... Either or Sakamoto or Tsuchiya made it for sure.
Fess up.
Who made it?
You can believe whatever you want...
You're not going home tonight, right?
I can't believe you've been tainted...
I can't believe this!
I hate you, Yoshii!
What the hell is wrong with you guys!?
Wait, why is Kubo here?!
First things first, Akihisa.
Why did you want to stay over at my place?
Well... I thought I should start...
Stop lying.
That was too quick!
Right, midterms are soon.
I guess it isn't a bad idea to have a study group.
Really?
Yeah, at your place.
No, not my place!
It's... occupied today!
What are you hiding?
Let's go find out.
A thorough house inspection.
No, not today.
My room's really messy.
I'll tidy it up for you.
But!
That's right... I should say that it's buried in things that girls shouldn't touch.
My room's buried under 2000 porn magazines!
I have to clean it up!
All of them are going out the window.
Leave it to us.
God dammit, this is exactly what I didn't want to happen!
Seriously, guys? You sure about coming over?
What are you hiding?
Judging by the lunch he brought today...
Chances are, he has a girlfriend.
What the hell is this?! You'd better explain yourself!
Well... I didn't say anything.
Don't worry. There's no way Yoshii's hiding a relationship from all of us.
Right, Yoshii?
Your eyes are deadly serious.
Well, we'll find out once he opens the door.
Akihisa, go on.
No...
Do you want to experience the pain of wearing only a shirt?
Staring up at someone with tears in your eyes.
You're gonna sell it?! You're going to sell my purity!?
Tsuchiya, remember to undo the top two buttons of his shirt.
Himeji, I expected better out of you!
Fine! I'll do it!
Your buttons?
No, the door!
I must be cursed!
There's no better evidence than this.
I'm so envious I want to kill you.
This is no good, Yoshii.
This bra is not your size.
She's in extreme denial.
What's that?
Cotton puff used for putting on make-up.
No, that's fish cake.
Fish cake?
What's this?
Those popular healthy lunches for women?
What's the matter, Himeji?
I can't deny it any longer!
Why were you fine with lingerie and cosmetics but not with lunches!?
Oh? Are these your friends?
A mature beauty...
And her boobs are huge!
You're terrible, Yoshii.
I want my innocence back!
I have no idea what you guys are going on about.
Fine, I'll explain.
She's my sister.
Sister?!
Hello, I'm Akira Yoshii.
Thank you all very much for taking care of my useless little brother.
Please continue to do so.
Perfect! She's acting like a normal sister!
Thanks, Sis!
I'm Yuuji Sakamoto.
Kouta Tsuchiya.
Hello, I'm Hideyoshi Kinoshita.
People get confused easily, but I'm not a girl-
Trap
You're a guy, right?
You're the first person to ever figure out that I'm a guy!
Of course.
There's no way my dumb and ugly and useless brother would have any female friends.
I'm guessing these two are male too.
Don't be so rude!
You just screwed up everything!
All three of them are female!
No, I'm a guy.
Female?
When did you start bringing girls over?
You've been caught red-handed. Minus 200 points.
No!
We've brought trouble into your life, huh, Akihisa...?
Yuuji.
It's okay as long as he's the same sex.
Don't get the wrong idea!
Plus ten points.
That's not making me feel any better!
Akihisa, I'll help out with dinner since I barged in and all.
Thanks.
Me too.
I'll help as well.
We can handle it ourselves!
You girls should just sit down and take a break.
But...
Sis, take care of them.
Okay.
Do you want to look through our family albums?
Can we really?
I'll show you some really
embarrassing pictures of him.
Anything but that!
Saved.
So what are you going to make?
We can make paella with these ingredients.
I love paella.
Wait, did your sister know we were coming?
No way.
My sister's terrible at cooking.
She probably made a mistake and bought too much.
Looks amazing.
You made paella?
Huh? Didn't you buy the ingredients for it?
It looks really good, Aki.
You really could cook, Yoshii...
They saw it! They saw it!
He's always so boisterous.
Minus ten.
It's your fault! You always bully me!
You hate me, right?
No, I love you.
As a woman.
My life is over!
There's an ancient Japanese saying:
The dumber the kid, the cuter he is.
Give up, bro.
No one in this world can love you more than her.
That means I'm the dumbest person she knows!
I think Aki's the dumbest person in the world too!
Me too! I believe Yoshii is the dumbest person in the entire world!
Stop! Don't pour salt on my wounds!
He really is dumb.
No!
Okay, now that we're done eating, let's start studying.
If you guys don't mind, I'll help out.
Will you really?
I've recieved a teaching degree from the university on the side.
I think I'll be able to help.
On the side?
Boston in America.
Wait... Harvard!?
I see... That's a bit cliche.
What is that supposed to mean?!
Here, these are study guides.
I found six under the bed.
My top secrets!
That will be a 60 point deduction.
Akihisa's
allotted
points
Akihisa's
allotted
points
Ten points for one?
No, because you have no brother-sister incest porn.
You're kidding me!
Take these study guides.
No! They'll discover my fetishes!
It seems like Aki has an absurd interest in big breasted woman with ponytails.
All right, let's start studying.
Why are you putting your hair up, Mizuki!?
I thought it'd get in the way...
Just tie it into a bun!
Minami, stop it...
Why? Your hair won't get in the way like that, right?
Minus 100 points.
Why?
You'll understand when you grow up.
What's up, Voyeur?
Where are the other 1994?
You took me seriously, huh?
Good morning, Yoshii.
Morning, Aki.
Morning.
Himeji, you changed your hairstye?
Yeah, I wanted a different mood.
Minami, you had a boob job?
No! I woke up and it was like that!
Seriously?
I'm still going through puberty... it's natural!
I will not let you defile the sacred secondary sex characteristics.
I had fun yesterday.
We learned a lot as well.
I don't know if I'll be able to keep living on my own, though...
Why can't she just go back to America?
She's your family, you know.
You've got a great sister.
Not at all.
I mean, she goes from deducting
points to trying to make out with me...
She loves bullying me.
That's not true.
Your sister loves you very much.
You're saying she thinks I'm dumb?!
Your sister cares a great deal about you and how you're living.
That means you're really important to her.
Really?
What should I make tonight?
Well, she finally came back to Japan, so I guess Japanese food is appropriate...
I'm home.
Oh, welcome back, Aki.
I'll go buy ingredients for dinner.
Dinner?
Hang on, Aki.
What's up, sis?
Midterms are nearly here.
Do you really have time to cook?
Well, not really.
But you're back from America-
I told you, that's putting the carriage before the horse.
I came here to see how you were living,
but you're wasting time on me. That's no good.
If you don't make the cut, you'll blame me for it, and then where will we be?
That's why you don't need to cook for me.
All you need to do is study hard.
Just leave the cooking to-
What the hell?
The only thing you care about is that grade I get on my report card.
Have it your way, then!
I'm going to study.
I hate her...
That's why I'm going to score high and shut her up.
Good morning, Yoshii.
Morning, Aki.
Don't talk to me or I'm going to forget it all.
I see...
Okay, I'll leave you alone to study.
All right, get ready.
Begin!
Answer the following questions:
Let's do this!
Question one: In 334BC, the last king of the Achaemenid Empire was Alexander the Great...!
Next!
He must be testing right now.
I shall begin as well.
All right, I've answered all I can.
I'll check my answers in the time left.
Pens down.
Pass up your answer sheets.
Class
Number
Name
BC
Alexander the
Name
Alexander the Great
I'll miss living on my own.
...Really, Alexander the Great.
You put the answer to question #1 in the name field,
so all your answers were shifted up one.
Please call me by my real name!
All right, Darius the Third.
Please stop making fun of me!
If I had written the answers
correctly, I would have done well!
Do you think you can use that excuse if you make the same mistake in the placement exam?
I put in a lot of effort...
I told you already - effort is just a means to an end.
Okay.
She's so strict.
Man, it's messy...
Wait, she doesn't cook.
Half-cooked
Burnt
Forgot to
add saffron
Added detergents
Gooey
Too much salt
Tastes
Horrible
These are... failed paellas?
Could it be that she was practicing hard to make my favorite food?
Effort is nothing but a means to an end.
...being proud of the fact that you tried is just putting the carriage before the horse.
I really am an idiot.
Hey, sis.
Yes?
I want to thank you.
I love you too.
Huh?
As a brother, of course.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
That's unfortunate.
If I...
If I feel like it, I'll make you dinner.
Really?
Only if I feel like it.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Sis.
Yes?
Do you know what's the best spice?
The best spice?
I'm not good at cooking, so I wouldn't know.
What is it?
I wonder.
Question 10:
What's the name of the author who wrote Adolescent Detective Gang and Mystery Man of Twenty Faces?
The culprit is one of you!
No, not me.
Next episode: Mock Test and
Phantom Thief and Love Letter.
This will be on your test.