For all people, east to west, west to east,
tell a fortune and blow off steam.
Invocations
This is just one example of the invocations recited
when you begin divining, as I'm sure you know.
Today, you're going to memorize all of them for a test.
What?!
There are ten chapters and
a hundred verses for all of them!
There's no way we can memorize all of them!
I'm bad enough already with ancient words like these!
This exam is a tough hurdle
all Rank 10 Urara must overcome.
If you can't pass it,
you'll never become a full-fledged Urara.
Hurdle
You could say it's your first big hurdle.
I-it's alright. We can make it through this challenge!
Yeah, we can do it together!
Okay, let's work real hard!
Yeah.
Study hard for the test, everyone.
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
ONE DAY
UNTIL THE
INVOCATION
MEMORIZATION
TEST
"Humble, so humble, we b... beseech of thee."
I give up~
"Dost thy presence be made... as a water strider..."
Chiya and Nono broke down!
Seek to calm thyselves.
This is naught but a test all Urara must weather.
Verily, it is of no difficulty.
Kon broke down, too!
My, seems you're all working quite hard.
Nina-sensei!
But you're not the only ones who are hurting.
I haven't eaten at all today,
in an attempt to share your suffering.
Nina-sensei, would you like some?
Get a hold of yourself, Kon!
You too, Nina-sensei!
Don't skip out on eating!
Just tell us tricks on how to memorize them!
I'm not sure if I could.
I went through a lot of trouble
memorizing all of them, too!
I cut myself off from sweets, I sat under a waterfall,
and I stopped Saku's sword mid-swing!
What does any of this have to do
with memorizing phrases?!
So I'm painfully aware of your suffering right now!
Actually, I'd like you to suffer more!
Guess she likes suffering.
CHAPTER
Anyway, why do invocations use all these ancient words?
If they used cute words,
they'd be super easy to memorize!
Like what?
O suffering, confused, lost little lamb.
I will divine your path by the name of Miss Plum.
Eloim, eloim, essaim!
Howl, my grimoire!
Like that!
So embarrassing.
So hard to remember.
Come on!
Then what kind of invocation would you want?!
I think the old, traditional invocations are just fine.
Like "kokkuri, kokkuri, please come forth."
Hmph. How naive, Kon.
Wh-what?
We're living in an era where it's every Urara for herself!
You have to make yourself stand out from the crowd,
or you won't last long!
Kokkuri, kokkuri, welcome, Master!
Bark!
How's that?
How about no!
I-I'd like them to be a little easier to remember.
Right?! Make them shorter and easier, and way cooler!
Uh-huh.
Like what?
Crow like a rooster!
I think...
...that'd be hard for a human to pull off.
Come, now, put your mind to your studies.
I-I'm sorry!
You shouldn't make light of the sacred invocations.
Sacred? I thought the invocations were just wordplay.
My, you've got that all wrong, Koume-chan.
Urara borrow the power of a god to tell fortunes, right?
Invocations tell the god that you're going to tell a fortune.
They're special words that ask the god
the favor of borrowing their power.
I will now boil something within you.
Please lend me some soy sauce.
Like that?
Could you have used a
more divine object in your example?
The words you use for the invocation
aren't what's important.
What's important is to pour your heart into
expressing your feelings to the gods.
If you can do that, then you can use
whatever words or methods you like.
There are scores of different invocations
that Urara use today.
Really?
Oh! So then we don't need to memorize
from this book, right?
That's it for studying!
Memorizing the standard invocations
is part of the basics.
The basics are always important.
Alright, everyone, good luck on the exam tomorrow!
Ugh, I really don't feel like memorizing all of these.
But I feel a little better now.
If you talk to the gods, they'll understand you.
Thinking about that makes me wanna study!
I-I have a hard time talking to strangers...
Now we've got a new problem.
I never thought Nono'd be this shy with the gods, too.
Not being able to even recite the invocations
is a bigger problem than the test.
Okay! Let's all help Nono overcome her shyness!
Yeah!
Huh?! N-no!
U-um, you all have to study, too.
And, and... it's my problem, so...
I think it's a challenge I have to get through myself
if I'm going to mature!
It's caving in!
Nono's right.
It might seem mean, but even though
we're friends, we're rivals, too.
As Urara, we're going to face a lot more challenges,
and we have to get through them by ourselves.
I respect Nono's courage in tackling her personal issues.
Let's both work hard!
Kon-chan...
MEMORIZE!
And to be honest, we don't have a lot of time today
to be helping other people out.
Yeah.
I've gotta work hard, too.
But what should I do?
MEMORIZE!
Hito futa mi yo, itsu mu nana ya, kokono tari,
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
Furube yura yura to, furube yura...
Spring forth, cry out, O spirits...
I feel my exhaustion melting away!
Yeah, I'm getting kinda sleepy...
Kon! When did return to normal?!
S-sorry to start singing all of a sudden!
No, Nono, you're a really good singer.
What song was that?
I don't remember where it's from, but
looking at this invocation made me remember it.
It's an invocation that cures illness
and fills one with energy.
I read in a book that it's used as a lullaby, too.
I can see why.
Wake up, Chiya!
Oh, a lullaby?
...itsu mu nana ya, kokono tari...
Big Sister, what song is that?
I feel like I heard it before.
Oh, really?
It's a magic song that makes you feel better.
Mom and I sang it to you when you were little.
She sang it so you'd grow up healthy.
My mom sang this song to me when I was little.
Nono, your mom passed away, right...?
Yes, when I was just a baby.
That's why I don't have a lot of memories of her.
Somehow, I remember this song.
I bet your mom really loved you, Nono!
She put her heart into that song!
You were too little to understand what she was saying,
but you understood her feelings.
That's so nice!
Moms really are nice!
Yeah.
THE
NEXT
DAY
Okay, last up is you, Nono.
Chapter 5, verse 4,
the nightgown divination invocation.
R-right!
Please, tell me what I do not know
A child, tossing and turning to sleep
As a tempest of dreams tosses
and turns the mind in the dark
After an all-nighter, that angelic voice
is working way too well!
I can't take it anymore...
We're in the middle of an exam!
But tell me, Nono...
Why did you put the invocation to a song?
U-umm, I'm still nervous about talking to the gods,
but I feel like I can do it in a song.
I see. You've found your own personal way
of expressing your feelings.
Right, that means Chiya-chan and Koume-chan
will have to retake the test.
Go back through and memorize it properly.
Okay...
Big Sister?
What is it, Nono?
Umm, thank you for singing to me with Mom
when I was little.
I'm going to work hard and become a full-fledged Urara.
Just you watch, Nina-sensei!
Hey, Nina, sorry to barge in.
Is it okay if I have dinner h-
Wh-wh-what?! What happened?!
Don't ask.
Just stay with me till morning!
Huh?!
I'm happy that Nono's growing up so fast,
but I'm kinda sad!
But I also think I should work even harder as her teacher!
Okay, okay, I'll hear you out, just calm down!
Nono's invocation was beautiful.
I can't let her beat me!
Please, tell me what I do not know
A child, tossing and turning to sleep...
That's kinda different.
This way's cuter!
Ever since I was little,
I could always get what I wanted very easily.
Enchanté, mademoiselle!
But there was one thing I could never get...
The one I hate the most...
the one I love the most in the world.
Today's lesson is about witches.
Does everyone know what a witch is?
Yes, Ma'am!
Witches are fortune-tellers, and are also called healers.
You could say they're the Urara of the West!
They ride brooms and fly through the sky,
and some say they use magic to
put curses on people who anger them!
Excellent answer as always, Kon-chan.
You sure are worked up for this lesson!
O-oh, no...
I'd say that Koume is the most worked up
about this lesson out of all of us!
AUTHENTIC
ATTIRE
My, Koume, you really love witches, don't you?
L-LOVE?!
I-i-it's not like I love them or anything!
Hard to protest when you're dressed like that.
I-I mean, witches are cruel and glamorous,
and wicked and elegant,
and rebellious and shameless,
and intelligent and invincible,
so there's no way I'd love them!
Which is it?!
And I didn't read anything about witches
being like that. How do you know?
Well, because I've met a real one. A real witch.
Tell us about her! Tell us about the witch!
I wanna know, too!
W-well, fine.
Yay!
When I was five years old...
Koume.
This girl here is an exchange student from another land,
and she'll be living with us from now on.
She's from a far-off place called France.
Her name was Marie Quispilquette,
and she was the first foreigner I'd ever met.
And the first witch, too.
Nice to meet you, Prune.
"P-Prune"?
That's how we say "plum" in my country.
"Pu" for short!
Sh-she kissed me!
That was a cursed kiss.
It's how witches say hello!
Wh-wh-wh-what the heck?!
A curse?! What's going to happen to me?!
You're going to be really good friends with me!
And since I'm here, I might as well stay in Pu's room.
Yes, go right ahead.
Right, Koume?
S-sure.
What a cute room!
But it's not good for a witch.
There we go.
M-my room!
Gotta be black!
Even my bunny!
Welcome to the Witches' Sabbath.
We're gonna have a fun time!
It flew!
Well, you like it?
Marie, what are you?
I told you, I'm a witch.
I'm actually three hundred years old.
What?!
Witches live a really long time.
That's amazing! I thought you were thirty!
Don't be rude. I still look like I'm eighteen!
Why'd you lie about it?!
Hey, how can I be a witch?
I fried up a mermaid and ate it to get my powers.
Huh?!
If you're not going to eat it, then I will.
No!
Marie liked playing tricks.
She was crueler and a bigger liar than anyone.
What are you gonna do with those flowers?
Boil them and make a tea.
Chamomile helps you fall asleep,
and marigold is good for your skin.
Even if you can't see it with your eyes,
there are lots of things that have fantastic powers.
A witch draws out those powers.
Really...
I can do stuff like this, too.
She was smart and playful,
and cute and fashionable.
My young self was absolutely entranced by her.
Marie is awesome!
She can use magic!
Marie is just good at stage tricks.
I-it's real magic!
She's just playing with you, Koume.
Marie is a real witch!
I'm getting really mad!
My mom and dad won't believe me at all!
It's alright. It's just the way things are.
What?
I've gotta focus on my studies.
After all, I came to this country to study.
What are you studying?
Eastern magicks.
I'm traveling around the world on my broom
to learn about magic,
so I can be the most powerful witch in the world.
That's my dream.
The most powerful witch in the world?
But it's a secret, okay?
Witches can't be cool unless they're mysterious.
That's a lip-zipping spell.
If I show them your magic, they'll believe it!
They'll believe you're a real witch!
If I have Marie's broom, I should be able to fly.
It's for Marie!
It'll definitely fly!
Save me, Marie!
Huh?
You're braver than I thought.
But I think that's a bit too much mischief, Pu.
Marie...
Wow, it really does fly!
Of course it does. I'm a witch.
But you can't show magic to anyone
that doesn't believe in it.
That's why you have to keep it a secret.
If you don't, there'll be a lot of trouble.
Why? It's so cool...
This is why you're still my petit Prune.
I'm not petit!
For a while, I didn't understand what she meant.
A mysterious disease is spreading through the city?
EPIDEMIC
Disease Rapidly Spreading
Yes, and the doctors are giving up on treating it.
Let's hold back from leaving the house.
Excuse me, Madam,
but there's a rumor going around town,
that the witch staying with the Yukimi family
is what has brought this sickness upon us.
What? That's ridiculous!
Yes, but it's led to distrust in the Yukimi name...
It may end up affecting young Koume as well.
We do not doubt you in the slightest.
But for your sake, as well as ours,
it would be unwise for you to stay...
Yes, I understand, Sir.
I'll go back to France, for Prune's sake as well.
I'm sorry.
Don't look so blue.
I'm used to being treated as a nuisance.
No, no, no, no!
Why?! You didn't do anything wrong!
If you're going to France, then I wanna go, too!
I'll be your apprentice and learn how to be a witch!
Please, take me, too!
You know, becoming a witch isn't easy.
A crybaby like you could never be my apprentice.
I could!
I'd become a witch, and then
I'd curse everyone who's mean to you!
That's a pretty good idea!
Maybe you've got what it takes.
Really?!
Uh-huh. So...
...become the most powerful witch in this country.
If you do, I'll let you be my apprentice.
This is a cursed kiss.
A curse to give this little witch
lots of training and difficulties.
Take care, Mademoiselle Prune.
Marie...
And the witch went back to France.
I understand it now.
Marie wanted to tell me not to become a witch.
That's why she gave me the impossible task
of becoming the most powerful witch in this country.
But I won't do what she wants me to do. I won't give up.
That's why I came to Meirocho.
The most powerful witch in Meirocho...
...a Rank 1 Urara?
Oh, you want to be a Rank 1 Urara too, Koume?!
I was trying to keep it a secret!
Why are you even keeping that a secret?
Then it wouldn't be cool!
Koume-chan, everyone, listen.
Though they go by different names,
Urara and witches are one and the same.
They possess fantastic powers,
but they have their downsides as well.
Outside of Meirocho, Urara are viewed much differently.
Sometimes they're feared or ostracized.
Knowing all that, are you prepared
to continue your studies?
Of course!
I'm gonna be the most powerful Urara
in Meirocho- no, the whole country.
I'll help everyone and explain to them
that witches aren't evil at all!
Then I'll go to Marie with pride.
That's my dream!
C'mon, Koume, hurry up!
I-it's not gonna work, I know it won't!
I... I trust Koume-chan!
I feel like I can do it today!
Go! Go! Go!
I think we're definitely over the weight limit!
Here we go! Ready, go!
I realized something here in Meirocho.
If there's something you can't get,
you just have to reach out further...
Then, you might be able to reach it tomorrow.
It's okay to chase a dream
from which there's no turning back.
So you better be ready for me.
My strong, kind, beloved witch.
Ow!
I told you it wasn't going to work!
One more try!
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Forbidden Things are Sometimes Totally Naked"!
We can't tell fortunes,
but there's something we have to say!
Captain Saku is so brave!
"Forbidden Things are Sometimes Totally Naked"
Captain Saku is so cool!
That is all!