Partner, Aisaka Sayo.
Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
She transformed!
It's a cosplay card!
Sayo-chan, you're so cute! Yay!
Y-Yay!
Err... Um...
Asuna-san?
Is there... something wrong with me?
Are you sure you're a ghost?
Oh boy...
So, that's what it was...
Geez, Asuna-san.
This is the reality they are living in now.
Each girl from class 3-A has made provisional contracts, thus transforming Negi from a chupacabra back to his real form!
But, in the world they returned to, they find a Mahora Academy that has been turned to ruins!
Frankly, this plot twist won't get fixed so easily.
In a good way.
Is it in a good way, mya?
Huh!?
"There’s a Rising Commotion as to How Everyone Will Get Along in Unexpected Situations," by Mana.
“How Will Everyone Get Along?” by Zazie.
“15 Points,” by Mana.
Negi-sensei, um...
Aah! I'm sorry!
Want it?
Ah! Thank you, Ako-san.
So you get hungry after using magic, eh?
Eh? You get hungry when using magic?
Yeah. That's right.
Ahem. May I please continue?
Uh, yes! I'm sorry about that.
Negi-sensei, what's the meaning of this?
Why'd the school turn out like this?
Where have the other students disappeared to?
ASIDE FROM THAT, WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO US!?
Everyone!
Be quiet. Settle down, everyone.
Be quiet! Nothing's gonna change if we're all gonna be noisy!
Just calm down and listen!
Whoa, Asuna said something flat out!
What's THAT supposed to mean!?
Question! Negi-kun, is this the real world?
No. This is not reality.
It's the same as the last one.
This is an imitation world created by magic.
An imitation world...
That means...
Is the Mahora Academy in the real world okay, aru?
Yeah, it's fine.
Nothing has happened to the real world.
Whatever we do, we must keep pursuing the evil magic powers
...and continue to bear with it 'til the end in this dimension.
But we'll definitely get out!
We'll get back to the real world.
REALLY!?
Yep!
That's why, before that happens, everyone must help and work with each other and do your best!
Um, how long will that take?
That, I don't know.
In order for us to get back, we have to search for a way to get out of here.
Does that mean that
...it'll take years
...and become old ladies...?
NOOOOOOOOO!!!
Ah... If thats what you're worried about, you can calm down now, mah cheerleader sistas.
This is an additional reality.
Time doesn't move.
No matter what, years will never pass by.
REALLY!?
Yep. Ermines tell no tales.
So you're an ermine!?
Hey now, you three...
Yes, Yue-san?
About searching for a way out.
Can't Nodoka's magic encyclopedia help us?
Ah! That is right!
Desu!
Oh! Nice, Yue!
No way. After we used that we warped here instead.
Have you forgotten?
That's right...
We can't be using some half-assed magic to throw this world out of order.
We can't escape that easily.
You again...
Why are you making things seem like it's impossible?
Negi and Takahata-sensei both said that we can get out, didn't they?
I didn't say that we can't get out!
I just said that we can't get out easily!
That's the same thing!
No, it's not!
Asuna-san! Eva-san!
Oh well, let's ignore the two idiots.
Idiots!?
Hey! Don't pair me with her!
In any case, Negi-sensei...
Listen to us!
BE SILENT.
Next, what should we do?
Errr... Yes! Umm... That's right.
Next is this!
HUH!?
Chupa Tee?
Yep. Everyone who makes a provisional contract with Negi wears this.
Don't give me that! It's the law!
The law?
Yes. The law. It's been decided.
Does that mean we have to buy it?
Of course.
Alright! The T-shirts are on sale!
Rice Scooper!
Is it alright to leave it to them?
Isn't it alright?
Instead of just talking, they should think positively for ways to act.
They will go first and we can help out from behind.
Also, if any of their companions can't move, neither can we.
Yeah, that's true.
On that note, aren't you and Chachamaru going to make a provisional contract with Negi?
Is there a need to?
If we could, we would've transformed and lifted the curse.
Master is a vampire, and I am a robot.
We aren't compatible.
What do you mean? Did you forget?
Yeah, pretty much.
Seriously, you're so casual it pisses me off.
Enjoy.
I am honored to drink your well-prepared tea.
I feel the heart of Japan seep into the very fiber of my being!
We are the Exploration Group!
And I'm the leader!
Leave the investigations of the surrounding areas to us!
We are the Research Group!
And I, of course, am the leader.
We'll be in charge of planning and investigation.
We are the Lifestyle Group!
Looks like I'm the leader.
We'll do our best!
Well then, every team should discuss their next course of action.
Yes, Ma'am!
So where should we start exploring?
Let's see...
What's wrong, Asuna?
Where's Negi?
Eh?
Oh yeah...
He's not here...
Whats going on?
Maybe he went to the bathroom, de gozaru?
It's okay if it's just that, but...
Sorry, you guys go on without me!
A-Asuna!
Oneechan...
So, should we stop?
Yeah. Let's stop.
Is that right? Will they understand?
Yes.
What are we stopping, mya?
I do not know.
Eh?
Refusing someone’s request is against my instincts.
Get lost.
How 'bout that?
What's so bad about it?
Everything!
It's my fault...
Things turned out like this because of me...
Everyone has to suffer like this because of me...
...because I don't have any power!
Silly Negi.
Asuna-san...
That's not something you should trouble yourself with.
If you feel down, then help us escape from this magic world.
Okay?
Asuna-san.
That's right!
So Asuna does have a good side to her!
N-No I don't!
This isn't what it seems... errr.
What Asuna said is right.
We've gotta try out best!
That's right!
Let's try to find a way...
...to get out of here if it means one less day here,
Negi-sensei.
Konoka-san... Setsuna-san...
And also...
come with us for a while.
So these are the shards of the fairies, right?
Just one more piece and it'll form a shape.
Alright, let's check the reference books and see.
If the books prepared here can't help us, we'll go to the Library Island.
I wonder if Yamada-san is there.
Alright!
Preparations for the operation are okay!
Leave the scientific analysis of the shards to us!
The data organization will be done by Chisame-san.
We're counting on you!
Eh?
Err... Yeah! Okay! Okay!
"Chiu Chiu's Fantastic Drifting Diary"
Don't peek!
Being a net idol should be tough!
No! I am not a net idol!
Yeah, okay~
Listen to me!
Now then, everyone!
Begin second attempt!!
Everyone's working hard.
No one really thinks it's Negi-sensei's fault.
Alright. We still have the Exploration Group meeting.
Let's go, Konoka. Setsuna-san.
Everyone's still your partner.
We are all one team, Negi-kun!
Please don't forget that.
Even so, this is quite a mysterious world.
The plumbing is fine, and we can use electricity.
Because of magic!
Makie-san.
Did I say something strange?
And just like that, you never cease to question things.
That's why you fail at life.
Huh? I fail!?
There they go again.
Do I really fail at life?
Yes, you do. You are a failure!
You fail at being Sasaki Makie!
Oh boy...
Well, how are we gonna do this?
Hey, Chizuru.
Don't tell me you're sending text messages.
Yup! I tried contacting the police, but it didn't go through!
Police?
I was wondering what she was doing with all those "tac-tac" noises.
Chisame-san, what about the internet?
It's kind of obvious.
That's too bad, Chiu Chiu-chan.
I SAID I AM NOT HER!!!
Yeah, okay~
Listen to me!
Oh?
It looks like you can only send mail in this world!
Looks like there's a lot of stuff in here.
We've even got raw food.
I wonder if it's edible.
Milk!?
She smelled it!?
She drank it!?
It's fine.
REALLY!?
If we use all this, along with what Yuuna-san and the others find,
we'll be able to pull off some meals.
Viva Magic Worlds!
Mail?
I got a message on my phone!
Chizu-nee is saying random things again...
Oh! I found some more!
Your knowledge on survival is amazing, Ako!
Of course, I’m health conscious.
Is that so...?
Ako, how about this?
No.
Thought so...
Don't ask if you already know...
Hey guys! Check this out!
I never knew we had a well!
Huh...
Negi-kun.
Takamichi, there’s a spell I want you to teach me.
I thought place has turned into ruins, it doesn't seem so.
The city looks the same, aru.
I think it'd be easier if we started by taking a stroll around the nearby areas first.
We don't know what's out there so we should be careful.
We don't know how safe it is here, either.
No problem.
If you want a trap as a bodyguard, I've got some ready.
What the...
But this is a magic world...
so we don't know what's out there.
What if there are monsters around, desu?
That's not gonna happen!
Looks like we need traps after all...
Mana! We need even bigger ones!
Understood.
Just leave it to Mana.
70 points.
How very kind of you.
Oh, speaking of which, where is Asakura-san?
This is terrible! This is terrible!
Ah! Asakura-san!
Where were you?
You shouldn't go off when you feel like it.
Forget that; we're in trouble!
The fairy shards...
Meanwhile, a few minutes earlier...
Carbonic Acid, Calcium...
Magnesium Oxide, Silica...
Aluminium Oxide, Iron Oxide...
The ratios are different, but...
...its contents are almost the same as limestone.
Let's analyze the other pieces and see what we can find.
Alright!
Ah! Chao! It's hot!
Hot!
There! Ayaka!
Why did you attack it?
It was a reflex...
At that moment my athletic senses became sharper like never before!
I wonder if it got broken.
If its contents are the same as limestone, it should be quite brittle.
It looks like it went pretty deep in the pillar.
Becuase of some suprisingly stupid power.
Did you say something?
Alright! If we can't take it out quickly, let's kick it out of there!
Ha! That's a good idea!
Please hold on!
Negi-kun!
Breaking it would be dangerous.
I think it will be better to use magic here.
Please lend me some power, any one of you.
Negi...
Who?
Who are you talking about?
From here on we will be guided.
Guided?
Yes. This time we will use the appropriate power that you partners have.
Ras
tel
Ma
Scir
Magister
Those that vow to each other end the light...
Spirits of all creation,
I call on thine now to guide us.
Tel
Ma
Amoris!
It stopped at Sayo-chan!
I see, Sayo-san has this power.
Sayo-san, please lend me your power!
Okay! That is, if you're okay with it.
Partner: Aisaka Sayo.
Show me the power within you!
Contract, activate!
Negi...
Negi.
Neki?
Is there... something wrong with me?
Are you sure you're a ghost?
Oh boy...
So that's what it was.
Geez... Asuna-san.
Negi-kun, in any case...
Let's extract the fairy shard.
Okay.
Sayo-san, you're able to manipulate anything you possess.
Really?
Please possess that pilliar.
Alright! Understood! I will do my best!
Alright, Sayo-san, excuse me.
It tickles!
Aah! It moved!
I'm really sorry, please bear it for a while.
That tickles!
Just a little more.
Yes! I got it!
Alright!
That felt so ticklish...
Thank you very much, Sayo-san.
It's nothing. I'm glad my powers helped.
Itadakimasu!!
Thus, life in the magic world has begun!
Their faith in each other and the difficulties they face now may give birth to an ultimate power.
And so! Will they be able to safely escape the magic world?
Good luck, Negi!
When it comes to cheerleading...
...breathing and dancing...
...is your life!
Next time,
"Yesterday's Enemy is Today's Friend," by Misa!
"They're so friendly they quarrel," by Madoka!
"Disagreeing is also part of love," by Sakurako!
Ne
gi
ma!
Yay!!
God...
Yes?
God, I have a request.
What is it?
Buy a Chupa Tee.
Cheapo.