She who travels against the flow of time. Homura Akemi.
To change the past, you travel between any number of parallel worlds,
repeating this month until it plays out as you desire.
Your existence leads us to one question.
Why does Madoka Kaname have such extraordinary potential as a magical girl?
At this point, I have a hypothesis.
A magical girl's potential depends on the karmic burden she bears.
Madoka's burden is fit for a queen or a messiah, yet she lives a normal life.
Why karma weighs so heavily on her, I cannot understand.
But...
Well, Homura.
As you repeat time over and over, Madoka becomes a strong magical girl over and over, correct?
I knew it. It's because of you.
Put properly, it's a side effect of your magic.
What do you mean?
Your repetitions of time have only one goal: Madoka Kaname's well-being.
As time repeats over and over toward that goal,
you gathered world after parallel world together.
All centered around Madoka Kaname.
As a result, if the karma from each world builds up,
and weighs on the Madoka Kaname in this timeline...
She receives unrivaled magical power.
Each repetition of time connects to Madoka Kaname.
Everything that's occurred has lead up to it.
Excellent work, Homura. You've made Madoka into the ultimate witch.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 11 The only guidepost that remains
The body of Mitakihara Middle School eight-grader Sayaka Miki,
reported missing on the 22nd, was found in a hotel room early this morning.
No signs of foul play were detected,
so police are leaving open the possibility that the death was an accident.
And now the weather.
Tonight will be rainy with strong winds.
Welcome home.
Hey, Madoka.
You don't know anything about what happened to Sayaka, do you?
Sayaka and Kyoko are both dead...
It's certainly nothing you couldn't have expected.
The foreshadowing was all there.
Why are you being so casual about it!? Everyone died because of you!
Well, think of it this way. Do you feel any compunction about doing the same to livestock?
This about what happens to them before they end up on your table.
Stop it!
I don't understand that reaction.
If you think this is cruel, it's just because you can't see reality.
Chosen by humans, they survive without biological competition.
They breed freely, without regard to natural selection.
Cows, pigs, chickens...
Their life is far less harsh than that of wild animals.
It's an ideal symbiotic relationship for everyone involved.
Are you saying we're like livestock to you?
If you were livestock, we wouldn't meet you halfway.
It's an imperfect arrangement, but we recognize you as sentient lifeforms and are willing to bargain.
If you still can't believe it, then I'll show you.
The shared history of humans and Incubators.
We've supported your civilization since prehistoric times.
An uncountable number of girls have made contracts with Incubators,
had their hopes fulfilled, then drowned in despair.
Beginning with a prayer, ending with a curse...
This has been the unbroken cycle of magical girls.
As as it's progressed, we've led you through the stages of history.
Stop this!
Everyone's dead! They died because you betrayed them!
We didn't betray those girls.
Their own wishes did.
Any wish bound by logic can be twisted.
And it's only natural that this leads to the worst possible result.
If such an obvious conclusion is a betrayal, then they were wrong to wish in the first place.
But I can't call it foolish.
It's true that their sacrifices changed human history.
Those tears they said hardened into the roots of your modern life.
Once you accept that, can you really quibble over the fate of a few?
Didn't you feel anything while you were by their side?
Didn't you realize how badly they hurt?
If we could understand such things, we wouldn't have needed to come to this planet in the first place.
In our society only the sickest of the mentally ill display emotion.
That's why we were so amazed when we discovered humanity.
We never imagined an entire civilization with each of its members  carrying their own personal emotons.
If you hadn't come to this planet...
You'd still be living naked in caves.
It hurts to say goodbye to one of my students like this.
Yeah.
We don't know what's happening.
There's a missing ninth-grader too.
We're going nuts trying to figure out what's going on.
And no one knows what really happened?
Sayaka seemed like she was having a hard time. She was fighting with one of her friends over a boy...
This must be really hard on the other girl, too.
Normally it'd just wind up a bittersweet memory,
but with this happening...
The police look like they're just going to write her off as a runaway.
They don't have any leads to go on.
How's Madoka taking it?
I don't know.
I can't figure out what she's thinking.
But it doesn't seem like she's lying.
This is the first time I haven't been able to get inside her head.
I'm such a terrible mother...
Don't give up, Junko.
She's seemed different lately.
She's always sitting there alone thinking about something, but she never asks me for advice.
I think I could help her, but...
You know how kids that age are.
They grow up into young women while you're not looking.
You just need to believe in her.
Madoka needs some time alone to deal with what she's feeling.
We just need to give her a little while.
I just wish I could do something.
You're always like that, Junko.
Can I come in?
This is Walpurgisnacht, right?
Kyoko said there was a witch so powerful that she'd have to work with you to defeat it...
You've been preparing for it here, right?
Is the whole city in danger?
Unlike the other witches, Walpurgisnacht does not need to conceal itself behind a barrier.
Just by its manifestation, thousands will lose their lives.
So we have to beat it.
With Kyoko gone, you're the only magical girl who can fight it.
So...
I'll be fine alone.
Kyoko Sakura may have needed help, but I can defeat Walpurgisnacht alone.
I wouldn't have needed Kyoko's help.
I just wanted to let her save face.
Really!?
Why is this?
I want to believe you, but...
I don't want to think you're a liar, but...
I can't believe you'll be okay...
I can't believe what you're saying is true...
There's no way I can tell you what I'm really feeling.
Homura?
Because... Because I live in a different time than you, Madoka!
I came from the future.
I meet you over and over.
And just as many times, I watch you die.
How can I save you? How can I change your fate?
I start over again and again, searching for that answer...
That's...
You don't understand...
It just makes you feel sick, doesn't it!?
To you, I'm just a transfer student you met this month...
But to me...
To me, you're...
Jsut the time I spend with you, over and over...
There are no words for what I feel...
Even though I've lost my way...
Homura...
I will save you.
That was my first desire...
And now, it's the only guidepost that remains for me.
It's okay if you don't understand.
It's okay if I can't make you understand.
But please...
Please! Let me protect you!
The thunderclouds are shifting away from it, fast!
It looks like it's a supercell! Issue the evacuation orders!
Here it comes.
Are we going camping?
Yeah! We're all going camping together!
Homura...
This time...
I'll settle things!
What's wrong, Madoka?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Can Homura really win alone?
If I told you she couldn't, would you believe me?
Words simply won't suffice.
You should see it for yourself.
See how Homura Akemi fares in the face of Walpurgisnacht.
Why does she still fight?
She still clings to hope.
If worse comes to worst, Homura can reject this timeline and continue her battle in another.
Persistently, she repeats this meaningless battle.
To stop now is to admit defeat.
The moment she realizes it's impossible for her to change your fate,
Homura Akemi will drown in her despair and become a Grief Seed.
She understands this.
Thus, she has no choice.
Whether or not she can win, Homura must fight on.
As long as she has hope, there is no escape...
Yes. Just like all magical girls throughout history.
Madoka. You saw it too.
But...
But!
Hey, where are you going?
Mama...
I need to go save a friend.
Leave it to the firemen.
This is no time for amateurs to get involved.
It has to be me!
Other people care about you, you know!
Think about what'll happen to us!
I understand.
I love you and Papa too.
I understand how much you care for me, and I know I can't just sacrifice myself.
But this is different. I love everyone, and I care about them.
That's why I have to leave now!
You can't explain it, can you.
Then bring me along.
No.
You need to stay with Papa and Tatsuya and reassure them.
Mama, you said I was a good girl.
You said I didn't lie and didn't break the rules.
Can you believe in me now?
Can you believe I'm doing the right thing?
Don't mess up.
Don't let anyone trick you.
Thanks, Mama.
If it keeps going...
But I can't stop it here!
No!
Why?
Why!?
No matter how many times I try, I can't beat it!
If I turn back time...
Madoka's fate deepens...
In the end, all my effort...
It's okay.
Don't worry, Homura.
Madoka...
Wait! Madoka!
I'm sorry, Homura.
Illustration: Buriki
You say embracing hope is a mistake, but you're wrong.
No matter how many times you say so, I won't change my mind.
I'll insist. Forever.
Episode 12 My best friend
My best friend.