All right! Kaleido Star is about to start!
While you're watching Kaleido Star,
keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can!
Well, well, well. I've finally
bounced back, everyone!
You see, I remembered how fun that day was.
And I remembered my policy:
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, I'll be super lucky!
And if I'm gonna do it, I just gotta do it!
I'll walk straight through the middle of myself,
and become a real Kaleido Star! I will! I will!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
I'm sorry.
At this point even if you come back,
there's no place for you on stage.
Your contract's been terminated too.
That was the obvious choice for me to make.
Yes, I know.
If you let me come back, I'll do anything.
I won't ask to be paid, either.
I really do love Kaleido Stage. Please, Boss.
If you're that set on being an unpaid
gofer, I've got no reason to stop you.
Do what you want.
Thank you, Boss!
It's the same as the first time I came to
Kaleido Stage by myself, to do the audition.
A fresh start from zero.
That time, my dream was
to become a Kaleido Star,
but this time it's a show
everyone can enjoy, with no battles.
It might take time, but the path to being
a true star will open up for me too, I know it.
Tea or coffee?
She's asking you if you'd like some tea.
Forget the tea.
How about a stylish cocktail or...
What?
Um...
Oh, no thank you, I'm fine!
What are you doing?!
You're on a trip by yourself,
even though you're so young?
Hmm? Oh, yes. But I've got a
lot of friends in the United States.
Oh, really? That's nice.
Friends are so important, aren't they?
Yes! They're all my really,
really, really good friends!
That's right... I'm not starting from zero.
I've got everyone with me now.
"My Amazing Fresh Start."
Sora! Over here, over here!
Mr. Policeman!
Sora! Good to have you back!
Mr. Policeman, I can't breathe.
I just don't understand
young people these days...
Whoops, sorry about that. I was just so happy.
Thanks for coming to pick me up, Mr. Policeman!
Everyone's waiting for
you to get back home, Sora!
I can't wait to see everyone!
Mr. Policeman,
because of what happened I figured
out that I really, really love Kaleido Stage.
You should say that stuff in front
of everyone who's waiting for you.
Yeah, you're right.
Want some candy?
Sure, thanks.
You know, I want to create a Kaleido Stage
where the audience and
the cast can all have fun.
I like it when people smile.
That's my Sora!
Welcome back, Sora!
I... I'm home...
Sora!
Geez, Sora, I was really worried, you know!
I'm sorry, Rosetta.
I didn't know what I'd
do if you never came back.
Thank you for coming all
the way to Japan for me, Ken.
What?!
Ken! You went to Japan?
It wasn't just me. I was with Mr. Policeman.
No fair! Where are our Japan souvenirs?
Oh, that's right. Souvenirs, souvenirs...
For Miss Sarah, a Ninja Transformation Kit.
For Mia, a good-luck charm.
Oh, it's cute!
For Marion and Jonathan, hagoita paddles.
Cool!
For Ken, a globe.
Huh? A globe?
For Anna, a jester's mask and a slap fan.
Sora, this thing has kind of a scary face.
That's a Japanese lion.
A lion?
Hey, Marion, she says this is a lion!
Wow!
Sora, are you really okay now?
You're recovered and everything?
I'm sorry, I guess I made everyone worry.
But I'm okay now.
I won't lose sight of my dream anymore.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I wonder why I got a globe...
Something that's only useful two or
three times in a person's whole life...
Something you don't miss if it's gone...
To you, I give this!
You'll be the fool and I'll be
the straight man! This'll be great!
How many times have I told you
I'm not going to pair up with you?!
What? Why not?
Bloodlust! I sense bloodlust from someone!
You villain!
Huh?
May!
May?
I can't hear a word she's saying.
She's barking.
Wow, this glass is really soundproof.
Hey, she's coming this way.
Galaxy Warp Seven!
Congratulations on winning
the Circus Festival, May.
What are you doing here?!
May, stop it.
Even if her contract's been
terminated, Sora's one of us.
Can't you even say "welcome back"?
"Welcome back"?! Oh please.
You can't go onstage, and there's
not even a room for you in the dorm.
Huh? No room?
Uh, we were going to
explain that after the party...
Oh... I guess that makes sense...
It's okay. You'll be a guest in my room,
okay Sora?
It means this is no time
for you to be here partying.
Hurry up and go see the Boss already!
Hurry up and get him to
let you back on the stage!
Because in my book, the festival isn't over yet.
May...
So basically she wants Sora to be back onstage?
Then why didn't she just
come right out and say so?
I just want to beat you
fair and square, that's all!
Thank you, May.
But I'm fine with the way things are.
Huh?!
Sora?
What do you mean by that?
I've decided not to fight
battles anymore, no matter what.
You're saying... you don't
intend to go back onstage?
No, I haven't given up on the stage.
I definitely want to go back onstage someday.
But I don't want to do battle onstage.
I want to work with
everyone to create a fun show.
That's my dream right now.
Are you stupid?!
What do you think?
Yeah! It looks good on you!
Okay, Sora.
I'll be working for you all from now on.
Whenever you want anything
done, please just give me a yell!
Welcome onboard!
Good luck!
One minute to curtain!
Okay everybody, stay
on top of things today too!
Make especially sure you give it all
you've got during the Demon Spiral
and the scenes after that
with the two of us in them. Got it?
Got it!
None of you are fired up enough!
I really want Sora to go back onstage, though.
Got it!
Sora decided this for herself,
so let's support her.
Someone get this set piece!
Got it, got it, got it!
Sora!
That might've been a little too heavy for me.
Someone deliver these costumes quick!
Got it, got it, got it!
Sorry to make you do this, Sora.
No problem.
Take this one to passage 3B
and this one to passage 2C.
Okay, I got it!
It's Mr. Leon and May as Romeo and Juliet.
Right now, Kaleido Stage
belongs to May and Mr. Leon.
I'll leave the costumes here, okay?
Thanks, Sora.
I thought I prepared myself for that. But...
But in the end...
I'm jealous of May and the
applause she's being showered with.
I feel kinda bad for having you do this.
No, I'm having fun.
I'm getting to see lots of parts of
Kaleido Stage I didn't know about.
I want to know lots more about Kaleido Stage.
You really love Kaleido Stage, don't you Sora?
Of course!
I'm gonna fall in love with it more and more!
Leon, so this is where you were.
I told the people who messed up
the lighting today to be more careful.
Leon?
Sora.
Leon was watching Sora. Why?
Whoa, it's green.
It's Japanese tea.
Hmmm...
Well, well, well, I don't know
if you'll like it, but I hope so!
I'll drink it. I'll give it a try.
Please do.
It's bitter!
Once you get used to
this stuff, it's pretty good!
Sora...
To be honest, I don't really get
why you don't want to battle onstage.
I'm still proud of the time when I was aiming
to win consecutive world championships.
But according to you, is that a bad thing?
No, no, that's not what I think at all.
But...
Of course you're amazing,
and I think May was great
when she won the festival too.
I just figured out that those
weren't my dreams, that's all.
Is it okay if I dream of
being onstage with you, Sora?
Of course! I'm definitely
going to go back to the stage.
And a show with you?
I'd like to do that right now!
Sora...
Oh, if you want more tea I can...
Oh, no more.
La dadi dadi dadi dadi dadi dum.
The oats have made a good harvest.
La dadi dadi dadi.
The green peas have made a good harvest too.
Are there any bad children around?
Are there any sleepyheads around?
Good morning, Sora!
Fool, what are you doing?
You're the one who asked me to wake you
up quietly so Rosetta wouldn't wake up too.
That's right! I have cleaning
duty first thing in the morning!
Well then, I'll just cuddle
up with Rosetta and...
Ah!
Sora, I have something important to tell you!
It's Layla! Layla's coming!
I can't believe you, telling lies
about Miss Layla. That's so low!
No, I'm telling you, it's true!
I didn't manage to tell you before,
but according to my fortunetelling
Layla's constellation, Leo, is very close by!
Well, I'll tell you flat-out,
yesterday was boring.
It didn't make me feel a thing.
The individual stunts may be attention-grabbers,
but the thing as a whole isn't a coherent show.
Right, it's like a bunch of
one-man shows jumbled together.
Mia, let's hear your opinion as the director.
Mia, this is Cathy Timor.
She's a noted off-Broadway director.
Well, I'm just a layman
outside my area of expertise,
but I just gave you my honest feelings about it.
I... I'm sorry. I think
Miss Cathy is absolutely right.
But I wasn't able to do anything...
It's my fault. It's all
my fault. I'm very sorry!
Am I fired? I am fired, aren't I?
That's why Miss Cathy is here. I understand.
You're interesting.
You've got talent.
That I'll admit.
That... "Demon Spiral,"
wasn't that what it was called?
Making that work within Romeo
and Juliet, that's not a bad concept.
The character adaptations are chic too.
As a setup, I think it's quite good.
The problem is your directing ability.
Right now our attendance rate isn't dropping,
but the demographics of the
audience are drastically unbalanced.
I'd like your help correcting that trend.
I'll take on this job.
Okay! Now that that's settled, let's go, Mia!
Huh?
Don't "huh?" me. I'm an outsider here,
so it won't work if you're not there, will it?
Uh, right!
Ugh, that's no good at all!
Leon and May, your timing
wasn't in synch at all right there!
Why were you so off?
Oh, that's because in performance
May can't get very much height,
so when Mr. Leon compensates,
his maneuver ends up looking small,
so that's why it looks--
The audience doesn't care about stuff like that!
Leon, May, come here a minute!
Leon, I get that your skill is
amazing and everything, okay?
So show me something that
makes my heart pound more.
May, your performance in New York
made my blood thrum in my veins,
but what was with you just now?
Come on, a Romeo who's
satisfied as long as he's shining
and a Juliet who's terrified of being hated?
That's not going to get anyone excited!
Don't take your audience lightly!
Okay, take five!
She's cool...
Did you find her?
No, she's not anywhere.
I'm sure she said she had
cleaning duty this morning...
Miss Layla's here and everything!
There she is!
Hi everybody!
What are you doing?
Just what it looks like. I'm wiping the windows.
This part was a little smudged,
and it just started bugging me.
Never mind about that, Miss Layla is here!
Sora!
Wow, that surprised me.
Sora, hurry!
Someone from Broadway
named Cathy is with her too.
Miss Cathy too?
Oh... but at the festival...
I'm disappointed in you, Sora.
That's what she said to me,
so I don't know how to face Miss Layla.
Hey!
You're hesitating and stopping
short over every little thing!
And you call yourself Sora?!
The Sora I know tries it
rather than thinking about it.
Or do you mean to never see
Miss Layla again for your whole life?
Rosetta...
Let's go!
You might have a chance too, Sora!
Huh?
A chance to go back to the stage... But...
All right, play it back for us.
Yes, Miss.
See, even you can tell, can't you?
What's with this listless performance?
Like right here, for instance.
Can you show us that bit one more time?
Rewind about thirty seconds.
All right.
The two of you aren't trying
to look at each other at all.
There's never been a pair of lovers like this.
Rosetta, wait.
Oh, just come on!
I can just sneak a look and...
Oh, hello.
Sora, what are you doing?!
Oh, look, it is Sora!
Hey, would you come down here for a sec?
I want to see you do Juliet!
I know you're not contracted
anymore, but just give it a try!
Leon...
Well, Sora? You've gotten
your chance right away.
Sora, even if you want to avoid the battle,
it looks like the people around
you aren't going to let that happen.
Kalos won't complain. There's no problem!
Come on, what's the matter?
Come on, let's see it!
Let's see your Juliet!
I won't do it.
What?
Please continue with May as Juliet.
Don't make me laugh!
What do you mean, you don't want to battle?!
You're just running away
from the competition, that's all!
You coward!
May...
Sora.
Yes?
You should think carefully about how
much your attitude just now hurt May.
There are times when you can
hurt someone by not fighting too.
Good work today!
Yeah, you too!
Don't let what happened
today get to you too much, okay?
Yeah.
You cheer everyone up
just by being around, Sora.
Even if you're not onstage.
I think you can just do what you think is right.
Ken...
Thank you, Ken!
Hey, Ken, are you coming or what?
I'm coming!
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Right. Good work today!
Thank you, Ken.
Mr. Leon...
Leon?
Didn't you want to become my partner?
My dream is different now.
I think my goals are different from yours.
The idea of a stage without any
battling might be just a fantasy,
but no matter how hard it is,
I want to make that real!
What if I told you to become my partner?
Hey...
Let me go!
Mr. Leon, you're hurting me!
Are you the one?
Are you the one who can become my partner?
Mr. Leon, please stop it!
No! No, let me go!
You're the same as her...
Sophie!
Leon!
I can't breathe, Mr. Leon...
Mr. Leon?
Sophie... I'm so glad you're all right.
I'm Sora, Mr. Leon.
So you're the one after all, then?
Mr. Leon...
Why? Why did he call Sora "Sophie"?
Who's "Sophie"?
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation, I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
The person who can become
my partner is Sora Naegino.
And so, my goal is a stage without battles!
Sophie...
Don't make me laugh!
Unexpected happenings and accidents,
and a present that makes
me really, really happy!
I'm not wrong! I'm not! I'm not!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"An Amazingly Humiliating Performance."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...