Front Line Corp. NA Branch
Zoura here. What's your status?
Everything is going as planned.
Continue standing by.
All right, we're going to start charging now.
It'll be over soon, so bear with it.
And we're done!
Your maintenance results show no irregularities in your control system or power supply.
No problems with your mouth.
Good!
Now, if you'll excuse me...
Really though, your every nook and cranny is thoroughly maintained.
You must have a caring master.
I do!
He's a wonderful master!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Ann still isn't done?
It's not something you can rush.
Just read a magazine or something.
But places like this all have lame magazines.
This article looks like it was made for you!
What now?
"The forbidden putty buffing mod!"
"Your bust will increase by 10 mm!"
Hey, what're you trying to say?!
Exactly what the article says!
Well, here's an article made for you!
"Increases your calculation abilities!"
”Tuna Jellycan with DHA!"
That does sound good!
I'm so tired...
You've finally finished!
Any longer and we would've rusted away!
I'm sorry, but there's one more thing...
I still need to have X-rays done.
They make you drink that Radiocontrast Jellycan, right?
It's all white and gross.
Actually, they've started using new fruit-flavored Jellycans that go down easier.
I'm getting cherry flavor!
Really? I wanna get a sip, too!
You don't have any reason to!
I'm fine with drinking it...
it's just a pain to deal with on the way out.
Wouldn't have killed 'em to give your chaperones a checkup, too.
They can't do that.
We weren't manufactured by Front Line.
Oh, but if you just want to check sight, hearing, or voltage,
you can use the self-diagnosis corner here.
Ooh, that sounds like fun! I wanna try!
Come this way for your X-ray.
Please, don't delay.
Oh, coming!
Please refrain from vomiting.
All right, we'll turn your power off for a bit.
H-Huh? You will?
We'll be X-raying a sensitive area next,
so it's a precaution against any unwanted problems.
Okay...
Don't worry, it'll be over soon.
Umm, tuna, and then blow fish,
cod, skipjack tuna, sillago, sea bream...
Oh, how did the X-rays go?
No problems whatsoever.
The detailed report has been sent directly to your master,
so you're all free to go for today.
Hey, you doin' all right?
The maintenance left her a bit light-headed.
She should return to normal soon enough, so don't worry.
Huh? But...
Your scheduled maintenance is now complete.
That Nurse Shinki gave me the creeps!
Don't be so angry, Ines.
Nurses as aloof as her are popular with men.
Do we look like men to you?
That receptionist nurse was way nicer.
Geez.
Huh? What's this?
Halt. We must ask you to submit to a cavity search.
Huh?
What for?
This company is developing a new Shinki line, hence the heightened security.
We wouldn't steal or anything like... that...
Then this would be?
Oh no!
I forgot to return it!
You'll have to come with us.
Look, I just forgot to return it!
C'mon, lemme go!
Cooperate!
That's enough of that.
Did you not hear her say it was an accident?
Or do you wish to cross swords right here and now?
Ann...
Well that sucked.
You simply must be more careful, Ines.
You're the last person I want to hear that from.
But I can't help but wonder where she picked those lines up from.
Hey, how long are you gonna swing that sword around?
I have a question.
Who are you?
Huh? What kinda question's that?
I'm Lene, she's Ines—
Leneshe?
A Russian spy?
I'm stumped.
Ann's totally lost her marbles.
Is it due to her maintenance?
They couldn't have botched it this badly!
We can't take her back to Master like this.
Should we take her back for another checkup?
Huh? Back to those Security Shinkis and that Nurse Shinki?
Wait!
Wh-What are you doing that here for?
A soldier must keep her weapon in optimal condition for when it will be needed most.
Just as planned,
I've replaced the data of that Shinki's AI unit with the new model's during maintenance and sent her outside.
The target is an Arnval model.
There should also be an Altines and Altlene model with her.
Retrieve her ASAP.
Huh?
Where am...
Who are you?
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, it seems you're awake.
What's the meaning of this?
What happened to my X-rays?
Perhaps... you should go back to sleep!
What's wrong?
Um, I...
The Strarf that's under development!
Why are you here?
Catch her!
There's a bug in her AI, so watch out!
She's out of control!
Catch her so we can fix her!
Out of control?
No, I'm...
Status report!
We've got trouble.
I slipped up and allowed the Strarf model escape the building.
Her AI is that of the Arnval's, however.
I'm heading toward your position immediately.
No problem.
Actually, this is more convenient.
We'll take the contents of both of their AI units.
Why're we doin' this, too?
We have to.
Ann was wielding those scary weapons a bit too seriously,
and glared rather menacingly at us...
Anyway, it's sure gotten loud around here, huh?
An enemy attack.
I told you, stop waving that thing around or you'll poke an eye out!
Whoah, wait a sec!
Where're ya goin'?!
That's my body!
Excuse me!
Please excuse me, we need to talk!
Who are you?
A challenger wishing to do battle with me?
Very well, I shall accept.
No, I'm not.
I have no desire to fight you.
It's just... that's my body.
Your body?
Hey! Wait up, Ann!
Master will scold you if you pick a fight!
Ines!
Lene!
How do you know our names?
Who might you be?
It's me! Ann!
You nuts? Ann's right here.
Right, that's my body!
I don't quite follow.
Huh?
Is there any way I could make you believe that I'm Ann?
Well, Ann's right here, so probably not.
Ines, your chest was actually a defect.
Master told me that it was 1 mm smaller than the normal Altines models.
D-Don't say that out loud!
He knew about it before he registered you,
but he said to me, "it's not the size of the chest that matters."
It's not true!
It can't be!
Say something, Lene!
It's true...
Huh?
I was registered before you were, so I heard the whole story.
But the only ones who know about it are Master, me...
and Ann.
So they turned you off during the X-ray examination,
and when you woke up, you found you were in a different Shinki's body?
Yes.
Then that means your minds must have been switched!
Well, it explains why Ann started swingin' her sword around like a psycho.
Also, what've you been all antsy about?
I see...
This body was undergoing an X-ray examination, so...
Oh, you need to eject the photoreactive Jellycan.
B-But first...
why were the contents of our bodies exchanged?
I don't know.
Well, whatever the reason, we know what happened now,
all we need to do is just swap your AI unit data, and everything'll be back to normal!
Could we possibly do that here?
Do you know how?
The AI unit is an essential component that governs a Shinki's emotions and memories.
Mishandling it could cause the data to become irrecoverable.
Oh no!
I could lose all the memories I have with Master?
Oh, I see!
Found something?
If two people hold each other and fall down the stairs of a shrine,
Body-Swapping Stairs
they can apparently switch bodies!
You kiddin' me?
Regardless, it is not something we should do lightly.
We should return to the lab, explain the situation,
and have them revert us to—
As soon as possible!
There you are!
You wandered pretty far out.
I'm a Front Line doctor.
Due to a handling error, we swapped your AI unit data.
We apologize for the trouble.
The lab has all the equipment needed to return you to normal.
Thank goodness.
How the heck did this happen?
I shall explain the details later.
Now, this way.
Oh, I'll have to ask you two to stay put.
We'll be back shortly.
Um, where are we going?
We'll arrive shortly.
Look, it's right there.
Please enter that car.
It shouldn't be a long distance, so why a car?
Well, obviously...
it's so we can get our hands on the AI unit filled with Front Line's latest technological secrets
as well as the Shinki model they developed.
Oh yeah!
I knew something was weird!
She's no Front Line Shinki!
There they are!
Where are you taking them?!
Ines!
Right!
There!
Hello?
Please, stay with me!
We're...
inside a car?
Curses, I was careless.
What should we do?
If we don't switch back soon, Master will worry.
And we're going to Japan in a week...
Japan?
It's where my master was born.
He's lived in America a long time due to his father's work,
but he's going back to Japan for high school.
Ines, Lene and I are all going with him.
So we absolutely must return to Master!
Master, huh?
I see...
You haven't been shipped out yet, so you still don't have a master.
I am programmed only to serve my master absolutely.
But what is a "master"?
My master...
is kind, but still a bit clumsy.
He loves us all very much.
Oh, I should have a photo of him in my memory!
He is... your master?
Ann, you okay?
Are you in there?
Ines!
We're bustin' you out, Ann!
Allow me!
Ann, are you safe?
You will not intervene!
I shall assist you!
Halt.
One move, and I'll pierce her AI unit.
Now discard your weapons.
I said now!
I guess you don't care about this girl's precious memories of her master, then?
Now come.
I'll take that AI unit out of your head.
Playing sick won't fool me.
Now, then, we'll return the AI units to normal.
In the interest of protecting trade secrets, we'll need to erase the memories you had while in each other's bodies.
Please understand.
And we only just became friends...
I do not remember such an occurrence.
Well, can't blame them.
It's enough that we're able to return them to normal.
Oh, incidentally...
you both saw and heard plenty of things you shouldn't have,
so we'll need to erase a bit of your memories.
Huh? Why us?
Now then, we're beginning.
Okay.
Very well.
I'm so happy you saved me.
If we ever happen to meet again,
I'll be the one to save you.
Don't make such promises.
Even if we could meet again, we wouldn't remember each other.
Take care of your kind master.
I will.
I hope you find a wonderful master too, Strarf.
This is...
Hina!
We're back!
Good job picking out the spot.
Oh, it's in full bloom!
Is something wrong, Hina?
I remembered something.
What?
The cherry-flavored photoreactive fluid.
Cherry?
Huh?
Hina, I don't remember you getting maintenance.
Hina, you've been kinda weird since you got reset.
I see.
I may have been reset,
but perhaps it was the events of that day that brought my memories back.
What day?
The day may come when you will remember it too.
Oh, Master's here!
Master!
Sorry I'm late!
Geez Master, you're late again!
Sorry, sorry.
I couldn't find a good dumpling shop.
We already have plenty of dumplings!
But it is good that we could all meet again this way.
With Master as well.
Oh, what's up? Talking about something?
Nothing at all, Master.
Lene, don't drink the Nitro Jellycan!
It's awwright!
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign