I think this development has to be a sign that Biribiri's going to be the heroine!
You're...
Help me!
Are you telling me you'd separate it from its body for your own sake?
I have to see her, no matter what!
They're probably from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
It's okay. Leave everything to your sister.
Honestly, I half-assumed he was.
This evening, the ball's in my court.
I have to go.
I have to go get her back.
My sister can't do it.
It has to be...
It has to be me.
She wasn't there?
Yes.
The underlings said that she'd already left by the time they arrived.
You said the student who rents that room is Ryugamine, didn't you?
What about him?
They asked him some questions when he returned, and
they were going to bring him back should it come to that...
However, it seemed he had some friends with him...
His friends should have just come as well.
You're useless.
What shall we do?
Hello?
Is this Ms. Yagiri Namie?
Who might you be?
My name is...Ryugamine Mikado.
Shall we make a deal?
I'm hungry.
My...
Welcome, welcome!
Russian sushi?
It's good.
It's cheap!
"What is life?"
Hi, mister.
"What do people live for?"
Are you hungry?
We have some good ingredients today.
Or so someone asked me, and I beat him to within an inch of his life.
Oh yeah, it won't make you sick.
I see.
It might be different if he were some middle school dreamer,
but it should be a crime for an adult yakuza to say that, right?
I see.
Hey, Simon...you don't get what I'm saying, do you?
Yeah, you're right.
Have I changed?
I've lived in this town...
For twenty years...
They haven't been in vain.
Those twenty years you've lived here haven't been in vain.
Nothing will be in vain as long as you
make use of them during the rest of your life.
Make use of them?
How am I supposed to do that?!
For example...
You could marry me.
Shinra...
Are you Mikado?
You look much more docile than I'd imagined.
Or maybe that's the kind of kid you have to look out for these days?
Anyway, what's this deal you mentioned?
I have the person you've been looking for.
I see.
How much do you want?
I don't need any money.
Then what do you want?
The truth.
What did you just say?
I want you to admit what your brother did to Harima Mika...
...and what you two did to her body.
Sadly enough, I only have circumstantial evidence...
So I'll be straight with you.
Turn yourself in.
I see. That's the type of person you are.
Hm?
I won't forgive anyone who gets in the way of my brother.
I won't have it!
Anyone who gets in my brother's way...shouldn't exist.
I see.
That's how...this person is.
Hey, tell me.
Where's my sister?
I have to go.
The girl needs me.
I have to be with her!
Hey, tell me!
That's the reason?
That's the reason someone had to
die and have her body used that way?!
They're even targeting me...!
That's the reason you killed someone?
Are you trying to make Yagiri
miserable with your complacence?!
What're you saying?
If that's all you can say after growing up and stepping out into this world, then shut that unpleasant mouth of yours.
It's okay.
I may be sugar-coating things...
But so what if I am?!
Aren't you the one who can't understand
that you should repent for killing someone?!
You watch too many dramas.
Those are just promises and Leibniz's
pre-established harmony; we live in reality.
This isn't some epic poem.
This'll work, right?
You're no hero, either.
Know your place!
What's so bad about all that?!
Pre-established harmony, promises, and opportunism?!
I love forced happy endings!
What's so bad about wanting to have one?!
I won't say it's for the sake of humanity or the world...
I just want to see one!
I want to believe in them!
That's right. I believe.
I believe!
That everyone...definitely will...
It may be a trite idea...
But the fact that it's trite means
everybody's thinking about it that much!
Is that all you wanted to say?
I have neither the power nor the knowledge to
challenge someone who doesn't understand reason.
I don't even have the time to try.
That's why...
I'm relying on numbers!
What?!
That's amazing!
They're all part of this, right?
It's awesome!
It's like one of the paranormal phenomena in "Missing!"
Sir, you have mail. Sir, you have mail.
Would you like to try dying once?
We got it!
Are you serious?
Well then...
Togusa, I'm counting on you.
Yeah.
Let's do this.
Just how many of them are there?
Wow, I can't believe this many
people showed up for our first gathering!
These are...
The Dollars?!
Hey, Isaac!
What is it, Miria?
Are these people also part of The Dollars?
Yeah, that's right, Miria!
Alright now, listen up.
We're part of the most "now," the youngest, and the most talked-about—
What is this?
They couldn't all be...?!
No way. No way!
Look! It's a franchise!
But we've only just met!
Amazing!
The sky over my hometown was clear and vast.
But...
It was also empty.
When I was a kid, this town was filled with adventure.
When did it all change?
I wanted to change something.
But I had neither the will nor a reason to leave.
That's when it happened.
Twice...twice...
Various worlds unfolded for me there.
Worlds that I didn't know and couldn't reach...
I was able to talk with Kida again, even though he'd moved to Tokyo.
I made new friends as well.
One day, I suddenly thought of something.
At first, it was only a simple joke.
A group?
Yeah.
I heard there are a bunch of different groups in Tokyo.
You mean make a group on the Internet?
No, we'd actually...make one in real life.
It'd be based in Ikebukuro and we'd spread rumors about it online.
We wouldn't tell people we were in The Dollars.
We'd just say we heard about them from
someone else, and get our name out that way.
I even made a group site.
It was secured by a password.
We leaked the password via email and different message boards.
We fabricated a lot of member posts on message boards, too.
Of course, there were lots of people who didn't believe us.
But then, others started standing up for us...
And everyone was happy.
Seriously?!
Everyone believes it!
These people are idiots!
I did have a bad feeling about this.
People in real life started calling themselves Dollars.
That wasn't all.
The number of members kept increasing while we weren't paying attention.
Even though we'd stopped giving out the password...
It was like someone somewhere...
Was giving out the information.
Is everyone watching?
Heeeey!
They may have gotten scared...
But the people I created The Dollars with disappeared.
Yet I didn't quit.
No, I couldn't quit.
Even I don't know why, but...
That's not true.
There may be some bad people here.
However, there should be tons of people who aren't.
All we have to do is make
The Dollars into a good group, right?
We could do things that will get rid of our bad reputation.
Like pick up trash around town or erase graffiti...
And so, the residents are quite perplexed.
The graffiti on this wall was definitely here yesterday...
As you can see, it is now completely gone.
It seems unlikely that one person could have erased...
...this graffiti that took many people to paint it...
It couldn't be...
I left for Tokyo on Kida's invitation.
And there...
The Dollars?
I don't know much about them, either.
Anyway, it seems there are lots of them and they all have short tempers.
They're apparently a gang, but no one knows what color they are.
Don't approach them just out of curiosity.
Don't be unnecessarily inquisitive.
But the strongest people in town now are The Dollars, right?
So, what kind of group are these Dollars?
If I had to say, I guess they're "clearly colorless."
The Dollars? I know them.
Because I am one.
I got a girlfriend by joining The Dollars!
They write stupid stuff on message boards—
Someone always replies to your posts.
At this age, you can't form relationships with anybody outside of work.
Have you heard? The Dollars saved some people from human traffickers!
The Dollars are the strongest!
Not really. It's fun; isn't that enough?
This is much more fun than I thought it'd be.
This is fun, isn't it?
What?
What's going on?
Who are these people?!
Hey, where do you think The Dollars' founder is from?
Is there an Arabian oil tycoon here?
Doesn't look like it.
The person who sent us that response
is the true founder of The Dollars, right?
Uhh...or so I've heard...
Togusa, the light's red!
It's red! It's red!
The quiet type, huh?
Dotachin, Dotachin!
I told you not to call me that.
Someone responded to my post on The Dollars' message board.
Everything's in order.
I'll let you meet her.
In return, I'd like for you to cooperate with me as well.
Celty.
He's not here.
What're you spacing out for?!
Start looking for him!
Yes, ma'am. Move it!
Where'd he go?
Shit. Move it!
Out of my way.
I've had it!
Who said that?
I have no head!
I'm a monster!
I don't have a mouth with which to talk, or even
eyes with which to communicate my passion to others!
Do you hear something?
Where's it coming from?
So what if I don't?!
Celty...
I'm right here.
I definitely exist here.
Who the hell are you?!
You're—
Since I have no eyes, I'll show you all what I really am!
Die!
Listen as much as you want to the
screams of those who've seen a monster!
The...the headless rider...
The headless rider.
Who?
The headless rider?
I'm here.
I'm right here.
I'm right here!
I'm already crying out...crying out that...!
"I've been born right here and now!"
All so my existence can be etched upon this city!
So you're Ryugamine Mikado?
Celty...
Give Celty back to me!
That's right.
I found out a single truth in this town.
I'd been looking for something too common, too easy to find.
That boy will probably once again...
Next Time: Everything's Relative.