"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Sis, thanks for the meal today!
No, no, you're free to
have something like this!
That was tasty!
Right!
When the eggs are tasty, it
makes you feel kinda happy.
Oh!
The price of gas is up two
yen compared to yesterday...
I wish I had filled up yesterday.
Why are even generous people
picky down to each yen
concerning the price of gas?
"The Yonder Here"
You know, they're turning the book I
lent you the other day into a game.
Though I'm not going to buy the game.
Kagami, your information is so old.
I reserved the limited edition the
moment the info first came out.
I bought the DVD box set for the
anime and various goods as well.
Man, you've gotten hooked on
the series more than I have!
You can get hooked more than
the one who told you about it.
Sis Yui is the type that
buys a car like that,
based on influence from others.
A car?!
Yeah. When I lent her manga about races.
I really got surprised back then.
I'm scared of the energy
that hobbies can create!
The game last night made three wins in a row.
Yeah! It's the beginning of a miracle!
If they can keep winning like this,
What is she talking about?
the playoffs, even the
Japan Series, are in reach.
I believe it's about professional baseball.
This is an incomparable,
wonderful winning streak!
Our teacher is heavily into it.
Oh, speaking of baseball,
The famous poet Shiki Masaoka
apparently loved baseball.
I heard that he played catcher
until illness forced him to retire.
Playing upon his childhood name, Noboru,
he used as his poet's title the kanji
for baseball, and read it as "Noball."
By the way...
The winner of the Major Leagues is
called the World Champions, right?
I was reminded of it by the Japan Series.
Hm? Come to think of it, it's
only within the United States.
Well, start talking about "World"
after you defeat our team, I say!
Just kidding!
The center of the universe is in Chiba!
She's really getting worked up.
It's pretty smelly.
You're right.
Oh, there you are. Kagami! Miyuki-san!
Hey, Konata.
Show me how to do this problem!
This is unusual,
for you to be asking a
question about your studies.
Some of these problems are pretty hard, too.
Oh, that's because those are problems
for the quiz game at the arcade.
I'm not good at the general
education questions.
There you go again...
Or rather, why not put more effort
into your academic studies?
You've got entrance exams coming up.
I may be like that over here,
but over there I'm called a "Sage" and stuff.
Yeah, well, why don't you just enroll
yourself in that Whatsit Academy?
And so I'm a bit short on sleep.
How late were you up playing?
Miyuki-san, you always
go to sleep at 11, right?
Yes.
That's early, or rather...
"Kids that sleep, grow ★" I see...
And I thought stuff like that
as I was watching Miyuki-san,
but Yu-chan, you sleep a lot,
yet you haven't grown so much.
That's what Sis told me! I'm
concerned about it too...
"That night, around 9 PM"
Oh, pardon me for calling so late.
My name is Kobayakawa. Is
this the Iwasaki residence?
Oh, yes, I'd like to
speak with Minami-chan...
Oh, she's already asleep?
Did she always go to sleep this early?
♪ Pittan la la moji pittan! ♪
You're singing very happily there.
Yes, yes. Yes, somehow,
I think it's all right...
Oh, yes, I'll relay the
information to Dad as well.
Yes, after the ceremony. Yes, right, right.
Oh no, nothing of the sort...
No, seriously... I'm still a minor.
Really, that's not it,
it's nothing like that...
Yes, then... yes. Yes.
You know, Kagami...
Even if you gesture, the other
side's not going to see it.
I know that. I can't help it.
Come to think of it, with phone calls,
you concentrate on the conversation,
so you can't help but stop
playing games and stuff.
But for some reason, your hand
feels a bit lonely when it's idle.
I know how that feels.
So, as I was on the phone the other day,
I was using one of those rollers to get
rid of lint and stuff on the floor.
You know, the ones that you roll around.
Oh, you can get stuck in
a rut with that stuff.
Simple processes like meaningless doodles...
Yeah, but the instant the
phone conversation is over,
you lose motivation to
continue stuff like that.
But a floor where only one patch
is clean seems kind of sad...
You can just finish it.
The passion to continue ends
along with the conversation.
So you leave it alone in the end?
He's pretty smelly.
I think it's good once in a while...
Here. ___ky. Po___.
Oh, I did stuff like that back
when I was in grade school.
Really, are you still a child?
But, speaking about what you did as a child,
didn't you yell "Bread factory!"
While you stirred yogurt and stuff?
Bread factory?
What, never heard of it?
No.
Hey, what was that just now? A bread factory?
Don't be embarrassed, you
can say it right now.
Shut up!
That game I lent you during
the first trimester...
Someone else wants to
play it, so give it back.
Sure. You mean that little one?
Yeah. Come to think of it,
I lent her a couple too.
Guess I'll get them back now.
Still, you're amazing, Hiiragi...
How's that?
Well, I found a couple games the other day
that I don't remember who I borrowed from...
I'm amazed that you can keep track.
Hey, now.
There are a couple of mine that
I don't remember who I lent to.
Just how lazy are you?
No, I think "The Rule of Forgetting
the Lender" definitely applies.
This is the truth of the universe.
Of course there's no such thing!
Yes, hello?
Is that you, Hiiragi? It's me, Misao!
Yeah, yeah, what do you wa--
Dammit... You're pretty good, Po___mkin...
What is it? What's wrong?
No, no, it's nothing... Sorry, sorry.
So, what do you want?
Yeah, let's see...
Oh, what was it?
Like I'd know.
I think it was something important...
If it's important, don't forget it.
I checked the results for
the Autumn Jumbo Lottery,
but none of them were winning tickets.
After all, it's not all that
often that you get a winner.
I sent a lot of postcards too, but
I didn't win any prizes either.
I see, that's a shame.
If it's this hard to win,
I start to wonder if the
people who sell these things,
or the editors, are cheating...
Konata, you shouldn't doubt people like that!
It's no good. I guess I'll
go to sleep for today.
Before that, I guess I'll go to the bathroom.
They say I have too much personal talk,
but that doesn't matter at all!
I was so sleepy...
Why do I feel so awake after
cracking a stupid joke?
"Next day, late at night"
It's no good at night after all...
I don't need to go to the bathroom,
so I should go to sleep
while I'm feeling sleepy...
So cold!
I was so sleepy, too!
Why does the cold wake me up
the instant I get in my futon?
"And yet the next night, late at night"
I can't take it anymore.
It's warm tonight, so maybe
I can get to sleep soon.
For some reason, my feet feel really hot
and I can't get to sleep... Why?
Am I the only one that feels stuff like this?
Lucky Star!
It's gotten to be the season where
roasted sweet potatoes taste good!
No, Kagami, you know...
No, I know. I know, so don't say it.
Want to have some?
Thanks.
But you'll get fat, you know?
You ended up saying it after all.
But I can't help it, you know?
I made eye contact with the guy selling them.
You'd feel bad not buying any, right?
You know, those eyes that say to
you, "I hope she buys some..."
"I'd be hurt if she didn't buy any..."
Oh, well, I see what you mean.
At Comiket, it's hard to put a
book down if you make eye contact.
You know, when you talk, you never
care about getting your points across.
No, no, I'm talking about when I'm
browsing through various circles.
When you pick up a book
in front of the seller,
you feel bad about leaving for
another table without buying.
But you put it down all the same, right?
Yeah.
Lately, they've been adapting
more light novels into anime.
It seems that way.
The novel that I lent you the other day
has turned into an anime three times already.
I think the new volume
is coming out soon, too.
I saw the anime version, but I
haven't read the novel yet...
It tires me out because
it's so full of words.
That again?
The games that you play
are even wordier, right?
I think that's the case. It's so strange...
It would help if they released all
of those books in gal-game form.
Hey!
Aside from that, I wonder when the
fourth anime season is going to start.
Well, what? Is that some kind of plot device?
Yu-chan, what are you up to over there?
The lid... It always ends up crooked...
Well, there are people like that out there.
Those that are a bit awkward.
You do it often?
Here. These cute faults that you
have are so like Miyuki-san.
Thanks. Sis, you really are amazing.
Sis, what should I do? It won't open now...
Oh, no. I did it in the usual manner.
What a problematic child...
The bag won't open? Hand it to me.
Oh, Sis, thank you!
Huh?
Why don't we rip it from
the jagged edge to open it?
No, hold on... I'll open
it properly, so hold on!
Fire!
It's all right...
Why don't we use the jagged
edge, or open it with scissors?
No, there's something about my pride...
It feels like I've lost somehow!
Sis... Is that a mosquito?
It's a mosquito.
Doesn't it irritate you, just knowing
that it's somewhere around here?
Even if it hasn't done anything to you yet.
Now that I know it's here, I can't
help but to make sure it's down.
That is what you call hunter's instincts!
I just had a thought...
If Yu-chan or I were to be asked
out by someone in our grade,
would that mean that guy
has a Lolita complex?
You're in the same grade,
but if you were to argue
otherwise, you could...
In this case, appearance weighs
heavily on the decision.
For instance, what if she was 30 but
looked like she was in grade school?
On the other hand, in that case,
you could say that you favored older women...
That's a pretty deep theme there.
It's hard to determine the theory.
You really are my dad.
Kagami would end up saying something
like "I don't care which."
Then, Dad, what about you?
You fell in love with Mom,
who looked like that,
and love this daughter so much...
That means you have a Lolita
complex, right, Dad?
No, no, hold on, you're mistaken there.
I like normal girls, not just young girls.
"Sometimes I have a Lolita complex."
In other words, it depends on the character.
In either case, you're a good-for-nothing...
Then, you always get clingy with me, Dad,
but would you be acting the same
way even if I had been born a boy?
Of course!
Yeah, yeah. I've got it.
Aren't you glad I'm a girl?
Oh, what? I think the bath is ready now.
Why don't you go on ahead, Yu-chan?
Okay, then excuse me!
He shooed her away because he felt
bad about having her listen in!
Hey, Dad...
Mom was really short, and she
knew you all her life, Dad...
Isn't she like a gal-game character?
Isn't she? Kanata was really
cute since she was a child!
I know that you were head-over-heels for her,
but I wonder why Mom decided to marry you?
When I said, "Because you didn't look my way,
I ended up as the gal-game
loving guy that you see here!"
She went along with it...
You're the worst.
But it's the truth.
Isn't that extortion?
No, no, that's not all, of
course. You know that, right?
When you were born, Konata,
I was really happy.
Oh, this mole looks a little
like yours, Sou-kun.
No, no, she has your eyes, Kanata!
No matter how you look at
it, she's our daughter.
But I hope that she grows a
different way than either of us...
Not like my height, or
Sou-kun's personality...
That's harsh...
But why are you suddenly
talking about Kanata?
I don't know much about Mom.
Konata, are you lonely
without your mother around?
Not really. Dad, you alone
are rowdy enough for two,
and now Yu-chan is with us.
I see.
Kanata... Konata has grown
up into a wonderful girl...
Though she's a bit different from the
"Short and has maniac knowledge"
kind of normal you were hoping for.
Hey, Konata.
I beg of you, Konata, make
sure you don't die before me.
For now, I have no such intent.
All right.
Kanata passed away early in life,
but she laughed at the end,
saying that she was happy.
The ones that are left behind
are still a bit lonely,
but I'd like how I end my life
to be something like that.
Laughing? How would you like to die?
Let's see... I'd like to be "moe-d" to death.
Dad, I'm sure you'd never die a decent death.
That's right.
I bought a digital camera today
to use for work research...
It's been a while since I last came here...
You're persistent.
Come on... One more, okay?
I wonder what they are doing right about now.
I'm in the middle of a game!
Sure, sure! Say cheese!
Geez, Dad!
Okay! Let's go for one more!
You've had enough, right?
Dad, you're being too clingy.
You're so cold, Konata!
And here we are doing a memorial
photo shoot with the new camera!
I thought you said it was for reference?
Don't be so hard-headed, okay?
Geez... Sou-kun is still the same as ever...
One more shot.
That's right, you never worried much
about what others were thinking.
Get away!
Ouch! That's so cruel, Konata!
Take that!
Honestly... He hasn't changed one bit.
But, you know...
Holding you is more and more like
the feeling of holding Kanata...
It makes my heart race.
Don't make such dangerous statements
with your head held high!
Mom's troubles are such fond memories...
What?
Really...
Dad may be like that,
but don't you stray away
and become a problem child.
Oh, by the way, Konata. That
game from the other day,
when you finish it, tell
me how I can finish it too.
Sure.
It's much more difficult than I expected,
But seeing that they play games as a family,
though I'm sure I'm just choosing
the wrong answer somewhere.
I guess they're doing well together.
I can't quite get to the sex scene
with the character I'm going after.
Wait, hold on! What are you
making your daughter play?!
I wonder if she's all right?
Maybe your process of educating
her is mistaken, Sou-kun?
Hey, why did Mom pick you, Dad?
I mean, you're just a perverted
old otaku with a Lolita complex.
Normally, nobody would pick you.
You'd go that far in saying it?
You really are harsh...
Really.
But you know, Kanata was
a very perceptive person.
Really, you always act like this.
I always start to forget...
Maybe she saw through it all.
...why he was...
...that even a good- for-nothing like me...
...the one I decided to be with.
...had one thing that I could
be absolutely proud of.
The thing you were absolutely proud of?
What is that?
The fact that I love Kanata more
than anyone else in the world.
Oh, yes, that was it...
I really am no match for it.
"Rookie Awards recipient
information:" "No awards given"
He accepts everything
about me, good and bad...
He shows me everything
about him, good and bad.
The place where I can feel most at ease,
the place that lets me be most at ease...
Just kidding.
Now that we're feeling nostalgic,
I guess I'll go for another shot.
Let's get another shoot with Yu-chan too.
I regret a little that
I can't be right there.
That's enough... I mean,
that wasn't just one.
Come on... One more, okay?
Dad, you really bought that
as a hobby, didn't you?! Geez!
What are you talking about?
I just wanted to break it in before
I went on a research trip...
But, just like how you guys
are in my heart, Sou-kun,
I continue to live in your hearts...
I will continue to watch over you.
Oh, here goes! Okay, okay...
I hope that you guys, who gave me
much happiness, stay happy, Sou-kun.
I wonder if they'll be surprised by this.
Dad, this photo?
It looks like a human
shadow is in this photo...
A real ghost photo?
Huh?
The bath is open now!
Yu-chan!
Wait...
L-L-Look at this!
What's wrong?
We have to delete it! Delete it! It's cursed!
Stop! Don't delete it!
Maybe instead of deleting it, we
should cast it into a holy bonfire?
Don't throw it into a holy bonfire!
Now that she's talking a bit,
the way I see her has changed...
But still, I have the image
that Minarin is a bit scary.
Though she's actually really sweet?
Oh, she's come back.
Minami-chan, welcome back!
I'm back.
Those two really get along
well with each other...
So you were in charge of the class log today.
Was our teacher still
in the teacher's lounge?
Oh, this is...
Yutaka... Your tie is crooked, no?
My dear sister!
No, no! I'm seeing friends
in this light again!
Maybe I'm feeling a bit tense.
Lucky Star!
3, 2, 1, okay... it's rolling.
So, have you found him?
Oh, he's not around? Anywhere?
You can't find the manager, either?
He's gotten away, dammit...
Well, in either case, they're fired.
In the first place, I thought that this show
Um... it's rolling...
was somehow dangerous to
start with, and yet...
I had said no at first.
Well, I can't win against a political power,
or due to an adult's reasoning...
Um...
Um, it's rolling.
Huh? What's rolling? Me,
or you, or the Earth?
No, not that.
Oh, then what?
As I've been saying, the camera is rolling...
Idiot! Stop it!
Isono! Isono! What is it, Nakajima?
Now, we'll have you listen up.
This time, we have a medley version!
1, 2, 3, 4!
"1. Legend of Lovely Minoru"
"2. Something I've Forgotten"
"3. Hare Hare Yukai"
"4. The Lifestyle of a Man"
"5. Take It! The Sailor Suit"
"6. Song of Shikaidar"
"7. My Dear Santa Monica"
"1. Legend of Lovely Minoru"
"2. Something I've Forgotten"
"3. Hare Hare Yukai"
"4. The Lifestyle of a Man"
"5. Take It! The Sailor Suit"
"6. Song of Shikaidar"
"7. My Dear Santa Monica"
"1. Legend of Lovely Minoru"
"2. Something I've Forgotten"
"3. Hare Hare Yukai"
"5. Take It! The Sailor Suit"
"6. Song of Shikaidar"
"7. My Dear Santa Monica"
"1. Legend of Lovely Minoru"
"6. Song of Shikaidar"
"7. My Dear Santa Monica"
"1. Legend of Lovely Minoru"
"6. Song of Shikaidar"
"2. Something I've Forgotten"
You didn't change even
when we blew the whistle!
Shikaidar really got a lot of airtime.
Why is that? We were telling
you to change the song.
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Soujirou here.
Kanata here.
Then, Sou-kun, I'll be going soon.
Are you going to go?
Yes.
Take me with you.
I still can't separate
my spirit from my body,
but I'm sure I can learn.
Sou-kun, you're still talking
about anime and manga...
Then, see you later.
No, Kanata!
Next episode: Delicate Line.
Sou-kun, the currents are
unstable, so I can't fly well!
Come on...