My apologies for the wait.
I have been rather busy this evening.
I don't blame you, given the situation.
Covering all that up will be difficult.
Well...
The work this time is too much for the Church to handle.
We are using any help we can get.
Now then, priest...
What will your decision on my request be?
Regarding the reward offered for the defeat of Caster...
Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
Thank goodness...
Now, once I get the Command Spell for defeating Caster, Diarmuid and I will be wholly connected.
My right hand's... gone!
My right hand...
My right hand!
I can't call Diarmuid without it...
I won't be able to make him protect me!
My right hand...
My right hand. My right hand. My right hand!
My right hand!
Hand...
My hand...
I have secured Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri in the new town.
I cut off her right arm, detaching her Command Spells.
Good.
Get out of there quickly.
Lancer will be returning soon.
Roger.
I saved Matou Kariya...
Without a doubt, he could threaten my master.
There are no excuses for this.
It's an act of rebellion.
But... what is this?
It's not regret...
Is this excitement that I feel?
It's true that Servant Lancer played an important role
in the defeat of Caster, as verified by eyewitness reports.
I have the right to receive one of the Command Spells, then?
Well...
Lord Kayneth Archibald.
I don't know if I can consider
you to be a Master at this point.
Lancer is jointly bound by contract to me and Sola-Ui, my fiancée.
And isn't Lady Sola-Ui the one who's currently
providing the mana and holding the Command Spells?
That's true.
I have temporarily given her the Command Spells.
However, the rights of the contract still lie with me.
To begin with, the declaration of being a Master was submitted to the Church in my own name.
Very well.
I recognize your right to the reward.
Now, Lord Kayneth...
Hold out your hand.
Take this, all of you, and drink from it.
This is the cup of my blood, shed for
all of you so that your sins may be forgiven.
It is the blood of contract!
I hope you will continue to fight nobly as a Master.
Yes, of course.
I only have a single Command Spell.
My situation remains dire.
Thus, I absolutely cannot allow the other
Masters to acquire additional Command Spells!
Lady Sola-Ui!
You incompetent fool!
You're useless and all talk!
You couldn't even protect a single woman?
That's some fine chivalry right there!
I am extremely sorry.
A temporary substitute she may be, but it doesn't change that fact that you failed to protect your own Master!
What good are you as a Servant?
I'm amazed you had the nerve to return here alone!
I am afraid, my lord, that Lady Sola-Ui
and I never had a proper contract.
We could not sense each other's presence.
That's all the more reason to be extra careful!
But my lord, Lady Sola-Ui still lives.
She continues to supply me with mana.
So what?!
Who cares about that when you can't even discern
her location because you're not properly her Servant?!
Sola-Ui, I shouldn't have given you those Command Spells.
I could not dissuade her.
I share the responsibility.
You actually have the nerve to say that?
Don't try to fool me, Lancer.
You were the one who incited Sola-Ui.
Never! I swear!
It's just like in the legend.
Are you truly incapable of being near your lord's fiancée without attempting to seduce her?
My lord, please retract those words.
Did I offend you?
You say you'll do wonderful things like swear me eternal loyalty,
but then you turn around and give in to lust like a beast!
Lord Kayneth...
Why?
Why won't you understand?
I...
I only wish to act honorably.
I simply desire to fight in a noble battle by your side.
Don't speak to me like that, Servant!
Know your place.
You're merely a ghost incarnated through magic!
You dare to lecture your lord?
How ridiculously absurd!
You don't like what I'm saying?
Use that precious honor of yours
to resist my Command Spell, then.
Oh, but you can't!
You Servants are mere puppets, and this is how things work.
Lord Kayneth...
My lord.
What?
You still have something to say to me?
No, that isn't it.
Something is approaching.
It's just as Kiritsugu said.
There are traces of a magical field.
But it's strange...
Maybe it hasn't been properly
maintained, but it's about to fall...
...apart...
I did not expect you to come here, Saber.
My...
My ally found this place and informed me.
He claimed this was your location.
Would you happen to have any idea
where my lord's fiancée is, Saber?
I do not.
What of it?
It's nothing. Forget it.
At any rate, are you sure about this, Saber?
You did not come here to chat, I'm sure.
But after using that technique on Caster,
you must have expended quite a lot of energy.
No more than the other Servants.
None of them will be doing any more fighting tonight.
They will focus on defense.
That is why we won't need to
worry about getting interrupted.
The dawn approaches,
but I believe this may be the
best night to finish our battle.
What do you think, Lancer?
Saber.
The only thing that still grants my
heart peace is your pure fighting spirit.
Her attacks lack strength.
Saber, you...
You won't use your left hand?
Don't get the wrong idea, Lancer.
If I use my left hand here, the shame of doing so will surely dull my blade.
It would be a fatal mistake to make against your spear.
Saber...
Therefore, Diarmuid...
This is the best strategy I can use to defeat you.
Pride rests on the blade of chivalry!
I...
I am glad to have met you!
I am Diarmuid O'Dyna,
first spear of the Knights of Fianna.
Here I come!
Splendid!
I, Arturia Pendragon,
King of Britain, accept your challenge.
Come!
Why can't he win?
And if he doesn't have a good chance of winning, he should be escaping with his Master!
Our highest priority right now is to rescue Sola-Ui...
But he can't even understand that?!
That useless Servant...
Him, of all people?
This is...
...a Self-Geas Scroll.
A magical item used by Magi to form an unbreakable contract.
Binding Spell...
Affected Party: Emiya Kiritsugu.
The Emiya family crest orders the following:
The pledge is to be observed by the affected party
upon fulfillment of the conditions described herein.
Pledge:
Kiritsugu, son of Norikata and the fifth descendant of the house of Emiya,
will be forever forbidden from
harming, or intending to harm,
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri.
Condition...
The curse of a Geas theoretically
cannot be removed by any means.
Even if you forfeit your life, as long as your magic crest exists, it will bind your soul even in death.
If I carry out what's written here, he cannot kill me.
However...
Under these conditions, my fight...
...will end here.
The Grail...
...and the pride of the Archibald family...
He wants me to throw it all away?
Sola-Ui...
Use your remaining Command Spells
to force your Servant to commit suicide.
The condition has been fulfilled.
Do all of you really want...
...to win that badly?
You all want the Grail that desperately?!
You'd crush the only wish I hold in my heart...
Do none of you feel any shame at all?!
I won't forgive you.
I won't forgive any of you for this!
All of you monsters who'd disregard a knight's honor for personal gain...
Let my blood taint your dreams!
Let the Grail be cursed.
Let the wish it grants bring disaster!
And when you fall into the pits of hell...
Remember the rage of Diarmuid!
The Geas binds you now, correct?
Yes, it's in effect.
I cannot kill either of you.
Not personally, anyway.
Kill me...
Please kill me...
Sorry.
The contract forbids me to do so.
Emiya Kiritsugu...
I finally understand what a fiend you are.
I was a fool to believe that although
our paths differed, our goal was mutual.
Up until now, I had faith in Irisviel's words,
and thus I did not doubt your character.
But now, I simply cannot believe that a man
like you would use the Grail to save the world.
Answer me, Kiritsugu!
What do you truly want the Grail for?
Even if it is my sword that wins the Grail...
If it means that I must yield it to you, I...
Answer her, Kiritsugu.
This time, you owe her an explanation.
Come to think of it, this is the first time you've seen how I do my killing, Iri.
If all you do is kill a Master, his Servant
might make a contract with another Master.
That's why I had to eliminate both
Master and Servant simultaneously.
Come on, Kiritsugu.
Speak to Saber, not me.
She needs to hear your words.
No.
Honor and glory...
There's no point in speaking to a
killer who takes pride in such things.
You would insult chivalry to my face, fiend?!
Knights cannot save the world.
They call certain methods of fighting good and others evil,
acting as if there were some nobility to the battlefield.
Such illusions, perpetrated by heroes throughout history,
have led countless young men to their bloody deaths, all for the sake of this valor and glory.
They are not illusions!
Even the taking of life, as a human act, must have laws and ideals.
Otherwise, every war would bring hell to this world!
And there you go.
You heard her, Iri.
Our Heroic Spirit here thinks the
battlefield is something better than hell.
What a joke.
It's hell itself.
There's no hope on the battlefield.
It has nothing but unspeakable despair.
Just a crime we call victory,
paid for by the pain of the defeated.
Yet humanity has never recognized this truth.
And the reason for that is, in every era,
a dazzling hero has blinded people with their legends
and prevented them from seeing the evil of bloodshed.
The true nature of humanity has not
advanced a step beyond the Stone Age.
Then, Kiritsugu...
Is your hatred for Heroic Spirits the reason why you force Saber to endure such humiliation?
Of course not.
I don't allow private feelings to interfere.
I will win the Holy Grail and save the world.
I am simply waging that battle using the
most appropriate methods at my disposal.
Righteousness cannot save the world.
I care nothing for it.
Kiritsugu, do you understand?
If you do evil out of a hatred for evil,
that rage and hate will merely birth new conflict.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
I don't know what betrayed you and caused you to fall into such despair in the past.
But your rage and sorrow are found
only in those who once sought justice.
Kiritsugu.
In youth, deep down, you must've
wanted to become a champion of justice.
You believed in a hero to save the world.
You desired it more than anyone.
Am I wrong?
I will end this ceaseless cycle.
The Grail will make that possible.
I'll make sure the blood I spill in Fuyuki
is the last blood humanity will ever shed.
Even if that means bearing all the world's evil, I don't care.
If it will save the world, I'll do it gladly.
Kiritsugu's gone, hasn't he?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!
Episode 16
Terminus of Honor
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
We can't allow this!
An alliance? Now?
Let me tell you the truth behind the Holy Grail War.
We'll accept his invitation.
Please die, so his dream can become a reality.
Such a boring ending.
Goodbye, Father.
Next Episode
The Eighth Contract