This is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to real persons, groups or events is purely coincidental.
Yes, that's right!
When I put on a classical music record, our shiitake mushrooms
started growing at an amazing speed!
Really?
I heard that electricity from artificial lightning makes them grow even more.
Electricity?
Yeah. The mushrooms feel threatened by the strong electric current,
so their filaments start growing rapidly to leave descendants behind.
Just shut up and do your homework.
A helicopter, huh?
That reminds me of Ogi. He liked helicopters.
Today is a real mess, but I get over it with a sigh
You get the idea, right?
What do you wanna do?
You act as if nothing happened
As if your heart didn't ache
It almost feels encouraging,
the way you're rushing me
Hold it and let it overflow
We're all imperfect
I can't see it well in the light,
but if we can change our future selves
Wake up and run
Go and surpass the mirage
Try to change and run
with the discomfort of freedom
We can reach that shining light
Follow it into the present
Don't hesitate to act
Deep or quick, just keep breathing
Hyouka
Ogi? You mean Ogi Takahiro from class 2-B?
Does the Sun Shine on the Peaks?
Who's that supposed to be?
I told you, he's in class 2-B.
I'm talking about an Ogi you don't know.
He was our English teacher in junior high.
You know, right, Satoshi?
Of course I know Mr. Ogi. But I didn't know he liked helicopters.
I thought everyone knew he loved them.
Did you know, Ibara?
Nope.
That's weird.
How come I know but they don't?
We've been together since Kaburaya Junior High,
and Ibara and I have been in the same class all along as well.
There's no way she wouldn't know.
So what about this Mr. Ogi?
Well... Ibara, don't you remember?
That time when a helicopter flew over Kaburaya Junior High.
A few dozen times as I recall, but yeah.
One of those times, Ogi rushed to the window in the middle of class to look at the sky.
He kept watching until the helicopter disappeared into the distance.
He just smiled and said something like, "Oh, I love helicopters,"
by way of explanation when he resumed class.
Yeah, now that you've described it in detail, I remember there being something like that.
Was that Ogi?
It was.
I'm glad my memory wasn't just playing tricks on me.
That's weird.
It might be weird, but it happened all the same.
But what about when that squadron of JSDF helicopters flew by?
That was quite a sight,
but I don't recall Ogi reacting like that.
What's a squadron?
A group of aircraft.
How did you know it was the JSDF?
Can you think of any other helicopters that would fly in formation?
And you're sure Ogi was there at the time?
Pretty much.
I remember I looked up the word AGM in my English dictionary when I saw the helicopters.
AGM?
What's that?
It's short for "air-to-ground missile".
But yeah, if something like that had happened,
surely Ogi would be out on the grounds dancing with joy.
Well, I doubt he'd actually be dancing.
It was a figure of speech.
So it was Mr. Ogi who was so happy about seeing that helicopter.
But then, it must've been not long after we entered junior high.
Now that you mention it, I thought, "There are some weird teachers in this school".
Fuku's right, though. I don't recall seeing him ever take notice of a helicopter since then.
Three years ago, huh? My memory's vague.
But now that I think about it, I don't remember Ogi doing the same thing ever again.
There are legends about him with way more impact, though.
The Mr. Ogi Menace!
Now you're just making stuff up.
No, it's the truth! Ogi told us himself.
He said... Well, I have some doubts myself,
and you probably wouldn't even believe me if I told you,
but it could well be possible.
Spit it out already.
He said that in his life so far,
he's been struck by lightning three times!
Lightning? You mean lightning, lightning?
Yeah. Thunder!
Three times... It's amazing he's still in one piece.
It wouldn't have been much fun-der!
Even Chitanda's figured out how to handle Satoshi.
He wasn't directly hit, but he wasn't unhurt either.
He said he passed out once, and he has burn marks on his body too.
But he's still alive, so he's quite lucky it wasn't worse.
That's true.
I don't remember any apparent scars though.
Struck by lightning...
Three times?
Is that even possible?
Kamiyama doesn't get many lightning strikes to begin with,
and yet you say Ogi got hit three times alone?
It doesn't seem like Satoshi would be lying.
He even said straight out that he didn't make it up.
Truth
Lie
But then, was Ogi lying?
Truth
Lie
It's too obvious a lie to really be one.
Wait a moment.
Satoshi, there were some old newspapers in the public library, right?
Yeah. A few.
There are a few in the school's library too.
Though only for articles related to Kami High.
That won't do.
I'm going home.
I'll drop by the library. You coming too?
Houtarou... it looks like Houtarou is actually serious about this!
No! I just... How should I put it...
Can't stop thinking about it.
Houtarou! You're Houtarou, right?
That Oreki Houtarou who's always saving energy, right?
Are you being controlled by aliens?
Or were you possessed by Chitanda?
Cut it out!
Oreki...
You should go home soon.
Go to bed early and tuck yourself in under a warm blanket.
I'm sure you'll be right as rain by tomorrow.
You're being rude!
Is it that unusual for me to be doing something out of my own free will?
Whatever. Let's just get this over with already.
Oreki!
What?
You can't stop thinking about it?
Kinda.
Are you going to investigate it?
I might not be able to find anything.
I can't stop thinking about that!
Wh... What?
There's something in this world that can tickle even your curiosity!
I can't stop thinking about what that could be!
She isn't exactly polite either.
Satoshi said he had homework and couldn't come.
Having the assistant librarian Ibara around would've been helpful,
but I couldn't bring myself to ask her.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Should we get going, then?
You go ahead.
You can ride on the back.
Nope.
Not a chance.
Please just go ahead.
Okay then.
Chitanda!
Yes?
If there's a way to search old articles,
look for the name Ogi Masakiyo.
It's written as, "a small tree, true and pure". Ogi Masakiyo.
Okay. See you later then.
As shadows grow and the air cools,
pearl strings of dew appear.
Cold Dew
Hyouka
According to my sister, who's been to the Kamikakiuchi mountains,
those 3000 meter high peaks cut off even the flow of the air,
so the weather on this side and the other side is totally different.
I shouldn't make Chitanda wait too long.
Kamiyama
City Library
Oreki!
I've found something about Mr Ogi!
"Cleaning the passes across the Kamikakiuchi mountains."
Mr. Ogi was a mountaineer.
On the 26th, the Kamiyama rangers organized
the cleaning of a path on the Abumi cliff.
Eleven people, including volunteers, took part in
picking up trash near the mountain path.
The leader of the Kamiyama rangers, Ogi Masakiyo (39) said:
"Due to the mountaineering boom, there are many people who don't know the basic rules."
"I want to make it clear that when you're in the mountains, it's a matter of life and death."
I see. So I was right.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Could you search through all the old papers?
You can see for yourself at the second floor counter.
I'd prefer it if my predictions ended up being wrong this time...
Excuse me. We'd like to search for some newspaper articles.
All right. What are you looking for?
Articles from three years ago, between March and May.
Any particular keywords?
Look for "accident", please.
There are twelve results. Would you like to refine the search?
That's not too many. Can we see them all?
Sure, go on.
Ongoing accidents among 60-70 year old people
Accident in Alaska - 5 dead
7 doctors suffer accident
Life: Ten years since the accident
Kamikakiuchi accidents, the most casualties yet: 11 wounded, 2 dead
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in Alaska - 5 dead
7 doctors suffer accident
Life: Ten years since the accident
Kamikakiuchi accidents, the most casualties yet: 11 wounded, 2 dead
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
7 doctors suffer accident
Life: Ten years since the accident
Kamikakiuchi accidents, the most casualties yet: 11 wounded, 2 dead
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
Guidebook to prevent accidents in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Life: Ten years since the accident
Kamikakiuchi accidents, the most casualties yet: 11 wounded, 2 dead
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
Guidebook to prevent accidents in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in North America, 8 dead, 2 unconscious
Kamikakiuchi accidents, the most casualties yet: 11 wounded, 2 dead
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
Guidebook to prevent accidents in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in North America, 8 dead, 2 unconscious
Mountain accident: 8 missing, also 4 veteran mountaineers
Kamikakiuchi accident victim saved by helicopter
Man fell in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
Guidebook to prevent accidents in the Kamikakiuchi mountains
Accident in North America, 8 dead, 2 unconscious
Mountain accident: 8 missing, also 4 veteran mountaineers
Found it.
Accident in the Kamikakiuchi mts - search in progress
It's from May 9th, right?
Excuse me, could we read these articles?
Chitanda's on to it too.
Maruto, could you help for a moment?
What's it?
We'd like to see newspaper articles from May 9th, three years ago.
Three years ago?
Sure, be right back.
Thank you very much.
Ah, it'll probably take about half an hour to get the articles. Is that okay?
Sure.
I'll let you know when it's done.
Thank you.
Oreki, now that we're here, want to have a look around?
I guess we could.
Ah, it's a Taira-no-Kiyomori special this time.
The cover's so pretty!
In this special he's portrayed as the son of the Shirakawa emperor.
There are people who believe that he is.
Whoa, nice one.
It's the Itsukushima shrine at Miyajima. I'd like to go there one day.
Vegetables Made Exciting
Look at all the cabbages!
They're such a nice color!
And there's so many tomatoes!
They all look so delicious!
That reminds me, Oreki! Our shiitake harvest was quite good this year.
Would you like some?
Look! Books about bugs, Oreki!
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
A Bee's Life
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
Honeybee Journal
Yamamoto Chiyoko
Dung Beetles
This one's about dung beetles.
They're so cute!
Why did you pick that one?
Is there anything you'd like to see, Oreki?
Famous Castles of
Japan
Well...
Wow, isn't that castle huge? It's majestic.
Your home's quite big too.
Not quite this big.
Maybe just a little bigger than average.
What exactly do you define as average?
Any luck?
They're in this file. Please take a look through it.
Thank you very much.
Whoa, it's heavy.
There's quite a few.
This is the newspaper from May 9th!
This is probably the day on which Ogi said he loved helicopters.
Two Kamiyama rangers in accident
There.
So... what does this mean?
It means that Ogi had no particular love for helicopters.
It's probably true that Ogi's been struck by lightning three times,
but can you imagine that happening to an English teacher in this town?
That's true.
So I thought,
what if he often goes somewhere with lots of lightning strikes?
Up in the mountains, right?
Is that what you guessed?
Kind of.
I thought, what if he wasn't just a teacher, but a mountaineer as well?
I came here to make sure.
Why would Ogi have paid special attention to that helicopter on that day?
Because it must've had some special significance.
Ogi was waiting for a helicopter to fly by.
Which means?
He must've been very nervous as to whether or not the helicopter would fly out.
That's why he rushed to the window the moment he heard the noise.
An English teacher being worried about a helicopter doesn't mean much.
But if he was a mountaineer as well, that's a whole different story.
Kamiyama is bordered by the Kamikakiuchi mountains,
A mountaineer from the city was worried about a helicopter.
It could've been for aerial photography, transporting supplies, or...
Or?
An emergency.
...sudden change in weather for the worse...
An emergency...
This article says that on the 8th, the weather was so bad that helicopters couldn't fly.
Yeah...
Ogi was worried about whether the prefectural police helicopter would fly over us.
Even during class, he had the weather conditions in the Kamikakiuchi mountains on his mind.
If helicopters were able to fly, that meant the weather had improved.
And if the weather had improved, the victims of the accident had a much greater chance of survival.
I wonder how he must have felt at the time.
I don't know how he felt, but I think I saw him smile.
We had a look through the papers from the next few days too.
The bodies of the two victims of the accident were found.
And it was the prefectural police helicopter that found them.
Um...
Hm?
Can I ask you a question?
Go on.
Why did you get so interested in this?
Is it so strange for me to want to look something up myself?
Well, yeah. I was thinking it wasn't like you at all.
I guess. After all, I don't usually do anything I don't have to.
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Damn, she just straight-out ignored my cool motto.
You can work hard for other people's sakes.
You've helped me a bunch of times as well.
This is a terrible misunderstanding you have here.
But you don't really care about yourself, right?
Then why did you bother confirming your own hunch today?
Sorry,
but I can't stop thinking about it!
When I heard the lightning story from Satoshi, I had a bad feeling.
Yes, you said that.
So, I wanted to check if my intuition was correct.
That's why I went to the library to investigate.
It would've been different if it'd needed a week-long investigation or something,
but looking through old newspapers isn't a big deal.
I even had help.
If my hunch was right, we'd need to be careful.
Careful?
If something like that had happened, Ogi couldn't just say he loved helicopters that easily.
Unless he was really that insensitive. It's best to be careful with people like that.
Was it that difficult to understand?
Insensitive as in,
he has no idea how other people are feeling.
Though I'll probably never meet him again,
so it's not much of a concern.
Oreki!
That's... so...
I can't put in words...
What's she trying to say?
If she can't put it in words, she wouldn't be able to tell me even if I asked.
All right, let's call it a day.
Thanks for your help.
You're welcome.
I'm glad I could see an unexpected side of you.
Give me a break.
Sorry...
See you tomorrow!
It'll be totally dark by the time she gets home.
She came along of her own free will. I didn't ask her to.
But still...
I guess I owe her one.
The situation is unscientific
A montage of emotions
Who's calling who?
You look away when our eyes are about to meet
I can feel it
Am I just imagining things? It's so cold of you
It takes talent to read minds
You know
I wanna know
Don't you?
I'll fix the fire of youth in your heart while I can
If we can do it today why leave it for tomorrow
I want to solve your mystery
Look for the back of the boy, burdened with secrets
Even today
You are a fantasy and I'm drawn to you
This growing curiosity
There's no twist in the story
I can't stop thinking about it
It's so interesting
But why?
Next time: Those Whom It May Concern.
Those Whom It May Concern