Not this...
Or this...
How cute!
Haruka!
What's wrong?
Big news!
The author of The Princess of Flowers,
Mochizuki Yume, is coming to Dreamy Shore!
The Princess of Flowers?
That book is my bible...
I've wanted to be the Princess of Flowers since I was a kid!
I can really meet its author?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
The Secret Behind the Story!
What is a True Princess?
50th
Anniversary
Art Exhibit
~The Realm of Dreams~
Mochizuki Yume (Author) Book Signing
Where: Dreamy Shore Picture Book Museum
"Mochizuki Yume Book Signing..."
It's true!
Mrs. Mochizuki hasn't made a single public appearance since this book's publication all those years ago.
And yet she's here at Dreamy Shore!
What do we do?
The Princess of Flowers was that princess Haruka dreamed of becoming, right?
Yeah!
I'm also a fan of Mrs. Mochizuki's work!
Your dream was to write picture books, right?
Yeah!
That can only mean...
That we've gotta see her!
Yeah!
So you let yet another Key fall into the hands of the Princess Precures.
Yes.
And how do you explain this?
Considering Twilight accompanied you...
It seems I've let these games continue for too long.
But worry not, Mother.
The Precures shall face defeat at
my own hands when next we meet.
Princess Twilight, you would go alone?
If so, then take this.
I look forward to your battle.
Very well.
I love the country air!
50th
Anniversary
Art Exhibit
~The Realm of Dreams~
Mochizuki Yume (Author) Book Signing
Where: Dreamy Shore Picture Book Museum
She's popular!
I'm surprised such an old book still has so many fans.
That's the beauty of picture books!
Encountering a picture book at a young age can change your whole life!
It sounds like a worthwhile line of work.
It is!
It's splendid!
What's The Princess of Flowers about?
If you want to know, well...
Long ago, there was a kind, castle-born princess who was surrounded by flowers and loved by all.
Her beaming face made both flowers and smiles bloom around her.
But one day...
A bird jealous of the princess's popularity lied to her that the neighboring kingdom's prince came to meet her
and took her deep into a terrifying witch's forest.
But she didn't fear the witch or blame the bird for lying.
After witnessing her grace, the bird reflected on his actions and saved the princess himself.
Once they returned, the bird apologized in tears for what he'd done over and over again.
She can't just let him off the hook!
Maybe...
but the princess did.
She thanked the bird for saving her,
told him to smile, and forgave him with a grin.
And when the bird smiled along with her...
the witch's scary forest turned into a beautiful meadow.
Finally, the princess and all of her friends continued their journey.
What a splendid story!
Such grace!
But there's one thing I always wondered.
Since the princess continued her travels without meeting the prince, the story never properly ended.
That's why I want to ask the author why she never wrote one.
Haruka, we've gotta hurry!
Everyone's lined up over there for the signing!
O-Okay!
We'll be able to meet Mrs. Mochizuki right around that corner!
Yeah. I can't stop shaking!
We've gotta relax!
I never thought I'd be able to meet the author!
What's she like?
Oh, I'm so nervous!
She's on edge.
I can't blame her.
It's time!
Next in line, please.
O-Okay!
It's her...
She's the creator of The Princess of Flowers...
Oh my.
Bonjour.
B-B-B-B-Bonjour!
U-U-Um...
P-Please sign this!
My, you must have read this quite a bit.
Y-Yeah!
Thank you.
U-Um...
I really love The Princess of Flowers!
I want to be just like the princess, so uh...
So like, I want to learn more about her, and...
Does the Princess of Flowers ever meet her prince?
How does it end for her?
I'm sorry, but I can't answer that question.
I don't intend to write an ending to this story.
Mrs. Mochizuki!
Why did you say you wouldn't write an ending?
Because there were so many children who read that book.
I first wrote The Princess of Flowers for my own daughter.
I wanted her to grow up to be like a princess.
Of course, I wanted to write an ending at first,
but after reading feedback the children wrote to me, I changed my mind.
Everyone imagined the princess's future in their own way.
The future my daughter imagined was a splendidly happy ending.
Stories are born from imagination,
so I felt it best to let my book nurture that.
I'm certain you have a future you'd like to see for the princess as well, no?
Well, I...
That Princess of Flowers belongs to nobody but you.
My own... Princess of Flowers?
No matter how beautiful it may be, fiction is but fiction.
To a true princess such as I, it is but vacuous nonsense.
Twilight!
O, pitiful paupers parading as princesses...
I shall put you in your place.
Yui!
Mrs. Mochizuki!
Now...
Let the banquet begin.
French braid!
Despair born from sealing these
plebeians' dreams provides energy.
Being of use to me is far more fulfilling for them than being stuck in those frames.
Turn them back to normal!
You should watch your tongue.
We'll protect the book!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go! Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its frigid frame...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
If you fools know not how to behave in the presence of nobility...
then I shall teach you the errors of your ways by force!
Play the melody of despair!
You are first, Cure Mermaid.
Your elegance and decorum are above par...
but you can't surpass me!
Mermaid!
Even such radiant talent is but
stardust in my wake, Cure Twinkle.
Do the flames of despair burn?
I'm certain you all regret playing princess by now.
Including you, Cure Flora.
Especially you, Cure Flora.
Peasants like you who lacks both faculty and finesse...
tarnish the title of "princess."
Those of nobility are bestowed with it upon birth.
I am the daughter of the ruler of woe, Dyspear.
I am Dysdark's black princess.
And you are nothing.
It's over. Your dreams shall vanish into ether.
We won't let you!
We shall defend our dreams!
Yeah!
That despair energy of yours won't work on us!
Yeah! No matter what you say...
we're the Princess Precures!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Rose!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dance, O roses!
Precure!
Rose Tourbillon!
You impostors!
We're not impostors! Our dreams are—
Princesses are one of a kind, like me!
Struggle to become one all you like...
but you never will!
Give that back!
Yet I pity you.
You'd have never encountered your futile dream if not for this drivel.
Allow me to open your eyes.
Stop it!
Twilight, you may be the better princess.
I knew from the day we met that
you fit the definition to the letter.
But after listening to Mrs. Mochizuki, I feel there's something more.
Princesses may share a title, but we all have our own princess inside!
I do too!
I learned that I have my own princess to become!
Flora...
Your own princess?
What nonsense!
That's my ideal!
The strength to not fear a witch!
The grace to have mercy on others!
And the inner beauty to make the world bloom!
Like the Princess of Flowers whom I've always admired!
That's the princess I want to be!
It's Flora's Miracle Dress Up Key!
So it was here the whole time...
Another new Key?!
Forfeit it at once!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
You're uniting with the Key's power!
You can beat Twilight!
Do you think you've won?
Your dreams shall fade to dust!
I'll become my own princess!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Lily!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
I... lost?
Me?!
Cure Flora.
I shall never accept you!
I am the only princess!
You did it!
I can't believe you really beat Twilight!
Yeah.
I see... strength, grace, and beauty.
The Princess of Flowers and the Grand Princess are one and the same.
Becoming a Grand Princess will bring me closer to my dream.
Principal...
Why did you choose to hold an exhibit now?
I wanted to use my brush to nurture the future of our children.
I thought Noble Academy's 50th anniversary was a fitting date.
Our first years are all such splendid students, too.
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Oh no, we can't go outside!
But we can have plenty of fun inside the dorm!
How about a scavenger hunt?
Oh, yes!
Solve the riddles to find the treasure!
Let's compete to find it first!
I won't lose! But what's the treasure?
Go! Princess Precure:
Found It!
The Treasure Inside the Dorm!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Fukuoka Prefecture - Hiroki (Age 7)
Hyougo Prefecture - Miyu (Age 6)