Dear Mr. Junichi Katsuragi,
I understand how you probably feel right now. Even if you're right about the way things are, we should still stand up for ourselves. I've decided to form a publishing company, joining forces with a few of our comrades. I would like you to see it as a new weapon in this old and tired battle. I hope you will join me in this endeavor. I want to talk to you about it, face to face.
- Arita
Arita
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
A Christmas party?!
And we're all invited?
Of course. It's next Sunday.
We'll be there!
If it's an Olympus party, does that mean you'll play for us?
Well, if you have a request...
Hey, Ritsu, are you going to the Christmas party?
Nishimi invited you, right?
I'm not really with their group, so I'll pass.
Sorry, I can't make it. There's a Christmas party at the church that day.
Then Kawabuchi can't make it either?
Yeah.
We should've checked first...
Maruo. If it's okay with you, I think I would like to go.
Really?!
Of course! You're always welcome!
I never thought you'd say yes, Nishimi.
It'll be better to put some distance between us like this, little by little.
Surely...
Hey!
You're late, Richie-baby!
H-Hey there.
All right! Next up is the Spiders!
What about the Beatles?!
Let's do some "Bang Bang Bang!"
Nishimi, want some cider?
Sure.
Feigning innocence, bang bang bang!
Bang bang, bababababababa-bang!
He's somebody I just can't beat!
Come on, Nishimi, let's sing together!
I don't really know pop songs like this...
Bang bang, bababababababa-bang!
I wonder what he's doing right now...
Maybe he's talking to her at church?
I go to a party alone and all I do is think about those two...
I'm such a fool...
Kaoru?
Ritsu...
What're you doing here? Shouldn't you be at church?
Yeah.
The church's Christmas party is over.
He isn't here with you?
Should he be?
Um... He went home with the little ones.
I see...
It's cold, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey, come on!
Gotcha babe!
Come to think of it, his birthday's coming up, isn't it?
I hope you finish in time.
Why?
Why do you say things like that?
You're wrong!
This is for...
Forget it! You're such an idiot, Kaoru!
What did I do this time?
I don't even know.
Women are just impossible.
Why did I lose my temper like that?
I'm the one who rejected him in the first place.
Even if I finished this, there's no way I'd be able to give it to him.
I'm so relieved.
You're in the clear for now Yurika,
but let me tell you something...
I know.
You're going to tell me not to see him, right?
You don't have to keep repeating yourself.
Chet!
No!
Sentaro?
What're you doing here?
How do you mean? I've been waiting for you.
W-What's with the formality?
Ri'ko...
I'm sorry.
I never realized how you felt 'til now.
I've said some pretty dumb things and probably hurt you...
I'm sorry. But... Well, how can I put it?
But about your feelings, I, well...
C'mon, Sentaro, why are you suddenly on your best behavior?
Stop it already. This isn't a mafia movie.
Did I get it wrong?
Yeah.
You got it wrong.
O-Oh, a misunderstanding. Sorry for talkin' all weird...
R-Right! We're like family. You made me nervous for a second there...
Wh-What a relief, then.
We're like family, so I couldn't stand the thought of hurtin' you.
I'm glad to hear it now, and not back then.
What's that mean?
I'm never gonna tell a blockhead like you.
There's something I have to tell you.
I'm going back to Tokyo soon.
I probably won't
see you again...
One of the guys from college
is starting up his own publishing company and he wants me to help out.
I plan on leaving right after New Year's.
It's taken me a long time to get to this point,
but I owe it to you for making me think I should give it a shot.
I'm grateful.
"I don't want to hear you say that, you idiot.
Please don't leave me..."
I could never say something like that.
Not when he's trying so hard to move forward.
Ritsuko!
Yurika!
W-What are you doing?
Looking for something.
I threw something away that was very important to me.
Hey, is that girl homeless?
Say, Ritsuko...
Don't mind me. Please, go on ahead.
A classy girl like you shouldn't be seen doing something like this, Yurika.
Ritsuko...
Let me help you.
P-Please, don't!
It's something important, isn't it?
Yurika...
So, what am I looking for, exactly?
Here it is!
This is it, right?
Yes!
But I'll have to start all over with clean yarn...
Was this going to be a present for someone?
Um...
Why would you throw away something so important?
I was confused.
I realized that it was stupid to knit a gift that I'd never be able to give.
Why wouldn't you be able to?
B-Because so much has happened between us...
And I hurt him once already.
You rejected him, didn't you?
And I couldn't just tell him that I like him now, after all that,
so I decided to let it go.
But then I thought that I was making a mistake.
See, there was another time before that when I said nothing and just gave up.
Do you regret it?
No. I'd given up on that a while ago.
It occurred to me that this person has been there
to support me all this time, whenever I felt down.
When I had no confidence at all, he did his best to encourage me.
This time, I want to be the one to tell him how I feel.
I finally decided to stop being so quiet about my feelings.
I'm sorry for rambling like this...
No, I'm glad you did.
I think you've opened my eyes a little.
So...
By the way, who is it?
Who's your prince, Ritsuko?
Oh, that's...
Should I try guessing?
W-W-What are you saying?! Please don't!
You're so cute!
Yes. I'm set to leave this weekend.
Working in Tokyo?
Yeah. A lot happened at college and I ended up dropping out.
But you'll come back once in a while, won't you? Like you've been doing?
No. I'm never coming back to this town.
Kaoru, our sessions were fun.
I'll miss seeing you and Sen-boy,
so you two better keep playing jazz together.
Brother Jun! Did you tell him you were going back to Tokyo?!
Hey, Sen!
What's up, Richie?
It's about Brother Jun!
Yeah, he's about to go back to Tokyo, right?
I heard from Pops.
Well, ain't got nothin' to do with me.
Hey, wanna jam?
You're gonna let that be the last you see of him?
There's nothin' left to say.
You looked up to him as a big brother since you were a kid!
You may never get the chance to see him again!
There'd be no point.
Once he's gone, it'll be too late!
Enough about Brother Jun already.
Let's get started here.
If you don't feel like practicin', I'm goin' home.
What's all the fuss about?
I guess some college students from Tokyo have come to demonstrate
against letting the nuclear aircraft carrier into port.
That's terrible...
In their eyes, I'm a traitor.
They may never forgive me.
But...
All I can do is search for my own path from now on,
using a different set of tools...
Oh, you're here, Richie.
Here, eat.
I made it myself, so it might be a little salty...
But if you ain't eatin' it, I will.
Is this really the time to be eating?!
Did you forget what I said?!
What're you talkin' about?
Don't play dumb! Are you gonna be this stubborn 'til it's too late?!
Brother Jun is leaving town today or tomorrow!
It's today.
I'm taking the night train, Kaoru.
Sen-boy,
this was rather old-fashioned of you.
Letter of Challenge
I thought it was some kinda joke.
No jokes.
I wanted to try havin' a real showdown with you, Brother Jun.
Wait... You're not really...
Am I on time?
I want in on it, too.
This is no duet.
They're seriously duking it out.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble, Pops.
Tell me about it! And when you reach Tokyo,
first thing you better do is get a haircut!
Sure, sure.
Well, I'm off.
Brother Jun!
I'll remember today's session
for the rest of my life!
Yeah.
Me too, Sen-boy.
What are you doing here?
I told you not to see me off.
I have four questions I want you to answer.
If you try to dodge them, I'll get on this train with you.
So be honest with me.
First of all, why did you tell me not to see you off?
I hate sad goodbye scenes.
Second question, why didn't you think to take me with you?
The work I'm gonna be doing is kind of a gamble.
Even if I took you with me, there's no guarantee of making a living.
Besides, you're still in high school.
Question number three...
Why didn't you do anything more than kiss me?!
Did you avoid touching me because you had already planned to just take off?
No.
I knew.
I knew how much you cared about me...
So,
my last question...
Won't you take me with you?
I want you to take good care of your own life.
I figured you would say something like that.
Now it feels like I've been set free, too.
I'm going back to my own world.
Thank you, Junichi.
Goodbye.
Yurika, where are you?!
Come out, Yurika!
How dare you embarrass us by walking out
in the middle of an arranged marriage meeting?!
Calm down, dear!
We're going back there together, Yurika!
Yurika, where are you?!
I'm going back to my own world.
I dragged you on board...
Now what?
What else is there?
The train's already left the station.
Yeah...
Well, when we get there, we'll go to my room first
and maybe I'll have you cut my hair.
It's freezing today.
Yeah.
Think I'll light the heater.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change