Grandma!
Tsubomi?!
Lord Coupe!
Moonlight!
I've got to help her!
Lord Coupe, look after Grandma!
Tsubomi!
Please.
Don't let Moonlight fight Sabark.
Now, the light shall be enveloped by shadow!
Moonlight,
I'll be there soon!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Please, Say It's Not True!
Professor Sabark's True Identity!
Potpourri...
Sunshine!
Marine!
Coffret!
You beat Kobraja?
And Kumojacky?
Piece of cake!
Well, to be honest, I'm amazed I managed to win.
You did great, Marine!
Snackies again?!
Leave ush alone!
Sunflower Aegis Impact!
There's no end to them.
I'm sho tired.
All right, planning time!
Hold it!
Time out!
Well, it's a long shot, but we could
try disguising ourselves as Snackies.
As Shnackies?!
What do we do after that?
We act perfectly naturally, and just sneak
our way through to Blossom and the others!
Oh, that's a good plan!
All right, we'll go after the next attack.
Got it.
Precure!
Fight!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Snackies!
Precure Grand Explosion!
Moonlight!
Why did you come back?
Grandma's safe!
So let me help you fight!
I appreciate the thought.
But I have to do this myself.
All right.
I will destroy you and become what I was truly meant to be.
Moonlight!
Sabark!
It's been a while, Moonlight.
That's Professor Sabark...
I think they're looking for the Precure!
Let's just act innocent and keep moving.
This looks bad.
What now?
Cky! I spot the Precure, cky!
Nice, Potpourri!
Let's run for it-cky!
Tsubomi's grandma!
Snackies?!
It's us!
Erika! Itsuki!
We finally found you!
You made it all this way.
What's wrong?
Just seeing you're safe...
We can finally give in to the exhaustion...
I'm not Marine, but that was as much as I can take!
Coupe.
The Heart Seeds?
That feels so good!
I'm fighting fit again!
Yeah! I'm ready for anything now!
All the Heart Seeds you've worked so hard to gather have granted you their power.
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
Moonlight!
I won't let you interfere in their battle!
Blossom!
Die!
Then I can be the true Moonlight!
Is that all you can muster?
I see you still remain the weakest Precure in history.
No, I'm not.
Slowly but surely...
I've grown!
I've changed!
You haven't changed at all.
You're still a weak, pathetic Precure!
It's true that I was weak, cowardly, and totally shy.
But meeting Erika and becoming Precure together made me realize something.
There's bright, happy people who shine like the Sun.
And quiet, thoughtful people with the grace of the Moon.
All of them have their own burdens,
their own worries tugging on their hearts.
But they're all living as best as they can, always searching for that ray of light!
They taught me something I never realized when I was so caught up in myself!
The strength of believing!
Your belief is worthless!
The moment it wavers, it will cost you all you hold dear!
I have my beloved allies fighting with me,
a family I love dearly,
and the most wonderful friends!
I love this whole world!
Even if I am the puniest, weakest Precure in history,
I will protect all their hearts!
And those feelings are stronger than anyone's!
It's time you had a taste...
of the belief we all share.
Chypre!
Got it!
Precure Body Punch!
Dark Precure!
Father?!
Professor Sabark... is Moonlight's dad?!
So that's why Grandma said that!
Please.
Don't let Moonlight fight Sabark.
What have I...
Father!
Don't you remember me?!
It's me, Yuri!
Your daughter Yuri!
Yuri?
Yuri!
Father!
Stay away!
How dare you hurt my father?!
What are you saying?
Is it not obvious?
It was Professor Sabark that created me!
I was created by Professor Sabark for one purpose,
and one purpose alone!
To destroy you, Moonlight!
To destroy me?
My father made you... for that?
Father, tell me this isn't true!
Tell me this isn't why you abandoned mother and I!
Father!
No... How could you...
Professor Tsukikage is no longer your father.
He's my father!
It is for him that I shall destroy you here and now!
Stay out of my way!
Die, die, die, die!
Die!
Yuri... don't give in!
Yuri!
I'm sure there has to be some reason that your dad's acting like this!
You can't let her beat you!
Not if you want to save him!
Blossom...
You said beating Dark Precure would mean proving you're not the child you used to be, right?
The Yuri I look up to wouldn't lose to her ghosts like this!
Believe in him.
Believe in how you really feel!
How I feel...
I...
I still...
We all believe in you, Yuri!
Damn you both!
Yuri...
Cure Blossom.
You've helped me find the courage to keep fighting.
Thank you.
I will fight with your belief ringing clear in my heart.
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Let's bring an end to this.
Very well.
We are destined to fight until only one survives.
Even if you do defeat me, Blossom will fight you.
Marine will fight you.
Sunshine will fight you.
Then I'll destroy them as well.
It won't be as easy as you think.
That's the power of our bond as Precure!
My heart shall falter no longer
I'll pick myself up and keep moving forward
Pathetic.
Let this bring an end to you!
Knowing the tears I shed that fateful day
Just you try it!
Have guided me back to where I am now
Precure Dark Power Fortissimo!
The shard of the moon I thought lost
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Slowly begins to return
Let my courage grant me the strength
To bring forth the future we desire
The light of the silver moon
Envelops even this sadness I feel
But now I see I'm not alone
I have the strength to face my destiny
Within me burns a fiery resolve
To protect this world from evil
So let me use this power I've been granted
To bring light to the darkness
Th-This can't be!
Courage, love, friendship, kindness, sadness, and joy.
The silver moon will only reveal itself
Within all our hearts lie countless emotions.
To those who truly believe
My beloved friends,
So as we all gaze up at the same sky
and this world, filled with precious hearts and lives...
I'll make sure it shines forever more
I shall protect them all!
Within me burns a fiery resolve
To protect this world from evil
So let me use this power I've been granted
To bring light to the darkness
Heart Catch!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself in the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
We pray that everyone can be happy.
We wish for the fighting to be over.
For sadness to become joy.
For tears to become smiles.
We know it's possible!
We'll make it happen!
Now transform, with all your heart and shoul!
Come on!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
HeartCatch Precure:
For the Earth, and For Our Dreams!
The Precure's Final Transformation!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!