Tsukuyomi
shrine
work log
Log keeper:
Micchan
Tsukuyomi shrine work log.
Log keeper: Micchan.
Tsukuyomi
shrine
work log
Log keeper:
Micchan
Our head of the family, Tsukuyomi Ruza,
has been a complete shut-in since the other day's incident.
Every now and then he flips through the channels, or stuffs his face with chips,
all the while, he's lazing about and complaining about how he doesn't want to work anymore.
Statistically, his most used phrases are the following three:
"I don't wanna work,"
I don't wanna work
"I've had enough,"
I've had enough
and "I wanna die."
I wanna die
"I don't wanna work" has been uttered 132 times,
"I've had enough" 1032 times,
while "I wanna die" is off the charts.
I wanna die...
I wanna die
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 8
Strategic Solitude
I'm not a shut-in.
Cursed be the one
who tries to enter my room
Sasami
I'm simply barricading myself.
I can't allow a single soul to enter the depths of my room.
You're so naive, Lady Sasami!
The Yagami sisters are powerful gods!
There's a great risk that they could infiltrate your room!
Don't worry, newcomer.
This time I'm desperate.
Instead of suppressing the power of Amaterasu, I'll use it to its full potential to prevent them from entering.
Oh, what a twist!
This spring break I'll put all my might into staying unmotivated.
I'll stay under my blanket and just sloth about!
I won't let anyone intrude!
Sa-sa-mi! Sa-sa-mi!
I'd rather drop dead than work hard.
He's dead...
Are you okay, Paparin?
I haven't talked to Sasami in 34 hours.
I haven't touched Sasami for 76 hours.
I haven't shared a bath with Sasami for 127 hours.
Teacher, get a hold of yourself.
Sasami?
Sasami? Sasami!
Sasami, I've wanted to see you so much!
Sasami's scent! Sasami's warmth!
The feel of Sasami's abdomen!
I love you, Sasami! I'm in love with you!
Sheesh, you're such an idiot.
So here we find ourselves, facing two problems.
The first being that our sister has fallen into the underworld, and cannot return just yet.
The second is that, for reasons unbeknownst to us, Sasami has locked herself away.
Take a look at this.
That's the house you share with Sasami.
That black object is the Ama-no-Iwato.
It's the materialization of the feelings "I don't want to look at anyone or anything"
and "I certainly don't wanna care," which all stem from great deity Amaterasu.
It's the ultimate barrier that appears when she shuts herself in, and rejects all contact with the outside world.
Oh my, that's very important!
Your comprehension is faster than usual, Tama.
Yeah!
As usual, you don't understand, do you?
If this goes on, it will be as if Amaterasu refused to look after the world,
which could result in the emergence of undesirable alterations.
Is this unusual snow a result of that as well?
I'm thinking of breaking through the
Ama-no-Iwato, so I can check on Sasami.
Please, hold onto me.
Here we go.
Ready, go!
I've got a bad feeling about this!
Warning!
Sasami?
If you come any closer, I'll attack!
Just leave me alone!
I don't want to leave your side, even if it's for a second!
I want to breathe in your sighs,
intake your sweat, tears, secretory fluids, and all other Sasami juices,
otherwise I'll just die without them!
Shut up, you pervert!
Sasami, stop shutting yourself in and release the Ama-no-Iwato.
Just leave me alone!
I'm not shutting myself in because I want to!
Aren't you dealing with some giant problem, that makes you want to reject the world?
You're being reticent.
If you're troubled, just ask for advice.
We'll be there for you.
This time help is just a nuisance!
Anyway, leave! Or I'll really attack!
Very well. I'll just force my way through and make you regret your cheekiness.
I'll spank your butt and make you apologize.
And then I'll free you from your problem!
Just give up and leave me alone!
A shut-in, who doesn't have the slightest idea of how much I love this game of war!
You want to erase my clothes?
How could you come up with something like that?!
No!
If you don't give up and leave, I'll make you stark naked, upload the pictures to the net,
and produce you as the nude model
Excellent☆Kagami who flies the sky!
That's so cold and heartless!
That's so mean, Mamarin!
Don't tease Kagami.
Please! Pretty please!
If you want someone in the nude, take me!
Don't undress!
I'm already naked!
Get lost, pervert.
I'll focus all my power on making
Excellent☆Kagami a worldwide idol,
Power slam! Back from LA after a month!
Won't retire
Kagami's
back!
turning you into a movie, a social norm, and a legend!
If you don't want that, then leave.
That's so mean, Sasami.
I thought we were friends.
Forgive me, Kagami.
I'm here!
Tsurugi!
It's hard to alter attacks that are
protected by Amaterasu's power,
but that doesn't apply to this sword!
The divine blade of Ama-no-Murakumo!
How did you...?
This sword's my totem, so I used it to pull myself back up.
Hey!
Normally gods can't break through the Ama-no-Iwato,
but a new generation god can just eat it up.
Tama, open a hole into the Ama-no-Iwato.
Okay, Tsurugi!
Kagami, take us to the Ama-no-Iwato.
Understood.
Mow it all, Ame-no-Murakumo!
I'll dig in!
They broke through?
Excuse us.
Now then, if you'd be so kind as to explain what's going on, Sasami.
I might not prove to be forgiving.
Don't be so strict. She has her reasons too.
Show them!
I... uh...
I didn't know what to do!
That pizza I had yesterday was really good,
but then when I woke up today, I looked like this.
I couldn't transform myself back,
and I was afraid you'd all hate me for it,
and my brother would end up abandoning me,
so I couldn't talk to anyone about it.
I wanted to organize my thoughts beforehand,
but you guys were so dense and decided to come to see me!
You're so stupid!
Leave! Just leave already!
I do understand how you feel, but we're friends.
You should've just asked for advice.
Kagami...
No matter how much you eat, you shouldn't end up like that in a day,
so there's a chance it's some oddity or sickness.
I'll explain.
The reason is that Tsukuyomi priestess.
There's this thing she didn't finish.
You'll have to tag along for this now, Sasami.
What? Are those the people of the Tsukuyomi shrine?
What's wrong, Tsukuyomi Juju?
Show me this power of yours, praised as the greatest in history!
Do not think I am but a mere doll that houses the power of Amaterasu!
Is that... me?
What? What's going on?
Where's Tsurugi?
Am I Mom?
Is this the past?
Tsukuyomi Juju, I'm the lazy gravekeeper, Baron Samedi!
I'll make this your final resting place.
Kill her, zombies.
Walking corpses are of the dead.
The dead belong to...
That's the Reverse Path spell.
The God of the Reverse Path is the giant rock placed to stop Izanami from returning from the underworld.
Therefore, it is powerful against the dead!
Oh, you foreign gods, repent and vanish from this land!
Such meddlesome folk.
Amazing...
But why would Tsurugi take me to the past?
What's this thing she didn't finish yet?
Mistress Juju! Where are you?
Is that Micchan?
Ah, Mistress Juju!
Mistress Juju!
Micchan!
Phew, I thought I was gonna die.
Normally you would.
I'm so very sorry, Mistress Juju.
Spectres are still gods, even if they have fallen.
You must use the utmost care when handling them.
Yes... I'm terribly sorry.
Ah, the Tsukuyomi shrine's still there.
This really... is the past.
By the way, Micchan. Didn't you have something important for me?
Yes. Actually, Mistress Sasami...
Huh? Me?
This way, Mistress Juju.
Sasami collapses every now and then. There's nothing unusual about that.
She even slipped out of the shrine a while ago and snuck into town.
She might have caught some eldritch illness there.
Yes, but no matter what the priests and
priestesses tried, she wouldn't get better...
If it's some kind of a curse, those of you who're lacking spiritual power are in danger.
Leave.
Yes. Please be careful, Mistress Juju.
Mom...
Did I wake you?
I'm so sorry, Mom...
No. I'm a Tsukuyomi priestess, but I'm also your mother.
Just sleep.
Grow up quickly, Sasami.
That's the only thing you can do.
The world will be a bit of a better place by the time you grow up.
I'm sorry for causing trouble...
I'm so weak...
Don't apologize. Weakness is no sin.
I'm pathetic for not being able to change the world, so that the weak like you don't get hurt.
I won't apologize either.
But I do my best.
Mom!
Now, will I die first, or will I see Sasami grow up?
Mom...
By now you...
That's... Brother?
Don't just move about so restlessly!
No one knows who you are.
We know you're harmless,
but if you dare cause even the slightest of inconveniences,
I will crush you like a bug the instant that happens.
I have no compassion or pity.
Merely...
I hope you will one day have your salvation.
I'm satisfied with my place and fate.
I see. Then I shall say nothing.
I'll return to nursing Sasami then.
With that showing up, it must mean Sasami was chosen.
What?!
I'm hungry...
Ah, it was you, Mom?
No! A Tsukuyomi priestess needs no selfish desires!
Endure the siege of wishes and reach purity mentally and physic—
Micchan!
H-How may I help you, Mistress Juju?
At ease. Do you have something for me to eat?
The meal for the night-watch will be ready momentarily.
Just wait a little bit, please.
Well.
For Sasami's dinner, how about some porridge?
Indeed, now something easy to digest would be best for Sasami.
Mom...
Very good, Micchan! Make some!
No!
You should make it for her, Mistress Juju!
But I don't know the first thing about cooking.
I'll show you!
Sasami's a mama's girl, so she'll be really happy if you make it for her.
Though I'm not really familiar with parent to child relationships...
You were spirited away after all...
Spirited away?
Your spiritual power was so immense at birth that an evil god set its eyes on you and abducted you.
All of your spiritual power was drained from you,
and with it your memories of your parents and your name vanished as well.
That's why I understand Mistress Sasami's feelings. Our situation is the same.
How is it the same?
I know the feeling that everyone around me is better than me,
and I feel cornered, so I try to do my best.
It'd be nice to have a family by my side who'd support me.
My daughter will be eventually thrown into hell,
but until then I will try to purify it, order it, and make it even if it's just a bit more peaceful.
That is all I can give to my daughter.
No. I'm making such excuses
to run away from her, the one who innocently clings onto me.
But I am a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I can be neither a normal woman nor a normal mother.
Mom...
What is the right thing for me to do?
Mistress Juju...
Mom's always thought about me...
She worked so hard to make the world even just the slightest bit better,
for the time when I inherit the position of the Tsukuyomi priestess.
But I betrayed her...
Stay back, Mistress Juju!
Micchan!
You monster!
Is that... me?
Let go of my daughter!
Dream on!
I got rid of the people, so no help's coming!
This shrine is protected by a powerful barrier!
How did you get in?!
While Baron Samedi kept you busy, your daughter took a little trip to the nearby town.
I clung onto her then!
Was it... my fault?
But I don't remember this!
This isn't my past!
I lurked in her so no one could sense me.
Not a single person would know of me in the original flow of history.
The original flow of history? What are you talking about?
I'm not talking to you.
Aren't you there, Tsukuyomi Sasami?
But... why?
Huh?!
Me?
I'm here to make a deal with you!
What's going on?
I'm an assassin of the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki.
I'm the spirit in this Sesshou golem! I'm the fair and golden nine-tailed fox!
The nine-tailed fox?
In this land you call me Tamamo-no-Mae who plays with the scales!
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey, have you ever wanted to change the past?
Sasami@Unmotivated
Sasami, it's time for the ending!
Don't shut yourself in! Come out!
No matter how fat you get, I'll always love you!
On the contrary, I want to sink into your flesh!
I want you to lie on me and crush me!
Calm down, Teacher.
The Ama-no-Iwato played an important role in this episode,
so we should lure Sasami out just like in that myth.
I understood that perfectly!
Uh... What should I do?
I'll pass on that comment.
We should just have fun, be loud and
extremely obnoxious around her bed.
We might get her interested so that she'd peek out of her blanket.
That's a great idea!
Let's have fun singing at the top of our lungs!
Everyone in front of your computers too, sing along!
I can hear your voice.
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony.
Huh? Mamarin isn't coming out at all...
Could it be that she's asleep?
Sasami, you shouldn't fall asleep during the broadcast!
That'll be a real broadcast scandal!
I just noticed that Tsurugi is asleep too.
I wonder what they're dreaming about!
She's mumbling something about the nine-tailed fox...
Foxy! Yay!
That made me sleepy too.
Preview
It's Unmotivated@Shopping time.
Unmotivated@Shopping
Today I'm introducing the Unmotivated Cleaner EX.
Unmotivated Cleaner EX
In case you were wondering how can a cleaner be unmotivated:
when it reels the power cord back in,
it lacks the motivation to do so until the end, so it stops midway.
The cord is all over the place, always in the way.
It's our recommendation if you want to piss yourself off.
Unmotivated@Shopping
Next time: episode nine.
Next Time
Episode Nine
It's not that I can't do it.
It's not that I can't do it