When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
One morning, a boy stepped through the door to the Twilight Zone.
Could that be...
Vertical pan action.
Zoom and horizontal pan action.
It's Isumi.
But, what is she dressed in?
Turned on by her clothes, boy?
WHAT?! She got on the bus without any hesitation!
This is ridiculous...
I'm getting on!
Go return the telephone pole to where you found it.
Ah, right.
Otherwise, TEP** will yell at you.
You're right.
I'm getting on!
I missed it!
You reap what you sow.
Isumi...
What in the world is going on?! Tell me!
Anytime you decide to come to my place,
you ask the most incomprehensible questions.
But she was wearing a blazer!
That's an easy answer.
You haven't seen Isumi recently, have you?
Yeah, I guess. Due to final exams and what not.
You saw an illusion!
I...llusion?
Yes, it has to be an illusion.
Everyone in the city looks like Isumi to you.
That can't possibly happen!
She was definitely Isumi!
Then how about this?!
She fell in love with a boy at another school
and is sneaking into the school wearing their uniform.
Yeah, since there are girls who transfer to all-boys schools in disguise just to be with the men they like.
On another note, you play along well at a time like this.
You could say that.
But man, the world has come to that?
Yes.
Even if there's a gate there,
or a wall,
or Nu****be,
Girls will jump over them!
It can't be...
No way...
Isumi is...
...trying to climb over it?!
Up I go.
I'm sorry, we eavesdropped.
I don't mind.
We won't fully deny the possibility,
but isn't the case you describe pretty rare?
I don't think you had to go and corner in a boy who's already distressed.
Messing with him is fun.
I mean, Isumi on a bus with a blazer.
It's a bit of a shame it wasn't
a sai*** uniform with a machinegun.
It's too old a reference.
It looks interesting, so Hayate, look into it for me.
Thanks.
Milady. Because it looks interesting?
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
Isumi has a guy she likes?! Oh no!
What's the matter, Sir?
D***IN today and D***IN tomorrow.
Sir! Ryu***do was mixed in with Power Rangers!
It was?
I'll put it away, then.
Sir, that's the shelf for special effects shows.
Gi**ra, Koke**ro, and Shouchiku...
Special effect shows are your specialty; to make such simple mistakes...
Did something happen?
Oh, nothing.
But, if you're so obviously disappointed...
What could have happened to Sir?
As his maid, I can't let this be!
A-Are you all right?
H-Hayate-san.
So he was acting like that.
After all, Milady did lay it on him pretty thick.
So that was the reason behind this.
Is something wrong?
No, just how he doesn't open up to me.
I'm sure it's something like it's easier to talk with Lady Nagi, who is the same age as him.
So being older than him is a handicap for me?
No, no, no, no, no.
After all, I did break the twenty year barrier, so am I past my expiration date?
Th-That's not the issue!
You're still in your prime!
Even if you were married...
Hey, that was...
Sir!
Is it all right to do this?
No, it's not.
Sir!
If I remember correctly...
Yes, keep panning down.
That uniform was...
Even if what Nagi said was correct...
Augh, thinking won't get me anywhere!
I didn't predict this development.
I will stand out in these clothes, won't I?
You always do.
In any case, normally he would have noticed us by now.
Next stop, Shiomi Municipal High School.
Shiomi?
It's been a while since I last came here.
This is where Isumi is...
Damn it! This gate won't keep Isumi and me apart!
Sir...
Isumi-san must have been wearing this school's uniform.
Why do you go that far for Isumi-san?
But, I wish I could do something for Sir's sake.
Um, if you'd like, I'll tell you how to get on the campus.
Butlers even know how to do that?
Well...
Rai******** Kick!
Why won't the gate open?!
Fine, take this. Back-
Sir.
What? What are you doing here, Saki?!
I could ask the same of you, Sir.
It doesn't matter what I'm doing here!
Well, it does matter to me.
I heard the situation from Hayate-san.
You think I can leave you alone in your current state?!
I-I got it. Thank you.
You can go in through the rip in the fence.
I don't see any rip.
What? But according to the map Hayate-san drew-
But I don't see one.
Oh wow. They fixed it well.
Oh, what are you doing here, Wataru-kun?
Y-You're...
Whatever. Can you let me in?
Sure.
I'm always fighting the tardy bell, so I need my ways in.
Not something you can brag about.
So, what brings you here?
There are times when men have to move on no matter what.
Sir, even if you act like ******, you only look pathetic if you're caught on the fence.
Shut up!
At any rate, will you give us a tour around the campus?
Sure, I don't mind.
It's a really normal school, I tell you.
A-A-A-re those...
U-Uhm...
They're a gang.
We're a normal school, so we have people like them.
Good puppy!
Puppies are so good. They purify our hearts.
What do you want?
What is she?
I don't know.
You don't know about female gang bosses?
Like I said, we're a normal high school.
No, no. We don't see female gang bosses these days.
S... Something just smelled good.
That was the scent of lavender.
See? We're a normal school,
so sometimes girls leap through time.
It's not the anime version.
It's the Harada ****yo version.
You can handle yourself from here, right?
I need to head to the school store, or else they'll run out of bread.
Bye.
The girl swiftly ran away.
Kiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiinnnnnnnn.
Ah, hey.
Y-Yes.
So nervous.
Twirl twirl.
Looks like this isn't the place.
Isumi... Where is Isumi?
Ready?
Y-Yes.
Looks like this isn't the place either.
Not here either.
It's not like today's a special service episode for Isumi fans.
Float float float.
Isumi is searching for something in this high school.
Where could Isumi-san be?
Sir?
What are you grunting about?
Eh?
Why is Isumi wearing something like that?
Sir, calm down.
Plus, what lies before her eyes is...
Who is that guy with a face that makes you want to touch it and has senpai written on his back?!
I guess you don't watch any DVDs with the context required to understand the situation...
That's the golden road of youth.
"Senpai, please use this to wipe off your sweat" attack.
What?!
So that's the now-gone-from-anime-drama-and-shoujo-manga
"Senpai, please use this to wipe off your sweat" attack?!
Young audience, ask your father and mother, who were born in the Shouwa era, about it.
I am just over twenty, mind you.
Note: 2008 is Heisei 20, so Saki is emphasizing that she was just barely born in Shouwa era
A white towel is a must item for all girls in love.
But I am aware it is a symbol representing that
she is ready to accept all of his sweat and tears of youth.
GAAHHH!!!
I may have not known the real Isumi.
I never knew Isumi was seeking youth,
the days you never know when the sun shines or dims.
You're right. I don't have the sweat of youth flowing in me.
What I have in me is nasty otaku blood.
Has God...
...forsaken me?!
Damn, the sun's bright.
Sir, the sun's behind you.
Thanks.
Damn, the sun-
Ru ruru ruru rutawa. Hantai kara yomuto?
Ru ruru ruru rutawa. Read it from the tail and you get?
Ton to tonton. Sukina bui ha? Tontoro ro-su.
Ton to tonton. What's your favorite part of a pig? Fatty roast.
This place brings back memories.
But meeting old friends feels a little embarrassing.
I must be careful not to be spotted by anyone.
Hayate-kun?
I got spotted seven seconds and three frames in.
Nishizawa-san. Looks like I've been spotted.
Why is Hayate-kun here?
Did he come to see me?
It might be faster to ask Nishizawa-san about them.
Um...
Did anything strange happen today?
Would you like to eat some bread, if you don't mind that I've already taken a bite.
Oh, nothing.
What am I saying at a time like this?
Um...
Y-Yes?
Right, I saw you!
No, something other than me.
Then nothing really.
This is a really normal high school, so we don't have any celebrities or presidents of IT companies.
Right.
Sorry to bother you during your lunch!
Ah, wait!
I do know the Shiomi High School Seven Mysteries.
Eh?
Ever since a manager of a club suddenly passed away,
a number of supernatural phenomena began to take place.
So people started quitting from the manager position because they didn't want to stay late after school.
Everyone calls it the curse of the dead manager now.
That's all part of a very familiar sounding story.
It's only a rumor, after all.
Or maybe!
Could Isumi-san have been asked to exterminate it?
Thank you very much!
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Oh... So Hayate-kun didn't come to see me.
Dang. This fried noodle bread stings my eyes.
Sir...
Yeah, I don't have a broad chest.
And neither sweat nor tears look good on me.
Sir!
So this is where you were.
I won't... I won't...
I won't let anyone...
...anyone other than me wipe my senpai's sweat!!!
Um...
You can.
Use my body.
Y-You can see me?
Yes, kind of.
It's come. It has come.
And, what do you mean by I can?
You can use my body as a medium so that you can fulfill your wish.
R-Really?
I can?
Yes.
That's right, I'm a loser!
Sir!
What?
I've had enough!
He's too bright for me!
There's no way I'd-
You hit me.
Even my father never-
Please don't finish that line!
This isn't about parody! It's about your life!
Sir, are you really okay with this?
You said it yourself, "There are times when men have to move on no matter what".
There are times when men have to run straight at the wall no matter how tall it is.
Okay.
Sir!
But, how exactly do I tackle that huge wall?
Believe it or not, I have more life experience than you, Sir.
A fight between men would mean-
It has to be the baseball showdown where one pitch means everything!
Throw it, chuck it, pitch it.
Fair and square. No regrets.
Okay, I got it.
Thank you, Saki.
Maybe one day, Sir will have wings on his back and will soon take flight from the window.
Since I'm his bible for teaching what freedom is...
No, this was right. It's for the best.
She doesn't really know what she's saying to herself.
So even if there is a song with a similar meaning, it's a pure coincidence.
Over and out.
Saki-san, where's Wataru-kun?
Sir has...
...gone to a man's duel!
Eh?
Senpai.
Please use this.
Hold it right there!
Who are you?
Yeah, who are you?
I challenge you to baseball!
I hereby request a man-to-man fight through a one-pitch match over her white towel.
Whoever wins gets their sweat wiped by the manager.
Don't make up deals, will you?
Interesting. I accept.
Sir...
Watch me, Isumi.
I will put everything that I've lived for
up to this day into this pitch!
What do you think he's doing, getting fired up all alone?
Take this!
My...
Sir!
I'm burnt out.
Saki... I may have lost... But I have no regrets.
Yes.
That was a good workout.
Please use this.
Thank you.
I guess there's nothing for you to brood over anymore.
Isumi-san!
It must have been a hard job.
Great job.
I'll take you back to your mansion.
I-I'm sorry, but-
I-Isumi...
I... I...
Wataru-kun, thank you for your help.
Thank you for the workout.
Looks like Isumi's thankful towards me.
I don't completely get it, but looks like things turned out well.
I guess I was just worried about things by myself... So lame.
You were a fine boy today.
Really?
Yes. You were cooler than any Sir I've seen to this day.
I see.
Let's go home.
We left the store completely empty.
Right with you, Sir.
Oh, so Isumi was just being a part-time manager.
Yes, so it seems.
I can't tell her that she was working part-time as a manager to exterminate the dead manager's spirit.
You often hear, "reality is stranger than fiction",
but you can't find strange stories that often in the world.
She's right. If not, Tamo** couldn't explain all the stories.
I agree, Milady!
No, it actually was a very strange story.
Next time, Hayate's rival will appear.
Student Council Trio's
Butler Network!
Good morning. It's Segawa Izumi.
It's Asakaze Risa.
Bomber! It's Hanabishi Miki.
This is the last of the Student Council Trio specials.
The three weeks flew by.
But this song is a true masterpiece
no matter how many times you hear it.
Yes, indeed.
We might even be able to be in the Kouhaku.
How about we make it the national anthem?
It should be made into this anime's opening theme.
All right, it's time for the service shot.
If you cut and paste the three
service shots, you get one picture.
That's amazing!
So we have no choice but to use it to make original goods.
Adios Amigos!
Hayate, you don't have to work anymore.
Does that mean... I'm fired?
No, that's not what I meant.
I'm saying you can take a break from your work and concentrate on studying until exams end.
I have prepared an emergency butler in case of a situation like this.
Nice to meet you. I'm Mecha Butler 13.
Next time, sure, Amuro had a place to return, but...
I'm more capable than him.
Next time, change switch on to Hayate, one, two, three!