No matter what I do...
I...
Like Ryuji.
I want it to work out between him and Minorin.
But it hurts.
It hurts so much it's unbearable.
I can't...
TAIGA!
I'm sorry.
I was dreaming.
I-It's okay.
It's understandable.
It must've been pretty traumatic for you when your friend, Aisaka-san, got lost.
And now that you've awoken from your nightmare, Takasu-kun...
Please turn in that form by tomorrow.
I'm going to repeat it for everyone else, but please don't forget.
And your reply?
Yes.
That's all for today.
In the end, the rescue team saved us, so we didn't have any real injuries.
Then Taiga's mother came to pick her up.
Are you keeping in touch?
Kitamura...
Sensei said that Aisaka isn't feeling well.
She's staying with her parents to rest.
Have you heard anything?
No...
I can't reach her cell.
I see.
Kitamura.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Let everyone think that the one who went down to save Taiga was you.
If Taiga ever asks you, tell her that.
Tell her that she was unconscious the whole time and didn't say anything.
Please.
Does that have something to do with what Aisaka asked me on New Year's?
It does, doesn't it?
I got it.
Taka-chan!
Wanna go somewhere good?
Somewhere good?
Yeah, yeah...
Let's get some good food!
Get your mind off Taiga-
Nothing, nothing!
It's cold!
Haven't those guys before us been in there for too long?
Takasu, you don't have to go home and make dinner?
Sorry we dragged you here.
Don't worry about it.
We came all the way here, I can't just go home without trying it.
I don't wanna go home even after trying it.
When I think that I have to talk about my future with my parents...
You don't have to get that serious about it yet, right?
The survey this time is just to decide how to divide up the classes.
Notocchi's definitely going into liberal arts right?
Yup.
I want to get into some liberal arts college.
Then work at a publishing house as an editor for a music magazine.
And then go independent.
I'm fine with just graduating high school.
I'll probably end up helping my dad with his work, I guess.
I see.
No offense, but I'm surprised you guys are really thinking about your future.
What're you talking about?
What do you have to worry about? You're really smart.
You're going into science, right?
You and Great Teacher Kitamura are more than good enough to pass the national exam.
I haven't even decided whether or not to go to college...
Next, please!
We finally got in.
Please have a seat anywhere!
So, how's it going?
Have you checked up on her yet?
On who?
Kushieda, of course-
Liberal arts!
K-Kushieda!
Why are you here?
I work here!
What about softball?
Practice ends earlier in the winter because the days are shorter.
Just so you know...
If you say, "A hot guy," I'll poke your eyes out.
A hot guy.
I'm sorry, three ramen bowls please.
Okay.
You have made a good decision.
Three ramen!
Okay!
You started yet another job?
Yup.
The pay's good, so I thought I'd try it out for a couple hours each week.
Why do you have to do that many-
Hold on.
Very soon the eyes will open...
The eyes will...
Open?
What?
Endless circle of transmigration!
Wait! That's dangerous!
Thank you!
Come again!
She really never changes.
Next customer, please come in.
If you hadn't told us...
I never would've thought she had just rejected a guy.
Really, women are hard to read.
Speaking of which, Notocchi, did you make up with Maya-sama?
She's still totally ignoring me.
No surprise there.
A girl's feelings?
Is she really not coming back just because she isn't feeling well?
Or is her mother selfish like that old man and won't let her come back?
Or...
I...
Or did she figure out that I heard her...
Like Ryuji!
Career plan survey?
Just write, "I will study hard, really hard!"
Even if I get into a national university that I can commute to from home...
Just how much do you think it'll cost for four years?
It'll be fine...
Don't worry about the money.
Here, natto bomb!
Sticky, sticky.
"Don't worry"?
You...
Unlike Yacchan, you're really smart.
After getting the best education...
You're going to get the best skills!
Then you're going to go down the best, happiest path in life.
Isn't there some kind of saying?
How does it go...
If you polish a gold stone...
The gold stone will really shine, or something like that.
"A jewel won't shine if you don't polish it."
That's it degansu!
Ryu-chan, you're all sparkly and shiny when you're studying!
Looks like I've got to work and make about 50,000 a month...
No way, no working!
But I still...
Working at Inage-san's place was an extra special exception.
You knew about that?!
You won't be able to study if you start working.
And a parent and child eating a cold dinner separately...
What's the point of living like that?
That's not happiness at all-
Because you keep saying, "Go to college, go to college!"
It's alright!
It'll all work out.
She's...
Always been like that.
It's alright.
Just because you don't have a father doesn't mean you're worse off than any of the other kids.
Because Yacchan is an amazing mom!
You'll always be perfectly happy.
Always perfectly happy?
If you're worried about Taiga, she's okay.
She always said she gets along pretty well with her real mom.
So I think she's probably having fun hanging out with her mom after such a long time.
I hope so.
Hey, Kushieda.
Takasu, you're here too?
You're here for the club budget?
Sorry! I'll turn it in later!
Yeah, don't forget, new team captain!
See you later.
The new student council president is pretty busy.
New team captain?
Weren't you already captain?
Well, Kitamura-kun's really busy with the student council.
So they combined the boys and the girls softball teams.
I was appointed the new team captain of both.
Looks like I'm just unlucky. Soon, I'll be just as busy as Kitamura-kun.
T-Then why did you take on another job?
Won't that make it worse?
No, no.
Haven't you heard?
"Work when you're young to rest when you're old."
But you won't be able to do either well...
I will.
I'm working hard so I can do both well.
Because that's...
Something you can see.
"Something you can see"?
It's Amin!
As lovely as ever.
Kawashima, what's with that attitude?
Don't come near me.
You'll infect me with your stupidity.
Isn't that great?
When the child's away, whatever the father does...
Where're you going, Kawashima?
Takasu-kun, this is where I say adieu!
Hey, class is going to start!
Skipping first period?
Why is it you?
Nothing.
Listen...
There's something I've been wanting to tell you for a long time.
After blaming everything on me nonstop, there's still something left?
That space you're sitting in is actually...
HAUNTED!
S-Seriously?
Between those vending machines...
A lonely girl who failed in love, in one fell swoop...
Why didn't you say so earlier?!
But nothing's happened, right?
I think ghosts have personalities too.
They only appear in front of people who they want to see and understand them.
I thought...
I saw a ghost too.
But...
I don't want to get lost in longing for something I can't see and lose the things I can see.
That's why-
Who cares.
I don't want to hear the rest.
You'll understand if you hear the rest!
Is that so?
You just to want say that if I had just kept quietly watching until the end...
If I hadn't said something unnecessary and messed it all up, it would've come out alright?
Nevermind.
Talking to you makes me feel like I'm on my period.
I won't waver anymore!
I'll face forward and chase after what I can see.
Ah, just shut up already.
I won't waver!
I'll decide!
I'll decide by myself!
Everything! Properly!
Shut up.
About your career plans...
I'm sorry.
I haven't reached an agreement with my mother.
Then do you still feel the same about what you wrote at the beginning of the school year?
Yes, well...
Takasu-kun, you're a really good student.
As a teacher, the more I expect from you, the more I want to talk to you about this.
Please don't expect so much.
My family's poor.
So the only problem is financial?
If you're interested...
There are scholarships and educational loans-
Is it so strange to choose not to go to college?
No, that's not it.
It's just that I can't tell from this career survey.
Not what someone else thinks, but what you, yourself, thinks.
How I...
Huh? It's dark.
Yasuko!
Still sleeping?
A job?
"It's alright."
"It'll all work out."
This is what she meant?
I thought there wasn't any point to living if a parent and her child didn't have dinner together.
Ryu-chan, you're all sparkly and shiny when you're studying!
How can I give it to her now?
What part of a love letter is embarrassing?
How about it? It's pretty sick, isn't it?
I don't have the courage to tell her how I feel.
I can only sit here and fantasize about what it'd be like.
Of course, it's pathetic.
But even so, I don't think it's shameful!
That's right...
It's not shameful to like someone.
I can't say that!
Something like that to someone who likes me!
Even if I want to, I can't!
She doesn't even answer her phone.
What should-
Yasuko?
Hey!
Why are you working more-
What?
TAIGA!
Where were you and who were you with until now?
That hurt!
You idiot, pig, dog, beast, demon!
Don't run away!
Ouch!
What's with you?
You suddenly tried to strangle me and now you look at me weird!
I was surprised because you just suddenly showed up!
You didn't even contact me once.
I was worried the whole-
I left my phone off.
What the hell is with that?
Explain everything properly!
Did you not come home because you...
What was I going to say?
Look.
I wasn't injured that badly.
The story about me being sick was a lie.
I'm completely fine.
I just wanted to skip school.
I-I see.
Completely?
Then...
It's been a while since I last saw my mom!
We stayed at a hotel, went shopping, ate at restaurants, went to the movies, and other stuff like that.
I totally let her spoil me.
That's it.
Let me in.
Didn't you say you wouldn't come into my house?
I lost my keys.
I'm going to get in through the window from your room.
Three second rule.
Can you get in within three seconds?
Whatever!
I'm coming in.
W-Wait!
Hey, since you're here, eat before you go.
There's some natto left over, so I can just cut some onion and...
I'm good, I ate before I came.
T-That's right, Inko-chan wants to say hi!
Isn't he sleeping?
No, this is...
Yeah, this is "playing dead."
One of his new tricks.
Did Ugly get a little fatter?
Really?
Y-You think so too?
It's because he has no stress without you here...
No, I mean, he probably ate too much because he's lonely.
He's as ugly as ever.
Poke, poke, poke, poke.
It really is nice...
This world with Taiga in it.
Hey, Ryuji.
Why are you crying? That's gross.
I'm not crying!
I was just yawning, yawning.
Oh, yeah, it is pretty late.
Bye, Ugly.
I'm going.
What's wrong?
This is... I had some free time so I was cleaning out everything.
Remember, at the end of the year it was so busy...
I see.
I'm clumsy...
But I really got it after what happened.
But...
Even a clumsy girl can be serious.
I was worried about it the whole time.
Hey, did you ask Minorin about her real feelings?
What?
Could it be...
Because of the big mess I caused, you couldn't ask her?
Why is she worrying about me?
I won't be clumsy anymore.
Even though...
You...
It'll be alright.
I'm sure it'll work out between you and Minorin.
Taiga...
Hey, Ryuji!
Don't just stand there, help!
I knew it.
I always forget to lock it.
A luxurious apartment with perfect security can be inconvenient.
Hey, be careful.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Thanks.
You went to look for me with Kitamura-kun and Minorin, right?
You don't remember, right?
Since you were unconscious.
Yeah...
But I think I had a dream.
Kitamura-kun was carrying me piggyback.
I said something stupid to him, falling all to pieces.
That was a dream, right?
Yeah...
"Something stupid," huh?
Does she want to act like it never happened?
In that case...
It was a dream.
But it is true that Kitamura climbed up carrying you.
But you didn't say anything.
You were unconscious the whole time.
That's what I heard.
Really?
Then I'm relieved!
I was worried, "What if it was real?!" for a moment there.
Yeah...
Alright! Bye!
Good night.
Taiga!
I'm okay.
One more time, good night.
Taiga, you're really...
Clumsy.
Right?
Thirty something rock, paper, scissors: scissors!
Yay, Yuri-chan won!
Here I go!
Cho-co-late!
Valentine's fun!