What do we do, Rider?
What now, mad dog?
Tokiomi...
I'll kill you.
Saber!
They're unable to mount an offensive.
If only Saber could use her left hand...
Hey, Saber...
We're getting nowhere.
Pull back!
Don't be ridiculous.
We must stop it here!
But right now, this battle is a stalemate.
Fall back.
I have an idea.
All right, everyone.
Regardless of our strategy,
we must buy ourselves some time.
I shall pull it into my Ionioi Hetairoi.
Unfortunately, even the
full might of my armies
will not suffice to kill that thing.
The best I can do is occupy it within
my Reality Marble for a time.
And after that?
I do not know.
After I catch a thing that size,
the barrier around my armies
will only hold for a few minutes.
So, Heroic Spirits,
I ask you to create a plan for victory.
Hey, kid,
you stay here, too.
Hey...
Once I activate the barrier,
I have no idea what transpires outside.
If anything should happen,
focus hard and call for me.
I will send a messenger.
Saber! Lancer! The rest is up to you.
Understood.
You struggle, all for naught.
Mommy!
What's...
Why not simply plunge yourself
into that mass of filth, mongrel?
For all your fury,
this is all you can manage?
He's going to sacrifice himself?
Kariya, consider this a kindness.
Intensive Einasherung.
K-Kill you...
Tokiomi!
Zouken...
Any ideas?
He said he'd buy us time,
but if we can't come up with a plan,
we're back to square one.
Say, Einzbern, any thoughts?
Hey!
Um, well...
How do you use this?
Iri-kun?
No, this is... I mean...
Ah, Rider's Master, correct?
Good. I need to speak with you, too.
W-Who is this?
It doesn't matter.
Caster has disappeared because of your Servant, yes?
Yes, I suppose.
Then let me ask you...
When Rider dispels his Reality Marble,
can he return whatever was inside
to a specific place?
To a degree.
The range would be limited
to about a hundred meters,
but it should be possible.
Rider is able to control
where he rematerializes.
Good.
When the time is right, I'll fire a signal flare.
Have him release Caster directly beneath it.
Can you do that?
I can... I think.
Probably.
One more thing.
Give Lancer a message.
Tell him Saber's left hand holds
an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
What did he say?
He had a message for you.
Something like, "Saber's left hand holds
an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm."
Is that true, Saber?
And is it something that could obliterate
Caster's monster in one blow?
It could.
But, Lancer... The weight of my
sword is the weight of my pride.
The wound I sustained in our battle
is an honor, not a burden.
If my left hand is the price
I must pay for Diarmuid Ua Duibhne's assistance,
that is worth more than any army.
Come, Saber...
I, too, wish to punish Caster.
Justifying his torture of the innocent,
and finding joy through
the spread of terror...
On my honor as a knight,
I cannot allow such evil.
Lancer, you mustn't!
Who must have this victory?
Is it Saber? Is it Lancer?
No, it is neither.
What truly must emerge victorious
is the code of chivalry
we swore to uphold.
Do you not agree, Heroic Spirit Arturia?
Lancer...
The King of Knight's sword
will carry my hope for victory.
I shall put my trust in you, Saber.
I give you my word, Lancer.
I swear it on my sword, I shall win!
That's King Arthur's legendary...
Saber!
Berserker? He's...
You presume to turn your back to me,
insolent dog?
What?
Saber!
What is Berserker doing?
And just as I had regained
use of my left hand...
Even if you are unaware of it,
your soul instinctively pursues joy.
Rather, because you wished to understand
this "complicated situation,"
you ordered Assassin
to investigate him alone in such depth.
All to satisfy your subconscious interest.
It's still too soon.
That tremor...
The first sign that Rider's Reality
Marble approaches its limit.
Rider.
I am Mithrenes of the Hetairoi.
I am here as the King's ears.
T-Tell him to wait for the signal,
then dispel the barrier, so that Caster
is released at that point.
Can he do that?
It is possible,
but we haven't much time.
Within the Reality Marble,
our army cannot
hold off the sea monster much longer.
I know...
I know!
Damn it! That Berserker...
Can't we do something about him?
I will go.
Lancer.
That is quite enough, madman!
This will be my only chance!
Archer...
There!
Directly below that!
Understood.
What took you so long?
Now show me, Saber.
Show me the true worth of the light
of your Heroic Spirit,
that I may appraise it!
The light...
It shines.
That sword...
is a vision that every soldier,
past, present, and future,
littering the battlefield sees.
In their final moments,
it is a dream both sad and noble.
She carries their will as her pride,
rallying them to hold to their loyalty.
The undefeated king sings loud and clear
the name of the miracle she
holds in her hands.
Its name is...
Excalibur!
This light...
Without doubt...
this light...
is the blessed radiance
of Jeanne and my shared joy.
What...
have I...
Were you watching,
King of Conquerors?
That was Saber's light.
Would you still claim her unworthy,
having witnessed her brilliance?
That light comes from her having taken
the hopes and dreams of her people
onto her own shoulders.
It was so dazzling,
it hurt to even look.
And then there's the fact
that she who bears this heavy burden
is but a dreaming little girl...
And the girl who ended up this way
gave up a happy childhood,
never knew love,
and was eventually cursed to live by her ideals.
This is painful to see.
Which is why she is so desirable, no?
She embraced dreams that
were too much for her.
And in the end, they overwhelmed
and destroyed her.
The tears of regret she must have
shed in her final moments...
I can only imagine how sweet
they must have tasted.
It seems I can never accept you,
Babylonian King of Heroes.
Oh?
So you've finally understood that.
Then what will you do, Rider?
Draw your weapons,
and show me your anger, here and now?
If only I could...
But I am afraid I have spent
too much of myself
to make war upon such as you tonight.
Of course,
if you would deny my withdrawal,
I would certainly have to retaliate.
I don't mind.
You have my permission to retreat,
King of Conquerors.
It would hardly be satisfying to
destroy you at less than full strength.
And I expect you may have
sustained some injury
from our friend in black, no?
Taunting me is tantamount to death.
Until we meet again, King of Heroes.
Our battle will decide our dispute,
once and for all,
and the Grail War with it.
Perhaps...
I never said that I would restrict the
honor of facing my greatest treasure
to one worthy soul, Rider.
Fool who longs for dreams beyond
the providence of man...
Only one in creation is allowed
to love her in her ruin.
And that is I, Gilgamesh.
Fleeting and brilliant one,
fall into my arms.
That is my decision.
Episode 15:
Golden Light
I am first spear of the Knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne!
I am glad to have met you.
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
shall face you.
En garde!
Next Time:
The End of Honor
Have at you!