I don't know...
I don't know!
It's not just that your wish doesn't come true when you lose three times;
your wish is reversed.
Hitoe's wish was to make friends.
And when you reverse her wish...
She loses... her friends?
That's not all.
She will never make friends again.
And now, with her third loss,
the battle for her wish has ended.
The words written here...
Hitoe told me that she can't see them.
Sharing all the fun and happy words with everyone...
It made me happier than I've ever been before.
Having friends really is nice.
She also said she doesn't know you girls.
All the memories she made during
her time as a Selector have disappeared.
I...
I just don't know what to do anymore!
Card
Remaining
Coins
Card
Remaining
Coins
Card
Remaining
Coins
Card
Remaining
Coins
I don't know, but...
Hello, Kurebayashi— Oh, Ruuko-san?
I heard you were sick. Are you better now?
U-Uhm, is Yuzuki...?
She hasn't come home yet.
Hello? Did something happen?
N-Nothing! Sorry to bother you!
Card
Remaining
Coins
Card
Remaining
Coins
Ruuko-san—
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
One, two.
One, two!
No more battles.
I need to stop them.
I need to stop them!
Any here?
No. I don't sense anything.
Kazuki
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Dueling
Tables
Available
Yuzuki-chan?
I haven't seen her yet today.
Is something wrong?
No—
I summon Amber! Amber, Attack!
If only I had a Guard card...
What's the matter?
Ruu?
Ruu's not happy.
Sad?
No...
Then let's battle!
A battle will make Ruu happy again!
Making me grovel before you... You were enjoying this!
No! I...
Ruu?
I need to stop them.
I can't go through there...
By the way, I can't get in touch with Akira at all.
Akira?
Do you need her or something?
Well, she took some outfits home with her...
Come on now, how could you let that happen?
I'm sorry. I did ask her to return them, but...
Man...
They can't get in touch with Akira-san?
What are you doing here?
U-Uhm...
Are you here for a shoot? What magazine is it for?
Magazine?
Well, I...
Oh, excuse me.
She's my guest.
Oh, so she's your friend, Iona-san? Sorry 'bout that, then!
Iona-san?
U-Uhm...
I knew you wanted to do it too.
You were feeling the urge, weren't you?
N-No! I just wanted to see Akira-san and talk with—
Oh. What do you want from Akira?
Well...
She's not here anymore.
Or rather, she'll probably
never come back again.
Huh?
She lost a battle against us.
And she lost to you too, right?
You came here to see if the girl you beat is well?
How sweet of you.
But perhaps this is just a victory parade for you?
That's not it!
Akira lost to another Selector besides us before...
Wait... That means...
You and Iona put on the finishing touches.
She lost thrice already. Game over for her.
No...
Then... Akira-san is...
I don't know.
She might be off crying for her mommy somewhere.
Just like your friend.
My friend?
Hitoe-chan. Isn't she your friend?
Hitoe? What did you do to Hitoe?
Hitoe... we beat her, too.
A... battle?
I'm sorry, but Hitoe... well,
her wish has already come true.
So she doesn't need
to battle anymo—
I'm so happy that your wish already came true before you lost three times.
I'm so happy...
This girl, too, has a very earnest wish she wants to see fulfilled. So... how about it?
That's right... I already have
Ruuko and Yuzuki as friends.
So even if I lose...
Hitoe...
All right. Let's battle.
She didn't know what it meant to lose three times.
It can't be...
You knew that Hitoe already had two losses?
You knew, and yet...
That's terrible! Why did you—?!
Are you finally in the mood?
You just can't forgive us for what we did, right?
You want to battle, don't you?
Battle!
Even if I... battled you...
Hitoe will never again...
Wish.
A wish... did you find one?
A wish...
You found one.
I don't have any wishes.
A lie.
You were the one who told me that battling as a Selector without having a wish is blasphemy!
But I'm glad I don't have any wishes...
I can always quit battling—
No! Don't quit battling!
Tama wants to battle together with Ruu!
Battle more!
I'm sorry, Tama... But I already...
Wanting friends and wanting to be together with someone you love...
Those kinds of wishes are worthless.
They're not worthless!
Your wish is different from the others.
I told you, I don't have any wishes!
But you do. We know you do.
You don't know! Why? Why are you saying this?
My wish... is the same as yours.
It was the first time I felt like that.
I didn't have a bad life.
It wasn't especially good either.
Wh-What are you talking about?
All I did every day was live.
I didn't ever question that.
I assumed that was all there was to it. But then...
I felt it.
I understood it.
I savored it.
That feeling...
It was the first time I ever really felt alive.
I felt my life and my soul.
Battle is my blood, my flesh, my bones.
No...
It's my very being.
But... if you lose three times, you'll have to suffer...
And if you win, someone else will suffer instead.
That's...
It can't be helped.
That's what these battles are about.
That's what we are about. Me...
and you.
Is she wrong?
I...
You felt it, too.
Once you feel that excitement, there's no way you can quit.
Try as you might, you can't keep the urge down...
You want it... You want to do it, right?
I want to do it with you.
How about you, Ruuko?
I want to do it.
Ruuko!
I want to battle, too...
I want to do it... I really want to do it...
But...!
Open.
What's the matter?
You said you wanted to battle.
I-I did say that, but...
this isn't what I meant!
Then what did you mean?
Just let go and have some fun.
Let's get started, then.
Battle!
Hey, Ruu!
Oh, my. Hitoe-chan was a lot more fun to play with, you know?
Get Bible
A spell searching for low-level cards?
Why would she use that now?
This is strange... something isn't right...
Why is she only using low-level attacks?
Tama, Grow!
Ruu! Battle! Do it seriously!
Very good, Iona.
You used a search spell to look through your deck and find out what was used in your Life Cloth.
If Ruuko attacks now...
Tama doesn't attack! Turn End!
Oh? Well then...
Next is...
Spell. Blessed Reminiscence!
I knew it!
Here it comes!
Arts! Anti Spell!
Anti Spell
Very good, Tama-chan!
Say, don't you want to keep battling?
I want more!
For eternity?
"Eternity"? What is "eternity"? I don't know!
It means "forever."
Forever! I want it!
Forever! I want to battle for eternity!
Eternity!
Yuzuki.
Over there. She's a Selector.
She's...
Where's Iona?
She's been in the dressing room.
Isn't it about time you bring her here?
Ah, yes! I'm sorry!
Yes, she is the one...
Iona-chan!
Huh?
I've found it...
finally.
Tama! Wish Crisis!
I've found it!
Iona-chan?
The shoot is about to start.
Can you please stand by?
Yes. I'll be there right away.
That was incredible.
Don't you think so, too?
Well... I...
Want to battle again!
Tama likes battling Iona and Ulith!
Forever battling! Forever battling for eternity! I love eternity!
For eternity! For eternity!
I've found it.
We won.
I wonder how many losses she has now...
Kazuki
It's okay.
You can stay at home, Grandma.
But...
The café Ruuko went to with her friend's mom is the one down the street, right?
Yes.
She said that Ruuko got up and ran out in the middle of their conversation.
Man, what's come over her?
Grandma, you stay put. I'll go look for her.
What just happened?
I...
I forgot about Hitoe, Yuzuki, and Akira-san...
I forgot about them all.
That was incredible.
Don't you think so, too?
I'm scared... I'm scared!
What's happening to me?
Just how far am I going to go?
Ruu?
Tama.
I'm sorry, Tama. I can't battle anymore after all...
Ruuko.
Yuzuki!
U-Uhm...
Hey, Yuzuki? You know, I—
So, did you do it?
Did you... battle?
So you did.
I did it, too. And I won.
I wanna wanna
see you!
Bring Ruu-Ruu
along too!
Akira told us to go to her.
Akira-san?
Hanayo-san, do you sense anything?
No. Nothing.
Ruuko.
What was the girl you went up against like?
What do you mean?
Mine was around our age.
I wonder what she was wishing for...
Yuzuki...
Now what's this?
So you two are still enjoying your Selector lives?
Well, of course you are.
Yuzu-pon is trying to enter the forbidden
realm of love with her cute little brother...
And Ruu-Ruu is madly in love with battling...
Just like she is.
Wh-What do you mean by that?
Akira-san?
I'm so lucky to have met you two.
Lucky, lucky...
That
Girl
is
Desire
Aki-lucky.
Once you give yourself to the shadow of the clockwork
tokeijikake no kage ni unadzuitara
darkness begins to encroach from the door of the end
owari no doa ga hiraki hajimaru yami
Menacing answers lie hiding in wait
ayaui kotae soko ni miekakureru
Today's wish will become tomorrow's taboo
kyou no inori wa ashita tabuu ni naru
Lost in a labyrinth where the world is turned upside-down
ten to chi wo utsusu sakasama no meiro
the gears slowly start to turn
mawaridashita haguruma
Quietly from within the waves of people
hitogomi no naka de mimi wo sumashitara
a bell rings out, beckoning my very being
tamashii wo maneku ano suzu no ne hibiku sora e
I have no choice but to walk the endless path
mugen no hate made wo susumu shika nai
for this is the future I willingly chose
jibun de eranda mirai dakara
In the wake of the unreachable summer clouds
todokanai natsugumo yureru kagerou
lies the place of smiles I'll one day reclaim
itsuka torimodosu egao no basho
What's going on? I feel like
something's different today.
Yuzuki! What's the matter?!
If Yuzuki loses...
I won't become like her.
That's not good at all.
That
Oath
is
Falsehood
That oath is falsehood.