Hey... Where are you taking us?
Just get in.
This looks like...
[AL] It's Central Command...
We were right below it.
[ENVY] Hey.
You guys are
plastered with filth.
[AL] So they've been there this
whole time... I never would've
guessed they were beneath
the command center.
[ED] So maybe it's
not just the Fuhrer...
The entire military
might be involved...
But hey... there is some
good news in all of this...
[AL] You saw it...?!
My body's still in there?!
It is... I tried to reach out
for it, but it said that
it couldn't go with me
since I wasn't its soul.
[AL] My body...
It still exists...! Yes... Yes!
[ED]
Yes.
And now that we
know it's there,
we're one step closer
to gettin' it back.
[ED] Al...? What's that weird
little cat doing in here?
[AL] Uh... Well...
Y'know that little girl?
[ED] Are you serious?!
She's inside your armor?!
[AL] Brother...! Stop yelling!
And while you're at it,
will you put on some pants?
Hey, what's the hold up...?!
Get a move on!
[AL and ED]
Agghhhh!!!
Jeez, Al... Did you really
have to bring her along with us?
[AL] What else was I supposed
to do...? She's hurt pretty bad.
[ENVY]
Hey!
Wrath'll take over babysitting
you now... Right this way.
Wrath?
[ED'S INNER THOUGHT]
Wrath... Is Fuhrer King Bradley?
Colonel?
What's going on?
Where should I begin...?
Fuery's been shipped south...
Falman's been sent up north...
and Breda's been
reassigned to the west.
[ROY]
Lieutenant Hawkeye is now a
personal assistant
to the Fuhrer.
[ED'S INNER THOUGHTS]
Huh--What the hell is this?
They're practically
holding them hostage.
[BRADLEY]
Go ahead and take a seat.
[ED THINKS]
The guard's left us alone...
There are three of us
and only one of him.
[AL] He's only got one
sword with him.
[ROY] So, he's that confident he
could take us all at once...
[MAY CHANG COUGHS INSIDE AL]
[AL COVERS UP BY COUGHING]
Um... Fuhrer?
So what was that in the hospital
that day... when you came
to visit me...? You really
had us goin', didn't you.
I don't recall lying...
I instructed you to
suspect everyone...
And not to meddle any further...
The only thing that you
need to know is that you're
important to us...
And there's no need for you
to dig any deeper...
Accept the importance of
your role and keep
your heads down...
You do that and no harm
will come to you.
Well that's great for us...
But what happens to all of
the people who
aren't lucky enough
to be considered "sacrifices"?
There's nothing you need to
know that I haven't already
told you... Is that clear,
Fullmetal Alchemist?
[ED] You chose that as my title.
I only joined the military
because I thought it might
help us get our bodies back...
But now? Now I know what's
the State Alchemist program
really is... You're using it
as a way to recruit your
sacrifices... Well I'm
not gonna let you
use me to accomplish
your sick goals.
I resign my title
as a State Alchemist!
The symbol of a dog...
Fittingly crusted with blood.
Your plans are gonna fail...
I swear on my own grave
that I'm gonna stop you...
I'll warn the other State
Alchemists... I'll tell them--
[BRADLEY] What was that lovely
young girl's name again?
Ah, yes... It's Winry Rockbell.
Your automail engineer...
And you grew up in Resembool
as well, if I'm not mistaken...
She's practically a
family member, isn't she?
[BRADLEY] I've heard that she's
made quite a name for herself
with her customers
in Rush Valley...
Such a sweet and trusting girl.
You stay away from her!
Just leave her out of this!
[BRADLEY]
Well. That's up to you.
If you'd rather not take it,
then I will simply
have to cut her down.
How thoughtful.
[AL] Uh, Sir. You don't
have to worry about us...
But I have to ask... If we're
going to continue to serve
under your watch... Will you
please allow us to keep
searching for a way to get
our original bodies back?
[AL]
Please, Sir.
I don't see why not... As long
as you don't interfere with
our plans... And what do
you have in mind, Colonel...?
You wouldn't do something so
petty as to quit the military?
Good question...
I'm on a short leash here...
but I still find that
preferable to giving up.
And I still have my ambitions...
Your plans don't change that...
So I'll hang onto this...
And I'll retain my rank, too.
That's fine with me...
We have nothing more to discuss.
[ROY] I would like to ask
you one question... Sir.
Would you now...? Go ahead.
Are you the one who
murdered General Hughes?
No... That was not me.
Then who did?
Colonel...
I agreed to one question.
We'll be leaving now.
[BRADLEY]
Oh, just one moment, Alphonse.
[AL]
Is that all?
That's all...
You are now dismissed.
[AL]
That was too close!
I almost got stabbed
in the head!
[ED]
Oh, hey, Colonel.
Help us out...
Have you got any change?
You want my money now?
Just give it...! Jeez...
that all you got? Really?
It's apparently more
than you've got!
Sure, whatever... See ya.
Heyy!
[AL] Sorry, Colonel...!
We'll explain everything later!
What the hell's with them?
No...! The Lieutenant!
Lieuten--
Is there something
troubling you Colonel...?
You appear slightly discomposed.
Well just how do you expect
me to appear... I had hoped
a young woman would
be standing there,
not a mustachioed muscleman.
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel?
Lieutenant.
I was getting worried... Uh...!
Sorry... uh, Lieutenant Hawkeye.
Reporting back to post
from latrine break, Sir.
[HAWKEYE] Major Armstrong
happened to be passing by...
He was nice enough to
watch my post for me...
Thanks for everything,
Major... I appreciate it.
[ARMSTRONG]
No trouble at all.
So you didn't run off.
Someone once told me to never
give up, no matter what...
And once was all I needed.
Just don't ever tell
me you wished you'd
run when you had the
chance... Alright?
It's too late for regrets.
[WINRY]
Hello...? Ed?
Well this is a surprise...
You didn't break your
automail again, did you?
[ED OVER PHONE]
What, no!
[ED] I'm calling... because...
Is everything alright?
[ED OVER PHONE]
Have you noticed anything weird?
Like any suspicious
people following you?
Well, Ed...
What is it?
[WINRY OVER PHONE]
You're creeping me out.
What's creepy?!
[WINRY] It's just... Well, it's
actually pretty rare to get a
call from you... And I've never
heard you worry about me...
This is weirder than a
snowstorm during the summer.
Well, fine!
Maybe I won't worry--
[WINRY OVER PHONE]
Thank you, Ed.
Really... Thank you...
It means a lot.
Uh... Sure... You're certain
everything's okay, right...?
Yeah... 'kay... Bye.
I think she's
still safe for now.
[GREED] You know, it's that kind
of desperate worry they're
gonna manipulate you with.
[ED]
Ling?!
Nooo, it's Greed... Still.
What do you want?
Your pal asked me
to bring this to you?
[ED]
Ling did?
What does it say...?
It's in some other language.
Yea... It is... But
he just wants you
to deliver it to some girl.
Lan Fan...? Is this
some kind of trick...?
'Cuz if you follow us
and try to kill her...
I've got more class
than that, alright...?
And as a rule of thumb,
I don't fight women.
And another rule of mine
is to never tell a lie,
but hey... It's your call...
Hey, wait! Ling!
[GREED]
It's still Greed, kid.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SCAR THINKS] Who is
that godless monster?
What cause would bring
him to initiate a civil war
and ravage an entire country?
[MARCOH]
Is someone there?
Who is that...?
Did you come from outside?
I can help you if you're
injured... Why don't you
come down here...? Is
everything alright outside?
It's safe to come down...
The guard won't be back for
a while... Let me help
you with your injuries...
I'm actually a doctor.
So you're an Ishvalan...? Was
your head wounded in the--...
You're not the one
known as Scar, are you?
Tell me who you are first... And
what are you doing down here?
[MARCOH]
My god!
This must be fate.
I'm the alchemist
responsible for the
extermination of your people.
[KNOCS] It's nothing serious...
Just a mild concussion.
She'll be fine after
a few days of rest.
[AL]
I'm so relieved...
[KNOCS] Well I'm sure as hell
not! You seem to think this is a
hospital...! You've filled
my house with patients...!
Where am I 'sposed to sleep
now...?! Tell me that!
[AL]
I'm sorry...! I'm sorry!
[KNOCS]
I'm not running a halfway
[LAN FAN] You're back, Alphonse?
[KNOCS] house for
injured young girls!
[AL] Lan Fan!
What are you doing?!
You shouldn't be out of bed!
[LAN FAN]
The young Lord...
Isn't he with you?
[AL] He's not...
But he's still alive...
I've got a message from him.
[AL]
Lan Fan?
[LAN FAN] It says... It says he
found a Philosopher's Stone.
The Young Lord has saved
our clan... And now,
we have to return
to our country...
We've gotta get the
news to our people.
Where is he...?
Will you take me to him?
What's wrong? Why are
you being so quiet?
[LAN FAN] Has something
happened to the Young Lord?
Please, talk to me, Alphonse...!
Where is the Prince?
[BRADLEY] So what do you
think of that body, Greed?
Decent enough?
Ah, so you must be Wrath...
Yeah, the body's great...
Listen to this...
It's royalty...!
The kid was a prince of Xing.
The funny thing is he let me
take control... He thought
I could make him emperor
or something... What an
ambitious little brat.
I spoke to him once about
politics... His naiÃ ̄ve theories
on leadership were amusing...
He said a king's duty is to
his people...
As if the people actually
mattered when ruling a country.
[BRADLEY] The fool. Just
look where his allegiance
to the people has gotten
him now... Typical human.
[LING]
Shut the hell up!
Don't underestimate humans.
I know, I know... He's
patient... Just waiting for
any chance he can get...
I've gotta stay on my toes.
He must be starting to
reconsider his ambitions.
[BRADLEY] Now that he's taken a
monster like you into his flesh.
[ARMSTRONG]
Fuhrer Bradley is a Homunculus?!
It can't be.
[ARMSTRONG] The only thing
I ever wanted to do was
protect my fellow countrymen.
And I'm not the only one...
So many soldiers have put
their trust in the military...
And this...? This is the truth?
[ROY]
You could resign, Major.
With your disposition... I'm
afraid you'll suffer otherwise.
How can we fight a war
like this...?! It's wrong!
[FASSLER] Major...!
You're disobeying an order...!
You're dismissed...!
Call Central for a
replacement Alchemist.
[ARMSTRONG]
I collapsed in Ishval...
I couldn't bring myself
to stay and fight...
The military's methods
were ghastly...
I could see their malignance...
but still... I chose to turn
away and run when I should have
fought to protest their actions.
That decision... It's haunted
me every day since then...
It makes me sick that
I abandoned my beliefs.
And now that I face the military
again... I have to fight...
I couldn't live with
myself if I ran away now.
[HAWKEYE]
And how do you plan on
handling all of this, Colonel?
The Fuhrer asked me
that... I told him
I wasn't gonna quit or
give up my ambitions.
The Fuhrer seemed like he was
downright eager to reveal his
true nature as a Homunculus
to me... It appears he wants
me to know there's someone
even more powerful giving
him orders... Seems
they're testing me...
I have to admit I'm honored.
You seem surprisingly calm.
I don't know... It's
just... Well, it's similar
to how I felt during
the battle with Lust.
[ROY] I've been called a
human weapon and a monster...
Maybe I deserve it, but
I can tell you this much...
I never feel more human than
when I'm fighting real monsters.
[LAN FAN]
I see.
He accepted the stone...
And let the beast take control.
[AL] I'm sorry... I wish we
could've stopped him.
[LAN FAN] Don't apologize...
I'm only upset with myself for
being unable to protect
him... But the Prince...
He's not gone...
He's just trapped inside
of this Greed creature, right?
I need your help... I want a new
arm... As soon as possible.
[AL] Are you sure...?
You haven't healed yet--
I need an automail engineer
now... Please help me!
[AL] Yeah, okay...
I'll introduce you soon...
But you need to get your
strength back first...
I'll ask Doctor Knocs to
make you some food--
[AL] I don't think you
should be up yet...
It's uh... May Chang, right?
May?
[AL]
What's going on?
You're a watchdog
for the Yao Clan.
I know you too...
You're the Chang heiress.
Very good... I'm the 17th
daughter... Princess May Chang.
I also know why
you're in this country...
To obtain immortality.
Too bad you won't
live to see me get it.
You won't even
leave this room, Princess.
[AL]
Hey, just hold on a minute!
I don't know what this is about.
But you can't fight like this!
[MAY CHANG AND LAN FAN]
Quit trying to interfere with
the affairs of our country!
My wounds aren't
going to slow me down.
Is that so...?
Well neither will mine.
[KNOCS] What the hell do
you two think you're doing?!
You're supposed to
be resting in bed!
[MAY CHANG]
Quit trying to interfere with
the affairs of our--
I don't care about the affairs
of your country, dumb ass!
Jeez... It doesn't matter
where you're from,
you're both my patients.
You're not planning on making an
even larger mess around here,
are you...?! HUH...?! Because
if you do, you might release an
unknown pathogen
from the floorboards...
and kill everyone in the house.
[AL] How could it get
messier in here...?
I wonder how long it's been
since he's bothered cleaning.
[AL]
I found this on the floor.
So that's where
it's been all this time.
[AL] Hey...! You can't
throw away a family picture!
I don't speak to
my wife and son.
What's the big deal...?
And who are you to decide
what I do with my own stuff?
[KNOCS] Why don't you go get
some coffee or something?
[WOMAN] Thanks for
taking the time to come by.
I'm actually
surprised you came...
I was honestly starting
to get a little worried.
It worked... I'm able
use my alchemy again.
[SOLDIER 1] Hey, very
nicely done up there...
That takes care of all of
our repairs for the day.
Yeah, you can always rely
on a State Alchemist...
These other alchemists around
here just can't compare.
You should've seen those guys...
We had a couple of local
alchemists helping us with
repairs this morning...
All they really ended up doing
was looking foolish, though.
They came strolling in like
they were the very best...
And next thing ya know, their
alchemy wouldn't work!
[ED THINKS]
He said this morning...
That was when we
were underground.
[WOMAN]
Mr. Alchemist!
Thanks again!
[EDFACE A]
Thank you.
[ED THINKS] I know Envy
told me that they're just
mindless energy...
but I don't know...
It just doesn't feel
right to me...
Which means I'm
not fully convinced.
Snap out of it...! I've got
bigger things to be concerned
with... The alchemy...
If those guys were right,
then we weren't
the only ones who
couldn't transmute
this morning.
If so... How come Scar
and that little girl were
able to use theirs...?
What does that mean?
[ED THINKS]
Could their alchemy be
different from ours...?
That's the only thing that makes
sense... I'm gonna have to make
them teach it to me somehow.
And maybe I can use it
to get Al's body back and take
down that bearded bastard.
[ED THINKS]
Oh, yeah... I've gotta get
this to the Lieutenant.
[MARCOH] They forced me to
follow through with their plans.
I made a Stone for them.
And I used the lives of
countless Ishvalans to do it.
And now... They're forcing
me to cooperate on an
experiment that's likely to
result in another genocide.
I beg you... Please stop it!
You have to kill me, please...!
Please take my life!
My own death is the only form
of revenge that I have!
Your appearance here... Right
now... You're like a god to me.
[SCAR] Tell me everything
about Ishval... I want to hear
the entire story... What
did you use my people for?
You'll tell me... all of
it... Give me the truth
before my right
hand destroys you!
[NARRATOR] The violence of war.
It manages to terrorize long
after it's ceased. The soil
is left with a thirst for
the spilt blood and the
burning flesh stains the air.
This was Ishval...
And all that's left is
a loathsome memory.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood
Episode Thirty...
The Ishvalan War
of Extermination.
I shall tell you the truth,
even if no one else will.