You can really grant any wish, right?
Rest assured, your prayer will be heard.
Are you ready?
Yeah. Do it.
Now... just accept it.
This is your destiny.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 5
I will never regret this
Excuse me.
That wasn't very ladylike of me.
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Didn't get enough sleep?
Yes, I was at the hospital and had to deal with the police until late.
What? Did you get in trouble?
They said I was sleepwalking or something.
Oddly enough, there were a lot of people with the same symptoms,
and when I came to, they
were all lying around me.
Huh? What's up with that?
The doctors said it was called a
collective hallucination or something.
I have to go back for more
tests after school today too.
What a bother...
You should've just taken the day off.
I couldn't do that! That'd make it seem like I was actually sick,
and my family would get
even more worried about me.
That's our honor student!
You're so tough!
It's been a while since I've felt this good.
I feel wonderful!
Sayaka-chan, aren't you scared?
Hm? Well, yeah, I am a bit scared,
but I took care of that witch
pretty easily yesterday.
When I think about how I might've lost my two best friends,
I find that a lot more scary.
So I mean, I guess I have more confidence?
Maybe I'm just at ease.
I'm just a bit proud of myself too.
I guess I'm flying high.
You can count on Magical Girl
Sayaka-chan to protect Mitakihara City!
So you don't regret anything at all?
I guess if I had to name one...
It'd be the fact that
I hesitated for so long.
If only I had known, I would have become a magical girl sooner.
If Mami and I had fought that witch
together, she might not have died.
I...
Come on. Don't tell me you're thinking of something silly.
I... I should've...
I'm saying all of this now because I'm already a magical girl.
But I didn't know back then.
It's like I was destined to become a magical girl from the start.
Sayaka-chan...
After all, I found my wish.
Something that I wouldn't mind risking my life to fight for.
I'm just a little frustrated it
took me so long to realize that.
That's why you shouldn't feel guilty.
You don't have to turn into a
.magical girl if you don't want to.
Simple as that.
Yeah...
Anyway, I've gotta get going.
Huh? Do you have something to do?
You could say that.
I see. So they're not releasing you yet.
I still haven't completed the
rehabilitation for my legs.
I need to be able to walk freely first.
They say the recovery of
my hand is a total mystery,
so they need to look at it more thoroughly.
How are you feeling, though?
Is any other part of your body bothering you?
No. In fact, I feel so good, it's scary.
It's even starting to feel like the
.accident was all just a bad dream.
It makes me wonder why
.I'm in this bed to begin with.
This is a miracle, just like you told me.
What's wrong?
I said a lot of mean things to you.
Being depressed was no excuse—
Oh, don't worry about it.
Right now, you should be
completely and totally happy.
So don't make a face like that.
Right.
All of this just doesn't feel real.
Well, I can't blame you for that.
I guess it's about time.
Kyousuke, let's get a breath of fresh air.
Why are we going to the roof?
You'll see.
What are you all...
We'll have a real party
.when you're released,
but since your hand healed
faster than your legs...
I-Is that...
You told me to get rid of it,
but I just couldn't.
I...
Go on. Don't be scared.
Mami-san,
my wish came true.
I will never regret it.
This is the happiest I have ever been!
So that's the city's new magical girl, huh?
Do you really want to start a fight with her?
It just looks too easy.
I could kill someone like her in a heartbeat.
Or what?
Do you have a problem with that?
It may not be as easy as you think.
There's another magical
.girl in this city, after all.
Oh? Who is it?
I don't know either, really.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
She became a magical girl after
making a contract with you, right?
In one sense, she did.
In another, she didn't.
She's an extreme irregularity.
Even I can't predict her behavior.
Sounds fun.
It's getting too boring
around here, anyway.
Gotta shake things up once in a while.
What did you want to talk about?
U-Um, about Sayaka-chan...
She's very persistent,
and can be kind of stubborn.
She also has a quick temper...
But she's a really nice person!
She's kind and courageous,
and she'll go to any
length to help someone.
All fatal flaws for a magical girl.
Is... Is that true?
Excessive kindness leads to weakness.
Reckless courage leads to carelessness.
There's also no reward
for dedication of any kind.
You can't be a magical girl
unless you understand that.
That's why Tomoe Mami lost her life.
Don't say it like that!
Sayaka-chan's saying
that she'll be fine,
but when I think she might
end up like Mami-san,
I just don't know what to do.
You're worried about
.Miki Sayaka, aren't you?
I can't do anything for her anymore,
so I want to ask you.
Could you be friends
with Sayaka-chan?
Don't fight her like
.you did with Mami-san.
It should be much safer if you all
fight the witches together, right?
I don't want to lie,
and I don't want to make
.any promises I can't keep.
So I want you to give up on Miki Sayaka.
Why...
She shouldn't have
.formed the contract.
This is partially my fault too.
I should've kept a closer
.eye on her, as I did you.
So—
But now that I've taken responsibility,
I must tell you that it's a
.mistake that cannot be undone.
It'd be like trying to bring
someone back from the dead.
Once you become a magical girl,
there's no hope for salvation.
That contract takes away everything in exchange for a single hope.
Does that mean you've given up too?
Given up on yourself
and on all the other girls?
That's right.
I won't make excuses
.and say I'll try to atone.
I must continue with my struggle, with whatever sin I have to bear.
It seems I've wasted your time.
I apologize.
Are you nervous?
Kind of.
One mistake and I'm a goner.
Madoka?
Sayaka-chan, are you going to...
Yep. I'm going on patrol
.to search for evil witches!
It's what a hero does.
Will you be okay by yourself?
Of course.
Mami-san did this too.
I'm her successor, right?
I can't do anything,
and I know I'll just get in the way,
but could you take me with you—
at least until I become a burden?
Aren't you trying a little too hard?
I'm sorry...
I shouldn't. I knew I'd get in your way.
No, I'm really happy.
Hey, can't you tell?
My hands have been
.shaking this entire time.
Pathetic, huh?
I'm a magical girl now, but I
kinda feel helpless by myself.
Sayaka-chan...
You're not a burden.
I'd love for you to come.
Having someone by my side
would make me feel a lot better.
That alone makes me feel invincible.
I...
I swear I'll protect you.
So relax and just follow me.
Let's go get those witches
together like we always have.
Okay!
You know how dangerous this is, right?
I'm stupid, so I might do something reckless if I'm by myself.
I think I'll be more careful just knowing you're by my side.
I see.
Well, so long as you have a plan, it's fine.
Kyubey...
You have a plan too. Right, Madoka?
I know how you want to protect Sayaka.
With you there, we'll have an ace up
our sleeve in the worst case scenario.
I...
You don't have to
say anything right now.
I'm sure Sayaka
will be against it too.
But I'll be ready whenever
you make up your mind.
Okay.
It's here.
This barrier was probably made by a familiar, not a witch.
The easier, the better.
I don't have a lot of experience.
You can't let your guard down.
I know.
Is that it?!
It's getting away!
Leave it to me!
Hey now, what are you two doing?
It's getting away!
Can't you tell? That's not
a witch, it's a familiar.
It won't have a Grief Seed.
If you let it escape,
someone's going to get killed!
You just have to wait until it eats four or five people and becomes a witch.
That way, you'll be able
.to get a Grief Seed from it.
Why would you want to slaughter the chicken before it lays any eggs?
You're going to just sit back and
watch the witch kill everyone?
Listen, newbie. I think you're
getting this all wrong.
Have you ever heard of the food chain?
I'm sure you learned about it in school.
The witches eat the weak humans.
And we in turn eat those witches.
That's the natural order.
The weak have to
.give way to the strong.
No...
You...
Oh, don't tell me.
You made a contract with him just to play out some ridiculous farce,
like pretending to be a hero
and rescuing people, right?
And what if I did?!
C'mon. Give it up already.
It ticks me off when someone gets in my way to play out a joke.
Sayaka-chan!
Hmph. Stupid rookie.
Cool your head a bit.
That's weird.
That should've been enough to put you in hospital for three months.
Sayaka-chan's okay?
She became a magical girl using a wish for healing, after all.
Her ability to recover
from damage is exceptional.
Who'd lose to you?
It's because people like you
..are around that Mami-san...
You're annoying.
You're so freaking annoying!
Actually, you shouldn't even
be talking to me that way.
You should respect your elders.
Shut up!
This isn't the time to be
jumping around, dummy!
Sayaka-chan!
Madoka, it's too dangerous!
If you're too dumb to understand words
and you don't get it when I beat you down...
I'll just have to kill you!
I won't lose...
I won't lose!
Why...
Why is this happening?
..There isn't a witch here...
Why do two people on the
same side have to fight?
It's hopeless.
Neither of them intend to back down.
Please, Kyubey! Make them stop!
This shouldn't be happening!
I can't do anything.
But if you want to stop them by force...
It's not like there aren't
.any options on the table.
Only another magical girl can come between their battle.
But you have the capacity to do that, if that's what you really wish.
That's right...
If I make a contract too...
It's over!
I...
There's no need for that.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki wo koete
will transcend time
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume wo
and destroy one of this world's dreams
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai wo nomihoshite
What is it that you seek
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani?
now that you're done hesitating?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no?
beyond this greedy admiration?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
I want to be armed with the power
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no youni
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
the next time I see your innocent smile.
微笑む君に合いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In my trembling hands I hold
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
the courage of a plucked flower
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings are all I can rely on;
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari wo yobisamasu
the prayer that awakens
光を呼び覚ます
negai
the light
願い
Illustrated by   Yuupon (nitro+)
Sayaka-chan, you became a
magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch.
She's a magical girl like you!
This is definitely wrong.
Episode 6
This is definitely wrong