[MAYU]
Do you know the Girl of White?
So pure and innocent,
with a heart as warm
as the morning sun.
But there is a Girl
of Black as well.
Cruel and wicked, with a heart
as cold as the darkest night.
She burns with jealousy.
Resenting every shining
smile that dances upon
the cheeks of the Girl of White.
And eventually, that bitter
hatred turns to thoughts
of erasing her very existence.
--Hello. Eavesdropping?
--[FUTASE gasps]
[MAYU]
Do you want to hear a secret?
[FUTASE]
Huh...?
[MAYU]
The girls I just spoke of...
They may be separate, but they
came from the same person.
Are you ready to go?
To the world of black and white?
[FUTASE grunts, gasps]
[FUMIO gasps]
All right, good work you two!
You're free to go.
See you next time!
Come meet me in my
dressing room.
[gasps] Urith--
[URITH (I)]
Not that name.
Not with people around.
I, uh...
Yeah, I'm sorry...
Remember.
This is our little secret.
I'll be waiting.
Okay!
[URITH (I)]
Oh, Iona.
You don't know
what you're in for.
[RUKO] You're saying Iona
is the Girl of Black?
Is that true?
You can tell me.
[IONA]
What's... happening to me?
So do you know...
where Fumio ended up?
[FUMIO] That was the last
I ever saw of her.
[HITOE]
I hope she's okay...
[YUZUKI sighs]
This is getting confusing.
So there's a Girl of Black
and maybe she's an LRIG?
What does that mean
for the game?
Anything?
And is the Girl of White
out there, too?
[gasps] White...
[HITOE]
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Mayu didn't tell me
anything else.
I'm afraid I'm
as confused as you.
[CHIYORI sighs]
[HITOE]
Chiyori?
[ELDORA]
If you gotta pee, just say so.
[CHIYORI yells]
--[HITOE gasps]
--Are you okay?
[CHIYORI]
I'm awesome!
[ELDORA] She has these
little conniption fits
from time to time.
Just ignore her and carry on.
So the WIXOSS novel
you wrote is, like,
the symbol of eternal friendship
between you and Fumio?!
Oh my gosh! I love it!
That's so cool!
Friendship?
But it was just
an online thing
when you first
started, wasn't it?
[FUMIO]
Yes.
I didn't know much
about being a novelist.
But when I did some research,
I read that a lot of people
test the waters that way.
[FUMIO gasps]
[FUMIO] To be honest,
I didn't expect things
to turn out so well.
A touching friendship,
a happy ending!
It's all so cool,
I could explode!
[ELDORA] What "happy ending"?!
This whole thing is a disaster!
[HITOE] I wonder what the
original Fumio is doing now.
[ANN] There's no way
for us to find her.
It's bad enough to have
to go through all this once.
But then getting out
of that card
only to become a Selector again.
That's awful.
[YUZUKI]
But wait. I don't get it.
You wrote some books.
Wish granted. You're done.
Why would you still be
fighting as a Selector?
It's not like it's
your wish, right?
That's a bit ironic
coming from you, I'd say.
Like how?
[FUMIO]
If you're a LRIG now,
that means you were
a Selector yourself once.
You must have had a dream that
meant more to you than anything.
I'm sure you believed
the words of your LRIG
and counted on her
to grant that wish,
no matter what kind
of miracle it took.
[YUZUKI] Hanayo wasn't trying
to deceive me on purpose.
She was always
looking out for me.
Even now.
That hasn't changed.
[FUMIO] Would it be enough
if your wish only came true
for a short while?
After all you've been through?
Well, I mean--
[FUMIO] I imagine it's precisely
the sort of thing
that would be meaningless
if it didn't last forever.
[YUZUKI sighs]
No... you're right.
I wasn't thinking.
[FUMIO]
How about you?
[CHIYORI gasps]
[ELDORA sighs]
Now you know.
That's how Fumio felt, too.
Being a novelist didn't
mean writing one book.
It meant writing them
for her entire life.
Writing only two novels
doesn't give me the right
to call myself a novelist.
I'm merely an ephemeral
shell of an existence
that will fade once
the writing stops
There's no end.
The wishes that we grant
are not mere fleeting fancies.
They must continue until death.
A miracle forged in tears.
There's no end.
No escape from this.
Unlike Fumio, I was neither well
read nor particularly creative.
That's why my choice of
subject matter is what it is.
Thankfully, my personal story
proved interesting
enough to sell books.
Or it has thus far.
[ANN] But the well of
knowledge has since gone dry.
[ELDORA]
You reached the end.
That's why you've got
writer's block, now, huh?
But it's all gonna work out!
Fueled by the power
of friendship,
her stories will live on in your
heart and continue forever!
[FUMIO]
Life isn't a damned book!
[CHIYORI gasps]
Ahh...?
[FUMIO "The power
of friendship" can't save you!
There's no such thing!
[CHIYORI]
But I know you can do it!
[FUMIO]
I'm not a writer!
I never was!
But I can't stop!
[CHIYORI whimpers]
[FUMIO] I don't know if
it's the promise we made,
or something built into me,
or just a fear of the abyss
that keeps me going.
What am I doing?
Why am I doing it?
I don't even know
who the hell I am anymore.
[ELDORA]
If you aren't trapped in a card,
you're trapped by a wish.
What can you call this
existence, but a curse?
Imprisoned by
the dream of another.
Forced to struggle
for it as an LRIG
and forever after,
until you lose yourself.
[FUMIO] I'm going to
the White Room again.
I'm going to speak
with Mayu again.
Because if I don't, then the
story can't continue, you see?!
So who's battling me next, you?
--You?!
--[CHIYORI gasps]
I don't care who,
but let's make it quick.
[CHIYORI gasps, whimpers]
[HITOE]
I'm not gonna battle you!
And neither will Chiyori!
I see. That's a pity...
But wait...
Thanks to that last battle...
...I can continue
the story after all.
I need to write.
I need to write...
[ANN]
You understand now?
I'm sure you think you're
acting on some sort of
moral high ground
by refusing to battle,
but it's not that simple.
--No, that's not what I'm--
--[ANN] Some people have
no choice but to do this.
And she's one of them.
[gasps]
[FUMIO]
The White Room...
Mayu...
The giant window...
I have to write...
I have to go...
...to the White Room...
[YUZUKI]
Don't let it upset you too much.
Fine...
[YUZUKI sighs]
--[CHIYORI sobs]
--Chiyori?
[YUZUKI] All she ever talks
about are those novels.
That must've been
pretty rough on her.
You're the one
I'm worried about.
[chuckles]
Yeah, it did kinda shake me up.
Poor Hanayo.
She's suffering just like me.
I guess there're
no winners here after all.
Even if an LRIG
becomes human again,
they still can't really be free.
Don't lose hope.
That's just another reason
for us to put an end to this.
[RUKO]
I'm so dumb.
I thought if everyone
knew the truth,
they wouldn't want
to battle anymore.
Like it's that easy.
Don't say that.
It's true.
Not everybody is like me.
Some Selectors need to win.
[YUZUKI] No. Fumio's
a special case, okay?
[RUKO]
It's not just her. Akira, too.
Even though the game hurt her,
she needs it to get
her confidence back.
I can't say I'm happy
to be a Selector,
but it did let me meet you guys.
[YUZUKI]
Hey, come on! Not you, too!
[RUKO] That doesn't mean
I want to give up.
[YUZUKI, HITOE gasp]
We can't judge.
Every Selector deals with their
suffering in a different way.
But no matter who they
are or what they do,
I'm not going to stop until I've
saved every one of them!
[gasps]
Ruko...
[RUKO] That goes for
Fumio and Futase, too.
I'm sure there's some way
to get them back to normal
and I'm gonna find it.
Iona, what you said...
[IONA]
You have to find yourself again.
I became your LRIG
because I believed in you!
Because I knew
you were strong!
That meant a lot,
and it helped remind me
of what I need to do
to stay on my path.
So, thanks, Ion--
[gasps]
[panting]
Iona?! What's wrong?!
[URITH (I) chuckles]
Such a good girl.
[gasps] I owe you everything.
[URITH (I)] Oh? Well,
I'm happy to hear that.
[URITH (I)]
Actually, though.
I have another favor to ask.
[gasps] What? I'll do it!
Anything!
[URITH (I)] It's something
that only you can accomplish.
[AKIRA]
Mm-hmm!
Sure. I understand.
But, it's her. She'll
probably refuse to battle.
Then you find what she
treasures most in this world.
Ah?
[URITH (I)] You're smart,
you can figure it out.
I'm looking forward
to a good show.
[gasps]
[URITH (I)] Whatever you do,
don't let me down.
[door latches]
[RUKO]
I'm home, Grandma!
So you are--welcome back.
[HITOE]
Uh. Hello again!
Hi! It's nice to have you!
[MAYU]
The Girl of Black.
The Girl of Darkness.
What's happening?
[MAYU] As I said,
you're the Girl of Black.
[IONA]
What does that mean?
[MAYU] You envy everyone,
bring everyone suffering.
You hate everyone,
and everyone hates you.
[MAYU]
Such a bad girl.
Such a lonely, lonely girl.
[IONA] You're lying.
I don't believe you!
[MAYU] Drowning, dripping,
drenched in hatred.
Oh, make them suffer!
Make them feel your pain!
[IONA]
No...
No, stop it!
[MAYU]
Battling for all eternity.
Spreading misery to everyone.
Such is the fate of
--the Girl of Black.
--[IONA] It's not true!
Stop it...
Wha-What now?
I think she's sick.
Do you have any medicine?
Let me see!
[YUZUKI] Wait! How are we
supposed to give it to her?
Oh. Guess you're right.
[YUZUKI]
This has never happened to me,
so I don't know what to say.
[RUKO]
Iona...
Can you tell us what's wrong?
Are you cold?
Do you have a fever?
Is it a stomach ache, maybe?
[IONA]
Why is she acting like this?
[RUKO] If there's anything
I can do, just tell me!
Please!
[IONA] Why is she
so worried about me?
I'm right here, okay?
[IONA] Is that why
this hurts so much?
I'm cold, that's all.
[MAYU]
You should know better.
Of course it hurts.
You're the Girl of Black.
Your body rejects the light.
And it rejects you as well.
Longing for white
will only bring you
more and more suffering.
But please, be as
miserable as you like.
She seems to be doing better.
Yeah.
[YUZUKI]
It's tricky...
...but this
"Girl of Black" thing
might be the piece of
the puzzle we're looking for.
Right.
Then you think Iona's
hiding something from us?
[YUZUKI] We'll get some answers
out of her when she wakes up.
Maybe we just need
to be her friend.
That might be the only way
to get her to open up.
[YUZUKI]
You think?
I don't think she
wants to trick us.
She probably has a reason
for not talking.
It was wrong, but, I mean...
I had things I didn't tell Tama.
I was so wrapped up
in my own feelings.
I didn't think about what
she was going through at all.
And I know that hurt her,
so even if Iona's different,
I don't wanna make
the same mistake twice.
[HITOE sighs]
[YUZUKI]
You're such a softie!
[RUKO, HITOE gasp]
Wha-huh?
I'm all like, "We'll get
some answers out of her,"
and now you make me look bad!
[YUZUKI growls]
[BOTH laugh]
Don't worry.
It's our second chance.
And this time, we're all
honest, and we're all friends.
I like it.
Yeah.
[knock on door]
[HATSU]
Ru?
[HATSU] I don't mean
to rain on your parade,
but it's a bit late. Hitoe's
parents might be worried.
Oh. I didn't notice the time!
I-I'll see you later!
[YUZUKI]
Hitoe.
Can I... stay with Ruko?
[HITOE]
Yeah. Go ahead.
If I was allowed,
I'd spend the night, too.
But I guess I'll see you
again soon, huh?
I'll walk you home.
We both will.
[HITOE]
This is far enough.
You guys have Iona
to take care of.
[RUKO]
Right. Be careful.
I'll call when
I get home, okay?
[thunder rumbles]
Uh-oh--I'd better get moving.
[AKIRA]
That took forever!
You sure like to keep
a girl waiting!
[HITOE]
Ah. Akira...
[AKIRA] C'mon, Hitoe,
let's have a Battle.
Huh?
[AKIRA] We haven't done it since
we got our new LRIGs, right?
It'll be fun!
I don't want to.
You scared I'm gonna
beat you again?
[gasps]
Aw, it's cool!
We'll take it slow!
So I can torment you
all night long.
No, you can't make me.
[AKIRA]
Aw, aren't you tough?!
Well, if you say no,
I'll just ask Ru-Ru!
Bye!
Stop it! She doesn't
want to either!
[AKIRA]
What?
[HITOE gasps]
You think I gotta listen to you?
I won't let anyone hurt Ruko!
Got it? We've had enough!
"Had enough"?
I'm just getting started!
Do not push your luck
with me, you little nobody!
We're not enemies!
We're fighting to save you, too!
Well, aren't you just a saint!
Sorry, but I don't buy it.
'Fraid it's gonna take
a Battle to convince me!
[MILULUN] You're wasting your
time--this doofus
doesn't even have
her LRIG with her.
Huh?!
That's right, I can't sense it.
[AKIRA]
What? Why the hell not?!
Looks like you'll have to play
plain old WIXOSS instead, huh?
To hell with that!
Damn it. Ugh, this sucks.
C'mon, think.
Urith is counting on me, here.
So what happens
if I let her dow-- Oh!
Oh god, no!
She's gonna hate me forever!
I can't take this!
What? I don't--
She'll dump me...
Throw me away...
No, I can't...
I hate this...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
[URITH (I)] You're smart.
You can figure it out.
I'm looking forward
to a good show.
--Akira, are you--
--[AKIRA] Wait a second.
There's still a use for her.
It's perfect!
[gasps]
[thunder cracks]
[IONA]
It's dark.
[RUKO]
The rain's really picking up.
[YUZUKI]
I hope Hitoe got home okay.
[IONA]
It feels warm.
[IONA grunts]
Iona!
Do you remember what happened?
It seemed like you were
in a lot of pain.
I'm right here, okay?
[IONA] I see.
It wasn't a dream after all.
[RUKO]
Feeling better now?
Yes...
Thank goodness!
I know it's silly, but you
looked like you were cold,
so I, uh...
[IONA] She does know how
an LRIG works, doesn't she?
[phone rings]
[YUZUKI]
Maybe it's Hitoe!
Yeah. Uh, Grandma? I got it!
Hey, Hitoe--startin' to
think you drowned out there!
[AKIRA] Hitoe can't come
to the phone right now,
'cause she's not playing nice!
[RUKO whimpers]
Wait, Akira?
[AKIRA]
Bingo!
The great detective Ru-Ru
solves another mystery!
[RUKO]
Where's Hitoe?
[AKIRA] Shut your mouth
and I'll tell you.
[RUKO] Ahh... Oh.
Yeah, no problem.
--[HITOE] No, Ruko!
--Hitoe?
[AKIRA]
You will not ruin this!
[crashing]
Akira! Stop it!
I'll be right there!
Please, don't hurt her!
[AKIRA] Don't be an idiot
like our little friend here
and forget your LRIG.
I wouldn't want Iona
to miss out on the party!
Yeah, but...
...Iona can't really--
[AKIRA]
Get your ass over here!
--[line clicks]
--[RUKO gasps]
Did she get soaked or what?
Ruko...?
Akira took Hitoe hostage,
and she wants me to bring Iona.
[YUZUKI gasps]
[IONA]
Fine. We'd better hurry.
You can't!
[IONA]
And have you go alone?
It's fine, I'm better now.
Okay. Thank you.
I'm sorry!
[thunder crakcs]
Over there!
[gasps]
Hitoe!
[thunder cracks]
No...!
Don't be a drama queen.
She's not dead.
I had to do something.
Look, she bit my arm!
What am I supposed to do
for my next photo shoot?
[YUZUKI]
You're the one who started it!
[AKIRA snarls]
This is a pain for me, too!
It's your fault for
not being with her!
Speaking of which, where's Iona?
[IONA]
I see you've sunk to a new low.
You guys missed quite
the show, by the way.
Hitoe was acting all hardcore.
"I won't let anyone hurt Ruko!"
And then I kicked her ass!
--[HITOE grunts]
--Stop it!
Can't have these little nerds
getting any big ideas,
you know.
If you want to
battle me that badly,
then let's get it over with!
Ruko!
But after I win, you're
gonna stop this for good!
[AKIRA]
That's cute and all,
but I don't think you
understand the situation here.
She's here!
Finally!
The rain kept me.
I hope I'm not too late.
Urith...
[URITH (I)]
How unsightly.
How disgusting.
I'm not interested in you.
What a letdown.
And besides, where's
the fun in that?
It might not be my style.
[RUKO] Next time:
"That Lie, a Scar".