On the night when the countless stars and the fleeting new moon decorated the sky,
Welcome
to
Fumizuki
Academy
I was cornered by two rather brave girls from my class.
Aki, will you hold me?
Akihisa, I beg you. Please hold me.
I... can't.
But why?
Don't... you like me?
It's... too hard for me.
If you don't want to, I'll get Tsuchiya to do it.
Is that what you want, Aki?
Yeah. I don't mind.
That's what he said. Will you hold them, Tsuchiya?
Here's one more.
The peeping tom
This is Stone Hugging, also known as the Killer Counter, a torture technique from the Edo period.
Argh
A
Peeping tom
holding
stone slabs
I will not forgive... cheating.
Akihisa, you too, please.
No!
These girls are being a little too brave tonight.
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
though a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Let's go back in time. Things were a little different than usual that morning.
Episode 5
Me, peeping, and the training camp!
While nervously waiting for the school trip tomorrow, Yoshii Akihisa received a letter.
It was a pretty arousing message.
"I know your secret."
Who could've done this?
Art thou unwell, Akihisa? Thou lookst down so early in the morning.
I-It's nothing! Really!
You're acting suspicious, Aki. You're hiding something.
Of course not, Minami! Look, my hands are empty!
I bet you... received a love letter.
Be more prudent, Minami. You know how the boys in this class are.
Who am I kidding? There's no way you'd get a love letter.
That's not true! Just this morning, my shoe locker was full of—
The next one won't miss.
I beg your forgiveness.
Then be honest and tell me!
Actually, I received some blac—
I shouldn't tell her about the letter. The criminals in movies usually...
A what?
Umm... Th...
Games
When under stress, the human brain plays association games with its memories,
Games are interesting
-teresting
-tailresting
tails
just like a rewinding roll of film.
cats have tails
underwear with cats
underwea- bikinis
T-The "Competitive Swimsuit Appreciation Society" sent me an invitation!
Documentary
A Day in the Life
of a Professional
Swimmer!
Aiming for Glory
in the Olympics
Akihisa watched a documentary,
"A Day in the Life of a Professional Swimmer" last night.
So, are you going to join?
I-I was always interested in them, you see.
Oh fuck, I've passed the point of no return.
And just what is it about athletic swimsuits that interests you?
What interests me the most is...
How they fit so tightly?
I sound like a frickin' perv!
Shimada, I hope thou knowst 'tis all a jest.
Oh? I didn't doubt it because it seemed just like him.
I told you to answer me honestly! What are you hiding from me?!
I... received some blackmail.
That's it? That's all right then.
And what doth it threaten you about?
It says to stay away from the girls around me.
Hmm. Judging from how serious it sounds, I'd say 'tis from someone jealous of thee.
In other words, it's someone who loves one of the two girls in our class, Himeji or Hideyoshi.
Akihisa, Shimada hath gone to fetch a metal baseball bat.
Did I count them wrong?
Then, how art thou being blackmailed?
What was it again?
"If you don't heed my warning, I'll make the enclosed photographs public."
These are from the last cultural festival, are they not?
W-When did he take these?
I hope there aren't any ridiculous ones.
I'm wearing boxers, so it's fine! I'm wearing boxers, so it's fine!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
Nah. If this is all he's got, I don't care.
Shit!!
Don't look at my pictures! I've been soiled! Don't look!
I don't get it, but calm down, Akihisa!
He's too powerful! Such a foul, dastardly plan!
Thou art worrying too much. Everyone dresses up as a maid at least once in their life.
Good morning, Akihisa, Kinoshita.
Ah, Himeji!
Good timing! Ask her if those pictures are really worth getting so worked up about.
What are you talking about?
Himeji, what wouldst thou do if thou saw pictures of Akihisa in a maid uniform?
Let's see. I'd run them through a scanner.
How else would I be able to show the entire Internet Akihisa's charms?
Don't be hasty, Akihisa!
Let me go! I've lost the will to live!
How about we ask Voyeur's opinion too?
Of course! That's good advice, Hideyoshi.
I'm so glad to have you as my bride.
Dost not thou mean "groom"?
I think both of you are confused about something.
Shit.
Oh, there you are! Voyeur, I wanna ask you some—
Do it later! I have an appointment.
Huh? For what?
Yuuji's getting married soon.
That's not something he can get out of.
I have bigger problems! I'm going to be known as a cross-dressing pervert!
How does it matter when you really are one?
Shut up, you married man! Go kill yourself!
You shut the fuck up! Go start working at a maid café!
Drop it. You're just making each other feel bad.
So like I was saying, this was confiscated from Shouko.
I'll propose to you if I win the tournament.
I love you, Shouko!
On the second day of the cultural festival at Fumizuki Academy,
Akihisa and Hideyoshi forged a proclamation of undying love.
Kirishima's so cute! She remembers that like it's something precious.
She's going to show it to her father as proof that we're engaged.
Shouko isn't good enough with electronics to pull this off. This is someone else's doing.
And what did you want, Akihisa?
Pictures of me dressed as a maid are about to be spread all over the Internet.
What on Earth happened?
Sorry, I went too fast.
It's like this... It went like this and that...
I see. Show me the pictures.
Here.
Good Lord!
What's wrong, Voyeur?!
They have... better angles than mine.
Even though you're my friend!
Don't worry! I won't spread them for free.
For free?! Don't spread them for money either!
I see. Akihisa's situation is kinda like mine.
Both of you are being threatened by someone spying on you.
Secret
Camera
Voyeur, I'd like you to investigate.
In return, I'll give you the porn mags you wanted—
I'll look into it.
I'll give you a copy of "Hidden Booty: Part Two"—
I promise I'll look into it.
That's all about the school trip.
School trip
Oh, we're going to the Mizuki plains?
It's really popular in the summer.
I can't wait! I can't wait!
Word of warning. Every class will gather separately before leaving.
I bet Class A will be going in a charter bus.
We'll probably be crammed into a minibus.
I bet I'll have to either sit on a baby seat or stand.
Or maybe in the trunk or on bicycle...
Class F has to find their own transportation.
Too bad
They aren't even taking us there!
It's called "social inequality."
There's nothing to do.
I'm bored.
Minami, what are you reading?
A book about personality tests.
Heh, that sounds interesting! Give me some!
Sure!
Well then...
Name the first girl you think of when you hear each of these colors.
One, green. Two, orange. Three, blue.
Green, orange, and blue?
Orange is Hideyoshi, blue is Himeji, and green is Minami.
I'd love to know why Mizuki is blue and I'm green.
I wonder if she'll get mad if I tell her I remember seeing her in green undies.
I won't get mad, I promise!
Because I've seen you in green undies!
Sakamoto, open the window, please.
Sure.
She's gonna throw me out of the window!
Let's see. Green is for "friend," orange for "source of energy," blue for—
Ah! Don't! Give that back!
Akihisa, who was the girl thou thought of for orange?
You, Hideyoshi.
That makes me happy, for some reason.
So, Minami, what about the girl associated with blue?
Question two!
It doth not look like she wants to answer.
Say the first two numbers between 1 and 10 that come to your mind.
Five and six.
Two and seven.
One and four, I guess.
I pick three and nine.
Yuuji
Hideyoshi
Akihisa
Mizuki
The first number represents the side of yourself you show to everyone.
Sakamoto's five means "cool and cynical."
Kinoshita's two means "calm and straightforward."
Aki's one means... go jump off a cliff.
Mizuki's three means "gentle and prudent."
Am I the only one who gets a death sentence?
Yuuji
Hideyoshi
Akihisa
Mizuki
The second number represents your hidden, true nature.
Sakamoto's six means "fair and kind."
Kinoshita's seven means "charming beauty."
Aki's four means... get crushed under a steamroller and jump off a cliff.
Mizuki's nine means "strong-willed."
Didn't my death sentence get even worse?
Looks like thou hast awoken.
Good morning, Voyeur.
I woke up because I'm hungry.
Well, it's almost time.
Let's have lunch then!
In that case, here! I made a lunchbox!
Please feel free—
S-Sorry! I already made one for myself!
Forgive me! I, too, made one for myself!
Mine's ready.
Just let Akihisa enjoy it by himself, Himeji.
Actually, I have some sandwi—
Chomp
Sorry, Akihisa. My hand slipped.
You should be more careful, Yuuji.
Oh, no! My hand slipped too!
I'll hold it real tight, so it doesn't slip.
Geez, what do you think you're doing? Here.
Aki, wanna eat these?
Yay! They look delicious!
P-Please help yourself.
Thanks! I will!
You know, Aki? I've been meaning to say this, but...
I put a lot of mustard in it!
Fire!
What are you, a spice demon?
Spicy
Oh! Hot! Hot!
Akihisa, that's lucky in a way.
I get it! Now that all my taste buds are dead...
Akihisa, have mine too!
Sure! Thanks for the food!
Three hundred joules! Clear!
What... happened?
I thought thou wert lost when thou started confessing the crimes of thy previous life.
Where am I?
The boarding house.
We arrived while you were away wandering between life and death.
The four of us are in the same room.
Well then, Akihisa's woken up too.
Let's get the ball rolling.
What do you mean?
We'll look for the people who spied on the two of us.
I have obtained some information.
Really, Voyeur?
I've found traces of the equipment the suspects used.
They used the same methods and tools on both Akihisa and Yuuji.
Culprit
Thus, I've deduced that they are, in fact, the same person.
Who is it?
I don't know.
I understand. You didn't have much time.
I only know that she's a girl and that she has burns on her rear.
What exactly were you investigating?
I put up tiny cameras all around the school.
Look at what it caught.
This is...
the girls' changing room.
Why is it pixelated?
I'm not gonna let you see it for free.
I thought we were friends.
Don't tell me that's... Shouko?!
That's Shouko's phone!
Correct.
Let me zoom in.
Let's see.
"I have a request. I'd like one more copy of Yuuji's proposal."
That's what she sent.
Fuckin' Shouko!
She's received a reply.
"Thank you. I'll give you a discount since this is the second one.
The school trip's tomorrow, so I'll deliver it to you next Monday."
Fucking close! Saved by the field trip!
"Meanwhile, here's some more."
What the fuck is this?!
I'm ruined for marriage!
At least it proves the two suspects are indeed the same guy.
This is where it gets serious.
She's replying to him.
"These photographs are simply amazing, but it'd be bad if we were to be discovered."
Sending message
Receiving message
A reply already?!
"Just between us, my mother found out last time. She literally practiced moxibustion on my rear."
"I still have those burns."
"Isn't it cruel to do that to a girl?"
This is all I've found out.
I see. This means it's one of the girls or Hideyoshi.
A girl with burns on her butt, huh?
But we can't see them, even if we flip their skirts.
Even my infrared camera wouldn't be able to see them.
I know! They'll be going for a bath soon, so we can get Hideyoshi to search for her!
Dost thou not see something wrong with thy premise that I can get inside the girls' bath?
Akihisa, look at the schedule for the trip.
"The following is the schedule for each class to use the bath."
Kinoshita Hideyoshi of Class F
Private bath no. 4
We can't use Hideyoshi after all!
Why is it just me?
You there! Freeze!
Put your hands above your head!
What?!
I said, put your hands above your head!
Kinoshita, come with me. Quick!
What the...
What the hell is going on?
We know what you're up to.
Huh?
I'm talking about these.
I found these hidden in a corner of the girls' changing room.
Someone was peeping on you? Who would do such a thing?!
Don't play dumb. We know it was you!
Thou art mistaken! The one who was peeping on you was... It was...
I can't deny that it was us.
Is that true, Akihisa?
I never would've thought you boys would do this.
You didn't do it, did you, Aki? I believe in you.
Why are you...
carrying torture devices if you believe me?
You're horrible, Akihisa! How dare you peep on me after I've had a big dinner?
I'm slimmer during the rest of the day, okay?!
That's what you're mad about?!
Me too! My breasts are bigger during the rest of the day.
No way. That's not possible.
Get them!
Shit! I said that out loud!
Yuuji! Do someth—
I will not forgive... cheating.
Shit! He's done for!
Him too!
We'll give you...
plenty of love, you hear?
That was a horrible accusation.
Although, I got off easy for being your victim.
It really is unfair. We haven't even started to peep yet.
We didn't even decided where we were gonna peek yet.
Saying that wouldn't have made it any better.
This is fucking perfect.
What do you mean, Yuuji?
If that's what they want, then that's what we'll do.
You mean...
Let's peek on the girls' bath!
Yuuji! If you just want to see Kirishima naked, you could just ask her!
S-Shut up! I don't care about seeing Shouko naked.
So we shall be looking for a girl with burns on her rear, nay?
Exactly! I didn't really want to go that far...
but if that's what they want, then so be it!
We'll peep as much as we can and find that spying bitch!
That camera and mic from earlier were also that girl's.
My goodness!
So the girl threatening us was also spying on the girl's changing room?
Now I have no doubts.
All right. Let's go!
Women's
Bath
We have half an hour before the girls are done with their bath.
The bath is right ahead of us.
There's no time! Make a dash for it!
Stop right there!
Where do you kids think you're going?
It's Mr. Fuse, the chemistry teacher.
Ignore him! Keep running!
You're not supposed to ignore me.
Summoned being, summon!
That's...
His summon!
Just like the Punishment Inspector, a teacher's summon is able to interact with physical objects.
In that case, we'll fight him with our own summons!
Leave it to me, Yuuji!
Hold a second. Let's hear your chemistry scores first.
My latest score in chemistry... was just one mark short...
Short of?
Double digits.
Thank God I asked, you moron.
Battling a teacher alone will be tough.
Allow me to assist thee.
Thanks, Hideyoshi.
Summon!
All right, Voyeur! Let's go—
He's gone already!
Stop right there!
The PE teacher... Mr. Ooshima!
Give it up, Tsuchiya!
Women's
Mr. Ooshima! This isn't peeping!
Then what is it?
PE training.
Summon!
Class F Student
Rapier
Shortsword
Points
Gender
Physical Education
Subject
Map
PE Teacher
A
PE
Weather:
Temperature:
Humidity:
Corridors leading to
the women's bath
Corridor to
women's bath
ESB in progress
Go on ahead, Akihisa! I have this under control!
Voyeur!
Good luck, everyone!
I will do it... I... I will—
I-Ironman!
Good grief! I can't let you idiots out of my sight!
I won't lose here!
Summon!
Eh? Where's your summon, Mr. Nishimura?
Well, one thing lead to another, so my marks are pretty low.
I see! Here's all my resentment in one punch!
You're going down, Ironman—
Wha—
Yoshii! Do you know why I didn't just revoke your summoning permission that time?
I wanted you to be the Punishment Inspector!
I can hit your summon as much as I want, and no one will stop me!
Clench your jaw!
Extra classes for being rude to your teacher!
Those three as well.
The first day of the school trip ended on that note.
But, the false accusations on the boys haven't been cleared yet.
Will they ever be able to find the girl who threatens them?
Ta-da.
Flickering, sparkling
the lightbulb goes pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
That's the root of the problem
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go
I want to fall in love.
There'll be no boundaries to my dreams.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Flashing, sparkling,
that's the correct answer
Question 5:
Training camp diary
Write a summary
of your first day
at the training camp.
Himeji Mizuki's
entry:
When the train was
stopping at a station,
I suddenly became
dizzy. The view,
the smells, even
the air was completely
different from
what I was used to.
I know something
good will happen soon.
Teacher's comment:
It seems the change in
environment has let you
experience many new
sensations. I hope you'll
be able to make some
great new memories
here.
Tsuchiya Kouta's entry:
When the train was
stopping at a station,
I suddenly became dizzy.
I still wonder why.
Teacher's comment:
Motion sickness.
Sakamoto Yuuji's entry:
As I took a deep breath on the
station platform,
I could smell something strange,
a bit sweet and faintly sour.
I wonder if that's the smell of this town.
Teacher's comment:
It might have been, if Tsuchiya wasn't
throwing up next to you.
That was a good bath!
Big baths really feel great, don't they?
Question 6:
Answer the following
question.
Give an idiom which
means "when bad
things happen,
they happen together".
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
"When it rains, it pours."
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
Other idioms which mean the same are "It's a good ill
that comes alone" and "Misfortunes come by forties". All of
these phrases can be used when bad things are happening to
you one after the other.
Let's be sure to learn from our mistakes so we don't repeat
them.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi's answer:
The endless cycle of birth and rebirth.
Teacher's comment:
Will you be in Class F in your next life too?
Next time:
Me, peeping, and
Friendship Amongst  Men
Question six.
Give an idiom which means "when bad things happen, they happen together."
The endless cycle of birth and rebirth.
Will you be in Class F in your next life too?
Next time: Me, peeping, and friendship amongst men.
This will be on the test.