I am a recognized authority
on the 4.5 tatami room.
I think I shall expound on
the aspects of that space.
Although I knew of one person
who lived in a 3 tatami room,
they grew more and more stubbornly
set against the tides of the world,
and last year their parents came
from their hometown to pick them up.
It might be a little hard to
believe, but near Joudo Temple
I've heard there are rooms that exist
with two tatami mats laid end-to-end.
If you slept on them every night,
there's no doubt you'd grow in height.
In Kitashirakawa Baptist General Hospital's
XXXX ward, it's said there are 1 tatami rooms,
but the students that knew of this
ended up mysteriously disappearing,
and their friends one by
one all met unfortunate fates.
And then there is the 4.5 tatami room.
Compared to the 1, 2, or 3 tatami rooms,
the 4.5 tatami room is a truly beautiful square.
Is it not magnificent?
2 tatamis can also form
a square, but it is cramped.
On the other hand, once you've
made a square larger than 4.5 tatami,
it becomes as spacious as Takeda Shingen's
lavatory, and one might even get lost.
After entering university, I became
a fierce supporter of the 4.5 tatami room.
Those people who live in
7, 8, or even 10 tatami rooms...
Are they truly worthy of ruling
over such a space as if it is their own?
I wonder if human beings
even have such capacity?
We humanity have the ability to
rule 4.5 tatami and smaller spaces.
Those reprehensible beings
who greedily lust for larger area
will surely be met by fearsome
rebellion from some corner of their room.
That was my assertion.
The 4.5 tatami room is my entire world.
That is my conviction, but now...
...there is also the objective
reality of the situation.
Where is the person responsible?
The Tatami Galaxy
Then I was a freshman university student
and before me lay open countless
doors to various different campus lives.
But I didn't join any of the circles.
A rose-colored campus life is, after all,
nothing more than an illusory dream.
I decided to train myself in the tranquil
space known as the 4.5 tatami room.
Terayama Shuji once said this:
"Throw away books and go out into the city."
But what was he saying to do
once you go out into the city?
For the next two years I spent
most of my time in the 4.5 tatami room,
and some people came to call
me the "4.5 Tatami Ideologue."
The 4.5 Tatami Ideologue
This is my inner sanctum.
The Eizan train runs behind it, and though it
only takes a few seconds to circle this space,
everything about me is crammed in here.
To the north is a cheap, flimsy door.
A note with venerable hints from the
previous occupant is still affixed there.
On one side of the door
is a sink of bottomless filth,
assuring the loss of any
would-be cook's motivation.
I steadfastly refuse to try my hand at cooking,
putting into practice my belief that
"men shouldn't set foot in the kitchen."
The majority of the north wall is a closet,
filled carelessly with unremarkable
clothing and books I never read.
My library of obscenity is also within.
In one corner of the east wall are
a vacuum cleaner and rice cooker
that do not look as if
they've been heavily used,
and most of the wall is a grand library,
in which an enormous number of
printed works have been assembled.
In the space between the
southeast bookcase and my desk
lies an area in which
various junk has been thrown,
and I believe if one were to
venture into it alone and get lost,
the chances of returning alive would be slim.
And then from the south to the southwest
there is a window which rattles
as the Eizan train passes by,
and there underneath it is placed my desk
that has been with me through high school.
In the west are socks
in search of lost partners,
the clothes that make up my everyday
life, and an old-fashioned world map.
A famous short story begins with a normal
man that one morning turns into an insect.
For me it was not something so dramatic.
But it had definitely become a problem.
A proper man shall not be perturbed no matter
what circumstances he might find himself in.
He must think through the situation calmly.
But as I had not had much
enthusiasm for going outside previously,
wouldn't going crazy trying to get
out make me quite shallow as a human?
While I sat down and calmly waited it out,
the situation might well
change for the better on its own.
I had come up with a single hypothesis.
It supposed that this was a
curse of that old fortune teller.
There was an old woman who emitted
freely an eerie aura as I passed by Kiyamachi.
The old woman said "Student
there, you'll be in trouble soon!"
"You have made a false step in life!"
I replied "That is not the case at all!
I am satisfied with the way I live!"
But the old woman continued,
"You shouldn't be so stubborn."
"I can sense you have talent, so there
is opportunity dangling before your eyes."
That is not an opportunity or anything!
Finally the old woman went
"Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh..."
Or maybe not, but she smiled evilly like that.
Hey, is anybody there?
As I cried out a line straight out of
some crappy drama to no response,
I had no choice but to take all
the embarrassment upon myself.
Well, it seems we've finally
entered the realm of science fiction.
I have a feeling there was once a movie
where someone was trapped
in rooms connected in this way.
Since water flows out, that means it should
be connected to the outside world in some way.
If I were some kind of mole-man
and could pass through the faucet,
I could struggle through to
Kyoto Water Bureau, but...
After two days or so, I ran out of food.
A source of protein?
Protein?
I was like a Robinson Crusoe washed
up on a deserted 4.5 tatami room.
But for me there was a faucet
with water, and furniture...
I had a set of everything; I could
hardly call this a state of survival.
I had a stroke of good luck.
In the 4.5 room next door there
were fishburgers and a castella.
So then, is it okay for me to eat this?
I don't really read much science fiction,
so if this really is that sort of phenomenon,
would eating this castella
cause some sort of harm?
And if this is all some sort of
hallucination, is this castella even real?
It is a castella.
Putting aside rational explanation,
this was indeed an honest to goodness castella.
And so the problem of my
food supply was basically solved.
As I could not see the light of the sun,
I could not determine
whether it was noon or night,
and though I made it a point to
delineate each day from the next,
I could not be sure that
my delineations were correct.
I can't ignore the nutrients
that I get from the castella.
I got it a few days ago
from a person named Ozu,
who came to visit a person
who lives on the second floor.
A couple of days before I became trapped,
I discovered a large cockroach
outbreak in our Shimogamo Yuusuisou.
I come and go to the
room on the second floor.
I made a cockroach cube
weapon but it malfunctioned.
- Sorry for the inconvenience. Please, eat this.
- Ozu
At the time I felt an
irrational anger come over me.
But should I not be thankful to this Ozu
person now that I am in this circumstance?
There were times I despaired,
but after I thought about it,
perhaps this situation could
be called a stroke of luck?
If I transfer to the room next door I can
get another castella and more fishburgers.
I might be getting lopsided nutrition,
but food would not be a
problem in the foreseeable future.
With things as they are,
I could think of this world of 4.5 tatami
rooms as a wonderful place to live.
From a physical perspective a
4.5 tatami space is quite small,
but one can find an expansive
inner world from within.
Within the world of imagination
there are no boundaries.
It could be said that I am the
ultimate Creator of this 4.5 tatami room!
I will survive.
I will have fun persisting in
this perfect 4.5 tatami world!
That way I will show this
god of fate who is boss!
I trembled with excitement!
This is coffee.
I thought that I might take this
opportunity to read the books I had not read.
I have as much time as I need!
This is fun! This is fun! This is fun!
Sometimes to pass the time
I would admirably think to study,
but Schrödinger's equation knocked me out.
As a pioneer in this 4.5 tatami world,
I wove a plan to bravely make my life here.
I would devise ways to use the castella
and fishburgers to make various other dishes.
I would undertake operation of a
systematic system of growing mushrooms!
I would even remodel many of
the rooms into a bowling alley,
or movie theater, or arcade, and create
all kinds of different amusement centers!
I would realize my own Utopia!
Just thinking about it made me excited!
Even doing something as shameful as this,
no one in the world would pay any heed.
I will not be pestered by other people.
It is indeed a world just for myself.
Absorbing myself in reading
20,000 Leagues Under the Sea,
I got drunk on cheap whiskey
and cried out toward the ceiling.
Becoming afraid of the silent
world pressing down around me,
I sang all the songs
I knew at the top of my lungs.
And so I discovered that I myself
wanted to escape from this 4.5 tatami world.
I didn't want to admit, but I was completely
and utterly sick of this 4.5 tatami room.
If I opened the door to the dirty
hallway and headed down that dirty hallway,
there would be the dirty
bathroom, and the dirty shoe boxes,
and then I could exit the
boarding house to the outside.
It was because I could always
go outside when I pleased
that I confined myself to the 4.5 tatami room.
The most real thing to me was a single
physiological need I was struggling with.
To put it plainly, I couldn't stand the smell.
One day I couldn't stand it anymore,
and I hastily left on a journey
Lavatory
to get far away from that room.
It must have been a week since I'd
been trapped in this mysterious world.
Anyway, let's see how far
these 4.5 tatami rooms go...
That day I must have traversed
over 1004.5 tatami rooms,
and yet they still continued.
Eventually I felt like a fool.
Alchemy
When I went searching in
the space between my desk
and bookshelf known as the
"Siberian Penal Colony,"
I found a thin little wallet.
If each 4.5 tatami room has 1000 yen,
each time I move to another
room I get another 1000 yen.
If I move to 10 rooms,
or 100 rooms, or 1000 rooms...
I made a curious discovery.
While taking a break I thought to read
The Curious Casebook of Inspector Hanshichi,
which I had bought at a used book fair,
but it didn't exist in that 4.5 tatami room.
The collections on each bookshelf
were different, if only slightly.
I noticed that although at a glance
the 4.5 tatami rooms seemed identical,
they were each slightly different.
Oh, it was all a dream!
I wonder why I hadn't thought
to break through the wall?
After all, the walls are thin enough to be
able to hear the conversations next door.
The Chinese exchange student next
door would often bring his girlfriend,
and they'd whisper sweet nothings to each other.
I regretted from the bottom of my heart
that I had not studied Chinese
as my second foreign language.
Even if I broke through the wall and invaded,
I'm sure he could just laugh it off with
the deep tolerance of one from the mainland.
Here we go!
Day xxx
Could it be that I was dead?
Had I fallen into a so-called 4.5 tatami hell,
forced to suffer for all eternity?
It's hard to believe... The leaves are
probably turning by now on the outside.
I had not eaten out for more than 1200 hours,
nor bathed in the sun's rays,
nor breathed fresh air,
nor spoken with another human being!
In this room was something I did not remember.
Lucky Cat Chinese Restaurant
It seemed to be the signboard for some organization.
Why did the 4.5 tatami
rooms have these differences?
They should all be my same 4.5 tatami room,
so what gave rise to these small differences?
In that instant I grasped the
structure of this 4.5 tatami world.
The bookshelves with books
I had missed a chance to buy,
circles which I shouldn't
have been a member of...
I see! These are my parallel worlds!
In these how many tens of days,
I had been crossing through
parallel universes of 4.5 tatami rooms
for each of the various
choices I could have made!
This is the dental hygienist Hanuki-san.
The previous autumn I'd heard
rumors of a beautiful dental hygienist
that gave the most excellent gum massages,
and so I'd visited the local dentist.
Lately I've seen a drunk
Hanuki-san looking completely different
yelling over the railing of the Mikage bridge.
I wonder what happened to that
cool professional demeanor of hers?
But a mental ruffian such as myself
was not able to grasp the subtlety of it.
I wonder what choice I made?
In this world I was close to Hanuki-san,
I lived together with a beautiful love-doll,
and I even seemed to have
exchanged letters with a proper lady.
It was a situation I could only dream of.
This one looked like a lifestyle
that had fallen into depravity.
Almost like I had become the disciple
of that person on the second floor
of the Shimogamo Yuusuisou.
I threw away my backpack
filled with 1000 yen bills.
It's not like I would ever make use of it.
T-This is...
Funds for continuing the Proxy War?
The occupant of this room seemed
like they reached toward the heavens.
I remembered feeling somewhat afraid.
Did I search for an even
greater happiness than this?
Isn't that almost like
Icarus flying toward the sun?
Come to think of it, I recall seeing
a flier about something like this.
Isn't this that fellow I've seen at Neko Ramen?
It's rumored that Neko Ramen uses actual
cats in its broth, but the taste is unmatched.
It was a calm conversation
that reminded me of youth.
I overheard the two worrying about who
would succeed them in continuing some battle,
but one of them was a fine specimen of a man
while the other was a resident of Shimogamo
Yuusuisou with a face like an eggplant.
I usually thought of that man as
someone I did not want to associate with.
But to think it was that ladies'
man who had such a "hobby"...
For some strange reason I began to feel
attached to these people I barely knew.
I felt as if Id known them a long time, yet
all that remained was this feeling of nostalgia.
Did you get paid?
Didn't the cameraman hit on you?
Not having a single person make fun of me
for doing a thing like this was hard to take.
If there were some slippery
evil companion here with me...
What do you think you're doing?
Are there maggots crawling
around your cerebral cortex?
...I'm sure they would have
completely belittled me like that.
And yet every occupant of
every room seemed to be having fun.
Even if it wasn't rose-colored,
I could see each 4.5 tatami
room had its own color to it.
Was it possible for me to have
made these choices, I wonder?
Ah, it's me!
Hey, you!
Help me, please!
But I had already realized.
My fate would change from
even the tiniest of choices.
An innumerable number of I's are born,
an innumerable number of
4.5 tatami rooms are born.
In other words, theoretically
this 4.5 tatami world has no end!
Anyway, it seems like these fellows
can cross through the parallel worlds
and gather in them one after another.
They can lose their heart with love
or liven it up with raunchy stories.
On the contrary, I only
tell raunchy stories to myself,
always absorbed in my solitary delusions.
But that can no longer continue.