"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Right. It's so smelly!
So smelly!
Golden Week is almost over now,
but are you two all right
with homework and stuff?
Actually, I'm not done yet...
I tend to play away these long
holidays. We're in trouble.
Right, Sis?
I'm sorry. I'm acutally
almost all done with mine.
You were playing with me
all this time...
"Efforts and Results"
Thanks for the meal.
I was talking about this one...
There's no way I would understand
something that baffles you, Kagami!
You're in college, aren't you?!
Go and wake Tsukasa up already.
I don't want to.
She won't wake up, anyway.
Wake up already!
Dad sure is late.
Was he at the groundbreaking
ceremony this morning?
--What time is it now?
--I'm home.
--It's already past noon!
Welcome back.
Good morning...
It's already afternoon.
How can you sleep so much?
Did you see the special finale
of Love Apron last night?
I missed it.
I fell asleep halfway...
Oh, you slept through it?
It was an amazing turn of events!
In the very end, a guy with
a red basin on his head...
Kagami, you have
a phone call from Miyuki.
Okay.
Would you like to hold a study session
that doubles as
a homework answer check?
Oh, that sounds good.
Let's do it, let's do it.
Kagami, you have
a phone call from Konata.
Would you like to hold a study session
that doubles as a homework cleanup?
Wait a minute! In your case, all
you do is copy all my homework!
And so, I would like to
copy your homework.
You're awfully straightforward.
It's all right for you to
copy my homework,
but if you don't do it all by yourself,
you're going to have
horrible scores on the first exam
after break, you know?
That's true... It won't be
for my own good...
I'm fine, because I'm good at
the one-night cram session.
So, show it to me.
You should worry at least a little bit!
Excuse me...
--Oh, welcome.
--Welcome!
Oh, are you part of the study group
as well, Izumi-san?
No, she's flat-out copying everything.
Anyway, you haven't
done anything at all.
What were you doing
during the break?
Let's see...
"Day 1"
23 pages of math,
20 pages of world history,
30 pages of English...
The break is five days long.
So if I think I'll study for five--
no, four hours a day...
Math goes at 1.15 pages per hour...
"Day 2"
Oh no, I haven't done anything today.
Let's see... I have three days left,
so I guess I'll work six hours a day...
"Day 3"
The coworker who has been working
under me for the past ten years
still doesn't remember my name...
I am Yutaka... I am Yutaka...
Two more days...
If I work frantically for
the next two days...
"Day 4"
Golden Week is almost over now,
but are you two all right
with homework and stuff?
Would you like to hold a study session
that doubles as a homework cleanup?
I thought about doing them all
as I initially planned...
The plan fell flat on its face.
Your resistance was futile.
But you're worse off than she is!
In the end, she tried her best
and did it on her own.
Deep down, she's very
serious about her work,
no matter what people say.
But her accuracy is so bad
that I can't bear to look.
So horrible... just so horrible...
Hey!
Were you able to spend
the short vacation in a fun way?
But then, you had quite
a bit of homework,
and you get a midterm
the day you come back.
I'm sure you couldn't have been
fooling around the entire break!
I didn't feel like I had a break at all!
Well, sorry to say,
but I didn't let any of that worry me,
and I played around!
Ma'am...
Yeah?
I didn't let anything worry me,
and I played around too!
Hey!
I thought things like that were made
so that you could never get them?
It depends on the item.
There's a few things that are
made to be difficult to get.
Isn't that right? That's why
I don't feel like trying them.
Oh, amazing!
Well, this one was an easy target.
I see.
If it's that one,
maybe even if it was me trying,
perhaps it will tumble...
"...and I'll be able to get it,"
is what you were thinking, right?
No, no, I'm not thinking
of anything of the sort.
But maybe I'll try just this once?
Go for it, Sis.
I thought I had that one for sure.
Too bad.
You're kidding!
Why?!
A wise man once said,
"UFO catchers are piggy banks."
That's a good one.
Oh, again... No!
--Announcing the results!
--I was no good at all.
--You are at Taiko Entry Level 1!
--Kona-chan, you have a
very good sense of rhythm.
--You are at Taiko Black Belt Level 5!
--No, a sense of rhythm
doesn't matter at all.
The skills you get by gaming are
usually useless in everyday life.
I can see that clearly
when I look at you.
Kona-chan, you're so strong.
Well, yeah...
How much money has she
fed into this thing?!
Izumi!
Is Izumi absent today?
Miss Kuroi, a phone call from Izumi.
Yes, this is Kuroi speaking.
Oh, Ma'am, I'm sorry, but I
want to call in sick today.
What, Izumi? This is unusual for you.
Did you catch a cold?
No, I have May sickness...
I'm really sluggish.
Hurry up and get over here!
Hey, we're going home now.
Why are you stuffing
your bag like that?
Since the exams start tomorrow,
I have to take everything home
with me today to study overnight.
Don't tell me you kept every textbook here
and studied only in school!
Good grief, there's no way
you'd make it in time
if you're taking all
your textbooks home
only on the night before the exams!
But I've always
made it through like this.
You sure are confident.
Well, I'll see how far
you can go with that.
"First Semester Midterms"
"Modern Literature" "Math" "English"
Okay, I'm gonna return
the exams you took the other day.
Not bad.
How was it?
It's like, don't ask me...
Though I did my best.
Now, how about that all-nighter girl?
Thanks to my studying,
I had it down pat!
I don't get it!
Lucky Star!
So sluggish... I don't feel
like doing anything.
Hey, we're going home now.
Despite what you say,
you always hang out with us
when we make these stops.
Oh, Comp-Fest!
QUO Cards for everyone who fills out
the order! I have to get them all!
All right, I guess it's time
to get a part-time job!
You really are a simple person.
Really, I've never heard of anyone
who tried to call in sick
with May sickness.
Though I understand how it feels...
They call it a sickness,
so it's a legit excuse, right?
Are you saying that seriously?
Yeah.
By the way, what exactly is
the May sickness, anyway?
Miyuki, explain it to her.
Well...
From the sense of accomplishment
of meeting a large goal,
like school entrance exams
or successfully being hired,
or the difficulties in having
interpersonal relationships
with people you meet starting in April,
or the inability to adjust to the gap
between ideals and reality
when it comes to the new life
you started to live,
there is a sense of apathy,
or downright depression.
So, if it's just that
your body feels sluggish,
I don't know if you can
really call it May sickness.
In the first place,
we're all in eleventh grade,
so that doesn't apply to us, right?
I always do my best with a fresh
heart in the spring every year.
Whatever.
But it's not just Konata.
You really tend to get sluggish
at this time of the year.
Even when you get home,
you just don't feel up to
doing homework and stuff.
Oh, me too!
I feel too lazy to make
the comeback, okay?
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
You're sighing and stuff.
I'm embarrassed to talk about this,
just like when I talked
about contact lenses.
But I've been too afraid
to go to the dentist,
and my cavity is getting
worse and worse.
It's so bad now that it stings
even when I drink water.
Isn't that normal?
I'm afraid of them too.
But why did you let it get this bad
before going to the dentist?
It's very strange,
but even though I knew
that it would be tough for me
when my teeth started to hurt...
For some reason, you don't
want to go to the dentist.
Even after the pain starts,
while you can withstand it,
you tend to choose not to go.
Are dentists really that scary?
I don't know because I've
never had to deal with one.
You've never gone to one?
I'm so jealous.
That distinct antiseptic smell
in the dentist's office...
The tension you feel
in the waiting room...
That, and don't forget the sound
of the spinning drills!
Change Getter!
It's so scary!
But boys might like
dentists and stuff, then.
Why?
I mean, they say that a drill
is like a guy's romantic ideal.
Dinosaur Empire!
I hear they're all about dueling robots
that use drills as weapons!
But I think they would hate
their teeth being drilled.
I always think how so many
of the dental assistants
and receptionists are so pretty...
Don't you think so too?
Come to think of it, they are.
I wonder why.
Can it be the aesthetic standards
of the person hiring them?
A beautiful dental assistant
and a drill, huh...
It certainly does seem to be
geared more towards men.
Then what would a dentist
geared for women be like?
First off, they'd have to get rid
of that smell or whatever.
And the chair that they use has to be
a fluffy reclining chair with a massage unit!
Then we'd have to add
aromatherapy as well.
Or have a foot massage at the same
time as the dental treatment.
Oh, that sounds good.
That, and be able to play games
to ease the pain of treatment!
A game might be rather hard to play...
But it's a good idea to have them
distract our attention.
Like putting headphones on and
listening to our favorite music.
Yeah, that's good.
That also sounds good.
Yeah.
But in the end, I still don't
want to go to a dentist.
Right...
What?!
What's up?
Well, another one of my favorite
series is turning into an anime,
but the cast is completely
different from the drama CD.
I don't get what you're saying.
Is it the unseen hand
of God yet again?
Politics? Or money?
I'm not one to ever buy drama CDs,
so I don't care who the cast is,
as long as the voice matches the
character as portrayed in the original.
That's not how it works, Kagamin!
Those that are used to
listening to the drama CDs
find it awkward when they
start watching the anime.
And it takes quite a bit of time
before that awkwardness is gone.
I see...
Even so, there is one good thing
to come out of this.
What?
The drama CDs and the anime...
You can enjoy two worlds
with two different voices.
The same piece of candy,
but twice as tasty!
You really are a strong customer.
Now, one of us is going
to take the nugget
that Miyuki-san has left uneaten...
Let's have a staring contest
to decide it.
What? That's so childish.
A staring contest? That sounds fun.
Though I think Kagami
will win, hands down.
Did you say something?
Then let's go.
It's a staring contest...
Blaaaaah!
That's too much!
Amazing!
That's not something
a human can do!
Hey, you guys are both overreacting.
I'm sorry I made you wait.
The bathroom was rather crowded...
Is something the matter?
Hey, show that face
you just made to Miyuki too.
I don't wanna!
Miyuki, it was amazing!
This was a face that you've
never seen before in your life!
Well then...
It's so amazing no matter
how many times I see it!
You could use that face for the
talent part of a college application.
That's right, Konata!
Use that to apply for college!
I'm sure you'll get accepted!
That doesn't make me so happy.
They were doing something on TV
like how many books an average
Japanese person reads in a year.
"Manga's not good enough,
ordinary books only, please!"
Is what they were saying.
Well, manga is, you know...
Do light novels count?
I don't know... Though I'd think
that light novels are okay.
What about picture books?
When you say a book, you have
the right sense of the word...
Also for the fantasy genre,
everyone would nod in agreement
if you say that Harry Potter
and stuff like that are ordinary books.
In the end, what exactly
is an ordinary book?
Besides, on that TV show,
they ended the show saying that
the younger generation is veering
away from reading on the whole.
But nowadays, we use the net
to look at all sorts of
websites and blogs,
so I think we have a higher
percentage of reading.
Yeah... I'm kinda getting it,
and I'm kinda not...
Hey, you two, let's go home!
Just a second.
Oh, I'm sorry, I can't go home
with you guys today.
You have an errand to run or
something? That's unusual.
Yeah. I started a part-time job.
I see...
Wait, she really started
a part-time job!
Is the Comp-Fest that
important to her?!
But, you know,
Konata really surprised me.
You're right. She really
started a part-time job.
I thought that she was just kidding.
That too, but...
I was surprised that
anyone would hire her.
That's a little harsh.
I can't imagine her working
diligently in the first place!
You have a point.
I wonder where she's working.
Maybe a bookstore or something,
since she loves manga so much?
Excuse me, can I have this?
Hold on a sec. I'm too busy right now.
Got 'em!
I hope she doesn't get fired...
Then how about a convenience store?
Excuse me, can I have this?
498yen...
Justtherightamount...
Thankyouverymuch.
Nah... I can't see that.
Then, what about a fast-food joint?
"Smile 0 yen"
I am smiling, what about it?
Maybe that's impossible too.
Along the same lines, a family-style
restaurant is out of the question.
Welcome...
Honestly, what kind
of job did she get?
Yeah...
Maybe counting the amount of traffic?
No way.
A video rental place?
You think so?
A pub?
No, that's not it.
Pizza delivery?
She doesn't have a license.
A cashier in a supermarket?
Impossible.
An instructor in a cram school.
You're kidding!
A bread factory.
Huh?
Let's see... What else...
Let's just ask her tomorrow.
Hey, Konata, what kind of place
are you working at?
Yeah, tell us.
Oh, it's an ordinary cosplay café.
Wow, that's so fitting for her!
But is that kind of place really okay?
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
I'm Akira Kogami! This is the
second episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm going to do my best
to deliver it to you!
Now, next to me is a wonderful
young man who will assist me,
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Oh... wa... wawa...
I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
assistant to Akira-sama!
I'm still very new, so I hope that
you'll at least remember my name
before you go home! Yeah!
Clap, clap, clap...
Now, this segment has just started,
but already messages from all of you
have arrived with a bang!
Akira's super happy! Thank you!
Well, this really is amazing.
It must all be a sign of your
popularity, Akira-sama.
Huh?
I saw it today.
Yes?
You were in it, right?
In the main show. You had a part.
Yes, I had the opportunity
to play a small part.
Well, it's all right.
But wait? What scene were you in?
Well, I believe it was
the 45th cut of part A,
the scene in the classroom
right after the holiday break.
Oh, oh, oh, I remember now.
You had such a small presence
on screen that I had forgotten.
This time, I only had one line
in the entire scene, so...
What's that?
You're dissatisfied by that?
Oh, no, that's definitely not the case.
Man, I don't know about
newbies acting like that.
When I first debuted...
Debut? Exactly how old were you?
Three years old.
Back then, I was ecstatic
just by getting a line to say.
Getting to speak isn't about
the number of lines.
Well now, I was surrounded by all
the great names in the industry,
so it was a series of tense moments.
It was a great learning
experience for me!
You really were tense, though.
You were rock solid.
A complete amateur.
You know, that was just
so you-know-what,
so how about you
try again right here?
What, you mean right here?
You might show up again
in a future episode, right?
Well, yes...
Then you have to practice
a little, at least!
I'm telling you that I'm going
to help you out right now!
Oh, I understand now!
I'm in your hands!
Give me the script.
Which cut was it?
Cut 45.
Oh, this...
Then I'll play the teacher, Miss Kuroi.
Please do!
Now, ready... Action!
Hey!
Were you able to spend
the short vacation in a fun way?
But then, you had q-q... um...
That's "quite."
Quite a bit of homework,
and you get a midterm
the day you come back.
I'm sure you couldn't have been
fooling around the entire break!
I didn't feel like I had a break at all!
What's up with that?
No good at all.
Your line just doesn't deliver.
Deliver?
Here! Right here!
It doesn't reach here at all!
I'm sorry.
Even a monkey can do it,
if it's just reciting a line!
I believe a monkey
wouldn't be able to do it...
Huh?!
I guess it's already
time to say goodbye!
Happy times really go by
quickly, don't they?
And so, please send us
questions and praise for me,
as well as your opinions of the show!
Oh, well... We hope to see you again
in the next episode.
See you!
And, what about it?
Those regulars on the show.
By that, you mean...
I'm talking about, how to put it,
like someone being pulled down...
Don't they all hate each
other or something?
No, I don't think that
is the case right now.
Then, how about you be
considerate, and--
Kona-chan, you're amazing!
That was very passionate!
Hey, Konata! Are there two
more songs of this sort left?!
Oh, I put in anime songs as well
as those live-action hero ones.
That's not the point
I'm trying to make!
Sing songs that even
we would recognize!
We're free to sing whatever we want.
Or rather...
Hey, Tsukasa, you have
to punch songs in,
or we'll have to listen to an endless
stream of her anime songs.
I wouldn't mind if that was the case.
This is fun in its own way.
What, you too, Miyuki?!
Sorry to get in front of you...
I'm gonna sing standing up.
What the hell are you up to now?!
I can't really get my voice out from
my stomach if I don't stand up!
You're going to sing even louder
than the last song?!
Hey, it's the original footage!
Oh, this is somehow quite amazing!
This looks like something from
way before we were born.
I have your drinks here.
Oh, thank you.
Who ordered oolong tea?
That would be me.
Who ordered iced lemon tea?
Who ordered orange juice?
That's me.
Who ordered ginger ale?
Please leave that one here.
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with
the next episode of Lucky Star?
Kagami here.
When I put in 200 yen to buy
a can of juice in a vending machine
and get one 50-yen coin and
some 10-yen coins as change,
I think, "I win!"
But on the other hand, when I'm
buying a 150-yen ticket for a train,
and after putting in a 100-yen coin,
I think that I have five 10-yen
coins left, so I put in four,
but I actually had only four
and am one short,
so I end up putting in another
100-yen coin to buy the ticket
and thus get nine 10-yen
coins as change...
that sense of defeat
is really something!
Next episode: Various People.
"Various People"
Look forward to it!