Did you...
Did you truly hate me so much?
The origin shot.
It throws the target's mana into chaos,
instantaneously causing the body to destroy itself.
What?
Time Alter:
Double Accel!
The origin shot didn't work.
Wait...
I see.
He's using Command Spells
as his mana source.
By the time the origin shot takes effect,
the Command Spell he was drawing
mana from has already faded.
If he doesn't use his own Magic Circuits,
the origin shot won't affect him.
But if I can get a direct hit
it will still rip through him.
You won't evade me this time.
Now that I know you're
moving at double speed,
I need only adjust my defensive timing
to compensate.
He's fast!
Were you driven to madness
because of me?
Because of me...
Time Alter:
Double Accel!
I have no chance at close range.
I'm out of Calico ammo.
The Contender needs reloading.
But...
Avalon...
Instant regeneration
that can even recover a crushed heart?
Then I'll have to destroy his brain.
However,
I cannot use my right arm.
Avalon's healing powers will work
on self-inflicted wounds, too...
I have a knife and two grenades left.
I still have twelve Black Keys
and eight spare Command Spells.
Time Alter:
Triple Accel!
Square Accel!
Even still, I will gain the Holy Grail.
I must...
It's the only thing I can offer
to you as compensation.
You would still
take up your sword
for such a reason?
As intractable as ever...
Where am I?
I knew you'd come.
I had faith you would make it here.
Iri...
This is where your wish will come true.
Within the Grail you longed for.
That is the Holy Grail.
Though it has yet to take shape,
the vessel is already overflowing.
You need only offer your prayer.
And then, it will be able to go outside.
Come now, please...
Give it a form.
Kiritsugu, you are the one
worthy of defining its form.
Who are you?
I am Irisviel.
No, you're not.
If the Grail truly is prepared,
she is already...
Answer me!
Very well.
I will not deny this is a mask.
I cannot communicate with
others unless I use
a pre-existing personality as a shell.
However,
I have recorded Irisviel's personality,
and it is absolutely the real thing.
And consequently, I have
inherited her final wish.
Are you the will of the Grail?
Yes, that is a correct interpretation.
I have a will, and I have a wish.
I desire to be born into the world.
Impossible.
If that's true,
how will the Holy Grail grant my wish?
Come now, Kiritsugu...
You should know the answer
better than anyone.
What?
You've known the way
to save the world for a very long time.
So I will do as you have done,
to carry out your desire,
and I will answer your prayer.
What are you saying?
All right.
I suppose you'll just have to
ask your inner self directly.
Where am I?
Three hundred people on one ship.
Two hundred people on another.
What?
Five hundred passengers and crew,
plus Emiya Kiritsugu.
Let us say that
these are the last five hundred
and one humans left.
Catastrophic holes
ripped through both their hulls simultaneously.
Only Kiritsugu has the skill to repair them.
So...
Which ship do you repair?
Obviously, the one with
three hundred people.
After you decide that,
the other two hundred capture you.
They insist that you fix their ship first.
Now what do you do?
I would...
Kill all two hundred.
Correct.
That is what Emiya Kiritsugu would do.
Next, the remaining three hundred
abandon their damaged ship,
and continue their journey on two new ones.
This time, there are two hundred on one,
and one hundred on the other.
But once again,
holes open in both ships
at the same time.
Wait.
You are kidnapped by the
hundred on the smaller ship,
who demand you repair their ship first.
Now what do you do?
You know what...
But...
Yes, that is correct.
No way!
How can that be correct?
I killed three hundred
to save two hundred!
The scales are completely unbalanced!
No, your calculations were not wrong.
You have always sacrificed the few,
in order to save the many.
Have you not, Emiya Kiritsugu?
You've spent your life killing the few
on the lighter side of the scales.
Even if it meant leaving a mountain
of corpses in your wake.
If that saved lives,
then those lives were worth more.
Is this what you wanted to show me?
Yes.
This is the truth of who you are.
This is Emiya Kiritsugu's answer.
In other words,
the outcome the wish-granting
device should create.
No...
I don't want this!
I wanted a different way.
That was why
I needed a miracle!
You cannot wish for something
you yourself don't know.
If you wish to save the world,
it can only be accomplished via
methods you understand.
Screw that!
How...
How is that any kind of miracle?!
It is a miracle.
What you tried and failed
to accomplish on your own
can be carried out on a scale
no man could enact.
What is that, if not a miracle?
Dad...
Natalia...
Emiya Kiritsugu,
you are the embodiment of Angra Mainyu.
The one worthy to bear all
the evils of the world.
Now,
the final question.
Three people are left.
Do you save two?
Or choose one?
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
You're finally back!
You see now, don't you?
This is the Holy Grail granting your wish.
You need only offer your prayer.
To revive your wife,
and take back your daughter.
We won't be able to go looking
for walnuts anymore.
That's okay.
Ilya only needs Kiritsugu and Mommy
with her to be happy.
Thank you.
Your daddy loves you, too.
If nothing else, I swear that's true.
Farewell,
Ilya.
Ilya!
Ilya, Ilya, Ilya...
Ilya, Ilya...
Why?!
My love, you've killed our Ilya!
M-My love...
Why?
Why do you reject the Holy Grail
and us?
Six billion people...
I curse you,
Emiya Kiritsugu!
And my wife and child.
Angra Mainyu
curses you...
I...
Suffer...
...until your last breath.
I will kill you.
You will...
...regret this!
And save the world.
I will never forgiv—
What a boring way to end things.
Why did you refuse it?
You saw all that, too?
You sacrificed everything
to make it this far.
How can you toss aside something
you worked so hard to obtain?
It's so stupid, it's incomprehensible.
It had too high a cost
for too little benefit.
That's all there is to it.
That thing
is no omnipotent wish-granter.
Then give it to me!
You may have no use for it, but I do!
If...
If the Holy Grail can create that,
then surely it can answer all my questions.
It longs for life, for its own birth!
Please, don't kill it.
It...
And you...
are so stupid I simply cannot comprehend you.
Irisviel...
You're late, Saber.
How could you keep me waiting,
while you played with your old mad dog?
Archer.
You should see the look on your face,
like a starving, wasted dog.
Step aside.
The Holy Grail
belongs to me!
Saber,
even on your knees,
in the throes of delusion,
you are still beautiful.
Sheathe your sword, and become my wife!
Why should you obsess over a fantasy
like a Holy Grail that grants miracles?
Cast aside your foolish ideals and oaths.
From today forward, you need only
seek me, and be only mine.
Accept, and I promise,
as king of all the world,
to give you every pleasure.
You would steal the Holy Grail from me?
For such nonsense?!
I did not ask for your opinion.
This is the judgment I have rendered!
Now, I shall have your answer.
I absolutely refuse—
Too shy to say it?
That's fine.
You may answer incorrectly
to your heart's content.
Before you can understand
the joy of devotion to me,
you must first understand pain.
Kiritsugu.
Ah, I see you have made your decision.
By my name, Emiya Kiritsugu,
I order you with my Command Spell...
Give me the Holy Grail.
Saber, use your Noble Phantasm
to destroy the Grail.
What is...
What are you doing, Saber?!
No!
By my third Command Spell,
I order you again...
Why, Kiritsugu?
You, of all people...
Why?!
Damn you...
You dare to interrupt my
wedding ceremony, mongrel!?
Saber, destroy...
Don't!
...the Grail.
Episode 24:
The Final Command Spell
I remember that face.
Tears in his eyes,
and joy in his heart.
It was a man.
The man was grateful to
someone or something.
"Thank you," he said.
Next Time:
Fate/Zero