Hey, come on.
Look at me.
Close your eyes and count to ten in your head.
Mom, can I take these off?
Why?
It's so hot.
But you're so cute.
Princess Anko.
You're so cute, Anko!
Well, if it isn't the princess.
It suits you really well.
Am I cute?
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Dela, try this oak leaf mochi.
Today's a special festival day for boys.
Dela, I thought I'd make some jam-filled oak leaf mochi too.
Dela, I tried making some oak leaf mochi with chocolate inside! C'mon, eat up!
Can't... move...
Seriously? What's wrong with you?
Such impudence!
How dare a whippersnapper like you insult me—
You didn't have to eat that much just because you were told to.
I hadn't planned to overindulge myself. Not originally.
But that girl just offered me one after another, and before I knew it...
So how many did you end up eating?
Who can say?
A grandiose gentlebird like myself worries not about such trifling details.
You don't remember, chicken?
What did you say?
Don't lump me together with livestock!
I don't see much of a difference.
How rude!
Bad things will happen to you if you keep going along with whatever my sister says.
She's not much of a thinker.
Now, now.
Don't talk like that about your own sister.
Big words from an even bigger bird.
Whatever you say, runt.
What, again?
What's that sound?
Taiko drums.
There's a festival coming up.
A festival?
Carnival!
Could you give it a rest?
Yes, a festival.
Carnival, that time when females throw caution to the wind and the flowers of love bloom in the streets!
Excellent! Let us journey forth!
I must find a bride for my prince!
Summer's in the air.
It's the time for festivals.
Hearts flutter with the sensation of love.
I shall journey forth to find a queen!
What's wrong?
Give me a hand here.
Oh? You fell from your high horse?
Episode 4
A Tiny Little Love Blooms
For better digestion
Digestion
Animals
It's so bitter!
For better digestion
Digestion
Animals
Deal with it.
Never thought I'd see a bird eat too much oak leaf mochi.
What's wrong with a few mochi when you're feeling well?
Look at Dela. That's what's wrong.
Isn't my sister keeping you?
You should go hang out in her room instead.
For better digestion
Digestion
Keeping me?! Perish the thought!
She simply asked me to sojourn here for a spell.
Why are you so haughty?
Because he can talk, perhaps?
I wish I could take this as well as you.
Indeed it worked.
So refreshing! So wonderful!
Now, to find a bride!
How odd.
I did not intend to land here.
Check it out!
Grandpa!
Anko!
An!
I told you to call me An!
Oh, is that for the festival?
Yeah!
Isn't it cute?
The neighborhood association has quite a bit of money this year,
so we had these new jackets made.
Thanks for this, Dad.
Not to mention...
Look!
Usagiyama Market!
You think it's cute?
There's no way we're gonna lose to the other shopping districts this year!
There's one for you too.
Want to try it on?
Call me An!
And no. I gotta go to school.
Do you dislike festivals, Anko?
I don't, but...
You feel heavier than usual.
Well then, let me drop a pound.
We're off!
How's that?
Yep, as heavy as always.
No doubt, good food and smooth bowel movements make you human.
You're a bird.
Quiet, An.
I am like no other bird, for I bear a noble soul.
Now, to find my queen!
How long is he gonna stick around?
Hey, good morning!
That looks great on you, Pops.
I know, right?
And what do you think of my headband this year?
Doesn't this just embody the spirit of our market?
The rabbit ears are cute!
"Cute"? Try creepy.
What'd you say?
There they go again.
Seriously, what do you think you're doing at your age?
See you later.
We're the same damn age!
The festival has come.
Hey, Anko.
I just made some croquettes. Want them?
I'm going to school...
Go on, take them.
The festival's coming up.
Want some soy pulp?
I've got some great sardines here.
But... I gotta go to school...
Just hand them out in class.
They'll love it.
That's so uncool.
Why?
G'morning.
Morning!
Morning, Tamako.
You do your homework, Anko?
I didn't have any.
What about you?
I didn't have any either.
And call me An, okay?
An?
Yeah, so she says.
She thinks Anko is too old-fashioned.
But it's cute.
It sounds like a kind of mochi.
That's why I hate it!
So, since I'm a carpenter's daughter, is "Kanna" old-fashioned too?
Mochizou's name really takes the rice cake.
So, nobody's figured it out yet?
Yeah, that's why it's so cool!
Gotta hide!
Yeah.
What is it?
Shh!
I'm looking forward to the upcoming group lecture.
Oh, yeah—
What's wrong?
Let's get people together.
Shh! I told you to be quiet!
Well, see you later.
You can have this.
What's up with her?
Maybe...
Yeah.
He was kind of cool.
Who was?
Seeing how slow you are on the uptake makes me feel a little better.
What?
I get it! They're enemies!
You're gonna be late!
Hey, wait!
Nothing's gone right today.
Morning!
Something wrong?
No, I'm fine. Good morning.
Oh, right.
You went home early yesterday, so you probably didn't hear about the museum thing.
Huh?
The teacher said we could go do some research at the museum,
so some of us are going.
Wow, I didn't know.
Right now, it's Momiji, Yuka, and me.
Tatsuya and Yuzuki are going too.
You're coming with us, right?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, Tatsuya!
Anko is coming too!
Sounds good.
All right. Next Sunday afternoon, at the school gates.
Next Sunday...
No way.
We didn't have enough people last year,
and we've got even more orders this year.
Can't Tamako help?
You're my daughter too.
Not like I had any say in it.
Anyway, you're helping out here all Sunday.
If you want to go to the museum, I'll take you there next week.
Where's the fun in going to the museum with my dad?!
You're helping, period.
Whatever!
I can see that.
Why does my dad have to run a mochi shop of all places?
Check this out.
I tried making one for Dela.
What do you say?
Do I not strike a gallant figure?
I couldn't care less.
Anko, do you hate festivals?
I hate how they're nothing but work.
Back then...
Forget it.
Okay.
Oh, it's Mochizou!
I've got something to take care of! Talk to him for me, please!
Tamako.
Tamako! Over.
She isn't here.
That you, Anko?
I can hear—
An!
You're talking to me today.
Okay.
Um...
Do you think Tamako will go look at the portable shrines during the festival? Over.
I can hear you from over here anyway!
What's this stupid thing even for?!
Don't scream like that! Over.
Oh, right.
Hey, Mochi.
You're home on Sunday, right?
My name's Mochizou, okay? Over.
No way.
But he said he'd help you!
He's Ooji's son.
He'll steal my secret mochi recipes.
And besides, won't they be busy with the festival too?
We don't have to worry about that!
He said that as long as he gets to make mochi with you at the festival, his dad can deal with it.
Why?
Yeah, he's after the recipes all right.
How dense can you be?
No, I think he just wants to spread the festival spirit.
Not you too!
What about this?
You want to go in the afternoon, right?
You could get up really early and finish all your work before lunch.
How about it?
Can I go if I do that?
What about the deliveries and other stuff around the neighborhood?
Leave those to me.
I'll help too!
Fine.
Really?
You'll have to get up at five, though.
Okay! I will!
All right!
Let's do our best for the festival!
Yeah!
Tamako Market
The festival's here!
Good morning, Sis.
You're up early.
Shiori's here too.
Good morning.
I said you didn't have to come in until eight...
I woke up early.
Here.
Okay.
You're so good, Tamako.
This is just the basics.
But today we also have these special Tamaya Joy-ket mochi!
Jacket?
Joy-ket. Joy as in happiness, you know?
Oh, a pun.
You could say that.
Is Dad okay with this?
Yeah.
Right?
Just do a trial run of 20, okay?
See? It's a special edition, limited to 20.
The mochi's gonna get stiff if you just stand around talking.
Sorry, sorry.
Give me a hand, okay?
But I suck at it.
That's not true.
I was a lot worse than you when I was little.
What song is that?
Dunno.
You're always humming it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Careful, now...
Well, this is a problem.
Yes, indeed.
I'm sorry!
If only I'd noticed sooner.
It's not your fault.
We need something up there, though.
This is... a toy from my grandpa's shop.
Close, but no cigar!
What'll we do?
I feel so light today.
Catch him.
What did you say?
Today, the festivities reach their yearly climax.
And today, my own store is the quietest of all.
Oh, what ambivalence lies between me and the world.
The paint will just wash right off, even after it dries.
That's the last one.
We made pretty good time.
Yeah, thanks to Shiori's help this year.
Let's enjoy the festival this afternoon!
Shiori, on your nose.
Me too.
Me too!
Don't you have to get going, Anko?
We'll handle the rest!
Go on.
Can I?
You can do it.
Do what?
Later, then.
We didn't get to make mochi together,
but I at least want her to see me carrying the shrine.
Mochizou, hold the damn thing higher!
My shoulder hurts!
Quit yer whining!
Wow, there're so many people.
Hey, Anko.
Oh, the florist.
There you are. I've been looking for you.
Could you help me out?
I'm a little short on capable hands.
Anko!
Y-Yes?
Can you hold on to her shoulder, please?
Hold still for a second.
Close your eyes and count to ten.
All right. We're done.
Don't touch your face.
This looks weird.
I wanna take it off.
But you're so cute.
Cute?
You're like a princess.
Really?
Yeah, it's really cute.
Oh, no!
What time is it, Kaoru?
Let me see... It's eleven.
I gotta go!
Do you have to be somewhere?
What? You're going?
Guess I couldn't go after all.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Usagi!
Usagiyama!
That looks so dumb.
I can't go and collapse before she sees me.
Joy
ket
The limited edition Joy-ket mochi are on sale!
We're back!
Oh, hey!
Anko?
I couldn't make it in the end.
Huh? Really?
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
It's not your fault.
I had fun all the same.
At the festival?
Yeah.
Look, there's Mochi.
He's wearing one of those jackets.
Was he carrying the shrine?
The rabbit on his back is crying.
Poor guy.
Welcome!
Try our Joy-ket mochi, now on sale!
Limited edition! Just for the festival!
Today only!
Kitashirakawa!
Good afternoon.
We're on our way home.
He heard me!
He heard me yelling!
Huh?
Anko?
She's not here.
Did she escape through the window?
Hold on.
A golden bird?
This is an omen.
C'mon, that's just Dela.
What is it?
Anko.
No!
What's wrong?
Nothing!
But...
Just leave me alone!
What now?
Leave it to me.
Time to entice her out.
See?
I hate mochi.
Didn't she love them when she was young?
She's lost her taste for them lately.
Let's smoke her out.
That stinks!
She won't hold out.
Don't try to act tough. Just come out.
Huh? What is it?
Dela, are you okay?
Um, excuse me.
We bought a souvenir for Kitashirakawa.
Huh? Where's the other boy?
He said he had cram school.
I see.
Anko, your friend's here.
Um... here.
You know, we bought a souvenir together for you.
Here.
I hope you like it.
Th-Thanks!
You're welcome.
Wait a minute, Anko.
It was this kid?
Looks like it.
What?
Um...
I was just surprised that Anko was this nice a kid.
Though your wishes may go unfulfilled
and your best laid plans go awry,
on a different path, a different flower
will bloom anew.
Heavenly.
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
It's that time of year when even the breeze is fragrant.
Tamako here.
This is the season for oak leaf mochi.
The old leaves of the oak trees don't fall until new sprouts grow.
That's why the oak leaves symbolize prosperity for one's children.
Episode 5   We Spent The Night Together
They're great when filled with red or white bean paste!