[MASTER HAWKEYE]
So you've decided to become
a soldier after all.
That's all the proof I need...
you're not ready to learn
"flame alchemy."
But, sir... I am... It's the
only thing left... I mean,
haven't I already mastered
the fundamentals of alchemy?
[MASTER HAWKEYE]
Of course you have...
And I regret even
teaching you that much...
Now that I know who
you plan on using it for.
[MASTER HAWKEYE COUGHS]
But... alchemy should be used
for the people... Shouldn't it?
Master...
Our country is constantly
under threat from all sides...
The military needs
alchemists... It's a matter of
defending our homes.
If we don't help them--
[MASTER HAWKEYE] I'm tired of
hearing that vile rhetoric.
I can't stand to see you like
this. There's no reason for a
man of your stature to suffer
in this kind of squalor...
If you would simply
join the military,
you could get grants for
your research, you could--
[MASTER HAWKEYE]
I don't need a grant for
something I've
already completed.
You've finished your research?
I've created the most
powerful alchemy...
It would only cause tragedy if
I placed in the wrong hands...
And now that
I've finished it,
I've allowed myself
to grow complacent.
We alchemists are
hungry creatures...
We must continue the hunt for
knowledge as long as we live...
If we forego pursuing the truth,
then we allow ourselves to die.
Trust me... I've
been dead for a long time--
Master!
[ROY] Are you alright?!
Master Hawkeye?!
Look after... my daughter...
She's in possession of...
my research...
Look after her...
[HAWKEYE] You've done so
much... I don't think
I can ever thank you enough...
[ROY] It's the least
I could do...
After everything
he's taught me.
You should take this...
You can call me in
the military if you need to.
[ROY]
Let me guess...
You also don't approve of
me becoming a soldier...?
Your father told me
soldiers are left to die
like trash on the
side of the road.
That may be...
But I know it's the only
way to make a difference...
And I know that I'll never be
happy if I don't try
to make this country
a better place.
Man... That must've
sounded pretty childish, huh.
Not at all... There's nothing
childish about caring.
[HAWKEYE]
I'd like to believe that
you're serious about this...
That you really do care...
Can I trust you, Roy...?
With my Father's research?
No, Hayate... Bad dog.
Sorry about that.
[ED] Don't worry,
it happens all the time.
So I uh... heard you're
working for the Fuhrer.
Yeah.
[HAWKEYE] Looks like things
got pretty serious.
[ED]
Yeah, but I didn't use it.
I didn't have to.
Well... I couldn't
pull the trigger.
[ED] It's pathetic,
huh? If I just...
Well, I was just useless.
[HAWKEYE]
Tell me what happened.
Y'know Scar...? I found out he
murdered Winry's parents.
[ED] She could've shot
him. But deep down,
I knew that would be wrong.
And all of a sudden, that gun
seemed like something evil...
Next thing I knew...
I stopped her...
But I honestly think
she would've shot him
if I hadn't been there.
She could hardly stop crying
once I got the gun away.
And it's my fault...
I've got no resolve...
I only manage to
make things worse.
You're just dwelling
on this stuff
because you made it back alive.
You need to stay
focused on living...
That's how you'll help Winry.
[HAWKEYE]
How else can you protect her?
I mean, after all...
You love her, don't you?
[ED REACTS TO COMMENT]
No no no,
i-i-it's not like that!
We've just been friends
since we were little kids!
She's like family to me!
I mean, of course I'm
gonna protect her! You know?
[ED'S NERVOUS LAUGHTER]
HAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!
What happened with Scar...
[HAWKEYE] I'm sorry...
This only added to your burdens.
[ED] I've gotta ask... Does it
ever feel like a burden to you?
[HAWKEYE] I've lost the right to
look at it that way...
So it'd be wrong to complain...
I'm not proud of it...
But I've killed too many
to feel sorry for myself...
Besides... I can't deny that I
am the one who chose this path.
You mean Ishval?
Can I ask you about that...?
Would it be alright?
[SCAR] It's time to confess.
Tell me your sins...
What did you do to my people?
[HAWKEYE] Ishval is a
harsh and barren country,
filled with rocks and sand...
Considering the terrain,
it's not surprising that it
would give birth to such
a stringent religion,
or that it's people would be
so earnest and resolute...
It's only natural that a
faction of the population
would protest the country's
annexation by Amestris.
Their mistrust
was soon justified.
[HAWKEYE] That one bullet
changed everything...
Their mistrust
turned to outrage...
And dissidence spread
like a contagion.
[EXPLOSION]
[HAWKEYE] It soon
escalated into a civil war...
And the fighting lasted
for seven long years.
Until a simple one page document
determined the Ishvalan's fate.
Executive Order
Thirty Sixty-Six.
The official order
to initiate the
[MARCHING SOUNDS]
Ishvalan War of Extermination.
[HAWKEYE CONTINUES]
It was like hell on Earth.
The air was tainted with the
smell of human decay...
And the desert sand soaked up
the blood like a sponge.
[HAWKEYE]
Most combat is blind...
A normal soldier might
fire erratically without
a clear target in mind...
But it's different for snipers.
Someone is sure to die
when we pull the trigger.
Where other soldiers don't
always have a direct line
of sight on the effects of
their actions... snipers do.
And, of course,
the State Alchemists.
Listen here...! I am the Iron
Blood Alchemist... Basque Grand!
Iron and blood!
I am both soldier and weapon!
Now stand down...!
I am the only man able
to take the lead
in this battle!
[FRIGHTENED REAX, FLEEING
ADLIBS, & PAINED REAX]
They took my leg...!
Those savage Ishvalan dogs!
[COMMANCHE]
Damn them...!
Damn themmm!
Hey... Roy! Roy Mustang!
[HUGHES]
So you got deployed too...
Well it's good to see you...
Although... You've changed
since the last time I saw you.
[ROY]
I could say the same, Hughes.
You have the eyes of a killer.
Yeah.
[HUGHES]
Look at this country...
It's not exactly the
future we imagined
when we were at the academy.
[ROY] Yeah. I guess that
future could never be.
[MAIL OFFICER]
Captain... You have a letter.
[HUGHES]
Oh... Thank you.
[HUGHES LAUGHS]
[ROY]
What...? What's wrong?
I've still got a
beautiful future...!
And her name is Gracia...
She's patiently
waiting in Central
for the day I can
come home...!
All alone.
How long before some jerk
puts the moves on her?!
No... Gracia would
never do that me...
She'd never have an affair like
that... But she is all alone.
Hey, Hughes...? I've got
a little advice for you.
It happens in movies
and novels all of the time...
The soldiers who never shut up
about their girls back home?
They don't make it.
Not funny, Roy.
[HUGHES] Alright then... I can
make it through this day.
This letter is all I need...
I can think about
tomorrow again...
Even if this damn battlefield
might not let me see it.
[ROY] I can't picture any
way out of this war...
No matter how much military
force we throw at it...
The desert seems to
just suck it up like water.
[ROY CONTINUES] All of this
destruction... for what purpose?
All that's left is sand.
True. It seems a
little excessive
to suppress an uprising.
Hello, Major Mustang...
Long time no see.
Do you still remember me?
[ROY THINKS]
Damn this war... Even her...
She has the
eyes of a killer, too...
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[HAWKEYE] Maybe you can
answer this, Major.
Why are we being
ordered to kill citizens...?
When we should be
the ones protecting them?
I thought alchemy was meant
to be used to help people...
So why is it being used
to kill them instead?
[KIMBLEE] Because that's
the job we State Alchemists
have been given to do.
You ask why we're here killing
these people instead of
protecting them...?
Because this is a war
and that's what soldiers do.
Isn't that right?
[ROY] You think this is our
job...? To cause tragedy?
[KIMBLEE]
Well that's how it seems...
But let's see. Tell me, miss...
You're not very happy
to be here, are you...?
Well, you don't appear to be.
[KIMBLEE CONTINUES]
But can you honestly tell me...
In that split second when
you take down an enemy...
You don't allow yourself
to feel the slightest tinge
of satisfaction and pride
in your skills?
Well Miss Marksmen?
[ROY]
That's enough, Kimblee!
I'll tell you what I don't get.
Did you people expect
something different...?
You act like you're surprised...
Like you didn't choose this.
[KIMBLEE]
Did you put on that uniform
thinking you wouldn't
be asked to kill?
The one thing worse than death
is to avert your eyes from it.
Look straight at
the people you kill...
Don't take your eyes
off them for a second.
[KIMBLEE CONTINUES]
And don't ever forget them.
Because I promise
that they won't forget you.
[KIMBLEE] Oh. Too bad...
There's the bell.
Time for me to get back to work.
I've gotta head out, too...
See ya later, Roy.
Hughes... Can you tell
me why you fight?
[HUGHES] It's simple...
I don't want to die...
That's the only reason.
[HUGHES CONTINUES]
The reasons are always simple.
[MASSIVE EXPLOSIONS]
[ROY THINKS]
If that's so...
What the hell is
the reason for this war?
[MARCOH]
The reason? There is one...
But it's worse
than you can imagine.
[SHOTS RING OUT]
[PEOPLE REACT TO BEING SHOT]
You took the lives of my people
to create a
Philosopher's Stone?!
[SCAR]
What happened to this Stone?!
[MARCOH] It was given to
Major Solf J. Kimblee.
He was known as the
Crimson Alchemist.
Did you see what
this man looked like...?
Did he have
black hair and cold eyes?
[MARCOH]
Yes...
[SCAR]
My brother...
Keep talking.
Eh-everything changed...
that single stone turned
the battle around.
[KIMBLEE]
Ahh... What a beautiful sound.
It doesn't get
any better than that...
I can feel it
deep in my bones...
Like a part of me
I never noticed before...
That sound is an
extension of my being.
And this land... This land
that's governed by death,
I will paint it red with this
shard of destruction.
I couldn't dream
of a more fulfilling job!
[EXPLOSIONS AND SCREAMS]
[KIMBLEE] Such a beautiful
sound...! Like a symphony...!
This stone is amazing!
It didn't take long after that.
The Ishvalans were slaughtered.
[HAWKEYE] With no other options,
the Ishvalans surrendered...
The High Priest of Ishvala,
Logue Lowe,
offered himself to the Fuhrer
on behalf of his people.
[BRADLEY] So... You're asking
me to take your life in place
of the remaining tens of
thousands of Ishvalans.
[LOWE]
That's correct... I stand--
[BRADLEY]
How arrogant of you.
Do you sincerely believe
that your single life is
equivalent to the remaining
multitude of your followers...?
Your stature has
gone to your head.
The life of any individual
human is only worth one life...
That's all--nothing more
and nothing less.
[BRADLEY CONTINUES]
Your life is not enough to
call off the extermination.
How can you be so inhuman?!
You will suffer the
hammer of God!
[BRADLEY] God, you say...?
Now this is intriguing...
How much longer
do you think your "God"
plans to wait before
unleashing his fury?
Just how many
thousands of lives must
I take before he decides
to strike me down?
[MONK 3]
You're a monster!
[BRADLEY]
Open your eyes...
God is nothing more
than a construct,
created by man to inspire
fear and promote order...
If you wish to see
me struck down
for all of these atrocities...
Use your own hands
to do so... Not God's.
[HAWKEYE]
And that's it.
The war soon ended.
And we were all discharged
and returned to our homes.
Now we know. We really are as
expendable as garbage to them.
Yeah... The power of one man...
It doesn't amount to much.
But that doesn't matter... With
what little strength I have...
I'll do whatever it takes...
to protect the people I love...
And in turn... they'll protect
the one's they love...
It seems like the least we tiny
humans can do for each other.
So you've decided to
take this path after all...
Even after what you
went through in Ishval.
Yes, sir.
[HAWKEYE]
If the world truly operates
based on the principals of
equivalent exchange,
then we soldiers
have plenty to give back.
If this world is
meant to prosper,
then it is our duty to
carry the bodies of the dead
across a river of blood
to their resting place.
[ROY] From now on...
I'm assigning you to
be my assistant...
I feel like I can trust you
to watch my back.
Although... I expect you
understand what this means...
You'll be able to shoot me
in the back as well.
[ROY] If I ever deviate
from this path,
then I want you to shoot me.
And I'm trusting you to do so.
[ROY]
Do you accept my offer?
Of course I do, sir.
[HAWKEYE] I'll follow you into
hell if you ask me to.
[ED] But even if the Colonel
does become the Fuhrer...
How will that change the fact
that this is still
a military state?
[HAWKEYE] Well it won't...
The first thing we'll have to do
is restore power
to the parliament...
We'll take it back
from the military...
And make it democratic again.
[HAWKEYE] Only after
the full extent of the
military's corruption has
been brought to light
can this country
move forward...
What d'you mean?
[HAWKEYE] For example,
those who were praised as
heroes during the Ishvalan
campaign will be brought
to trial as war criminals.
That's right... In a
just, peaceful world...
After all that we've done...
we'll be seen as mass murderers.
[ED] And the Colonel is trying
to make sure this happens...?
Isn't that just like
committing suicide?
But the Homunculi were
the ones pulling the strings...
They caused the civil war.
Even if they were the
ones responsible for it,
we were the soldiers
who carried it out.
[HAWKEYE] You should never avert
your eyes from death...
Never forget the
people you've killed...
Trust me. No matter how
much time passes,
they will never forget
the ones who killed them.
[ED]
It's not right.
You don't have time to
start worrying about us...
Your hands are already full...
You need to look
after your brother, Ed...
And you need to
get your bodies back.
[HAWKEYE] You better get to it.
You've got plenty of
people waiting for that day.
[ED] I'll get our bodies back...
And Al will help me.
[AL] Good night, Dr. Knocs...
Sorry for the intrusion.
[MAY CHANG]
Excuse me... Mr. Armor?
I just wanted to thank
you for your help...
You saved both of our lives.
[AL] My name's not Mr. Armor...
It's Alphonse Elric.
[MAY CHANG]
Your name is Elric?
[AL] You remember
Edward Elric, don't you...?
The little alchemist
you screamed at...?
Well I'm actually his
younger brother.
[AL] It's kind of a long story,
but I lost my body.
[MAY CHANG] So you're his
younger brother, huh...?
You probably look
just like him, then.
[AL] How rude! For starters, I'm
way taller than my brother is!
And I don't have a
mean face like his...
And I'm a much
better fighter too!
[AL] And I don't have a temper
like he does. I'm a gentleman.
[MAY CHANG]
Oh, Alphonse!
[MAY CHANG] I really hope that
you get your body back soon.
[AL]
Oh... Well thank you.
[ENVY] Hope you're decent,
Doc. It's time for your supper.
[ENVY] Huhhh... It sure
is quiet in here.
Are you thinking about Ishval
and crying yourself to sleep?
[NARRATOR] The release of a
devil into the wild ushers
in the beginning of a new
battle, but there is
still no end to
the war in sight.
The young man continues
to stand his ground,
with hope guiding his
sight beyond the horizon
toward the future.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode thirty-one...
The Five Hundred
and Twenty Cens Promise.
There is another
world resting there,
that only your closest
allies know of.