It's hot...
Today's the start of September, yet why is it still so hot even in the morning?
We had to eat the leftover curry...
Good morning, Minorin!
Yo, yo, you two.
How have you been?
H-Hey, Kushieda, how are you-
Hey! Everyone!
Did you do your summer homework?
Did you brush your teeth?
Did you take a bath?
What's with you, Haruta?
You're all over the place.
You sir, something happened to you during summer vacation!
Summer vacation is old news!
The hopes are in the second term.
We're going for the next stage, the cultural festival!
Or something else new...
Sounds nice...
How nice, something happened during your summer vacation...
Yuri-chan Sensei?
But that's true... Of course something happened...
After all, it is your seventeenth summer.
It's completely different compared to the summer of someone who just entered her thirties.
Life is really unfair...
It seems like nothing happened to Yuri-chan Sensei.
Therefore, it was decided that this year's festival...
will also only be open for one day.
Even with the president's power...
This isn't something that they just pushed onto us.
This is a negotiation.
We are still negotiating with the teachers.
That's right!
If things go as we want, there will still be meaning even if we give up on a two-day festival.
I'll do whatever it takes to make this year's culture festival amazing.
After all, for me, this is my last major school event.
Feint!
Takasu-kun, let's look for a UFO next.
Hey! Stupid Chihuahua!
What the hell are you doing?
Like I said....
My nails are long, so I can't touch the ball.
They'll break.
You Stupid Chihuahua!
Her cute smile...
Ami-chan really is an angel.
I'm a Tenori Taiga fan.
As for me, I'm for Kashiwagi.
Kihara is great too.
Taiga is riding Ami-chan like a horse!
I want her to ride on me!
Ladies and zentlemen!
What?
There aren't any ladies!
What's with the "zentle"?
Everyone, wouldn't you like to see that girl you have in your hearts in a really cute costume?
Are you okay?
You didn't get caught in something weird over the summer?
Listen to the whole thing first!
The cultural festival is coming up.
Tomorrow in our long homeroom class, we in 2-C have to decide on our event...
And I'm on the cultural festival committee!
So what?
So...
If we decide to do a maid cafe for the cultural festival, we'll be able to see all the girls in maid outfits.
If the event is picked by whichever one gets the most votes, and all the boys get together and decide...
We will surely get the majority vote!
How's that!?
Sounds good.
Even though it's coming from Haruta.
Wait a second...
If it's like that, instead of maid outfits, I want to see China dresses!
We could do that too!
Takasu, you agree, right?
Y-Yeah, certainly...
I always see her in a maid-like outfit at the restaurant.
In a China dress that snugly traces her body... That's...
No, that's no good!
Something that fits snugly means I'll have to make bra pads again.
What are you talking about?
Oh, nothing!
Rather than China dresses, I'd like...
Lolita or something...
Takasu...
You're a genius!
In that case, I want nurses!
We need stewardesses!
You, fool! Call them cabin attendants!
Wait, wait, don't keep saying whatever!
What were we talking about-
Cosplay cafe.
If we do that, that would solve everything.
That's it!
Taiga, I'm going ahead.
Okay.
Ryuji!
Look at this!
What? All of a sudden...
Wow, this is bad.
That Stupid Chihuahua tore it!
Hey!
Stop talking badly about others.
You stepped on it, fell, and tore it all by yourself.
It all began because you avoided the ball!
I said that's because my nails-
Quit it.
I'll stitch it up.
You're spoiling her again.
Make sure you do it by next week.
Hey! Don't just walk off after leaving the blame on me!
Hey!
They're pretty lively.
Kushieda!
Let's go back to class.
Y-Yeah.
You're right.
By the way...
About the UFO...
As a diet warrior, instant noodles really are my enemy.
Knock on wood!
I have to put another piece of cloth on the back.
I guess I'll sacrifice one of Yasuko's old winter underwear.
Your cell's ringing.
It's fine.
That shitty old man.
Shitty old man?
What's that?
Whatever it is, it bothers me, so answer-
Shut up!
What's with you?
I said to leave it alone.
He's a guy who got re-married,
found me inconvenient, gave me an apartment, and drove me out of my house.
He threw me away. He's that kind of cold-hearted man.
He's your dad?!
Shitty old man!
Whatever kind of man he is, your father is your father.
Don't call him a shitty old man.
Even if you are apart from your family, somewhere in your heart, something more like-
I said he's a shitty old man!
Shit-ty-ty. Old.
You don't have to remember that!
Hemorrhoid.
Inko-chan, again.
What?
Ryu-chan, are you talking about Papa?
I'm not talking about Dad!
He was a wonderful guy.
"Always ready if I'm stabbed."
You're talking about that again!
That's not the least bit wonderful.
Don't talk about that in front of people!
Why?
So...
We would like to chose our event, and the Miss Ohashi candidate.
I don't think anyone has any objections...
To making Ami-chan our candidate for Miss Ohashi.
On our side, we have no objections...
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
I'm really happy for the thought, but I've been selected to MC the Miss Ohashi contest.
So, even though you've kindly selected me, I can't be in the contest.
So, I think Aisaka-san would be great!
After all, Aisaka-san is really tiny and cute.
That, and she's really famous throughout the whole school.
What the hell are you saying, Idiot Chihuahua!?
Why do I have to do something like that?
But it might be good, actually.
Taiga is pretty famous.
It might actually go well.
You bastards...
Hey, hey.
That's no good, Tiger-chan.
You're a member of this class too. You have to actively participate in these kinds of events too.
Hey! Stupid Chihuahua!
If you don't get it by just me saying it, I'll smash the whole festival-
It's okay.
Calm down, calm down.
If it's Aisaka, you might really win.
Right?
Alright!
Then, our Miss Ohashi candidate is Taiga.
Next, what will we do for our event?
Yes!
Yes, Noto-kun!
How about a cosplay cafe?
Isn't that way too geeky?
That will definitely overlap with what other classes are doing.
I definitely don't like it!
Hey, well, it's not like I want to do it myself...
But, I don't really like things like this,
but I think it'd be nice if everyone could have fun...
That is, a hau-haunted house...
I got a nosebleed.
Don't get me wrong. I'm not trying to say something weird.
I just... A hau-haunted house...
Kushieda, why don't you quit that.
Your body can't keep up.
I won't let you...
I won't let you.
Yuri-chan?
Coffee shop? No way!
Let's form a band and do a live concert.
But, in Japan, that's the worst thing you can do.
After all, it's just a dream to really get everyone worked up in just a day.
At any rate, it'll just break up by Christmas.
Anyway, we can't decide on anything like this!
In the end, we will do this by a deciding vote!
Everyone, write what you want to do on a piece of paper!
Whatever the girls write, it'll be useless.
They can't defeat the combined might of the boys.
Alright, everyone's done, right?
In that case...
Shake and lottery!
Hey, a lottery?!
Let me announce it!
This year's event for the cultural festival is pro-wre-
Who's the one who wrote pro-wrestling?
Why didn't you do it so majority wins?
Oh.
That Stupid Chihuahua...
I'm going to shove her down several levels of hell every time she ressurects...
Give it up. You should have fun at a class event every now and then.
You're too narrow-minded.
What? You're always the one being all happy.
Happy? Me?
Since we came back from the trip, the whole time...
Huh?
Why?
What's wrong?
It's weird. I can't withdraw any money.
The balance is zero.
Fine, I'll-
Impossible.
It's because I ignored his phone call...
He does this kind of thing.
I can't believe it.
Phone call? The one from before?
He's been calling nonstop for a while.
But they ticked me off, so I ignored them all.
And now he empties out my living allowance.
That shitty old man!
I really want to kill him!
You shouldn't say that about a parent.
This is extortion.
As a start, answer it.
You can't do anything unless you talk it out.
And you need the money, right?
So she answered it...
But why am I going alone to meet him?
I see. I got it.
My daughter won't come to see me.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I wanted to meet Taiga, no matter what.
But I just made her hate me even more, I guess.
I'm sorry.
Takasu-kun, right?
Please, order anything you want.
Well, that's okay...
It's almost dinnertime.
No, wait, okay, I'll order something.
An egg bagel, please.
Okay.
Excuse me!
Can we order?
He'll have an egg bagel.
And, I think I'll get the salmon bagel.
Put a lot of cheese in it, as much as you can.
Oh, before I forget.
The money.
I... I really wanted to meet her.
I had something important to talk to her about.
Something important?
So, are you and Taiga, that... Dating?
Absolutely not.
She's just a friend, and we're definitely not dating or anything like that.
We're living next to each other so somehow, we just got along... Or something.
I see.
Then, you've probably heard a lot about our family from Taiga.
I remarried, and the woman I married was too young.
Taiga couldn't get used to our new life.
Then misunderstandings piled on top of each other...
My wife's name is Yuu...
Taiga or Yuu... It got to the point where one of them had to leave.
And then Taiga...
I want to live with Taiga.
Once again, together.
I wanted to tell her that today.
There's absolutely no mistake.
I want to start all over again with Taiga and myself.
I'm going to divorce Yuu soon.
And then I'll live with Taiga.
Because I'm her father.
Because I love her.
It's tough.
Your dad says he's coming to get you.
Hey, what are you doing?
Do it properly. You have to rinse for more than five seconds-
Be quiet, don't help me.
In exchange for having you go meet that guy, I promised I'd do the dishes, right?
Then wash them properly.
Just go away.
Somehow, your dad is... a little weird.
He's not really like a normal adult or-
I told you to go away!
Go make some tea or something.
Your dad was really worried about you.
So, he wanted to live with you again-
Idiot.
I'm talking seriously here.
Your dad said he wanted to live with you.
I was asked by your father-
It's none of your business.
Don't talk about other people's families.
You're the one who sent me there!
I was just there to take the money, and that's it?
That's right.
That's why I'm washing the dishes.
That's why this is the end. I won't meet that person again.
Hey.
Don't jerk me around. Listen-
Shut up!
Don't touch me like that!
Your dad was depressed because you ignored him!
I felt sorry for him!
I'm the one you should feel sorry for!
Tai... ga...
Alright...
Did everyone get a copy?
I really felt responsible for this...
So I tried making a script for the pro-wrestling show.
Hey, maybe we should call it quits?
Hey, here.
Everyone!
I beg of you, please just try to show a bit of interest.
We can't go back.
Yuri-chan already stamped her approval on the form and turned it in.
Hey, this might actually be interesting.
There's a part for everyone.
I'm impressed Haruta-kun did all this.
I'm the lead!
I'm a little happy.
Ami-chan...
She's right.
Wow, it's really well-put together.
Haruta-kun, let's work hard!
Alright!
Let's start practicing.
Yes!
The time, the near future.
Under class leader, Ami-chan, the students in 2-C were living happily in peace.
However!
There was someone who thought that peace was very unpleasant.
The personification of evil, Tenori Tiger, and her follower, Yankee Takasu Ryuji.
Wait a minute.
Why am I her follower?
On top of that, a Yankee?
Why am I the "personification of evil"?
It'll all be okay, just listen until the end!
Tenori Tiger attacks the classmates of 2-C.
Their friends get brainwashed one by one.
However, with Ami-chan's desperate plea, the brainwashing is reversed.
In the end, everyone combines their power and succeeds in driving out Tenori Tiger and Yankee Takasu Ryuji.
That means, happily ever after. Happy end!
How's that!?
He told us to listen to the end, and it ends like that?
But it's simple, yet dramatic.
It just might work.
No way!
I'm definitely not doing this!
Aisaka-san is always so selfish.
Hey!
Why am I always the one who has to do weird things?
"If hitting me will end it, hit me as much as you want."
As you wish!
"But! Nothing will come of it!"
Tenori Taiga's really into it.
Already practicing? Amazing intensity.
Then, Taiga, next is Sennou's line.
Your line, your line.
"Taiga keeps screaming something..."
Ami's changed a little.
Yeah.
What's that?
Don't know. Haruta-kun said it was for a special role.
Everyone, listen!
We've gotten a decision from the school!
This year's cultural festival is a competition amongst all the classes.
The first place class gets a great prize.
By the way this is our prize.
First, for one full year, a refrigerator in the classroom.
Don't you want to cool your drinks?
Installed ahead of schedule, a moisture-providing, state of the art air conditioner which is planned to be installed next year.
That would be installed in our classroom this month.
Don't you want moisture?
The bathroom power which we are forbidden to use will become usable.
Don't you want to blow-dry your hair with that?
And finally, a discount ticket for Kanouya Supermarket.
Don't you want a discount ticket?
Hey boys, get your act together!
Hey, what are you going to do about dinner?
Buri.
How do you want the buri?
Teri.
Grilled?
Sorry.
I was waiting here.
For a while.
You stalking bastard.
Taiga!
Stop being so damn stubborn!
Let me go, you stupid dog!
You're on his side?
That's horrible!
I thought you were always on my side.
It's because I'm on your side that I'm saying it!
It's for you!
Who is that?
It's your father, right?
He's come to get you.
You should at least listen to what he has to say!
No!
That's just a stalker.
I don't need that!
Don't be stupid!
You were crying because you had been thrown away!
Be honest!
You really want to go home, right?
What the hell do you understand about me?
I don't need him, a guy like that.
I wasn't thrown away, I threw him away!
I threw him away because he was useless trash!
You... That guy...
That person, does he really look like trash to you?
No matter how much I want him to, my dad won't ever come home!
This isn't for Taiga's sake.
I...
Sorry, Taiga.
It's okay.
If you say so, then...
So...
Don't make that face.
Tai-
It's a good thing... Right?
I'll think of it like that.
I don't know if I can think like that or not, but...
If you say so...
I'll think of it like that.
This was good.
It was good.
Definitely.
Right?
Koigakubo Yuri.
This summer, I turned thirty.
Gyaa.
Everyone, please give me a present.
Or rather, please take me.