kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
Are you ready, my ladies?
Prepare to advance!
Forward!
Advancing!
Where are our allies?
40 degrees to the left!
Ready main cannon!
Distance, 400!
Load H.E.A.T. round!
Roger!
Olga?
Leave it to me.
We've been canned up in here for three days.
I'm not dying until I get a shower.
Target sighted!
Fire!
Direct hit!
Anna, inform the rear guard.
One enemy unit neutralized. Advance to our flanks.
Roger.
Filicia, cover Anna.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Even though it's flashing, it's not thunder, so calm down.
I understand!
F-From 3 o'clock!
It can't be...
Lieutenant Anna!
Paper supplies...
Bamboo supplies...
The Chirping Crickets
Offerings for the Deceased
Come on, Noël!
If you don't press it down firmly, it won't get clean!
It's so hot...
It's too cold in the winter, but since this building is also cool in the summer, it's a real lifesaver right now.
Huh? Wasn't it Rio-senpai and the Commander's turn to do the laundry today?
They were busy or something and asked us to switch with them.
Whose is that?
Filicia-san's.
For some reason, she said she wasn't hungry and told us to eat it.
In that case, I'll have some!
What is that? Getting ready for dinner?
Wait, what are you doing?
If you play around with the food, you'll get cursed.
I-I'm not playing around!
It's almost time for Obon, you know.
What the heck is "Obon"?
Fiesta du Lumières.
Fie...?
Fiesta du Lumières is an event specific to Southern Helvetia.
According to their folklore, the souls of the departed return to the Earth for a short time during the summer.
In order to commune with these spirits again,
lanterns are set adrift on a river.
In the countryside, this festival is often called "Obon."
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Huh? Then it's the same thing!
The souls of the departed come back...
Wait! Hold it, hold it! What do you mean?
You mean that ghosts actually come back?!
You could say that.
Paper lanterns? That sounds so wonderful!
Back home in the country, we only lit lamps.
No way!
When people go to heaven, they stay there forever!
Things that wander around on the Earth are bad!
That's not true at all!
But the Church...
We're back!
Hey! Come give us a hand!
When did you two go shopping?
Ah! Those are...
They looked good, so we bought some.
Of course, these as well.
How's this?
That's wrong, Father. It's like this.
I'm done!
Your mother and father?
I see! It's very well made.
What?! Even the Church approved it?!
That Fie– whatever it is.
Right. If we were in the central region, there would have been an uproar,
but this is the countryside.
What's that about?
Where I come from, we make horses and cows out of cucumbers and eggplants
to act as mounts for our ancestors.
Afterwards, we all dance to entertain the ancestors who returned.
Senpai, you're both making them as well?
Yeah. Last year we just watched, but...
It's our job to observe and join in with the local inhabitants to smooth over relations..
If you don't get too hung up over it, it's just a normal festival.
Right, Filicia?
Filicia-san?
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
Yeah, I'm fine. I just made a mistake.
But it sure is rare for the Commander to be that clumsy.
It's just like Kanata.
It's been rather hot for the past few days, hasn't it?
I haven't been able to sleep well.
I'm going to take a short break.
Filicia-san...
The Commander sure is acting strangely.
First, it seems she didn't finish her lunch.
Then, she ignored our food expenses and bought watermelons and other things.
She has a lot going on, as well.
As I thought, I should really...
Stop!
Everyone has times when they don't want to talk to anyone!
Just let her be.
Noël?
Do you know, Rio?
I read the records.
I was there in person.
Therefore...
Filicia...
Keep your arm steady, just like that.
There, there.
And then, a monster that looked like the Commander came out...
They say that a lot of things used to live in this ocean.
It's hard to believe.
Have you heard?
The ones who caused the world to slowly come to an end...
It was we humans who completely destroyed everything.
But that's... just a rumor.
But if that's the truth...
Then for what reason are we fighting?
I'm... still alive...
Ideograms...
I'm sorry...
It would be great if I could read your last words, but...
This equipment...
Could you be... from the previous age?!
Commander...
Lieutenant Olga...
Martina...
Anna-san...
Why... am I the only one...?
Why... are you crying?
I see.
So... there are people who still live in this world.
I am sorry...
I am truly sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
It's because we lost...
...to them.
We weren't able to protect you.
I am truly sorry.
The world has already ended.
No way...
You are just the dregs.
You are the final remnants of humanity we had left behind.
Humanity can...
This world can no longer return to its former prosperity.
Don't decide that on your own!
But that is the reality.
That's why it's fine for it to end.
This shell of a world, which is living in the depths of despair, is just too sad, isn't it?
No, not at all.
Why? Is there any meaning to living in this world?
That's...
Help me...
I'm right here!
I'm alive!
I beg of you, please save me!
You are...
I'm sorry.
If my unit had arrived just half a day earlier, I'm sure this wouldn't have happened.
Princess Iliya...
But I was a little surprised.
By what?
Because you ignored the Fiesta du Lumières last year.
What's with the change of heart?
That's...
It's a nice color, right?
I bought it from that old man earlier.
Wow!
This is amazing!
Isn't it?
Certainly...
Long ago, that person was everything to me.
Just like her, this country...
Its people were the ones I'd wanted to protect.
But every now and then, I think...
"What point is there in doing that?"
That's why, if she were to actually return...
I thought I would want her to tell me.
More so, how about you?
Everyone is worried about you.
You're right.
I might have made them feel a bit uncomfortable.
But that's a requirement for a commander.
It's not just them!
Even I... that is...
That is?
Anyways! You don't have to suffer alone!
Even I can listen, too!
Thank you, Rio.
Then, I'll take you up on your offer and fill you in.
What is it?
The truth is...
I'm worried about the summer fat.
At this rate, I won't be able to wear winter clothing.
I'd heard that eating watermelon would make you thinner, so I thought I'd try it out, but...
Wait, what's wrong, Rio?
Are you still playing dumb?!
Because at that Vingt campaign—
Ah! Did you believe that I was thinking about that?
A-Are you saying you weren't...?
It's so pretty...
Shall we go too?
Kureha-chan made one too?
I-It's not like I believe in souls or anything, though.
It's my duty! Duty.
Umm...
Filicia-san, who are you sending off?
Companions from long ago.
And a lone unknown soldier.
It's for the ones who'd taught me many important things.
Could that person be...?
Filicia-san.
If there's anything troubling you, I...
Well, I might not be of any use though...
But!
It looks like I've made you worry.
I'm sorry.
But it's all right.
That's so sad.
I want to worry about you!
Filicia-san is always worrying about me!
If something is worrying you, then I want to worry about you!
Because I love you, Filicia-san!
I love you too, Kana-chan.
Don't change the way you are now.
Please.
Filicia-san.
I'll tell you anytime.
These heavy words won't be forgotten.
I think that's a great thing.
Commander...
Filicia...
Me too...
Oh, everyone...
How adorable.
Please come again next year, my ancestors.
Dad... Mom...
Mother... Sister...
That person is...
Hey, Rio, you asked me earlier if there was any meaning to this world.
Yeah.
Since I was the only one left alive, I thought about that for a long time.
"Why am I the only one still alive, and is there any meaning in that?"
And then I realized it.
I'm sure there isn't any sort of meaning to this world.
But isn't that still wonderful?
Because if there isn't one, then you can decide what it is for yourself.
And I found it.
The reason why I'm here.
And then the Father...
And then?
He was really scowling. Then Yumina-oneechan...
To definitely never let those children feel the same way I did.
Yeah...
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
Phone Duty
State of Emergency Declared
Next time: Phone Duty · State of Emergency Declared