Takasu-kun!
I'm...
Going to go after her!
Takasu-kun, go left. I'll take the right.
Let's go!
Student Council President,
they're running in the halls.
I'll overlook it this time.
What...
Will I say when I catch up to her?
I don't know.
I don't know, but...
Not here...
The school entrance!
Taiga, can you hear me?
Hey, Taiga, you've always wanted to know, right?!
I...
Takasu-kun...
I like Takasu Ryuji too!
I like him!
I've always liked him!
But...
I thought I should let you have him!
I thought that if you, my best friend, needed him...
But that was just me being arrogant.
I...
Underestimated you!
I said it just now, didn't I?
My happiness is something I decide!
Same for you, you're the only one who can decide your own happiness.
So that's why...
That's why, Taiga...
Let me see your way of doing things!
Kushieda!
At some point, I... Tripped...
Did it stop?
That freaked me out.
I thought you were crying.
You think I'd cry?
Of course, that's what you would think, normally.
Then you'll be rewarded.
Remember when I said there was something I can see?
Yeah, I think so...
Actually...
It's the strength... Inside of me...
Strength?
I told you about my brother, the baseball player, right?
I used to play baseball too.
Honestly, I was better than him.
But I couldn't continue playing because I'm a girl.
That's why I plan to save money.
Then, I'll get into a sports university by my own power and aim for the national softball league.
Then I'll shout out to the whole world:
"This is the happiness I chose, the happiness I caught with my own two hands!"
Maybe it's just stubbornness.
Kushieda...
But because that was my goal, I decided to quit crying.
Even if it's hard or painful, I decided I'd try my best.
But...
I guess it's some kind of reward if someone is there to see me through the hardship, the pain, the tears.
What happened to that hairpin?
Oh, that...
That must have been the present you tried to give me on Christmas Eve, right?
That's—
I'm sorry...
I really didn't know at first.
I thought it was a present from Taiga.
Even though I decided not to take it...
Knowing you'd be hurt...
I want to apologize for wearing it in front of you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Huh?
Where is it right now?
It's in my room.
But—
I won't accept it.
You know...
There's something else I can see.
It's that you like Taiga.
Yeah...
Alright, Takasu-kun...
It's the giant goodbye.
Run toward what you can see!
Go, Takasu!
Ta-ka-su, hey!
Ta-ka-su, yeah!
Ta-ka-su!
I knew you'd come.
W-Why?
You're really honest in weird ways.
Even though you ran away, I knew you'd definitely come to work.
Hey...
About earlier...
I...
I heard Minorin's voice.
Don't laugh!
I'm not laughing.
Don't laugh.
Please.
After work, listen to what I have to say.
If...
If I look like I'm going to run away again...
Catch me.
Please.
We got a lot.
You lied!
Ya—
Yasuko...
Taiga!
What are you doing here?
Don't touch me!
Stop being so stubborn!
Just what do you think you can do by yourself?
H-Hey, Taiga...
I take it you're Takasu-kun.
Y-Yes.
Thank you for being her friend all this time.
From now on, she'll be staying with me—
Who the hell would want to stay with you, your new man, and that brat?
W-What?
What's going on?
I don't understand.
Yacchan's the one who doesn't understand!
Ryuu-chan, you promised that you wouldn't work!
But you lied and broke your promise!
I won't forgive you!
You won't forgive me?
For my sake, you added on extra jobs.
Then you fainted...
If it's going to be like that, then I'll work!
What's wrong with that?!
We're family!
Because we're family, we should help each other out—
I don't care about anything else!
I just want you to study hard!
I want you to find something you want to do and live a great life—
Who's the one who didn't study?!
The one who threw away what they wanted to do and didn't become some great person...
That's all you!
Ryuu-chan...
Don't try to push your failures on me!
I—
Taiga...
T-Taiga?
Taiga!
Come back, Taiga!
That damn old man's company went under, and he ran away in the middle of the night.
Seriously?
Then he told my real mom to take care of me.
But she already has a new family.
And she's got a baby on the way.
The father is tall...
So the child will definitely have long legs.
I'd be way out of my league.
There's...
No way I can become part of a family like that.
If I were there, I'd only make everything awkward.
I know, because it was the same at that damn old man's place.
Because I was there, everyone...
I always...
Thought the same thing...
If I hadn't been there,
Yasuko definitely would've had a better life.
She's still young.
She could probably still go back to high school...
Ryuji?
Adults are really selfish.
They mess up everyone else's lives because of their own problems.
But...
I think I might be the one who's messed up Yasuko's life...
Because I'm a kid.
That's right...
If I weren't here...
Ryuji!
No, you pig-brain!
Don't do something foolish!
W-What?
I think you've got the wrong idea...
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Baldy! Baldy!
What can you solve by doing that?
How can you say something so naive like "Because I'm here..."?
You said the same thing! Just now!
But I'm alive!
Because...
You're here!
I thought it would be okay.
No matter who you like...
No matter who you spend the rest of your life with...
Just you...
I just want to be able to see you, Takasu Ryuji!
So...
So don't ever say things like "If I'd never been there" again!
What happened?
What are you doing?
What, "What happened"?
Are you trying to kill me?
Oh, my, that's no good.
It's cold.
I said I'm sorry!
No!
You never said it!
You're really nitpicky.
What sign are you?
I'm a Taurus!
I'm not good with astronomy...
But Genghis Khan is good.
I'm not talking about that!
In two months...
I'll be eighteen!
I'm going to run away from Yasuko and the others now.
I'll run and run.
Then I'll sleep and wake up, and then I'll run until it's my birthday.
At that time...
Marry me!
That way, we'll be adults too.
We won't let anyone get in our way.
I'll give you my life until I die!
I lov—
Hold it right there!
No fair!
I said I'd say it first, didn't I? So listen to me!
You cheating dog!
What?
You should let the guy say this kind of stuff!
Let me say it!
I promised Minorin.
I'm going to show her my way of doing things.
T-Then...
Together...
I...
Lo—
What is it?
At a time like this?
Ignore it.
Let's hurry up and finish.
It's cold...
What the hell is that?
That'd be a waste!
Just answer it!
O-Okay.
Hey, Takasu, what the hell are you doing?
Kitamura?
Your moms are calling all over the plac—
Nevermind, just come to the address I tell you, now.
W-Wait, Kitamura!
Your snot got on my hair!
Wh—
Why are you looking like that?
Why are we meeting at your house?
Your mothers haven't contacted us yet.
My aunt and her family aren't here today, so come in.
You'll catch a cold if you stay like that.
Take a shower first.
Turn right at the end of the hall.
Here, this and this too.
I can't believe I'm being taken care of by you...
You're right...
Thanks.
Hey, Taiga, your shoes!
Kawashima?
Nothing.
Oh, yeah, Yuusaku said he'll bring you a change of clothes.
I'm sorry about all of this.
i'm going in.
You... Love Taiga, don't you?
W-What are you talking about?!
You do, don't you?
Yeah...
Say it properly...
What's with you?
Say it.
Why?
I love Taiga.
You look so dumb saying something so lovey.
You're the one who forced me to say something lovey!
Taiga!
Making me so worried like that!
How could you?! How could you?! How could you?!
Minorin!
I'm sorry!
Kitamura...
Taiga, Taiga!
I'm sorry for everything.
It's all right.
Anyway, what are you planning to do now?
Taiga!
Well...
We...
Plan to run away-ken.
Huh?
We're serious-ken.
I see.
If you wait two more months, huh?
What do you see?!
Running away and then getting married?
That's way too much!
Until Ryuji turns eighteen, then...
Just where do you think you'll be sleeping?
Well...
For now, we could stay in a business hotel or maybe even a manga cafe for now...
Do you plan to live like that forever?
No... Well, after I come back...
Do you think you can come back?
Just imagine the rumors going around school if they ask the police to search for you...
You two might even get expelled.
Well...
I...
All those things I wanted are broken.
That's why I decided to not want anything.
But my feelings were returned.
My wish came true.
And that's is where I decided to break this never ending cycle myself
No, I have to break it.
That's why... That's why...
This is an account with a pretty nice amount of money in it.
All the money from my part time jobs are there.
Why?
Takasu-kun...
Taiga...
I don't think you're right at all.
There's absolutely no way I can agree with it.
Minorin...
But...
If this is your way of doing things, I can't object to it either.
So take this.
You'll definitely give it back to me one day.
Hey...
This is the key to my summer house.
You went there once, so you know where it is, right?
Kawashima.
I can't let you forget about me.
Take these.
Thank you.
Everyone.
Bye, Ami.
Thanks for today.
Good work!
Minorin's got a little something to discuss with Amin.
Why do I have to—
So you made up!
Good for you, Stupid Chihuahua.
Whatever, just go!
She's go—
Well then.
Minorin...
Stupid Chihuahua.
See you again.
Definitely see you again!
Bye.
Wai—
What "little something"?
Hey, let go.
My legs are so weak, I can't even stand.
Wait, what are you do—
What?
You wanted to show me your crying face?
Tears are a nosebleed of the heart.
And what are those tears for?
Because Taiga stole Takasu-kun?
Or—
I don't know...
Even though I decided not to cry...
To never cry again...
You're so pathetic.
But I've learned one thing.
If you fall while running down a hallway, blood drops will fall.
If you fall in life, tear drops will fall.
That's stupid.
It's way too early for us to be talking about life.
From here on out...
For ten more years, for twenty more years, for sixty more years...
Life will just keep going on.
When you're all ready, you need to make a good escape.
About Yacchan—
Don't worry.
I'll do it right.
Bye.
Wait!
Oh, yeah!
Bring your hair dryer.
I don't want the stuff I have to carry being too heavy.
Okay, I got it.
Then, don't bring too much frilly stuff.
It'll just take up space.
I know!
Come out right after you're done!
If something happens, call me right away!
Right away.
I'm home.
Not home yet?
I-Inko-chan?
Yasuko?
This is your grandfather and grandmother's house.
I know they'll take good care of you if you show them this watch.
Mirano-san?
She called last night saying she'll be taking a vacation.
Dammit...
She ran away.
How much of a kid can she be?
If I run away too...
I'll never become an adult.
Even after my birthday.
Look! Look!
It's chocolate!
You showed it off yesterday too.
Eat it already, just how long do you plan to show it off?
Until it's just about to expire?
Weren't you the one who said that school isn't a place for exchanging chocolate?
I'm not!
I just brought it!
Right, Taiga? Huh?
She's absent.
Takasu-kun too.
What?
Did they both catch a cold?
More like a fever.
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
Ohashi!
Hey, you...
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
You're sure you're okay not seeing them off?
What? I can't hear you!
Even a muscle girl like her...
I guess it was just too much to be dumped by both Taiga and Takasu-kun.
Why do I have to have a snowball fight with—
You!
Take this!
The White Ball That Knows No Sin!
Since they're snacks for running away together, I tried to pick some that were a little grown-up.
Look.
Chocolate cigars, chili crackers...
And—
I brought some lunch too.
Here.
Everyone knows you should buy lunch from the train station when you run away...
Though, I'll take it.
How'd it go...
With your mom?
She only cares about what everyone else thinks.
I don't think she'll make a big deal out of it.
Hey...
How'd it go with Yacchan?
Okay I guess...
Now that it's like this, I can say it...
When Yacchan said, "We're a family of three,"
I was so happy.
You know how my family is like.
That's why...
When we're really becoming a family like this.
Will...
Yacchan cry?
No, I don't mean it like that!
It's not goodbye forever!
It's not that I don't want to run away with you...
I think it's really great, but...
Yeah...
You're right.
Hey, Taiga...
Father!
F-F-Father!
This is certainly...
Then you must be... That is...
Nice to meet you!
I am your grandson, Takasu Ryuji.
And this is my wife.
And...
I have a request.
We're not...
Running away.
Ryuji showed me his own way of doing things.
Now it's my turn.
Hey, Ryuji.
Don't laugh.
Don't get mad.