When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Pier 13
Garbage Collection Site
Authorized Personnel Only
Where am I?
What have I...
What in the world was I...
This is an awfully ugly robot.
Eight.
I am going to fight in earnest!
I remember now.
I... I...
I can't meet my end like this!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
That voice...
I-It's like this enormous suffering!
Here begins a story of science
fiction and suspense!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
A Big Bother, Even for Peter
As I thought, the butler
uniform just won't do.
Huh? Wh-What is this?
Don't tell me... not again...
It's settled! Metamorphosis!
No, no, that can wait for another time.
Another time?!
You mean, you have plans for
me to cross-dress again?!
Wh-What was I thinking?!
Yes, well, eventually.
Depending on the ratings, it
may get slotted in earlier.
But that aside, for today,
I was thinking you can't be dressed
like that for the amusement park.
A-Amusement park?
So there you have it. You're
going to change clothes!
Help me, Maria!
Yes, ma'am!
Wait! I can... I can change on my own!
Ah! That looks quite good on you!
Honestly! I'm capable of
changing on my own, you know.
Dressed like that, somehow it makes
you actually look like a boy your age.
Then we're off, Hayate.
Oh, yes.
Oh, Nagi, your hat.
Aww...
But Miss, will you be okay
going to an amusement park?
Huh? What do you mean?
No, it's just that you're a
bit of a social recluse, so...
Don't refer to me like I'm at the
forefront of some modern disease!
B-But you don't like going out and stuff.
Fool. What are you saying?
As if I would bother to go
out to the amusement park!
What?
This is within the bounds of the property.
Mi... Mi... Mi...
What is this, Michael Jackson's house?!
Pow!
See? We didn't need to actually go out.
Well, the luxury that the Sanzenin
family commands certainly is something.
But there's one at Isumi's
place and at Saku's, too.
What are you ladies doing, getting
them like it's a PS3 or something...
But why this sudden visit
to the amusement park?
What?
Th-That's because, you know,
during the seaside camp,
I didn't get to have much fun with
you because of how things were.
And besides, summer break's almost over
and I-I want to enjoy it as much
as possible, just the two of us.
Uh, no, so... um...
Huh?
But I think an empty amusement
park feels a bit sad...
Wow! Look, look! Friends of the forest!
What the?!
We've got a new friend
visiting us today, nyu!
M-Miss, what is this?
Well, it is an amusement park.
It's only natural to have
some mascot characters.
I'm Little Kik Punch, a forest
fairy of NagiNagiLand, nyu.
That's not a nice name.
Man, we haven't had a
visitor in so long, nyu!
Seriously... Seriously, thank you for coming!
I mean, thank you, nyu!
I think I just heard his true feelings...
I-Incidentally, when was the
last time you were here?
Hmm, about 3 years ago, I guess?
3 years?!
I see, but 3 years...
It's got to be tough for
the people on the inside.
There are no "people on the inside"!
Uh, but you're wearing stuffed suits...
I said there aren't and I meant it!
We're fairies of the forest!
I mean, fairies, nyu!
Hey, kids! Here we go with
the NagiNagi workout!
Get over here quick
I'm a bit mad
But why do you have such a grand
amusement park at your residence?
At mach speeds
The old geezer gave it to me
a while back for my birthday.
The old geezer? Oh!
If I recall correctly, I've met him, too...
What's wrong, Hayate?
N-No, it's nothing.
B-But so it was a birthday present.
I guess your grandfather
is quite kind to you.
Do you really think so?
What? He's not?
If you think so, look carefully around you.
Look carefully?
In fact, all the rides
at this amusement park...
...require that you're over 140cm tall!
Must be at least 140cm tall to ride
140cm!
140! Got it?!
In other words, almost none of
the rides are available to me.
Th-That's a horribly elaborate
way to pick on you.
It's inconceivable that he would do
anything that might make me happy.
That's why I hate him.
The Miss is as tiny as
ever and can't ride them,
but you can, right?
Everyone, come on over here!
We've got our first visitor
ever to ride the attractions!
What? What?!
H-Hayate, are you okay?
Y-Yes.
But if possible, I'd like
something safer next...
In that case, the horror house might be good.
The horror house?
Good idea. That won't have a
height requirement, either.
N-No, wh-wh-what are you saying?!
H-H-Horror houses are... s-s-scary!
Well, that's what they're for, after all.
N-N-No, I'm not scared! I'll
have you know, I'm not scared!
It's just that, you know,
it'd be dangerous if there's a
hole in the floor or something!
This is bad. At this rate, they're
going to bypass the horror house.
After we've practiced so hard!
But if we're not careful and we
make the Miss cry or something,
we might get fired.
We can't have that...
I'll go check first to see if
there's anything dangerous.
Well, if you insist...
Him alone?
Entering the horror house...
...will be him alone!
In that case, I can friggin' roll him!
Y-You're going to friggin' roll him?!
Then, I'll be going.
B-Be careful.
But man, the degree of
perfection here is impressive.
It's really amazing.
This might make the Miss cry...
Wh-What are you doing?!
Well, we have to scare you.
That'll kill me before it scares me!
But you know...
I'll use the back of the sword.
That weapon doesn't have a back...
H-Hayate!
Given this situation, maybe
I'll be permitted to use that!
Please make sure to get permission for it!
The greatest technique of Dragon Shiryu!
Rozan!
You're too optimistic, my dearie.
Nope, still didn't happen
Actually, what is this all about?!
You're trying to make this
look like an accident,
but you're clearly out for blood!
Hmm... You want to know why?
Well...
If I had to say, I suppose it's
a direct grudge against you.
Y-You're...!
Who are you again?
Y-You don't remember me?!
Um, I have no idea who you might be,
but what grudge do you have against me?
B-Bastard! Unforgivable!
Flip.
I doubt you can see me in this dark!
I'm going to get close to you now...
D-Damn it!
Let's see how well you hold up.
There! We turned the lights on,
so you won't be scared, Miss!
Ah! This isn't scary now.
Hayate! You're all right!
Y-Yes.
Who the heck is that?
I don't know who he is or where
he's from, but he's one ugly robot.
Y-You...
...stinking brat! You, too, huh?!
Watch out, Miss!
Bastard! You're new here! The hell
are you doing going after the Miss?!
Ow! Owowowowow!
O-Ouch! That hurts!
Don't underestimate us! Don't
underestimate the forest fairies!
D-Damn it all!
Debt-ridden butler, just you remember this!
I'll get even with you for sure!
Wh-What in the world was that about?
No idea...
Miss.
Let us go.
This is your precious summer break.
Please enjoy the amusement
park to your heart's content.
Hayate!
Yes! Let's go!
I've got nothing to do.
I haven't had a single customer.
This break was a good opportunity,
so I thought I might get to see
Hayate if I worked here, but...
Hayate, hurry, hurry! We're going
on the merry-go-round next!
Yes, Miss!
Love is about passing each other by.
To be continued in the second half.
Finally, a group of four!
(Tou-tou yonin gumi!)
What animal has long ears?
(Mimi no nagai doubutsu nanda?)
Mikado Hyper Energy
Fujisusono Training Grounds
And now, we will hereby...
...commence the test for the
new caregiver robot, Model 9!
Contacts! Activate Model 9!
Activating!
Activate targets!
Fire Caregiver Missiles!
All missiles found their targets!
Good! Fire Caregiver Laser!
Good.
Activate Caregiver Goldion Hammer!
Approved!
A sink or swim moment.
Please wait a moment
The experiment is a success!
The aging population will
have nothing to fear now.
Chief, something moving at high
speeds is approaching Model 9!
"Something"?
It's too small. I can't verify the data!
Model 9, intercept it!
Boost, on!
M-My Model 9...
All right, the control chip's mine now.
Slot.
Spin... Spin...
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin,
spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin!
That debt-ridden butler's
no match for me now!
Hey!
You there, robot!
Whose industrial spy are you?!
M-Miss Makimura!
Don't tell me that even
you've forgotten about me!
Oh! Hold it right there!
I feel like I've seen that
robot somewhere before...
Damn it all! Miss Makimura, wait for me!
I'll... Without fail, I'll...
Maria, I really, really had fun today!
It was like Hayate went all-out,
whoosh, and hopping with a smile!
Yes, yes.
Hayate really enjoyed it, too!
It makes one happy when one does nice
things for others, doesn't it, Maria?
You've made yourself very clear,
so please go to bed now.
I wonder if Hayate is all right.
I treated him for everything
in general, but...
I've burnt out.
Into pure white ash.
This is my chance!
I can friggin' roll him now,
in one fell swoop and...
Hold it right there!
He's mine!
Y-You're the robot from earlier today!
As I recall, you showed up in Episode 3.
You're the caregiver robot, who
was defeated by Hayate. Eight!
Oh!
You! You recognize me...?
Tama, why are you the
only one who remembered?!
Hayate, unlike you, sitting on
your laurels as the protagonist,
I've watched the opening
sequence to death every week.
Why? Because it's the only place
where I show up on a regular basis!
And this Eight's in a similar situation.
He gets no screen time, but he
shows up in the opening sequence.
That's why I knew!
What? Was this robot in here?
We haven't seen the "very generous
people" next to him lately, either.
Now, I'm going to get my revenge!
The sound effects are quite thrilling.
Wh-What could this commotion be?
Let's leave it to Hayate.
He's been on a roll today!
Yay...
R-Revenge?!
It was all your fault for going on a rampage!
Shut up! Because I was defeated by you, I...
I lost everything!
Eight, you're going to become the
best caregiver robot in the world.
With my creator's expectations
riding solely on me,
I spent day and night undergoing experiments.
It was boring, but I did my best!
Why? Because...
Chief Developer
Shiori Makimura 22yrs (single)
Eight, are you doing okay?
Yes, because I had her.
Eight, you're amazing!
You're so cool!
Eight!
Beet!
That's from "Beet the Vandel Buster".
She was everything to me.
But on that day...
What?! Eight was defeated
by some scummy human?!
And he was defeated like that?
And my Caregiver Missiles didn't even work?
Ch-Chief...
Then we'll cancel the project.
Crushed!
The idea that we should have robots
do everything is wrong to begin with.
Besides, its design and functionality
are both super lame.
Ch-Chief!
Thus, I lost everything
and I ended up being disposed
of as nonburnable trash!
Spacey and forgetful, the Chief
completely forgot about me
and it seems she's been devoting herself
to developing a new caregiver robot...
But my... my pain will not be assuaged...
I want to recapture her smile
again and to do that...
Hayate, I have to beat you and that
stupid pigtail girl to a pulp!
Rarrr!
Wh-What?! You're just a pet, you bastard!
Shut up, Scrap Sandayuu!
The butler-in-debt's a scummy human,
who's pitiful and boneheaded,
and I don't care how much
you friggin' roll him.
But anyone who harms the Miss
will have to answer to me!
Sure, the Miss is spoiled,
willful, and domineering.
She acts on impulse and she
never admits to being wrong.
She's twice as stubborn as others,
ignorant of the world, and haughty,
and yet, her weakness is that she
can't sleep alone in a darkened room.
And while she insists that
she has athletic ability,
she actually doesn't, which all
makes her a worthless person...
But to me, she's the person I owe my life to.
What's wrong, Nagi?
Well, I don't really know,
but I feel like something was
said that really pisses me off...
So, anyone who turns against the Miss...
I'll crush them all!
Wait!
Hayate! Wh-Why you!
He was out to kill you and
you're going to protect him?!
I know how lonely and sad
it feels to be abandoned.
But...
But we had someone who
took us in and saved us...
That's why we're here now.
And that goes for you, too, Tama.
How I feel...
You understand how I feel?
I've experienced something similar, so...
I see.
If you understand how I feel,
Hayate, let me friggin' roll
you, right here and now!
The sound is growing louder again.
According to security's report,
that caregiver robot from
earlier has come for revenge
and it seems to be going on a huge rampage.
Um, are you sure we don't need to go help?
Like Hayate would lose against
someone he's fought before.
But it's Version 8.1 now and
it seems to have powered up.
8.1? That's just a patch.
Besides, Hayate is fighting for me, you know.
It sort of warms your heart, doesn't it?
I just hope he's not getting burned...
Awaken!
My new lethal mode that
came with the upgrade!
Mosquito Destroy Mode!
The Japanese summer is
filled with mosquitoes.
To ensure one's owner sleeps comfortably,
this functionality is a must.
Um, why don't we stop right here?
You won't be able to win
against us like that.
Sh-Shut up!
No matter what it takes, I
will once again get her to...
Eight!
Th-That voice... It can't be...
Ch-Chief!
Eight, thank goodness, you're here!
I... I remembered you!
S-So? What are you doing
here after all this time?
You already abandoned me...
I'm sorry.
But you're wrong about that.
There was a little mistake...
Chief?
I threw you out as nonburnable
trash without even thinking...
I really feel bad about that.
Chief!
I was wrong.
It doesn't matter now!
Eight, you're not nonburnable trash.
Damn, what a tearjerker!
Yeah.
You're oversized trash.
What?
Hello. We spoke on the phone?
Oh, please take care of it.
So this is it?
Yes, thank you.
Ch-Chief?
Have you heard of the Consumer
Electronics Recycling Law?
Apparently, you're not allowed to just
throw electronic appliances away.
But don't worry.
The workers will disassemble
you properly to dispose of you.
So there you have it. Bye now.
Aren't you glad it was the Miss who found us?
Yeah.
But this ends on a far too dismal note!
Oh, we have to save Eight somehow!
But what can we possibly do?
Leave it to me.
Hello? Is this Makimura?
It's me, Nagi Sanzenin.
Listen to me. You must not heartlessly
destroy that junky robot.
Good.
Just like her, right?
What?! I had no idea you
had such a special talent!
Hayate! Hayate!
Did you use stuff like Kamehameha
to defeat your opponent yesterday?!
No, I haven't quite gotten that far...
Incidentally, shortly after
leaving the residence, Eight...
Miss Makimura, please go out with me.
What? Sure.
And thus, it seems he's
moved on to a new phase.
Next time, in pursuit of the throne
of victory in the Fishlympics,
they will fight the guardian of the lake!
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Isumi's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Last time, Isumi wasn't able
to say anything about the song,
so this time, I'm here to back her up!
Thank you, Nagi.
So, Isumi, this song is, you know...
It's got your sort of dreamy feel,
and a laid-back, mellow feel,
plus this "boof" feel, so I think it's good.
Oh, dear
I am afraid that does not get
the message across at all...
Hm, well, you know, it's a nice song.
Thank you, Nagi.
Bye-bye!
Preview
This time, we're fishing!
We're going to fish up tons!
First, we'll do fly fishing!
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
Fly fishing? Aren't we starting
with something far too advanced?
Sanpei in "Fishing Lover Sanpei"
was catching tons with fly fishing.
If Sanpei could do it,
there's no way I can't!
Miss, it's not good to get
manga and reality mixed up!
I got one! I got one! I got one! Yaaah!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"I Wonder Who Came Up with the Sound
Effect 'Kapooon'. It's Awesome".
I never imagined that the
moment we were left alone,
I Wonder Who Came Up with the Sound
Effect 'Kapooon'. It's Awesome
that Hayate would sidle up to me...
The fun will be in the
red zone again next time!