"The Dollars?"
I don't really know much about them, either.
Anyway, there are a lot of them,
and I hear all of them have short tempers.
Being absent on your first day of school...
I said I don't know!
Anyway, don't go near Heiwajima Shizuo.
Orihara Izaya?
He's really dangerous, so definitely don't get involved with him.
Yeah, that's Simon.
He works to pull customers into that Russian sushi bar.
Khorosho, khorosho!
It's Russian sushi.
It's good.
It's cheap!
Hey, mister, don't run away.
Russian sushi!
Excuse me.
Do you speak Russian?
Yes, I do.
Thank God.
How do I get to this place?
Ah, just go straight down this street.
Are you tourists?
Yes.
This is an enchanting city.
I'm sure you'll have a great time here.
Thank you very much.
If you have time, be sure to visit this restaurant.
Ikebukuro: a lively borough that spans both east and west.
To the north, there's a large-scale entertainment district.
They say that in one day over one million people visit this massive area.
Ikeburuko...
This town is full of criminals.
Like him...
And her.
They come to this town looking for something,
seeking something, wanting to change something.
The class representatives have yet to be determined, so would anyone like to run?
A new town:
One where no one knows your past.
It's a chance for you to recreate yourself.
However...
Sonohara...Sonohara Anri, is it?
Anyone else?
Then the girls' representative is decided.
I'll leave the rest to you, Sonohara.
Uh...umm...
Are there any boys who want to be class representative?
I want to do it, but it might also be a pain...
Yet I'd feel bad if someone else did it...
You do it!
You serious?!
But I'd have to deal with her!
Yes.
Uh...umm...
I'm Ryugamine...Mikado.
Sonohara!
Um, about the meeting we have with the other classes, I've never done this sort of thing before, so...
Excuse me! I've some business to attend to!
I underestimated you.
I can't believe you'd proactively pursue a lovey-dovey rendezvous and try to hunt a girl down when,
in elementary school, you burst into tears when people
spread rumors about you and your childhood friend.
Yeah, yeah...
But you're still naïve.
Just because you came to Tokyo doesn't mean
your life will turn into a feel-good romantic comedy.
I-It's not like I...
On that note...let's go pick up some girls!
I'm in the now,
I'm the future,
And my time for popularity has come!
They'd never go for a high schooler.
People come to this town in search of change.
But change never comes easily.
Even if you try to change locations, you're still the old you.
What? No way.
I have a boyfriend anyway.
That doesn't matter! Just having some tea with a guy doesn't count as cheating.
Oh, hey, did you hear?
Yumi's new boyfriend is in The Dollars.
What?! Really?!
I wonder if she's scared at all.
How interesting! Let's talk about it over tea.
Aren't The Dollars like a biker gang or something?
No, they don't ride bikes or anything.
There are some people in this town who perpetuate violence.
They wear a specific color that signals what group they're in,
Otherwise known as "color gangs."
However, there's one gang that's been gaining prestige recently, yet has no identifying color.
But if you had to pick one, it'd be "clearly colorless."
That's The Dollars' color.
They communicate through their private website.
They say they're a special kind of group.
Oh yeah, there are rumors going around that
The Dollars are behind those recent slasher incidents, right?
Oh, really?
Like I said, we should talk about this more over some tea.
I know a great place.
The Dollars?
Yes, I know that gang.
What sort of people are in it?
The Dollars are amazing!
I heard they're getting involved with the Chinese mafia.
And the stabbing of that Yakuza guy was
also supposedly perpetrated by The Dollars.
Argh, this sucks.
They all ran away because you were wearing that depressing expression.
Kida!
How goes it?
Um, you're the kid with the manga-style name...
Mikado, right?
Wanna go to Toranoana with us?
Suji Yasuda's doing a signing there today!
Don't yell stuff like that out loud.
Huh? Why? What's wrong with talking about the artist Suji?
The Dollars?
Yeah, I know the name...
I heard the rumor from my friend today...
Hmmm.
I've never seen them, so do they really exist?
Are you saying it's an Internet prank?
I don't know about that, but...
If they really do exist, I wouldn't want to get anywhere near them.
The Dollars?
They fight with the Flame Haze that's sealed in the basement of Sunshine 60, right?
That's not it, Yuma-chi.
They're angels that fly around going, "Pi, piru piru" and show their panties.
Why're you asking about The Dollars?
I can't really say...
You get scared after hearing those stories?
I've heard a lot of rumors, too.
They're a rather dangerous lot.
Is...that so?
You shouldn't approach them just out of curiosity.
Don't be overly inquisitive.
You're so cool, Kadota!
You're totally like a mature main character who's just a bit cranky.
You'd be popular among girls who like middle-aged men.
No, no, no...
Shut up!
There are also areas in this town you shouldn't enter.
You won't get sick!
Try it once!
You won't die if you just try it once!
Man, I'm hungry.
Yeah.
Let's get something to eat before we go to the next—
It's the headless rider!
No way!
Huh?
I don't need any occult crap this early.
She's working pretty hard.
Some people get swallowed up by the city and disappear.
And others search for them.
I'll meet her. I'll definitely find her.
My love will bring her to me.
Is that Harima?
Harima!
I thought you were someone else! I'm sorry!
And this town is full of danger.
Hey.
Like here.
C'mon, let's get some tea.
And here.
He wanted to change.
You serious?!
He felt like something would change in this new town, that something would happen.
But...
The only thing waiting for him was a darkness hiding in the shadows of this bright city.
He froze with fear.
He feared he might not be able to live in this town.
I know how you feel!
Huh?
You're treated as a sexual pervert when you ride the train, people try to recruit you into cults wherever you go,
you go home and get into trouble with your neighbors, and to top it off, there's The Dollars and the headless rider!
That's the concrete jungle of Tokyo!
But!
Overcome it!
You pledged to become a fine Ikebukuroer,
so show us all and overcome this tribulation!
Mikado!
Ryugamine...Mikado!
Well, I'll be around, so there's no need to worry.
Kida...
And never forget to smile when you pick up girls. Smile.
But, I'm pretty sure it's impossible to pick up girls who're already part of the workforce.
What're you saying?
All we're trying to do is talk to them, so we're fine.
You're putting on airs even though Harima Mikawa's gone?
So you're a class representative?
She's getting bullied. And in a totally cliché way.
With that much makeup on, they can't be too imposing.
My boyfriend's, like, here with me today.
Kyoko's boyfriend's in The Dollars, you know.
Hiroshi!
Yo, yo! You talkin' to one ov da Dollahs here! Let's get it on! Yeah, man!
People like him will all do the same thing in this situation.
Man, this is so cliché it's actually interesting.
I know I should help her.
But, how...?
Stop it, you guys!
No way, I'd get killed.
Then...
Hey, Sonohara, what a coincidence!
Let's go!
He's so cool!
That's it!
That's the only way!
She getting bullied?
So, you plan on making them stop?
Also, this city plays host to countless unimaginable events.
Uh, umm...
Eh? Eh? Eh? What?
Eh?
Huh?!
J-Just wait a—
Da-da-da-da...da.
What?!
Er, umm...
Bullying people isn't cool.
Huh?!
Not at all.
What's it to you, geezer?
You're right, it doesn't matter to me
whether you get beat up or die in a ditch.
Even if I do punch you, you're still going to call
me a geezer despite the fact I'm twenty-three,
so our irrelevancy to each other extends to eternity.
Huh?!
Humans are quite spirited.
Well, my hobby isn't hurting young girls...
So I decided to make it...stepping on young girls' cell phones.
Wai—
Who is this guy?!
I'm through with this.
Stepping on girls' cell phones isn't my hobby anymore.
Hiroshi!
Yo, yo, yo!
Hey, man!
Violence?
Oooh, how scary!
Wh-Why you...!
Whoa, I give up!
Wait! Wait!
I won't forget this!
The interlopers take to the stage.
Yeah, you're a good kid, trying to save someone who's getting bullied.
Long time no see, Kida Masaomi.
Yeah...hi...
Those are Raira Academy uniforms, right?
Congratulations on getting in.
Thank you very much.
It's rare for you to be here in Ikebukuro, isn't it, Izaya?
This is the Orihara Izaya who we're not supposed to make an enemy of?!
Oh, he's just my friend.
I'm Orihara Izaya.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryugamine Mikado!
That sounds like the name of an air conditioner.
Uh, yeah...
So, why are you here in Ikebukuro?
I'm here to see someone.
I already met him, though.
No way! That's a convenience store trash can!
It just flew over here!
Why?!
This is bad...
I-za-ya...
A bartender?
Didn't I tell you never to come to Ikebukuro again, I-za-ya?!
Shizu-chan...
Don't you work over at the west entrance?
I got fired a long time ago.
And I told you to stop calling me that.
I have a name, and it's Heiwajima Shizuo!
Heiwajima Shizuo?
Another person we shouldn't make an enemy of!
Oh, Shizu-chan, are you still mad I pinned that crime on you?
No, I'm not.
I just want to punch the shit out of you.
I'm not good at dealing with you, since you don't listen to reason.
I'm in trouble now...
Just let me go.
There he is! That's him!
You did a great job of embarrassing me back there!
Don't you know what'll happen if you mess with The Dollars?
Huh?
Is he wearing bartender clothes?
No way! He wasn't here before!
He-Heiwajima...Shizuo?!
Who the hell are you?!
Some people lose the ability to think clearly in the face of fear.
You were aiming for my head just then, weren't you?
So you knew that I could die depending on where you hit me, right?
And since you knew that, trying to hit me there means you wanted to kill me, right?
Then, you won't complain no matter what I do to you!
People who possess overwhelming power tend to inspire instinctual fear.
To him, acting violent is like wearing clothes—no, he lives solely on violence—no, he's violence incarnate.
That man...
You idiots! Don't run away—
Alright, see you!
I...won't...let...you...run...away!
Wait! How...?
From above...?
He chose the wrong part of my joke to make
fun of, but I'll answer his question anyway.
I was making a delivery to a regular customer on the top floor of that building.
Simon, you...
Shizuo, fighting isn't good.
Shut up!
See how you like it!
Hey, Mikado, now's the time!
What? No way! Mikado!
Huh? Wai—Just a—
I can't breathe!
I-I'm sorry!
Sometimes, this city can send you a gift.
A very small, yet large miracle.
Like the possibility that the adventure he'd been looking for—a new story—was about to unfold...
And...
Um...
Thank you very much.
Eh?
Please excuse me.
Eh? Uhh...
And sometimes, nothing unfolds.
I found you.
My love...
They said it's The Dollars again.
I heard! They were fighting with a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo—
I heard The Dollars started a fight.
They started an impromptu fight with Heiwajima Shizuo?!
Apparently.
No, that's not it.
I just happened to see the fight, but
those guys are just Dollars impostors.
I'm not talking about that.
Recently, a bunch of people calling themselves
"The Dollars" have been mugging people on the streets.
Eh?
They're scary, they're terrible, those Dollars.
Be careful.
...Thanks.
They sure are scary...
Those Dollars.
Izaya came to Ikebukuro, so just when I figured
I'd snuff him out, Simon jumps in and interferes.
But, just why did he come here...?
This city is filled with foreigners.
They come here looking for something,
seeking something, wanting to change something.
Welcome, Welcome!
It's the same for me.
Sushi's good!
Eat sushi!
Please listen to my story.
To the story of me and her; a tale like no other.
I'd like you to listen to the whole thing.
Next Time: Living In Isolation.
You'll surely be kept on the edge of your seat and lose your sanity.