The clash between Angela-sama and Lilia-sama has finally arrived!
Who will be the one to take the control over this school?
Angela, I won't hand this school over to you!
Don't do this, Lilia!
Both of you, stop it now!
Don't try to stop me, Sharuru-sama!
Angela, this school doesn't need swords!
Love. Love is what it needs!
We're putting on a play based on this work for the cultural festival.
U-Umm...
That sounds awesome!
It's kinda filled with passion.
I'm going back home.
Please wait!
What should we do? If you align your wills with ours, we can revolutionize this school together!
I'll pass.
Hey, Amahara!
Don't worry. We'll make the underwear.
I knew you'd do it, Hayama-san.
You are a goddess descended upon us from the heavens!
Our victory is in sight!
Let us venture into the rainbow paradise!
Nayu seems pretty excited about this.
I've got to do my best.
This will be the last activity I'll get to do with everyone.
We look forward to work with you!
We need to make these six costumes, right?
For this one, you'll need a strapless bra and a corset.
You may also want to increase the petticoat to the volume of skirt.
For the bondage costume, you'll need a stick-on bra and satin underwear.
The bunny outfit is made of a thin satin material, so cover the nipples with stickers and wear a T-back.
I think bikini-style underwear will be good with this one.
But first of all...
Why are you tying me up?
She's just measuring your sizes.
Stop reacting to every single thing.
Let's see... Your bust is 84.
I-I'll be outside.
We'd also appreciate it if the members of the Underwear Society would appear in our performance.
What? You mean us?
Yes. We had plenty of members in the spring, but there's only three of us now.
So it's just the president and vice-presidents.
We won't give you much lines, don't worry about that!
Let see... Mizuni-sensei would be perfect for the rabbit!
M-Me?!
You'd be perfect!
There isn't anyone who could do it better than you!
R-Really?
There's no way I could do it!
In that case, I'll do it.
But I'm not sure whether you can wear this costume without breasts...
What?!
I don't mind doing it.
I'd like to do something to help Nayu-chan and the Underwear Society.
Haruka-chan...
Thank you very much!
Then this one will be Amahara-san.
I think Komachi-kun would be perfect for this.
Komachi-kun will be cross-dressing?
Yeah, that might look good on him.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Aren't you in the Kendo Club, Jinguji-san?
Please help us with our stage combat.
I can definitely do that.
Then let's do what we can to make this a great cultural festival!
What the hell? I'm going to be in it as well?
Don't worry. It's just a woman's role.
No one will notice that it's you.
That's not the problem here! I'm not doing it at any cost!
You won't?
Well, you see...
Then it's decided.
Wait a second!
See you later!
Sure!
Nayu-chan, don't push yourself too hard!
Okay.
Amahara-san...
You're late.
I never thought you'd come hang out with me.
I'm not here to hang out.
Is there something you want to talk about?
Maybe you've got something on your mind.
Even if I did, I'd never ask you for any advice!
Then why are you here?
Have you ever been to Kyoto?
Huh?! N-Not yet. Why?
No reason.
Besides, moving must be difficult.
Y-Yeah, you're right.
And changing schools...
Wai- What the hell are you doing?!
I-I'm sorry. Do you think it'll come out?
Geez... Don't surprise me like that.
Is that Polaris' new product? Do you think I could see it?
What?!
Please!
Just a little peek, okay?
It's cute while it's still so mature.
What about the bottoms? What are they like?
Seriously...
I'm home!
Wait, let me see a little more.
H-Hey!
Nayu...
Welcome.
Excuse me.
Amahara-san, thank you for coming.
Pushing yourself doesn't suits you.
Oh, that's right! Would you lend me the bra you wore for the overnighter?
I want to use it for the Acting Club's costumes!
Fine, fine.
Don't forget to bring the bra!
I get it already!
That girl was the daughter of Amahara-san from Polaris, right?
Yup, she is.
This fried chicken is delicious.
Nayu...
Are you really sure about Kyoto?
Of course. It'd be fun.
I'm sure I'll learn a lot from it.
I bet Japanese pattern underwear is fantastic as well.
Hayama-san!
We've got a favor to ask you.
What is it?
You know that our class is running a café for the cultural festival, right?
Do you think you could make some maid outfits for us?
I'm from the Underwear Society, not the Crafts Club.
The Crafts Club girls refused to make the maid outfits.
That's why we want you to make them.
The underwear you made for that magazine was great.
Hey, you don't have the time to do that.
We're already helping the Acting Club.
No, it's fine. I'll make them.
Nayu-chan!
Though, I won't be able to make that many.
Really? Thank you!
We'll leave the design up to you.
Nayu...
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah, it'll be fine.
I'm just glad that people have accepted the Underwear Society.
Class Rep, what are you doing out here?
They're all changing.
So you don't know about it either.
About what?
It's nothing.
Tell me, I'm getting curious!
Hayama-san is going to transfer.
Transfer? H-How come?
Because of her brother's work.
You can come in now, Komachi-kun.
Ah, Amahara-san! I'm glad you're here.
Your costume is done, too.
Why's there a costume for me, too?
They don't have enough members, so they asked us to be in the performance.
I haven't heard anything about that!
Please? Come on.
Wait!
Try it off for me first.
Everyone looked great in their costumes.
Yeah.
Hayama's transferring...
Do Shiraishi and Jinguji know about this?
You looked cute in your costume as well, Slanty-Eyes.
Komachi-kun, how did you feel wearing it?
You needed my bra to wear these?
Yes.
Komachi-kun?
Was the shock too much for you?
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Okay!
Hayama!
Umm... I'll walk you home.
It's raining.
Do you think it'll let up?
Is it true that you are transferring?
You're going with Keigo-san, right?
That's...
So it is true.
I...
Why didn't you tell everyone about it?
H-Hayama...
Please don't tell anyone yet.
I'll properly tell them myself once the cultural festival is over.
Alright.
Thanks.
One frankfurter, please.
One frankfurter!
Alright, alright.
W-Welcome.
Maids, huh?
Those clothes are cute.
Nayu-chan made them for us.
Hayama-san did a lot of work.
Indeed.
Mizuno-sensei!
Yes?
Take a look at this!
Did you know about this?
Get Hayama-san right away.
What in the world is this?
Calm down, Tsukamoto-sensei.
The school's name is in here. On top of that, you're calling yourselves the Underwear Society.
I've also heard that you're participating in the cultural festival without permission...
by helping the Acting Club with their costumes.
Yes...
The play is canceled.
No way! You don't need to go that far!
I can't allow a delinquent club to participate in school activities.
Excuse me.
What is it, Mizuno-sensei?
The members of the Acting Club and Underwear Society...
have both put a lot of effort into this cultural festival.
It'd be unfair to stop them at this point!
These girls have worked hard to create good costumes and underwear.
The cultural festival is a place for students to show off the fruits of their labors.
Please, reconsider your decision until you've seen what these girls have made.
Please!
Sensei...
I agree with Mizuno-sensei.
Me, too.
Sorry, we just got out of our class' shop.
What's wrong? You guys seem down.
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
Our angelic savior has been captured by a demon!
That's perfect. Looks like you're all here.
Did something happen?
The play might be canceled.
Amahara-san, I need to speak with you as well.
About my appearance in a magazine?
Then in that case, why don't you just punish me?
Amahara-san!
What a sight.
It's their fault for letting it get to their heads.
Hey, girls.
Tanihara-sensei!
You came!
I haven't seen you since graduation. How have you been?
What's wrong?
Actually, Hayama-san...
Hayama?
Tsukamoto-sensei, these are the costumes these girls made.
What's going on?
She said a delinquent club can't participate.
What?
But Mizuno-sensei asked her to hold her judgment until after she looked at the costumes.
The curves really are beautiful.
The lace has been layered skillfully. It's wonderfully spreading.
W-What do you think, Tsukamoto-sensei?
Excuse me.
Is Hayama in here?
Sensei...
This is my homeroom teacher from elementary school.
I'm terribly sorry one of my students has been causing so much trouble!
Hayama, you apologize as well!
I heard you're running an Underwear Society.
What are these perverted clothes?
I had high hopes from you since your grades were good.
I can't believe you're chasing after boys already!
Is this all you think about?
You're an embarrassment to our school!
Is underwear really something to be ashamed of?
Are you saying you don't wear underwear?
What?
The Underwear Society does nothing more than study underwear!
We'd never do anything immoral!
That's right! We've learned a lot of useful information about underwear!
I used to think that underwear was perverted as well...
but I learned the importance of wearing proper underwear for my developing body!
I'm talking to Hayama! You've got nothing to do with this!
You're right.
Underwear is something everyone wears. It isn't something to be ashamed of.
On that note, you're the one who has nothing to do with this.
Please get out of here!
Seriously, there's something wrong with this school's teachers!
Ah! Tanihara-sensei!
Thank you, Tsukamoto-sensei!
I still refuse to acknowledge the Underwear Society.
However, I'm willing to overlook the magazine incident this one time.
I'll also allow the play.
Yay!
Thank you, Tsukamoto-sensei.
Then these girls will be able to continue their work, right?
The school has no right to prevent students from studying underwear on their own.
That's great, Nayu-chan!
Yeah.
I'm am not done talking yet!
Amahara-san, make sure you get the school's permission before doing anything again! You girls, too!
Don't try to stop me, Sharuru-sama!
Angela, this school doesn't need swords!
Love. Love is what it needs!
Warriors from another school have invaded ours!
Keep fighting among yourselves!
This school will be ours!
I'm glad Jinguji took my spot.
Though she can't act well.
W-What is it?
I'm glad we got to put on the show.
I was worried what would happen for a while there.
Thanks, everyone. This cultural festival has been a lot of fun.
thank you too, Amahara-san.
It looks like we get to keep running the Underwear Society, too.
What are we going to do next year?
Next year...
Nayu-chan?
What's wrong?
Next... year...
Spit it out already!
What?
You have to tell them eventually!
Nayu-chan?
I'm sorry for keeping it a secret.
I...
Kyoto? Really?
Nayu hasn't told anyone, huh?
I don't think the Underwear Society knows, either.
It came up a few years ago, but I refused at the time.
Nayu found out about it afterwards and seemed to be bothered by it.
So... When will you be going?
Next month.
I'm transferring.
I'm sad about you leaving, too.
I'll always cherish the times we spent together.
I got tear stains on my favorite underwear.
You're talking about underwear at the very end?
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!