Look, isn't dropping out of school kinda reckless?
Can't we wait until graduation at least?
Those who hesitate long enough...
...Don't make it anywhere in life!
Even the venue manager told us so!
But... how are we even
supposed to tell our parents?
- How about taking a sabbatical?
- Oh! That could work!
That way we can still
go back to school after.
We don't need that!
Trust me.
We're gonna make it for sure.
The agency told us, right?
That we'll revolutionize the
girls band genre,
That we'll definitely hit it big in Tokyo,
And that they'll get us a major debut!
There's no way we'll
hit it off that well.
Agreed...
And when did they tell
us to drop out of school?
So why?
I mean, why not?
Always so confident...
If we leave an escape route,
we'll definitely be tempted to run away.
Having somewhere to run away to
will just distract us from moving forward.
I mean...
It's because it's a difficult path
that it has to be all or nothing!
Momoka...
Come here!
AIM FOR THE BUDOKAN!!
We'll make it to the Budokan together!
So... should we stop for a toilet break?
We're all ears, Momoka-san.
Shut up.
Then answer.
You little...
Stop provoking her!
I need a break...
Noted.
Start by apologizing.
8: IF YOU WERE TO CRY
Me?
She's right, you know.
Subaru-chan? Why are you siding with her?
I'm not siding with anyone.
It's just, shouldn't bring this up
during a concert of all places.
The stage is for our customers.
It's a sacred place!
It's not a place for you to vent
about your personal matters!
But that's exactly why I wanted to say it there!
So that you'd listen!
Sit down you two, we're in public.
I would've expected you of all
people would've stopped her, Subaru!
Me? I've already given up on stopping her.
This is just embarassing, I'm heading back.
I think you won't want to miss this.
You're the one who should be apologizing!
Me?
Yeah?
You just quit without consulting
any of us? You're gonna end it like that?
I don't wanna hear this from the one
who decided we'll go pro without asking!
Cut from the same cloth...
Actually, wasn't this your plan to begin with?
Real sorry.
Forget all that!
I'm pushing forward!
Keep getting fired up like a
dumbass if you want,
But you're gonna regret this.
Do you even realize how popular
Diamond Dust has gotten?
That's even more reason to
not give up without even trying.
That's even more reason to want to prove...
...That we weren't wrong!!
Stop being delusional.
You're the one who is trying
to look away from reality!
Shut up already!
What do you even know about me?
Then tell me!! Why did you
continue with this band to begin with?
If you really thought you weren't up to it anymore,
Then why didn't you go back home on that day?!
Why start a band again?!
Look, all things aside, don't drop out of school.
I refuse.
Whatever floats your boat then.
Are you running away?
Please, don't run awa--
Shut your mouth.
Please don't worry!
It's all acting for a TV show!
Things are heating up!
Idiots.
Punch me if you want. I'm used to it.
Probably better that way.
At least that will give me a
reason to hate you now.
And you'll be no different from them.
Want some water?
So it ends once again...
Oh, it's just starting!
Finally done...
I'll call you tomorrow.
Ah, finally free of that horrid atmosphere.
Hey!
What?
Where did you get that guitar?
I got it when we were leaving.
That an issue?
You.. got it?
Mine-san gifted her a spare guitar.
She said she couldn't help it
with how "real and genuine" her voice felt.
She wanted to encourage her
because she's just like you, she said.
Thanks.
I'll let them know you'll be returning the van then.
OK, no worries.
Ah, sorry, I'll be stopping here too.
I can drive you home.
Bit of a pain with all the traffic, right?
Trains are still running, so...
And don't forget the meds
for your motion sickness, Tomo-chan!
Don't call me chan...
- See you later, then.
- Drive safely!
Are trains still running at this hour?
Nope!
Just thought I'd lend you an ear.
I'm feeling considerate today!
Gotta say, I've always liked
the chill vibe of this place.
Should move to a place like this.
Wanna come once a room frees up?
Eh? I'd have to think twice before
deciding to be your roommate...
Oh, come on.
Did Rupa and the others know
that Nina was gonna say that?
No way.
But I guess we should've seen it coming,
with how gung-ho she's been lately.
You're the only one who didn't notice.
Why didn't you stop her?
It's a free world.
You of all people should know
how reckless she's being.
Even as an indie band,
we haven't released anything yet.
We've got accepted into
the festival, at least.
Rupa-san has also received an offer from a label.
Huh?
I'm not lying this time.
I mean, you're a former Diamond Dust member.
Tomo-chan and Rupa-san too,
They've already got a rep online as a mystery duo.
And just recently,
A certain vocalist tweeted
about really liking Nina's voice,
It got quite a bit of traction.
Really...?
We've already got this many followers.
27,851 FOLLOWERS
And in a survey for who the customers
are coming for in the next show...
...We ranked number one!
I see...
Despite what you said, Nina isn't delusional.
Now, it's not like we can compete
with DD or anything,
But we're at least making a big step in the right direction.
...What did the other two say?
They were always planning to go pro, so...
And you?
I'll tag along~
Everyone grows up eventually
We're just waiting for you.
So you were all in on it, huh.
Not really.
It's just... that it's like Nina puts it.
If we're serious about this,
it's gotta be all or nothing!
It's because it's a difficult path
that it has to be all or nothing!
Gonna need one of these...
And, uuuh...
One of these.
...Should be enough for now.
A minor.
F.
Sol.
Come on, anyone could do this.
Okay, so...
FREEDOM, FREEDOM,
From todAy i've become fREEEE!!
TodAy and tomOrrOw
I'll doO the things i lIKEEE!
Chaka-chang!
Dear father,
Thank you for raising me until now.
I'll be working hard on my own now.
You don't need to send me any more money.
BUMPKINBANK
I'll send you back the bank card too.
Regards, Nina.
To: Iseri Muneo
Welcome one, welcome all!
What are you, a sushi place?
Ouch... is that not good?
Just say "hello" like a normal person.
How many times have you been here?
I'm not the type to pay attention to details...
Especially as a customer.
Yum.
Eat that and you're fired.
Will I...?
Of course!
I swear, why did you have to
come work here of all places?
It's my first time working, so I thought it'd
be better to be with someone I know...
Hurry up, goddamit!
We've been waiting forever!
I'm so sorry.
What country did she crawl from?
She's sure got a mouth for a foreigner.
Hey--
I apologize for the delay.
Tch, you better.
Thank you for your patronage.
Rupa-san...
This is a daily occurrence.
Just like you, I need rock to vent.
I'll go check the soup stock.
So, how are things with Momoka?
Nothing's really changed.
Even if we tried to talk,
we'd probably end up fighting again.
I'll repeat myself, but if this fallout
continues, we're leaving too.
I get it.
Hey, welcooooo... ome?
One medium.
Hello!
One medium!
Would you like a beer?
Nina.
Would you like to order?
Do you have time after this?
No, I...
...I do!
Girls Band Cry.
See, she didn't mean any harm or wanted to bully you.
You two just got into an argument, and her hand slipped.
You understand ...right?
What a relief.
Now, I want the both of you to write an apology,
So let's make up with a good handshake!
Iseri-san...?
Where are you taking me?
We're close, we'll be there in a sec.
I see.
Something wrong?
Not really,
It's just that seeing you driving now...
I don't think I hate it that much anymore.
Sheesh...
They could at least send a message
to let us know how it's going...
Have faith.
The opposite of love is indifference after all.
For two people to still try to talk things out
even after all that arguing...
That's proof of love.
Or proof of idiocy...
Is this it?
Just open the door and you'll see.
What can I even rely on, is there anything like that?
People always tell me to just do it by the book.
But its words are so complex I dunno where to look
My today hasn't changed in all these years
Diamond Dust...
This is what all or nothing means.
Not having the luxury to sing what you really want.
In order to make a living,
You need to ask yourself: What sells?
What does everyone like? What's trendy?
Pushing through a never-ending cycle.
...But that isn't true for everybody.
The artists who are able to
create what they really want...
...Are but a handful.
I USED TO BE YOUR FAN, BUT NOT ANYMORE
Even the other original members of DD...
Without Momoka it's dogshit now
It's so over for them lmao
Fucking hate the vocalist
Whatever
At least she's hot
Is it me or does DD kinda suck ass now?
The DD I loved is dead
Qutting as a fan from today
You've let me down for the last time
They need a reality check
...Didn't wanna go down this path.
But this is what they chose. To make a living. To keep living.
But that's not a guarantee
that your music wouldn't sell, right?
Before it even got the chance, you gave up on it,
And quit the band before even trying.
But the reality is that they
succeeded by doing the opposite.
This is what DD was meant to be.
At first, all of us kept saying:
"Screw all those idol wannabes playing it safe!"
"We're gonna make it with our music!"
But it fell on deaf ears.
FOR: MOMOKA OF DIAMOND DUST
The reality is
Even if you've got the talent,
if you can't sell, you can't sell.
What we used to scoff at became
the only songs that would blow up.
That's the world of entertainment.
The pressure of reality began to weigh on us,
So we had no choice.
If we rejected it, we wouldn't have been able to push forward.
They chose to continue.
And that's not a right I can deny them.
But I didn't want you to have
to make the same choice.
You asked why I didn't go back home
and formed a new band, right?
When I saw you singing back then...
...I saw my younger self in you.
You didn't care about what sold or being validated,
You just sang what you loved.
That's the Nina I loved the most,
because it reminded me...
...Of who I used to be.
That's why I wanted you to keep singing as yourself.
Not chained by anything,
I just wanted to hear you sing.
Thank you very much!
We are Diamond Dust!
Make some noise for the next band too, okay?
And what about my feelings?
Nina...
And what about MY feelings?!!
Nina!
Let me go!!
I'm not part of your backstory!
So don't you dare chain me to your memories!
So let's make up with a good handshake!
Is it even possible to fill this void?
Iseri-san...?
Maybe someday.
If it were up to you, would you keep going?
Iseri-san!
Nina, wait!!
This void feeling,
This eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés...
Even if your fingers tremble...
...your songs still gave me the strength to live!!
What you really should be protecting
Isn't the you from your memories,
But your desire to reach others with your music!
Wanting to convey your feelings, your joy,
Your anger, your sorrow...
That's the real reason why you stared a band, right?!
That's why you started singing at school, right?!
Why you came to Tokyo!!
Because you wanted to connect, right?
What are you scared of?
What are you chickening out for?
I'm living proof!!
That there's someone who has been saved by you!!
I can't stand you,
but you gave me the courage to fly!!
Someone who was so overjoyed
to just sing alongside you,
Someone who's been willing
to bet everything on you,
Someone who always
believed in you... and your music!!
Momoka-san...
Please don't run away because of me...
Momoka...?
It really is her...
It is!
Nina, let's go!
Quick!
Hina...
- Hey!
- ...Coming!
I'm leaving. Get home by train.
Momoka!
Momoka-san!
Momoka-san, wait! Momoka-san!
Dumbass.
Are you insane?
Now we're even.
Why are you running away?
When there's no need for you to run away...
When you've done nothing wrong!!
Shut up!!
Momoka!
You don't need to
speak to us, just listen!
We heard you started a new band!
Show us what you got!
We have no regrets!
We're shooting for the top!
And we'll prove to you we weren't wrong!
We'll keep making a living until we do, so...!!
We don't intend to lose either!
We'll make you admit that this...
is what we're meant to be!
We'll prove to you that we weren't wrong!
Huh...?
So whimsical...
What gives you the right to act so mighty
After that dogshit of a
performance you put on?!!
Momoka...
You wanna be idols?
If you've got no regrets, then play the part of the cute girl better, goddamit!!
You're pros, right?
We'll be squaring off at the next festival.
And after your snooze of a performance,
We'll steal every last one of your customers!!
What's that even mean?
A declaration of war!
Momoka!!
We'll never forget, so...
Get on, Nina.
You know her?
Yeah...
Not at all.
Fuck.
Fuck!!
What's so funny?
Momoka-san...
What now?
I think I've finally realized...
I love you.
What are you on about?
Isn't it obvious?
It's a confession.
Even if my fingers tremble...
There's no right answers, there's no giving in.
My whole life, I've just been me. That's all there is to it.
No matter how much I fight from here on, tomorrow isn't set in stone.
How did it go?
What's up, Rupa?
Told you so!
Ah, good grief.
I knew it... those girls are a riot!
NEXT: THE CRESCENT MOON RISES