Irisviel!
Are you okay?
Someone waited for Kiritsugu to leave
so they could mount a direct assault.
Given the thunder and the
brazenness of the attack,
our assailant is Rider.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Greetings, Saber!
Rider?
I came to see the castle
you were occupying, but...
You picked a really gloomy one.
Hmm?
And battle armor?
Why such an unrefined outfit?
Are you foregoing your
modern-day fashions tonight?
Rider, what are you doing here?
Can't you tell?
I came to share a drink with you.
Now stop standing around slack-jawed
and show me the way!
Do you have a courtyard
more suited to a banquet?
This old castle's far too dusty!
They say the Grail will be claimed
by the one most worthy of possessing it.
And the war here in Fuyuki is a
ritual to determine that person.
But I say that bloodshed is
unnecessary to measure worthiness.
If we Heroic Spirits can all mutually
agree on who ranks highest,
the issue will resolve itself.
Oh?
So you wish to prove yourself
against me first, Rider?
Exactly.
You, as a fellow king, will
not ignore my challenge.
Of course, this is less of a Holy Grail
War and more a Holy Grail Discussion.
Which of us is the vessel
most worthy of the Grail?
The answer lies at the
bottom of this barrel.
That's enough comedy for one night,
mongrels.
Archer, why are you here?
Oh, right.  I saw him wandering about
town and invited him to join us.
You're late, Shiny!
Though I shouldn't be surprised, since
you travel by foot, unlike myself.
Surely you don't mean to hold a feast
of kings in this depressing courtyard?
How do you intend to make amends
for dragging me out here?
Let's not be impolite.
Here, have a drink.
What is this swill?
You honestly believe this is sufficient
to measure a Heroic Spirit's quality?
Seriously?
I found this among the best for
sale at the local marketplace.
You can only say that due to
your ignorance of true wine,
you mongrel.
Oh!
Behold, and be amazed.
This is the drink of a king.
Excellent, excellent!
Fantastic!
Be it wine or swords,
only the best is held in my treasury.
I believe this alone should settle
the matter of who is the true king.
Archer.
Your wine is exquisite and certainly
deserves the finest of cups.
Unfortunately, the Holy Grail
is no mere wine goblet.
Our discussion on the Grail
cannot progress further
until we learn your reason for seeking it.
You do not command me, mongrel.
First, given that we each
strive for the Grail already,
our reasons are meaningless.
But that is beside the point.
The Grail is mine, to begin with.
Without exception, every treasure in this
world can be traced to my collection.
So have you held the Grail?
Would you know it by its appearance?
No.
My criteria for possession are entirely
different from you mongrels.
The vastness of my storehouse
overtook my personal knowledge
of its inventory long ago.
But that a treasure exists
is enough to show that it is mine.
For another to claim it...
They would be the most foolhardy of thieves.
Your words make as much sense as Caster's.
Apparently, he is not the only
Servant suffering from delusions.
Come now.  I'm not so sure.
I think I have an idea as to Shiny's true name.
But, Archer,
then you have no particular
desire for the Grail to grant.
Of course not.
But I must punish those
who would raid my coffers.
It is a logical reason.
Tell me, Archer.
What are the justice and the reasoning behind that?
The law.
The law I enacted as king.
If you break it, I shall punish you.
Discussion has no place.
If that's the case...
There's nothing for us but combat.
King of Conquerors.
You accept that another may lay
rightful claim to the Grail,
yet you would take it for yourself by force?
For what reason
do you seek its power?
T-To be reincarnated.
What?
Hey!  Don't you want to conquer the world—
Idiot.
No matter how powerful the magic
that has brought us to this era,
we are still Servants.
I wish to live a real life in this world,
as a human.
And with my own two hands, I shall
stand against Heaven and Earth!
That is the essence of conquest!
So it begins, persists,
and finally ends.
This is my path of conquest.
That is not how a king should act.
Oh?
Then tell us the desires of your own heart.
I wish to bring salvation to my homeland.
With that omnipotent, wish-granting artifact,
I shall change Britain's fate of destruction.
King of Knights,
you claim that you would change fate?
Meaning that you would alter history itself?
Yes.
Even this is a wish a miracle
cannot bring to pass,
if the Grail's power is truly
limitless, then surely...
Ah, Saber...
You are saying that
you'd erase history shaped by you yourself?
Yes!  Why do you question
me?  And why do you laugh?!
The homeland to which I gave my life,
which gave me my sword, was obliterated.
Why should it be strange that I mourn it?
Can you believe this, Rider?
The little girl who calls
herself King of Knights
said she gave her life to her country...
What right have you to mock me?
A king should be prepared to sacrifice
if it ensures her kingdom's prosperity!
You're wrong.
A king offers no sacrifices.
His country and his subjects
offer themselves for him.
Not the other way around.
What?
That is the reign of tyrant!
Yes.
We are tyrants, and thus are we heroes.
You, Saber...
If a king regrets
his reign or its ending,
he is simply a fool.
A worse ruler than a tyrant.
Iskandar, after your reign ended,
your heirs were murdered,
and your empire split into three parts.
Have you no regrets over how things ended?
None.
If that came to pass by
my subjects' sacrifices
and my decree...
The collapse was inevitable.
I shall mourn the loss.  I shall shed tears.
But I shall never regret.
You...
And never shall I wish to undo it!
To foolishly meddle with the result would be
an insult to every person who lived in my time!
Only a warrior sees honor in destruction!
What good is a king who ignores
the plight of the weak?
A just rule, under just laws!
That is a king's desire!
So,
as a king, you are slave to this justice?
That is acceptable.
A king will sacrifice herself
for her beliefs.
Then you cannot even live your own life.
To rule a country is to
give up living for oneself.
King of Conquerors.
You, who seek the Grail out of
pure selfishness, can never understand.
You are only a man who rose to
power to satisfy his endless greed!
A king without greed is not even fit
to decorate the throne!
Saber!
You said a king will sacrifice
himself for his beliefs.
In life, you were surely a
saintly and immaculate person.
One of noble bearing, beyond reproach.
But who can admire the martyr's thorny path?
Who dreams of such a life?
A king...
A king must lust more, laugh louder,
and rage longer than any other.
Every aspect, good and evil,
must be beyond the extremes
of any normal person.
The king must be thus, to inspire
envy and admiration in his followers.
He must light a flame
in each of their hearts,
so that they long to be like
their king, as well!
King of chivalry...
Perhaps your justice and ideals
once saved your kingdom,
and delivered its people.
But...
What became of those subjects you saved?
Surely you recall.
What?
You saved your people,
but you never led them.
You never showed them how a king should act.
They lost their path,
and you left them to it.
You were content to walk alone and composed,
preferring your own pretty little dreams.
You are not a genuine king.
You are someone trapped by an ideal
of a king who exists for others, not himself.
Just a naïve little girl.
I...
Assassin!
Is this your doing, Shiny?
Tokiomi lowers himself.
This is insane!  Why are
there so many Assassins?!
We are the one, who has become many.
We are the many, who are one Servant.
We are that one Servant's
shadows.
A Heroic Spirit with multiple
personalities, each embodied?
R-Rider, hey...
Easy there, boy.  You need not panic.
The generosity a king shows
to his banquet guests
is another measure of his quality as a ruler.
You would welcome these to your
table, King of Conquerors?
Of course.
The king's speech is for all to hear.
Friend or foe, if they have come
to listen, I shall offer a seat.
Come now!
If you wish to speak with us,
sit and drink from this cup.
This wine is as your blood!
Very well.
As I said, this wine is as your blood.
If you insist that it be spilled,
then so be it.
Saber and Archer!
Here is our banquet's final question.
Must the king stand in solitude?
For the king, there is
no other way!
Incorrect.
You have understood nothing.
I will have to show you now
what a true king is.
What the...
A Reality Marble?
This can't be happening.
He summoned a vision from his
mind into the real world?
We stand upon the same sands that
my armies once marched across.
This landscape, where we
shared joy and sorrow,
is burned into the minds of
all those countless heroes.
This world lives again,
because it still exists within our hearts!
Behold my endless armies!
Their bodies returned to dust,
and their souls returned to
the world as Heroic Spirits.
They are legendary warriors,
who still pledge loyalty to me!
My bond with them is my greatest treasure,
the path of my rule!
The ultimate Noble Phantasm of Iskandar.
Ionioi Hetairoi!
Each of those soldiers is a Servant!
Good to see you again, partner.
A king
must live such an illustrious life
that it embodies his peoples' ideals!
Hail!  Hail!  Hail!
It is commanding the envy of all these heroes,
and leading them forward that makes me a king!
Therefore,
a king does not stand in solitude!
His will
equals that of each of his followers!
Hail!  Hail!  Hail!
So, then...
Prepared to face me, Assassin?
As you can see, this land is a desert plain.
Unfortunately for you, this battlefield
gives our numbers a distinct advantage.
Crush them!
That was less interesting than I'd hoped.
Now that we have each said our piece,
I think that's enough for the night.
Wait, Rider.  I still...
No, be silent.
Tonight was a banquet of kings.
But you, Saber...
No longer do I acknowledge you as one.
Little girl, wake from your sad dream.
If you cannot,
you'll lose the last sliver of pride
you still claim as a Heroic Spirit.
The king's dream you spoke of is a curse.
What?
Pay him no heed, Saber.
You are correct.
Follow your chosen path.
Watching someone carry that
heavy burden of kingship,
struggling with the pain and anguish...
It is superb to behold.
Stand your ground, little King of Knights.
Depending on your actions,
you may prove worthy of
still more of my affection.
Saber...
I remember.
There was once a knight who left Camelot,
saying King Arthur could never
understand others' feelings.
Maybe
those feelings were shared by all
who once sat at the Round Table.
Episode 11
Discussing the Grail
The second act is about to begin.
I'm not an ordinary human.
It is not as simple as that!
Seek out your desire.
Your path is now clear.
That is an evil which must be vanquished!
Next time
The Grail Beckons