Bro...
I won.
I... won.
Now, hurry up!
Drop that weapon!
Your...
stomach is bleeding!
It's for your own good.
Drop your weapon and surrender!
No.
If he surrenders...
Wait, don't shoot!
Let me explain what's going on.
Hurry, throw away your weapon!
Wait for me...
Mario...
Shoot him!
Fire!
Hey, guys.
What will you do once you get out?
It wouldn't be bad for all of us to live in that house, would it?
Well, what do you think, guys?
Mario, will you keep boxing?
You'll need to fix your right hand then.
Sign: National Police Shibuya Police Station
Turtle, you'll survive no matter where you go.
But... don't cross the police too often.
Soldier...
Your mind's set on being in the SDF.
I know it'll be tough, but don't give up.
Sign: Shonan Special Disciplinary School
Cabbage...
You're too kind.
So don't let yourself get tricked easily.
Uncovered...
You're a smart guy.
You'll definitely be rich when you're older.
Joe...
It's my deepest wish that you meet your sister again.
Setsuko...
I'm glad...
that I met you all.
Numerous bullets were fired, piercing Sakuragi's body.
As his consciousness faded,
his only thoughts were of his friends.
We're... free.
Welcome home!
Thanks, Setsuko.
Then I drove a left hook into that G.I.
I wish you could've seen it, Setsuko.
Minakami...
But that guy was tough.
He still stood up.
Did something...
happen to Sakuragi?
So I finished-
Hey, tell me what happened!
Minakami...
Bro...
is dead.
What the hell are you doing, Bro?
Setsuko's... in tears.
Didn't we all promise?
We were all supposed to get out together.
Yet...
you've left us... all alone.
You can't do that, Bro.
Let's hope that by summer, two years from now...
we'll be out on the streets.
"On the other side of the tree that carries everyone's dream, a rainbow arches across the sky."
"Happiness dwells on the other side of the rainbow bridge."
"It takes courage to cross that slippery path,
which wants to throw us back to the beginning."
"Bro taught us that."
Bro...
we were really...
really fortunate to have met you.
June 6, 1957
June 6, 1957.
The promised day.
Yo.
You guys all got out safely.
Turtle.
What's up with your hair?
I like it.
Shut up.
Uncovered, what do you think?
Doesn't the air in the city smell great?
Mario.
Cabbage, you got more meat here.
Mario!
Tell us... about Bro.
We heard Sasaki was there.
And that he was already badly injured before the MPs shot him!
They killed him, didn't they, Mario?
I don't know the exact details.
He... died.
He won't come back, no matter what we do now.
The last thing he said...
was that we should all work hard to reach our goals.
So...
I'm going to walk my own path.
You guys should do the same.
See ya.
I'm glad I met all of you.
Be well.
Wait, Mario.
We know just what the hell you're thinking!
Were you planning to kill Ishihara and Sasaki by yourself?
What do you think we're here for?
Don't shoulder everything on your own.
Let's do it together.
Uncovered, come up with a good plan.
Leave it to me.
All right.
Now that that's settled, let's get some drinks to put us in the mood.
Yeah.
I'm starving.
Bro...
These guys are all idiots.
They're... the greatest idiots I know.
The boys' six hearts were as one.
Unless they settled their business with Sasaki and Ishihara,
they couldn't go anywhere on the streets.
Their long summer was about to begin.
Two months later...
Soldier was training in the SDF.
Joe was working as a helper in a band.
Don't take too long, Joe.
Yeah, sorry.
Cabbage worked day jobs to earn a living.
Turtle got cigarettes every day from the American base and sold them on the black market.
Mario began working as a bartender-in-training.
Each worked individually to earn his own living.
Then...
What?
That bastard.
A mayoral election?
He's the leading candidate?
Bullshit!
That pervert is running for mayor?
Tomorrow...
Sasaki is speaking in public.
That's where the battle will begin.
That's what I was waiting for.
We'll split into two groups.
One will go to Sasaki's speech.
Two groups?
What about the other group?
That one will go to Numazu in Shizuoka.
Ishihara's there.
Ishihara?
So that's where he was hiding.
Let's send them both to hell.
Yeah!
Wait.
Ishihara...
Let me settle with him myself.
All right, Mario.
You're gonna put an end to this.
Sign: Marui Tertiary Hospital
Secchan, you have a visitor.
Okay.
Mario.
Hey.
Are the others doing well?
Yeah.
They're all getting by.
Really?
That's good.
Here.
What's this?
I don't really know how much I owe you,
but it's rent for back then.
But I don't need it.
No.
I need to give it to you now.
I might not be able to later.
I'm going to see Ishihara.
Wait.
What are you going for?
Are you going for revenge?
Are you going to kill him because he killed?
Stop this meaningless nonsense and think about the future!
That's not it, Setsuko.
As matters stand, we can't move on.
We can't forget about Ishihara and Sasaki.
We're just... dealing with it, as men.
I'm sorry, Mario.
But I don't think...
Sakuragi would have wanted you to do this.
Mario...
See this?
This bullet was found in Sakuragi's body.
I want you to have it.
Please, Sakuragi...
Protect him for me.
What happened?
We could've been killed!
I-I'm sorry.
There are people on the road.
Hi, Dr. Sasaki!
Long time no see!
You're in the car, right, Dr. Sasaki?
Doctor!
What do you guys want?
Move out of the way.
It's a reunion of old friends.
Why don't you show yourself, Doctor?
Hey!
What do you want?
Doctor, we heard the news.
You're a candidate in the mayoral election, right?
Y-Yeah.
S-So...
How are you all connected to him?
We owe him for when we were in the Shonan Special Disciplinary School.
Thanks to him, we managed to reflect on our behavior.
Do your best in the election.
We're all... rooting for you.
S-Sure.
Uncovered, you sure that was good enough?
Yeah, more than good enough.
Well, just watch.
This is only the tip of the iceberg.
I was waiting.
You came... to kill me, right?
Yeah.
I did.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I've waited too long.
Kill me, Sakuragi.
Sakuragi?
Sasaki, you're a lying bastard.
Sakuragi's still alive.
He thinks I'm...
Sakuragi.
I want you to kill me.
Just as I tried to kill you.
I knew it.
You killed him.
Kill me, Sakuragi.
Or did you forget?
I sure didn't.
That feeling when I drove
the blade into your stomach.
It felt great.
I know.
You can beat me to death.
A slow death wouldn't be too bad.
Okay, Sakuragi?
Why?
Why did Bro have to die for an addict like you?!
For...
For garbage like you...
Ishihara!
I'm just... dealing with it, as a man.
I can't move on if I let him live.
Setsuko...
I can't forgive him for killing Bro.
I just can't!
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Bro is dead.
He has gone beyond the end of the rainbow.
His teachings remain in the hearts of the six boys.