What's in it?
Things that are important to Master?
Is this a love letter?!
Where are you three from?
Um, we apologize, but we're in a hurry...
You've got some nerve!
Hm? I don't remember packing a box like this.
Did someone give you that as a moving gift?
A Strarf-model Shinki?
Didn't a Strarf model win last year's tournament?
What?
Dad, you signed me up for a consumer review Shinki?
Why?
A surprise?
No, I'm not saying you jumped the gun...
Geez, what's our Master's dad thinking?
He's already got us three here.
And he gets another brand new Shinki?
I wouldn't mind if things were a bit livelier around here.
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
The Secret Ingredient Smells Like Gunpowder!
Now, about your name...
Hi... na.
Registration complete.
My name is Hina.
It is a pleasure to meet you, Master.
Welcome, Hina.
Hina?
Yeah.
She just activated, so she's still like a baby.
You three should introduce her to the place.
Here you go.
My name is Ann. Let's be friends!
My name is Lene.
And this is Ines.
She's configured to be my little sister!
Don't call me configured!
Nice to meet you.
What kinda greeting is that?
I wish to see your strength.
We don't do that around here.
Looks like I'm gonna have to lay down some ground rules.
Got it?
First, Rule #1!
You may not go to sleep before Master does!
What did you change it to?
An old Japanese-style room!
Rule #2!
You may not wake up after Master does!
It feels warm, doesn't it?
Rule #3!
I think I have a better idea.
Be clean at all times!
It doesn't matter if you're not made for cleaning.
And Rule #4!
Fine, then.
This may calm you down.
Wait, why are we underground?
I mean, are you even listening?
How about we try the middle button?
What kinda middle is this?
So uh, yeah.
I'll tell you all about Master.
When he was younger, he lived in this very house,
and I was right there with him!
That's enough, Miss Childhood Friend.
He used to live overseas due to his father's occupation,
but he moved back to Japan to enter high school.
And since we just finished unpacking his luggage today,
our wonderful life with Master can...
Hm? Um, are you listening?
Hello!
I'd heard that the Eukrante that's always by the school got her butt kicked recently,
but I never thought the paw-petrators would be right next door!
I know!
We should give Master a gift to congratulate him entering high school!
Ooh, good idea.
But what should we give him?
Hina, what do you think?
Do not call me by that name.
Why? Master went through all the trouble of making it for you.
The only one allowed to use it is Master!
I-In that case, what should we call you?
Strarf will do.
Well then, Strarf,
what do you think Master would like?
A tournament championship.
Or perhaps the strongest weaponry available.
I don't think he'd like those too much.
Why?
Our Master's not into battling.
Wh-What was that for?
Something is here.
Is there a mouse?
Do I look like a mouse to you?
She's pretty brash for a newcomer.
You're supposed to give your new neighbors soba when you move, not rain death upon them!
What's all the noise for?
Nothing at all! It was probably just a mouse.
Hehe, yeah!
And Hina—
I mean, Strarf here got a little trigger happy.
Master.
Master, do you truly have no interest in Shinki Battling?
Ah...
well, battles are dangerous.
Ah, that means supper's ready!
I'll help you!
Geez Master, didn't you have frozen pizza last night?
Is this everyone?
Strarf said she would be going to sleep early.
I'm pretty sleepy too...
What're we gonna talk about this late at night?
The high school entrance gift!
I thought of a good surprise for Master!
We'll all make him a feast!
A feast?
Y-You can't mean...
we'll be cooking?!
Cooking?! But that's...
"Another Shinki Cooking Accident!"
"This one slipped on oil and fell into the pot!"
"She was deep-fried!"
"Following the incident..."
"Ms. S, who once took a bad trip through a blender, said..."
"'Having Shinkis cook food... is a recipe for disaster!'"
M-Maybe this isn't such a good idea...
But think!
If Master comes home to a splendid home-cooked meal instead of a TV dinner,
just imagine how happy he'd be!
Master would be...
happy?!
All right!
We're doin' this thing!
If we all work together, neither the devil nor food preparation can stand in our way!
With that done, let's pick out our menu!
We're totally doing Japanese cuisine!
Sashimi, tempura, sukiyaki, geisha...
Exactly!
Well then, let's order our ingredients!
Keep it within next week's food budget!
Yeah, yeah. Okay, we need some shrimp, octopus, tuna...
Added to the cart!
I want to make a cake, too!
How about omelette rice?
Were we not created to fight?
The time is ripe!
Now, our battle begins!
Hm?
Where's Strarf?
She said she couldn't help with anything but battling, so she passed.
Time's short, so let's get started!
So, we'll start with...
Oh, wait just a moment!
We'll start with this!
Huh? Apron Armor?
If you wear this over your figure,
young boys will be overjoyed!
So, a PVC apron?
Well then...
Wait, wait!
There's still one more thing to do!
What else is there?
Master's gonna get home before we even get started!
This is the one thing we can't skip!
Antibacterial spray is an essential part of preparation!
Onward! To cooking!
I'll wash the rice!
That'll take days!
Shrimp beard!
Don't play with your food!
Got it!
Ah! That's my armor!
We're making great time!
This isn't so dangerous after all.
It's a bit too salty.
Here I go!
What are those three doing?
I dunno, but we should get in their way!
As revenge for yesterday's cat-tack.
Time to pounce, Mini Meowchines!
Shoot, it's getting dark.
Pick it up, guys!
Once we're done... with this...
We'll heat the pumpkin in the microwave...
so we can get a knife in... and cut it more easily...
Victory is sweet!
Yay!
All right, on with the plan!
Oh boy...
We have to clean this up, quick!
Y-Yeah.
I brought a vacuum cleaner!
Get to the breaker!
Where is it?
I'll take care of it!
Lene!
What... is this?
What?
Ines!
What the...
Mission complete!
Consider it your punishment for not bringing soba!
Strarf?
Stand down.
You saved us...
Come back, Mini Meowchines!
I'll test my strength on you. Come!
Shut up!
Shutupshutupshutupshutupshutup!
And eat... your veggies!
Got it!
Such obstacles are hardly worth my time.
Here comes the main course!
Would you like a side with that?
Slice it here!
Wow, it's still mov—
Now I'm berry mad!
Wow.
We're out of ammo!
So it's come down to this...
Catreat!
I'll remeowmber this!
Thank you, Strarf!
Think nothing of it.
We were all built for combat, after all.
Hey! Get moving, Master'll be here any minute!
Oh no!
Strarf, help us!
W-Wait...
Hurry, hurry!
What time is it?
Why must I be forced to...
This'll finish the omelette rice!
For what reason?
And the finishing touches...
I'm home!
And we're... done!
Master, Congratulations on
entering High School!
Welcome home, Master!
Master, Congratulations on
entering High School!
Today, we all worked together and made you a feast!
Master, Congratulations on
entering High School!
I cooked it with love!
"Enjoy"?
Enjoy the meal
Oh, that's what you meant.
Hm? Ah!
What the heck are you doing?
Now I smell all fishy...
Strarf played a big part, too!
I did not truly...
Those octopus balls look delicious!
Hina, can I have one?
Thanks, Hina.
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Master, I'm glad we made you happy!
The PVC apron thing didn't work too great, though.
I hear that if you equip White Sock Armor onto your figure too,
young boys will love it even more!
Where do you hear these things?
Lenient... far too lenient.
We'll have an action-packed episode, all for Strarf!
Master's gonna get mistaken for a Shinki thief! Talk about bad!
And we'll find the real criminal and clear Master's name!
Next time
"Clash! Battle Trike!"
Next time on Busou Shinki: