“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
It's a matter of great importance to me.
Before long, I'm going to forget what my own face looks like!
No! Ah!
Yagiri Drug Manufacturing, huh?
Is this really it?
The place where they're doing human experiments?
It's not Harima Mika.
You can use as much money as you like.
Who we are right now is eternal.
I love you,
Certy.
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Brain's Base
Production
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
People are fake.
The world is filled with them.
People say "I love you" or "I'm fond of you,"
but they're only binding themselves to others.
"Look at me. Be with me."
They only demand things, and consume.
My love is different.
It is more encompassing and perfect.
Yeah. I got it, Nee-san.
Thanks for transferring the money. I'll talk to you later.
Shall I go buy you a drink?
Look, there's a vending machine right over there.
Wait a second.
You're such a cute girl.
Dependent Love
You still haven't found them?
Please accept my apology.
What the hell was the surveillance team doing?
According to the one who was on duty last night,
he was staying at the same hotel as they were,
but apparently Seji switched locations in the middle of the night.
I was still in contact with him via cell phone around seven.
If something's happened to him...
He has promised us that he wouldn't leave Ikebukuro,
so I'm sure he'll turn up.
Really?
And what do you think will happen to us if the police catch so much as a glimpse of them?
Well...
That's it.
I can't wait on you people any longer.
Supervisor...
I'll be back soon.
They were nothing more than dolls to me.
Pretty and expensive imported dolls that my uncle kept buying me.
Since I was little, I never liked dolls.
I think my uncle gave them to me, not to make me happy,
but rather because he liked them.
Hey, Seji. Look at this!
Isn't it pretty?
Now, I wonder what this one is.
Yeah, what is it?
Our house was as still as death, and Seji and I were always alone.
Since before my brother was born, I had often been left in my uncle's care,
and he let me come into his study as much as I liked.
That's where it was.
My uncle told me it had been smuggled into the country;
he would stare at it as if entranced, and would sometimes even talk to it.
It was beautiful.
More beautiful than any of the dolls my uncle had ever given me.
I didn't feel that it was mysterious or cruel,
instead I thought that this head alone was a living creature unto itself.
Still, that's all it was to me.
Therefore, when I secretly let my brother into the study that day,
it was merely to play like we always did.
Perhaps I just wanted to share my secret with him.
Isn't it pretty?
That was how it all began.
The thing that I regretted ever since...
This is the first time we've met, isn't it?
Did that list of illegal immigrants come in handy, Yagiri Namie-san?
I'm honored to have the supervisor of Yagiri Drug Manufacturing's 6th institute
come specifically to a run-down place like this.
Please, put it down wherever you like.
It's an emergency. Find out where my brother is.
I'll pay you as much as you want.
I haven't been able to contact him since last night.
He should be somewhere in Ikebukuro.
It hasn't been that long. Why are you so worried?
He's with a girl. A girl with a scar around her neck.
A girl? He is around that age, isn't he...
Get started, right now!
Wait a minute!
Aren't there more important things you should be investigating right now?
There's a rumor that your company might be ripe for a hostile takeover by that big foreign corporation, "Nebula", isn't there?
If that happens, your position will be–
Orihara Izaya-san. I don't have time to chat with you.
That's surprising.
I wouldn't have thought a prestigious woman like you would be in love with her brother.
What do you know about me?
The Yagiri Namie I know is a fine woman.
Your family runs a business, but after your father made a blunder and had to resign from his position,
your uncle took over as the new company president, and started acting all cool.
Therefore, you joined the company and through sheer hard work,
you made it to where you are now despite your young age.
Also beautiful, I might add.
You do know quite a bit, don't you?
You should have no trouble finding my brother.
Your brother... It's best not to interfere with people's affairs too much.
I'm not interfering! I'm the only one who protects that boy!
A stalker is the only one who never realizes what he is.
You think you're just protecting him.
Don't confuse me with the likes of a stalker!
How scary! I'm just kidding.
All right, I'll help you. However, we're doing it my way.
Police and informants are different, after all.
What are the rules for that?
I do have one question.
Would you say you're jealous of the girl with the scar around her neck?
Why?
There's no reason for me to envy that girl.
The true, red-rusted envy that burns within me is...
Nee-san... there's a girl I like.
I noticed Seji acting stranger than usual.
He would randomly say that he wanted to go into our uncle's study,
then sneak in and stare at it obsessively.
What Seji loved was not a person.
It had no heart, and it didn't even have a body.
I wanted to remove it from his gaze,
and so I joined the company, later asking my uncle if we could bring it to the company building as a research subject.
That's when it began. We came into contact with "Nebula",
and despite my eagerness to make sure none of our research leaked out,
my security card was stolen.
The card only I had.
Nee-san... I...
I think I may have killed someone.
What should I do?
What I felt in my heart that moment was neither fear, nor anger but boundless joy.
It was me who Seji needed most then.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
Let Nee-san take care of everything. Okay?
It's not that woman, but her.
So you have been going out with her, after all.
It's okay. Leave her to me too.
Everything will be fine.
At the time, I didn't know that a stupid stalker-girl named Harima Mika had been following Seji around.
And then we found Seji's room in such a state...
I will protect you, no matter what it takes.
Yes, yes. Looks like there's no reason to panic.
The police have them, and I wouldn't be surprised if you got a phone call within the next minute or so.
Hey. It's the police, but don't worry, it's fine. It's nothing big.
...Probably.
Quit joking!
Yes?
Yes, it is.
What? What's wrong?
We're leaving? But we haven't...
Wait!
I'm glad you love me that much.
I love you too. Forever and always.
I'm scared.
Of what?
Please, take me away from here!
I want to be alone with you too.
But where...
What's that?
A lover's quarrel?
No! Stop! No!
Hey, calm down. We're not shady people.
No! No! Stop!
Listen to me.
You...
Let go of her!
I'll be fine. I'm not hurt. Go on.
I'm not sure why, but you gotta follow her, don't you?
I've always wanted to say this:
"Leave this to me. You go on ahead!"
Wait!
Look out!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
You're...
Stop!
No, you stop!
Let me go! I said let me go!
Is that kid your girlfriend?
That's right! We're meant for each other!
Why is she like that?
How should I know?!
What did you say?!
Don't you think it's just a little bit irresponsible of you
not to know anything about the person you love?
You don't have to know anything about someone to love them!
Then why... why do you think you're meant for each other?
Because I love her! There's no other answer than that!
Love isn't something you can put into words!
That's why I...
The black bike!
...will show you through my actions! I'm going to protect her, and that's all there is to it!
I've always liked you more than Izaya.
Which is why I'm letting you off with only this!
If I take this out, it'll start bleeding.
I'll have to buy a bandage for it first.
No, or should I use super glue?
So to sum it up:
Your head is attached to a body.
You caught it, but then a high school student helped it get away,
so you chased after it, but then another student showed up and ran away with your head.
And you want me to believe all that nonsense?
I'm not saying you have to believe it.
I believe you. However, why was Shizuo-kun there?
Oh, I totally forgot. I was in the park waiting for further orders on a job for Izaya.
Then Shizuo came along and we talked a bit.
I was told afterward that the job went to Dotachin, so it was all right.
Orihara-kun...
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you, Shinra.
You do seem pretty confused. I'm here to talk with you as much as you like.
Why does my head have another body in the first place?!
Well, I have no idea what I'm talking about since I haven't actually seen it,
but if you'll allow me to speculate a bit...
For example...
Maybe it found a girl with the right physique and replaced her head.
That's disgusting.
Maybe there was a freshly made corpse.
Cut it out!
Still, that... that's...
There's no way what I did was wrong.
Rebuilding that girl for Seji after the incident...
I have to go.
It's okay. Everything's fine.
She...
It must've been scary. But there's nothing wrong with what you did.
My love did not falter when she ran from here and joined Seji, either.
My love was a stepping stone for Seji's, and Seji knew it.
I knew that he knew it. It was all so twisted, and yet...
Damn it. That was a Raira Academy uniform.
Who was it?
I understand. Leave it to me.
Anyway, we have to find that kid from Raira.
Then I have to meet with my head and talk to it.
To the head that saw you and did nothing but scream?
What do you propose we do with this head, which seems to be attached to a living person?
Are you saying we should separate it from its body just for you?
Certy.
I don't want to accept it.
The fact that my head and memories are gone.
Or that what I've done over the past twenty years has been a waste.
It hasn't been a waste.
We're going to get her back for sure.
You wait right here.
Hey, your cell phone...
did you drop it?
I don't know.
It wasn't in my bag, even though I know I put it there.
She can't go on without me.
We have to be together.
Yeah. You're right.
Okay. Let Nee-san take care of everything.
How impudent.
That doll should have stayed quiet and obedient, like a doll should.
Without imposing on my love.
I've made up my mind. I don't want to have any more regrets. Never again.
Got it? I want you to relay that message to your subordinates.
I don't care if she's dead or alive.
If you have to, eliminate her on sight!
I see. Everybody's busy.
How exciting. How exciting! How exciting!
This town is still overflowing with things even an informant like myself does not know, always being born, and then vanishing!
This is why I can't get myself to leave cities filled with humans!
People-love! I love humans! I love them!
That's why...
humans ought to love me back.
Thank you.
Have you settled down at all? Can you answer some questions?
You said you don't remember anything, right?
So in other words, you suffer from amnesia?
Let me say this again.
You should go to the police, or the hospital, or...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay, it's okay. Don't apologize.
I have to go.
Before that person gets in the way.
Forever and always,
I have to go.
Seji,
Seji-san,
I love you.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Next time on
Durarara!!
The First and Last
The headless rider, Orihara Izaya,
and the girl with the scar on her neck showed up again.
To top it all off, the guy in the class next door is a member of the Dollars!
Next time: The First and Last.
I always dreamed of an out-of-the-ordinary life. However...