There is one thing that no one in this world has ever seen.
This is all a downright lie.
This kind of...
What's this...mold spots?!
I just removed all the mold not too long ago!
It is something very kind and sweet.
Where’s the rag...rag...
Probably, anyone who had a chance to see it would want it.
And that is the reason why the world has hidden it,
in order to make sure no one could easily get their hands on it.
Crap, I can't get it off...
But, if I use this...
But someday, someone will find it.
One person will be able to get their hands on it.
That's how it has been arranged.
Eco, eco, eco,
ecology...
Inko-chan.
Are you still asleep?  It's morning.
I caught you!
Ryu-chan, you're so cold.
I told you last night that I’m starting school today.
Oh yeah, it's the opening ceremony.
Congratulations on your promotion from last year.
Is that the attitude you should take towards your son as he goes into a new grade?
Hey, this room is dark...open the curtains.
They're open.
Really?  Oh.
That really is a huge luxury apartment building.
I wonder what sort of people live there.
After that was built, our blessing of the sun was snatched away,
and that caused the laundry to stop drying properly,
and everyday things like mold, mold, mold...
That sinister glare!  Ryu-chan, you look more and more like your father every day!
Don't compare me to someone like th-
Aaaaah!
You look so hot!  Even more and more like your dad!
What?  You're leaving already?!
What about my breakfast?
It's in the same place as always.
That...
Only that...
I never wanted to hear that.
Because of these eyes that you praise so much, I...  I...
Hey!  Wait up!
Huh?
T-T-T-T-Takasu-kun!
What do you think you're doing?!
What...?
I didn't mean to!
What...why?
Please spare us with these!
Huh?
It's all we have right now!
Seriously!
See, we aren't wasting your time, right?
Well no...
We're very sorry!
I am...
Again?!  You really do find a lot of wallets, don't you.
Sure...
Hey, it'd be great if we're in the same class again.
I know!
Found it!
Yay, we're in the same class again!
Crap, I did it ag-
Hey.
I see we're in the same class again this year, Takasu.
Kitamura...
This concludes another fruitful opening ceremony.
Each person must go to class, and prepare for homeroom.
Another new class...
I'll have to start over again by clearing my name of everyone's preconceptions.
It will be alright.
I know that won't be necessary for everyone, even if it's only a few people.
Sure, thanks.
That's true, there are those like him who do understand me.
And, also in this class...
Hey, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year!
Oh, you're in class C too, Kushieda?
You're Takasu-kun, right?
Do you remember me?
I'm around Kitamura-kun from time to time...
It's Ku-Kushieda Minori, right?
Oh wow, you remembered my full name.
I think that makes me happy!
Well then, let's go enjoy class with great cheer and eloquence!
Yeah.
S-Sure.
And so that...
What’s wrong, Takasu?
Oh, uh, nothing...
I'm j-just gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay, then I'll go on ahead.
What's this...such a small body, like a doll, but something...
...extremely hateful.
As if you did anything wrong, you would be taken down and devoured.
Um...this is...
Whoa, it's real!  Delinquent Takasu and Palm-sized Tiger are...
Idiot!
Palm...sized...tiger..?
Oh I get it, Palm-sized...Tig-
And the name fits perfectly.
Okay, that's all for today.
Those of you that haven't turned in your surveys yet,
please remember to come by the staff room later.
A-Alright, Takasu-kun?
Yes.
Are you okay, Taiga?
You were late to arrive this morning, too.
It was because I went to the doctor, he said something about house dust...
Oh, a modern day illness.  That must be hard.
That Palm-sized Tiger is friends with Kushieda Minori.
Now I'm the one with the problems here...
Are you doing alright?
Oh, I guess.
Well you know...
That was amazing wasn't it, Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun?
Palm-sized Tiger is still as strong as always.
And Takasu only looks scary, but he really isn't a delinquent.
Really?
It looks like the misconceptions will be disappearing quickly.
Taiga, what's up?
Oh, nothing really...
T-Takasu-kun, maybe you're unsure of what you want to do in the future?
Huh?
B-B-But I need you to turn in your survey.
All the other students besides you have turned theirs in.
I'm sorry, I totally fo-
I'm sorry!  I'm sorry!
You don't want to hear from someone who's still wandering around
not knowing what they'll do with their own life, right?!
I'm out of line...
Gosh, I'm late.
Time Zero is going en-
A-Are you okay?
My bag, bag...
I-I think I'll just leave her alone for now...
Hey!
You, w-w-what are you doing?!
What do you mean?
I just came to get my bag...
Your bag...your bag's the one in the next seat!
Did I mix up the...r-r-rows?!
Le-Le-Le-Le-Le...
LET GO!!
Why my bag?!
Hey, can you just...
Damn...
What are you?!
A-Aisaka?
Hey!
Idiot!
She's messed up...
This is messed up...
You see, Dad is in Heaven.
He was such a handsome man!
And he always kept a magazine under his shirt, so he was always prepared to be stabbed.
Ah, it makes me tingly!
Just because he resembles you...!
It only makes trouble for me.
If I didn't have a face like this, nobody would be scared of me,
and I would have never had to become involved with Palm-sized Tiger,
and I would have been able to have more self confidence,
and then...
Oh that’s right, the survey.
Hm, what’s this?
To Kitamura Yusaku-sama.
From Aisaka Taiga.
I see how it is...
You put this in my bag by mistake, right?
I haven't looked inside so I can't imagine what could be in it...
But I’ll just return it to you.
Crap!  I need to stick it back on...
Does she happen to be a big klutz?
I'm going to sleep.
That's weird, it's not time for Yasuko to come home yet...
Yeah, yeah!  Mirano-chan!
Alright, I'm going to drink more and more!
Hello?
The window is...
Ow!
What is this?!
I...know this size from somewhere...
Aisaka!
Use a tissue!
What was...
W-w-what are you...?
Forget it.
What do you mean, "forget it"?
Oh, you mean that letter?!
Now that someone knows about that letter, I can no longer live with myself.
I have no choice but to die!
Then stop trying to kill me!
I don't want to die, so I have no choice but to kill you!
Otherwise, you can just lose your memory!
That's impossible!
It's alright.  If I hit you hard enough with this I may not be able to take your life,
but I can probably send your memories flying.
Don't do that!
Okay, listen!
That letter...
Shut up.
Shut up, shut up!
You saw it.  You read it, didn't you?!
So I’m trying to say...
I refuse to listen.
So forget everything about that l-l-love letter!
It was empty!
Emp...ty?
Yeah, so I don't know what was inside.
You know, you're lucky you didn't give it to Kitamura.
You got away without the embarrassment of such a failure.
H-Hey...
Gosh, how hungry are you...?
I got tired of food from the convenience store.
Convenience store?
Why, don't your parents cook fo-
Everyone has their own family situations.
Here.
If you had just quietly handed over that bag,
then none of this would have been necessary.
How are you going to compensate for this?!
You still have some on your face.
Bear.
It seems like you were born to add a garlicky scent to the oil of the fried rice...
You know what?
What part of a single love letter is embarrassing?
Listen, that's nothing embarrassing at all!
Wait here a moment.
Look!
What is all of this?
Do you know what that is?  I'll bet you don't.
That's a list of songs I created on the theme of, "If I were to hold a concert for a girl I liked."
Those are poems I wrote for her,
and MiniDiscs to play if I were on a drive with her.
Although I totally don't have a license yet.
I have plans laid out for every possible scenario.
How about it, disgusting isn't it?
Lacking the courage to confess my love to her, all I can do is imagine like this.
It's definitely shameful, but I still don’t think it's embarrassing!
You should be proud, you know.
You didn't just imagine, you tried to take action.
Think positively, with great cheerfulness and eloquence!
"Presented to Kushieda Minori."
That's right, like Kushieda Minori!
Hey!
You like Minori?!
Tsk, how impertinent.
Hey, learn your place.
Hush!
You shouldn't be talking!
What's with you?!  You said forget about it!
S-Shut up.  L-Love wart.
I'm sorry, Inko-chan.  We woke you up, didn't we.
What's this disgusting thing you're showing me?
How dare you insult a part of my precious family!
I-Iiin...
Oh, that’s good, Inko-chan!
Introduce yourself to the guest!
Today's the day you'll finally be able to say your name.
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-n-n-n-po!
'Inpo' is the Japanese abbreviation for 'impotent'.
No, you see, today Inko-chan wasn't in the mood.
Gosh, it's already this late!
Anyway, about this...we are like two peas in a pod.
I won't say anything to anyone.  Trust me!
No.
Why?  I mean I fed you and everything, just go home already!
Actually, I beg of you to go home!
My sick mother will be back soon.
No, I don't want to!
Plus, I can't trust you.
Besides...
What about love letters...they're out of style, aren't they...?
I can't have you being all wishy-washy now!
I'll listen to all your emotional problems,
but it's late today, so how about tomorrow, okay?
Really?
You're going to help me?
I will.
I will, I will, I will, I'll do anything, I will.
Anything at all?
Will you listen to me like a dog?
Do anything to any extreme, for me?
I will, I promise.
So let's call it quits, alright?
Okay?
I wonder how she got through the window.
Well...
Oh, I'll escort you.
It's alright.
It's close, and I have a sword.
That's the dangerous part...
Hey, about that hole...
Oh, that.  I’ll just cover it with paper or something and hide it.
Here.
Use it if you want.
If it costs money, I'll pay you back later.
See ya, Ryuuji.
Yeah...sure.
Did she just call me by my first name...?
Hello, this is the Takasu Resid-
Hurry up and get over here, you're-
Yes...?
You hung up on me, didn't you.
Hurry up and go where?
What?
The veranda...why?
Why?
You said you would do anything for me, like a dog.
Wait, yesterday's thing was about helping you with the Kitamura situat-
If you don't come, do you know what will happen?
I can show you what will happen now, if you want.
Uh, no...but you see....
Just wait ten more minutes.
The seasoned rice will be cooked in ten minutes.
Three?
Ah, no...
Do you want to eat some too?
Wow...
Excuse me...
Huh?
It's open...
What is this...smell?!
Aisaka-san...I'm coming in.
What is this unbelievable smell?!
Aisaka!
Let me...
...please let me...
...clean your kitchen!
What's this,
a second round of sleep?
She looks almost artificial.
The sleeping Aisaka really looks like a doll,
and this lifeless apartment looks like part of a doll house.
But it's too big to be a doll house.
I have fifteen minutes, more or less.
Okay.
What is this?
Hey, I'm still working on it, but it's gotten a lot cleaner, hasn't it?
It was horrendous.
The water collected in the sink was foul
and the pipe was full of slime, mold, and rotten kitchen wastes!
It was hellish.
The room was full of dust, too.
Trespassing, and forced cleaning...
You didn't go around leaving your marking, did you?  You dog.
D-Dog?!
Oh wait, that would be rude to the other dogs.
Even if all guys are similar dogs, you are a mongrel.
A mongrel.
What an ungrateful woman, when someone took the time to...
Where is your "itadakimasu"?
To the Rice God and the manufacturers, I am grateful to receive this meal!
You...
Hey, your nose stopped running.
That’s probably because the room is clean...
W-What did you just say?
Shut up!
Unsettled agreements.
New misunderstandings.
Genetic power.
Taiga, you're...
...admirably klutzy.
Shut up.  Go rot!