There's only one little day left of this long break.
How are you all spending it?
I'm so bored I could die.
All thanks to this completely useless dog.
It's not my fault you couldn't see Kitamura.
He said he's busy with club and student council stuff during the break, didn't he?
It's the dog's job to do something about that, isn't it?
You couldn’t have a decent conversation even if you did see him.
I'll send you to hell!
It got on me!
What are you doing?
Hurry, get something to wipe it with.
It's because you said something stupid!
It's so noisy.
She woke up.
Try to wipe it with this.
You two were trying to eat omelet rice while Yacchan was sleeping!
I wrapped yours and put it in the fridge!
Did you put my name on it?
In ketchup, "Yasuko"?
I will, I will, so don't cry!
Okay, I got it. I'm going to sleep some more.
What am I going to do? It's going to stain.
It'll come out if you clean it right.
I'll clean it for you, so in exchange...
Johnny's again?
It's alright! Please!
I can't go by myself!
You should help me out with Kushieda too!
Shut up, I'm going to skin you!
W-What?
Kushieda's... Off today.
Even a working girl has to take a day off every now and then.
It's your fault for trying to be happy all by yourself.
Unlike you, who confessed and was confessed to, I still haven't done...
Eyes! My Eyes!
Don't say stuff like that, you horny dog.
What are you doing?!
This is cute!
Let's see...
For you to wear that, your height is too...
What I want is the bag, the bag!
O-Okay...
Welcome!
So I'm little and have short legs.
But it's not like I've bothered anyone because of it...
Wha-
Ryuji! This!
The bag, right?
Not that, the model!
Model?
Look, that person!
It's this person, right?
It really is!
Her name's Kawashima Ami.
She's the daughter of the actress Kawashima Anna.
Why is a girl like that in a place like this?
Sorry for making you wait, Ami.
Ki-Ki-Kitamu...
Hey, it's Takasu and Aisaka!
What a coincidence!
W-Why?
Hey, hey, they're coming here!
What do you want me to do?
What's with you two?
You guys really are close.
T-That's not it!
What's up, Yuusaku?
Well, I was just thinking of introducing you.
Yuusaku?
This is Kawashima Ami.
She used to live in my neighborhood.
I guess you'd call her a childhood friend.
And this is Takasu Ryuji and Aisaka Taiga.
Childhood friends.
Nice to meet you.
Me too!
Is that...
Ah, yeah, we were just looking at this.
And then...
Oh no!
I'm embarrassed I'm dressed like this.
I should've done my clothes and makeup better.
When I don't have work, I tend to let everything go.
No, um... Not at all!
Why don't we all sit together?
That's okay, right, Ami?
Of course!
This place brings back memories!
We used to come here a lot.
Yeah, yeah, with our families.
Here, Takasu-kun, please.
Would diet sugar have been better?
Um, no...
Or do you prefer it black?
Hey, hey, that was careless.
I'm sorry!
Yuusaku used sugar, so I just automatically...
I-It's okay...
I did it again!
People are always telling me, "Ami, you're really clumsy and silly."
I'm sorry!
No, not at all! I like sweet things.
Thank you! You're really kind!
Oh no! What was I doing?
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I'm going to the toilet.
Me too... The toilet.
I give up. I don't know what to do.
Just like I expected, you left.
Weren't you going to the toilet?
W-What?
I want you to answer me honestly.
Takasu, what do you think of Ami?
How could I think?
Bringing a cute girl like that all of a sudden, I was so nervous I started babbling.
I'll give you that she's cute.
And she's a really nice girl.
She's kind of silly, but kind of pure?
Well, just watch them for a bit.
I'm bored.
Hey, Ami-chan's ice tea is all gone. Go get more.
You're ignoring me?
Anyways, you've had an awful attitude for a while now.
I got it! I'll get your boyfriend to get it for me.
He seems like he'd listen to anything Ami-chan says.
Is it okay if Ami-chan steals him?
I don't need him at all though!
He's not my boyfriend.
Yeah?
Whatever.
Frankly...
Those are Ami's true colors.
Selfish, childish, and high-handed.
A stereotypical princess-type.
It's like she's been possessed by a devil.
In this boring town, this is about all you can expect from a boy.
Hey, hey, how tall are you?
I just noticed it, but aren't your proportions strange?
I can't believe they sell clothes in your size!
Even so, I can't believe Taiga can be okay with all of that...
There was a mosquito. A mosquito.
Wait, it was a fly.
You!
Hey, Ami, we're going home.
Yuusaku!
I got it, I got it.
Sorry, Aisaka.
We'll leave now.
Another bowl!
There isn't any left!
You already ate two and a half bowls of rice!
It's all her fault!
That evil girl... Just thinking about it makes me hungry!
You mean it makes you angry.
But he was worried, that Kitamura...
What should I do?
Does Kitamura-kun hate me now because of that?
I'm sure he doesn't.
Kitamura knows the whole story...
I hate that girl!
Don't cry...
And you! Getting all giddy over that girl!
I-I didn't...
Besides, no decent person would call themselves, "a silly girl"!
Whatever. It's not like I'm ever going to see her again.
This is where I act like an adult and swallow my hate.
Hey, that's mine!
Shut up!
I will be attending this school starting today.
I am Kawashima Ami.
Please call me Ami!
You're...
The girl modeling for Can Vi?
She's so cute!
An angel has come down from heaven.
Thank you, God.
Everyone, please get along with your new classmate.
Um, first we have to decide on your seat.
Here!
I want her next to me!
We won big time!
I'm so glad I'm in this class!
I'm so embarrassed, I'm afraid I stick out too much.
Why? It looks good on you, so it's okay!
Yeah, and you have a great figure.
Really? But I really want the same jersey as everyone else!
Ami-chan really is cute, and she's got a great figure...
But my cuteness detector, Minori Radar, isn't picking up anything.
Minorin?
Are you okay, Ami-chan?
Why do I fall when there's nothing here?
It's so uncool!
Ami-chan, you're pretty clumsy!
You're a silly girl.
That's not it at all!
But... Sometimes people say that.
"Ami, you're silly."
I knew it.
But really, I'm not like that!
I got it, I got it.
I'm telling the truth.
That's amazing.
She's really got it covered from every angle.
Why didn't you tell me she was transferring here?
If I had said something, Ami wouldn't have shown her true colors, right? That's no good.
What's with that?
To tell you the truth, I don't dislike Ami's real self.
I want everyone to know her true self.
And to like that Ami.
But that's...
If they don't like her after that, then even Ami would be satisfied.
I don't want her to have to lie anymore.
Me first!
I didn't know there was a vending machine here.
Why?
Because you left even though fourth period's about to start.
I was curious, so I followed you.
No good, no good. This girl's true colors are...
Except lunch time, it's against the rules to buy a drink.
Then...
We're accomplices.
I'll pay.
It's okay.
That's to apologize for yesterday.
Apologize?
I was surprised that you were in the same school.
Aisaka-san too.
Yuusaku didn't tell me anything.
Hey, did Aisaka-san say anything about yesterday?
Yesterday?
Yesterday, everything was my fault.
Because I'm a little silly, I think that really annoyed Aisaka-san.
We were just talking...
But all of a sudden Aisaka-san called me cheeky, and told me I was full of it.
Then...
But, it isn't Aisaka-san's fault.
If I were more together, that would never have happened.
Sometimes girls just hate me, so I don't mind.
I'll keep trying hard.
I get it now.
That's why I don't want you to tell other people about yesterday.
I...
I get what you're trying to say.
So let's go back.
Thank you!
Let's hurry!
"The sun was high when they, with no fanfare in their preparations, departed."
The parts about the sun being high here explain how the sun is rising up by saying that it is climbing upwards.
It is simply pointing out that the sun is flourishing.
Why?
Takasu-kun, Minori is very angry!
You and the girl who transferred are somehow suspicious!
Are you cheating? Is it cheating!?
If you throw Taiga aside...
You'll be punished!
Shit.
Why do I have to be treated like this?
From Takasu, to Kushieda.
Sorry to change subjects, but what do you think about people who call themselves silly?
Does anyone have any questions so far?
What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, Takasu.
Haruta said he'd introduce the three of us to the girls on the track team.
Of course, you're going, right?
I'd just scare them if I went.
That's not true!
You're just there to even up the numbers.
And...
Tenori Taiga!
That's how it is.
What did you do to accomplish this?
I didn't do it on purpose! I fell and it got like that!
I'll go get a rag. You can go home.
That's okay, I'll wait for you in the classroom.
Ryu-
Ick.
Why are you here?
You're an eyesore.
Don't come here, you damn brat.
Scary!
No wonder even the teachers are afraid of you, Aisaka-san.
When I went to the teacher's room, all the teachers were saying how cute Ami-chan was.
They were worried that Ami-chan would be bullied by you.
They really don't like you.
I'm really going to enjoy seeing how long that two-faced personality of yours can last.
I could expose your real personality easily.
But that's just too boring, don't you think?
I'll keep watching you.
Even if our classes change, even when we graduate... Just like a stalker.
You're really an annoying shorty.
That's why you don't have any friends.
Wait, there was one!
Takasu Ryuji.
He's got a face like a Yankee, and he's totally into me.
Gross! But then you're all alone now?
I really feel sorry for you.
Even that philanthropic Yuusaku hates you.
What'd you say?
I told him what you did to me at the restaurant.
I think he probably hates you now.
You're really finished now!
Kawashima?
Hey, move it.
Ryu-chan made fried pork cutlets!
Even though it tastes best when it's just made.
If you're worried...
Go and get her.
It got blurry.
Taiga! I'm coming in!
What?
You are here... With your lights off.
Hey, Tai-
What did you come here for?
What do you mean, what?
It's dinner time!
T-Taiga!
Are you okay?
Kitamura-kun...
Hates me... She said...
That girl said she told him everything.
I... I...
It's okay.
What's okay?
Kitamura knows everything.
About Kawashima's real personality, why that happened at the restaurant, her lies, everything.
Really?
Really.
Besides, Kitamura's not the kind of guy to hate someone over something like that.
You're the one who should know that best.
Then... Why am I short?
Why do I have a strange name?
That's...
What!?
Just because she's 165 centimeters tall!
Because she has a name like a girl in Sailor Moon!
On top that, she's Kitamura's childhood friend.
My bad. Are you okay?
But worrying about stuff like tha-
Unlike you, I'm sensitive!
You...
Ryu-chan!
There's no sauce for tonight's pork cutlets.
Pork cutlets?
It's Kurobuta.
TL note- A very high quality pork.
What about pudding? Pudding.
Just sauce!
Huh?
Hey, we're going home. Yasuko will be late for work.
Ryuji, look at this.
This is...
This means she's taking a break from work, right?
Is there anything at our school that's worth taking a break from work?
Isn't that...
That girl!
That's Kawashima Ami, isn't it?
What's with that get-up?
And those bags... They're all sweet things.
Is she going to have a party at home?
No, that's not it. That's...
I just discovered something interesting.
You're really annoying.
If you stick to me that closely, I'll get you!
Newly named, Stupid Chihuahua!