So cool!
What, you want to play the guitar too now?
I've never tried before...do you think I can do it?
Be as cool as Momoka-san?
Yeah, no.
You've never touched a guitar.
It'll just distract you from singing.
She's off in her own little world.
Well, it's always like that after your first concert.
It's definitely gotten into her head.
Screaming out my bottled up feelings
as loud as possible, until I'm out of breath.
It was the first time I did something like that.
I was always so obsessed
with the image people had of me...
Nina!
Practice time.
Coming!
BETWEEN GRATITUDE AND SURPRISE
Alright, let's stop here.
- What do you think?
- Pretty good.
Let's give it a listen.
I want to break everything
My courage has left me
Please, someone give me a reason to exist
Oooh, that sounds good.
There are countless
Nina, can you vary the pitch a bit more
at the start of the verse?
Please, someone give me a reason to exist
Like this?
Yeah, it's a bit boring otherwise.
Also, let's redo the drums too.
Like, now?
I gotta wake up early tomorrow, you know.
Diamond Dust?
Yeah, I saw her looking them up.
They're probably on her mind a lot.
Could be, but think about it, they're real pros unlike us.
Yeah, but...
If she really had any regrets,
she wouldn't have teamed up with a pair of amateurs.
But...
No way.
Oh no!
What's up?
Sorry, I'm going back for today!
See you tomorrow!
-I'M IN FRONT OF THE STORE.
-SUBARU-CHAN, YOU OKAY?
Not even a read receipt, huh...
Definitely a boyfriend.
Huh???
Didn't think she had one though.
Maybe she's trying to get back with her ex?
No way, that's ridiculous!
Why are you so prickly about it?
Well, I mean...
Do you really think that's it?
Band girls are pretty popular, especially with band guys.
We're their main prey.
Prey...?
You better be careful too.
I'll call her.
Like hell she'll answer.
We'll find out more tomorrow.
Well, we can hang out with whoever we want
in our free time anyway.
Hey Momoka-san, what do you think about them?
You know, about Diamond Dust.
Not much.
What do you mean by that?
I'm not feeling resentful or anything if that's what you mean.
I just want the best for them.
Then why did you quit?
I don't want to talk about it.
And you, stop getting distracted.
You have to sing, nothing more.
What kind of band were you?
I told you, just drop it.
I want to know.
Catch.
We met in our high school's Light Music Club.
But all of us were skilled
and passionate about it from the start.
We all shared the same ambitions.
Felt like it was destiny, you know.
I thought it was a miracle. It gave me chills.
And I was right about the miracle part.
Guess what, at the school festival,
our concert was so packed, we physically
couldn't fit any more people.
We ended it with a bang.
After that, we decided to leave school to pursue our dream,
and came here as indie musicians.
We managed to get noticed by a label,
and...that's when I left.
Momoka-san.
You could smile like that too, huh...
Uh, shorry, I wasn't shleeping...
Might as well have slept on my bed...
It's from Subaru!
Wait, what?
SORRY, I'M LEAVING THE BAND!
The hell?!
We should probably drop it...
How can you say that?
We promised to do this together. We can't give up that easily!
I'm not saying we should give up.
If she wants to be in a band,
she'll ditch her boyfriend and come back.
If we start pressuring her, it'll just get nasty.
You think so?
Could it be that you never had a boyfriend?
Have you?
Sorry for intruding...
The heck are you doing?
I don't know, this place stresses me out.
You're the leader, so take charge.
When exactly did I become the leader?
I'm warning you, Subaru acts all annoying here and...
Well, try not to get mad at her.
Oh?
Subaru...
...-chan?
This way, Grandmother.
Could I be of assistance?
- Subaru... - Could you be lost?
Grandmother, I'll just give them
directions and come back...
The heck are you doing here?
The heck was that message?
Of course we'll come running!
We'll talk about everything later,
but you need to go for now!
At least explain what's going on!
I told you I-
And these people are?
Ah, Grandmother!
They're...my friends. From acting school.
Me, acting?
Who else?
It's quite lively in here, isn't it.
Enough to make my head spin.
It's pretty crowded in here, after all...
Subaru-chan.
- Posture.
- Yes ma'am!
I keep telling you to pay attention to your posture.
A person's daily habits always show when performing.
It is crucial to always maintain a good physical and mental balance.
Yes, Grandmother!
You two as well, I'm counting on you
to correct her if she forgets again.
Excuse me for a moment.
Subaru-chan.
Yes, I know.
Is she actually Tendo Awa? Like, the actress?
Woah, took you long enough.
Well it took me a while to connect the dots,
I didn't know anything about Subaru until now.
Yeah, she's my grandma.
She suddenly said she wants to visit yesterday.
Wait, so your whole family's in the acting business?
Not really.
My parents have normal jobs.
You don't actually want to be an actress, do you?
Definitely not. But the thing is, I can't just throw it at her like that.
Then what was that message supposed to be?!
I don't know, I just panicked, or like, you know...
"To deceive your enemies, start by deceiving your friends."
Yeah, right.
Either way, with her that's the the minimum level of precaution.
She seemed pretty nice though...
Yeah, at first glance. But she's from Kyoto,
so if you take what she says at face value,
you'll be in for a world of pain.
Really?
- Posture.
- Yes ma'am!
We should start heading back now.
I want to see how much your acting has improved.
Okay.
Would you two be willing to join us?
Um...yes?
W-What is it?
W-Well, i-it's just that...I have feelings...for you.
Don't laugh!
A theater exercise?
Yes, a romantic scene.
You are going to confess to her,
and Subaru will be trying to win her back.
I...see.
WHAT'S THIS EXERCISE?
Sounds wonderful!
IMRPOVISED ACTING!
BASICALLY JUST WING IT!!
Well then, let us get back to the school and give it a try.
LIKE HELL I CAN DO THAT!
Will you come as well?
NO WAY!
CAN'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT AT THIS POINT
NOWAYNOWAYNOWAY!!
JUST GIVE UP!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
No thank you.
I think Nina-san must've misheard you.
JUST SHUT UP AND COME DAMN IT!
DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY IN THE BAND OR NOT?
I CAN'T DO IT!
Improvised acting means no prior discussion.
Yes ma'am!
Then let us head back.
Wait!
You are...
I don't wish to lie to myself anymore!
I also love you with all my heart!
Then why did you leave me?
Excuse me?
I took our relationship seriously from the start.
I always thought we'd be together forever.
So how could you just leave me so easily?
Well...
Answer me!
Was everything you told me just a lie?
No, I...I really did mean it, but...
Then why?!
Taking it out on me through acting was a low blow!
I don't see the problem here.
Put yourself in my shoes.
I don't actually want to leave the band or anything.
In the acting world,
I'm nothing more than Tendo Awa's granddaughter.
- It's just that...
- What is it?
Something's not right.
My grandmother never shows up unexpectedly.
It's not like her, she's not spontaneous.
Mystery solved!
Girls Band Cry.
You got a role in a drama??
MY EARS! Don't yell into the microphone!
I can't do anything about it, my grandma got me the role.
It's a small role, so it'll only take a week or so,
but no rehearsals for me until it's done.
Got it.
Are you okay with that?
You skip rehearsals to study too, don't you?
That's different.
- It's the same thing!
- No it's not!
Stop fighting.
But Subaru-chan might leave at this rate!
That's par for the course in a band.
But I don't want her to...
Why are you even sulking?
Because you don't seem to care, that's why.
From where I stand, you're the one that doesn't seem to care.
I'm saying I'll come back.
Trust me!
But...
Listen, we all have things we don't want people prying into.
You wouldn't want someone prying into why you came here, right?
Well...
We're wasting time.
You can go, Nina. We're only recording the drums today.
The heck's their problem?
Here I am, trying to be considerate and all...
Grrrr...
Are you free tomorrow?
No!
But actually yes!
Where is this?...
My house.
Come on in.
THE NEXT DAY
Awesome...
You'd get sick of it pretty fast.
- Is tea fine?
- Yeah.
You can sit wherever you'd like.
That one's great for playing games.
Thank you.
Look at this.
She's so pretty...
I wanted to talk to you properly before you
start getting all grumpy on me again.
STARRING TENDO AWA
SUBARU
That movie's where my name comes from.
My grandmother chose it.
Wait, don't tell me that's...
Yep. Apparently,
that movie launched her career.
It was long before I was born.
To her, this name was meant to bring me luck,
if I ever wanted to become an actor.
But you don't.
Exactly.
I'll always be given special treatment because of my grandmother.
And besides, I don't like pretending to be someone.
It's embarrassing.
But you know,
when I tell her that I'm still aiming to become an actress,
she genuinely smiles.
Without putting on an act.
Not with a fake smile.
So, what do you think?
If it were you, what you would do?
Here.
Got it through your thick skull a bit better now?
But...you can't keep things as they are.
If you're not going to become an actress,
you should tell her that as soon as possible.
I know, right?
You really should.
I was hoping that if I went to acting school,
she'd just see that I don't have the talent for it
and give up at some point...
See you later.
And don't worry, I'm not gonna leave the band.
Really?
That concert made me realize,
I kinda like playing the drums.
I'm trying to open up to you here, say something you little-
What's this?
I'M SORRY. - NINA
If you're gonna feel bad about it,
don't throw a fit in the first place.
A FEW DAYS LATER
And here we have the main character of
Detective Grandma's Case Files Part 6,
the famous Tendo Awa-san!
I'll be in your care.
I'm her granddaughter, Subaru.
I'll be playing the role of a cashier.
I'll be in your care.
That's a lot of makeup.
That much is necessary if you want to stand out.
Bands can go pretty hard on that front too, you know.
- So you wear makeup too?
- Depends on the occasion.
Don't start imagining it now.
Action!
Is Subaru really going to tell her?
Yeah, she said she would.
She said she'll probably have to quit acting school
and go back to live with her parents,
but she wants to stay in our band.
Will it really be that big a deal?
Maybe she should keep quiet for now if it's that bad.
You're not wrong.
But she knows she'll have to say it someday.
Cut!
Let's check it.
Was that it?
Yes, we're done for today.
It was our first collaboration.
You must be happy.
It has always been my dream,
to share the stage with Subaru.
Do you want her to become an actress?
Of course.
After all, she got her name
from the role that changed my life.
You know,
my daughter always deeply
hated this line of work.
She'd always complain about me trying to push her into it,
even though I was never there for her at home.
So you can imagine my happiness
when Subaru said she loved acting.
She was the only one who smiled at me.
The only one to find value in what I was doing.
When she said she wants to try it herself,
I was truly thankful.
Cut!
Let's check it.
Well, let's see how it went.
Grandmother!
Great job.
Um, could I talk to you for a minute?
What is it?
It's not urgent, but I wouldn't want you
to miss your train either.
Yes, I should probably get going soon.
I see.
Alright, I'll say it then.
You see...
it's just that...
I...
Grandmother.
Well...
Subaru-chan, trouble!
We forgot something! Come quick!
No time to waste. Let's go!
Huh, what? Hey! Wait!
Wait, don't push me!
Stop, what are you-
You little hypocrite!
I'm sorry!
Shut it!
You were the one who told me
to clear things up!
- Well...yeah!
- Don't just agree, say something!
And after I finally prepared myself for it!
Well, it's just that...you know,
everyone has their share of problems and stuff.
Huh??
You need to be able to like, put yourself in others' shoes,
and understand that things might be tough for them too and stuff.
- You get me?
- Listen here you little!!
It hurts!
Unlike you, I've been taking that into account all along!
And you just...
Still, one day you'll have to tell her.
When is that?
When you find something you want to do.
The heck is wrong with this girl?!
I don't know.
I'm done!
Done, done, done and done!
I steeled my resolve because you wanted me to stay,
And now, I'm stuck between a flip-flopping
self-righteous prick
and an apathetic know-it-all!
I can handle my stuff on my own,
just leave me alone!
Subaru-chan...
So, how's that for some acting?
Phew, I feel better now.
I know that I'll have to
do it sooner or later.
But until then,
I have your two butts to kick up!
Alright, here we go!
Nina Iseri: Rina
Momoka Kawaragi: Yûri
Subaru Awa: Mirei
Tendo Awa: Naoko Kôda
To be continued: "Raise your voice."