The cultural festival is almost here.
Lower your hips more!
Brainwashing Beam!
Somehow, everyone pulled it all together...
Vice President...
It looks like we're running out of posters.
I got it, I'll immediately order some more.
Vice President...
About the divisions in the schoolyard...
That's pretty much already been decided...
Somehow, we all got dead serious.
What do you think?
I tried putting a few things together.
It's cute!
It's really amazing, you're shining!
It's great!
I'm going to shine too!
Kushieda, about your costume...
Somehow...
This kind of thing...
Isn't so bad.
Another long day.
Yeah.
Hey, do I smell sweaty?
Do you think it's okay if I go without showering?
Dinner with the old man?
Answer my question, you mongrel.
O-Ow...
You don't smell.
Well...
He's trying hard, that old man.
Even though he must be busy at work, he comes to pick you up every day.
Eating out together...
I don't think I can forget everything just like that.
But, well...
He knows some pretty good places.
I don't mind hanging out with him for a little bit.
What?
I didn't say anything!
Isn't that...
If he comes to pick me up this early, I won't have time to change.
So that is your dad's car.
You're not thinking it's all happy, happy, smile, smile, right?!
I'm not, I'm not!
Hey, he's waiting for you.
The old man really has been trying hard.
He's frantically trying to get back the lost time and trust.
But... He's not the only one trying hard.
Taiga is...
Also trying hard to respond to his feelings.
"Brainwash Beam."
"bibibi bibibi..."
Out late again?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, hey...
About the cultural festival...
Everyone! Tomorrow's the festival!
We're going to knock it out of the park!
Yeah!
Hey, where are the makeup tools?
That's...
Hey, go on!
Just thinking about asking that Stupid Chihuahua something gives me the creeps.
Now, now...
Now's the time swallow your pride...
What are you smiling about? It's creepy.
The old man said he's going to come all the way to see you.
This is where you have to go all out.
You stay there for ten minutes!
Don't come in until I've settled things with that Stupid Chihuahua.
Okay, okay...
S-Sorry, Takasu-kun...
Could you move a little?
Sorry!
No way, what's with that?
A present from you to me has got to have a catch to it.
Oh, no, Stupid Chihuahua. Of course there's nothing like that.
Please, I'd like for you to eat this.
W-What are you doing?
You're kidding! This is from that super famous restaurant!
I went yesterday with my father.
I thought I'd bring you back some.
Even my model friends have a hard time getting this.
Hey, try it.
Right now, here?
Just try it!
No way, I want to eat it at home with tea...
Eat it right now, now, now!
I got it. I'll eat it. See?
You ate it.
It's good, it's good.
See? That's enough, right?
Now go away.
You ate it, right?
Now you have to do what I say.
What the hell? I knew there was a catch!
In the cultural festival's pro-wrestling show, just once is fine, switch roles with me.
I want to do a better role too.
I can't believe Taiga wants to be the lead.
Yeah, her dad is going to come to the cultural festival.
She wants to show off a little.
You know about her family too, right?
They've been trying to rebuild their bonds as father and daughter...
What the hell?
Kushieda?
What the hell is that?
You have to be kidding me.
Hey, wait. What's with you all of a sudden?
I have to open her eyes.
I have to tell her, "You can't believe that kind of father."
Why?
Something that horrible...
If you're Taiga's best friend, you should be happy for her.
Happy? Me? Why?
Why?
Why should I be happy when my best friend is being fooled by a father who just showed up?
I can't just smile and watch my friend get hurt.
I absolutely can't.
Trade, trade!
Quit it! I got it!
You're way out of line!
You don't even know anything! Don't decide everything by yourself.
Taiga's dad is thinking about his daughter, he's a good guy.
You met him.
You can still say that even though you've met him?
Takasu-kun, when you met that man, were you really looking at him with both of your eyes open?
Were your eyes really looking?
What do you mean?
W-Wait.
R-Ryuji... Minorin...
Handshake!
R-Ryuji.
I want to die.
That's my spot.
Hey, move, move.
Hey!
See? A perfect fit.
This is definitely my spot.
Hey...
What did Kushieda do after that?
She went home.
Seriously?
I'm amazed you could yell at the girl you like like that.
That was Kushieda's fault.
I can't believe it...
That she was the kind of person who would say crap like that.
How annoying.
I'm not going to be all nice and sympathize with you just because you're a little down.
I figured as much.
Alright.
Let's go back, we're going to start practice.
But... I... Even though everyone was all excited, I ruined the mood.
It's okay. I fixed it up for you.
If you're with me, you'll be able to get through it, right?
You've... changed. Really...
I look like that to you?
I want to change too.
What should I do?
Don't ask me! Think about it yourself.
Kawashima?
I won't stick to you like Taiga.
And I can't become a shining Sun to you like Minori-chan.
You've said that before.
Equals...
I correct that. I'm...
Kawashima Ami is walking on the same street as you...
Just a little further ahead.
Ryu-chan, hurry up.
I'm hungry.
You're always late these days.
It can't be helped, I've had to prepare for the cultural festival.
It'll be ready in a minute.
Okay...
Hey, I heard Taiga-chan is going to move.
Where did you hear that?
When I was taking a nap, it was noisy next door...
We're going to get rid of all the furniture so...
Hello!
I'm sorry for making so much noise.
This person who said he was Taiga-chan's father was there.
He said that the apartment was too small for both of them to live in, so...
Yeah?
Somehow...
He's a pretty selfish father.
Yeah!
Coming back all of a sudden, suddenly...
You're spouting that crap too?!
I mean, isn't it a good thing?
The two of them, living as a family in a new house, starting over again.
It's not good!
I don't want Taiga-chan to go.
We're already a three person family.
You, really...
Don't wanna, don't wanna!
Why won't she talk to Yacchan?
It's smoky.
You mean she's being standoffish.
She hasn't come home yet?
Even though the performance is tomorrow.
That old man should have thought about tonight...
No...
If Taiga's okay with it, then it's okay.
She's got a lot riding on everything going well.
Hey, you got home.
Yeah.
What is the topic for tonight's consultation?
Again...
It's not about me. It's about Minorin.
Make sure you apologize to her.
I... Didn't say anything wrong.
That's not it.
It's not about being right or being wrong.
There are more important things than that.
That's why apologies and forgiveness become necessary.
Either way, make sure you apologize!
Got it?
Then came the morning of the cultural festival.
They're lining up!
What will I do? What will I do?
Calm down, Haruta.
How can I calm down, Taka-
Hey, stop fooling around.
What?
What are you trying to do? You masked mongrel!
I was just...
I caused a lot of problems for everyone yesterday.
So today, I wanted to put a lot of effort into being a villain.
You don't have to try so hard!
You're perfect at the "just needs a little improvement" level.
In a lot of ways.
What's with that?
More importantly, did you apologize properly?
N-No, not yet...
What do you mean?
If you don't hurry up, you're going to waste your chance to be with Minorin during the festival.
Hey, Kushieda.
You're in style today!
Does it suit me?
It does, it does!
You're the only one who can wear it.
Making such a pathetic face.
You're making me all shy!
Take that.
And that, and that!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Hey! Be quiet.
It's finally time!
This is a report from the ticket counter.
Eighty percent of the seats are taken.
If it keeps going like this, we might even end up with people standing.
Really?
Alright!
Now, here's to the success of 2-C's first performance of the Pro-Wrestling Show!
Fight!
One shot!
"2-C's Pro-Wrestling is really awesome"?
What's that?
It's good?
I heard that Kawashima Ami's appearing in a super short skirt!
I heard that Tenori Taiga and Yankee Takasu-kun are really funny!
That's...
2-C's legendary secret treasure!
The red thread symbolizes fated love.
That's right! The super important, secret treasure!
The homeroom teacher's red thread.
Stop it! Anything but that!
You all were members of 2-C, right?
Wow, I've gotten really nervous.
We're on soon.
Taiga?
Y-Yeah, I got it.
Now, Tenori Taiga-sama, please come out!
Taiga-sama, your orders!
This red thread...
Shishishi datte!
Did she just mess up?
She did.
She did, she did.
Say it again.
Cut it!
Roger!
Stop it, that's...
Stop it! Don't cut it!
Don't cut it!
Wow! This is great!
Hey, this isn't in the script!
There's no choice.
Noto!
Shadow Warriors!
Send the homeroom teacher to the morgue!
Morgue?
Where they keep the bodies of the dead...
Ami-chan!
Keep going, keep going!
How cruel!
All of my friends have been brainwashed! What should I do?
God has been watching everything.
Warrior Ami!
If you can understand what is really in people's hearts...
You'll be able to free your friends from the brainwashing.
Now I will ask you... This is the question.
No matter what, I must receive your answer to this.
This is an important, important chance to attack.
This is really...
What is the name of the most beautiful goddess in the world?
That is....
Kawashima Ami!
That's right!
What were we doing?
Ami-chan...
Saved...
Us!
Damn you!
Using such underhanded methods!
Youja, youja... Weehhh!
We won't forgive you, Kawashima Ami!
Ready, set....
I can't see! What is this?
Today's main event!
Tenori Taiga versus Kawashima Ami!
Push!
Here you go!
Wow!
Ami-chan!
Behind you!
A-An opening!
We won't let you!
You guys!
You've been getting too many good parts!
Going to Ami-chan's summer house!
Here we go, Tiny Taiga!
One, two...
Let go, I got a cramp in my back!
Just a little more.
I'll be on top when we switch.
Alright!
They loved it, they loved it!
Yay!
This mask can be a little stuffy.
Hey, about the next show, can we get the lights to go on from all sides?
Welcome home, Master.
I-It's not like you have to drink my tea.
Welcome, Princess. Your very own prince has arrived.
It's like they're all cosplay cafes.
It seems kind of worthless.
Everyone is having fun.
It looks like there are a lot of customers too.
Yes.
The vice president went out to neighboring schools and advertised the festival.
The first show turned out great.
Yeah!
If it keeps up like this, the next show...
Hey, what're you doing?
You're eating your ribbon.
It must be really delicious, that crepe.
Can you let me have a bite off the corner?
It's pretty good.
Y-You can have as much as you want.
You're really generous.
Kitamura, you're really...
T-Taiga?
Ryuji, have some too!
It's time to do my rounds for the student council.
Sorry, you guys go ahead.
Hey, are you trying to kill me?
Kitamura-kun... The part where Kitamura put his mouth...
It's almost time for the next show.
I know that.
Stop being so cranky.
You're the one that put it in my mouth.
I know that!
Did you get an email from your old man?
You keep looking at your phone.
I'm just playing a game.
Even when you're about to go on?
There are still some showings left.
So if he comes, you can just switch with Kawashima...
Who cares about me?
You better think this Minorin thing over.
Alright! It was a huge success!
Hey, supporting actors! You were amazing!
Yeah...
In the end...
Taiga didn't play the lead, not even once.
Was I really not looking, like Kushieda said?
No way... If so, then I'm really...
A really perverted guy!