So Ra No Wo To
Man, I hate this stupid snow!
Especially now that HQ's said we need
to be sure to do all our patrols.
You still haven't given up over
Jacott-san, have you?
That's not exactly it.
Well, I don't think there's
anything wrong with it.
You can look all you want,
and if you don't find anyone,
you can still believe they're alive.
What?
Kureha-chan, I thought you might be looking
like Rio-sempai for a second there.
What's wrong?
Under that cliff!
Eleven o'clock!
Four hundred meters or so out!
Wake up!
Hey, wake up!
Even his clothes are frozen!
Kanata, take off his coat.
We'll change coats with him.
OK!
Look at him...
A Roman soldier!
A Visitor - A Burning Field of Snow
I can't believe you were actually able
to bring back this facility.
I can see how you earned your reputation
as the greatest genius in academy history.
Now victory is ours!
It's all thanks to you,
Kannagi Noël-kun.
Noël-chan!
While on patrol, the two
of them found her.
It's a Roman soldier.
Her left leg is broken.
Her fingers are turning
black and red!
Frostbite. If we're not careful,
she'll lose the fingers.
The witch of Helvetia...
Leave her to me!
Looks like she'll be fine.
The fingers are OK, too.
Great!
Where's Noël-chan?
She said she'd stay with
her for a while.
But I don't know... She seemed to think
this was really important,
like when she was fixing
the Takemikazuchi.
I see...
A trumpet.
She might be a spy, yeah...
I was really surprised.
Well, yeah.
No one thought we'd run into
a Roman soldier there.
No. It was the first time I've ever
seen anyone from Rome.
They say they're all
enemies, right?
So I was thinking they'd
be scarier somehow.
The people of Rome probably
think the same about us.
But I realized, when I saw her...
They're just like us.
Hey, Kanata, you...
Hey, Kana-chan.
It's almost time for school
lessons to end.
The peace talks are still
going badly, aren't they?
So I hear.
Are we reporting her?
If we do, she'll be taken to the
Capitol and interrogated.
We have to!
They're invading enemy territory
during unstable times!
A soldier should be prepared
for torture...
Interrogation.
I will decide what to do with her.
Please give me some
time, Kureha-chan.
Don't forget, Captain.
We're soldiers.
Can I ask one thing?
Did you meet anyone when you
were carrying her here?
I don't know.
OK.
Thanks.
Say, Rio. What would you do?
A Helvetian soldier...
What were you going
to do with these?
Where am I?
Am I a Helvetian prisoner?
I don't speak Roman.
Fine.
So you took me prisoner-
What was that scream?
What's wrong?
She woke up.
I'm glad.
Imperial Roman Army, First Armored
Division, 13th Legion B-Company
Master Sergeant Aisha Aldola,
serial number 1031021.
What are you doing here?
Imperial Roman Army, Warrant Officer
Aisha Aldola, serial number 1031021.
What was your mission?
<Identification number 1031021.>
You've got guts, then.
Well? Did you learn anything?
Not a thing!
She doesn't speak any Helvetian.
All we learned was her serial number
and that her name is Aisha.
I'm Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann.
I'm in charge of this fortress.
You have really nice breasts,
just the kind I like.
Would it be all right if I played
with them for a bit?
Can I run my fingers
all along your body?
What are you saying, Captain?
She really seems unable to
understand Helvetian.
But this is a problem. We can't
interrogate her like this.
We need to find someone
who speaks Roman.
Then...
Until we can interrogate her
and file a proper report,
we'll keep her here.
But...
I thought I'd place a bet.
I've got no part in this.
Aisha-chan, welcome to
Clocktower Fortress.
<Clocktower Fortress?>
Yup, Clocktower Fortress.
<Ah, I see... Then I made it.>
<Grandmother...>
Maybe it's too hot.
She ate it.
Is it good?
<To escape, I need stamina,
so I'll eat your food.>
I'm sure she's saying it's good!
What's going on here?
Kanata's always like this,
but Noël's never that
nice to anyone...
She may be trying to atone.
Have you ever seen
a fossil of an angel?
Angel?
<They don't understand me, I know...
What's wrong with me?>
I should have studied Roman.
That's right.
If we could talk, we could...
Working hard, huh?
Hey, Yumina-chan?
You guys got enough people at
the church to help shovel?
Yes.
The kids are really working at it.
Glad to hear it.
I guess they're really growing up.
That's right.
People grow and get
better every day.
Just like Kanata-san's
trumpet playing...
Rio would say she's not there yet.
Hey, weren't you heading to
Treize to buy more goods?
Some stuff happened, and I ended up
having to come back.
Sorry to hear that.
Oh, speaking of the Fortress,
I heard this awful rumor...
Thank you!
<It's a wonderful melody.>
<Ah, I didn't know there were
trumpets like that left.>
<Can I play it?>
I think Rio-sempai would let you.
<It's a good trumpet.>
<Really, I haven't seen
one this nice...>
That song was amazing!
This is so wonderful!
Iliya's song filled me up, and then Rio-sempai's,
and the same song is in Roman, too!
Sound really does fill the air!
The same way in Rome
and in Helvetia.
First aid.
<Danke.>
Dan...ke?
<Yeah, danke.>
What's "danke"?
It means "Thank you."
I thought someone saw us.
This city never bore the
full brunt of the war,
but almost everyone here's lost family and
friends, one way or another, in the war.
They're nice people,
but you know...
Mikhail,
you remember the guy who
runs that distillery?
I was at his place until yesterday.
He said the Helvetian
Army's on the move,
heading here.
If that's got something to do with a Roman
scout being all the way out here,
then it's a big deal.
Anyway, we need to ask her.
Naomi-san, do you know anyone
who speaks Roman?
I sure do!
I am Yumina.
I am a servant of the Helvetian
Orthodox Church.
May the blessings of
the all be upon you.
Heretic.
There's one God.
That greeting is blasphemy.
What are you saying to her?
Just a greeting.
Go on! Ask her!
Why are you here?
If you don't tell us, you put everyone
here in a very bad position.
If you feel any sort of obligation to them,
then tell us the truth.
I can't tell you about my mission.
But I wanted to see the
Angel Fossil located in this town.
She says she wants to
see the Angel Fossil.
Angel Fossil...
What?
My grandmother was
a Maiden here.
a soldier here.
<She was captured at the Eastern Front
and met my grandfather.>
She was captured at the Eastern Front
and met my grandfather.
<As I grew up, I listened
to her stories.>
I grew up listening to her stories.
<So I wanted to see the Angel of the apocalypse
that brought judgment
to the world in the distant past,
the one my grandmother spoke of.>
That doctrine is wrong!
It was the devil that destroyed
the world!
Just tell us exactly
what she said!
She wanted to see the angel of the apocalypse
that destroyed the world.
That's why she came...
A call to advance?
That code is...
Royal Guard Platoon, 9th Independent
Mobile Division...
The 9th... It can't be...
Colonel Hopkins!
Is he famous?
He's known as the
Demon of Vingt.
They say he brought weapons
back from the old age,
wiping out three towns
in a single night.
It's all right. He doesn't
know you're here.
It's all right.
Either way, you don't have
time to worry about it.
You need to decide what you're
going to do, and fast.
You can either give her over...
There's nothing to decide!
We're Helvetian Soldiers!
I lost the bet.
You didn't make it in
time, did you, Rio?
Wait!
Rio didn't want anyone
else to suffer.
That's why she'd do what
she could, she said!
That's why she left, wasn't it?
I don't want this to happen!
We're all the same!
We're all together!
I will now give my order as leader
of the 1121st Platoon.
This order is mine alone, and I will
take full responsibility for it.
Are we clear, everyone?
I am Commander of the 1121st Platoon,
Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann.
Yesterday, a Roman scout
was captured in Treize.
Unfortunately, there was an accident during
questioning, and we didn't get any details.
We've actually had reports of
a Roman soldier here in Seize.
Do you have any ideas?
No, Colonel.
Understood.
As of this moment,
the 1121st Fortress
is under the command of the 9th
Independent Mobile Division.
Stay quiet.
I'm sorry.
Aisha was telling me about the
legend of the Flame Maidens.
But it's strange...
According to her...
Shh!
Search everywhere!
Did you find her?
What about over there?
Nothing over here!
Find her!
Open this door!
She's gotta be here somewhere!
Post more guards by the exits!
I hadn't asked your name
yet, she says.
Noël...
Ihr name ist Noël.
Noël... Noël Kannagi?
Ja...
The Witch of Helvetia...
The Invisible Reaper...
The Invisible Reaper?
A rat, maybe?
Noël-san?
Hello?
This is the 1121st Fortress.
A massive Roman Army contingent has appeared
at the Seize border with No Man's Land?
Fill the Blue Sky
Next time:
Fill the Blue Sky.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.