Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
Thankful to someone?
It seems I am needed!
This is a present from me!
I-I lost...
You bind him with a scarf
embedded with wires--
She's asleep!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
"Valentine's Fest"
It's finally the season, huh?
Yes, it is.
The season that I want winter to end soon
and hope I can save on my heating bill.
That wasn't what I meant...
Didn't we just have this conversation?
It's almost Valentine's!
Valentine's is an important day!
It's the day to gorge on chocolate!
That's not what Valentine's is for.
I've also heard this conversation before...
Miss Yoko, do you plan to
give chocolate to anyone?
I was not planning to.
It's not a big deal. If you're thankful
to someone, you can give some to them.
I see. Thankful to someone?
"A Day to Gorge on Chocolate"
I just remembered.
Hm?
Something happened the other day...
Oh, my. It cannot get down from the tree.
Wh-What should I do? It's really high up.
The tree looks thin, so it might
not take my weight if I climb it.
But, I must rescue it!
It seems I am needed!
I have more important things to do
than make these useless things.
Useless things?
So, Yamaji helped me rescue the cat.
What? Isn't that an event
that's more fitting for me?
Event?
So, what happened to the cat?
Well, after we got it down, it ran away.
I can't believe it. It was over, just like that?
I apologize I could not meet your expectations.
You set off a flag for it
coming back to repay you.
Repay me?
You've heard stories of animals
who repay people for saving them.
My, if the kitten came to repay me,
it would be so cute. That would be lovely.
Like...
I got this fish for you. Here!
Salted salmon?!
I got this cash for you. Here!
Cash?!
I guess I'll let you touch my
paw pads... just this once!
That's it?
And she gave it a personality, too!
Where's Yamaji?
Huh? Yamaj--
I'm at your service.
Yamaji!
Y-Yes?
Um, this might be a weird request.
If the kitten comes to repay you,
please save the moment!
I'm not sure I understand.
Please!
Teru.
Teru!
What? Bel?!
Teru, thanks for always taking care of me!
I'm very thankful that you took me
in and were so kind to me.
So, here. This is a present from me!
That dream sounded like Bel's last words!
It's because of Miss Yoko's story.
Well, it wasn't a bad dream.
Thank you...
That's what happened this morning.
Wow.
Good for you, Hayama. She was repaying you.
You're right.
Of course, the way a cat shows its love
is different from how humans show love.
Being able to understand and receive that
love shows how good of an owner you are.
Once an animal lover, always an animal lover.
You're a model pet owner.
That's something I can't ignore.
Hayama's a model pet owner? Now that's bold.
Then, has El ever given you a repayment gift?
Of course she has! But, just
having her by my side is plenty.
Isn't that how a pet owner should think?
Is it?
Nishiyama!
Then, why don't you two have a
competition to see who cats like more?
What?
"Bel Hayama (1 years old)"
Didn't you take pictures of your cat before?
Whoever takes a cuter cat picture, wins!
Stay still, Bel.
H-Hey, don't come here!
My almost-tendinitis wrists that have been holding
the camera since morning are quickly healing!
Master Beelzebub!
They're all so cute, I can't pick!
They're all best shots!
I brought my pictures.
Me, too. Here are my best shots.
We will judge the results.
Oh, they're cute.
So cute!
They are very cute. But, it is like
comparing two peas from the same pod.
What do you mean?!
That's not true!
Well, she is cute.
Yes, so cute! Maybe it's a tie.
Can I have this?
Yeah, let's trade.
You won't get a real competition
between two cat fans, I guess.
What was the competition for, then?
Well, we got something
out of it, so all is good.
Oh. Well, if we want a competition...
Futaba Odagiri!
We have a competitor.
The older Tsuji sibling. You're probably
going to challenge me, right?
I'll challenge you this time!
What?!
"Jumbo" "Hamburg Steaks"
Jumbo hamburg!
You're on!
"Jumbo" "Hamburg Steaks"
What?
They wouldn't let me in!
Is this one of the places you're banned from?
Oh, I forgot!
You had forgotten?
They let me in. Which means, I win by default!
Total victory for me! Oh, yeah!
Woo-hoo! Oh, yeah!
I-I lost...
Wait a second. Think about it carefully.
--That's not right! They wouldn't let me in,
--Woo-hoo! Oh yeah! Whoo!
--because I'm a bigger threat!
--Hey, listen! Think about it!
--Woo-hoo! Oh yeah! Whoo!
Anyway, congratulations on your win.
Oh, uh, what was your name?
Ni... Ni... Nishi-something?
How do you know my name?
He only said the "Nishi" part, though.
It's "Nishikawa"! Ni-shi-ka-wa!
And it's Miss Nishikawa to you.
Add the "Miss" you glutton!
Yamaji! You be quiet!
That's pretty cool.
It's just like Sasame told me.
Oh, you heard from your sister.
Yup. You're, uh, one of her friends, right?
What?!
Well, thanks for always taking care of my sister.
Oh! Well, er...
It's my... pleasure!
Miss Yoko is being considerate!
Sasame!
Hm?
Guess what! I won against Odagiri!
You didn't win. From what you said,
that doesn't count as winning.
What?! B-But she said "congratulations."
You know, uh, Nishihara... kawa... tani...?
It's Nishikawa.
Yeah, Nishikawa. And I was even polite and said
thanks for always taking care of my sister!
What?!
It's what a big bro would do.
I was super being an adult.
--You idiot!
--Huh?
Why'd you say that to her?
You probably made her feel awkward!
But, that's what I'm supposed
to say to your friends.
Yeah, if we were friends already.
Nishikawa and I aren't that close yet.
Really?
You idiot!
We're still building our friendship!
I didn't even say any-- Hey, Sasame!
Do you have any good ideas?
When I give Yu the chocolates,
I want it to be memorable.
Hm, memorable?
I wonder how many types of chocolates
I can eat with my allowance this year--
I'm not talking about you!
Don't you think a hand-knitted scarf
and handmade chocolate is best?
What? Isn't that too normal?
Really? You bind him with a scarf
--Woah.
--embedded with wires and force-feed drugged chocolate.
Big sister!
You're going to do it?
I'm going now. I need to get ready.
Be careful on your way home.
Thank you!
Ah, that's what Miss Usuda is planning?
Young Master Takezono will have a fine Valentine's.
I also want to...
Huh?
I also want to make chocolate.
Apologies, but my hearing has declined recently.
Chocolate! I want to make chocolate!
Ah, I see. You want to keep
it as emergency food.
No, for Valentine's!
And who will you be giving it to?
My friends. And, I will send a mountain
of chocolates to Father, too.
You're going to hike up
a mountain with everyone?
No, I am talking about Valentine's!
Oh, Sonobe. I want to make chocolate.
Good. This time of year is as busy as Christmas,
and any help I could get,
even yours, would be helpful.
Not for the shop! I want to give homemade
chocolate to people I am thankful for.
Of course, I will not slack on my duties here.
Miss Yoko wants to make chocolate from scratch?
She will probably start off energetically,
but get exhausted because
she's not used to making sweets.
And then she'll be sick in bed, and Valentine's
will be even busier than Christmas!
That's my situation. Please,
you'll be helping me so much!
No way! Why do I have to?
You can just ask someone else.
You're the person for the job.
What?!
You don't have anything to do
on Valentine's anyway, right?
How rude!
What are you doing?
I was asking Nishiyama to
give me a hand at the shop.
I can help! You don't need to pay me, either.
What?
You can pay me with cakes instead.
No, thank you. I will pay you.
Aw, too bad.
I would love if you could help out, too, Hayama.
As long as I don't have to wear that maid dress.
All... right... mm, hmm...
I can't hear you!
All right, let's work hard today!
Yes!
Miss Yoko didn't faint from exhaustion.
What?
Hey! Why am I wearing these clothes?!
Oh, good. They fit perfectly.
This isn't what we agreed on!
You didn't want to wear this maid outfit,
so I prepared a different one for you.
It's fine. It looks good.
I agree.
I wanted to make some for you two,
too, but I didn't have enough time.
Is prepping for Valentine's that tough?
I pulled two all-nighters making
Hayama's new maid outfit.
Not my fault!
Thank you for waiting. We will allow people
to enter in order, so please do not push.
Welcome! I can ring you up here once you
have decided what items you would like.
Wait, why did she make me work, too?
Don't say that. Look how busy it is.
What about that other guy? The former butler?
My apologies! I have my hands full with making
a special chocolate cake I'm giving to Miss Yoko.
Why are you making that now?!
Excuse me, Miss Sonobe?
She's asleep!
She did say she hadn't slept for two nights.
How can she be sleeping when it's this busy?
It's fine. You take care of
things when it counts!
Y-You bet!
Welcome!
So easily manipulated.
I apologize for the long wait.
Don't worry. It is Valentine's. Keep it up!
Thank you very much!
Ahh!
I-It's so busy!
Sonobe. Wake up, Sonobe!
Sonobe!
Oh, you're tired already, Hayama? How careless.
You're amazing, Nishiyama.
Of course. I'm just getting started.
I'm going to take a short break, then.
Wha--?!
Excuse me.
Y-Yes. How can I help you?
As expected from someone who can
take care of things when it counts.
She makes life hard for herself.
Thank you very much.
One limited edition Gâteau Chocolat.
Okay, one Gâteau Chocolat.
What, it's the Tsuji siblings.
What are you doing here?
I-It's not a big deal if a guy
buys Valentine's cakes.
Yeah, it's not a big deal.
There are lots of limited edition items during
Valentine's and Christmas. He saves up for this!
Doesn't it take courage for a guy to buy
chocolate-flavored things around Valentine's?
I don't really care. I get tons of chocolate
at school, so it doesn't faze me.
Wow, that unexpected.
Yeah. He's popular at school.
Even in my school club, I'm an
important mascot character!
Ah...
Thank you very much. Please come again.
Sorry. I just wanted to see
Nishiyama working hard on the job.
Nothing interesting to see here.
Then, would you like to start working here, too?
She's awake?!
No thanks, that's not my thing.
--If you agree now, I'll throw in a dessert.
--That's not my thing?
--Oh, no thank you.
"Sold Out"
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much for working so hard.
I got to catch up on my sleep thanks to you!
Sonobe! Kneel!
"February 14th"
Yesterday was pretty tiring.
I want to try on a maid outfit sometime, too.
Maybe I'll ask Miss Sonobe next time.
Won't work.
Huh?
Miss Yoko said that she likes making
people who dislike it wear them.
Ah, I see. That's why Nishiyama is a maid, too!
Nishiyama... a maid? No way.
Sh-She asked me to wear it,
and that was the only thing she had.
I-I wasn't wearing it because I wanted to.
Ah, it makes sense now.
What are you talking about?!
I never want to wear those clothes again.
I don't like wearing it or anything!
Y-Yeah, right? It fit you size-wise,
but it didn't look that good.
It looked like the clothes were wearing you.
You look better in more straight-cut clothes.
Y-Yeah, that's right.
I thought it looked pretty good on you.
D-Don't make fun of me!
Nishiyama!
I actually think that, though.
It's because you're complimenting
her when you usually don't.
Thank you for all your help yesterday.
Th-This is a thank you for everything,
including yesterday. Here!
Oh, is this the charcoal stuff
to get rid of odors?
They're truffles! I made them from scratch.
What?!
I put the gratitude I have for you
into them when I made them.
Miss Yoko made these from scratch?
They don't melt, but they're edible.
Right? I can do it if I try.
You're amazing, Miss Yoko!
It's not melting?
Not really.
Oh, Tsuji!
Here you go.
What?! Chocolates? F-For me?
Yes, please accept them.
Nishikawa gave me chocolates!
Wh-Wh-What should I give back to her?
How much should my return
gift cost? Three times? More?!
Like a house or something?!
Here, Yamaji. Some for you, too.
What?! I get some, too?!
Thank you very much! I will offer
them on the family altar!
You can just eat them. Chocolates
should arrive to Father today, too.
That is all of them.
Hm? What? That's it?
What about me?
Where are the chocolates of gratitude for me?
Miss Yoko?!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
The next "Three Leaves, Three Colors"
is the last episode!
Let's have Miss Yoko say the title.
Okay, I will.
Next time is, "I Am Graduating
from Bread Crusts."
I hope you enjoy it.
Well, that's not happening.
"Next time: I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts"
Nope.
It will!
"Next time: I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts"