Listen, Minami.
What.
Question 10
Me, Romance, and the Art of Love
Um...
I'm sorry about earlier!
Whatever.
You can go and get lovey-dovey with Mizuki all you want.
Aw, don't be like that.
Let's think of another plan.
If we lose to Class B, Himeji will have to transfer—
What's your problem, moron?!
All day long, it's just Mizuki this, Mizuki that.
Why does only Mizuki get the special treatment?
Minami...
Then what is it? Why do you always treat me like this?
Do you think I'm a man?
N-No, it's not like—
I'll talk to her parents if they force her to transfer.
Minami!
Don't talk to me ever again!
I don't want to see your stupid face anymore!
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
through a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Previously on the show...
Previously on the show
Yay!
Class B's rep, Nemoto Kyouji, knows that our heroes are weak after returning from their suspension
Suspension  Suspension  Suspension
Declare     an     ESB
and thus wants to declare an ESB on Class F.
That's why Akihisa and the gang tried provoking Class D into declaring an ESB on them first.
Provoking
Declare     an     ESB
If they can fight Class D first, they'll get time to restore their marks before the next battle.
They can bolster their forces this way, and Class B will have to reconsider attacking them!
Marks
That's why Akihisa and Shimada had to pretend to be a couple and enrage Shimizu into attacking us.
Angry
outburst
Beforehand
Declare ESB
Class rep     Me
Pretending to
be lovers
O O
o
Akihisa
Shimada
Boys
Girls
Shimizu Miharu
Provoke
Class Rep
Nemoto Kouji
Current state of
Class F's forces
Have not recovered marks
since being suspended
Weaker than ever
Gain time because
of Class D's ESB
Immediately
Forces
Can not
Declare ESB
Effect
Prevent
At least, that was the plan.
Good job screwing everything up, asshole.
No sane man would think you two were going out after that!
Sorry.
I should have coached thee more about the fine art of theater.
Shimada and Himeji did very well though.
Not at all! Thank you, though.
Why do you always treat me like this?
Voyeur, what is Class B up to?
They've finished replenishing 70% of their forces.
One squadron is already preparing to start the battle.
They're faster than we thought.
They are prepared to fight to the death, indeed.
We need more time.
First of all, Voyeur,
go spread misinformation in the enemy camp.
What would you like?
Make them think Class D is preparing for an ESB...
against Class B!
Understood.
What's the point in doing that?
Nemoto only wants to win and restore his standing in his class.
He won't risk a fight where he may lose forces.
AAAAA
Declare ESB
If he thinks he's gonna be attacked by Class D, he'll hesitate to attack us.
AAAA
Declare ESB
I get it! He's not after our facilities, after all!
Next, Hideyoshi,
arrange a meeting with Shimizu Miharu of Class D.
We'll stir her up, make her mad.
Declare
an    ESB
Rage
If we can get her to fight us, it's our victory!
Declare
an    ESB
Why must it be I?
You'll need to take Shimada with you to have the desired effect on Shimizu.
I can't ask Akihisa or Himeji to do that now.
I see. I understand!
Next up is Akihisa.
What is it?
Are you hungry?
Yeah, I guess I am.
That's too bad, pal. You're the star of our operation.
You need to be brimming with power on a full stomach...
right, Himeji?
That's right. An army marches on its stomach, doesn't it?
That's where you come in, Himeji.
Please cook something for Akihisa—
Now that I think about it, I already ate my lunch during class. I'm so stuffed I can't eat another bite!
Isn't that your lunch up there?
Delicious
No! How could this be?!
Shit happens. Himeji, can you whip something up for him?
Of course! With pleasure!
Yuuji, stop this!
Akihisa, whaddya wanna eat?
What?
I should ask her for something simple... something even she won't screw up!
We're running out of time, Akihisa.
Something she won't mix with her own otherworldly ingredients!
I know! Boiled eggs!
Mizuki's
Handmade Cooking
Today's Special
Boiled eggs
Ingredients: Only eggs
Akihisa says he'd really like to eat Jell-O!
Boiled eggs
Ingredients: Only eggs
Today's Special
Jell-O
Numerous unspecified
ingredients
But you don't know what she'll use to make that!
He'll have to eat it in the midst of battle, so can you put it in a drink pack like in field rations?
Today's serving style
Field rations
So that the contents can't be seen
Then I can't even see what color it is!
Field rations
I got it! I'll be right back!
Wait! At least ask me what flavor I want!
Get a grip, Akihisa. I'm not going to make you eat it.
It's just another weapon for our war.
So that's it. Why didn't you say so?
But Himeji's still gonna make you eat it.
You fucking bastard!
Home
Economics
Jell-O
Mix the gelatin and sugar like so.
What the? She's making it normally.
Thank God!
First, dissolve the cocoa powder in the corn soup.
Hey, what was she cooking again?
Keep it down! She'll hear us!
Jell-O
Oranges or spring onions? I wonder which one Akihisa prefers!
That's not it! That's not what you should be confused about, Himeji!
She's trying her best to make you something nutritious, although I can't say what it'll taste like.
Since we're adding spring onions, let's add some fermented soybeans too!
Jell-O
Don't! Don't!
But I've heard that soybeans don't really improve circulation, after all.
Saved!
Oh well. It's still nutritious!
3rd inning
Besides, raw fish improves circulation!
She made a double play.
Pickled mackerel? Pickled mackerel in Jell-O?!
She's worried about your idiocy, so she's providing you with DHA.
Oh, no! This won't do!
Great! Himeji realized her mistake!
I almost forgot the mustard with the soybeans.
That's not what you were supposed to realize!
And ginger in the mackerel too.
That isn't it either!
And we'll enhance the taste with...
Please, at least leave out the ginger.
I know! An adult taste of taba—
Let's go! You'll never be able to eat again if you watch any longer.
Wait! At least let me see if she meant tabasco or tobacco!
It's already too late for you.
Here! Eat up!
I have to go clean up the home economics room.
What shall we do with these?
Nemoto will probably send an envoy to Class D...
to ask them if they really plan to attack his class.
But then he'll know we're the ones who spread that rumor!
That's why we're going to assassinate that envoy!
Envoy
If we do that, he'll start suspecting Class D.
Dammit
It'll make the rumor we spread seem even more likely.
God in Heaven, thou art merciless!
Merciless
That's the way a war is fought.
Voyeur, I leave it to you.
Acknowledged.
Envoy
What's that?
W-Why you—
Envoy
Amen.
Mother!
He's been executed.
Good job, Voyeur.
You're really good at covert ops!
This operation was too easy to be proud of.
What did you use to distract the crowd?
You don't have the clearance to know that.
Nemoto will think this is a warning from Class D.
We bought us some time, haven't we?
Hideyoshi, what's the status on the negotiations with Class D?
We agreed to meet in an empty classroom.
Minami agreed to join us as well.
Then we just have to meet them there and make them angry.
But I wonder if we'll make them angry enough.
I have an awesome plan. Trust me.
There's one thing bothering me.
What is it, Voyeur?
There was an eyewitness who saw Nemoto talking to someone in Class A.
Class A?
That's strange. What's he doing there?
Yuuji!
Shouko! Why... What are you doing here?
No, what are you still doing in school, Yuuji?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Yuuji! Mother collapsed.
Huh?! My mother collapsed?
She's so healthy that she doesn't even catch colds!
Never mind! We have to go home!
Hold it! I have an important plan to pull off—
This is more important.
Hold it! Wait! How do you—
Shut up and come with me.
Shouko! Think about it!
That sounded suspicious.
What do you mean, Voyeur?
If it was that serious, someone would've contacted Yuuji on his cell phone.
Nay, that's impossible.
His cell phone is in nary an operational state.
They still could've said it over the intercom.
Then does it mean, when Nemoto was talking to someone from Class A...
...it was Kirishima he was talking to?
Good Lord!
Damn! Only Yuuji knew about the plan to make Shimizu angry.
Did he tell you anything?
Nothing.
Hostility
Lie
Why did Nemoto do this?
Could it be that he knows what we're planning?
No, it's more likely that he's also trying to buy time.
Lie
He's trying to prevent us from making any moves until he figures out Class D's real intentions.
Now you've done it, Nemoto!
It's almost time, isn't it?
M-Minami!
I'm only here for the discussion with Class D, got it?
What can we do, Akihisa?
There's only one thing we can do.
If Yuuji isn't here to guide us, we'll just have to do something by ourselves!
Question 10:
Consider the
following situation
and answer
the question.
You are lost in a forest and
all alone. As you advance
without a torch through
the dark forest, you find
a tiny cabin on the shore
of a lake. You are delighted
at your discovery and
enter the cabin to find
a chair, a bed, and a portrait.
Describe three characteristics
of the person in the portrait.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
1. A cheerful face
2. Gentle eyes
3. Bright surroundings
Teacher's comment:
This is a psychological test to
determine what features you'd
look for in the person you'll
fall in love with. The dark forest
represents your anxiety.
The portrait you found represents
the person who supports you
when you're anxious.
It seems the person you love is
a cheerful, gentle, and fun person.
Shimizu Miharu's answer:
1. Unflinching eyes
2. A manly chest
3. A ponytail
Teacher's comment:
The last one is slightly weird.
Shimada Minami's answer:
1. Broken fingers
2. Twisted, bent knees
3. Dislocated wrist
Teacher's comment:
All of these are weird.
Sissy, I missed you!
What the... Get off, Miharu!
Your chest is just like a calm ocean!
Flat
She's calling her as flat as the horizon, isn't she?
I said, let me go!
I always think of you 360 days out of the year!
So she forgets about her during Obon and the New Year?
Halt, Shimizu!
Shimada is Akihisa's lover! Unhand her!
There it is! The operation is go!
What are you talking about? Are you dreaming?
There's nothing going on between Sissy and that swine.
It's written all over her face.
I don't think that pig is even suitable for Sissy in the first place!
I know I'm not cool, and I suck at studying, but—
Cool? Studying?
I'm not talking about something so trivial.
That's not it at all.
I've always been watching how you two interact,
and you, swine, are the worst man I've ever seen.
I've seen the difference in how you talk to Himeji and Sissy, even though they're both from your class.
You're so nice and considerate toward Himeji, as if she's some princess from a fairy tale,
but you don't show Sissy even a bit of the kindness a girl deserves!
I'll be frank.
This pig doesn't see a speck of the charm Sissy has.
He dares to treat her as if she's just another male friend of his!
There's no way I'd measure his suitability for Sissy on the basis of appearance or academics.
On top of that, even if it was all an act,
she said she loved you, yet you ran after Himeji!
Admit it! You think of her as a man, don't you?!
Minami!
Are you going to go after her?
Will you try to cheer her up in the unrestrained way you talk to your friends?
Won't you ever stop hurting her?
I'll go.
Thou wouldst only make it worse.
I don't know what just happened, but I guess I should leave too.
I don't know what the purpose of this meeting was supposed to be, but know this.
I don't think of you as a rival for my love anymore.
It's useless to try making me jealous of an animal too blind to notice how charming Sissy is.
The only one who does...
is me.
Shimizu.
Do you still have something to say?
There's something I want to tell you. Please hear me out.
Fellow classmates, we're going to declare an ESB on Class F!
How could this be?!
I thought the meeting failed.
So what do we do now?
It's not easy for us to win with our weakened forces.
Relax! I prepared for that as well!
Yuuji!
It was actually a lie by Nemoto.
My mother was fit as a fiddle.
Thank God for that.
Well done, Akihisa.
It wasn't how I planned it, but you managed to piss off Shimizu.
So Yuuji, how are we gonna defeat Class D?
We can't beat them in an all-out battle.
We'll ask them for a battle between the class reps!
So you had the balls to show up, after all.
Same to you.
I didn't want to fight Sissy to begin with.
I'll be satisfied if I can crush that animal into a pulp.
That's how it is, Akihisa. It's your show now.
Do it!
Thanks, Yuuji!
I'll never forgive you. Prepare yourself!
Professor, please grant us permission.
Granted!
Summon!
There's something I want to ask first.
What?
Did you lie just to incite this battle?
So you did.
Sissy was crying
because of what I said,
but you... you are the real reason!
She's sad because you are in her life!
Gender
1-h sword
Student of Class D
Points
Gender
Woodsword
Student of Class F
Points
Why is this insect by her side?
Why does she talk to this monster, who only toys with her heart?!
You... You used her for your own benefit! You would lie through your teeth if you had to!
How dare you remain at her side, pretending to be her friend?!
It wasn't a lie!
I know I'm an idiot, but I know what I should and shouldn't lie about!
I don't believe you! I won't believe you!
Those were my true, unwavering feelings!
I won't be fooled by your lies!
That's enough!
Yuuji, what are you...
Leave the rest to us.
This is cowardly! It's foul play!
So what if it is?!
This isn't a competition! This is war!
Yuuji!
Go.
Yuuji, I won't let you—
Why are they attacking me?!
It hurts like hell! Hey!
I can't take any more!
Shimizu!
Now that he's been punished, will you let that incident slide?
Let's see. I don't think I've quite let out all my anger yet.
I'll make it so that he spends the rest of his life taking supplementary lessons.
Was this the plan all along?
I'm sorry, man. You know we couldn't have won against Class D otherwise.
The only way out was to call for a truce.
It was your fault for hurting Sissy in the first place!
I apologize! I apologize from the bottom of my heart—
If that really was a lie, I won't forgive you so easily,
Gender
1-h sword
Student of Class D
Points
Gender
Woodsword
Student of Class F
Points
Gender
Woodsword
Student of Class F
Points
Student of Class D
but I'll let you off with this for now.
Our negotiations are successful then.
Listen up, men! We're pulling back!
Welcome!
And thus, the war was over.
Any updates, Voyeur?
It looks like Nemoto and Class B have given up.
Aye, 'tis sound.
There's nothing in it for him to fight us now.
Furthermore, I managed to retrieve this.
Wassat?
I don't know what the purpose of this meeting was supposed to be,
Is this from that time?
but know this. I don't think you're even worth talking to anymore.
The audio records from the meeting.
Wait! Don't play everything back!
Hold him down real tight.
Aye.
Let go, Hideyoshi!
I do not think so!
Won't you shut up already?
Do you still have something to say?
There's something I want to tell you. Please hear me out.
I want to clear something up.
I already know you were just pretending to go out with Sissy.
No, not that. Um...
Just that... you're not the only one who knows that Minami is charming.
What nonsense is this?
You're always insulting her! You don't treasure her as a girl!
It's true I don't treat her like a princess.
I do talk to her like she's a male friend, all rude and unrestrained.
But you know what?
What? Go on.
I think the Minami I can talk to freely...
the Minami I can have fun with...
the Minami who sometimes shows me her cute, sweet side...
I think that, yeah...
she's a very charming girl.
Wow, I didn't expect that.
Aye, I never thought he could be so straightforward.
H-He was so frank.
I-I didn't want you to hear it.
Especially not now!
You really say things no one else can.
It made my heart beat faster.
How manly.
My life is over!
Noin, wave!
Big Sis, welcome home!
T-Thanks.
What's wrong? Your face is all red!
Hazuki, what do I do?
What's wrong?! Did something happen at school?!
Listen, Hazuki.
Yes?
Your sister is...
helplessly in love.
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem.
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby.
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you.
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N.
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go.
I've fallen in love.
I don't want any doubts in my heart.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Sparkling, glittering.
The right answer is pop!
I'm so dead.
How am I gonna apologize to Minami?
Yo!
What's with the gloomy face, Aki?
M-Minami?!
What?
No! Um... Uh...
I'm sorry about yesterday!
What? Did you do something again?
No! I'm talking about...
I'll punish you really hard if you stir up any more trouble, okay?
Idiot.
Question 11:
Answer the
following question.
What do you call
someone you've been
very close to in your
childhood?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
A childhood friend.
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
Do you have any childhood friends?
The friends you make when you're young are usually
friends for life. They're a rare treasure to find after you've grown up.
I hope you take advantage of the moment and make lots of friends.
Sakamoto Yuuji's answer:
Childhood fr— Aaargh!
Kirishima Shouko's answer:
Fiancée.
Question 11.
What do you call someone you've been very close to in your childhood?
Childhood fr— Aaargh!
Fiancée.
Next time: Yuuji, and Shouko, and their childhood memories.
Next time:
Yuuji, and Shouko, and their childhood memories
their childhood memories
This will be on the test.