I have no wishes anymore
Chaika - The Coffin Princess
My hope was hard as rock, and now it is brittle
My body is battered and broken,
and I will not last long
But I will look back on my proud life
with a mask of false courage
The reason flowers blossom
is to say goodbye and wither
This is the law of the world
All of mankind is cruel
We betray and we are betrayed
Goodnight, let us sleep now
You will hear a song
A sad, sad song
A song about you
Fill the blackness
The floating fortress dispatched by the Republic of Centr and the Wiepr Kingdom has been shot down.
Other nations have been attacked by the Principality of Hartgen, as well.
It's believed that Hartgen is using a powerful Gundo to attack them.
Shall we prepare to counterattack?
Not yet. Once we open fire, there's no going back.
We'll wait for the Gillette Squad's report.
What's going on? What about the tournament?
Who cares?!
Hey! The throne room is in chaos!
What?!
Hey! Chaika, wait!
The Girl Who Carries the Gundo
Chaika! You okay?
Layla's words, true.
I am tool. Purpose served.
No reason to live.
We will relocate to a new castle.
Come, The Gustilator.
Brother!
Toru!
Shin.
Accompany the emperor.
Yes.
Hang in there, Brother.
Akari, run.
Chaika's Gundo is in the corner of the room.
Leave this place to us.
Captain, inform headquarters.
Thank you!
Do you think there's anything you can do now, half-Chaika?
Give back remains!
Dear me. After I was kind enough to let you escape...
You...
What will you all do?
I...
Brother...
Akari, as of this moment, I'm no longer a saboteur.
You and I are no longer brother and sister.
Brother, don't go.
Fredrica, I will contract with you.
Toru, eat my flesh.
Otherwise, you'll die.
Fredrica, let's go.
I will defeat Gaz.
Toru! I go with!
Be safe.
Toru, want to go with!
Sorry.
Toru!
Why?
Shin, I'm sure you think my behavior is strange.
Ah, no...
All the technology that I have developed
is merely a gateway to much deeper magic research.
If this castle and the Guys in the heavens are linked,
the thoughts and feelings of all people
on the continent will flow into me ceaselessly.
There is still much that I must do.
What is that?
Emperor Gaz is back? It can't be!
Gaz intends to start another war,
and take in all the resulting fear and despair swirling about the continent
to make it his own magic source.
He has already killed King Hartgen.
Our questioning within the castle revealed that the Principality of Hartgen's armaments are trivial.
The black Chaika spread baseless rumors
in an attempt to get King Hartgen to start a war.
Gaz set up all of this.
I see. I'll relay this to General Fyodor and the council.
Give back!
Give back remains!
The remains are gone.
She consumed all of the remains and brought Gaz back.
Brought back Father?
This is perfect.
I'll make you into dolls, too.
These girls are like Arina and Irina,
my adorable little dolls.
The half-Chaika can be your toy, girls.
I'll play with the red one.
What's going on here?
Gaz is back?!
Yes.
Should we attack?
No. We'll return immediately.
What?
Our army alone can't stand against him.
If we go there now, Gaz gets exactly what he wants.
Fredrica! Get us in, no matter what you have to do!
Bust in anywhere!
Barrier...
Come, that which bursts and scatters!
The Burster!
Chaika...
Okay, Fredrica! Keep blasting at it!
I didn't expect him to come this far.
He has earned my praise.
Allow me to take care of him.
Fredrica! Go in!
This is Gaz's device for absorbing feelings,
the "Guy"?
It appears that once the first one is activated,
it goes on to activate the next one, and so forth.
He must be planning to link them all to the one that came down for him.
How long do we have before they're all activated?
I don't know the details,
but it will most likely be complete by tonight.
If that happens, all of our thoughts and feelings will become Gaz's.
Is there nothing we can do?
Where's your brother and the white girl?
They went to defeat Gaz.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear.
Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy these.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
Toru.
Absorb feelings...
Will not allow!
So you've given up being a saboteur.
Back off, Shin.
Fredrica, stay out of this.
Does this mean you finally understood my words?
That had nothing to do with it. I chose this.
Fredrica.
That's right, Toru.
You're not cut out to be a saboteur.
That is best for you...
Emperor Gaz awaits.
Consider it an honor that he has consented to see you.
Are they immortal?!
They must have a weakness!
Nikolai, you're late!
Come, that which blows all away.
The Blast!
That which protects, come undone!
The Breaker!
Don't forget...
I fulfilled our objective.
It was I who brought Father back.
So what?!
Did they get the black one?
No effect...
Toru...
Come, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Gaz...
I have lived for five hundred years
by replacing my own body through magic.
In doing so, I have reached a conclusion.
Humans forever seek war.
Humans kill other humans for anger, for hatred, and for love.
A hundred, even two hundred years later,
humans will kill one another
for the most trivial of reasons.
What is it that you hold in your heart right now?
You are proof of all that is human.
If you desire battle so deeply, you should work under me.
Quiet.
I have observed everything you all have done.
Most of my body was carried here on your back,
embraced within your heart.
You have my praise. You did splendid work.
I'll gut you.
Fredrica!
Humans hold within their hearts the intent to kill.
A stimulus no bigger than a thorn
gives that intent control over their hearts.
What did you say?
Your heart is now filled with the intent to kill.
You turn your blades upon me because you cannot restrain it.
It is humans like you who respond to my expectations
and do the best work for me.
Serve me.
Nobody's listening to what you say.
You lived for five hundred years, and that's all you've got?
I'm disappointed.
Try being reborn one more time, bastard!
Your existence fascinated me.
But now I'm tired of it.
The Shield!
Hmm... Number 357, eh?
My wand.
Eliminate.
Establishing target.
Target is...
Unable to lock on target.
What?
Cannot eliminate Chaika.
Niva... Why?
I have personality.
Please load charges.
Out of magic fuel.
Convert from magic fuel consumption mode
to memory consumption mode?
Yes.
Target sighted.
Destroy target?
Yes. I give father funeral.
Activating attack magic.
Zikra, azulwa, istatu...
Come, to overwhelm and defeat.
The Meraviglios!
Brother...
Chaika...
Sir Gillette!
The floating fortresses in space went dark!
Did that saboteur...
Chaika...
What did you do?
Hey!
Wake up, Chaika.
Please...
Don't leave me alone.
Chaika!
Five years after the war's end,
after continuing to threaten the continent even following his death,
the Taboo Emperor, Gaz, used the remains gathered by the Chaikas
to return to life using magic,
but destroyed himself shortly after.
He and the floating fortresses vanished completely.
Many girls believed to be Chaika,
his alleged daughter, are confirmed dead.
We have retrieved the emperor's fortune, the Gundo, as well.
We have thus determined the issues regarding the
Taboo Emperor and his daughter, Chaika, to be resolved.
Chief Gillette, you have truly done magnificent work.
Give the Nikolai Squad my thanks for their efforts, as well.
Thank you, sir.
Officer Konrad!
Please, none of that.
I'm still not used to that title.
Chief Gillette, why don't you take some time off?
No, as you can see, I have too much work to do.
I've traded my sword for a pen,
but it's not an easy thing to wield, is it?
Chief, how is your wound coming along?
What, this? It's only a scratch.
To me, it's nothing more.
Irritating!
Fix door, when?!
It won't be fixed until Brother fixes it.
I won't fix it.
Gift.
Thanks as always.
What writing?
A tale of the intense love between two saboteurs.
Finished writing?
No, this is only the prologue.
Their journey of love is only just beginning.
White girl, where?
Out for a walk with Brother.
She seems to be feeling well today.
Watch your step there.
Thank you.
I live on in you
I live inside you,
twisted and tainted
The ark of our genes
rocks on the water,
sailing for the end times
All that I can offer you
is the day our curse was broken,
but one day, one day,
we will meet again,
as long as you wait for me on this Earth
What is there to be lamented?
I think on the proof we lived together
and bite into my beautiful lips
I will devote my life, my love,
and whatever time I have left
to you