Student Council Room
President,
please review these.
Got it!
Basketball Club, you're approved!
Volleyball Club, you're approved!
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
You're approved! And you're approved!
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
Oogai Middle School
Approval
Student Council
You're good too, Science Club!
Then please review the next batch, as well.
Got it!
You're approved, and you're approved, and you're approved...
Wow, Mana's super busy!
Mana, you need to hurry!
It's almost time for your meeting with the advisors.
Got it!
After that, you need to help out the Kendo Club at 4,
and we'll meet Aguri at Solitaire at 5.
Got it!
We'll be helping out around the shop there today.
Sure.
Oh, time for her milk.
Here you go, Ai!
Drink up!
I feel bad for how busy Mana is.
She gets so swamped that she'd welcome any help available.
Any help available...
I can't help!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Solitaire
Master Davi!
"Master"?
I beg of you,
please teach me how to transform!
Huh?
Trans...
Form?
I want to transform into a human just like you!
Where'd this come from?
When I'm in this form,
I can't help Mana...
I wanna turn into a human and help Mana out!
I see.
Well, if you insist...
Master Davi!
Teach me to do it, too!
I wanna be a human, too!
We beg of you!
Well, when you're in human form,
you can't fly,
you can't call each other,
and there may be other abilities you'll lose in transformation.
Even then, I still want to help Mana!
I want to help Rikka, too!
Me three!
All right then, let's try it.
Hurray!
However...
transforming into a human consumes a lot of power,
so for now, limit yourselves to under an hour.
Okay!
It's All For Mana!
Charles's Big Transformation!
Now then...
Traaaansform!
That was amazing!
She transformed in an instant!
But I don't quite understand how...
Don't worry.
All that matters is wishing to transform from the bottom of your heart.
Wishing to transform from the bottom of your heart...
Yes.
I'm gonna try!
Yeah!
First, imagine the human you want to transform into.
Then, wish strongly...
A girl just like Mana...
A boy around Rikka's age...
A cool dude...
I wanna be that!
What am I, a chair?
Why am I a rain boot?
And what am I a kettle for?!
All right, focus harder and imagine again.
Got it!
This time, I'll be human!
I'll be human!
Traaaansform!
Yay! Transformation Charlmplete!
But I'm pretty Lanshort...
You are the youngest.
I'm the oldest dude here, so why the Chell am I shorter than Charles?
Good question!
Still, you all did well for your first try.
That said, you're not used to it,
so make certain you don't stay human for more than an hour...
Gawn, gawn...
Huh?
Oh, those kids...
Ta-dah!
Who are you?
I'm Charles!
I'm Lance!
Guess who I am!
Huh?
Whaaaaa?!
Are you absotively posolutely Charles?
Charl!
Is that you, Rachel?
I Cheltainly am!
We all Lanceformed just like Davi did!
That's splendid!
I didn't know you could transform!
What a shocker!
Could you all tell me one thing?
Hm?
Why did you turn into humans?
Well, uh...
I've always wanted to study and Chelxercise with Rikka!
Cool, way to show teen spirit!
I want to sing lullancebies for Alice!
My, how pleasant!
Ooh, me! Me!
I want to be Mana's Charlssistant!
Charles...
You did say you felt bad for how busy Mana was.
Thank you!
With all that said, perhaps you could acknowledge their determination?
I'm asking as well.
I understand.
This is proof that you fairies have matured.
I ask each one of you to please support your partners, even as humans.
Gotcha!
Clicky, clicky, clicky...
I'm Charlnished!
Here, Mana!
Wow, you did great!
Thanks a ton!
All right!
Time to Chel some homework!
Oh, I already finished my homework during lunch.
Huh?
Then, I'll go Chelk dinner!
Actually, I finished that this morning!
That's right, you're Rikka...
I can't Chelp at all!
Come on, that's not it.
I'm happy just by having you around.
But...
Alice,
I'll help you sleep with a lullanceby.
Gooo to sleeeep, gooo to sleeeep,
gooo to sleeeep...
It seems he sang himself to sleep.
Indeed.
He's rather adorable.
It's as though I've gained a younger brother.
Indeed.
Alice, Laynce me on the bed...
La lala lalaaaa...
I'm totally gonna help Mana again today!
Thanks, Charles!
It's great that you could help Mana.
I couldn't find any way to help Rikka.
I already said I was happy just having you around.
Fine!
Then I'll just never leave Rikka's side!
I'm gonna help Mana out even more!
I can't wait for school to end so I can do loads of Mana's work!
Charles seems really happy.
It's making my heart race, too!
Let's see...
What should I gobble up today?
Let's take the opportunity to lure the Precures out and find the location of the princess.
And steal more spotlight from the three stooges, as well.
Yay, school's out!
Transform!
Lucky you...
I want to transform, but I turn into an elementary schooler.
I'll just work twice as Charld for you!
President, who's she?
Um...
Well, she asked to be hired as an assistant...
I'm Charles!
Nice to Charlmeet you!
"Charlmeet"?
Oh, Chorry...
I mean, uh, nice to meet you!
Now then, give me any work you please!
Could you staple these documents for me?
Leave it to Charles!
Let's see...
Finished!
That was fast!
What should I do next?
Well, can you take inventory for the equipment we'll use for the cultural festival?
Gotcha!
Check, check, and check!
I finished!
That was fast!
And it's perfect!
The president has some impressive acquaintances!
You're an excellent assistant!
I know, right?
Charles is always helping me out!
And you two look so much alike.
Almost like sisters!
Hey, Aida, do you have a minute?
Sure, what is it?
I need this handed to the Student Council President of Second Middle School ASAP.
Can you go?
They seem to be extremely important documents.
I'll go.
Please, allow me.
Okay, you've got it.
Thanks.
But President!
You have a meeting for the cultural festival soon,
and you're scheduled to help the volleyball team after that...
Oh yeah!
Geez, if only there was a second me...
Let me do it!
Charles, out for delivery!
I'm so Charlighted to be helpful to Mana!
If Mana were here...
I'll help you with your Charluggage!
Why, thank you for your kindness!
Be Charleful!
I'm so sorry!
Mommy!
Thank you for saving my son.
Oh, you're Charlcome.
Wait wait wait wait wait!
I got it back...
An hour's Charlapsed!
But can I give up on helping Mana?
Charltainly not!
Charles is late...
Is she okay?
Man, First Middle's tough.
Our school keeps losing like chumps.
But I wanna win today, even if I have to cheat!
Then again, a win doesn't mean a thing if the match isn't fair.
It doesn't?
Aw, just cheat.
Huh?
We shall grant...
Your desire two-fold!
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Self!
A Selfish?
It's you two again!
Get 'em, Selfish!
Mash their matches to mush!
Sniper Serve!
I heard a dark heartbeat!
Huh?
It's a dark heartbeat!
Let us go.
One more Sniper Serve!
Everyone, this way!
Hurry!
Mana! Rikka!
Are you girls all right?
Yeah.
Girls, let's go!
Precure Love Link!
Wait, Charles is gone!
Is she still in her human form?
She was helping me with work...
In that case, she might not have heard the dark heartbeat!
I'll go look for Charles!
Go.
We shall handle the situation here.
I owe you one. I've gotta go!
Seeeelf!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
We'll face you!
Now we got us a match!
Selfish Selfish go go go!
Saintly Sniper Serve!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
I shall finish you!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love loooove!
Court change!
The Ace Shot didn't work?
This guy's got two faces.
If you defeat his first one,
you'll still have to contend with the other!
Right there is when his other face reveals itself!
That's when he activates a Court Change,
meaning he can fight forever!
What should we...
Don't worry. We'll just attack both sides.
Indeed.
We shall combine my Ace Shot with your Lovely Force Arrow!
But Heart isn't here.
Haha, it seems it's the perfect day for our victory!
This serve is for the gold, Selfish!
Right! Saintly Sniper Serve!
Phew, I finally Charlivered it...
I'm Charlexhausted...
Charles!
Mana?
A Selfish appeared!
The girls are fighting!
Huh? But I didn't Charlhear a dark heartbeat...
There may be other abilities you'll lose in transformation.
That's why I couldn't Charlhear it...
I'm sorry!
I didn't listen to Davi!
It's Charll my fault!
It's not Charll your fault.
It's mine, too.
After all, you turned into a human for my sake.
So this time, I'll do my best to help you!
Mana...
Let's go, Charles!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
I have to hurry!
Your time's about up, ain't it?
This match is ours!
Don't worry, I know Heart will come!
Indeed, she will!
Girls!
Sorry I'm late!
I'm sorry!
Cure Heart!
We've been waiting!
Great, let's go!
You girls shall aim at its front!
I shall aim at its back!
Gotcha!
We have but one chance!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Love love looooove!
Love!
"Invincible" my gut!
Don't you whine to me!
Hmph!
Huh?
Everyone...
This was all my fault, so I'm sorry.
You just wanted to lighten Mana's load.
I know how you feel, Charles.
You want to help the people you love.
Same here.
You know, I was so happy that you tried so hard to help me.
Juujou even said we looked like sisters.
I really think of you like a little sister, Charles.
Because I love you!
Mana...
Um, excuse me...
We owe our thanks to a student from this school.
She helped me, too.
I wanted to thank her again, but I didn't catch her name...
She was all "Charl", right?
Oh, that's her!
She kept saying "Charl"!
Do you know who that might be?
We do!
Her name is Charles, and she's splendid in many ways.
She's a good friend of ours.
She's always helping us out, too.
I'll tell her you were here.
Bye-bye!
Charles!
Charles, I'm so proud of you!
Mana...
Girls...
Leave it to Charles!
You've all deepened your bonds with your fairies and reached a greater stage, no?
Bravo!
Aguri...
The time has come.
I shall present to you your final trial.
Our final trial?
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
Watch Us Again!