Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Challengers, adventurers, pioneers:
those who answer to that
kind of name are all fools.
Smart ones follow those fools,
and they praise those who
succeed and laugh at those who fail.
And a star will never
stop challenging herself
and trying to be a real star.
Even though she is laughed at,
she never stops running.
This fool aims high,
aspiring to be a real Kaleido Star, the
likes of which have never been seen before.
Sora Naegino...
I will not acknowledge
that you're a Kaleido Star.
Never!
"An Amazing New Rival."
He is just so wonderful.
Those mysterious eyes are just so...
Irresistible!
Mr. Leon...
I'll see you very soon.
Mom, Sora will be in the show. Right?
Will she be in the show a lot?
Yes.
Where's Sora?
Isn't she here yet, Mia?
Not yet.
Ken, she's not in the
dressing room or the lobby!
I wonder where she went?
Sora is such a bad girl!
Miss Sarah, you look too happy.
My sixth sense tells me
that she's in an absurd place!
So why do you look so happy?
She must think she's such a big
shot to be late on a day like this.
Right, Jonathan?
Marion, didn't you come
here to help your father?
That's what I told you.
But really, though...
I came here to see Leon Oswald!
Oh... Of course.
The prince of the circus world from France.
The Pegasus of the stage.
He's one of the top talents in the world!
And his past is shrouded in mystery.
So mysterious...
This is no time to talk
about something like that!
Today's the first day that she's
going to perform with Mr. Leon.
She still lacks a sense of being a draw.
Sora, where did you go?!
Found her!
What?!
Look!
What is she doing?
Since Miss Layla is gone,
we lost some of our audience, so...
I think Sora worries about it in her
own way, so she's advertising the show.
Shoot!
I'm also going there.
Please don't, Anna.
Why can't I?
Kaleido Stage is fun!
Everyone--
Here!
She did it!
Awesome!
You're great!
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
I wonder if my advertising helped a little.
You guys, please come
visit Kaleido Stage too.
It is a very wonderful show
which combines a play and acrobatics.
I already know that.
But Miss Layla's not there.
Anyway, do that thing again!
But, I have to get going soon...
Sorry.
OK! I'll do it just one more time!
Shoot! I have to hurry!
Oh, I'll take a shortcut!
Please come visit Kaleido Stage!
Uh...
The worldwide top star, Mr. Leon Oswald,
will appear on stage starting today!
Since this "Saiyuki" is a love story,
we can't start without Sora,
who plays the princess!
Everyone, for the time
being, please get ready.
She's here!
Sora's here!
OK! We're opening the show, stand by!
Let's start!
Sorry I'm late!
You're late!
What were you thinking?
Boss. Well...
Since Mr. Leon came all the way here,
I thought it would be nice
if I advertised the show a little!
You should think carefully
about what you're supposed to do!
What? That's why I thought
I should advertise and...
Even a fur seal can do something like that.
You can do that?
I understand what Boss wants to say.
But I still can't draw in the audience
doing just my show like Miss Layla, so...
Sorry!
Really, you're hopeless.
Change quick.
Okay.
Oh, um, Mr. Leon. I'm very sorry.
Finally, it's time to perform
in front of the audience.
I'll do my best.
So I look forward to performing with you.
You don't need to appear on stage.
What? I don't?
I can handle the stage myself.
What?
He's so cool!
It's no time to be saying this!
What are you going to do, Sora?
I'll go on stage, of course!
I don't think he was serious
about doing it all himself!
I'll go change clothes quickly.
Huh?
I can't reach.
If you want to take it off, I will help you.
Thanks.
Fool?!
But I only want you to
take off the animal costume!
I'm well aware of that!
Fine. Then please.
Sure.
Damn.
You just said "damn," didn't you?
You said "damn"!
Did not!
Now stay still. You don't have much time.
--Damn...
--You did say it! You did, you did, you did!
C'mon, hurry!
I thought you'd go to heaven or something
after we perfected the
legendary great maneuver.
I'm a spirit, not... a... ghost.
I made Mr. Leon mad.
But he'll forgive me if I work really
hard and make the show exciting, right?
Your constellation is Sagittarius.
It is the sign for heading
straight for your dream.
But you don't have enough radiance yet.
The road to true stardom is still a long one.
Please be my dream, Sora.
I'm going to be Miss Layla's dream?
That's right.
I know you can become a true Kaleido Star.
I am...
You don't need to be depressed.
You can see me,
--That's all right. Leave me alone!
--which means that you're--
I just have to do my best however I can.
That's all! That's all! That's all!
Oh, I remember...
So cute!
Good. They like it.
It looks like my first
strategy worked just fine.
Then go to the second strategy!
Why must I...
Hopefully, with this Mr. Leon will...
He's not there?!
I wonder what happened.
Wait a minute.
I don't believe it. He's leaving!
Is he really leaving?
Sora!
You're awesome!
What? What is going on?
Mr. Leon...
Please go back to the stage.
Change of plans. We're going to
put on the clown show right here.
Mr. Leon!
Um...
Please wait!
We're still in the middle of the show!
If we have to show them a
half-done job, it's better not to do it.
But that's not nice to the audience
who took the time to come here.
The audience came here to see me at my best.
A show in which I don't shine is meaningless.
But don't we go out on stage
to make the audience happy?
So I think the show must go on.
You have it backwards.
What?
I'm not here for the audience.
The audience is here for me.
I have the greatest
technical skill in the world.
The audience needs only
come to the theater to admire me.
If I knew Kaleido Stage was a place
that puts on stupid performances
to pander to the audience,
I wouldn't have come here in the first place.
There are children who don't
know anything about your skills.
Those kids are not my audience.
Who knew the one who perfected
that legendary great maneuver
was this kind of person?
I shouldn't have come to this place.
Even if you do have the best
technical skills in the world,
I don't like you.
But the current Kaleido Stage needs you.
And my skills alone can't draw
in the audience like in old times.
So, please.
Please don't leave, Mr. Leon!
Not my problem.
The clown show is about to finish.
What?! No way! What shall we do?
We have no choice.
We have to cancel.
Is it okay, Boss?
All right.
No!
You can't cancel the show!
If Mr. Leon won't be in the show,
I will finish it by myself if I have to!
What?!
That sounds interesting.
If I manage to finish the show all by myself,
will you remain at Kaleido Stage?
I will not make any promises.
If you want to do it, go
ahead, do as you want.
You should learn that the
audience is a performer's enemy.
What?
Why does the audience have to be our enemy?
Playing both roles means
you have to do your maneuvers as well
as Mr. Leon's continually without a break.
Physically, it's impossible.
Also, what are you going to do with the last
scene where the two of them meet again?
Don't worry.
I'll make sure to pull it off.
So, Ken. I have to ask you a favor.
Okay.
That's not Mr. Leon!
What's going on?
I'm going to pull this off no matter what!
No matter what!
Good! I can do this!
Miss Layla entrusted Kaleido Stage to me...
No matter what happens, I have to protect it.
In order to protect Kaleido Stage,
we need Mr. Leon.
No matter what kind of person he is.
Those kids are not my audience.
Those children are also an
important part of the audience.
Just like when I was a child and
I saw the show for the first time.
It was whimsical and it was fun.
I forgot myself in watching the show.
That is the Kaleido Stage.
--Hurry!
- -Okay!
Good luck.
Thanks.
That was a quick change...
I'm not allowed to show a tired look.
Here!
Even Sora must have reached her limit,
since she's been going nonstop.
I've never seen a person as reckless as her.
I've never seen anyone who
goes as far as she does, either.
But the one who becomes a real
shining star could be someone like her.
Destroying monsters while spinning...
Can she do it?
Landing on top of that mountain
while spinning is difficult in and of itself...
Since she is staggering that much,
she has no choice but to slow down the spin.
But...
if she does that, the
maneuver will be incomplete.
She's speeding up?
What?!
She's so awkward.
I can't keep watching her.
But...
Without a doubt,
I've never seen her type before.
Sora Naegino...
The last scene is the
reunion with the princess.
Go!
Go for it!
From this point, the directing will
change depending on Sora's ideas.
So, I will give you instructions.
Roger that.
Ken, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Okay, turn off the light.
A-5, turn the spot light on.
Wow! It's the princess!
You're right!
There's the princess!
All right, she is doing well.
It's so pretty.
Turn the light off.
Turn the B light on.
Okay.
I pulled it off!
In the last scenes, I should throw
myself into the protagonist's state of mind.
And hold her gently with all my love.
Leon!
Bring out Mr. Leon!
Take a hike!
Leon! Leon! Leon! Leon!
I'm scared.
Leon! Leon! Leon! Leon! Leon! Leon!
You should learn that the
audience is a performer's enemy.
Her performance went well, but they...
This isn't good.
What?
How pitiful, Sora Naegino.
Excuse me?
You were rejected as Leon
Oswald's partner, weren't you?
Isn't that why you're performing for two?
What shall we do?
Uh... Well... Well...
I don't care. Let them continue.
Yes, sir.
What?
Is she a trapeze artist?
Eternal Angel Turn!
She uses the swing so easily and freely.
Dream Spiral!
Amazing...
She's so bold, and her performance
is overflowing with confidence.
Do you understand?
I can be Leon's partner.
But you cannot, Sora Naegino.
Who is that?
I believe she's the girl who passed with
the highest scores in this year's audition.
What's going on?
Is this part of the show?
I wonder if it is.
Mr. Leon!
But she's pretty cute, isn't she?
She is totally my kind of gal.
Excuse me... Who are you?
Me?
I'm the next Layla Hamilton!
What?
I'm going to kick you out.
And I will be the Kaleido Star.
From now on, I won't let you call yourself
a Kaleido Star when you have no talent.
Do you understand?
Mr. Leon!
If either of them could be my partner,
it might be worth it to
stay on a little longer.
Mr. Leon...
I changed my mind.
I wouldn't mind staying here a little longer.
Really?
Then you'll appear on stage with me--
Not with you. With me!
Mr. Leon certainly is great.
He can see how talented I am!
Both of you. Ad-lib and follow me.
Let's go!
Yes!
Wonder...
Arrow!
What is this?
They're fighting.
If I remember right,
that's the girl who passed
audition with the top score.
May Wong...
But why?
I'm going to protect the Kaleido Stage
that Miss Layla entrusted to me!
I'm the one fit to be a Kaleido Star!
Not you!
A new Kaleido Stage has been set in motion...
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
I'm not a kid anymore.
And so, surprisingly,
Rosetta came to us saying that
she wanted to join Kaleido Stage.
But it seems there's some reason behind this.
Sora, please help me.
Of course, I want to stay
with Rosetta, but...
All right!
For my beloved friend,
Rosetta, I'm going to help her out!
I will! I will! I will!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Another Amazing Newcomer."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...