Have some fun? What are you planning?
Why, a battle of course.
A battle? But you're—
Suzuko.
What?
He's a Selector.
I hadn't realized.
But why?
It's one of my LRIG's specialties.
Everyone would be too wary if they knew the Bookmaker was a Selector.
And I wouldn't be able to snack on them either.
Snack on them?
Even I can't avoid having to battle
when my limit approaches.
So I pick out some random prey and devour it in secret.
Though I have to say they're pretty much just junk food to me.
Oh, but his flavor was unexpectedly delicious.
Shirai-kun, wasn't it?
His screams truly whetted my appetite.
So much he almost brought me to a climax.
Don't, Chii-chan.
I'll battle him.
Suzu...
It's okay.
I won't lose.
And there they go with the sickening drama.
Seeing it in person makes me want to throw up.
That's what makes it arousing.
You're such a pervert.
Be sure to satisfy me, Suzuko-chan.
Open.
Born into memories everything is given life
born memory subete ga umare
Everything is erased, everything is overcome
subete wo keshite subete wo koete
The memories that make me whole scream throughout my head
watashi wo kumitateru kioku sakendeiru wa atama no naka
find my real
Where did it all begin to change?
doko kara kawatta no
The things I believed in have all become lost
shinjiteta mono maigo ni natta
Even if the seasons turn
kisetsu wa sugitemo
The place from my memories remains forever unchanging
omoide no basho wa ano koro no mama na no ni
Pull me from this maze of fear
nazo fuan oshiete
Should I continue on?
susunde mo ii no
I'm searching for my past and future
kako mo mirai mo sagashiteru
Dive into memories, if only I could see you
dive memory aetara ii ne
Smiling like you did back then for our promise
ano hi no egao ano yakusoku
In these endlessly repeating days
kurikaesu nichijou no naka
Distorted by the ever-present static
noizu ni makare yugandeku
I still don't know, I still want to, I still can't lose it
mada wakaranai mada motometai mada nakusenai
Flip open the card of your broken heart
oreta mune no kaado wo hiraki
Lost in the storage of my memories
samayou no kioku no naka
find my real
Daybreak
Suzu...
Ril, Grow.
I summon the SIGNI Gareth and Percival.
Turn End!
Guess I'll get started.
Carnival, Grow.
I summon the SIGNI Senya and Antares.
Attack!
Turn End.
Suzuko.
I know. We'll go on the offense and seize the initiative.
Right.
Ril, Grow.
Coin Bet!
Honest!
Reveal every card in your hand.
Oh, sure thing!
We'll be able to deal with those.
Yeah.
I play a SIGNI and full attack.
Turn End.
I should say I'm not surprised, Suzuko-chan.
Huh?
It's obvious how many Selectors you trampled over
and how many precious memories you stole to get here.
Didn't it feel incredible?
Listening to their screams as you finished them off!
I've never—
It's okay! Don't be ashamed!
It's only natural for the strong to devour the weak.
How can you say that as a Selector?
You should know the fear of battling and the pain of losing memories, so why?!
Who can say?
Carnival, Grow.
Coin Bet.
Joker.
Turn Antares into Machupi.
His card changed.
That ability exists?
Banish all her SIGNI!
How...
Full attack!
Ril!
My ability is Joker.
It can even do things like this.
Coin Bet.
Berserk.
Stop...
Suzuko!
Ril, Grow.
You must know it's futile.
Coin...
Bet.
Honest!
Use Honest...
on me!
What happened?
Berserk was...
She used her own feelings of not wanting to attack to cancel it.
This is how Suzu battles...
Yes, that's great!
Suzuko-chan, keep on stimulating me like that!
Battles just gotta make you feel good, you know?
This reminds me of when I was a LRIG.
He was a LRIG?!
Battles were just so delightful.
Savagely scraping at each other's lives.
Looking down on your enemy,
forced to their knees in despair.
But then... the excitement wore off.
Every single one of them clung to their garbage-like memories and destroyed themselves.
Crushing weak bugs isn't bad, but it doesn't feel good either.
Eventually, the Selector I was with disappeared,
and I tried my hand at living in his body,
but what I truly longed for was...
That battle in the gorge between life and death!
That's the instinct of us LRIGs.
Right?
And then I found it, my greatest idea.
I'd become a Selector myself, and play
with the battles however I wanted!
The cards chose me exactly as I wished,
and I got a LRIG of my own.
Carnival is my ideal LRIG,
shaped to my exact preferences.
Once I started spreading rumors of the Bookmaker,
those suckers came biting right away.
As I was enjoying myself watch them kill each other, hoping to escape despair,
I came up with an even happier game to play!
I'd find the strongest person I could who wasn't swayed by garbage memories,
raise her, shatter her, and have
the time of my goddamn life!
You're wrong.
Huh?
Memories...
Emotions aren't garbage.
It is because of mine that I'm standing here right now!
Then just try and kill me with those memories.
Grow. Summon Gaiten and Regulus.
Attack!
Carnival, attack!
Guard with a Servant!
Coin Bet!
Joker!
Eliminate the power of her Servant!
He can even change his opponent's cards?
Hey, Ril.
We were born to battle.
Humans and the world they live in
are just toys for us to battle with.
That's what we LRIGs do.
Don't you agree?
So hey, come. Get over here.
When her ninety days pass, you won't
be able to battle as a LRIG anymore.
But if you become a human, you can be a Selector over and over and battle as much as you want.
It's easy! All you need to do is lose!
Take Suzuko-chan's body as your own!
What are you say—
Come on, Ril.
Let's have fun together in this shitty world!
Ril?
That might be nice.
It's your turn.
Ril, Grow.
Ril, attack!
Ril?
Why?
Because I am a LRIG.
Didn't I just tell you? It's our instinct as LRIGs.
Ril...
This must be a lie...
If you think so, then simply confirm it.
Confirm it?
Coin Bet!
Honest.
Use Honest on Ril.
Ril, tell me how you really feel.
I battle for what I believe in.
That's all.
What you believe in...
Turn End.
Doesn't it feel like you're about to go crazy from the despair of being betrayed by someone you trusted?
Oh damn, I'm getting so hot.
This is going to be the best finish ever.
Carnival, Grow.
Hey, it's no fair for you to get off by yourself.
Okay, go ahead and finish her.
Carnival, attack!
Activate Arts: One Victory Two Spoils.
Stop his attack and damage him!
What?!
Too slow!
She pretended to betray her?
She delayed the timing of his Coin Bet so that Joker couldn't nullify her attack.
Suzuko.
How nice.
They trust each other so deeply.
Mel.
You believed.
Yeah.
So basically, some shitty brat and her shitty LRIG
playing at friends pulled one over on me.
Too bad for you, foolish former LRIG.
This is just perfect. I'll take your hope, your trust,
and everything you want to protect...
And smash it all to pieces!
The mystery concealed in WIXOSS...
It began with a girl named Mayu
Comprehension. Shirai-san is no longer...
I regret it.
I feel like I placed an unreasonable
burden on Suzuko-chan.
Needless. You don't have to worry.
Huh?
Suzuko-san is strong.
Ril, attack!
Spell: Chain Breaking Victory Hymn! Banish Saizo!
Use its banish effect to search for a Rise card!
I trash Annabelle to play Impact!
Life Burst!
Banish Tendou!
Both of them are low on Life Cloth.
And they each have only one coin remaining.
Coin Bet.
Blind.
Turn End.
Even Blind...
Suzuko, it's our turn.
Right. Coin Bet!
Honest!
Tell me exactly which cards you have concealed with Blind and where they're placed.
Bravo! That was a perfectly worded question.
Is this enough for you?
There are no traps.
Yeah!
I summon SIGNI!
All-out attack!
Now he's down to one Life Cloth.
Satomi already used his last coin.
He can't use Joker to change cards anymore.
In other words...
It looks like this'll be my last turn.
Arts: Phosphorescent Samsara.
Let's go wild.
It's coming!
Okay. If I counter it with Arts: River Deluge—
What?
The Multi-ener!
Don't tell me it was then!
Looks like you can't pay the cost of that card!
Too bad!
That was his aim?
It's been fun, Suzuko-chan.
Truly fun.
I'm so impressed with your growth. Now let me get a good look at your face.
Don't worry, I'll always remember you,
as one of my cherished memories.
It's time for the finale. End her, Carnival!
Are you sure, Kou? Can I really destroy your toy?
Suzu...
Mel!
Can't I bet one of my own coins on Suzu?
I'm not sure, but are you serious?
Yes.
No.
Mel!
If Suzu disappears, then you'll—
This is our battle too!
Let's fight together, Mel.
Together...
It's the first time you've said that to me.
Thank you, Mel.
Suzu!
Chii-chan?
Use this!
All in!
Yeah.
Coin Bet!
Requiem.
Wh-What is this?
What'll happen?
I don't know, but probably...
The combined power of Honest and Berserk turned her true wish as a Selector, her strength of heart, into an attack!
What the hell is that?
Read the mood!
You're fucking worthless!
Hurry up...
And drop dead!
Ril won't lose.
We won't lose...
As long as we're together!
It's not over...
The abyss is endless.
As long as you rotting meatbags are
filled to the brim with memories and desires,
the battle will begin anew.
Struggle, anguish, scream, and despair.
I'll be here, laughing down at you.
We won.
Yeah.
I could hear your voice.
Ril, I—
Thank you.
I was only able to come this far thanks to you.
Ril?
Your earnest feelings changed me.
I...
It's only because you were always with me...
That I...
Take good care of Chinatsu.
You earnestly chased after Chinatsu.
So much that it was painful.
Ril!
Do you have any last wishes
regarding your memories?
I want to remember.
I want to always remember you.
I'll never forget.
I won't forget either.
Yeah.
Ril...
Suzu.
Welcome back.
Chii-chan... Ril is...
Ril is gone...
I've had enough of this!
I'm through with battling too.
I'll treasure this memory you protected.
I won't run anymore.
Even if it hurts, I'll look straight ahead.
Just like you.
Yeah...
Sorry I'm late.
Good to see you, Dad.
Hey, did I keep you?
Yeah, just a bit.
Oh, he's back.
I'm home.
Hello.
Welcome back.
We've got a real feast today.
I made it myself.
Hey, is that old candy store we used to visit
in elementary school still around?
Yep, it's still there.
We used to go and buy gummies
and chocolate and ice cream.
We got as much as we could for
a hundred yen and ate it at the park.
And after that, we did homework.
Sorry that I always asked you to help me out.
Well, you were the expert in Japanese though.
Yeah, but it was only that one subject!
Today was so much fun.
Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Chii-chan, it's time.
I know.
So this is goodbye.
Yeah.
Hey, Chii-chan.
Do I resemble Suzu?
I was always too scared to ask.
I'm just a LRIG, and all I can do is battle.
I couldn't be Suzu's replacement.
That's not it.
You're you, Mel.
And not anybody else.
Thank you for always being by my side.
You're my precious friend.
Chii-chan.
Thank you. I had fun, Chii-chan.
Chii-chan, no matter what happens, we'll always...
Be friends... forever.
Flashback to a faint memory just outside my consciousness
flashback bouyaketa mama no kasuka na kioku
It's always kept me going until this very day
zutto tsunaidekureta kyou kono hi made
Someone pulls back their tiny hand
chiisana te wo hiku no ga
Hello.
But I can no longer remember who
dareka omoidasenai
Before I lose the something resounding in my heart, I will fight
mune ni hibiku nanika wo ushinau sono mae ni tatakau
This is a nice place.
Um...
Who are—
I don't want to erase them, no matter the pain in my heart
keshitakunai tatoe mune ga kidzutsuitemo
That's really cute!
I've had it ever since I was a child.
We'll never get those moments back
mou modorenai shunkan wo
I can't remember where I got it though.
But I know it's important.
They're undeletable even against the flow of time
keseyashinai toki ga tattemo
It's irreplaceable.
And one day I'll share them all with you
kasaneta akashi ga itsuka oshieru
I'm Homura Suzuko.
What's your name?
Chinatsu...
Morikawa Chinatsu.
Then you're Chii-chan!
Let's be friends, Chii-chan!
I don't want to erase everything that makes me whole
keshitakunai watashi wo tsukuriageta mono
So I will reclaim it in my heart
ima kokoro ni torimodoshite
I'm undeletable and nobody else
keseyashinai hoka no dare ni mo
Can change who I truly am
hontou no jibun wa kawaranai kara
One day, for sure. Just like those days...
If we're together...
Then one day, for sure.
And finally I can remember
ima nara omoidaseru