It's time.
I'd better go get her.
Now, who should we work on next?
Maybe I'll ask Kanade what she thinks.
Hey.
Hinata!
Otonashi-san.
Naoi!
What are you doing here?!
And where did you come from?
So... did the two of you need something?
Ah, yes.  Where were you headed, Otonashi-san?
Ah, yeah.  Where were you going, Otonashi?
It's none of your business!
It's none of your business.
I've got business with Otonashi!
I'm here to help him accomplish something!
But that would be my role.
You're not necessary.
Get lost.
Good.  Look into my eyes.
You're a roll of toilet paper.
Realize how swiftly toilet paper is washed away.
Hey, now, cut it out!
H-Hey, Hinata!
Please allow me to assist you.
Do you guys even know what I'm trying to do?
Of course.
Of course I do.
You're trying to obliterate us one by one, right?
Coming from you, it sounds more like a crime.
If you think about it, Naoi,
you don't have any regrets now.
I want to be with you.  And besides,
I don't want to be obliterated before him.
Don't stay behind for a reason like that.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Be obliterated.
Nobody asked you.
Say, Otonashi-san, you need a partner, right?
Please use me, Otonashi-san.
Is something the matter?
What is this?  Did you do something again?!
What are you talking about?
I haven't done-
What the hell's this?
Is it an enemy?  Can we shoot it?
It's invading...
Something's invading me, Otonashi-san!
Damn it!!
Hinata!
Can this thing die?
Did we get rid of it?
What was that?
Target intercepted by Hinata-san and Otonashi-san.
It's been exterminated.  No casualties.
A second one showed up, huh?
It'd be natural to assume it's one of Tenshi's new skills, but...
That doesn't sound right to you?
No, it doesn't.
This is an edict to all Battlefront members:
No one is permitted to travel alone.
Move together with a minimum of one other person at all times.
The Shadows will be considered an enemy unrelated to Tenshi.
Be sure to maintain high alert.
Roger.
And you, Yurippe-san?
I'm headed out to eliminate some possibilities.
Student Council President, Tachibana Kanade-san.
Please report to the Student Council room immediately.
Hey, that's Yurippe, isn't it?
I repeat.
What is this about?
Student Council President, Tachibana Kanade-san.
Crap.  She might hear from her what we're trying to do.
Please report to the Student Council room immediately.
That can't be good.
Let's go!
You got it.
What are you guys doing?
Let us listen.
I, as the ex-deputy president and
current vice president, permit them.
Why is this under your jurisdiction?
This is the Student Council room.
Fine.
So?  What are these Shadows?
I don't know.
You didn't program them?
I did not.
Then it could be a bug.
When was the last time you did any programming?
The day before yesterday.
Timing-wise, it's a perfect match.
I'll be sending people into your room, understand?
Takeyama-kun, it's your show.
Roger.
And call me Chr-
So, what sort of program did you write?
Wings.
"Wings"?  You added wings?
So you can fly?
No.  They're for decoration.
"Decoration"?
Yes.  Decoration.
Why?
Because I was told that I would look more like an angel that way.
"Told"?  Who told you that?
Crap...
That would be me.
I felt it would add to her supremacy as president, so I,
the ex-deputy president and
current vice president, suggested it to her.
A president with wings looks supreme, you say?
Yes.
Wings for the president.
I believe it's fitting.
What a dumbass.
By the way, you're being pretty obedient.
You don't seem heartless at all.
No different from how you were before.
No, she is heartless.
As the vice president, I get stabbed by her each day.
Um, why?
When she's in a bad mood, she stabs anything near her.
As the vice president, I'm often nearby, so as a result, I'm stabbed often.
I was stabbed this morning, actually,
and my intestines were hanging out for a while.
But right now, she seems to be in a good mood.
What a dumbass.
Do you copy?  Please respond.
How is it, Takeyama-kun?
I couldn't find any bugs.
Besides, this program is for decoration only, so it's a relatively simple one.
It couldn't possibly produce a bug with a mind of its own that attacks people.
Also, please call me Chr-
What about the other programs?
There's Overdrive in passive mode.  Hand Sonic in active mode.
All of them are just the same as before.  Although their forms look different.
What would you like to do?
Is she going to make him delete it?
She'd have to write it again from scratch.
Hey, did you just hear that gunshot?
What gunshot?  I didn't hear any-
It's coming from outside!
Look!  Over there!
It's those monsters!
My God!  Look at how many of them...
Kanade!  Please!
Yurippe!
Wow...
I'm going, too!
H-Hey!
Otonashi-san!
Are you okay, Yuri?
Otonashi-kun.
Sorry for the wait!
Hit the deck.
I don't need help!
Don't be like that.
How unwise.
Whoa!   Dancing in the shadow!
I kiss you.
I'd hate to get hit with that.
Are you trying to cut us down with them?!
That's just part of my plan.
Take it out next time!
Stop horsing around and support each other!
That was...
Is everyone safe?
Yeah.  What were they?  Are they monsters?
Those freaky creatures never existed in this world before.
Is this some sort of nightmare?
A carnival of nightmares.
Maybe we've been in this world for too long.
What do you mean?
You've seen invincible monsters in games meant to prevent one from being able to play said game forever, right?
That's not funny at all.
At any rate,
she's acting as our ally.
Hey!  Hey!
Fujimaki?
We got a problem...
Takamatsu!  Takamatsu lost!
Those are his glasses.
I saw it.  That Shadow ate him.
"Ate"?
By the time I saw him, he was already completely covered by a Shadow.
I tried to save him, too!
But I couldn't do anything.
In the end, his glasses fell...
Who'd have thought he'd drop his glasses...
How unreal.  And then what happened?
He was sucked into the ground.
"The ground"?
This is too much of an irregularity...
What's going on?  A third party that's not related to any of us is starting to take action.
What exactly is going on?
I found Takamatsu!
Takamatsu-san!
Takamatsu!
What's going on?  Everyone was worried about you.
"Worried"?  Over what?
"Over what"?  You got eaten by that shadow monster!
I don't understand what you're speaking of.
Maybe he doesn't realize what happened?
You got eaten by a Shadow!
And then you got sucked into the ground.
What did you do after that?
What did I do?
I woke up at the dorm and came to school like I do any other day.
"Came to school"?
You're here to attend class in that uniform?
Well, yes.
You'll be obliterated!  Don't you get that?!
"Obliterated"?
What do you mean, "obliterated"?
Holy crap.  He's gone bonkers.
Well, he was to begin with, but still...
Takamatsu...
That's enough, Hinata-kun.
Enough of what?
I'm sorry to say this, but you're interrupting class.
Let's go.
You sure we wanna leave him?
He'll be obliterated!
Just come.
Ooyama-kun!
His reactions just now speak volumes.
I've grasped what's happened to him.
He's turned into an NPC.
H-Hold on!  What does that mean?!
This is too hard.
If he's an NPC, then he doesn't have a soul anymore, right?
In that case, where did his soul go?
Maybe that's what was eaten.
What's that supposed to mean?!
You mean he's even lost the chance to be obliterated and has to take classes here forever?
That's right.
That's...  That's even worse than dying.
So, really forever?  He's locked in here forever?
What kinda sick joke is that?!
Fuck!
That's just screwed up...
So something like this is possible in this world.
It'd be better gettin' obliterated by Tenshi.
Plus, it looks like the Shadow is multiplying.
What do we need to do, Yurippe?
Something strange is starting to happen in this world.
To begin with, the appearance of enemies other than Tenshi.
For lack of originality, we call them Shadows.
Unlike Tenshi, they appear suddenly and attack us at random.
Once eaten by a Shadow, you lose your soul and are turned into an NPC that attends class every day.
Currently, they are multiplying without limit.  The cause is unknown.
We have no countermeasure at this time.
As Yusa-san said earlier, you need to protect each other by staying in groups.
Now, in the midst of this crisis, we have people developing a different ideal within the Battlefront,
and they are trying to lead the organization in a new direction.
That direction could lead to a countermeasure to the crisis we're facing.
So, as the representative of that faction, Otonashi-kun,
could you share your ideal with all of us?
She knew about us.
Go on up.
Screw you!
That's all baseless!
It couldn't be true!
Yeah!  Nothing like that could exist here!
Well it does.
Yui found it.
Even I died as a worthless husk of a person.
But in this world, I was able to give her purpose.
The same applies to me.
I am God...
But Otonashi-san managed to help me regain my human heart,
all with a single pat on the back.
It's entirely your choice which path you take.
What about you?  What will you do, Yurippe?
Me?  I've always done what I want to.
I can't protect you all, either.
So I'll continue to do what I want.
We don't have much time.
All of you should give it much thought.
That's all.  Dismissed!
You have a moment?
What do you want, Yuri?
Make her work to intercept the Shadows.
Kanade?  Why?
She's more suited for fighting without thought.
At least, based on what I saw.
So you were watching...
Man, we can't deceive Yurippe's eyes, can we?
But Kanade is on our side.  She should stay with us!
So are all the other members.
To protect them, we need her strength.
We need her great strength, which she used to fight against the Battlefront for so long.
You're right.  It's a fitting role for her as an angel.
She's not an angel, you know?
Huh?!  What did you just say?!
I said she's not an angel.
She's a human just like us.
You never realized?
God is omniscient.
You're shaking.
Y-You're not an angel?
"I'm not an angel."
I'm certain I said that to you when we first met.
She was calling you an angel or whatnot.
I'm not an angel.
She did!
Yeah, a lot's happened since, hasn't it?
This is all your fault!
In that case, why is Kanade here?!
Why wasn't she obliterated for being the Student Council President?
She must have her reasons for staying here.
Right...
Then just like us, she has some kind of regret.
We'll need to take care of that, too.
Right?
So, Yuri...  What will you do?
There's something I want to find out.
Are you going to fight against the Shadows?
If it's necessary.
It's dangerous to go alone!
What can I do?  I gave everyone the freedom to choose.
I'm sure some will follow you.
They need time to think.
It's an important decision.
Yeah... it is, but...
If everyone's been obliterated and has safely left this world by the time I return,
then I'll believe you did what you had to do.
Stop that!  I'll be waiting!
Don't be an idiot.  If you wait alone, the Shadows will get you.
You should leave this world before that happens.
Don't worry about me.
No, we will worry.
Hinata-kun...
What are you saying all of a sudden?
This Battlefront started with just us two.
We spent lots of time together, didn't we?
So we'll end it together.
I won't leave without you.
You're such an idiot, as always.
Sentiment won't solve a thing.
Enemy!  Enemy raid!
Kanade-chan, please go.
Hand Sonic: Version 5.
Well, we'll meet again if we can.
Yurippe!
What a terrible nickname.
But... maybe that's why people flocked to me.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll stop it here.
That transformation.
Just like that boy, if an NPC's program can be rewritten...
That means there's a person using that software to change NPCs into Shadows, setting them to attack us.
There's someone playing God for this world and using this to screw around with us.
Wherever this person is, there must also be countless computers.
And if so, there's only one possible place.
Checkmate.
Raise your hands in the air.
Hm?  What's this now?
"Checkmate"?
Were you playing chess?
He's the one behind all this?
The world requires computers for everything.
Playing an analog game is good, too, though.
Despite being young, you have a good hobby.
Wait right there!
Me?
What were you doing?
Here?
Yes.
I was setting up a new computer.
For what reason?
Maybe it's because computers are valuable, but they often get stolen.
If they go missing, I need to replace them.
Do you have any idea who takes them?
Not at the moment.
May I go now?
Yes, thank you.
My apologies for keeping you.
There's no mistake.
That burglar is playing the role of God in this world right now.
Using the PCs they've stolen, they're starting to tamper with the NPCs.
But how should I capture them?
I don't have time to waste.
The Shadows are multiplying this very moment.
Well, it's easy to say "steal,"
but these aren't easily transportable.
Do they sneak in at night and carry them out on a dolly?
Or maybe out the window?
There you are.
What?  No way...
Not the Guild again!!!
We're going to break through!
Knockin' on heaven's door.
What is this world?
I thought even God would be surprised!
So the war's... going to end...
I don't think anyone'd notice even if you disappeared right now!
Get lost!
Disappear pitifully, just like toilet paper!
I only move when it helps Yurippe!
One hundred...  Just think, we have reinforcements.
We'll be a band next time, too!
I am amazed you made it this far.
Reach out!
If I'm obliterated from this place...  can I redo my life?