Three weeks have passed since that body swapping business ended.
Nagase made a complete recovery,
so we've been busy making up for lost time by working hard on the SCS paper.
Three weeks ago,
I told Nagase how I felt about her,
and she said that she felt the same way.
But between her injury and all the work on the paper,
we haven't had a chance to talk alone.
In any case, peace and quiet had returned to the Student Cultural Society.
Or so we thought,
until school was over the next day.
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
Quit beating
around the bush!
How about laughing more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
That comic was pretty cool.
Time for some curry.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Curry hot pot
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
me yui
We should get married
I love youuuuu
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
The whole world
Let's go
to Disneyland
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry, I can't
go out with you.
Seriously.
Done tomorrow's
homework?
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
A Story That Continued
Before Anyone Realized It
Here already?
You're always early, Inaba.
I wasn't able to finish up at home.
I have to get this done today.
Are Yui and Aoki around?
I need to check a few things.
I ran into them on the way here.
They'll be late because they're on monitor duty today.
Don't you find it annoying to have to wait all the time,
even if you know it's not their fault?
Well, we can't blame them if it's not their fault.
Makes you want to take out your frustration on whoever happens to be around, right?
Of course not.
What's the point in that?
To feel better by blowing off steam.
You've got a real nasty streak.
I've learned that complaining about things that only bother you a tiny bit
is actually pretty good stress relief.
Wow.
You're able to reduce your own
stress by taking it out on me?
And yet it doesn't really increase my own.
What's wrong, Inaba?
Inaba?
Hey... What are you doing?
Does your back itch or something?
H-Hey!
Hold on!
What's going on?!
Take off your clothes.
Wh-Why should I take off my clothes?
We have to take off our clothes before we can do it.
Do what?!
I know.
You're just toying with me to relieve stress, right?
Ow...
I-Inaba!
What are you doing?!
Get off!
Get off! Get off!
Wait!
You've got it all wrong!
Really! I have no idea what's...
Inaba?
Can someone please explain...
what the hell's going on?!
Yui?
What's wrong?!
Blood?
Did I do this?
Why?
Student Cultural Society
'Sup!
Whoa! The table!
What happened?!
How did it break?!
Wait, Yui. You're bleeding.
Let me see.
Iori!
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
Sorry, I'm going home.
Huh?
What was that all about?
Is it okay to leave it like this?
Are you going out?
Is something wrong?
Was I about to go outside?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Whoa!
Nagase Iori
I need to take this call!
Hello?
Is this Nagase?
Hey, Taichi! Tell me!
Are we...
Huh?
Um! Uh, what?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
G-Good evening.
Uh, yeah...
Good evening.
Sorry!
I must be confused.
I think I called you unconsciously.
I just felt like I needed to talk to you.
A-Actually, I just had a sudden urge to see you, too.
It's like my body was moving on its own.
You too?
Weird.
Something's not right.
Yeah...
Hey, you said you felt like you
needed to talk to me, right?
What did you want to say?
You wanted to talk to me too, right?
Yeah...
Well...
I wanted to talk about the confession!
W-We never had a chance to clear things up.
Have your...
Have your feelings changed since then?
They haven't.
I still feel the same way I did then.
Really?
Then...
Same here.
Um, I feel really embarrassed right now.
This is definitely embarrassing.
Th-That's enough for today!
Yeah, let's call it a day!
O-Okay, we can do that.
Well, sorry about the weird phone call!
Bye!
Wait, Nagase!
Your girlfriend?
Sh-She's not my girlfriend!
Look at you blush.
But that's good to know.
You were acting weird before.
You're still acting kind of weird,
but at least I know it's because you're lovesick.
You've got it wrong!
Well, maybe it's better to leave it at that.
But...
You're so cute!
Hey, how do you know what it means to be lovesick?
You need to give your big brother a proper explanation!
I-Inaba!
About yesterday...
U-Uh...
There's trouble.
Yui and Aoki were taken into police custody.
Huh?
What?!
I don't know any details,
but the teachers were talking about it.
I tried calling them, but neither of them are answering.
The cops have them now.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
Why would the police take Aoki and Kiriyama into custody?
Hell if I know.
Doesn't anyone have more information?
You rang?
Huh?
Fujishima...
Uh, I don't think anyone was talking to you.
Well, if you know something, tell us.
You shouldn't order people around when asking for a favor, Inaba.
Please tell us what you know, Fujishima.
Yes...
If you let me rent Nagase for two hours,
I'll consider it.
What?!
It's a small price to pay.
I'm sure that Nagase will be happy with the deal.
Hey, Fujishima.
That's dirty.
Don't touch her!
There it is again!
What are you trying to do?
What are you doing, Yaegashi?
Dance practice?
Not exactly.
I understand.
If we can find out what happened to Aoki and Yui,
you can have two or three hours!
So tell us, Fujishima.
That was a joke.
I was going to tell you anyway.
What?!
It was a joke?!
My sacrifice was for nothing!
You guys looked way too serious.
I was trying to inject a little humor.
But I didn't think you would be so mortified by the idea.
This morning, a group of boys from Akitaka High were giving some girls from our school trouble.
Kiriyama happened to pass by and beat them up.
But it sounds like she used excessive force,
Police
so the cops wanted to talk.
That's when Aoki showed up and went off on them.
"Where are you taking her? Let her go!"
Police
I hear that he put up a good fight.
Well, she was helping girls from the same school,
so she should get off with a warning.
Damn straight!
If they try to punish her,
I'll do whatever it takes to stop them.
How do you know what happened, Fujishima?
My dad happens to be a high-ranking cop.
That's all.
Glad to hear that.
This connection will come in handy.
It won't come free.
but I can give you a discount.
Beware of Suspicious Characters
A conspiracy is born.
This partnership scares me.
Beware of Suspicious Characters
So Kiriyama and Aoki never came to school.
Hey, I've been thinking.
Kiriyama beat up boys from another school, right?
But she's...
I was also wondering about that.
Yui suffers from androphobia.
She's gotten a lot better,
but not to the point where she could grapple with a bunch of boys.
Yet...
You also acted strangely this morning.
Yeah.
Did you hear a voice in your head?
You heard it too?
Both of you could hear it?
Long time no see.
Or maybe it hasn't been that long.
Has it?
Heartseed!
Yes, did you all start hearing voices in your heads yesterday?
And then your body automatically does what your mind wants.
Stop messing with us!
We're not your guinea pigs!
Oh, I haven't apologized to Nagase yet.
I would like to say that I'm sorry from somewhere around the middle of my heart.
If you're sorry, you should leave us alone.
No, I'm repeating myself here,
but you people truly fascinate me.
So I'll explain what's happening this time:
Your deepest desires have been unleashed.
Our desires have been unleashed?
As I mentioned before,
this phenomena will end when
it's no longer entertaining.
You could say that I'm helping you
discover your true selves.
True selves...
I have a question.
Is it against the rules to hide in our rooms?
Huh?
Student Cultural Society
Of course, Inaba is very sharp.
All I have to say is that hiding in your room
could be just as entertaining.
If not, I can make it entertaining.
Make it entertaining, huh?
Student Cultural Society
I'm being a little too generous.
So long then.
So it's Heartseed again.
Sorry to have made you worry.
You don't need to apologize.
I wasn't worried about you.
That hurt!
That really hurt, Inaba!
I'm glad that you got off with a warning.
Yeah, I made it out okay...
And Kiriyama's absent again today.
Yui wanted to save those girls
so badly that she beat up the boys.
You wanted to stop the cops from taking her away so badly that you put up a struggle.
Under normal circumstances,
you would've shown self-restraint and stopped.
But your desires were unleashed,
and you acted on them.
That's probably what happened when Yui
broke the table two days ago.
So when Inaba made a move on me...
Stop talking!
You have the sensitivity of a rock!
Do not mention how I disgraced myself.
Hell. Want me to pummel you
until you forget it happened?
Um...
What are you talking about?
See? Look what happened!
Idiot! Moron! Dumbass!
S-Sorry...
It's no big deal.
Two days ago, before you showed up,
my desires were unleashed,
and I kinda put some moves on Taichi.
Oh, really?
But don't get the wrong idea!
This was right after I happened to come across some dirty pictures.
I-I don't know how far I would've gone.
But it probably wouldn't've been too far!
I think...
Since I have no experience...
Moving on!
When we were swapping bodies,
we were able to keep everything amongst ourselves.
But that won't work when our desires are unleashed.
Yui and Aoki have already used violence against other people.
That's right. Outsiders might end up getting involved this time.
We have two options right now.
The first would be to suppress your emotions.
The second would be to just not think about it,
go wild, and have more fun than usual,
instead of keeping yourself in check.
What do you mean?
Basically, you either take it easy so you don't have any dangerous urges,
or you do whatever you want
to avoid any stress build-up.
Both options sound difficult.
That's amazing, Inaban!
You already have a plan!
Sucking up won't do you any good.
It's also important to help each other.
Yeah... That's an option too.
Hm? Is it a bad idea?
No, not at all.
It makes sense to help each other.
The rest is up to luck.
We'll just have to play it by ear.
That's all I have to say.
I'm sure Yui will be here tomorrow.
We can continue this discussion then.
Society
Yeah, I don't know what would be the right thing to do,
but we should be fine if we work together.
Yeah, I just know it.
It's all you, Taichi.
You have to be there for Iori.
Yeah...
But I'll be helping everyone, not just Nagase.
You only need to worry about Iori.
And Aoki can take care of Yui.
Oh, I guess you're not up to the task.
Student Cultural Society
You'd better not underestimate me.
Hey, aren't you coming to class, Inaban?
I still need to work on the paper.
I'll be there in a bit.
We can help.
It's okay.
Just go away!
I can't get any work done when you're around.
Student Cultural Society
Bye.
Did I pull it off?
Is everyone else doing okay?
What should I do?
Taichi, can you talk now?
Sure. You usually don't call this late.
Sorry, there's something I wanted to say.
Picking up where we left off before...
O-Oh, that...
This might not be the best time,
but I think this is important, too.
Can we return to the status quo for now?
Uh...
Status quo?
I realize I'm asking a lot from you after everything that's happened,
but I think it'd be a good idea to
maintain our distance for now.
You know how our desires are basically out of control at the moment?
Yeah...
I feel like it would be a bad idea to get closer
under these circumstances.
You're right.
Sorry, I wasn't thinking clearly.
That would be dangerous for us.
Very dangerous.
Who knows what we might do?
Also, I have something to confess.
Confess?
I still lack confidence.
Sometimes, I wonder if this is really okay.
So I'm a little excited about having our desires unleashed.
Excited?
My deepest desires will be unleashed.
It might help me discover the real me.
I can't help but look forward to it.
I don't want to be so self-centered,
but I can't help myself.
Okay, confession time's over!
Sorry to keep you up!
I'll buy you lunch or something.
That's the real you talking.
Huh?
The real you is making these objective observations.
You can discover elements
of the real you in your everyday life.
When you're around, it feels like everything's gonna be okay.
Goodbye.
Okay, see ya.
Everything will be okay.
I'll find a way.
I can't screw up this time.
Falling Apart
Next Time
Yahoo!
Cute! Sunny! Strong! Super cute!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't look! I made a huge mistake!
I guess I'm not good enough for you.
How would I know?! Don't ask me!
I'm disappointed, Inaba.
I never thought you would give up on your friends.
I see you're busy shakin' out that thin red velvet cloth
But before you take your leave, might I ask where you're off to?
Me, I'm headed for the morning, travelin' to the west
Then may God be with you
Your eyes, reflecting up to me from the teacup
look just like a rabbit's in a cage
Must be because we forgot to add the sugar
But who cares about that
Your love is sweet enough
I cry out, again and again to the dawning sky
Are there really things in this world that I truly cherish?
This aching in my heart, and the place where I belong
Maybe even those are things that I hold dear all the same
Cry out
Nagase Iori
Tune in next time!
Laugh more
Rice? Bread?
me yui
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
Let's go out
Screw that
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow