Lulu... I've failed as your friend.
I knew your feelings, but pretended not to have noticed.
I lied to you, even though you're my friend.
It may be too late, but I must tell you this.
What happened the day I parted with Kureha's love,
as well as the reason why.
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
viens avec moi
Come with me
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu ni
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shitara
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so approve me
kaze ni matta ehon no page ga
The sight of the wind flipping the pages of a picture book
kage ni natta kioku wo yurasu no
uncovers memories of days long past
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
karappo na sekai no naka
in this empty world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Flashback
11 Years Ago
HISTORY
She's done for.
You're right. Let's exclude those who would be a burden.
Exclude them.
At that time, I had resolved myself.
I accepted the fact that I would die all alone, never to be found.
But then...
Don't worry. You're not alone.
I'm your friend.
We'll be together forever from now on.
Mommy taught me.
So long as you don't forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as you don't back down on love, even if you were to lose something, you won't become invisible.
I will... protect you.
Is your love true?
Kureha?
Kureha!
Where are you?
I won't forget love.
I won't back down on love.
Growl!
The two of us...
are friends!
That was how Kureha and I became friends.
We shared many different things.
That love was sweet, gentle,
and seemed to make my entire world shine like the stars.
That led to my mistake.
I thought that the world had approved of me.
But then...
There you are, traitor.
Don't come out!
We hear you took in a bear.
Someone saw it!
Unreal!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb! My mama told me.
She said that bears are our enemies!
Bears are evil! They need to be excluded!
That's not true! Bears can be our friends!
Are you sticking up for the bears?
Unreal!
Then that means you're evil too!
Exclude! Exclude!
Exclude! Exclude! Exclude!
Everyone! Look at the evil girl who's sticking up for bears!
Exclude!
Traitors have to be excluded!
Stop!
Kureha... she did that for me.
She was hurt so much because I'm a bear.
It's my fault for being a bear.
If only... if only I were a human girl...
Would we be able to stay together?
Would I be able to protect Kureha?
Please tell me, Kumaria-sama!
Is your love true?
My love is true! Growl!
All rise!
Welcome to the Severance Court.
Let all living beings bear witness to this face off of man and bear.
Let us begin the judgement.
For man and for bear—
Life Sexy!
Judge
Life Sexy
JUDGEMENS
Life Cool!
Prosecutor
Life Cool
JUDGEMENS
Life Beauty!
Defense
Attorney
Life Beauty
JUDGEMENS
Is this where Kumaria-sama lives?
Kumaria-sama is long lost to us.
She became a meteor and scattered across the planet.
That can't be...
The Lily Judgement shall now begin.
Bearfendant Yurishiro Ginko.
Please state your case.
I want to be with Kureha forever! I want to protect her!
So please...
Please turn me into a human girl!
Very well.
However, there will be one condition.
You are to part with your love.
Put simply, she will forget your existence.
Not only that, you'll never get to tell anyone what happened here.
It's as if you're The Little Mermaid! Shiny shine!
When she awakens, Tsubaki Kureha will certainly reject you.
Reject?
No!
A-A bear...
Stay away...
Someone... no!
You were right, Lulu. In exchange for my wish to become a human girl,
I had to part with Kureha's love.
And then...
One day, for certain, shall come the day
bears and people can be friends forever.
I was returned to the world of bears.
Even so, you insist on loving that daughter of man?
I won't back down on love, growl!
How dreadful. From this day forward,
you are no longer a cub of Kumaria-sama!
You corrupt this world, Loner Queen Ginko!
Begone, sinner who betrays her mother!
You must wait.
In time, you will find Tsubaki Kureha again.
And then, if you can become her friend again... shiny shine!
My wish will come true?
Yes. Please exchange your promised kiss with her. If you succeed...
I can become a human girl, growl?
I inquire of you, bearfendant Yurishiro Ginko:
Will you become a human?
Or will you back down on love?
I won't back down on love.
I'll become a human!
Growl!
I waited for that time.
And eventually...
Lulu, I met you.
restricted number
Yes?
Is your love true?
It's true, growl.
The Invisible Storm has blown in.
The time is now.
I know.
I won't back down on love!
I won't back down on love either.
I'll support your love all the way, Ginko.
Lulu, you've always been by my side.
You gave me love without asking for anything in return.
Lulu...
Thank you.
Huh?
Sure!
Don't you worry! I'll protect you!
Alright, let's go to the human world!
Growl!
The Day The Two Transferred
HISTORY
Yurishiro Ginko
Yurigasaki Lulu
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why I became a human girl.
Kureha, I wanted to become your true friend.
We crossed that barrier...
Sniff sniff.
She's here!
She really does have a deliciousmell.
Lulu, from the very beginning, you were my true friend.
Girls, I believe you understand.
We must exclude the bear
hiding in our school at all costs.
I trust you are well prepared.
Let us reconfirm the identity of the bear bait one last time together.
Let's search sacrifice!
Confirm
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Ai Gekiko
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Serina Kanako
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Shimatai Saori
Uesu Aoi
Tanaka Karen
Evil
Tsubaki Kureha
Shall I lick that wound for you?
Keep it to yourself, growl.
Goodness, you're quite on guard today.
Listen closely.
I want to eat that girl—Tsubaki Kureha.
That lust is the desire we share.
Come, let us be off to find and eat her.
Ah, that rich scent of deliciousmell!
She exudes the fragrance of a girl who won't back down on love.
Deliciousmell, grind.
Grind grind grind grind...
Yes, you're doing very well.
Teach those girls that the hunters may indeed become the hunted.
Bear Death Ray Vehicle reporting in!
We have visual on the target.
Ecokumagical beam, preparing to fire!
Scum?
Spark spark! Scum scum!
Megabear Energy is charging.
Countdown to full power: ten, nine, eight...
She really is just an animal.
Only beasts are so easily lured in by bait.
So tell me how you tamed her.
Did you whisper sweet nothings and then give her a nice peck?
You super disgust me.
Bear Death Ray Vehicle reporting in.
Confirmed hit on target Alpha.
We wounded her, but she got away!
This is D5. We've received word that the lily garden door has opened.
We will now move to confirm.
So that really is where they were
sneaking in from, those crafty animals...
Oh, right! I brought something fun.
Look what we found while we were ransacking your house.
That's...!
Your mother drew this?
A bear and a human being friends?
Writing a story like this is
what got her killed by a bear!
"Kumaria-sama"? How stupid was she?
This world has no god.
The only thing that rules this land is the invisible atmosphere.
Bear.
Bear, bear.
Come quickly. Your bait is right here.
That was a bit too close for comfort, right?
I wonder where they pulled such a tasteless weapon from.
Come on, let's go and eat Kureha.
You won't lose.
Your desire to have her all to yourself is stronger than anything they have.
I won't forget love.
I won't back down on love.
Scum...
Trouble!
I finally found you.
My true love.
What are you going on about?
You accepted me, did you not?
True love...
won't break in the face of any storm!
won't leave me alone!
I can hear her... Kureha is calling for me!
It's the same as back then!
That day I was left behind, only Kureha found me.
She gave me her love.
This time, it's my turn to save her.
You can't!
You can't. We're bears.
I won't allow you to say you've forgotten.
I am your lust. Your love itself.
No!
True love... will let me weather any storm!
Are you trying to abandon me?
It's impossible! I'm your desire!
Only death awaits a beast without desire!
Goodbye.
I...
...will shatter...
...myself!
Such a fool.
Kureha, I found you, growl!
Stay away!
Don't come one step closer to me!
What do you think you can change now?
This entire situation is your fault.
From the very beginning, you weren't my friend!
Humans and bears are severed!
Struggle all you want, but we can never be together!
I know, growl. That's why...
No matter how much I'm rejected, I'm going to be your friend again.
I'll become your friend and give you my promised kiss.
Then I'll be able to become a human girl.
So long as you don't forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as you don't back down on love, even if you were to lose something, you won't become invisible.
Stop it!
It's your fault that they all died!
Even Sumika died!
I shan't forgive the bears—I won't forgive you!
Disappear.
Go back to the other side of the barrier. I already sent Yurigasaki-san back.
Go, and don't ever come back!
Stop!
No... stay away.
Please!
Kureha, I won't back down on love.
Flashback
Kureha-chan, I won't back down on love.
No... I don't want to lose anyone else...
Lulu!
Sorry, Kurechin.
I came back.
Kurechin is a terrible liar.
Lulu! Lulu!
Kurechin helped me escape.
She said that I wasn't her friend,
but I could see right through her lie.
So listen...
Kurechin will forgive you, Ginko.
No, I'm sure she already has.
Lulu...
Ginko, you can become Kurechin's friend.
Fulfill... your love.
I know your promised kiss will be fulfilled, Ginko.
Look, I gathered up the pieces of your future.
Well? I'm such a genius, right?
Lulu?
Lulu!
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger
Defendant Tsubaki Kureha.
Will you admit your own sin?
Lily Bear!