What will you sing?
What should I go with?
Yeah, I do feel kinda thirsty.
So...
Aren't you gonna sing?
I'm fine.
Don't be such a stiff.
You came here wanting to meet someone new, right?
No, I had no idea I was coming to a mixer.
Fine, I get it.
If you're feeling shy, I don't mind singing with you.
Come on. Pick something.
H-Hey...
Let me go!
Acting like that will only make me want to bully you more.
No!
S-Stop it!
What if something like that's going on right now?!
I see the guy turned into you midway.
I'm sure he has 108 sexual
harassment fantasies or something.
I don't even want to fantasize her being with another guy!
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Twelve
Wanted To Get Closer
Didn't you say it'd be a gathering of book lovers?
I did.
These guys are total bookworms, you know.
Huh? Do I not look like an avid reader?
You do seem like more of a playboy.
Mean.
But remember how you recommended me "The Crimes of Earl Bailey," Ricchan?
He likes it too.
I couldn't put it down.
Especially after they found out Molly was pregnant.
Yeah, that was unexpected.
Did you know there's a sequel?
Well, it's more of a mixed media thing, really.
Mitsui!
Listen to me when I'm singing!
I'd rather discuss books with Ricchan than listen to you.
Fine.
Let me join you!
Ricchan, what other books do you like?
Ricchan?
Er, stuff by Mishima Yukio or
Yamazaki Toyoko, to name a couple.
End of song
Proper readers really do have superior taste.
I met this girl from South High recently.
She said her hobby was reading,
so I asked her what she liked to read.
Her answer? Fashion magazines!
And people who get all teary-eyed
over cellphone novels are weird too.
They're always so overconfident, you know?
Oh, and people who pretend they're readers
just because they sampled something simple.
They keep asking for recommendations, but
the books we read are way out of their league.
Hey, Kawai.
This was really good!
That one scene, in particular!
Doesn't it make you feel all, "Why don't you look for something yourself"?
It doesn't.
It's normal to pick up an interest in books by starting with simple ones.
If you ask me, it's weirder to ridicule the desire to read all kinds of books.
Ricchan...
Er, well...
You're a nice girl, huh?
It wasn't my intention to ridicule them.
I loved how you stood up for your opinions, though.
Don't run.
Ouch!
Knock it off, Mitsui.
But Ricchan's so much cuter in person than in her pic!
My phone's ringing!
Logs
Mayumi
Mayumi?
A text?
Usa here.
Sayaka said she saw you at the karaoke place by the station.
Are you okay?
Want us to come bail you out?
"Us"? I'm so pathetic!
Though I guess having to use Mayumi's phone for this is messed up in itself.
That'll be 1,000 yen for five minutes.
She replied!
I'm not okay.
But I'll figure something out myself.
I'll leave now.
So she doesn't need my help.
Even so, she admitted she wasn't okay.
Hang in there.
We're waiting for you.
If you need our help, please let us know.
Anyway, isn't it ridiculous that this
phone costs 1,000 yen for five minutes?
If Mayumi keeps this up, I don't
think she'll ever find a boyfriend.
Ricchan.
We're thinking of packing up the karaoke and getting—
I have to go.
I'm sure the people at my boarding house are waiting for me with dinner ready.
Usa.
Sumiko told me to come pick you up since it's gotten quite dark.
That really wore me out.
Why does Mayumi want to go to these things?
Good job making it back.
Great. None of the guys there clicked with her, huh?
Your bag looks heavy.
I took a few books I like with me.
So she really had no idea.
Like, seriously...
I'm sick of it!
I'm sick of the questions, the texts, and the restroom!
Restroom?
You're not gonna tell her to give it a rest?
Give it a rest already!
W-Well, you deserved that!
Yeah, I could tell! It made me reflect on my actions!
You think it'd be okay to tell her that?
I'll choose my words more wisely.
I do.
And yes, please do choose your words more wisely.
You knocked me out of commission for quite a while.
Stop exaggerating!
It's the truth.
I thought you'd retreat into your shell if I told you guys would be coming.
I didn't mean to lie to you, but still, I apologize.
If you don't like karaoke, then next time...
No, that's not what I mean.
I'm just not cut out for that stuff.
No, come with me!
Mitsui seemed to be really into you.
He's been calling you cute ever since I sent him your pic.
Pic?
Say cheese
You know, the one we took before.
I sent it to a few people.
Mitsu's a great guy, you know.
You should act more like a high schooler and get a boyfriend—
Who said you could do that?
I'm sorry to say this, but I don't want to go on any more of your outings.
You don't have to get that mad.
Hanging out with guys is fun,
so I figured I could help you enjoy yourself.
Don't let your shyness get the better of you.
Come with me. We're friends, right—
Maemura, aren't you just looking for
someone to hang around you all the time?
Sorry. That was uncalled for.
Don't be.
I have this bad habit of getting too gung-ho about things.
I'm sorry.
I got into a fight with a friend over something similar, so maybe I was overcompensating with you.
I know you didn't mean any harm.
I'm sure your friend will forgive you if you apologize.
R-Really?
Yeah.
No texts today?
I'd kinda gotten used to it as the BGM track here.
Did she get through to her?
Library
Sorry.
Got something to do today. Can't stop by the library.
Kawai...
It's closing time now.
Okay.
She's been on her own an awful lot lately.
Sorry!
You're late, Maemura!
I told you we'd be heading home together.
I got held up.
That voice belongs to Kawai's...
Haven't you been walking home with Kawai lately? You sure about this?
Uh, we didn't really click.
Or, well, she seems to prefer being left alone.
She does give off that impression.
So yeah, I'm trying to distance myself.
She's a nice girl, though.
That so?
Let's go.
Well, I had a feeling this would happen.
Even so,
I had so much fun discussing books with her.
Oh, I guess I was the only one who felt that way.
K-Kawai, I...
I'm sorry I gave you bad advice.
It's the book!
I was reading a really powerful scene.
It moved me to tears again.
You were right.
I should try not to read such engrossing books outdoors.
I mean,
it gives people the wrong idea.
True... that.
Heavy stories can get to you before you know it.
Yeah.
That said...
you only have to endure it for a little longer today.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
But these words...
Yer late, ya twerps!
Here I am, heartbroken,
and you two were out there in the twilight, enjoying your teen romance?
Die in a fire!
Not only did my juniors keep me in the dark about another mixer,
they also used the names of recent kids' anime as code for the time and place!
Do**mi
P**cure
Drained
What the?
Everything's starting to feel so stupid.
You callin' me stupid?
What?
Just because you went on your first mixer...
You lucky...
I hate them, so I'm fine this way.
I'm truly glad...
that you're so petty.
I dare you to say that one more time, you frickin' virgin!
Who was Irene, again?
Oh, she's the pretty maid.
There are too many characters, and I have no idea what some of these job titles are.
This is seriously too highbrow for me.
Hard to
memorize
I didn't know you liked western stuff.
If maids are your fetish, then
you've certainly got the right idea.
So, what's it like?
Is it "Oh, yes! Come on"?
Or is it "Please don't, Master"?
Personally, I like it when the master and servant switch roles in bed.
It's not erotica!
If it's a normal book, then why aren't you reading it in the living room?
You usually show it off.
Kawai was really hooked on this book.
After what happened, I'd look
like I was trying way too hard.
It'd also be embarrassing if she thought I was reading something way above my level.
Well, it is too
hard for me
I'm not trying to be considerate.
I'm just interested in the book.
If only I could enjoy the kind of stuff she likes without having to push myself...
I want to get closer to her!
Our neighbor gave us some homemade umeshu.
Apparently it's five years aged!
Delicious!
And it goes down smooth!
It's got a high alcohol content, so don't drink too much.
And you two get plum juice.
Five years ago, huh?
Kazuya was by my side back then—
Wait, was it Hiroki?
Or was it Yuuji? Ryou?
Nah. Naonori?
17cm?
Not even a name anymore.
Those were the days.
Perfect size, too.
How can you say all that with a straight face?
Just like alcohol, women only
grow more delectable with age.
But sometimes you might crack one open and find it's all rotted away by germs.
I don't wanna hear that from you!
You're a germ that rots men away!
It's not fair that you get to be
happy despite being such a bitch!
Seriously!
I'm not the least bit envio—
Wait, who was that?
Kawai?
That's not juice in Ricchan's glass!
And it's half-gone already!
Oh dear! Get some water!
C-Could it be...
Is this that thing where an accidental
drink causes all those things to happen?
My body's burning up.
Do something about it.
I thought it was just an urban legend, but I'm finally gonna get lucky!
Okay, time to split up the guys and girls.
My luck vanished in an instant!
What am I gonna do with you?
Uhhnn... Lucky...
How about that? I went all out for you!
"Unlucky"! Get it?
Too much for a virgin to take, right?
Sayaka!
You don't play fair.
You're such a bitch, and yet you
have such a nice friend in Tsuneko.
Come on, Ricchan...
And despite all your grumbling, the two of you just connect.
Even though you're such a bitch.
That's three times now.
I don't think I'll ever meet a friend who I'll click with in that way.
Here, have some water.
If you don't mind telling us, we'll lend you an ear.
She's the kind of girl who can't live without friends, huh?
You're not blameless yourself, Ricchan. You
held back and went with the flow for a while.
Wouldn't that give her the impression that you're kindred spirits?
And if she's the kind of person who thinks sharing everything is what friends do,
what you said probably felt like total rejection.
U-Um, this is all because I thoughtlessly told her to speak her mind.
So I'm partly to blame.
Don't be stupid.
That girl was spot on. They didn't click.
That's all.
They would've drifted apart eventually either way.
They were missing something very important.
That means I can't make friends with anyone!
I don't think I'll ever meet someone I'll click with
No two people are perfectly compatible.
It's not a problem if you don't click.
The important thing is to accept that and still want to get closer to each other.
For example, Maemura sharing your picture without asking.
I'd find it weird too,
but I'd let it go if it landed me a nice guy.
You're not flexible enough, Ricchan.
That's more loose than flexible, really.
And sometimes you think you click with someone, but you realize you don't once you get to know them better.
You actually clicked with someone?
I hear you.
I mean, you and that boy at the mixer clicked on the topic of books, right?
But it didn't work out, right?
Well...
I mean...
Oh, and people who pretend they're readers
just because they sampled something simple.
A-Anyway, I just couldn't stand him!
Did you actually get into a fight at the mixer?
That must've killed the mood.
It didn't exactly turn into a fight, but...
Good thing he wasn't short-tempered, huh?
Can take
a hint?
I think you're too nice, Usa!
Even though you were insulted, you're taking things positively.
Insulted?
You're too considerate, or more like too masochistic!
You haven't quit your job either!
I will,
I will
And that girl from your junior high...
Who, Hayashi?
You're being nice to her despite what she did to you!
You should be more angry!
Oh yeah. She got mad at the mere mention of Hayashi that one time.
Do you not like me being nice to Hayashi?
Well, right now...
That's not the issue here!
Are you taking this seriously?
I'm sorry!
I'm trying to say...
I'm hungry.
Gonna go buy dessert.
Not in that state, you're not!
He's right, Ricchan!
Barred from
going out
It's bedtime now. Hold your urges in.
Barred from
going out
She's sulking.
What's this adorable creature?
I have a few snacks in my room. Let me go grab them.
I'm coming with you.
The bakery at the station only
makes thirty cream puffs a day!
I don't have anything that fancy!
You're completely wasted, aren't you?
I said I'm coming!
The girl I'm in love with wants to come to my room drunk!
How lucky!
We're coming too, obviously.
Figures.
Right. Unlucky.
Ricchan, you've never been inside a boy's room before, right?
Let's play a game to see who can find the snacks first!
Okay, here we go!
Swimsuit pics: 5 points! Nude photos: 20 points!
Money shots and uncensored pics get a bonus!
Porno DVDs: 50 points!
What about my "Guide to 48 Forms of Bondage"?
Obvious crap like that gets -50!
Listen up, Ricchan.
Aim for below the bed, under all the stuff in the drawer, and behind the bookshelf.
What happened to looking for snacks?!
Where am I?
Last night!
The type who
remembers
Usa and the others aren't here.
This book...
He didn't have to go out of his way to read something this difficult.
I don't hear any movement.
You boys can sleep outside!
Usa
If they look in that box, I'm in trouble!
20 points
What are you doing, Ricchan?
N-Nothing!
What's that? Show me!
Usa's fantasy diary?
I-It's me, Usa! I'm coming in!
Kawai!
The hell is this? So boring.
Did Kawai see this notebook?!
Oh no. What if it weirds her out?
K-Kawai!
Your comments are too funny, Usa.
Smegma
Flora
Spaced-out Sally
Agreed
Weirdo
Key person
How could you call Flora "Spaced-out Sally"?
Don't you think she's a bit strange?
Sorry I peeked at
your notebook,
but...
Well, you should call her mysterious.
Will you show me your notes again when you're further in?
S-Sure, but promise you won't laugh.
That's impossible.
No hesitation, I see.
When I do, please leave your own comments again.
Anyway, try and
finish Chapter 3
Okay. Got it.
It's kinda like an exchange diary, right?
Dummy!
W-Wait, Kawai!
If you don't mind...
let's exchange phone numbers and email addresses!
I mean, in case something like the mixer happens again.
It feels stupid to have to borrow Mayumi's phone each time.
I've turned on the Bluetooth, so if you don't mind...
Only if you don't mind, of course.
Kawai Ritsu
Save?
Yes
No
Send/receive complete
Kawai...
Looks like the two of us
might've been closer than I thought.
Damn you two for flirting first thing in the morning!
What is this, Playboy Conan?!
Women Rider?!
Stop dragging morning television into this!
Usa Kazunari saved
Kawai Ritsu saved
Kawai Complex
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
Only a special man can lay claim to this beauty
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little pity in the air
I poke my nose where it doesn't belong
And applaud your eccentricity
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please