Summer vacation is an opportunity for once-in-a-lifetime experiences!
Let's all push our boundaries
and have a fulfilling vacation.
Where is everyone going?
It's summer vacation, so everyone's heading home!
Home?
Summer's here!
We're on break!
And we're staying at Haruharu's place!
Yeah!
Now girls, don't let the excitement of summer vacation go to your heads.
Minamin, what's with the huge suitcases?
It's simply luggage for the trip.
Can't forget this one...
You need all that just to stay at my house?
I've never stayed at a friend's home before, so I didn't want to be inconsiderate!
But I suppose I packed a tad more than expected.
That's more than just a tad...
I think the excitement got to your head first.
Let's get going already!
Have fun, girls.
What's that mean?
You're coming with us, Towa!
I already packed your luggage!
Now, let's be off!
W-Wait!
Let's go!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Hurry up! It's this way!
So this is your hometown, Haruka?
Yeah, it is!
It was built for postal handling ages ago,
but now it's a tourism hotspot!
Huh, this city's got a nice atmosphere.
So, which of these is your home?
Why, it's right down here!
Haruya
I'm home!
Hey, Sis!
Welcome home, Haruka.
Haruka! Haruka!
Haruka!
Haruka, dear, you've grown so tall!
It's been a while, ma'am!
Pardon us.
Haruka! Haruka!
Oh, friends of yours?
Bonjour.
My, what a splendid how-do-you-do!
They're Noble Academy students, all right.
To Haruka's House!
Our First Sleepover!
Now, come this way.
Thanks for your hospitality.
I brought something from my home for you all.
It's nothing much, but...
Whoah!
My, how thoughtful!
But you really didn't have to go so far.
I wanted to express my gratitude.
A smorgasbord of high quality melons!
Stuffed in a suitcase...
Sorry 'bout the ruckus earlier.
Lot of customers, huh?
Would you like us to help out?
We're fine! You're on summer vacation, so you should be relaxing!
Oh, it's no biggie. It never hurts to switch up the vacation routine once in a while.
Experiencing the unexperienced is the raison d'être of summer vacation!
Welcome!
Eight dorayaki, coming right up!
Thank you for stopping by!
Thanks for the meal.
Minami, go to the customers
over there and take their orders.
R-Right!
Towa, deliver these tea refills!
Certainly!
Three orders of red bean soup, correct?
I brought some refills for your tea.
You can tell she's got experience!
Good goin', Haruharu!
The anmitsu's done!
Anmitsu?
Oh, you like anmitsu?
What? Oh, yes...
Let's eat!
It tastes great!
Nothing beats a treat after work!
So, how do you like our anmitsu?
It's exemplary!
Good!
Exemplawhat?
She means it's tasty!
My skin feels so smooth!
You've got a bathhouse in walking distance? Your house rules!
I know!
There are plenty of summer events to bring the town together, too!
Yeah, like tests of courage!
T-Tests of courage?
Don't worry! We're going to a Bon festival instead!
Ph-Phew...
'Cause Minamin's afraid of ghosts!
We all have something we fear!
Something we fear...
Towa, is something wrong?
Not at all!
Now, let's be off.
A break from butlering!
That's cold!
Now!
We're all set!
Here come the flowing noodles!
It's a summer vacation experience!
Oh my!
This is harder than I'd thought.
Goodness!
Gotcha!
Ah!
Got one!
It's yummy!
Oh, you two, catching flowing noodles takes patience, not perspiration!
Give it a try!
It's scrumptious!
Indeed!
The neighbors gave us some fresh corn this morning!
Have at 'em!
Wow, those look great!
Don't mind if I do!
It's sweet!
Eating in such a manner...
It's a summer vacation experience.
Huh?
Got you!
I won!
Ooh, I want a rematch!
Whatever are you doing?
Shooting watermelon seeds!
Whoever shoots the furthest wins.
Shooting seeds?
Oh, me next!
Hey!
You're on the clock, buster!
Now get back to work!
It's a summer vacation experience.
Right...
What?
Wow, that was far!
I'm startin' to feel sleepy.
Probably because we've been busy all day.
Slump.
Lemme join you.
Girls, where are your manners?
There's nothing wrong with sleeping on tatami mats!
Is that so?
Then pardon me...
Lie down, Towa! It's relaxing.
No, I'm just fi—
Gotcha!
These mats are wonderful for cooling off.
Indeed.
Awake now?
Where are the others?
Learning how to make sweets.
Want to join them?
No, I'll refrain.
You were turning in your sleep.
Did you have a bad dream?
No, I'm fine.
I've used those words quite often, myself.
I just didn't want to worry others, after all.
But speaking out can lighten the burden.
The evening...
When the sun sets,
I remember my days as Twilight.
I feel as though the darkness will swallow me whole once more!
I'm scared of night falling...
Oh! Towa, you're up?
It's gotten pretty dark, so let's get going!
Indeed.
But to where?
We won't spoil the surprise...
but it's a summer vacation experience!
Coiffure de merveilleuse!
Here we go!
Haruka!
Oh, good evening! Making the rounds?
Yeah! Someone's gotta protect the town!
You disposing of your fireworks safely?
You know it!
Great! Stay safe and have a blast!
Sure thing!
Aww...
Guess that was our last firework.
I want more!
Wait just a minute!
The fireworks have only just begun!
Suitcase #2 is flush with fireworks!
Minami, how hyped were you for this trip?
Here, take this.
Thank you...
The light is beautiful.
Hey, fireworks!
How pretty.
Hey, wanna join us?
Heck yeah!
Perhaps not all nights are bad.
Still scared?
Not at the moment...
If you're ever scared of the night again, just spend it with us like you are now.
You can rely on us a bit more, you know.
Minami...
So, you're not scared of ghosts when the others are near?
N-No!
Though perhaps a bit...
Time for the grand finale! Here we go!
Curse you, Lock...
Commanding me to collect despair with such conceit...
I'd hoped an outing would lift my spirits,
but it's lifted naught but sighs.
Princess Twilight is no more.
I've naught but to forget her...
Who dares disturb my despondence?
It's her! My former Princess Twilight!
How dare she find joy in spite of me!
This shall not do!
Whoah! Wh-Who're you?!
Now, show me your dream.
We'll keep this city safe from fires!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
A Dyspairvil.
Run this way, everyone!
Dyspairvil!
C-Could it be...
darkness?
Such a pity...
Shut!
My elegant Black Princess, I had hoped to serve you for as long as I lived...
And yet...
O, how swiftly sympathy becomes scorn!
You're naught but to perish, Twilight!
Minami!
Shut, you've followed us this far?
Do not interfere.
I am after naught but Twilight.
Then you've no business here!
What?
This lady is Twilight no more.
She is our friend,
Akagi Towa!
Isn't that so,
Towa?
It is!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Prepare yourself this instant!
How beautiful!
Blast it, you only fuel my hatred!
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
Pair!
Dyspair!
Excellent!
Dyspairvil!
Scarlet!
Dyspair!
Not happenin'!
You won't lay another finger on Scarlet!
Flora! Twinkle!
Dyspairvil!
Viiiiiil!
Lily!
Luna!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Shine, O Moon!
Precure!
Full Moon Humming!
So this is what it means to have friends to depend on!
Indeed!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Dyspairvil!
Fireworks!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Spark!
Dyspairvil!
If it is my fate to be pursued by the darkness, then I shall avert my eyes no more!
I shall expel the darkness as often as I must!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Burning!
Adieu.
She truly is beautiful!
Your fate is naught but to taste defeat at my hands!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Please continue to protect this splendid town.
Bummer!
That jerk totally ruined our firework party!
No, I wouldn't call it ruined.
Tonight has been such fun that I won't sleep a wink!
Then let's get home and keep the party going!
It's summer, so a late night or two wouldn't hurt, right?
And I brought just the thing!
Oh yeah, you still had another suitcase, right?
What's in it?
You'll have to wait and see.
Aw, now I'm curious!
Delightful!
Hey!
Girls!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Oh, I feel faint...
Are you okay? Did you catch a cold?
What shall we do? Of all the times for us to not be by her side...
Worry not. I have Perf and Aroma by my side.
Wait, just Perf and Aroma?
And we're not supposed to worry?
Go! Princess Precure:
Save Princess Towa!
Fight On, Royal Fairies!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Chiba Prefecture - Rio (Age 5)
Kumamoto Prefecture - Kanon (Age 6)