SERN will take the time machine.
SERN? What do you mean?
Makise Kurisu.
Okabe Rintarou.
Hashida Itaru.
You three are coming with me.
What about Mayuri?
Shiina Mayuri is...
...not needed.
Don't.
Don't do it.
For FB... FB... FB...
Mayuri?
Mayuri!
What the hell is this?!
Get away from her.
Okabe, get away from her!
She'll kill you, too!
You'll pay for this.
I'll make her pay for this!
42.
CRT.
It's on.
Hurry!
Okabe!
I'll go!
But if it fails...
Do it now!
Okabe!
Leap!
suujuuoku mono kodou no kazu sae
Even the world's billions of heartbeats
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
Are nothing to you but a fleeting and insignificant question
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
We may be trapped in the past or lament the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
But predetermination does not allow the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and imagined futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
Are naught but vain theories we may hold
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what the two clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e
As they point toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
And now I cross the boundary between worlds each second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
Because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no ruupu e to
And a loop in time without sadness will once again
nomikomarete yuku kodoku no kansokusha
Engulf me, a lonely observer
Metaphysics
Necrosis
Mayuri was still in elementary school
when her grandmother died.
She went to the grave every day.
Even six months after her grandmother's death,
she was still going.
She always had her grandmother's pocket watch in her hand,
and she was always, always looking up at the sky.
Like she was waiting for her grandmother to come and get her.
And then one day, there was a ray of light.
It was the kind called Rembrandt Lighting,
or an angel's ladder.
It felt like the light was drawing her up.
Like she was going to disappear...
Mayuri!
Okarin...
I won't let it take you.
You're my hostage.
You're going to be my hostage.
I'll use you for human experiments.
The words that came out of my mouth
were from some show I'd seen as a little kid.
Mayuri and I had watched it together.
Some mad scientist, screaming like an idiot...
I see.
So Mayushii is your hostage, right?
Then, I guess I can't go, huh?
What's wrong?
Were you napping?
What time is it?
What time is it?!
What?
It's almost five.
You're going shopping, right?
Shopping...
I'll order pizza.
Thanks.
Just don't get the tropical special.
I hate that thing.
Agreed.
The time leap worked?
Okabe?
Where's Mayuri? Where is she?!
What's wrong with you, all of a sudden?
Mayushii said she was going to Miss Ruka's,
to invite her to the party, remember?
Are you going shopping?
The development conference is canceled.
Canceled?
Why?
Did something happen?
We're done here for today.
Both of you, go home now!
What's going on?
Just go home!
Okay? Do it!
What's with him?
His phone starts ringing, and then...
Phone?
This is Mayushii.
I can't answer the phone right now!
If you'd like to leave a message...
There's nothing to indicate that the world line changed.
It's different than the D-mail.
I really am back at 5:00 PM.
It's the bullet train!
No, the bullet train is white.
After this, Mayuri will return with Suzuha.
Should I go to the police?
No, who'd believe me?
That I've come from the future?
Three hours left...
I have to do something!
Mayuri!
Mayuri?!
O-Oka... No, Kyouma—
Where's Mayuri?!
Sh-She already left.
Left?
When?
Th-Thirty minutes ago, I guess.
She said she was going back to the lab.
Didn't she get back?
Um, I'm sorry.
It was so nice of you to invite me to the party, but...
Did she say she was stopping anywhere?
Mayuri-chan?
No...
If you see her, tell her to call me right away!
O-Okay.
If the world line hasn't changed,
then if I don't do anything different,
she should do the same things as last time.
Where is she?
Nyan-nyan!
Feyris can't answer the phone right now.
If you need something...
Where are you, Mayuri?
Mayuri?
Too bad.
Assistant...
I told you, we're done today.
Go home—
Be honest.
You time leaped from the future, didn't you?
How could you tell?
The second you answered the phone, you seemed to change.
From the way you're acting,
I can guess that something happened.
Yeah.
But I don't have time to give you the details.
Just run.
Run? Where?
Anywhere.
Just get away from the lab.
Got it?
Tell me later, okay?
Yeah. Tell Daru, too.
Got it.
Okabe...
What is it?
Don't do anything weird.
I know.
Okabe Rintarou!
Hey, where's Ochanomizu—
Have you seen Mayuri?!
Shiina Mayuri?
She just invited me to your party—
Where is she?
Turn right, up there...
Hey, which way is Ochanomizu?
I have to take Nae shopping...
Ask at the police box!
And once you've taken her, don't come back!
What do you mean?
I'll tell you later.
Mayuri...
Mayuri!
Okarin!
Look! It's the first star!
What?
Just come with me!
What about the party?
It's canceled. I told Kurisu and Daru.
Why?
I'll tell you later!
But I asked Suzu-san to come, too,
and Daru-kun was ordering pizza...
Just listen to me!
Okarin...
I'm sorry.
Mayushii doesn't understand...
You always do things I don't understand,
but today, I really don't understand you.
Did you really want to do the experiment, after all?
Mayuri...
That's not it.
But just for now, can you listen to me?
There's no time.
I'll explain the details later, I promise.
Okay.
Sorry. Mayushii just got scared.
Don't apologize.
It's not your fault.
There are so many people here.
It's rush hour.
Huh?
But no one's at the platform...
Once again,
the following lines have been shut down, due to a bomb threat.
They said they don't know when the trains will start again.
How stupid of me!
Not now...
Okarin?
Mayuri, get to the subway now!
Okabe Rintarou, right?
What's wrong?
You're coming with me.
What are you standing there for?
Move!
Run!
Run, as fast as you can!
Who are they?
Okarin!
Go, quickly!
Run, Mayuri!
Shiina Mayuri was the one who died.
Okabe-kun...
I mean, Okabe Rintarou has been captured.
Mayuri!
Damn it!
I won't let you kill her!
Mayuri, I will save you!
I'll save you...
...no matter what!
Canceled?
Why?
Did something happen?
Yeah. Actually...
I got word
that Mr. Braun is planning to return tonight.
Okarin, did you do something again?
Yeah, I suppose so.
But what about Mayuri?
I'll talk to her.
It's dangerous to be here.
We're done here for today.
Was I too forceful?
No...
It doesn't matter if I was acting weird.
For now, I just need them away from the lab!
This is Mayushii.
I can't answer the phone right now!
Why is it taking so long?
It's going to end up like last time!
I need to find Mayuri.
Rukako
Hello?
Rukako! It's me! Okabe!
Oka... I'm sorry, Kyouma—
Where's Mayuri?!
Is Mayuri there?
Mayuri-chan?
Yes.
She's just heading bac—
Stop her!
Tell her not to move until I get there!
She said she was going back to the lab.
Just do as I say!
O-Okay.
Mayuri-chan!
It's the bullet train!
No, the bullet train is white.
Mayuri!
Okarin!
Are you okay?
I was about to go fix Fubuki-chan's costume,
and then go to the lab.
Fubuki-chan?
A cosplay friend of yours?
Yeah!
She said a thread on the costume I made came undone.
I just got a message from her.
So that's it.
Once it's fixed, I'll go right to the lab,
so I'll make it to the party.
Wait. The party...
The party was cancel...
I mean, it was postponed.
Why?
We can't use the lab.
It can't be helped.
I see...
So I wanted you to come with me for a bit.
Right now.
What about Fubuki-chan?
I'm sorry, but do it later.
It's an emergency.
Um, did something happen?
Yeah, we're going to be away for a while.
On a trip.
Together?
Um, well...
I can put Fubuki-chan off till tomorrow,
but this is very sudden.
Where are we going?
I'll tell you later.
We don't have much time to catch the train.
But Mayushii isn't ready at all, and...
Don't worry about it.
Come on, let's go.
Wait, Okarin!
Um...
Huh?
G-Goodbye.
Yeah, bye-bye!
Isn't Akihabara Station that way?
We're taking the subway.
I see.
It's been a really long time
since you pulled me along like this.
Yeah.
We're heading back.
Huh?
Okay.
Let's go.
Assistant
Did something happen?
Tell me later, okay?
Kurisu, huh?
My watch isn't working...
That's strange.
I just wound it.
There are so many people here.
The Sobu line shut down.
Shut down?
Yeah.
A bomb threat was called in.
I see...
Hey, Okarin.
Um, well...
Mayushii has a lot of places she wants to go,
but it's okay for now.
In exchange,
when this is over, I want you to tell me everything.
Yeah.
I promise.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I can't help you.
Let's have that party sometime.
Yeah...
Sometime.
Sometime...
For sure.
Mayuri-oneechan!
It wasn't...
I didn't mean to...
I just wanted to surprise her...
I won't let you kill her!
I will...
...save Mayuri!
kisei sareta chikai mujihi naru, juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
the promise we made in captivity turns out to be a phantom
seimei no tenshi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The angel of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
A flapping butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
A miraculous butterfly
anata he sasageru
I will consecrate them to you
namida no butterfly
A butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
A radiant butterfly
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything may now be rewritten