What's wrong?
They said they
wanna negotiate.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 1]
It's just one man...
He's unarmed...
He's coming now.
Keep your hands in sight...!
You make one wrong move
and we will shoot!
[ROSS]
It's alright.
Go on and let him through...
I know for a fact
that we can trust him.
[BROSH CRIES]
Lieuuuutenannnnnt!
Do you think there's any way
that I could see my husband?
[BREDA OVER INTERCOM]
You can't see him.
It's too dangerous out there.
I'm sorry...
We're still not sure who
we can trust in the military...
We just can't risk it.
[BREDA OVER INTERCOM]
I know it's tough...
...but please be patient.
Yes...
I didn't think about that.
[FATHER] Sooo. You mean to tell
me that you reject the truth?
[ED]
Yeah, exactly.
And listen here...
Don't go thinking you've won
just 'cuz you got us here...
We aren't gonna just sit back
and let you sacrifice us.
[FATHER] Your words will do
nothing to alter your fate.
Let's get out of here...
Can you stand?
[FATHER] No, none of you
will be leaving.
Escaping is futile...
You're already deep
within my stomach.
[DARIUS SHIVERS IN FEAR]
[DARIUS]
What is that stuff...?
This Father guy
that we're after...
Is he beneath those things?
Mustang's still alive.
Right about now,
the good Colonel
is with our father...
Although I'm afraid that I can't
vouch for his
physical well-being.
[AL] May!
What are you doing?
I've come a long
way to talk to him...
Envy told me
that you're immortal.
[MAY CHANG]
So you're not denying it?
That's all I need...
I'll handle this one, Alphonse.
[AL] Wha--... Not on your
own...! He's too powerful!
[MAY CHANG]
It's fine...
He can't control my alkahestry.
[AL] Even if he
binds our alchemy...
you shouldn't fight him
on your own, we can help.
I'll be alright...
Just keep the smaller
Homunculus out of my way.
She makes it sound like
he's the easy one to fight.
[ED THINKS] How were
they able to force
the Colonel through
his gateway?
If he can strong-arm
us through the gate...
Why hasn't he done it before?
[ROY]
Fullmetal.
[ROY] Shortly before
I was deconstructed...
Selim said it was their last
resort and they didn't
have any other choice.
Which can only mean
that it must carry some
kind of risk for them.
[ROY]
Most likely.
Then we might have a shot.
Well look at that...!
[ED]
We can use our alchemy!
[AL]
He ran...!
He didn't even try
to use his shadows!
[ED] That's definitely
a good sign!
[AL]
Yep!
[FATHER] Why must
you rude children
keep destroying my home...?
You should behave
like proper guests.
Enough talk...
Now give me your stone!
[FATHER LAUGHS]
[SHAO MAY SCREAMS]
[SHAO MAY AND MAY CHANG SCREAM]
I did not request your presence
and have no need for it...
Now leave.
[ENERGY BURST]
[MAY CHANG BELLOWS]
No, young lady...!
He's not actually trapped!
[EXPLOSION]
[MAY CHANG SCREAMS]
[MAY CHANG WINCES
AS SHE TUMBLES]
[AL]
May!
[CENTRAL MP 1] What the hell's
going on around here?
[CENTRAL MP 2]
No idea, sir...
We still haven't been able
to contact the command center.
[CENTRAL MP 3]
Reporting in, sir...!
The city's been overrun
by Ishvalan terrorists...
They seem to be attacking MP--
Hold it!
Pardon me...
We simply do not have
the time to explain...
Please forgive us.
[HOUSEWIFE SCREAMS]
[HOUSEWIFE]
No! No! Please...!
Help me! Please don't hurt us!
We're sorry for intruding...
We won't harm you,
we just have a question.
[ISHVALAN 2]
Can you tell us...
Is this your house
here on the map?
[ISHVALAN 3] Wow, I can't
believe how dark it's getting.
[ISHVALAN 4] I hope everyone's
doing alright out there.
Is this the right place?
It sure is...
No doubt about it.
Good...
Now we just wait.
[ISHVALAN 4]
Alright, Scar... It's up to you.
There's something
rather comforting
about facing death like this,
wouldn't you agree?
[BRADLEY]
It's all that matters...
Nothing else
even seems to exist...
outside my pure
instinct to survive.
[BRADLEY] Rank...
personal history and birth...
...race, sex,
the name given to you.
[BRADLEY]
It's all meaningless...
This is the only
thing that's real...
To fight on behalf of
my own life and nothing else.
I've never felt so complete.
[BRADLEY CHUCKLES]
I guess you could say
I've finally arrived.
What's wrong...?
Don't tell me that's
all you've got... Is it?!
Because that's
nowhere near enough!
[BRADLEY] The only chance you
have is to destroy me!
Now fight, nameless human!
[SCAR ROARS AS HE ATTACKS]
[SCAR AND BRADLEY
GRUNT WHILE FIGHTING]
[BRADLEY VOMITS BLOOD]
[BRADLEY BELLOWS]
[SCAR]
You look surprised...
I'd even say shocked...
To be honest...
I'm still a little
surprised myself.
It goes against my beliefs...
I even swore to myself
I'd never use it.
[BRADLEY GRIMACES IN PAIN]
[SCAR] But when I considered the
enormity of what was at stake
and what I could do...
I relented...
and accepted my only choice.
My brother's circle of reconstruction...
I've accepted both
halves of alchemy!
[BRADLEY SMIRKS]
You miserable humans
never give up...
I'll give you that much.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SHAO MAY SCREAMS]
[AL]
May!
Damn... Hey, Al.
Get over there
and help May.
[AL]
What about Pride?
Don't even worry about him...
I can handle him on my own.
[AL]
If you say so.
[SHAO MAY WHIMPERS]
[FATHER LAUGHS]
Young lady!
I would rather you not
keep squirming about, Hohenheim.
[FATHER CHUCKLES]
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse!
[ED] What's the
matter, Pride...?
Your attacks are a little
more half-assed than usual.
Try not to get too confident...
You haven't fulfilled
your purpose yet so I don't--
[ED] So that means you still
can't kill me, right...?
Then I've still got time to
beat you into a
lifeless shadow!
[SELIM] Really...?
Is that your plan...?
Your stature has led you
to prove your worth by always
fighting those who
are larger than you.
So then...
You don't exactly have much
experience fighting those
who are smaller than you!
[AL] Well, Dad...
Sorry if I hit you!
[EXPLOSIONS]
[AL]
Damn brat!
You overlooked the simple fact
that since I have
always been small...
and I did the fighting...
I know exactly how
a runt is gonna try to win!
[SELIM EXPRESSES SHOCK]
[AL]
Teacher!
[IZUMI] His hands-free alchemy
doesn't make for a fair fight!
[FATHER] It appears
the time is upon us.
[SELIM SNICKERS]
[ED BELLOWS]
[AL WHIMPERS]
[IZUMI GRIMACES]
[ROY STRUGGLES]
[ED GRUNTS]
[FATHER] I'm done with
indulging your frivolity...
It's time to put you
to work, my sacrifices.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
It looks like night out there.
[CREMIN]
Hurry...
Please hurry...
We've gotta get to
the center of the circle.
Please! We'll die here!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
Quit acting up!
[CREMIN] I'm begging you
to take me to the center...!
[CREMIN] Please do it...!
We'll be swallowed!
[CREMIN]
Hurry!
It's finally time!
[IMPACT RUMBLE]
[BIRDS CHATTERING
AS THEY TAKE FLIGHT]
This planet of ours...
Have you ever considered
the possibility that it might
in fact be a life form?
Actually...
It would be more accurate
to refer to it as a
vast nervous system.
[FATHER] One that's retained its
every memory since its inception
and has witnessed
the universe unfold.
[FATHER] Just think of
the massive quantity
of information that such
a system would hold.
[FATHER]
But an even better question...
How much power could one gain
if they opened
that system's gateway?
Have you ever
considered that...?
Think about it.
[ED GASPS]
[FATHER] And now that
I have you gathered...
I shall use you as sacrifices
to open the planet's gateway!
That is a pretty
good plan, pops!
Where'd he come from?!
[GREED] Hope you don't mind
me using it for myself!
[GREED] This world...
will finally belong to me!
He got him.
[GREED CHUCKLES]
[FATHER] I was expecting you
to make an appearance.
[FATHER] I know
you too well, my son...
[FATHER]
Have you forgotten that you
were born from
my extracted avarice?
[FATHER] Anything that you
might happen to desire...
I can assure you
that I desired it first.
[GREED]
Ed!
[HOHENHEIM COUGHS]
[EXPLOSION]
[FATHER LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
The very center of this world...
...is right here!
[FATHER LAUGHS INSANELY]
Evil bastard!
[SELIM SNICKERS]
[FATHER LAUGHS INSANELY]
[DARIUS] What
the hell's going on?!
[PANICKED MUMBLING]
What is this?!
[TERROR-STRICKEN CRIES]
[ED CRIES OUT]
[FATHER LAUGHS WICKEDLY]
[EXPLOSION]
[GREED BELLOWS]
[MAY CHANG SCREAMS]
Fight for me...
Let your gateways
fight for my soul...
Shed your energy for me!
[FATHER LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[FATHER] What truly
magnificent energy!
It's immensity
is indescribable...!
I can barely contain it!
Now that I've
obtained enough power...
I will open up
this planet's gateway!
[MASSIVE ENERGY RELEASE]
[CROWD MUMBLES IN FEAR]
[WOMAN]
What's happening?!
[ASSEMBLED CROWD
BEGINS TO CHOKE]
[PEOPLE IN CROWD GASP FOR AIR]
[MASS HYSTERIA AND SCREAMING]
[SOLDIERS CHOKING
FOR AIR AND COLLAPSING]
[CREMIN CHOKING]
[ENERGY BURSTS]
[EXPLOSION]
[WINRY CHOKING]
[PIANKO] Winry...
Win... ry...
Why can't... I move?
[DOOR OPENS]
Ms. Pinako...
What's happening?
The next time I see you... Hohenheim...
I'm gonna slug you.
Save us, Ed... please... Ed.
[MASSIVE ENERGY RELEASES]
[GIANT DOORS RUMBLING OPEN]
[FATHER LETS OUT
A GHOSTLY GROAN]
[FATHER BELLOWS]
Hear me, God!
[FATHER] I demand you answer
the cry of my soul!
[FATHER]
Come to me!
[DOORS RUMBLING OPEN]
[FATHER]
Join me...! Yes...!
I will no longer be bound
to you or your consequences!
I'll force you down to this
earth and into my bowels...!
You have no choice
but to be absorbed!
[FATHER CRIES OUT]
[EXPLOSION]
[NARRATOR] If the only
word you can muster
to describe him is "god,"
then you have no choice but
to bow before him, humans...
But if you refuse to
acknowledge him as such,
then fight for the existence
he aims to control.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 61:
He Who Would Swallow God.
God is the creation of humans
with nowhere left to turn.