In year 850,
the Colossal Titan once again appeared out of nowhere and broke the wall,
permitting the Titans to advance further.
Soldiers fell one after another facing down the Titans.
Then...
Eren!
Come!
Eren fell prey to a Titan as well.
Mikasa's just amazing.
How can she move that fast?
She isn't as calm as usual.
So I'll win, no matter what!
I'll survive, no matter what!
Just as Mikasa was cornered,
a mysterious Titan suddenly appeared to fend off the other Titans.
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
I Can Hear a Heart Beating
Defense of Trost (pt 4)
Okay, your maneuver gear's good to go.
I've given you all my blades too.
Just leave me this one.
At the very least, I refuse to be eaten alive.
B-But...
Armin.
I won't leave you behind.
B-But, with so many Titans around,
you can't possibly carry me along...
Let's get going!
No! Please, let me go!
I'll just end up getting more of my friends killed!
Wait!
Listen to me!
I've got a suggestion.
A suggestion?
It's a two-person operation,
so you two should decide whether to carry it out.
I know it's crazy, but...
Couldn't we use that Titan?
That Titan?
It's only attacking other Titans.
It seems uninterested in humans.
I was thinking of luring it to the supply tower somehow.
If it handles the other Titans for us,
we could get everyone out of this alive!
Lure it? How would we even pull that off?
I think it acts on instinct.
If you two defeat the Titans in its vicinity,
then it'll start looking for other Titans.
Most likely, it'll move towards the Titans swarming around Headquarters!
How could we do something so risky based on a mere guess?!
But if it does work, we could eliminate every Titan at HQ in one fell swoop!
It's at least worth a shot.
Are you serious?!
If we're facing certain death either way,
the path to take is the path with a chance of victory.
Let's go with Armin's plan.
You want to side with a Titan to fight against Titans?
Yes. Precisely.
It won't even be funny if we fail.
But if we succeed, everyone will be saved.
Make up your mind.
I get it! Dammit, I get it!
Am I really cut out for this?
Can I handle a position with this much responsibility?
No! Wait!
The Titans are relatively concentrated around there.
This is our chance!
Go! Hurry to HQ while you can!
It's now or never!
We're finished if our gas runs out!
Everyone! Move in!
Jean!
Thanks!
I only got out because of you.
Huh?
It's all thanks to you!
I told you before, didn't I?
You're cut out to be a leader!
I seriously don't know.
Dammit!
How many of us made it?
Using the deaths of our comrades...
How many died on my command?
You're part of the supply squad, aren't you?!
Stop it, Jean!
These bastards abandoned us!
Do you even have a clue how many died?!
The Titans invaded the supply depot!
What could we have done?!
It's your job to figure something out!
Take cover!
Dammit!
There are too many people gathered here!
Hurry! Inside!
Run for your lives!
Where's Mikasa?!
She crashed back there! She's been eaten!
This is normal...
This is reality, isn't it?
Was I just chasing a delusional dream?
I thought I knew reality.
Just thinking about it, it's obvious...
There's no way to beat these gigantic monstrosities.
What?!
What... is that?
Mikasa?!
It's empty...
We did it! We just barely made it!
You're... all alive?
We did it, Armin!
Ouch!
Your plan was a success!
Everyone! That Titan's an abnormality that slaughters other Titans!
It's not even interested in attacking humans!
If we play our cards right, we can all get outta here alive!
We'd... use the Titan?
You'd rely on a Titan's help?
That's more delusional than any dream!
It's not a dream.
I don't care if it's an abnormal or whatever.
Just let it rampage here for as long as possible.
Realistically, that's our best option for survival.
Currently Disclosable Information
Design of the 3D Maneuver Gear (pt 3)
(The fan unit)
The gas is blown onto the fans to make them spin
Output power is controlled by the gas pressure
Currently Disclosable Information
Illustration of the Titans' size
It's okay.
That Titan's stronger than average.
They can't take over the building while it's rampaging outside.
How much do you know about that Titan?
Shouldn't we discuss that after we're safe?
True that. Let's get out of here alive first.
We found some!
They're Military Police supplies, though they are covered in dust...
Will three bullets be enough?
Do these guns even work against the Titans in the first place?
It's better than nothing.
Even if there are still seven 3-4 meter class Titans in the supply room,
blinding them all at once isn't impossible with this much firepower.
First we'll use the lift to lower a large number of people into the center of the chamber.
Next, they'll fire directly into the faces of all seven Titans at once.
We'll blind them.
The next instance will decide everything.
Seven other people hiding near the ceiling will swoop down to attack their weak spots while they're blind.
In other words... if we follow this plan,
we'll be gambling everything on this single attack.
The whole point is for seven people to kill all seven Titans simultaneously.
The seven people should be the most physically capable ones.
You'll have to shoulder the burden of everyone's lives...
I'm sorry.
No problem.
Whoever fails, all of us will die.
The risk is the same.
But...
I'm a nobody.
Is my plan really the best option?
We've got no other choices except your plan.
There's no time left to think.
This idea's our only shot.
Now, we've just gotta give it everything we've got.
Don't worry. Be confident.
You've got a talent for reasoning out the best solution.
That intuition has saved my life before, and Eren's life too.
Huh? When?
The lift's ready!
The guns too! All of them are loaded!
You just aren't aware yet.
I'll tell you more later.
Okay...
But can we really kill the Titans without our 3D Maneuver Gear?
Sure we can.
We're only up against 3-4 meter class ones.
It's easy to target their weak spot.
Who cares how big they are?
It's always the spot at the nape of their necks...
Length: 1 vertical meter. Width: 10 centimeters!
Or just ram your blade up their assholes.
That's their only other weak spot.
What?! I've never heard of that move!
First time I've heard about it too.
Reiner, those might just be your last words.
We're all good. There's still only seven.
Follow the plan!
Calm down! Lure them in closer!
Hold!
We shouldn't fight at a disadvantage
if we want to keep casualties to the bare minimum.
We must end it in this one strike!
Wait!
Ready!
Fire!
I got it!
The others?
Pardon me... for suddenly... stabbing you... from behind...
Oh shit!
It's Sasha and Connie!
Hurry! Help them!
I'm...
I'm really sorry!
Mikasa!
You saved me!
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm safe, thanks to you!
Then stand! Now!
Sorry...
Never mind.
Geez. That was too close, Annie.
I'm glad you weren't injured.
We got them all!
Everyone stock up on supplies!
Hell yeah!
We're safe now!
No more Titans are coming in!
That abnormal berserker's keeping them at bay!
I surrendered to a Titan...
How can I look everyone in the eyes now?!
I'll spank you for that later!
Let's just get outta here quick!
I don't think I'm cut out to be a commander.
So don't say that anymore.
There's something I'd like to tell you. Don't get mad, please.
You're not strong, Jean.
That's why you can understand how the weak feel.
And you're good at judging the situation correctly.
You always clearly know what you're supposed to do, don't you?
Your orders were right.
That's why I could run. That's why I'm alive.
Are you all ready?
Let's get outta here!
We've gotta bail now!
Go! Go! Go!
We need to meet up with the main units!
Mikasa?
Mikasa, we've gotta hurry!
That Titan...
They're eating it...
Its body can't regenerate?
I think uncovering the truth about that Titan may be the key
to freeing ourselves from this desperate situation...
I agree.
If they just rip it to shreds like that, then we won't have learned a single thing!
We should get rid of those Titans currently devouring it,
and at least try to keep it alive.
Are you insane, Reiner?!
We can finally escape this deathtrap!
But what if that Titan could become an ally?
Don't you think it'd be a weapon more powerful than any cannon?
Our... ally?
Are you for real?!
That's...
The abnormal that ate Thomas!
Hey...
What was that about helping it?
Looks like it burnt itself out.
Whatever. Let's get going!
There's no way that monster's on our side!
Titans are Titans.
What is it?
Mikasa!
It's Eren...
He's even got his limbs back...
Eren was eaten by that Titan back then.
What just happened here?
Then Eren... did all of this?
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
"I'll exterminate all the Titans."
Eren's ironclad determination transformed him into a Titan.
Regardless, the Garrison designates him the enemy of mankind
and turns their blades against him.
Where is the Left Arm?
Defense of Trost (pt 5)