Please...
...marry me!
I guess there's no choice.
Since you've said it, I'll marry you.
Note: Takasu Ryuuji's Pen
Ryuu-chan, look!
Taiga-chan gave birth to so many puppies!
They're yours.
So it was a dream...
Horror Movie: I Gave Birth To Puppies
Even though it's finally summer break...
...watching these stupid DVD's gave me a nightmare.
A future like that is pretty awful even for a dream.
Oh, Taiga!
I had a horrible dream.
You were a dog, and the dog was my husband.
Anyway...
It was the worst dream I've ever had.
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
You, Going to the Sea
A premonition?
Correct.
That dream is a warning which tells me if I don't have a plan, I would have a terrible future waiting for me.
So, in order to change the future...
I think one side should fully support the other side starting from the trip tomorrow.
I understand that, but...
Why are we playing badminton?
I told you.
It's so that we can decide...
...on the side that's giving support.
Listen, don't ever touch the range.
Stir the rice bran once a day,
and remember to change Inko-chan's water in the morning and at night.
I wrote the rest down.
I'm leaving now.
Where are you going?
I told you already. I'm going on a trip.
Bye, Ya-chan.
The weather looks like it'll be good today.
I'll be looking forward to your support on that "plan".
Hey, is it really okay?
Fine, you win! Just get him off me!
I would've won if that retarded dog wasn't there.
It's probably your punishment for choosing something you're good at.
Seriously, nothing good ever comes with dogs.
Will it really go smoothly?
Just leave it to me.
By the time this trip ends, Minorin and you will be...
What is it?
What's wrong?
Good morning, your timing is perfect!
Amazing, simply amazing!
What's wrong? You don't look good!
Say something!
What's wrong with them?
My, this is a perfect day to set off!
Don't look!
Speaking of which, Ami still isn't here.
There's still some time left before the meet up time.
Really? Then let's continue!
Huh?
What's up with them?
No one is here.
Y-Yo...
You're two minutes late, Ami.
Good morning, Amin!
You're late, stupid Chihuahua.
I wonder where everyone is...
Hey, don't run away, you stupid Chihuahua!
Ami, we're here!
This tastes awesome!
The plum inside makes it even more awesome!
As expected of Takasu.
Do you want to be my wife?
No thanks.
Gosh, you're so mean.
Huh?
Speaking of which, Aisaka-san isn't here yet, is she late?
Takasu-kun, do you have her contac-
Ow!
What the hell are you doing?
My, the stupid Chihuahua was awake?
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open.
We're on a trip, so don't fight!
Oh yeah, Kawashima, what have you been doing during the summer holidays?
Me?
I was working the whole time.
So you started to work again?
What about you, Minorin?
Part-time job, club activities, part-time job, club activities, part-time job, club activities...
Taiga, what about you?
I...
What is it, Taiga?
...made this.
I think I just heard "senpai" in a weird voice...
Is this...
Yeah, supernatural soundtracks from the CD I reserved.
As expected!
No, I'm going to scream!
Aisaka, do you like horror in general?
Maybe...
That's unexpected.
It's also unexpected for Kushieda to be afraid of supernatural stuff.
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm super scared!
When I say I'm super scared,
I mean I'm seriously super scared...
Minorin is really afraid of horror,
ghosts and supernatural stuff.
That's why we shall scare Minorin to death.
Then you'll save her, since she would be in despair.
"I'll protect you, Kushieda", like that.
This is the "Scare Minorin, then Prince Charming Will Arrive" plan.
Anyway, all scary things are forbidden!
It's the sea!
God, how long are we going to walk?
We can see it already.
Go in and you should be able to go to the balcony.
So this is Ami's villa!
Are we staying here?
Correct, Minori-chan.
Wow! I'm super grateful!
But we need to clean up the place first.
No one has been here since last year.
L-Last year?
Yeah...
This is going to be one long battle...
Since such a beautiful sea is in front of us, just leave cleaning for later on!
She's right, we'll clean later!
Me too!
I'm going, too.
What about you, Takasu-kun?
All right!
Why am I cleaning by myself?
This feels so nice!
Hey...
What is it?
That looks like a human head.
A drowned body!
What should I do?
I've touched corpse water!
It seems like they're having fun.
You really came, Yuusaku.
Of course.
Takasu came, so as his best friend, I have to come.
What about the student council?
What are you talking about?
Nothing really...
Takasu!
Ami wants us to buy stuff.
There's a motorbike in the warehouse.
Motorbike?
Take Taiga with you.
Aisaka?
I don't want to go...
I'm scared of bikes...
What?
Be careful.
I got it.
Bye!
You had a chance to be with him alone...
I have my own plans.
Before they come back, we have to find a possible place to carry out that "plan".
Just be honest if you're lovestru-
There was a fly, a fly!
Seriously, even if she says a possible place...
Is this the bathroom?
I should clean this place-
W-Who is it?
Sorry! I didn't notice!
Takasu-kun?
I'll leave immediately...
You're pretty daring for coming in while a girl is taking a shower.
I-It wasn't on purpose!
It's fine, I'll keep it a secret from everyone if we do it now...
What are you talki-
Hey, don't you want to do it with me?
Do what?!
Clean the bathtub!
My gosh, what were you thinking about?
What's with that expression? It's priceless!
Taiga!
The stupid Chihuahua?
Pretending to take a shower?
Toying around with a guy's pure heart?
So, have you completed the
investigation on the second floor?
You suck!
That's why you got trolled by the stupid Chihuahua!
Fine, I'll check it out myself.
I'll teach the stupid Chihuahua a lesson while I'm at it.
Hey, you stupid Chihuahua!
She was really taking a shower...
The stupid Chihuahua is like...
Boing and boing...
...and BOING!
Cut the pointless crap!
We're back!
You bought a lot of stuff...
Where's Kitamura?
He went to park the motorbike.
I-I see...
Let me hold it.
It's all right...
...since you bought everything.
Really?
W-What's wrong?
No...
There was something that touched my... my neck...
You're imagining things.
M-Maybe...
I guess-
Something really touched me just then!
It's like sticky... It's like seaweed!
This is the smell of seaweed! It's seaweed!
It must the ghosts of animals
which were killed by seaweed!
Sea otters!
It has to be the bodies of sea otters
if we're talking about seaweed!
A sea otter that's covered with seashells?
This is a curse of the sea otters and seaweeds!
No, I don't want spicy!
I like it spicy!
How can you eat it if it's not sweet?!
Hey, Ryuuji!
I know, I'll make a sweet-flavored one just for you.
Special treatment for Aisaka-san again...
You'll get hated by other girls like that...
Including Minori-chan...
Did someone call me?
Is it almost done?
It looks pretty good.
Yeah, I just have to put in the curry powder...
Hey, you guys should prepare-
You guys are preparing dinner already?
Should I help set the table?
Y-You...
Hey, Taiga!
Yuusaku, what's wrong with you?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I heard Takasu's voice, so...
I didn't know you girls were here.
Are you an idiot?
Taiga, get a hold of yourself!
I'm so sorry!
Hey...
Show us your naked body, you narcissist guy!
Stop it already...
Why are you saying that? You phony!
Stop it...
Not bad, not bad!
Just now...
I saw a black and hairy thing...
It's probably the ghost of the seaweed!
Seaweed...
Kushieda?
Yuusaku, you're the worst.
I'm sorry.
Whatever, just go!
Oh...
Everyone, be careful!
There's an evil spirit in this house...
Is there something I can do?
Make the curry super spicy...
Got it.
It looks good!
I was kind of rushed,
but I made it very spicy as Kushieda wanted.
Yay!
Let's eat!
I'm going to eat!
Not bad.
It's pretty good.
It's not as spicy as I thought.
Really?
Taiga, do you want to try some?
You're right, it's not-
Minorin?
WHAT?!
It's spicy!
In the throat, it...
It's so spicy that it hurts!
It's here! It's coming into my head!
Woah! Again!
Are you guys all right?
Takasu-kun...
You're amazing!
It's so spicy and delicious!
This certainly has a mysterious drawback...
I feel strange...
It's so good!
There's more if you want.
Refill!
I thought I was going to die.
Okay, I'll go clean the dishes.
I'll go with-
What is it?
It was too spicy...
I need some medicine now.
Do you have a stomachache?
The medicine is...
Aisaka, are you not feeling well?
I bought some anti-dyspeptic pills.
It's in my room, do you want to come with me?
T-That's...
Please take of her.
Wha- Wai-
It's a chance for you to be alone with him.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Then I'll leave her to you.
Hey.
I have a stomachache, too...
Just kidding.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
Because you were dazing off...
I'll never get tired by looking at you.
Is that a compliment?
It's complicated.
What is?
Oh right, let's go to the seaside
now if it's all right with you...
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Help me with the glass cups.
I'll do it.
Sorry, what did you say?
Nothing.
Enough water?
Is it working?
Probably...
I see, that's great.
I'd feed bad if I saw you in pain.
Oh, do you want to lie down for a bit?
You're really good at washing up.
That's because I always do it during work.
Takasu-kun, that was some amazing curry.
No, you're flattering me...
Oh, right.
I'll give you something for helping me.
Keep it a secret from everyone.
Takasu-kun.
Does the green tea ice cream good?
Yeah, it does.
It probably tastes average.
There are a lot of stars.
They're beautiful.
We're alone together...
Is this a chance for me?
K-Kushieda, do you have a boyfriend?
I wonder if the seaweed ghost is still around?
Takasu-kun, have you ever seen ghosts?
No, I haven't...
I believe ghosts exist in this
world, but I've never seen them.
I don't believe people who said they've seen them.
I've also thought about this in the same way:
I believe in the future, I'll fall in love, get married and become happy.
But actually, I've never had that feeling for anyone before.
I feel distant to those who talk about love in this world.
That's because I can't see it.
Since ghosts don't exist, I'll never see them, so I'm going to give up.
That's why my answer to your question is...
No, I don't.
Takasu-kun, what about you? Can you see ghosts?
I think I can see them.
That's why I go to places like supernatural spots and watch horror movies.
I think like this:
When someone who believes in ghosts sees a ghost, they'll get shocked, too.
There are some who will continue to think they don't exist even if they see it,
but there are also some who will see it because they try their best.
That's why you can't be sure that you'll never see it.
Oh, what's that?
A UFO?
It's probably a satellite.
Satellite...
Oh, I thought it was a UFO.
I think it would be great if you can see ghosts.
Perhaps there are ghosts that want to be seen by you...
That's why a lot of strange things happened today.
The seaweed ghost was telling that it's there!
Why are you suddenly saying that?
I wonder when I'll see it.
No, it's nothing!
She's one weird person.
Ryuuji, my stomach doesn't hurt anymore.
Oh, then?
I'm so full!
Why am I also...
Hey, what should we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm talking about our plan.
You're making it impossible.
What about you?
I'm just supporting you.
Gosh, it's actually so tiring.
I thought spending a whole day with Kitamura-kun would be enjoyable.
But it's giving me a nervous breakdown...
I guess so.
But I'm totally fine being with you.
What are you talking about?
How rude!
This is so stupid.
This house is so big, but we're sitting so close to each other.
I think it's because we're used to being cramped in a small apartment.
Hey you.
Ryuuji.
Sometimes, I think that dream is kind of...
What's wrong?
Nothing, let's go to sleep.
Good night.
Huh?
Did I leave my bag in here?
What is this?
It's sticky...
Ryuuji!
What do you think this is?
I left it in my bag...
But it was warm when I touched it!
It's like someone put it on just then...
There's something strange with my room, too.
There were strands of hair on my pillow...
What was that-
N-No, it's...
This has to be a dream!
Yeah, this has to be a dream!
It's a sequel to the doghouse dream!
Then we should wake up if we close our eyes, right?
Yes, we will!
I hope...
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
Fireworks
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
I'm scared of freaky things! I'm scared of ghosts! I'm scared of monsters!
Calm down, Kushieda!
But...
I'm scared of UFO's the most.