Togame!
Are you okay?
Togame!!
Togame! Stay with me!
Togame! Togame! Togame!
Togame!!
meguriatta ga un no tsuki
巡り逢ったが運の尽き
Our encounter becomes thy fortune's end
Mazui
presents
Katana-
gatari
harari koboreochiru
ハラリ 零れ落ちる
Though words doth joined
kotoba tsuranetatote
言葉 連ねたとて
From my lips run over
dare mo watashi ni aru makoto fure mo dekin jaro
誰もわたしに在る真 触れも出来んじゃろ
Can yet any convey the truth I hold?
sakura mau ga gotoku
サクラ 舞うが如く
As cherry blossoms doth dance
konjou to wa osaraba
今生とはおさらば
To this life I bid farewell
saredo oya ni moratta
されど親に貰った
Indeed this body, parent-hatched,
kono mi ga kawaii
この身が可愛い
I cherish duly
inochi yori omoi
命より重い
But graver than life,
bebe matoi warau
ベベ纏い微笑う
Here, smile-clad
kizu wa taenu kenka joutou
傷は絶えぬ喧嘩上等
Put forth battle, such my scars not fade
kakugoshiiya
覚悟しいや
Ready I stand
nuite wa modosu katana to saya tachikiru ha shura
抜いては戻す 刀と鞘 断ち斬るは修羅
To draw is to return, the sword and sheath, to cut what is the battle
sono sakeme ni ochita yume no fu wa muzan zo
その裂け目に堕ちた夢の腑は無惨ぞ
The heart of the dream abyss-fallen lies bestial
ai mamiete tagiraseru chi wo wakeaeru nara
相まみえて滾らせる血を分け合えるなら
If we share such seething blood as we face,
itoshii sonata todome wo
愛し其方 止めを
Then, my love,
sashitekunnamashi
刺してくんなまし
Deliver the finishing blow
hana no sakari ga oshii kae
花の盛りが惜しいかえ
Dost thou lament the flowers' bloom?
Seitou
Hakari
Scales,
the True
The army general director in support of critical tasks under direct control of Yanari Shogun of the Owari Shogunate, Togame the Strategian.
The strange task she is performing started three days ago,
when she and the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika arrived here at Hyakkeijou in Oushuu,
and met the 10th sword Seitou Hakari's owner, Higaki Rinne.
Oushuu - Hyakkeijou
Three
days ago
Hyakkeijou.
This is where everyone in Hida Takahito's rebellion was publicly executed.
It is a land of fate for these two.
What is this...
My chest hurts...
Like it's being compressed or something.
It feels like something important to me is being trampled.
Togame!
I never imagined that my homeland would be in such a state when I finally came back to visit.
Good grief...
Hey, is there really a holy man living in a place like this?
It doesn't look like anyone can survive here.
Should we go check out the nearby towns?
No, that won't be necessary.
Higaki Rinne is here, just hidden from us.
What do you mea—
Why is there a girl here?
Oh?
Is that how you see me?
It's been a while since I was a girl.
I guess I'll have some fun.
Well anyway, pleased to meet you.
I am Higaki Rinne.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
You're Higaki Rinne?
The holy man?
Indeed I am.
Yo, Togame-chan.
Yep, you don't even have to say it.
You're after Seitou Hakari, correct?
I see, I see.
Sure, I'll hand it over.
It's buried over there, so go ahead and dig it up.
It's probably about 30 meters underground.
You have to do it yourself of course, Togame-chan.
It's right underneath where you're standing.
Well, have fun!
He disappeared...
Togame! Are you okay?
It's morning already?
Don't overdo it.
Just rest for today!
I can't do that.
I have to dig 30 meters by myself.
Whatever happened to your schemes?
Normally you'd have come up with some plan to negotiate with Higaki.
I don't want to see him.
Even since finding Higaki Rinne, you've been acting really strange.
It's hard for me to just watch you being cornered like that.
Then don't watch!
Higaki Rinne, huh...
What's wrong, Yasuri-kun?
Togame-chan is in her own little world digging, huh?
Because you went and buried Hakari 30 meters underground.
Why did you bury Seitou Hakari?
It was just a hassle.
And throwing away something that a friend gave me would be kind of rude, so...
It was just the most convenient way.
You got it from a friend?
Yeah.
From Shikizaki Kiki himself.
From Shikizaki Kiki?!
Yep.
Wait, how old are you??
Around 300 years?
350 if you include the time I was human.
Have we met somewhere before?
Nope.
I'm a holy man here, after all.
I fundamentally avoid things of the world.
But I sort of feel like I know you...
That's because of how you're seeing me.
What you're seeing is a projection of your memory.
Projection of my memory?
Right, a true perception based on your true memories.
Hakari doesn't have anything to do with it.
People look past my own existence and see a perception of their own memories.
Even with me here, we don't really exist.
That's what a holy man is.
I don't really understand you...
What exactly is a holy man?
Well, in a word, a holy man is something like a mirror to people.
A mirror?
Yeah.
A magic mirror that reflects the truth.
Yasuri-kun, have you heard of this foreign fairytale?
What?
In a far off land there lived a queen.
She had a mirror that she always asked,
"Mirror, mirror on the wall, who is the fairest one of all?"
The queen wanted the mirror to say it was her, but it would reply with the name of another whom she hated.
What do you think, Yasuri-kun?
Should the mirror have given that answer?
It's not like a mirror can talk in the first place!
Exactly.
It wasn't the mirror answering, but rather the queen's true feelings responding to her vanity.
If what you say is true then everything just becomes what you want to see.
A holy man doesn't do anything.
Or rather, cannot do anything.
It's you humans who actually carry out tasks.
Doesn't anything come to mind when I say that?
The instant you saw me, you gave me this form.
Itezora Konayuki...
Nee-chan...
Kiguchi Zanki?
Tsuruga Meisai...
Itezora Konayuki, Nee-chan, Kiguchi Zanki, and Tsuruga Meisai, huh?
I lost to those three.
Three?
I didn't lose to Tsuruga Meisai, but...
Sounds like it was a harsh experience.
You feel regret and guilt, right?
Yasuri-kun, looking at your own memories is recognizing the parts of you that you don't want to face.
People change their memories to suit what they're most comfortable with.
However, that doesn't work with me.
It seems I've failed.
At this point I've conveyed to you all that I needed to, so we'll part here.
When you're with me, you will have to face your darkest memories whether you want to or not.
Yasuri-kun.
From the perspective of a holy man beyond human understanding...
You too will have to face the darkness you avoid.
The 12 Maniwa Corps heads has been reduced to just two.
W-What should we do, Houou sama?
There's nothing we can do.
With the loss of Oshidori, we have no choice but to continue on with our plan.
We will head for Oushuu.
Additionally, we don't know when that man will make his appearance.
W-What is he, I wonder?
I believe he's a subordinate of Princess Hitei.
Princess Hitei...
Houou-sama...
Yes?
Might you have any idea of who that man actually is?
The way you've been talking about him, it sounds like you know him from long ago...
You're pretty sharp.
I have an idea, but I'm sure I'm mistaken.
M-Mistaken?
Right.
There's no way he could still be alive, or that he'd be working under Princess Hitei.
He was a ninja of pride and respect.
This was before you were even born.
N-Ninja?!
Was he your friend?
Like I said, it can't be him.
That man died long ago.
There aren't any ninja left who hold their head high, us included.
Pengin...
If we succeed at the negotiations with the strategian and manage to get all the Perfected Deviant Blades, we'll be retiring from active duty.
And I must bear the responsibility for losing 10 of the 12 heads.
I will entrust the future of the clan to the next generation.
Y-You're joking...
It's no joke.
In fact, the only one left to hold the torch after I'm gone will be you, Pengin.
I am but a relic of the previous generation,
along with the strategian and Kyotouryuu and Princess Hitei...
And also, Shikizaki Kiki's Perfected Deviant Blades.
Houou-sama...
Now then, let us hurry.
That masked man may attack at any time.
I... I see.
Yo, Yasuri-kun.
You look bored.
Becoming weaker when wielding a sword is almost like a curse.
Curse?
The day after winning Outou Nokogiri
Shinou Issou Dojo
Kyotouryuu: Bellflower!
Bellflower
Ow...
Impressive.
I thought I'd be able to keep up the act for a bit longer, but this is my limit.
It's my loss, Shichika-dono.
What do you think?
I believe I may have shone some light on your troubles.
I don't really get it...
What I'm saying is "To excel at an art is to excel at versatility".
Even for an amateur such as myself,
I can still put up some semblance of a fight.
You're saying it's strange that I'd get weaker by holding a training sword?
That's why I used the word "curse".
This is just my intuition as a swordsman, but in the same way that the Shinou Issou school holds certain tenets at its core,
your Kyotouryuu may also have certain core concepts that make it what it is.
Nee-chan!
I am a sword.
As are you.
Shichika...
My little brother...
You finally killed me.
No!
I... I...
Is this what happens when a sword tries to use a sword?
The complete inability to wield a sword is the nature of Kyotouryuu.
Nee-chan!!
A sword can't use a sword...
Is that the "curse" of Kyotouryuu?
Congratulations, Yasuri-kun!
It seems you understand now.
Good job!
There's one thing I want to ask.
What's that?
You said that your appearance and behavior are a projection from my memories, right?
Exactly.
Then who did you get that arrogant personality from?
Ah, that comes from how Togame-chan sees me.
You've taken a form from Togame's memories?
Yep.
Because you two saw me at the same time.
My appearance and behavior are from your memories, and this personality is from hers.
So even Togame has something she's weak against?
Everyone has something difficult to deal with, or that they don't want to remember.
Something Togame finds difficult to deal with?
Hida Takahito!
Hida Takahito?
Yes, that personality is exactly like my father.
That pompous manner of speech, those antics, that cavalier attitude...
And to top it all, forcing me to do physical labor.
It's exactly the sort of thing that guy would do!
I-I see...
Recognize the parts of yourself that you don't want to face...
It's true that my father is what came to mind upon returning here.
In his dying breath, he told me something.
For me to have forgotten something so important...
I guess that unpleasant woman is with Higaki Rinne around now...
Owari Castle grounds
Princess Hitei's Palace
Higaki Rinne the holy man?
Though, to entrust Seitou Hakari to that holy man of all people...
That's very much like something you'd do.
I wonder if he's there to get in the strategian's way?
Don't be mistaken here...
It's not like I'm the one who gave it to Higaki Rinne.
In fact, it's a bother for me as well that he has it.
More importantly, what happened with Dokutou Mekki?
The most poisonous of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades, Dokutou Mekki...
For you to have failed at assassinating Maniwa Houou and let him run off with it...
I am dishonored.
Dokutou Mekki in the hands of Maniwa Houou...
I honestly have no idea if this'll bring misfortune or catastrophe.
But if the strategian does manage to get a hold of Seitou Hakari,
the stage will finally be set for all of Shikizaki Kiki's 12 Perfected Deviant Blades to be assembled.
The fulfillment of your ultimate desire is at hand.
Stop, stop.
I don't know who might be listening, so refrain from saying anything careless.
The way you put it, it almost sounds like I'm the descendant of the legendary swordsmith Shikizaki Kiki who ruled over the Sengoku era,
and that I've have kept track of the Perfected Deviant Blades and stayed one step ahead of that unpleasant woman to collect them.
That's totally not true of course, so there's no need to say it.
Indeed.
And of course, you are by no means Shikizaki Kiki's descendant.
My apologies for saying something that might cause a misunderstanding.
That's right, I am Princess Hitei.
I deny anything of myself outside of that.
Whether I achieve my desire or not, I still deny it.
Also...
Something's been bothering me.
You don't have to do it now, but could you look into something for me?
What might that be?
I called the strategian and Kyotouryuu here not long ago...
After I told them where Seitou Hakari was, Shichika-kun seemed kind of strange...
10 days ago
Seitou Hakari is somewhere around Hyakkeijou in Oushuu.
Its owner is the holy man Higaki Rinne.
What about the strategian?
Unpleasant as always.
Come to think of it, that's her first time in Oushuu isn't it?
I wonder why?
She's part of the army, so wouldn't she be familiar with that area?
Well, it might just be my imagination, but I don't mind the idea of sending you out on a wild goose chase either.
The relationship between Yasuri Shichika and Hyakkeijou...
Or maybe it's something to do with the strategian?
Go find out for me.
As you wish.
The two demonesses of the Owari Shogunate.
Real names unknown, history unknown—
Princess Hitei and the strategian Togame.
The day of their showdown is fast approaching.
What?
Higaki Rinne received Seitou Hakari from Shikizaki Kiki himself?
He said he got it as a friend.
How could you forget to tell me something as important as that?
Well, I just told you...
Is there anything else you forgot to tell me?
Hurry and and say so if there is!
He said you've forgotten something important.
And if you don't face the part of you that you're avoiding, you'll never remember.
I think that's everything I forgot to say.
I see.
So, do you intend to fight with Higaki?
I can't imagine myself fighting him for no particular reason, but...
But?
If you asked me why I fight, I'd say I have to fight.
So I can find the answer to that.
You're pretty straightforward, as always.
If you do find the answer to that, tell me.
I'd love to know.
Okay.
Feel free to fight him.
It'll be a good experience for you to go toe to toe with a holy man.
Yeah.
Just to let you know ahead of time, I am way weaker than you.
What, you're already making excuses for losing?
That's not it.
You can't win against people weaker than you.
That's what I mean.
Shall we start then?
Come whenever. Or just watch me go first!
Kyotouryuu:
Lily!
Kyotouryuu
Lily
He got me!
What?
Kyotouryuu: Rose!
Kyotouryuu    Rose
Whoop, that's no good.
You're not getting away!
This is weird!
It's different from any of my fights up till now...
I can't land anything on him!
We're going nowhere at this rate!
Kyotouryuu: Shichika Hachiretsu!
Shichika Hachiretsu
Whoop!
Dammit, that's unfair!
Wait, are you...
This guy's not fighting at all!
He made the first move, yet he doesn't have any intention of fighting!
You've forgotten something important.
And if you don't face the part of you that you're avoiding,
you'll never remember.
It seems I've failed.
What do you think history is?
I think that history is the proof that humans lived.
The proof that humans lived to their utmost.
That's why it looks and is the way it should be.
And yet, this history is very different from how it should have been.
I spent much time trying to correct those errors.
And for now, my role here is over.
At this point I've conveyed to you all that I needed to, so we'll part here.
Hide yourself here for a while.
Do not come out under any circumstances.
If history goes according to how I imagine, you will not die.
You will be the sole survivor in this cruel history to come.
The samurai code says I should kill you, but even for the sake of correcting history, that is one thing I cannot do.
I cannot possibly kill my own daughter.
Yo.
So the one who came to kill me was you after all, Mutsue-kun.
I ... you...
That's... That's enough!
Why are you making me remember this now?
If your fighting strength is 10, mine would be around 7.
In a straight-up fight, I wouldn't even be a match.
That's why, by this point you should be torn into pieces!
However, your 10 strength is divided between offense and defense.
So basically, your attacking strength is only 5.
And so when I transfer all my strength into defense, your attacks cannot penetrate it.
If I had to name Seitou Hakari's focus as a Deviant Blade,
Note: True defense
I'd call it "Seitou Bouei".
Seitou Bouei
What exactly does Seitou Hakari's focus do?
It's the most true sword in the world.
I'm its owner after all.
Like hell!
What part of you is "true"?
Come on, it's not fair to judge me like that.
My current personality comes from Togame-chan, remember?
Dammit, why am I putting up with this?
This isn't even a fight!
What's so fun about giving me more memories I'd rather avoid?
It's fun.
I love harassing people.
Even for this fight, you should be able to learn something.
"Fighting is futile".
"There's no meaning to victory or defeat".
Togame-chan said it would be a good experience for you,
but any experience you get from fighting is pointless.
Any experience you'd get would only be unhappy.
You've been fighting close by her for a year, but you don't seem to have learned anything from it.
As kind-hearted as I am, I don't even feel like teaching you anymore.
I don't need your help.
She takes fighting too far.
It's almost like the concept of life itself is a fight for her.
What could her objective be?
You may know it, but you don't see eye to eye.
You just sympathize with her.
No! I—
—fell for her?
But the way I see it, your feelings aren't anything like that of love.
I can't let that one go.
Don't get angry now.
I'm sure you can calm yourself enough to listen.
I have no idea what Togame-chan's objective is, but I can tell you it's not something worth sacrificing herself for, much less others.
You must have realized that you've killed no small number of people over the course of your journey, right?
Robbing people of their greatest purpose—life itself.
Am I wrong?
Yasuri-kun, people die when they are killed.
You two have been ignoring such a simple principle.
From my perspective, you, and of course Togame-chan, lack resolve.
"Hakari" means "scales".
You need to consider what you're doing and how it relates to everything around you.
Could you tell that to Togame-chan too?
She probably won't talk to me.
Sure, I'll tell her next time she takes a break.
That would be right now.
Seems she got tired and decided to take a break inside the hole.
Togame!
What...
Why do you fight?
Why do you fight so far as to sacrifice me?
That's obvious.
For Togame, of course.
That's right...
I'm fighting for Togame!
From the day I met Togame, I...
The way I see it, your feelings aren't anything like that of love.
Forget love or anything!
I fight for Togame!
If it weren't for her, I wouldn't fight at all!
Got it, Higaki Rinne?!
Togame!
Hang in there!
Togame! Togame!
Shichirin...
Shichika?
Are you okay?
How was your fight with Higaki Rinne?
It wasn't really a fight.
All he did was run.
Run?
He called it Seitou Bouei or something.
All his strength became defensive.
Isn't that running from a fight?
Well, that's one way to do it.
A fight is an agreement between two parties, so if your opponent abandons the fight, you can't win.
That's not true!
There's a big problem with that strategy.
If we can take advantage of that, we can defeat him!
What is it then?
I totally don't know what to do against a guy who can't lose.
Come on, think about it yourself a bit.
Obviously...
I see...
So that's it...
I love you very much.
Shichika...
I remember what my father's dying words were...
That's good to hear.
This is Seitou Hakari, no mistaking it.
You found it faster than I thought.
Well, you did present that strange riddle through Shichika.
But you realized something, right?
If you had kept your offensive mindset while continuing to dig, would you have thought that hilt and blade was Seitou Hakari?
I probably wouldn't have.
Seitou Hakari is a sword upon which you weigh yourself.
It's not a sword that cuts people.
It is a sword that cuts oneself, tests oneself, and knows oneself.
That is why it is bladeless.
You could say it is swordless.
Well done!
It makes sense if you think about it.
A Japanese sword is not something you can safely preserve underground.
But if it doesn't have a blade to preserve, then there's no problem.
I'm not really a fan of that way of reverse thinking.
But I guess that's just like you.
That annoying personality is exactly like that man.
Who is "that man"? Mind telling me?
He's my...
...father.
I can't tell you his name though.
I see.
Sounds like you didn't like him.
Were you hostile to him?
Completely the opposite.
In fact, I live for the sake of my father.
You could even say this sword collection is for his sake.
But you're uncomfortable with him.
Because you admitted that, you found Hakari.
And despite avoiding you, you stand before me now.
I wonder though, why didn't Yasuri-kun try to have another go at me?
I'm sure you could figure out a way to defeat me.
If Shichika used all his combat strength on defense, what would happen?
You wouldn't even have a fight, never mind a match.
So basically, by abandoning offense, even without winning, the result will be effectively victory.
Continue.
The essence of a sword is its blade, something that doesn't bend or break, and cuts well.
That's what I had always thought...
But without a blade, you don't even need a sheath to protect it.
If you can hold it with resolve, all you need are its hilt and guard to be able to face yourself.
That's what it means.
Precisely right!
Good job discerning that.
You're pretty smart, Togame-chan!
Having someone with the body of a little girl patronizing me like that really annoys me.
Higaki, as a reward for figuring it out, will you answer one question of mine?
Sure, I'll answer as many as you want.
You said you received Seitou Hakari from Shikizaki Kiki himself.
What kind of man was he?
I guess he was a denying kind of guy.
Denying?
I feel like I've heard that somewhere before...
Well, I said I was a friend, but it's been so long that I've forgotten quite a bit.
But apparently he saw the profoundness of himself in me.
And eventually, he denied what he didn't want to face, and left.
Not before pushing Seitou Hakari onto me though.
He was endlessly troublesome.
I really didn't want to get poisoned by it, so I buried it pretty quick.
Wait, so it wasn't recently that you buried it?
Nope, I did that right after I got it.
And then they built a castle on top of it, and then that castle burned down, and then they turned it into an execution ground...
The eras sure fly by.
I see...
Seitou Hakari was buried here before Hida Castle was even built...
So that's how my father saw the distortion of history.
And then to correct that history he drew his bow against the Owari Shogunate...
And then made the ultimate sacrifice.
He put all his friends and family on the line to draw that bow.
All for the sake of history...
Around that time, he must have felt that the completion of the forging of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades was almost at hand.
Completion?
Don't say such weird things.
The "Perfected" Deviant Blades have already been perfected.
Huh?
Don't tell me you've been taking Yasuri-kun along with you all this time without even knowing?
What do you mean?
How shocking....
How could you not know that after crafting the 12 Perfected Deviant Blades,
he went on to forge his final and ultimate
Completed Deviant Blade, "Kyotou Yasuri"?
S-Shichika is one of Shikizaki Kiki's swords?!
Not Yasuri-kun precisely, but rather Kyotouryuu.
So that's why Sabi Hakuhei referred to him as a relic of Shikizaki Kiki?
He said Shichika was of Kiki's bloodline, and that Sabi himself was a failed creation...
Well, it's not so much "bloodline" as "swordline".
Bloodline
Swordline
It's true that Shikizaki Kiki and the Kyotouryuu founder Yasuri Kazune were from the same generation...
So that means there was some connection between the two?
Was Shikizaki Kiki involved in the formation of Kyotouryuu?
Completed Deviant Blade Kyotou Yasuri...
That's why they're swordless?
Anyway, I'm taking Seitou Hakari.
I learned a lot.
I've come to understand your strategy of forcing a match to a draw by neither winning nor losing, all for the sake of your objective.
Precisely... not quite right there.
You must throw away objectives for the sake of your objective.
That's the lesson you needed to learn.
Ambition, aspirations, vengeance...
You must throw aside all these objectives for the sake of your true objective.
I understand that much.
I can throw away everything but my objective.
Even after conquering what you couldn't face before, you still retain that stubborn streak.
Well, whatever.
If that's the way you live then you can just force your way through it.
By the way, what were your father's last words?
That's obvious.
The words of a father to his daughter.
Especially considering how cute a daughter I was.
So what was it?
Just tell me!
"I love you very much."
I didn't think I'd be able to say that.
So I'm one of the Deviant Blades that Shikizaki Kiki made, huh?
I totally don't feel it at all.
Well to be precise, the Completed Deviant Blade isn't you yourself, but rather Kyotouryuu.
The founder Yasuri Kazune, your father Yasuri Mutsue,
and even your sister Yasuri Nanami were all the Completed Deviant Blade "Kyotou Yasuri".
I guess I feel it doesn't change anything.
Kind of like, "who cares?"
You're pretty easygoing.
You should bear some troubles in mind at least.
Well, I guess that's fine too.
So maybe the fact that I can't use swords is the curse that Shikizaki Kiki bestowed.
Possibly.
Eitherways, there are only two left, right?
Your dream is almost within reach.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We don't know anything at all about Dokutou Mekki or Entou Jyuu.
Also...
When you talk about "dreams" or "objectives", I feel like that holy man's going to appear out of nowhere again.
You really aren't good at dealing with him, are you?
I don't ever want to meet him again!
It's not that funny!
Dewa
We're already at Dewa, huh...
Since we're here, why don't we pass through the Shougi town on the way back?
Why do we have to do that?
So you can see Kiguchi Zanki?
Huh?
What do mean "huh"?
Cheerio!!
Your jealous streak is really weird.
We have to get back to Owari as fast as possible, so we can't go through the Shougi town!
For your sake.
What?
I'm fighting for your sake.
That's the answer I gave.
Togame, what's that?
Hey...
Is he alive?
It's a sword wound.
This is...
H-Help...
Please help...
It doesn't matter what happens to me...
But please save Houou-sama...
The strategian and the Maniwa Corps.
They have allied, they have fought.
But the final hour of their destiny together has arrived.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
shira nu
知らぬ
I don't know
shira nu furi de
知らぬ振りで
Pretending to know nothing
unazuka nai
頷かない
I don't nod
ina mu
否む
I deny it
ina mu kokoro
否む心
My heart that denies it
oikake nai
追いかけない
I don't chase
maane utsushiyo wa yume
まあね　現し世は夢
Maybe this world is a dream
de sou kashira
で、そうかしら？
And, is that true?
iwa nu kika nu towa zu
言わぬ　聞かぬ　問わず
I don't say I don't listen I don't ask
tashikame nai
確かめない
I don't check
mie nu hate nu nige zu
見えぬ　果てぬ　逃げず
It's invisible, it's endless, it doesn't escape
kawara nai kaware nai
変わらない　変われない
It's unchanging, it's unchangeable
watashi wa mirai no subete makimodosou to shinai wa
私は　未来の全て　巻き戻そうとしないわ
I won't try to rewind all of the future
kirai na koto dake mate ri
嫌いな　ことだけ待てり
Only things I hate are waiting
soba ni aru nante
側にあるなんて
Those are beside me
ina ina
否　否
Nay Nay
hitei hitei hitei hitei
否定　否定　否定　否定
Deny deny deny deny
me no mae no kako
目の前の過去
The past in front of me
wa ina mu
は、否む
I deny it