Toukai Bus
Please...
Marry me!
I guess it can't be helped.
If you're that desperate...
I'll let you marry me.
Ryu-chan, look, look!
Taiga-chan had so many babies!
They're your kids.
A dream?
Even though it's finally summer vacation...
I had a dream like that just because of a stupid DVD I borrowed.
Even though it was just a dream, it was horrible...
...that kind of future.
Taiga!
I had an awful dream.
You were a dog.
That dog was my husband.
Anyway, a horrible dream.
A warning?
Yeah.
A warning that if we don't take countermeasures, that horrible future is waiting for us.
So, to change that future, one side should support the other with everything they got during the trip.
I got that, but why badminton?
Because...
We have to decide...
Which side!
Listen, try not to use the stove.
Stir the nuka pot once a day.
Don't forget to change Inko-chan's water every morning.
And check the notes I left.
Alright, I'm off.
Off? Where?
I told you. A trip!
Bye, Yacchan!
It looks like it'll be good weather!
I'm relying on you! With the plan.
Hey, is it really okay?
Yes! You won, so get this off me!
If that stupid dog hadn't burst in there, I would've won.
That's because you tried to compete using an event that you're good at.
You got what you deserve.
Nothing good happens when dogs are involved.
But, will it really go well?
I told you, leave it to me!
By the time this trip ends, your relationship with Minorin will...
What?
What's wrong?
Good morning! You're both right on time!
Excellent!
What's up? You guys are quiet!
Speak up!
Y-Yeah...
It's beautiful weather!
Yeah.
That reminds me, Ami isn't here yet.
There's still a little time before we were supposed to meet up.
I've got it!
What's with those guys...
No one's here.
H-Hey.
You're two minutes late, Ami!
Morning, Ami!
You're late, Stupid Chihuahua!
W-Where is everyone?
Hey! Don't run away, Stupid Chihuahua!
Ami, we're right here!
This is really yummy!
It's got pickled plums! It's so good!
It's great, Takasu.
Want to be my wife?
I don't!
You meanie!
Oh, that reminds me...
It seems that Aisaka-san isn't here, was she late?
Takasu-kun, contact...
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, Stupid Chihuahua, you were awake?
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open.
Can you stop fighting? We're on a trip.
Kawashima, what'd you do during summer vacation?
Me? I worked the whole time.
Oh! You started working again?
How about Minorin?
Club, job, club, job, club, club, job, club, job, club...
And Taiga?
Well, I...
What, Taiga?
Was making this.
Just now, a weird voice said "Senpai!"
Is this...?
Yeah.
I put together a CD of things to call ghosts.
I knew it! No! I was called!
Aisaka, you like that kind of horror stuff?
K-Kind of.
I'm surprised.
But it's also surprising that Kushieda hates horror stuff.
I hate it, I hate it, I really do!
Minorin really hates horror, shinrei, occult... Everything.
So, I'll scare Minorin to death.
Then you are going to save the scared-to-death Minorin.
"I will protect Kushieda!"
A "Scared Minorin Knight Appears" plan!
Anyway, scary stories are absolutely forbidden!
It's the ocean!
How far are you going to make us walk?
You can already see it.
Go around the back.
You can go straight up to the deck that way.
This is Ami's summer house?
We can stay here?
That's right, Minori-chan!
Wow! I'm so happy!
But... First, we got to clean up...
No one's been here since last year.
Since last year?!
Y-Yeah...
This seems like it'll be a tough fight.
There's such a beautiful ocean right in front of our eyes.
Who cares about cleaning now?
That's right! Cleaning is for later!
Me too!
I'm going too, but what will you do?
That's good!
Why am I cleaning by myself?
Feels good!
Hey, hey.
What's up?
Doesn't that look like a person's head?
A drowning!
What should I do? I came in contact with extract of drowned body!
They look like they're having fun.
You really came, Yuusaku.
Of course I'd come!
There's no way I wouldn't go when my best friend, Takasu, is going.
Was that okay? With the student council?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Takasu!
Ami told us to go shopping.
There's a motorbike in the storehouse.
A motorbike?
Then you go, and take Taiga with you.
Aisaka?
I-I... Won't go.
Motorbikes are scary.
What?
Take care.
I got it.
Bye!
And it was a great chance for you two to be alone.
I had a plan!
Before they come back, we have to find a place where we can carry out that plan.
If you're too shy, you should just sa-
There was a mosquito, a mosquito!
A place we can use...
This is... The bathroom.
Got to clean here too.
W-Who?
My bad!
I didn't notice you were in there.
Takasu-kun?
I-I'll leave now!
You're actually pretty bold.
Coming in here when a girl is taking a shower.
It wasn't on purpose!
It's okay... Now, secretly...
What are you sayi-
Hey, don't you want to do it?
Do what?!
Clean the bathtub!
What were you expecting?
What's with that face? That's a masterpiece!
Taiga!
Stupid Chihuahua did?
Pretended to take a shower...
Played with your boyish heart...
Then? Did you finish checking out the second floor?
Useless!
You get played by that Stupid Chihuahua because you're like that!
Fine, I'll go and look.
And I'll tell off that Stupid Chihuahua on the way.
Hey, Stupid Chi-
The Stupid Chihuahua was really taking a shower.
She was...
Boing and boing and boing!
You don't have to say that!
I'm home!
You bought a lot! Where's Kitamura?
He said he'd park the bike.
I-I see.
I'll carry it!
I-It's okay!
You went and did the shopping, so...
Okay.
W-What's wrong?
Just now something... Something... On my neck!
Isn't it just your imagination?
Y-Yeah. You're right.
J-Just now something definitely touched me!
Something slimy... Or seaweed like...
It smells like seaweed! It's seaweed!
Like an animal possessed by seaweed. If it's seaweed, then it's a dead body of a sea otter. Dead in the sea!
It's a seaweed and sea otter curse!
No way!
I don't want spicy!
I want spicy!
If it's not sweet, I can't eat it!
Hey, Ryuji!
I got it! I'll make yours sweet.
Special treatment for Aisaka-san?
That kind of thing will make girls hate you.
Including Minori-chan...
Did you call me?
Is it almost done? It looks good.
Y-Yeah.
All that's left is the mix.
Hey, you guys should also get ready for...
Hey, getting ready for dinner?
I can help set the table.
Y-You...
Hey, Taiga!
Yuusaku, are you crazy?!
Oh, sorry. I heard Takasu's voice so...
There were girls here too.
You idiot!
Taiga, get it together!
Sorry, sorry.
Hey! Hey!
You there, with the great and heavenly body!
Let me have this nude shot.
Quit it.
What are you saying now?
Hey, quit it.
Just now... Something black...
It was that seaweed ghost. Probably...
Sea... weed?
Kushieda?
Yuusaku, you're the worst!
Sorry...
Just get out of here!
O-Okay...
Everyone, be careful.
There's an evil spirit in this house.
Is there something I can do?
Please... Make the curry very spicy!
I got it.
It looks delicious!
It's just whatever was here, but as Kushieda asked, I made it as spicy as I could.
Alright! I'm eating!
Itadakimasu!
It's good!
This is delicious!
This isn't as spicy as I thought.
Really?
Yeah! You want to try?
You're right, it isn't...
Minorin?
Spicy!
In your throat!
It's hot! It hurts!
Yay! I'm pumped up!
A-Are you okay?
Takasu-kun...
You're the best!
It's super good and super yummy.
Certainly... Strangely enough, it calls for more.
I feel kind of strange.
There's still more left.
Seconds, please!
I thought I was going to die.
Alright.
I'm going to go wash the dishes.
Me too...
What?
Maybe it's because I ate something spicy...
I want some stomach medicine.
Your stomach hurts? But medicine...
Aisaka, are you feeling sick?
I brought some stomach medicine.
It's in my room, want to go together?
That's...
I'll leave it to you.
Wai-
It's a chance for you two to be alone, right?
What's wrong?
Nothing! Please take care of her.
Sure.
Hey, hey.
Ami-chan's stomach hurts!
Just kidding.
W-What?
Nothing!
It's because you were spacing out.
I don't get tired of looking at you.
Is that a compliment?
Maybe, maybe not.
What's with that?
Anyway, if you like, we could go together to the bea-
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Can you take the glasses?
I'll do it.
Sorry, what was it?
Nothing.
Is that enough water?
How is it? Does it look like it's working?
Yeah, I-I think so.
Yeah? I'm glad.
Seeing you in pain is painful for me too.
Do you want to lie down and rest?
You have great washing techniques!
I do it a lot in my part time jobs.
Takasu-kun's curry was amazing too!
No, it wasn't that...
That's it!
To thank you for helping me, I'll give you something good.
But don't tell anyone!
Takasu-kun, is the green tea flavor good?
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah? The red bean flavor isn't that great.
There are a lot of stars out!
T-They're pretty.
We're alone.
This is what they call a chance.
K-Kushieda, do you have a boyfriend?
I wonder if that seaweed ghost is still around here.
Takasu-kun.
Have you ever seen a ghost?
No...
I believe that ghosts exist.
But I've never actually seen one, nor do I believe the stories of the people who have.
And, along those same lines...
I believe I'll some day fall in love, get married, and be happy.
But I've never actually been like that with someone.
I feel very far away from people all over the world who are falling in love naturally.
Because I can't see it.
Maybe there aren't any ghosts after all.
I'll never see one... I'm on the verge of giving up.
So, the answer to your question is: I don't.
Can you see ghosts?
I... Might want to see one.
So I go to haunted places, and watch scary movies.
I think for people who can see ghosts, when they first saw one, they were really surprised.
There were some who saw one, and couldn't believe it.
On the other hand, there were some that tried hard and finally got to see one.
So you don't have to decide that you'll never see one.
What's that?
A UFO?
That's a man made satellite.
Man made satellite? That's all it is.
I thought it was a UFO.
I hope you see a ghost someday.
I-I think somewhere out there is a ghost that wants you to see them.
That's why there were so many strange things today.
That seaweed ghost is trying to show itself!
What's that, all of a sudden?
I wonder if I'll be able to see it someday.
Nothing!
You're weird.
Hey, Ryuji, my stomach's feeling better.
And?
I'm full!
Why me too?
Hey...
What will we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm talking about that plan, of course!
You're not doing good at all!
And what about you?
I'm just support this time!
Even so, I'm tired.
I thought I'd be in heaven, spending all day with Kitamura-kun.
But instead, I'm so nervous, I'll die early.
That's true.
But when I'm with you, I'm fine.
What's with that? So rude.
How stupid.
Even though this room is so big, we're still stuck together.
Maybe it's a habit from being in that small room all the time.
You...
Ryuji, I was thinking...
That dream might just be...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
Huh? Did I leave my bag here?
What... What's this?
And it's kind of slimy!
Ryuji!
What do you think?
I had it in my bag, but when I touched it, it was warm!
Like someone had just been wearing it.
My room was weird too!
There were long hairs on my pillow.
What was that?
I-It must be...
This is a dream, right?
Yeah! That's it! It's a dream.
It's a continuation of that dream where I'm a dog, living in a doghouse.
So if we close our eyes, we'll eventually wake up, right?
We will, we will!
I think...
I'm scared, scared, scared!
Ghosts are scary! Monsters are scary!
Calm down, Kushieda!
But, maybe the scariest are UFOs.