- Nishimura: WELCOME TO
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY.
A PREP SCHOOL IMPLEMENTING
THE WORLD'S FINEST
AND MOST UNIQUE SYSTEMS.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU MAY BEGIN THE TEST.
- Nishimura: ONE SUCH SYSTEM
IS THE SUMMONER TEST WAR.
A BATTLE BETWEEN
CLASSES UTILIZING AVATARS
REALIZED WITH STATE-OF-THE-ART
TECHNOLOGY.
ANOTHER IS CLASSROOM EQUIPMENT
BASED ON THE STUDENTS'
PERFORMANCE.
AT THE END OF THEIR FIRST YEAR,
THEY TAKE A PLACEMENT TEST.
BASED ON THE RESULTS, THEY
ARE DIVIDED INTO SIX LEVELS.
THE HIGHEST, CLASS A,
THROUGH THE LOWEST, CLASS F.
- THIS IS IT.
THE PLACEMENT TEST.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE WAY HARD.
BUT I GOT THIS!
- ( panting )
- ( gasps )
HIMEJI!
HEY! ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD.
- LEAVE THIS CLASS, AND YOU'LL
BE GIVEN A ZERO ON THE EXAM.
NO EXCUSES.
- NO EXCUSES? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- I'M PERFECTLY SERIOUS. STAYING
HEALTHY IS A PART OF THE TEST.
- WHATEVER! HOW IS THAT FAIR?
- YOSHII...
- C'MON, SHE'S OBVIOUSLY SICK,
THAT'S NOT HER FAULT!
- ( panting )
- YOU'RE LATE, YOSHII!
- HEY, IRON MAN!
- MY NAME IS MR NISHIMURA.
HERE, TAKE THIS ENVELOPE.
IT'S FOR YOU.
IT'S THE RESULT OF
YOUR PLACEMENT TEST.
YOU'LL BELONG TO THAT
CLASS FROM THIS DAY ON.
- COOL!
- YOSHII, I CAN TELL YOU
THIS NOW.
WHILE OBSERVING YOU
OVER THE PAST YEAR,
I HAD A SUSPICION.
WELL, THAT YOU MIGHT
ACTUALLY BE AN IDIOT.
- WHAT?
- BUT WHEN I HAD A LOOK
AT YOUR TEST RESULTS,
I REALIZED I'D MADE
A TERRIBLE MISTAKE.
I UNDERESTIMATED
YOUR TALENTS, YOSHII.
YOU HAVE COMPLETELY
SHATTERED ALL MY EXPECTATIONS.
YOU ARE, IN FACT, BEYOND A
SHADOW OF A DOUBT,
THE REAL DEAL.
A GENUINE IDIOT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Nishimura: WELCOME TO
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY.
A PREP SCHOOL IMPLEMENTING
THE WORLD'S FINEST
AND MOST UNIQUE SYSTEMS.
- HOW COME I'M IN CLASS F?
THAT'S LIKE THE
LOWEST RANKED CLASS.
MAN, I THOUGHT I DID
BETTER ON THE TEST.
I ANSWERED ONE OUT
OF EVERY TEN QUESTIONS.
- Nishimura: WELCOME TO
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY.
A PREP SCHOOL THAT TAKES PRIDE
IN HAVING THE LATEST EQUIPMENT.
- WHOA.
THEY'VE GOT WORKSTATIONS
WITH RECLINING CHAIRS!
LAPTOPS? NO WAY!
TELL ME THOSE AREN'T
FREE FOUNTAIN DRINKS!
LOOK AT ALL THOSE SNACKS!
I WANNA BE IN CLASS A!
NASTY MATS? OLD PILLOWS?
SHORT TABLES?
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO
BE A CLASSROOM?
- Nishimura: FUMIZUKI ACADEMY
IS RUTHLESS.
IF YOU WANT TO HAVE
A BETTER LIFE IN SCHOOL,
THEN YOU SHOULD
DO BETTER IN SCHOOL.
THAT IS THE LAW OF THIS ACADEMY.
- NO FAIR. THIS IS VIOLATING
MY CIVIL RIGHTS!
- WELL, AT LEAST YOU'RE NOT
ALONE. GO AHEAD AND SIT DOWN.
- FINE. WHERE WOULD YOU
LIKE ME TO SIT, SIR?
- I DON'T CARE.
WHEREVER YOU WANT.
- THERE'S NO ASSIGNED SEATING?
- ( cushion deflates )
- EXCUSE ME. MY CUSHION THING,
IT SEEMS TO HAVE RUN OUT
OF ALL OF ITS CUSHION.
- PLEASE PUT UP WITH IT.
- ( wind blowing )
- EXCUSE ME. THERE'S A DRAFT.
IT'S COLD IN HERE.
- PLEASE PUT UP WITH IT.
- EXCUSE ME. ONE OF THE LEGS
ON MY SHORT TABLE BROKE.
- PLEASE PUT UP WITH IT.
- NOT POSSIBLE!
- ( laughs ) I WAS JUST KIDDING.
- Nishimura: LIKE I SAID,
FUMIZUKI ACADEMY IS RUTHLESS.
- OKAY. SO, YEAH, I'M YOUR
HOMEROOM TEACHER, MR FUKUHARA.
I LOOK FORWARD TO TEACHING
YOU AND ALL THAT STUFF...
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH SOME TOOLS,
YOU GUYS JUST STUDY OR WHATEVER.
- MAN. THIS CLASSROOM
IS RIDICULOUS!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
SPEND A YEAR IN HERE?
TALK ABOUT DEPRESSING.
- DON'T COMPLAIN.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SHOULD'VE
DONE BETTER ON YOUR TEST.
- YUUJI? I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE IN HERE!
- IT'S NOT JUST ME.
- ( chuckling ) HEY, WHAT'S
UP? I'M IN CLASS F, TOO!
- SHIMADA! OF COURSE!
IT TOTALLY MAKES SENSE THAT
YOU'D BE IN THIS CLASS.
- ( growling )
- ARE YOU TRYING TO
CALL ME AN IDIOT?
- YOUR BREASTLESS CHEST IS
FORCING YOUR RIBS INTO MY EARS!
IT HURTS SO MUCH MORE
THAN A NORMAL CHICK!
( moaning )
I CAN ALMOST SEE IT.
ALMOST!
- I GREW UP IN GERMANY.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT I CAN'T
READ THAT STUPID KANJI!
- YOU ALL ARE LIVELY, AS USUAL.
- HIDEYOSHI?
- CORRECT. GLAD TO SEE YOU.
WELCOME TO CLASS F.
- IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
WELL, I GUESS THIS IS WHAT
YOU'D EXPECT FROM A CLASS F.
THERE'S JUST A BUNCH OF SCRUFFY
LOOKIN' DUDES EVERYWHERE.
LUCKY US.
- DOESN'T THAT INCLUDE
YOU TOO, THOUGH?
- THAT'S TRUE, BUT IF WE
CAN ONLY HAVE ONE GIRL,
I'M GLAD IT'S YOU, HIDEYOSHI.
- THANKS, BUT I'M A GUY.
- I'M THE GIRL, YOU JERK.
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT.
GIRLS ARE KIND AND GRACEFUL
AND HAVE THIS SOOTHING
SPIRIT ABOUT THEM
THAT MAKES EVERYONE FEEL
GOOD ABOUT THEMSELVES.
SOMEONE LIKE YOU WHO'S
VIOLENT AND SCARY
AND DOESN'T EVEN HAVE ANY BOOBS
THAT BREAK MY SPINE IN HALF.
PLEASE STOP! YOU'RE
GONNA SPLIT ME IN TWO!
- HELLO? I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
- ( gasping )
- I WAS AT THE NURSE'S OFFICE.
IT TOOK LONGER THAN I
THOUGHT IT WOULD.
- ( class murmuring )
- IT'S HIMEJI.
- AH! YOSHII. HI!
HOW ARE YOU?
- I'M GOOD. THANKS FOR ASKING.
- THAT LOOKS KINDA PAINFUL.
- NO! MY SPINE IS NOT
SUPPOSED TO BEND THAT WAY!
IT'S NOT NATURAL. IT'S ALSO
NOT BENDING! IT'S BREAKING!
- YES, SO CLOSE!
- ( gasping )
( groaning )
- CALL A DOCTOR!
- I SAW...
- DON'T SPEAK! ARE YOU OKAY,
KOUTA? SAY SOMETHING!
- THEY WERE LIGHT BLUE.
- STAY WITH ME!
- WHAT A RELIEF I'M NOT
THE ONLY GIRL IN HERE.
SEATS AREN'T ASSIGNED
OR ANYTHING,
SO WE CAN SIT
WHEREVER WE WANNA SIT.
- COOL. THANKS
FOR TELLING ME.
SO, IS THE SEAT
OVER THERE TAKEN?
- NO. ALL YOURS.
- THIS SUCKS. CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
ENDED UP IN CLASS F.
- NO. I KINDA LIKE THAT WE'LL
GET TO STUDY TOGETHER, YOSHII.
- ( coughing )
- OH NO. YOU'RE NOT
STILL SICK ARE YOU?
- YEAH, A LITTLE.
- WE'VE GOT THIS
CRAP-DRAFTY CLASSROOM,
CUSHIONLESS CUSHIONS,
OLD WORN OUT MATS WITH DUST
AND WHO KNOWS WHAT ELSE,
NOT THE BEST ENVIRONMENT
TO BE RECOVERING IN.
- ( clock chiming )
- ( coughing )
- SO, WHAT DID YOU
WANNA TALK ABOUT?
- I WAS JUST THINKING, SEE...
SCHOOLS ARE LIKE A
WEIRD SOCIAL THING, YOU KNOW?
THERE SHOULDN'T BE A
NON-EQUAL-NESS
AND A SEPARATION-NESS
AMONG CLASSES.
AND BESIDES, NO MATTER WHAT US,
THE LOWEST RANKED STUDENTS SAY,
WE END UP SOUNDING
LIKE SORE LOSERS.
FOR FAIRNESS AND JUSTICE,
I THINK WE SHOULD BATTLE IT OUT!
- BASICALLY, YOU'RE SAYING
YOU WANT HIGHER QUALITY
CLASSROOM EQUIPMENT FOR HIMEJI.
- WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BE SO BLUNT?
YOU CAN'T JUST SAY CRAP LIKE
THAT. IT'S EMBARRASSING!
- WHATEVER.
ACTUALLY, I WAS THINKING
ABOUT STARTING A WAR MYSELF.
- YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH.
I THOUGHT WE COULD PROVE
THERE'S MORE TO LIFE THAN
WHETHER OR NOT YOU MAKE
GOOD GRADES IN SCHOOL.
PLUS, I THINK WE CAN WIN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY? WANNA TRY?
- YEAH! WE SHOULD DO IT! LET'S
CALL FOR A SUMMONER TEST WAR!
- HEY GUYS, LISTEN UP.
AS CLASS REPRESENTATIVE,
I HAVE AN IDEA.
I THINK IT'S TIME WE CHALLENGE
CLASS E TO A SUMMONER TEST WAR.
- ( all gasping )
- YOU'RE KIDDING?
- A SUMMONER TEST
WAR. IT'S SUICIDE!
- Nishimura:
AT FUMIZUKI ACADEMY,
THERE'S A SYSTEM CALLED
SUMMONER TEST WAR,
ALSO REFERRED TO AS ST WAR.
AS LONG AS AN APPROVING
TEACHER IS PRESENT,
A STUDENT CAN SUMMON
THEIR AVATAR,
WHOSE OFFENSE POWER IS BASED
ON THE STUDENT'S PERFORMANCE
IN A PARTICULAR SUBJECT.
THEY FIGHT USING
THEIR AVATARS.
IF THE BATTLE IS WON BY
A LOWER RANKED CLASS,
THEY CAN EXCHANGE EQUIPMENT WITH
THE LOSING HIGHER RANKED CLASS.
- NOW, I CAN'T BE THE ONLY ONE
TIRED OF THIS CRAPPY CLASS!
- All: WE ARE!
- RIGHT! THIS IS ALL
WE HAVE TO DO.
WIN A FEW WARS, AND
CLASS A'S AWESOME STUFF
COULD BE OUR AWESOME STUFF!
- ( all exclaim )
- WE'RE THE LOWEST OF THE LOW!
THE BOTTOM OF THE
FRIKKIN' BARREL, GUYS!
- ( chanting) All: YEAH!
- WE'RE JUST A GROUP OF LOSERS.
NO ONE RESPECTS US BECAUSE THEY
DON'T EVEN KNOW WE'RE HERE!
BUT WHAT THEY'VE
FAILED TO REALIZE
IS THAT WE HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE!
WE HAVE TO TRY.
WE CAN AT LEAST DO THAT.
AND DON'T FORGET,
WE HAVE THIS GUY!
- ( gasping )
- MOST PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THE TRUTH ABOUT HIM.
GUESS WHAT,
HE'S A PROBATIONARY STUDENT!
- ( all murmuring )
- UH, IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
- DO YOU HAVE A
QUESTION, HIMEJI?
- IS A PROBATIONARY STUDENT
SPECIAL OR SOMETHING?
- YEAH, NOT JUST ANYBODY
CAN BE ONE.
IT'S SPECIAL TREATMENT
FOR A STUDENT
WHO ISN'T VERY GOOD IN ACADEMICS
AND DOESN'T SEEM TO
HAVE ANY MOTIVATION.
- IT'S CONSIDERED THE
SAME THING AS STUPID.
- UH-HUH.
PRETTY MUCH IT'S SOMEONE
WHO'S COMPLETELY USELESS.
- OH, HE REALLY IS SPECIAL.
- AH! I'D CRAWL UNDER THE RUG
IF WE HAD ONE!
- IF WE WIN A SUMMONER TEST WAR,
WE CAN HAVE A RUG AND MORE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, YOU GUYS?
SHOULD WE DO IT?
- ( all cheering )
- AWESOME! LET'S START THIS OFF
BY CHALLENGING CLASS E.
AKIHISA, SINCE YOU'RE THE
AMBASSADOR FOR CLASS F,
YOU HAVE TO OFFICIALLY GO
AND DECLARE WAR ON THEM.
- WHY ME? AREN'T WAR
DECLARING MESSENGERS
FROM LOWER RANKED CLASSES
NORMALLY GIVEN HELL FOR IT?
- NO. THAT KIND OF THING ONLY
HAPPENS IN THE MOVIES.
YOU'RE AN IMPORTANT AMBASSADOR,
THEY HAVE NO CHOICE BUT
TO RESPECT YOU.
- BUT...
- LISTEN TO ME.
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT MISSION.
ONLY YOU CAN DO THIS, MAN.
YOU WOULDN'T WANT TO LET
EVERYBODY DOWN, WOULD YOU?
- MMM-HMM.
YOU LIED TO ME!
- I FIGURED AS MUCH.
- YOU EXPECTED THIS?
- I'M CLASS REPRESENTATIVE, GIVE
ME A LITTLE BIT OF CREDIT HERE.
- AT LEAST PRETEND
LIKE YOU'RE SORRY!
- NOW, THERE'S NO GOING
BACK FOR US. IT'S DONE.
ARE YOU READY?
ISN'T THIS WHAT YOU WANTED?
- YEAH IT IS. LET'S DO IT!
- REALLY?
THE SECOND YEAR STUDENTS ARE
TRYING TO CALL FOR AN ST WAR
ON THE FIRST DAY OF A
NEW TERM? HOW INTERESTING.
APPROVE IT.
- I'LL LET THEM KNOW
IMMEDIATELY.
- I WONDER HOW IT
WILL TURN OUT.
GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO WAIT AND SEE.
- WE'LL USE MR HASEGAWA AS THE
ATTENDING TEACHER FOR THE WAR.
WE'LL NEED TO SECURE
HIM ON HIS WAY TO CLASS E
BEFORE THE FIFTH PERIOD.
- MR HASEGAWA? DOES THAT MEAN
THE SUBJECT WILL BE MATH?
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
I'M LIKE WAY GOOD AT MATH.
- YES. WE'LL USE MATH.
MINAMI EXCELS AT IT, SO THAT
CAN BE OUR MAIN STRENGTH.
- ARE YOU ANY GOOD
AT MATH, MIZUKI?
- IT'S NOT MY BEST,
BUT I'M NOT BAD AT IT.
- YAY. THEN MAYBE WE CAN
FIGHT TOGETHER.
- NO. SHE WON'T BE
ABLE TO FIGHT.
- WHAT? WHY NOT?
- THE SCORES ON THE
LAST TEST WE TOOK
ARE WHAT BECOME OUR AVATARS'
OFFENSIVE POWER.
STOP AND THINK ABOUT THIS
FOR A SECOND.
- THE LAST TEST WAS...
- IT WAS THE PLACEMENT TEST.
- AND SINCE I LEFT THE ROOM
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE EXAM,
MY SCORES ARE ALL ZERO.
- BUT, ONCE THE ST WAR STARTS,
SHE'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE A
RECOVERY TEST TO MAKE UP FOR IT.
ALL SHE HAS TO DO
IS FINISH THAT TEST,
THEN SHE'LL BE ABLE
TO FIGHT WITH US.
- ALL RIGHT.
- WE'RE ALL COUNTING ON YOU.
- OKAY.
- ( clock chiming )
- MISTER HASEGAWA
HAS BEEN SECURED!
- ALL RIGHT EVERYONE.
BATTLE TIME. LET THE WAR BEGIN!
- All: YEAH!
- GOOD GRIEF. FOR IDIOTS
THEY SURE ARE COCKY.
- ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
GET READY!
LET'S TEACH F A LESSON
THEY'LL NEVER FORGET!
- All: YEAH!
- MINAMI SHIMADA.
PREPARED TO FIGHT!
- HIDEYOSHI. I SHALL
PARTICIPATE AS WELL!
- KOUTA TSUCHIYA.
I'M DOIN' IT, TOO!
- I APPROVE THIS WAR!
- I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- SUMMON.
- I'M SUMMONING
MY AVATAR. SUMMON!
- WHY WAS MY TRANSFORMATION
SO DRAMATIC?
- THEY'RE COMING!
- ( exclaiming )
- Hasegawa: BE CAREFUL...
REAL HUMANS ARE NOT ALLOWED
TO PASS THROUGH THAT AREA.
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'LL HAVE TO
GET THROUGH US FIRST.
- YOSHIKO MIKAMI. I ACCEPT
THIS CHALLENGE. SUMMON!
- HELLO... GOODBYE!
- EXCUSE ME, BUT THAT'S MY LINE!
- OH, NO!
- WHEN IT COMES TO MATH,
I WON'T LOSE AGAINST CLASS E.
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASS.
- IRON MAN!
- SCARY...
- IN ACCORDANCE WITH
THE ST WAR RULES,
REMEDIAL CLASSES ARE REQUIRED
FOR ALL WHO HAVE THEIR
SCORE REDUCED TO ZERO.
- NO, HELP ME!
I DON'T WANNA TAKE A REMEDIAL
CLASS TAUGHT BY A DEMON.
( wailing )
- IF YOU WANT TO PASS
THROUGH HERE,
YOU'RE REQUIRED TO
DEFEAT US FIRST.
- FINE. THEN I GUESS WE'LL
JUST HAVE TO DO THAT.
- SUMMON...
- BRING IT ON!
- WELL THEN, IF YOU'RE READY,
YOU MAY BEGIN THE EXAM.
- ( yawning )
- OKAY, YUUJI, WHAT'S
YOUR BIG STRATEGY?
- I DON'T HAVE A STRATEGY.
- WHAT?
- THE WHOLE GAME
DEPENDS ON FORCE.
ONE CLASSROOM TRIES TO RUSH IN
AND OVERWHELM THE OTHER,
AND THE CLASS WHOSE REP
GETS TAKEN OUT
IS THE ONE THAT ENDS UP LOSING.
- BUT THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE GONNA
BE OVERWHELMED, IS THERE?
- THERE'S TROUBLE.
WE'RE GONNA BE OVERWHELMED!
- WHAT?
- WELL, THAT ISN'T SHOCKING.
THEIR SCORES ARE
BETTER THAN OURS.
IF WE KEEP FIGHTING
THEM LIKE THIS,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE WE LOSE.
- OH, NO!
- BUT THEY ARE ONLY CLASS E
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD,
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'RE REALLY
THAT MUCH SMARTER THAN WE ARE.
IT SHOULD TAKE THEM
A WHILE TO BEAT US.
AND THAT TIME IS THE KEY
TO OUR VICTORY.
- MY SCORE'S DROPPING!
- YOU NEED TO FALL BACK, NOW.
IF YOU DON'T TAKE A RECOVERY
TEST, YOU'LL DIE. GO.
- OKAY!
- I NEED TO TAKE A
RECOVERY TEST, PLEASE!
- NOW UNDERSTAND, THE SCORE OF
THIS EXAM WILL BE YOUR SCORE
THE NEXT TIME YOU
SUMMON YOUR AVATAR.
IF YOU GET A LOWER SCORE
THAN YOU HAVE NOW,
YOUR AVATAR WILL GET
WEAKER INSTEAD.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO TAKE THE TEST?
- I AM, YES.
- WHAT SUBJECT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO TAKE?
- I WANT MATH, PLEASE.
I HAVE TO ANSWER AS MANY
AS I CAN TO GET A BETTER SCORE!
- I CAN'T FIGHT ANY MORE!
- I GOT YOUR BACK.
OR WE COULD JUST TAKE A
STRATEGIC WITHDRAWAL.
- THIS BATTLE IS MINE!
- ( avatars screaming )
- NOT GOOD.
- ATTACK THEM.
- ( grunting )
- SOUNDS LIKE OUR
DEFENSE WENT DOWN.
- THIS IS BAD, YUUJI!
- THEY'RE ONLY NUMBERS
ON A PAGE...
AS LONG AS I DON'T HAVE
TO READ JAPANESE, I'VE GOT THIS!
IT'S KANJI!
I'LL JUST HAVE TO SKIP THIS ONE
AND MOVE ON TO THE
NEXT QUESTION.
- ( avatar groaning )
- THOSE WHO DIED, MEET ME
IN THE REMEDIAL CLASSROOM!
- ( all groaning )
- NO. WHAT ARE WE GONNA
DO NOW, MAN?
- OH, IS THAT ALL YOU GUYS HAVE?
LOOKS LIKE IT'S ALREADY COME
DOWN TO THE CLASS F REP.
WOW. THE CLASS E REP HERSELF
HAS GRACED US WITH HER PRESENCE.
YOU SEEM CONFIDENT.
- WHO DECLARES WAR ON THE FIRST
DAY OF A NEW TERM ANYWAY?
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
OUR TWO CLASSES
IS STILL IN THE
PLACEMENT TEST SCORES.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME YOU ACTUALLY
THOUGHT CLASS F COULD WIN?
- WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW, RIGHT?
- OH, I SEE.
YOU REALLY ARE AN IDIOT.
THAT EXPLAINS YOUR TEST SCORE.
- I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT A STRATEGY YET OR NOT,
BUT NOW WOULD BE A
REALLY GOOD TIME FOR ONE.
- OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW,
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I DID HAVE A STRATEGY
AFTER ALL.
- WHAT?
- COME ON, MAN. WHY ELSE WOULD
I HAVE WANTED TO KEEP YOU HERE?
- MMM-HMM. YEAH, I GET IT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ARE YOU TELLING ME HE'S A...
- THAT'S RIGHT. AKIHISA YOSHII
IS A PROBATIONARY STUDENT!
GO AHEAD. SHOW THEM THE KIND
OF POWER YOU POSSESS, YOSH!
- WELL, I GUESS IT
CAN'T BE HELPED.
AFTER ALL, YOU'LL
HAVE TO DEAL WITH
MY WICKED SKILLS EVENTUALLY.
SUMMON!
- ( all gasp )
- THE AVATAR OF A PROBATIONARY
STUDENT HAS A UNIQUE ABILITY.
AS PUNISHMENT,
THEY HAVE TO HELP FACULTY
MEMBERS WITH THEIR CHORES,
SO THEIR AVATAR CAN
ACTUALLY TOUCH THINGS.
- ( gasps )
- BUT THAT'S NOT ALL.
ANY INJURIES THE AVATAR RECEIVES
ARE ALSO FELT BY THE SUMMONER.
- ( moaning in pain )
- SEE? ISN'T THAT INTERESTING?
- I DON'T THINK SO!
- FINE. I'LL GO AHEAD AND TAKE
CARE OF THE LITTLE GUY FIRST.
SUMMON!
- YOU WON'T WIN THAT EASILY.
LET'S GO!
( battle cry )
- OW! HE LANDED ON THE
SAME SPOT! THE PAIN! THE PAIN!
JUST WHAT I'D EXPECT
FROM A CLASS E REP.
YOU DON'T TOTALLY SUCK.
- SO WHAT? HE'S AN IDIOT
AND USELESS?
- NO WAY. YOU JUST DON'T
GIVE HIM ENOUGH CREDIT.
- YEAH, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
AS CLASS REP, I'M GONNA GO AHEAD
AND PUT AN END TO THIS THING.
- ( panting )
- GET READY.
I, HIROMI NAKABAYASHI,
CHALLENGE YUUJI SAKAMOTO!
- PLEASE WAIT!
MIZUKI HIMEJI FIGHTING!
I ACCEPT THIS CHALLENGE.
SUMMON!
HERE I COME!
- WHAT'S WITH HER SCORE?
- HER POWER IS LIKE
A CLASS A LEVEL!
- WHAT'S SOMEONE LIKE THAT
DOING IN F?
- SHE'S FINALLY HERE.
- HIMEJI!
- MIZUKI HIMEJI? DON'T
TELL ME YOU'RE IN CLASS F?
- YOSHII!
- HEY, SHIMADA.
- SHE'S LIKE AN OUT OF
CONTROL SMARTY!
- NOT TOO SHABBY, BUT I'M NOT
THE LEAST BIT SURPRISED BY IT.
- HOW CAN HER SCORE
GET SO HIGH?
- THE SCHOOL'S EXAMS HAVE AN
UNLIMITED NUMBER OF QUESTIONS
AND SO DOES YOUR SCORE
AS LONG AS YOU CAN ANSWER
WITHIN THE TIME ALLOWED.
- THEN YOU DID HAVE A STRATEGY.
- I WAS BUYING US TIME
'TIL SHE FINISHED.
- NO FAIR. NOBODY SAID
THERE WAS A SMART PERSON
IN YOUR STUPID CLASS.
- THEY DIDN'T? I'M SORRY!
HERE I COME!
- OH, NO!
- Nishimura: AND THUS,
THIS SUMMONER TEST WAR ENDED
WITH A VICTORY BY CLASS F.
- AWESOME! THAT WAS AMAZING.
WE COULDN'T HAVE WON
IF YOU WERE AS STUPID AS WE ARE!
- AW, THANKS.
THAT'S REALLY SWEET OF YOU.
- I CAN'T WAIT! NOW
WE GET TO EXCHANGE
OUR EQUIPMENT WITH
CLASS E'S, RIGHT?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT THAT GREAT,
BUT IT'S BETTER THAN THE
CRAP WE'VE GOT!
- OH, NO. WE'RE NOT
EXCHANGING ANYTHING.
- WE'LL JUST STICK
WITH WHAT WE'VE GOT.
IS THAT COOL WITH YOU?
OR WOULD YOU RATHER
MAKE THE SWITCH?
- NO WAY. SERIOUSLY?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT'S WHY WE FOUGHT!
- SO IS EVERYTHING WORKED OUT?
- WHY ARE YOU DRESSED
LIKE THAT, HIDEYOSHI?
I GET IT! YOU'VE FINALLY
ACCEPTED WHO YOU REALLY ARE!
- UM, YOSHII. I'M SITTING
RIGHT OVER HERE.
- WHAT? THERE'S TWO OF YOU?
- NO, IDIOT,
THAT'S MY TWIN SISTER.
- I'M OLDER TOO. BY LIKE THREE
MINUTES. I'M YUUKO KINOSHITA,
AND AS AMBASSADOR FROM
CLASS A, I HEREBY CHALLENGE F.
WE ARE OFFICIALLY DECLARING
WAR ON YOU LOSERS!
- ( all gasp )
- WHY? WHAT DID WE DO TO YOU?
- DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
TAKE IT EASY ON YOU EITHER.
WE'LL CRUSH YOU MERCILESSLY.
YOU'VE BEEN WARNED.
- ( theme song playing )
- Fukuhara: QUESTION TWO,
NAME THE PLANT THAT HAS
A SUBTERRANEAN STEM
THAT SOMETIMES IS EDIBLE AND IS
CALLED "LILY" IN ENGLISH.
- Akihisa: A SWEET POTATO!
- Fukuhara: PLEASE DON'T JUST
FOCUS ON THE WORD "EDIBLE".
- Akihisa: NEXT TIME!
LILIES, ROSES, AND HEALTH
AND PHYSICAL EDUCATION!
- Fukuhara: THIS WILL BE
ON THE TEST.