So hot...
It's the first of September...
Why are the mornings still so hot?
We'll need to finish yesterday's curry, fast...
Good morning, Minorin!
Hey there, you two.
You been doing well?
H-Hey!
How you been, Kushieda?
'Sup, guys?
Did you finish your summer homework?
Did you brush your teeth?
Did you shower?
Why are you so happy?
Oh-ho!
Someone must've had an eventful vacation!
Summer break's in the past!
We're living in the second term now!
On to a new stage in the Culture Festival!
To find something new—
Must be nice to have something
happen over summer break...
M-Miss Yuri-chan?
But sure...
Of course something happened...
After all, it was your seventeenth summer...
Completely different from the summer
of a single woman who's hit thirty...
- Indeed, the world can be so cruel...
- I guess nothing special happened for her.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Ohashi High School Culture Festival
(Part One)
So, once again, they're limiting
the festival to one day, huh?
The president's influence wasn't enough.
This wasn't a unilateral decision.
We made a deal.
Victory is ours!!
Negotiations with the faculty are underway.
Exactly.
If all goes as planned, surrendering a second
day of festivities will be more than worth it.
We'll do whatever it takes to make
this year's Culture Festival a hit.
This will be my last major
school event, after all.
Then next time, let's look for UFOs.
Whoa!
Hey, Dumb-chi!
What was that, slowtard!?
Like I said...
I can't touch the ball.
My nails are too long.
Might break one.
Stupid Dumb-chi!
Oh, that cute smile...
Ami-chan is an angel...
I'm a Palm-top Tiger fan.
I'll take Kashii.
I'd say Kihara's definitely fine.
Oh! Ami-chan's riding the tiger!
Oh...
I want her to ride me...
Ladies and zentlemen!
What's this about?
There aren't any ladies here.
And what the hell does "zentle" mean?
Aren't you fellas interested in
seeing the girls you pine for...
looking cute in a non-everyday way?
You feeling okay?
Don't tell me you got into some
weird hobby over summer.
Just hear me out!
The Culture Festival is coming up.
And during tomorrow's long homeroom,
our class will decide what
we'll be doing for it.
And!
I'm on the Culture Festival committee!
So what?
So...
If we choose to go with a maid cafe, we'll
get to see the girls dressed as maids!
If the guys unite and force a vote,
we'll have an indisputable majority!
How's that sound?
Not a bad idea.
Especially coming from Haruta.
Hold on.
In that case, I'd replace the maid outfits...
with cheongsam!
Ooh!
I can picture that.
Takasu, you with us?
Y-Yeah, sure...
I basically get to see her in
a maid outfit at the restaurant.
A skintight cheongsam
would be much more...
No, that won't work!
If it's too tight, I'll have to
make her bra-pads again.
What are you mumbling about?
Uh, nothing.
But I'd replace cheongsam with, uh...
Lolita dresses?
Takasu...
You're a genius!
I want nurse uniforms!
How do stewardess outfits sound?
Dumbass! They're called flight attendants!
- Don't forget shrine maidens!
- Hold up, guys!
Don't get off topic!
Wait, what were we even talking about?
A cosplay cafe...
is the perfect solution, no?
Boys' Locker Room
That's it!
Taiga, I'm heading out.
Uh-huh...
Ryuji!
Look at this.
Wh-What now?
Whoa, this is bad.
Dumb-chi tore it.
Honestly.
Could you not slander my name?
You tripped over yourself and tore it.
It's your fault for dodging that ball!
I already said that my nails are—
Stop it.
I'll mend the tear.
There you go, spoiling her again.
Make sure it's fixed by next week.
Hey!
Don't you shift the blame
onto me and walk away!
Hey!
They're so spunky.
Kushieda.
Anyway, we should head back to class.
Y-Yeah...
You're right.
B-By the way...
Th-The thing you said about UFOs—
Yep, instant noodles are truly
the enemy of Diet Warriors!
Oh, so scary!
Absit omen.
I'll have to patch this with
another piece of cloth.
Guess I'll sacrifice one of
Yasuko's old long johns.
Taiga, your phone.
Don't care.
Damn that stupid bastard...
Stupid bastard?
Who're you talking about?
Whatever. Your phone's annoying.
- Make it sto—
- Shut your mouth!
Wh-What's your problem?
I said to leave me alone.
The man gets remarried and
decides I don't belong,
so he gives me an apartment
and throws me out?
He abandoned me!
He's completely heartless.
You're talking about your dad!?
No, a stupid bastard!
He's still your father, no
matter how awful he is.
"Stupid bastard" is a bit much...
With family, you're always connected in
your hearts, even when you're apart.
Like, you know—
I said he's a stupid bastard, and that's that!
Stu-pid!
Pid! Pid!
- Stupid bas! Pid tard! Pid pi—
- You don't need to learn that phrase!
Piles!
- Piles! P-Piles!
- Inko-chan, not again!
- P-P-Piles!
- Oh? Talking about your daddy, Ryu-chan?
- No way!
- He was so wonderful!
He kept magazines tucked under his shirt...
That story again!? That's not wonderful at all!
And don't go blabbing that to other people!
Aw, but...
And so...
We need to decide on a class exhibit, and
choose a candidate for the pageant!
Topic
Culture Festival
Culture Festival Committee Member
Haruta Koji
Uh, for the pageant, we'll go with
Ami-chan, since I doubt anybo—
Um...
Ditto
Kawashima Ami
Sorry, I can't do that.
I appreciate the thought, but I'm the
pageant MC, so I can't be a participant.
However, I believe that...
Aisaka-san would be a perfect choice!
I mean...
She's so little and cute!
And she's well-known around school.
What are you babbling about, Dumb-chi!?
Why should I have to deal with that hassle?
Oh, but that actually might be a good idea.
The tiger certainly is famous.
I can see this workin' out.
Stupid jerks...
Now, now.
That won't do, Taiga-chan.
You're a member of this class too,
so you should actively participate in such events.
Damn it, Dumb-chi!
If you aren't going to listen to me,
I'll crush the whole damn festival!
There, there.
Hold it in. Hold it in.
You might actually win.
Yeah?
'Kay!
Then, Tiger will be our pageant candidate!
Let's move on to what our class
will do for the festival!
Ooh! Ooh!
Yes, Noto-kun!?
How does a cosplay cafe sound!?
What!?
Isn't that super lame?
I guarantee some other
class will do the same.
- I'm totally against it!
- Um... Well...
Just my two cents...
Not that I personally want to do this...
Can't stand it, myself...
But I wouldn't mind if everyone
manages to have fun...
So, um, I think...
A h-haunted...
Got a nosebleed...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't going to say anything weird.
Just that a h-haunted house...
Kushieda.
That's enough.
You're falling apart.
Not gonna happen...
So not gonna let it happen...
Y-Yuri-chan?
Cafe? No!
Form a band and put on a concert?
Yuck. Worst thing you could
do in Japan right now!
That excitement won't last longer
than a day! It's an illusion!
It'll all fall apart by Christmas!
What's she ranting about?
Something bad happen to her over summer?
Come on, we're not getting anywhere!
Let's just put it to a vote!
- Write down your idea on a piece of paper!
- Now we're voting?
Won't matter what the girls write.
They're a disorganized mess.
They stand no chance against
a united male front!
Okey-doke! Everybody done?
Here we go!
Shake!
And!
Draw!
W-Wait! A draw!?
Announcement time!
This year, our class will be
putting on a pro wrestling—
Who actually wrote down
"pro wrestling show (no holds barred)"!?
Seriously! What is this!?
More importantly...
Why didn't you go with majority rule?
Oh.
Stupid Dumb-chi...
I'll beat her into all kinds of hells when
she passes through Samsara!
Just give up and enjoy
a class event, for once.
You need to open your heart.
Gimme a break. That, coming from
the guy who's suddenly all excited.
Excited? Me?
Ever since we came back from the trip—
Huh? Why?
What's wrong?
Weird.
It won't let me withdraw money.
The balance is zero.
Well, guess I'll just...
Impossible...
It's because I've been ignoring his calls.
So this is how he reacts?
Unbelievable...
Calls? Like the one the other day?
He's called a bunch of times recently.
But I ignored them all because
they pissed me off.
And now he's emptied out the account
for my living expenses!
Stupid bastard...
I wanna kill him!
You shouldn't say that about your parent.
Incoming Call
Stupid Bastard
He's threatening me.
Just pick up, would you?
Nothing will change if you don't talk to him.
Besides...
You'll be in trouble without the money, right?
So.
She picked up...
But why am I meeting with him by myself?
I see...
I understand.
So you're saying my daughter isn't coming.
Yes... I'm sorry.
I really wanted to see her.
But I guess I've dug myself
into an even deeper hole.
Sorry about this.
Uh, Takasu-kun, was it?
Might as well order whatever you like.
Uh, yeah. No thanks.
I'm having dinner in a bit.
E-Er, I mean, I'll take you up on your offer!
An egg bagel!
Oh, really?
Excuse me!
Can we order?
An egg bagel for him.
And I guess I'll have this salmon bagel.
With lots of cheese!
As much as you can fit!
Oh, right.
Take this, before I forget.
The money.
I really wanted to see her.
I had something important to tell her.
Something important?
Uh... So are you and Taiga, y'know...dating?
N-No way!
Heck, we're just friends.
There's nothing romantic about it.
We just happen to be neighbors, and we
somehow managed to hit it off...
I see.
In that case, Taiga must have
told you about our family.
I remarried someone significantly
younger than me.
Taiga had a hard time adjusting...
And that led to misunderstanding
after misunderstanding.
My new wife, her name is Yu...
It got to the point where either
Taiga or Yu had to leave.
So Taiga...
But I want to live with Taiga!
The way we did before.
That's what I came here to say.
No mistakes this time.
I want to start over with her.
Yu and I will be separating soon.
So I'm going to live with Taiga.
Since I'm her father.
Since I love her.
This is big.
Your dad's come back for you.
Man, what are you doing?
Do a better job!
Rinse for longer than five seconds!
You're so annoying.
Don't touch anything.
I promised to wash the dishes in return
for you meeting with that man.
Then do a better job!
Oh, go away!
You know...
Your dad's kind of weird.
Doesn't act like a typical grown-up.
I told you to go away!
Go boil water and make tea or something.
Your dad's really worried about you.
That's why he wants to live with you again.
You an idiot?
I'm serious about this.
He said he wants to live with you.
And he asked me to—
It's none of your business!
Don't meddle in someone
else's family issues!
You're the one who sent me!
So you take the money, and that's the end?
Yes.
That's why I'm washing the dishes for you.
That's why it's settled now.
I'll never see him again!
Hey.
Don't give me that crap!
Face—
Shut up!
Don't touch me!
Your dad was depressed
about you ignoring him!
I felt bad for him!
You should feel bad for me!
Taiga?
Okay!
Everyone get one?
I felt responsible for what happened...
The Pro Wrestling Show!
so I made this!
A script for a wrestling show.
Hey, shouldn't we drop this idea?
Here.
Folks!
Could you show some interest!?
It's too late to turn back!
Yuri-chan already approved
and submitted our proposal!
Oh...
This might be fun.
Everyone's been assigned a role.
Haruta-kun, this is much
better than I expected.
Oh, I'm the star.
I kinda feel like celebrating.
Ami-chan...
Wow, she's right.
This is really well done.
Haruta-kun, let's do the best we can!
Okay! Let's start rehearsing!
Yeah!
In the near future,
the students of 2-C are living happily in
peace under their leader, Ami-chan!
However!
There were those who found
this peace offensive!
The Palm-top Tiger—evil incarnate—and her
underling, Takasu Ryuji the delinquent!
Hold on.
Why am I her underling?
And a delinquent?
Why am I evil incarnate?
No questions. Just hear me out, 'kay?
The Palm-top Tiger attacks
the members of 2-C!
They are brainwashed one by one!
But! Ami-chan's furious efforts set them free,
and everyone joins together in the end,
successfully driving the Palm-top Tiger
and badboy Takasu Ryuji away!
And then they live happily ever after.
How do you like it?
This is what we get
for hearing you out?
But it's simple and dramatic.
This might turn out well.
No!
There's no way I'm doing this!
Jeez... You're so selfish.
Hey!
First the pageant, now...
Why are you so intent on making
me do these weird things!?
If hitting me will make you feel
better, go right on ahead!
All right! That's what I'll do!
But violence is not the answer!
Hey, the Palm-top Tiger's really into it!
Rehearsing already?
That was so intense!
Right on!
Now, deliver the tiger's brainwashing line!
Say your line.
Look, right here.
The tiger appears, shouting incoherently...
Amin's changed lately.
Yeah, you're right.
Whoa! What is that!?
No idea.
Haruta-kun said he had a special
role for me to play.
Listen up, people!
The school just rendered their decision!
This year's Culture Festival
will be a class competition!
The first-place class will receive
an extravagant prize!
Oh...
I should mention the prizes!
Option one!
A refrigerator in your classroom
for the rest of the year!
Love that chilled juice, yeah?
Option two!
The classroom gets one of next year's primo
air conditioners installed this month!
Love that moist air, yeah?
The ban on electrical devices
in the restroom will be lifted!
Love to curl your hair, yeah?
Finally!
Coupons from Supermarket Kanoya.
Love those coupons, yeah?
Huh? What?
Hey! The guys need to pull their weight!
R-Right...
What do you want for dinner?
Amberjack.
Prepared how?
Teri...
Yaki, right?
Sorry.
I've been waiting for you
here...this whole time.
So...
Damn stalker!
Taiga!
Stop being so stubborn!
Let me go, you stupid mutt!
And stop taking his side!
That's cruel!
I thought you'd be the one
person on my side!
I'm saying this because I'm on your side!
This is for your own good!
Who is that?
Isn't that your father?
Hasn't he come for you?
You could at least hear him out!
You're wrong!
That's a stalker!
I don't need him!
Stop being ridiculous!
Hey!
Weren't you crying about being abandoned!?
Admit it!
Be honest with yourself!
You want to go home, don't you!?
What do you know about me?
I don't need that loser.
He didn't abandon me.
I abandoned him!
Tossed him like a pile of worthless trash!
Damn it...
Do you...
Do you really see him as trash!?
My old man's never coming home,
no matter how much I beg!
This isn't for Taiga's own good...
I'm...
Sorry, Taiga...
Enough.
I'll do what you say.
So...
Get that look off your face.
Tai—
This is for the best, right?
That's how I'll try to see it.
Though I don't know if I'll be
able to change how I think.
But if that's what you say...
That's what I'll do.
This is a good thing...
This is...a good thing...
Isn't it?
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
I, Koigakubo Yuri, snuck over
the 30 barrier this summer.
Tee-hee.
Please give me presents...
Actually, please just...take me.