What's the matter?
So, you are going to Mistran?
Did you offend anyone?
Well it's a place with a lot of delicious food and beautiful girls.
It's already been half a year since the cease-fire started.
It's always the survivors from the war that are the winners.
Hey, Clim!
You're so lucky, Captain Tamos!
Damn!
Oh, you're awake now, young lady?
This is our loot, please take it.
Ah...caramel!
I-It's really an honour to receive such a precious gift.
Er...Sergeant!
It's nothing special.
I've told you that if you have a good relationship with the bugler, you will not miss the retreating bugle.
The drafting has stopped. Trainees should be rare...
Are you a volunteer?
Yes. I want to learn music.
What???
Well... Not really...
It's nice to be honest, little girl.
Private, what's your name?
Kanata
My name is Sorami Kanata!
Resounding Sound
The City at Dawn
There is a festival in Seize today.
Festival?
Therefore, I have to stop here.
Look.
That's where you're assigned to.
We call it the "Time telling fortress."
Find your way there.
Yes sir!
Appointment document.
Private Sorami Kanata,
Effective immediately, you are assigned to Platoon 1121 of Seize, Trois Province.
From the Army Headquarter of the Republic of Helvetia.
Task Completed at 13:20.
Thank you very much!
The city of lakes and glass, Seize.
Hold on! Hold on!
Report time is 15:00.
Eventually, I will let you show your nice sound.
Direction check. Complete.
Time check. Complete.
Equipment check. Complete.
Move...
Forward!
Welcome!
G-flat.  What a wonderful sound!
Wow...A fish.
10 Yen 25 Sen...
How beautiful, this doll ...
I-I am sorry!
What's up, Rio?
A little cat lost in the festive atmosphere.
She's heading towards somewhere she doesn't know.
That's inevitable.
Small cats always love to wander around.
That's why they are lovely. Am I right?
You would have been right, if it were a wild cat.
But unfortunately, that is a tamed cat.
I was really frightened...
But I have found another nice place.
What's the matter?
Thank you!
Huh?
Oh Soldier-san.
A girl from the fort?
It's worth celebrating!
For the flame, thank you.
Thank you!
I see.
It's my turn!
Take this!
Thank you.
Hey!
Are you an idiot?
You are all wet! Are you going to report in this uniform?
A...Actually...Well...
Oh. Take care.
Thank yo-
...That's enough. Come along with me.
Huh?
Ahh...
Is the water temperature okay?
Yes. It's perfect.
That's good.
Seems like you are a target that everyone loves to shoot at. Can't you try to evade?
Take it easy. This dye will fade after drying.
Don't worry.
Excuse me, is that the festival?
It originated from a local tale of Seize.
A tale? What is it about?
The Maidens of Flame, protecting the city.
I am sorry for all this trouble.
It'll be billed. The repair is already done as well.
And also there's this.
Filicia?
She's really a busybody.
So late.
So late.  So late. She's really late!
I deliberately came out to welcome her!
My, just be patient and wait.
It's from your father, right? It is really pretty.
D-flat.
Thank you very much for the bath.
Well...I don't know why I always get easily lost...
But it is really my pleasure to meet nice people like you.
Take your time.
But please don't get lost here again.
Huh?
Oh wow! Ha Ha Ha!
You can distinguish pitches?
A clear and melodious sound, and it's nostalgic.
Well...I don't really mean this...
You thief!
Idiot!
Thank you very much.
Geez...
How can you forget about your life for that kind of thing!?
But that bell...
Let it be...
Just, let it be...
Late.
Happy.
Excuse me...
I have something to do so I am leaving.
Don't get lost again.
That bell must be very precious.
What should I do?
Oh crap!
Over there?
Move forward!
Aimerais-tu, en ce monde, voir quelque chose s'effacer
Would you like to see something, in this world, erase itself
Et que l'air soit plus pur, le coeur des hommes transformé
And the air be purer, the hearts of men transformed
Et pourtant, tout est si fragile ici, sur la Terre
And yet everything is so fragile here, on Earth
Il n'est rien qui soit futile, tu sais
There is nothing that is futile, you know
D'un coté beau ou bon et quelquefois prodigieux
From one side beautiful or good, and sometimes prodigious
Maidens of Flame?
A long time ago,
Way before the world became like the one we know.
Et de l'autre laid ou pauvre et bien souvent monstrueux
And from the other ugly or poor, and often monstrous
At the bottom of the valley in this city, there was a demon living there.
Qu'importe ce que ton coeur te dictera, souviens-toi
Whatever your heart dictates to you, remember
Que la différence naît dans tes yeux
That the difference is born in your eyes
The demon breathed fire, and shook the earth.
People were living in hardship.
Chante toutes les couleurs du Monde
Sing all the colours of the World
And one day, it kidnapped the maidens who lived in the fortress,
Sans manquer une seule note
Without missing a single note
and imprisoned them in an underground labyrinth.
Chaque chose a sa place ici
Everything has its place here
However, the maidens didn't give up.
Chaque émoi forme la symphonie de notre vie
Every excitement forms the symphony of our lives
They sounded the gold horn bestowed by the angels to escape from the labyrinth.
By borrowing the enormous power from the spider,
They knocked down the demon, and cut its head off.
Savoure l'harmonie du ciel
Savour the harmony of the sky
But the heads started breathing out fire.
Vois que tout est essentiel
See that everything is essential
If this kept on, the town above would be engulfed by the fire.
To prevent the fire from spreading outside, the maidens held the demon's head one by one.
Et comprends que, toi aussi, tu en écris la mélodie
And understand that, you too, you write the melody
People splashed water at the demon's head and the maidens,
And the fire was finally extinguished after a year.
After this, to worship the maidens who sacrificed their lives to save the town,
the Water Festival was started.
She didn't come after all... that newbie.
Don't worry about that!
Look, captain! Rio-senpai is...
Indeed. It suits her very well.
Letting her perform the ritual is the righteous choice.
Wasn't it decided by drawing...?
I am lost again.
I am so useless.
It's also fun when I'm lost,
But that's because I meet new friends.
Being alone... I don't like it.
Lost?
Yes. I want my mom.
Relax.
If you want it...
Your feelings will be felt.
Really?
Yes.
The sound will surely reach.
...surely reach...
Sound it,
and reach her.
Maidens of Flame, we bless your rest peacefully
Clench the demon. Relieve the curse.
Pray that the day of the demon's awakening never comes.
This is ...?
The golden horn!?
Could it be the awakening of the demon!?
Kureha!
Please reach!
May it.. reach someone!
It reached!
Sound it, and...
Get up immediately!
Private Sorami Kanata!
Huh?
Here, is...?
How long do you still want to sleep?
Here, is the Time telling fortress.
The station of Platoon 1121.
Yesterday... well... I am sorry for the trouble I caused!
Indeed, it was troublesome.
I'm sorry!
However....
I'm just kidding.
However, don't be reckless again.
It's reckless to do such things just for this bell...
Let me tell you,
Trumpet!
Why this fortress is called the "Time telling fortress".
This is the Sound of the Skies!
Kazumiya Rio,
It's my name.
I am going to teach you how to become a trumpeter.
Please take care of me, Staff Sergeant Rio-dono.
Just call me Rio.
Filicia...
It's the captain's decision. We don't use military rank here.
Er...
Then...
Rio-senpai!
So, shall we start now?
Reveille. Let me hear it.
This girl is really bad at it...
First Battle - The story of the Chair
Next time: First Battle - The story of the Chair