Come on, Senpai!
Let me try a new lock move on you!
It's called the Hundred-Twenty Lock!
One, two.  Here we go, let's dance.
Come on, please, Senpai.  Can I?
"Here we go, let's dance"?
Let me try the new lock on you!
They're so cute.  Aren't they, Shiina-san?
How unwise.
Gosh.  Is this grade school?  We're just gaining kids one after another here.
Are you speaking about me?
I'm God, remember.
Huh?  You're still going on about that?
You were clinging onto Otonashi, crying your eyes out.
Who cried, you said?
You're who's going to cry...
For example, recognize how useful a clothespin is.
Lament over how you're even less useful than a mere clothespin...
C-Clothespin...
It can clip.
By clipping, it keeps things from falling.
Meaning the laundry won't get dirty!
It's amazing!
It can even be used as a hairclip if need be!
Compared to that, what good am I?!
I can't do anything!  I'm not worth anything!
You.  Don't use hypnosis just to let off steam.
Otonashi-san.  Good morning.
What was this about?
He bothered me first.
I tried to wrap up the matter as amicably as possible.
How is this amicable?
You made a big man cry while on his knees.
Otonashi-kun.  Naoi-kun.
I've got something for you two.  Come here.
What do you want, calling us out here?
Naoi-kun, I want you to restore Otonashi-kun's lost memories.
You're ordering me?
Who do you think you are?!
She's your leader.  Your boss.
Be obedient and listen to her.
Wait, my memories?!
Yes, your memories.
Naoi-kun's hypnosis is the real thing.
You should be able to regain the memories you lost.
I see.  I would like to take part in that.
Hold on!  Don't go deciding this without me.
Why not?  Don't tell me you want to remain oblivious of your past?
Well...
Sure, I want to remember.  But, what is this anxiety?
Could it be that I'm worried that this life will end if I remember?
I...
I didn't know I was enjoying this life with everyone this much.
But, when I remember my past, will I be able to spend time with them the same way I have been?
Even then—
Otonashi-kun?
H... Huh?  Oh, yeah.
Sure.
No matter what past you see, please don't lose sight of yourself.
No matter what happens to you, I alone will be at your side.
Please say something.
I'll be at your side, too, so relax.
Yeah, that's reassuring.
Huh?!  What's the difference?
Well, fine.
Please have a seat.
Okay, let's begin.
Is school fun, Onii-chan?
Not at all.  I don't even go there.
It might be fun if you go.
Maybe, if I was smart.
I'm an idiot, so to people with poor grades like myself, it's no place to be.
Isn't studying fun?
How could it be?  It's studying.
How about friends?  Is playing with your friends fun?
I'd rather watch TV or play games alone.
It's a bother to cater to what others want to do and laugh at jokes that aren't even funny.
Really?  I'm looking forward to studying.
I look forward to making friends, too.
Oh, right.
Here.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
You piece of shit!
I don't understand the point in life.
I don't get the meaning.
I can't even seem to build interest in others.
I live without getting involved with others because that's just easier.
I'm satisfied to work sluggishly part-time, making just enough to eat.
Even then, I always go to see my sister.
With the little money I make, I buy her manga.
I randomly choose one from the stack, so I don't even know if I'm buying her duplicates.
I might be buying a different title each time, too, so that the story never flows.
Still...
Thank you, Onii-chan.
My sister always says that.
She seems to be happy with anything I give her.
She's different than me.
She has hope in life, so I'm sure she'll find purpose, too.
Yet, these past two years, she's been stuck in the hospital.
Poor thing.  If only I could switch with her.
If she could switch with me, who has no hope nor purpose in life...
These are the thoughts that make me come back here.
Winter's come.
Summer is a tough season to work, but winter is even worse.
My fingertips are so cold, they feel like they'll chip off.
Even then, I'll continue to work to live on.
"Live on"?  What for?
No, I can't think about that.
If I think, I might even quit working.
I have to continue working like this,
so that I can live on and buy presents for my sister.
Oh yeah.  On Christmas, I'll ask the doctor to let her go outside, even if for just a little while.
Do wheelchairs become useless in snow?
If so, I'll carry her on my back.
I'd walk to the ends of the earth, if it were her on my back.
Then, I'll buy whatever she wants, wherever she wants.
If possible, I want to let her have some cake at a nice store.
Looks like I need to make more money.
If you could go out on Christmas, where would you want to go?
The main street in the city.
Somewhere like that?
All the trees will be lit up.  Did you know?
No.  I never bother to go places like that at Christmas.
I heard it's really beautiful.
They started doing it just last year.  The doctor told me.
Then, you wanna go there?
I can?
I'll ask if you can.
Even if they say no, I'll sneak you out.
Really?
Yeah, I mean it.
Yay!  Thank you, Onii-chan!
That's the biggest "thank you" from her I've ever gotten.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry!
I've started working several other part-time jobs.
At home, all I do is sleep.
I feel able to work because I have motivation to.
The one thing I worry over is how her condition is only worsening.
Permission to go out obviously wasn't granted.
So after visiting hours, I snuck into her room, and took her out to the nighttime city.
Wow!  Hey, do you see these?  They're amazing.
Very pretty.
Yeah.  They're really pretty.
I'm glad I got to see them, too.
It's all thanks to you.
Well, the fun continues.
First, we'll get your present.
I'll buy you anything you want.
I made lots of money just for today.
So I can buy you anything, no matter the price.
What do you want?
How about we go check out some shops?
We can even go to a jewelry store.
Or do you want to go to a department store?
Onii-chan...
Thank you.
Sure.
There's a surprise waiting after we go shopping, too.
We'll go to dinner!
I've not been there myself, but I put in reservations for a nice restaurant I found in a magazine.
There'll be a full-course meal.
A full-course meal, I tell you.  Isn't that amazing?
I continued to talk and walk.
Then if you'll excuse me, I'll be off.
Are you continuing to live alone in that house?
It'll be lonely.
I'll be fine.  I'm used to it.
Are you sure?  Will you really be all right?
If anything comes up, let me know.
You can come for dinner anytime you'd like, too.
Yes.  Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for your kindness.
I had a purpose in life.
That purpose had been right beside me, all along.
I just never noticed.
I was able to live on just hearing "thank you" from her.
Her gratitude was enough to make me feel alive.
I was happy...
I was such an idiot.
To only notice this now...
She meant so much to me, yet I couldn't do anything for her.
All she ever did was read the manga I brought for her at the hospital.
Was she...  Was she really happy with her life, that consisted of just those things?
And, now that I've lost her, has my life ended, too?
My days had been filled with happiness that I didn't realize existed.
Those days are gone.
I don't have anything by my side anymore.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much!
Take care of yourself.
I might be able to find purpose in life again.
I think I can find meaning in it again.
If I could spend my life for someone else...
Have you recalled?
Yeah.
It doesn't sound like you had a pleasant life.
Could you leave me alone for a while?
I once lived sluggishly and without putting in any effort, but you taught me the purpose of life.
I found that purpose, and I died in the middle of working toward the dream I'd found?
I died without accomplishing anything?
That's just not right...  It's not right!
I can't die off like that...
Hatsune!
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
People's hearts are unstable for a while after they regain their memories.
So you're not the only one.
I'm weak, aren't I?
That just emphasizes how strong you are.
That's not true.
So, did something change?
Your feelings.  Are you going to keep working with the Battlefront?
I will.
I can't go rest in peace yet.
I see.  So now you have motivation, too.
Yeah, so I look forward to working with you again.
So, what do you need to report to me?
We're short on today's meal tickets.
So what?  Wanna do Tornado?
No.  Today's operation will be Monster Stream.
It's finally here!
It's a carnival of despair.
What is this operation?
Is there a monster living in this world?
Yes.  It's the Lord of the River.
"Lord of the River"?
There's a river not too far from here, right?
We'll be gathering food from there.
I-Isn't that just fishing?
That's right.  Is there a problem?
Ah, no...
They got me going on an imaginary fantasy...
I wonder who will win.
I can't wait.
What are you doing there?
Weeding and various other things.
I-I see.  Oh, right!
You should come, too.
Hm?
We're all going fishing at the river.
"River"?
It's against the school code to go near there since it's dangerous.
What's the big deal?  You're not the Student Council President anymore.
Break the rules all you want.
But I'm still a student.
Just who are you trying to bring?!
Come on.  Let's have her come along.
She's our enemy!  She's the Battlefront's nemesis!
He's a dumbass!
How unwise.
Listen to me.  She's harmless now.  She's not our enemy anymore.
But she was the former Student Council President!
Not to mention, the deputy president is with us.
Exactly.
But more than that, I'm God.
I told you, you aren't!
What are we gonna do, Yurippe?
She's not the president anymore, so why not?
Y-You sure about this?
Our memberlist is getting crazy...
Come to think of it, no one brought anything with them.
A notice was sent to the Guild, so don't worry.
They sent the maniac.
"Maniac"?
Who's he?
That's Saitou.
He knows lots about guns, too, but he's a fishing maniac so the Guild calls him Fish Saitou.
When we do this operation, he comes to the surface with fishing equipment on a cart.
He brings them from that far away?  Just how much does he love fishing?
Basically, he's another dumbass.
Okay, let's start!
What a dumbass...
If I hadn't asked that stupid question in the beginning, I might have been on your side.
There's no one like that.
Well, there can be one, right?
There isn't one.  Even if there were, they'd be obliterated.
Tachibana.
We won't be obliterated.
So you can get along with us.
Here.  Let's fish with everyone.
Ow!  Ow!  Ow!  You hooked it on me!
What do I do next?
You got it wrong.
First, you use a lure or put some bait on the hook.
So, you're okay with worms, huh?
What's next?
Swing the rod toward the river as hard as you can!
T-Takeyama!
Call me Christ!
Wow, you've got some amazing strength...
Overdrive is in passive mode.
"Passive"?
Maybe...   Maybe, she might be able to do it.
Do what?
Fish up the Lord of the River.
It's a real monster, just like the operation name.
Something's tugging.
M-Monster Stream!
You mean this?!
Originally, Monster Stream was a sign of the lord's anger.
When this happens, everyone takes cover.
But if it's her, then maybe...
Are we really going to do this?
Just how big is it?  The rod's going to snap!
I don't want you to underestimate my skills.
It's made so it can fight against the lord!
Even so, this isn't going to let us pull it up!
What?  Are you guys trying to fish up the lord?
They're out of their minds.
Matsushita Fifth!
I'll give you the beef udon ticket, so help out!
Bring it on!
Oh, Hinata-senpai, you're so full of openings.
Maybe I'll take this chance to get a firm kick in.
Stop being cheap and help out, too!
We need more help!
Otonashi-san!
What the...  What a weak bunch.
Pull!  Pull!  Pull!  Pull!  Pull!  Pull!
Come on, gang!  Pull it like you mean it!
Now!
She got it out of the water!
Yeah, with us!
Who's the monster here?
Look out!
This isn't good.
It'll eat us if we fall straight down!
Crazy for you!
God never falls.
How unwise.
It's going to eat us!
I must save them.
Hey, with this, I don't think we'll hafta do Tornado for a good while.
What?  We're going to eat this every day?
More like, how are we gonna preserve this?
It'd be a waste to throw it away.  Can't be helped, then.
How about we cook it up and offer it to the NPCs?
Yeah, you're right.
I guess that's the only way.
It's like we're volunteering, huh?
Forget the Battlefront.  We're becoming some kind of charity organization.
But, we don't have an enemy to fight against, so will we really still be the Battlefront?
Then what else are we gonna be?
The "Slackers-So-We-Don't-Get-Obliterated Team"?
What kinda name is that?
Chop, chop, chop, chop.
I never thought a time like this would come.
Hey, Tachibana.
Can I call you by your first name?
Why?
Because we're closer friends now.
We are?
You mean we aren't?
We fished together and we're cooking together.
Besides, I've thought ever since you told me...
You have a pretty name.
I really like your name.
It's "Kanade" as in "to play music," right?
If that's what you wish, then please do.
My first name is Yuzuru.
You write the "tie the strings" part in kanji.  Call me that, too.
So, Kanade...  I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Will you continue to hang out with us?
Why?
Because I don't want you to be fighting
with others anymore.
I want you to have fun with everyone.
And, plus...
I want to be with you, too.
I see.  If that's what you're telling me to do, then I will.
It's a promise, you hear?
Okay.
Where did Yurippe go?
Oh yeah, I haven't seen her.
I bet she was watching us from somewhere high and above.
She wouldn't participate in a volunteer activity like this.
Hey!  Why don't you help, too?!
Yurippe!
Yurippe!  Who did this to you?!
Tenshi.
Tenshi?
Hold on!  Kanade was with me this whole time!
Matsushita Fifth!
So we're locked in...
I look forward to seeing you again.
Trap...
What does this mean?!
We can't perform a diversion against such a scary person!
I'll show you one possibility.
Is Kanade all right?
Angel Player...
I'll show it to you physically.
How unwise!
Looks like it's showtime!
Those who cannot keep up will be left behind!
You look busy...
Please be safe, Kanade!