“Durarara!!”
Created by Ryogo Narita
Original art by
Suzuhito Yasuda
Design
Koichiro Natsume
Kazutomo Suzuki
Masashi Yabe
Naohiro Tafu
Design collaboration
Dengeki Bunko Editing Department
Dengeki Bunko Magazine Editing Department
Series organization
Noboru Takagi
Character design
Takahiro Kishida
Tatsuo Yamada
Mechanic design/animation director
Chief animation director
Akira Takada
Art
Kiyoshi Ito
Color design
Hiromi Miyawaki
CG Producer
Norikazu Kanbayashi
Photography
Hitoshi Tamura
Editing
Kazuhiko Seki
Assistant director
Shinya Kawazura
Music
Makoto Yoshimori
Opening Theme
“Uragiri No Yuuyake”
by Theatre Brook
Song and lyrics by Taiji Sato
Arranged by Theatre Brook
(Epic Records Japan)
Executive producer
Takeshi Ochi
Naoko Koyama
Music producer
Keichi Tonomura
What is this “urban legend”?
The black motorcycle! It's the headless rider!
The men riding the black motorcycles have nothing above their necks...
And despite being completely headless, they can still move.
It doesn't look like it's going to be that tough a job, but be careful anyway.
I... didn't hear about you becoming a hero of justice.
What the hell was that?
What the hell is that thing?!
Animation producer
Yumi Sato
Producer
Akane Yokoyama
Atsushi Wada
Yasuyo Ogisu
Kozue Kaneniwa
Hiroo Maruyama
Director
Takahiro Oomori
Production
Brain's Base
Ikebukuro Dollars
Aniplex
ASCII Media Works
Hakuhodo DY Media Partners
Movic
Daily broadcast at
www.durarara.com (PC/Mobile)
The headless rider?! I've heard of him!
My friend said she saw him go by her!
Damn... I'm not really interested in the matter.
If that's what you're after, I took a picture.
Look!
The headless rider?
It's this guy, right here!
We've heard of him, haven't we?
I think we saw him near Sunshine.
Really?
We didn't know for sure, but everyone there was making such a fuss, so we thought it must've been him.
Everyone's talking about it a lot.
Looks like it showed up again, the black motorcycle.
But is it really true that he's headless?
It's just a rumor that was spread in bad taste.
Still, I've heard rumors that seem pretty believable.
There's no way he's headless.
If he's not human...
then he could be, couldn't he?
In reality, all of the people who've actually met it have become really quiet.
I'm sorry, but I don't know much about it.
What about you?
What's your impression of the legendary headless rider?
Is it scary? Is it cool?
Does it seem like it's really a good person?
No, maybe...
you just don't know what to think?
Today, I'll tell you everything I know about the headless rider.
It may get long and convoluted, but I'd like you to listen attentively, and be intrigued.
Lonesome Misery
First, let me introduce myself.
My name is Kishitani Shinra and I am twenty-four years old.
I'm an unlicensed doctor in this town.
Moreover, you could say I'm a traveling witch doctor.
I treat people who have been wounded by illegal weapons,
and perform plastic surgery on those who need to alter their appearance.
I may look like this, but I have a pretty skilled hand, and people trust me.
Well, let's get on to the real subject here.
I'm home!
That's right. I live with the headless rider.
Certy Sturluson.
I'm home, Certy.
I just finished another one of those easy jobs I get all the time.
How was yours?
Don't peek!
Sorry, sorry! I didn't mean it in a, how should I say it, dirty way. It was a completely unintentional...
You look a little irritated somehow.
Did you forget to take your calcium pills?
Are you telling me to "Go suck an eggshell"?
Not a bad idea!
I really do think so.
Although, I'm not really into the nutritional sciences, so I wouldn't know much about the amount of calcium in an eggshell,
or how efficiently your body would absorb it.
Of course, we don't even know where your brain tissue is in the first place,
so there's also the question of whether calcium would help at all.
Shut up.
Hey, Certy. I know I've asked this before,
but what does the world look like to someone who, like you, has no eyes?
I can't try to explain it to someone else when I don't even understand it myself.
She has no head,
but she has eyesight, she can hear sounds and she can smell.
However, just because she doesn't have a head, it doesn't mean she can see in all directions at once.
Although, it does appear that her field of vision is a little wider than that of the average human being.
This is nothing more than a theory of mine,
but what would you think of the idea that the sci-fi looking substance,
constantly steaming up from your body like a shadow,
has its particles released into your surroundings instead of light,
thereby gathering information about your surroundings by absorbing any disruption they encounter?
Of course, anything far away would be less perceptible.
I don't care. As long as I can see and hear, that's all that matters.
Certy, you're always like that.
I'm just curious to know how different the world you perceive is from mine.
I'm not just talking about vision either.
It's also a question of values.
Not your values as a human,
but as a fairy who has been born into a body in this town.
The merits of the world as seen by a Dullahan.
What's wrong?
Tell me what's on your mind. What happened?
Orihara-kun said that your job today was going to be easy.
I finished the job itself easily, without any complications.
And?
We're really both smugglers in our own unique way.
I depend on your existence as much as you depend on mine.
I'm not willing to admit to that last part.
Don't say that.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
I'd really like for us to be on friendlier terms.
From here on out.
Is it just me, or is the atmosphere here getting creepy?
Why, it's just you, of course.
By the way, have you heard of the Dullahan?
Apparently, they're headless fairies from Ireland,
and there's an old man in Yoyogi park claiming that he'd seen one.
That old man started making a fuss,
shouting "It has no head! It has no head!"
So he must've been talking about the Dullahan's head, right?
Is he still there?
Who knows? I sure don't.
How interesting.
Certy Sturluson isn't a human.
She's a Dullahan mentioned in Celtic folklore and the like,
a kind of fairy.
Do you know anything about a portrait painter?
That person isn't here anymore.
Hey, didn't he say he was leaving for Yokohama?
The Dullahan ride carrying their heads under their arms
in two-wheeled carriages pulled by headless horses, called Cóiste Bodhar.
They visit the homes of people whose time has come to die.
If those people open their door,
a tub full of blood is poured onto them.
That legend, which reeks of death,
and her true form, in reality, don't have much in common.
Except for the fact that she's headless, of course.
Why did she come to Japan,
to Tokyo, to Ikebukuro?
Why is she so obsessed with her head?
Let's discuss that for a moment.
It was twenty years ago.
She suddenly woke up in the mountains,
only to find that her head was gone.
It was at that moment she realized that she had lost most of her memories.
Such as why she did what she did,
and memories of her distant past.
However, she clearly remembered the fact that she was a Dullahan,
that her name was Certy Sturluson,
and she knew how to use her powers.
Despite that, the first thing that shocked her was...
Just now, I wasn't using my head to think that.
That very fact.
Then she realized that she could feel the presence of some type of consciousness emitting from her neck.
Pondering the circumstances, she reached one conclusion:
Her head and body shared her consciousness,
and the memories she had lost were still in her head.
Then she made up her mind... that from then on, the purpose of her existence would be to find her head,
the head which knew the true purpose of her existence.
Perhaps her head had left her body of its own accord,
but even then, she would never know until she got her hands on it.
He's already left Yokohama.
Next, I tried Tama, and after that, Chiba.
No matter where I went, it was the wrong place.
Shouldn't you have just put it off till tomorrow?
I was desperate.
My head could have been there.
I wanted to get it back, no matter what.
Within one day, if possible.
I hate living like this, with my memories and everything a blur.
It seemed that her head, which she had been following using what little presence she still felt around her,
had gone overseas.
Apparently, the ship it was on had left for Japan.
She resolved to stow away on a ship and sail after it,
but the question of the horse remained.
This was a familiar spirit of the Dullahan that possessed the corpse of a horse.
If she had to, she could get rid of him,
but where would it go after that?
That was probably something her head still remembered.
Then she thought that even if she knew how to get rid of the horse, she wouldn't be able to get around very quickly.
Just then,
she found...
that thing.
In the end, I never caught up.
However...
I do know that painter guy.
He had been in South Ikebukuro Park since about two days before.
Yeah.
Want me to come with you?
It can't be too convenient going alone. Right?
It's done!
That's amazing!
He drew it prettier than you, Arisa!
Hey!
You really are good, ojii-san!
No, no, there are still plenty of things I want to draw that I can't do yet.
Thank you very much!
You're welcome!
Let's go.
Come again!
'Kay.
I'm sorry, but it's already getting dark,
so I'm done for the day.
Is it true that you've seen a Dullahan?
Yeah. Yeah, it's true.
I saw it when I was young, in the mountains of Ireland.
With my own two eyes.
What do you mean when you say it lost its head?
It lost its head?
That's not it.
It had no head.
It just didn't have one.
Look.
It was a woman. A terribly beautiful woman at that.
On a night thick with fog, I passed by her on a mountain road.
She rode by with an amazing vigor.
It was a terrifying, yet beautiful, sight.
It wasn't something of this world. I knew that right away.
I went back to the lodge and told everyone,
and they said it was a Dullahan for sure.
Evidently, they had been living there since times of old.
Why wasn't your Dullahan carrying its head?
I couldn't draw it.
The more I drew, the more it changed in appearance.
Even though I'm sure I remember seeing her, I just can't seem to reproduce exactly what I saw.
What color was the woman's hair? Her eyes?
What type of expression did she have?
If I could describe it in words, I wouldn't be trying to draw it.
Come to think of it, a strange man came up to me recently.
He said that these drawings are perfect the way they are.
That it's better with her having no head.
He sure was strange.
Why are you so obsessed with her?
That was the most moving experience of my life.
That night was a once in a lifetime thing.
I want to bring it back. The memory of that time, of that very moment.
Ojii-san... thanks.
I see.
By the way,
you don't remember meeting that man before then, do you?
No.
That Dullahan may or may not have been you.
Or he could have been mistaken altogether.
It was me. It had to be.
Is that so?
Where was I riding to?
What was I thinking, what was my goal?
Do you really need to worry about it that much?
You're an elusive, and very unconventional being.
And almost as a consequence, your goal is to fulfill your own wishes.
What do you mean?
I'll state it simply. Give it up.
I wonder if what that strange man said is right.
Maybe it is better that you have no head.
Let's stop looking for that head of yours and go somewhere,
just the two of us.
Anywhere will do.
If you want, I'll even take you back to your hometown– whatever it takes.
I'll go there too. And then we'll be together, and–
Not that I don't like you,
but I'm fine living here, just like we are now.
Don't say that.
It's fine!
In that case,
could you at least act a bit more like a girl?
Enough!
So there are some differences between her values and mine, after all?
I digress, though. Back to what I was saying.
Her story, since she got on the ship. No...
our story, since we got on that ship.
She bargained with one of the crew members and became a stowaway,
but she soon noticed that she stood out terribly.
The woman I know her as now looks as ordinary as can be,
but when I first met her, it was quite a shock.
I was four years old at the time.
My father and I were on our way home to Japan.
Hey! Dad! Dad!
There's a lady in the cargo hold!
Even by a stretch, my father, Shingen, is not what you'd call an ordinary man.
Hurry! Hey! Hey! Dad!
When he heard about what I had seen, his natural response as a parent should have been to laugh it off.
But he was different.
Maybe it was because of his nature as a doctor; he immediately became interested.
Excuse me, miss.
Excuse my impudence, but is it true that you have no head?
My dad told her:
"Let me dissect you just once, and I can tell you where you should be going."
She consented.
Of course, he had to take precautions, so she started getting nervous.
Apparently, she doesn't remember much of what happened then.
Maybe the anesthetic used on humans didn't work on her,
and thus, she went into shock.
Looks as though she feels pain, but not nearly as intense as humans do.
She has no heart. Even her organs are only organs in shape, but have no functions.
She has arteries, but there is no blood flowing through them. There is only flesh.
It's as if she is a living mannequin.
However, look at this.
How can this thing die?
What a terrible father, right?
Having his four-year-old son dissect her.
Still, thanks to this kind of "education," I learned the medical skills I have today.
You never know what good will come of these things.
What's wrong?
From the first time I saw her, I was enchanted.
That feeling hasn't changed at all during the last twenty years we've lived together.
And she has been looking for her head the whole time while working as a smuggler.
I wonder what she'll do if her head ever comes back?
What will happen to her?
Is her will the same as her head's?
Or...
What are you taping?
What should I say...
I wanted to talk about my everyday life in detail,
for the generations after us.
I don't care what it is. Just keep it quiet. I can't sleep.
My bad, Certy.
Well, that's it for now. Stay tuned for more.
Woah!
It's perfect!
Huh? How is it perfect?
A real Dullahan is supposed to be holding its head.
It's perfectly fine without the head, don't you think?
There's no way it is. You only say that because you haven't seen the real thing.
She was an extremely beautiful woman.
Yeah, I bet.
Still, I really think she looks better without her head.
It's more charming that way.
It's perfect like this.
So you have nothing to worry about, ojii-san.
It's okay if you can't draw it. It's fine just the way it is.
Okay, but I'm still drawing.
I'm telling you, it's fine right now!
You're a strange man.
I'm not that weird.
This story is fictional. It has nothing to do with persons,
groups of people or events in real life.
Bait and Switch
Next episode
Durarara!!
Do you want to discover a heartbreaking life with my "Lovey-Lovey Get You" program?
Then tune your heart in to the shy, yet cool, Kida Masaomi channel!
Next episode: Bait and Switch
Don't miss a once-in-a-three-hundred-year chance!