Thank you for riding with us.
Passengers changing to
the Chuo Line, Yamanote Line,
Keihin-Tohoku Line, Tokaido Line,
Joban Line, Sobu Line, Keio Line,
or the Tohoku, Hokuriku, and Joetsu
Shinkansen Lines. Please transfer here.
This train will be
turning back at 17:54 as...
Miss?
Miss!
Good morning. You've reached Tokyo.
Thank you.
I had to get off at Shinagawa
and take the blue line...
but I came all the way to Tokyo.
Um, blue...
Well, there's light blue and indigo.
Bound for Kamata and Kannai...
Get your grilled eel bento,
katsu sandwich, and katsu curry here!
Grilled eel, katsu sandwich...
Grilled eel, katsu sandwich,
and katsu curry...
Grilled eel, katsu sandwich...
Grilled eel, katsu sandwich,
and katsu curry...
Whoa.
Um...
Yokohama...
In March, at the age of 17,
I moved to Tokyo.
Because I hate to lose.
Because I wasn't wrong.
Snow!
This unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
Crying in a crowd with a voiceless voice
Come morning
The footsteps drown out the voice
No matter how much time passes
It never dries
The cold, muddy waters of a decaying city
In a world where nothing changes
We have to live through it
It may be dumb, but we have no choice
We've already started walking
It may seem unreal
It may seem stupid
This hopeless city of ours
But I still saw it with my own eyes
I touched it with these hands
See? See?
See? There it goes again
It's so stupid
Shine a light through
The hopeless darkness
This isn't a dream
Even in a dead city
Giving up won't change anything
Even now, now
Now, this unfinished beat covers the night
Embracing us before we're crushed
Even if your hand is unreliable
That is your own hand
There will be change
If you just reach out
TOKYO HEAVE-HO
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
It's Iseri. I'm here to pick up my key.
That figures.
I mean, I got here pretty late.
Still dead.
Um...
Is this it?
Excuse me, is this...
Keep it down!
I'm sorry!
This is it.
Yeah, I figured.
These places usually have...
No?
Excuse me.
Ow!
I live next door. Can I help you?
Um... My name is Iseri. I just moved here.
Oh, is that right? Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
It's just that I don't have the key.
I was supposed to get it
from the real estate agent today,
but I showed up too late.
Did you call?
My phone battery died...
Want to use mine?
The phone number is saved on my phone.
Then why don't you recharge it
at our place?
It's okay, we don't mind at all.
No, thank you. I'm sure it'll work out.
Thank you for the offer.
Excuse me! I'll just leave my bag there!
Yes, finally!
9 MESSAGES FROM SUZUNE
That figures.
SUZUNE
CALLING
Hello.
You finally answered.
Mom! Nina answered her phone!
Sorry, my battery died earlier.
What are you doing?
The man called us.
He said you never showed up.
I know.
I'll go tomorrow.
Enough. Leave her be.
Bye.
Do you really think
you can make it over there?
Sorry, my battery's low.
AROUND HERE
I'LL BE PLAYING HERE
That's close by.
"22:00"?
No way!
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
Whether my fingers tremble or not
There's no right answer
There's no losing
-I've been me all my life
-She's actually here.
That's all there is
No matter how much I fight
There's no tomorrow
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
You're Momoka Kawaragi, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm a big fan of yours and Diamond Dust.
Thanks.
I really love your songs.
I just moved to Tokyo
from the countryside today
with the help of your music.
That right?
It's true! Really.
I've probably listened to it
a thousand times.
I saw on social media
that you were playing here tonight.
It felt like fate.
Then would you buy a CD?
Yes, of course!
A thousand yen.
Here.
Thanks.
That's not a thousand yen.
You're so straight-laced.
Did I say something weird?
No.
I'm just kind of happy
to have a fan like you.
Hey.
Like I said last time, this is our spot.
What? Then write your name down.
Go play somewhere else.
Let's go.
O-Okay.
Hey!
Get back here!
Run!
You're dead!
Why am I running too?
That's a good point.
Maybe if you tell them
that you don't really know me,
they might forgive...
Get back here!
Yeah, never mind.
This way!
Damn it!
Idiots.
What does that mean?
It means thank you.
Then why were they so mad?
What's your name?
Nina.
Nina Iseri.
Kawasaki and Shin-Kawasaki?
Wouldn't you expect
Kawasaki to come after Shin-Kawasaki?
But it wasn't.
You could've just looked it up.
My phone died.
So that's why you're locked out.
My uncle told me that Kawasaki would be
a good place to live in Tokyo.
What a lie!
Tokyo?
What?
Kawasaki isn't in Tokyo.
It's actually in Kanagawa Prefecture.
Just like Yokohama.
What? He said
it was on the edge of Tokyo...
You got tricked by your uncle
and real estate agent.
I bet they gave you an unpopular room.
That's why rent was so cheap...
Although, I actually love Kawasaki.
Yes, I mean,
I got the chance to meet you after all.
I always carry the ticket for the canceled
Diamond Dust concert in my hometown.
Would you autograph it?
Wow.
Here you go.
One medium beef bowl.
So this is a beef bowl!
Is this your first?
What planet are you from?
Kumamoto.
They don't have this chain?
We do!
But my family always eats at home.
What are you, some rich girl?
No, it's not like that.
Yummy! What is this?
Is it that good?
Yes!
That was delicious.
It's almost time for the last train.
What's your plan?
I'll make do.
How?
Come on.
Thanks. I'll leave money here
for the both of us.
Thank you!
I take care of my fans.
It was very delicious!
Thank you very much!
You wanna fight?
Thank you!
You said it meant thank you!
It's the complete opposite!
My bad.
Is this it?
Be prepared, it's cold.
The heat doesn't work.
Do you live with family?
No.
Go on in, it takes forever
to get these off.
The room up ahead.
Excuse me.
The light's on the left.
You okay with cats?
Have a seat. I'll pour you some coffee.
Thank you.
So cool.
Do you play?
Not at all, but I wish I could.
Want to hold it?
Can I?
Go on.
Wow! It's heavier than I imagined.
It doesn't suit you.
That figures.
I'm kidding!
Anybody can learn
to look good holding a guitar.
You're still in high school?
Yes. I'm 17.
I'd be in my third year
if I was still in high school.
Do you want sugar?
Yes, please.
I also dropped out and moved here
with a friend when I turned 17.
It's already been three years...
So you're still 20?
I don't know why, but that stings.
But maybe this really is fate.
Yes, it's fate!
Um...
You just got here today, right?
Yes. If you'd like to exchange...
I'm going back to Asahikawa tomorrow.
Girls Band Cry.
Going back?
I'm leaving this place.
I'm heading back home and quitting music.
Why? Your songs are so amazing.
Thanks.
It'll get cold.
Momoka.
I don't have a choice.
Not everyone can make it big.
It's hard living off my music earnings.
I spend all my time at my part-time job.
But you made this song
and it's gotten so many views.
I gave it away.
I don't have the rights to that song.
Details!
Please.
You don't need the details.
Please!
I mean, you're the one who made it!
You couldn't have just given it away!
You can.
You can't!
- You can!
- You can't!
You're stubborn. A stubborn Kumamoto girl.
You got that right.
Please stop that.
Don't touch me.
Damn it.
What's with you?
You were so timid just minutes ago.
You're so weird.
Because that song...
Good evening.
If you make a racket,
the neighbors will complain again.
You're heading out now?
Is he...
He's...
Y-Your boyfriend, right?!
You live together?!
Calm down!
He's just a roommate.
You think
I could afford to live here alone?
But he's a man.
Yeah, but he's only interested in men.
He's probably staying over
at his boyfriend's.
Boyfriend?
Tokyo is so different!
It's Kawasaki.
We have different rooms and schedules.
We barely even see each other.
But...
You should think about
finding a roommate too.
Or else you'll just be spending
all your time working part-time.
How much is rent?
Fifty thousand.
And work?
I will, but I haven't found one yet.
Are you going to be okay?
I have savings, and I got some money
from my family when I left.
Oh, you got it easy then.
Sounds like you'll be fine.
As long as you have money...
What do you know about me?
Don't just assume that I have it easy!
Thank you for the coffee.
I should leave.
Hold up.
You walk pretty fast.
Look, I'm sorry.
You dropped out of school
and moved here at your age.
Of course it isn't easy.
What's your dream?
I don't really have one.
You don't have one?
I didn't come here because of a dream.
I just didn't have anywhere I belonged.
People acted like I was at fault
even though I did nothing wrong.
And I didn't want to lose to that.
I see. Then I need to apologize again.
What happened?
With you.
Why are you moving back to Asahikawa?
It was nothing big.
Just your usual fighting and splitting up.
You mean Diamond Dust?
Yeah.
When we split up, we talked about
who the song belonged to.
And since they said
they were going to continue music...
You just gave it to them?
At the time, I figured
I could just write another good song.
What?
So you're just a softie.
But I think that's cool of you.
Hey! That hurts!
Oh, your face is red.
Shut up!
Hey! You're messing up my hair!
Wanna go karaoke?
Now?
You know some old songs.
My grandma likes them.
But you still became
a fan of Diamond Dust.
Yes, I listened to you
when I was feeling really stuck
and it felt like you were singing about
exactly how I was feeling.
That I can't lose.
It's like my theme song.
Tonight was the last night for that song.
The last Diamond Dust song I'll ever sing.
I...
Okay, next song.
Ow...
Oh, it's just you.
Good morning.
By the time you read this, I'll be gone,
and the movers will have probably started.
I'm going to go pick up my last paycheck
and wait at the station for my train.
Anyway, I want you to have my guitar.
Enjoy your new life in Tokyo.
Sorry!
I'll unlock it now.
Yes, thank you.
GOOD LUCK!!
MIDDLE FINGER UP!
I'll be right back!
Momoka.
Momoka...
I'm sorry!
- What?!
- Hey, you!
Momoka!
Are you really sure?!
If you stop, it all ends!
If you say it's over,
then it really is over!
You okay?
I'm going to say something
really stubborn and selfish now!
I came here because I didn't want to lose!
So I don't want you to lose either!
Please...
raise your middle finger with me!
You can sing it, right?
Yes!
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
Whether my fingers tremble or not
I'm currently at a crossroads
You won't find on any map
What should I use to guide me?
People often say to follow the book
So many words I don't understand
Today is no different than that day
Will filling in this blank
Solve everything someday?
How would you move forward?
It's so blank
It's so long
The answers tend to be superficial clichés
Whether my fingers tremble or not
There's no right answer
There's no losing
I've been me all my life
That's all there is
No matter how much I fight
There's no tomorrow
No matter how much I resist
Next episode,
"Three Nocturnal Creatures."