Ah!
What should I do?!
This is the biggest pinch
Spring Onion Ramen's been in!
We were trying to figure out if Mitsuki should go to the audition...
...and we ended up getting into a huge fight!
Because...
...if we had just let her go...
...the handbook said that something would threaten her life!
Besides...
...it seems like Takuto's feelings are...
No
new
me
ss
ages.
Au
di
ti
on.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The audition...
I have to go...
I won't let you go.
What are you fooling around for?!
Look at this.
Au
dition.
Audition?
That's right.
That's why...
...you can't transform her...
You can't help her go to the audition!
I didn't want to say this, but...
You and that girl...
...are somehow seem to be related.
If you get any closer to her...
...it'll bring back your memories from when you were a human.
You know what will happen then, right?!
I love you...
I want to be with you forever...
I don't want you to become a ghost, Takuto...
Run! To the Audition!
I'm so tired...
I'm going to rest for a bit...
The whistle's missing...
What should I do?
I can't call for Takuto without it...
Takuto...
I don't want you to become a ghost, Takuto...
Mitsuki-san!
Did something happen?
Takuto!
Madam...
It doesn't look like she's in the house.
Madam!
I'm fine...
I was feeling a little dizzy...
For heaven's sake...
How much more is she going to make me worry?
Running away from the hospital in her state...
Hospital?!
Madam.
Please rest.
Did she collapse?!
You have to watch your health.
No!
I won't let you go!
I won't let you go... even if it kills me.
I mean...
I just gave you a serious confession...
But...
...it's the fifty-seventh time.
Gah!
No matter...
No matter how many times I confess...
...I'm always serious!
Takuto, you insensitive jerk!
Ow!
It hurts!
Are you okay?
Takuto's worrying about me?
It hurts so much that I can't stand...
Well, you're a tough person...
You should be able to handle this.
Hey!
What do you mean, "I'm tough?!"
So you are fine, after all.
Damn it...
If it's come to this...
My final trick...
If you aren't going to listen to my advice...
...I'll report everything that's happened to the Shinigami main office.
You'll be punished.
Do whatever you want.
Takuto!
No matter what the handbook tells you...
No matter what the Shinigami main office will do to me...
...I have to go.
Why?
Why do you go that far for her?!
I don't even know that myself.
But...
...I can't just leave her alone!
If she can't sing...
...I get this feeling that she'd die from that alone!
You're terrible... so terrible... Takuto.
In that case...
...I'll do whatever it takes to make her miss the audition!
I'm going to get in the way!
Really... where'd she go off to?
With her health...
A whistle?
Dr. Wakaouji.
Did someone from her home call?
The housekeeper, Tanaka-san, did just a moment ago...
And?
She hasn't gone home yet.
That girl...
She lost the whistle?
Yeah.
I might have an idea.
I'm going to look right now.
Please let me know if something happens.
Today's a sunny day, just like yesterday.
It looks like it'll be this summer's hottest day yet.
Well, next up is the traffic report.
Let's ask Kawada-san from the traffic center.
Kawada-san?
Yes!
I... fell asleep out here?
It's cold...
Takuto isn't coming...
I probably can't make it now...
Eichi-kun...
Mitsuki...
The moon... you know...
We can only see one side from the earth.
Really?
Such a beautiful moon...
But... on the other side... there are lots of craters left by meteorites.
It hides its wounds and keeps on smiling.
The first time I met you...
...I thought your name fit perfectly.
Eichi-kun...
I won't cry.
I won't cry... until I see you again.
If she ran away from the hospital...
...there's only one place she could have gone.
She has to be where the audition is being held!
She didn't get on, huh?
Next Stop: The Park
Good morning!
Ah.
Good morning, Madoka-chan.
Thank you so much for yesterday.
I had such a great time!
I did too.
You looked good yesterday, Madoka-chan.
I'm going to do my best today!
I'm looking forward to this!
Well.
Shall we start the camera test?
Okay!
Please...
Then... Madoka-san...
This way please.
Answer the phone, Mitsuki.
Where is this?
Which way should I go?
I can't move anymore.
Oh no.
What's wrong with this girl?
It's probably for a TV show.
They do this all the time lately.
All those variety shows...
I'm sorry...
I wasn't a good girl...
You must all be worried since I ran away from the hospital...
It looks like I won't make it to the audition...
Everyone...
Takuto...
Meroko...
Even though you helped me so much...
Besides...
I...
...still haven't apologized.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I...
All I wanted was to sing...
Eichi-kun... I wanted just to see you...
Mitsuki!!!
Mitsuki!
Hold on!
She isn't breathing.
Open your eyes!
Please... open your eyes!
Mitsuki!
Eichi-kun?
Takuto...
Just now... Takuto...
What are you doing?!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing... falling asleep in a place like this?!
Ah... um...
This way!
Ah... hey! You! Hold it!
Wait!
Um...
Does it still hurt?
Eh?
Ah... no... it doesn't hurt anywhere now.
Okay.
When does the audition start?
Um...
It's already 11 o'clock?!
What should I do?!
The audition's already started!
No way!
Hurry up.
We can still make it.
Huh?
You want Eichi to notice you, right?
You can't give up, then!
Okay!
You think I'll let you get there on time?
Absolutely not...!
Ah!
Ah?
What's wrong?!
Kya!
Don't look!
H-Hurry up and get away from there.
My shoe's stuck... I can't get away!
Then...
Don't look!
Sorry, did that hurt?
Geez... Takuto...
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
All right.
We're almost there.
Okay.
I'm just getting started...
Warning!
Glass!
Mitsuki!
Are you okay?
Just look at her face...
Huh?
Meroko!
Why am I seeing stars all around?
Are you okay?
Yeah... somehow...
Ah..?
Ah?!
No way!
Mitsuki!
Eh?
Takuto...
Ah... that was close...
O-Oh crap.
I wonder if this is for TV too?
They do a lot of filming these days, huh...
Too easy.
Ah!
It's Full Moon !
Full Moon's  right here!
What?!
Full Moon ?!
Really? The real thing?!
Full Moon ?
Then the filming just now...
There she is!
W-What do I do?!
Let's run!
This way!
An idol couldn't possibly be here...
We should still make sure.
Somehow... we managed to lose them...
There!
Huh?
The studio is in that building!
Okay!
Let's hurry!
Over there!
She's going in the building!
Crap... they found us!
What a relief...
Ah... s-sorry...
But... that was...
Was that... my first kiss?
But... it wasn't gentle at all...
I-I'm sorry about that.
Eh?
Sorry that it wasn't from someone else.
It's your fault for collapsing in the first place... that's why I had to use mouth-to-mouth...
No way!
You don't have to put it like that...
Well... don't worry about it.
It was only just mouth-to-mouth...
That... wasn't... a kiss...
It doesn't count as a first kiss.
It stopped...?
Why now?
We were almost there.
Meroko's doing, huh?
There's no way a Half-Shinigami can beat me.
Sorry...
I asked you something you didn't want to hear...
Don't worry about it.
Anyways... don't give up.
Didn't you decide that you were going to do your best until Eichi noticed you?
Yeah...
But... I won't make it there in time now...
I'll get you there in time.
Eh?
Meroko!
If you want to rat me out to the
Shinigami main office, go ahead!
I'm going to help her, no matter what happens!
You got that?!
Takuto...
Let's go.
Okay!
So pretty...
Even if they're just replicas...
...they're really beautiful, Takuto.
You can go the rest of the way by yourself, right?
Yeah.
All right!
Go for it.
Okay!
Thank you for waiting.
We will be announcing our decision now.
The image character for Mermaid Tear is...
...Wakamatsu Madoka-kun.
No way...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
That girl...
She didn't make it in time for the audition...
That means that I accomplished my mission, right?
No.
Not at all!
What do you mean?
Isn't everything okay now?
You don't have to go around
protecting that girl anymore.
No! Not yet!
I'm not going to just let her run away!
I won't let her give up on singing that easily!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The Voice of Song that Can't Reach Him
Look forward to it!