It's the day to gorge on chicken and cake!
You're acting strange...
Huh?
...the both of you.
You are wonderful, Miss Yoko.
Cat paws are amazing!
Mommy, that's a pretty Christmas tree!
It is!
It's finally the season, huh?
Yes, it is.
The season for my heating bill to be costly.
That wasn't what I meant...
It has gotten pretty cold.
I couldn't get out of bed this morning.
That's it!
Huh?
I can just wrap myself
in blankets when I am home.
Then, I can save on heating!
I see...
Miss Yoko!
Ah!
I will buy a heater for you!
Excuse me...
Oh, apologies.
Here you go.
Miss Yoko! Huh?
Anyway, I wanted to say that
the Christmas season is here!
Oh, I see.
Christmas is an important day!
It's the day to gorge on chicken and cake!
That's not what Christmas is for.
What?!
Then what else is it for, here in Japan?
I guess it has become a day
for chicken and cake here.
Hey, let's have a party!
A party!
My, what a wonderful idea.
All right!
I'll gorge on chicken and cake!
I told you, that is not what Christmas is for...
I'm excited for the party.
A Day to Gorge on Chicken and Cake
Miss Yoko!
Oh, Futaba.
Morning!
Is Hayama at school already?
Yup, she had some class rep duties.
She sounds busy.
Such a good student.
She's great at looking good
in front of teachers, too.
Oh yeah, about the Christmas party,
I'll be baking the cake, too.
My, how fantastic!
Miss Yoko will host the party,
Hayama will bring snacks, and...
Were you talking about
Christmas plans just now?
Yeah, the three of us are having a party.
I'll tell you something you might want to know.
Huh?
Christmas also happens to be...
...Teru's...
...birthday!
Wha...
What?!
What's up with you two?
N-Nothing!
Right, Miss Yoko?
Q-Quite right, Futaba!
Hayama's birthday is on Christmas.
That means...
A devil was born on a holy night?
Such contradictory occurrences!
It's fine if you're a fallen angel— I mean,
it doesn't matter when you were born!
Quite right!
All planned by God— I mean, the Devil?
What are you both talking about?
You're acting strange...
Huh?
...the both of you.
Oh, yeah!
Miss Yoko said she had
something to tell just me.
Eh?
I didn't say....
Come on!
Wait, F-Futaba!
I'm nervous, because I'm
thinking about it too much.
Indeed.
What should we do on Christmas?
I know!
Let's throw a birthday party for Hayama,
but pretend it's a Christmas party.
Hm?
What do you mean?
Let's surprise her by telling her it's a Christmas
party, but it'll actually be her birthday party.
My!
We will set up a trap for her!
It's not supposed to be a trap...
Anyway, let's keep it
a secret from Hayama.
Got it.
What are you doing, Sonobe?
Passing out Christmas cake flyers.
I told you before to stop
passing out flyers here.
That's too bad.
I thought that if our sales go up,
I might give you a raise...
What?!
N-No!
Go home, this instant!
Cake shops must be busy
at this time of year.
That's right.
We have cake orders and
have started making stollen.
I am helping too.
What?!
You're making cakes, too?
I help out measuring and
sprinkling things on top.
Yes, it takes longer with more people,
but it's helpful at this time of year.
Of course!
Who do you think I am?
You are wonderful, Miss Yoko!
Uh, what's with this conversation...?
So, does that mean you'll
be working on Christmas?
I give you permission
to take that day off!
What?
You have finally made friends.
For the sake of your friend's birthday party,
I am willing to work my fingers to the bone!
Sonobe...
Well, frankly, her usefulness level is more than a cat's paw.
Of course!
No, really, what's with this conversation?
Wait just a minute!
Cat paws are amazing!
H-Hayama!
Why—
Because obviously I'm curious about
what do you two want to talk.
Sorry, we have been hiding
something from you.
Sonobe!
Actually...
...I'm planning on making
bear and cat-shaped cakes.
What?!
Wow!
I kept it a secret, because
I wanted to surprise you.
Geez, you can keep as many of those
kinds of secrets as you want!
We're off the hook, somehow.
Sonobe got us out of this one.
I love Christmas.
The streets are buzzing with excitement.
And it's fun to pick out presents.
Which one is better?
Pink?
The red one's good, too.
It took an hour to decide,
and I ended up getting both.
I splurged and invested all
of this month's allowance.
Yeah, that's the plan for that day.
It is the first time I am throwing
a birthday party for a friend.
Anyway, let's have a great Christmas!
It is Hayama's birthday!
What?!
W-Wait!
Nishiyama?
What did you say?!
What was it about Hayama's birthday?!
Oh, you overheard?
Hayama's birthday is on Christmas.
What?!
We're having a surprise birthday
party for her, so keep it a secret.
I'll buy something for you.
Please do.
Yay! I've been wanting the premium card game!
You're kidding...
No way...
I'm excited.
Yeah!
Hm?
Nishiyama?
What's wrong, Nishiyama?
Christmas...
Huh?
Christmas is...
Oh, you do like Christmas.
This year—
I don't care...
What?!
There's nothing to celebrate, anyway.
Huh?
What's gotten into you?
You love Christmas.
Let's have a Christmas party.
It's okay...
Maybe I'll just eat curry on Christmas.
No way!
You're having a Christmas party with me!
Come on, get up!
Let's go buy a cake!
Closed for the day
Come back again tomorrow
I'm leaving now.
Oh, wait, Teru!
Bring this with you.
I stewed it overnight for you, Teru!
Uh...
Have fun at the party.
Hayama-chan
Hm, where should I put this?
Hurry, hurry!
Hayama's coming soon!
She's here!
Hello.
Hayama!
Happy Birthda—
Oh, you scared me!
I thought you were going to shoot me!
Shoot you?!
That aside, you had a very
amazing face just now!
Happy Birthday Teru-chan
Geez, my sister told you after all, huh?
I didn't want you to feel like you had to
celebrate with me, so I didn't say anything.
So that's why...
Well, I usually celebrate along with Christmas anyway,
so I'm used to my birthday being secondary.
That's so sad.
Thanks, though.
It's been years since I've
celebrated with friends.
Then, let's have some cake.
Thanks!
I helped, too!
I measured and sprinkled things on top.
Thanks, Miss Yoko!
Oh right, I have something, too...
From my sister...
I will eat it!
Woah!
Don't force yourself.
M-Miss Yoko?
You can do it!
Miss Yoko?
Amazing.
I-I feel like I could run
a whole marathon.
Miss Yoko!
It was no good, huh?
As expected.
Cheer up, now.
I can't stand that Christmas
was also Hayama's birthday.
Were you able to enjoy your Christmas?
Hayama?!
It was also the day I was
brought into this world!
Apologize!
Apologize to Christmas!
Oh my, what for?
The streets celebrate my advent.
Apologize!
Hayama...
Just, apologize!
Apologize to Christmas!
It's the first snow of the winter...
...but it's piled up so much.
Unusual weather.
But the snow is really exhilarating.
We cannot open unless we
clear this snow away, though.
That's right.
How cold!
My back aches, too.
How can you...
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
How can you make Miss Yoko shovel snow?!
Sonobe, you must have made it snow!
You're the first to accuse me of that.
It is still snowing.
It is.
I was just thinking, will the snow
stop people from coming?
Not necessarily.
Blizzards and typhoons exhilarate people and make them want to go out.
Is that what happens?
I'll have some!
See?
Futaba!
You are having cake on
a snowy day like today?
Yup, somehow, when I saw the snow, it gave me a craving for cake.
I see, one with white whipped cream?
Tiramisu, chocolate ganache,
and opera cake, please!
Has the snow around you melted?
Teru!
It's snowing a lot!
Let's go out!
No way.
What?!
We got a nice blanket of snow.
It'd be a waste not to go out!
Staying warm indoors
is the best on cold days.
Oh, come on.
Just for a little.
It's really cool!
Woah, hey!
Ta-dah!
I made a snow hut!
What?!
You made this by yourself?
I didn't know it's possible to make one!
Isn't it amazing?
It's warm inside.
Here, go inside.
I'll bring something to drink.
We can drink it inside.
It really is warm in here.
How strange.
Even though it's made out of cold snow...
Teru?!
1 New Message
Hayama Kou
Teru is~~~~~~
Received Mail
Hayama Kou
Big trouble!!
What?!
Apparently Hayama got caught
in an avalanche in the garden!
In the garden?!
I knew I should've stayed in.
Teru! Let's play!
Teru! Let's pla—
I told you...
I got an email saying that you're in trouble.
...use the doorbell.
The snow has not stopped.
Yeah, it might keep snowing
the rest of the year.
Miss Yoko, what are you
doing for New Year's?
I have nothing planned.
Will you be on your own?
Yes.
That won't do!
You cannot spend it alone!
I have nobody to spend it with.
Why don't the three of you spend it together?
Huh?
That is, of course, if Hayama
and Futaba agree to it.
I'm up for it.
Me, too.
It's lonely spending New Year's by yourself.
Thank you both!
If that's the case, you should
have a pajama party.
Paja— What?
Girls are beings that have pajama parties.
At a recent conference, it was shown that
more than an eighty percent have
a pajama party by graduation.
What conference was that?
You will remain in the other twenty percent.
What?
I am the daughter of the Nishikawa family!
I will execute a pajama party splendidly!
Does that sound good?
Yeah.
Well, yes.
Then, just like our Christmas party the
other day, we will cook and have cake—
Oh, pajama parties are a little different.
We just relax in bed talking
about things in our pajamas.
What?
That is a party?
Do you have enough blankets
for us at your place?
Well, er...
So, what are we supposed to do?
People usually talk about
people they like, right?
Then, let us begin.
I love rice!
Paired with fried cod roe,
I can eat it forever!
I love cats!
But I love dogs too!
I can't decide between them!
Pajama... party...
Oh, I forgot I made some snacks.
Oh, then I will make some tea.
Miss Yoko!
Are you oka—
This is totally wrong.
A real pajama party has
more squeals and giggles.
What are you trying to do, Sonobe?
I'm not trying to do anything.
I just want Miss Yoko to experience
normal high school girl things.
What's that camcorder for?
To document the memories.
Jeez.
Oh, my.
Well, I'm glad that she will not spend
her New Year's alone, at least.
Good morning, Hayama.
Wrong.
Happy New Year.
Ah.
We got worked up and
fell asleep without realizing.
Yes, we did.
Food's almost ready.
Mommy!
Mother!
There, there.
We will eat soooooon....
All right, let's pound some mochi!
Pound mochi?!
Er...
What's this?
Oh, it's a mochi pounding machine.
Off                                  Steam                                Pound
You said "pound mochi," so I thought
we'd be using a mortar and pestle.
As did I...
I asked for it for my birthday!
Wow!
Let's eat it now!
After a pajama party,
the high school girls eat mochi.
What a rare event.
Why do you have the
camcorder out again?!
Uh-oh.
Yummmmm!
It's so fresh...
Yes, it is delicious.
Yeah!
Soy bean flour, spicy, pan-fried with soy sauce,
edamame paste, fermented soy bean, or walnut!
How many should we each have?
What?
How many each?
Mochi is a must-have on New Year's!
Eat as much as you want!
What?
We're not competing in a big-eater contest!
H-Hey!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
An event
in February
must be...
An event in February must be...
Yes!
The Festival of Broken Needles!!
The
Festival
of Broken
Needles!!
The
Festival
of Broken
Needles!!
An event
where a
memorial
service is
held for
broken
needles.
An event where a memorial service
is held for broken needles.
Mainly in the
Kanto region
It's an
event
geared
towards
women.
It's an event geared towards women.
Valenti—
Valenti...
Vale
nti...
A
Or the
Or the Bean Throwing Festival!
Valenti...
Or the
A       A
A        A
A     A
Or the
Bean
Throwing
Or the
Bean
Throwing
Festival!
Next time:               A Day to
                  Gorge on Chocolate