So, you’re Negi, huh?
You’ve grown.
Take this staff. And take good care of yourself.
Wait! Hey, wait!
Wait, Father!
You’re my father, right!?
Wait!
Wait… Father…
Negi, you freaking retard!
You drifted off and slept in my bed again! Isn’t your futon bed on the floor!?
I-I’m so sorry, Asuna-san!
Huh?
Then, what’s this…?
My insides are gonna come out!
Seems like it!
"Looks like it’s camp!" by Motsu!
"Why?" by Shichimi.
Training camp, huh..?
Negi, over the break, you’ll accumulate more partners and study more magic. Whaddya think?
I want to know more about magic!
I second that!
As do I, desu~
Good idea. One must always start by learning the basics.
Don’tcha think that’s a good idea, Asuna?
What are you doin’, Ane-san?
And I’m done!
Whaddya think? Let’s give these Chupacabra-signed T-shirts as premiums to the members!
We should’ve gone with this instead! With this we’ll be reeling in sales!
Without a doubt?
Obviously with a doubt!
And anyway, that’s your handwriting, not a chupacabra’s!
It’s~ o~kay! If we don’t tell, they won’t know!
That signature… isn’t “chu,” but “cha,” you know.
Aniki, you okay?
Ah, sorry, I’m just a bit sleep deprived…
And so…
We finally made it! Training camp!
Yay!
You can see Library Island from here!
You sure can, huh?
I remember Kaede-nee telling us about this place!
She said that not a lot of people come here.
There’s also a hot spring inside the forest!
Hot springs~ Camp is the best!
Alright! First, we’ll set up our campgrounds!
This doesn’t very look like the completion pic, does it?
It’s alright! It’s fine as long as it can endure rain and wind!
It didn’t hold up.
Aniki, how about you give it a shot?
Yeah, good idea.
Negi, you can set one up?
Yes… for the time being…
Whoa, how cool!
The Boy Scouts originated in the UK, you know…
Could someone help?
Nodoka-jouchan should be fine.
Ah, yes, I’ll do my best.
Alrighty, then, shall we get started by preparing the meal?
The person in charge of the meals is… Asuna-san, right?
Preparations are A-OK and without any mistakes!
A fishing rod…?
Ingredients are best taken by Mother Nature!
Now, watch me get ‘em!
Natural improvement!?
Akashi Yuuna, a member of the Basketball Club. As of right now, she’s having a pretty deep moment.
What’s this?
Yuuna…
She’s clutching the basketball… what’s she up to?
Ah, look!
It’s Mana.
Why is Yuuna…?
Ah, maybe she…!
What, what?
Do you think that Yuuna likes…?
So pretty…
So wonderful…
I’m in love!
Are you serious!?
It’s perfect! A cross alms MG-42 modified machine gun…
Yuuna is locked on!
Takamichi!
While walking around the forest, I saw you, so…
Eh? Were you investigating on the darkness?
You could say that.
Oh yes, the school dean will be returning from England.
The school dean?
I hope that doing so will make our investigation progress a bit, but…
When a change occurs, we’ll be busy. You seem to be tired.
But, it would be a nice change of pace for you, don’t you think?
How’s it going? Catching anything?
Ah, Negi-sensei!
It’s useless; we can’t catch anything!
Did it not occur to Asuna… to buy some fish?
If we fish, we can avoid using money, and it’ll be all-you-can-eat!
But that’s if we can catch anything…
I’m gonna catch something! Just you watch, I’ll catch it with a bang!
Bang, bang, boom, boom, booooom, bang!
NOOOOOOO! MY THERMOS!!
Looks like we’re gonna starve for the night!
Ane-san, you need to read a bit further!
What’d you say?!
ANIMAL ABUSE!
Here’s your thermos, de gozaru.
Oh, thanks.
Eh?
I got something! I got something!
Ojou-sama, let me help!
For generations, it has been the Sakurazaki family’s mission to protect and help the Konoe family…
This time for sure I will wield this fishing rod to protect Konoka Ojousama’s honor and pride!
I shall aid my master for this important achievement!
Secchan, hurry or the fish’ll get away!
Forgive me, Ojou-sama!
Together on 3!
1… 2… 3!
That’s amazing!
I agree, desu!
As one would expect, Ojou-sama. For you to be able to catch such a large fish… you must be a fishing genius!
Are there even fish this big here?
Maybe she’s just a good fisher, de gozaru.
Exactly! This skill is Ojou-sama’s high class technique!
I caught something!
Me too, desu!
So am I!
Holy crap, what a catch!
Now, we don’t have to worry about our lunch!
Well, duh! There’s no mistake in my plans!
Negi-sensei’s at “camp”?
What hour? What minute? What second? Lastly, where did they go!?
Who knows… I just saw everyone leave earlier this morning.
Why wasn’t I informed of this, Makie-san!?
Well, you were out like a log, so…
My, what a heartless person you are! You were even given a very beautiful trainer, too!
Not like I asked for it…
But you’re wearing it anyway, mya!
Ah, it’s no use. I shall heal my utter despair with the newly acquired Negi-sensei goods.
What’s this?
This is the latest item by the Yukihiro Group Merchandising Club:
The Negi-sensei Gachapon, with a Negi-sensei figure inside every ball!
Ah.
Inside, there are five different kinds of Negi-sensei figures.
There is even a secret one, supposedly, mya.
If it’s just a sample, did you have to bother with putting them into Gachapons..?
My, you don’t get it, don’t you?
Turning the knob once every day,
and experiencing the excitement of which Negi-sensei will meet you for the day is the thing fun and enjoyable, isn’t it?
Well, then! Let’s see which Negi-sensei figure I will meet for the very first time.
Sorry. I like tight spaces and all.
Motsu and Makie – gazing deeply into each other's eyes.
Daddy!
What, again?
And Motsu thought “There's no way, but to accept this now, yeah?”
by Kaede
It’s so yummy!
Since we fished them up, they’re fresh!
It’s the best, desu!
We caught so much to the point where we don’t even have to worry about dinner!
See? I told you there was no mistake in my plans
But there seems to be a lot of seafood roaming this lake, huh?
Nah, more like…
Wah, it’s a good thing we found it before it started spreading!
You’re right.
Afternoon tea with a green wind.
Love and bravery’s Ambassador of friendship.
They call me…
The Black Rose Baron.
Black Rose Baron…
You seem to be doing fine, Negi Springfield-kun.
Hey you! Who on earth are you!?
Your style of speech is ungrateful and reckless.
Baron, I have something to ask of you!
Above is a fire. Below is a flood. What am I?
It’s a riddle!
I got it!
It’s a hot spring!
That’s when a flood is above and a fire is below, though.
That’s right…
A fire is above and a flood is below…?
I got it!
A forest fire at riverside with a barrier on top!
There’s no way that’s the answer!
I got…
The answer…
That’s when...
That’s right…
A fire is…
I got…
There’s no…
The answer…
That’s when
That’s right…
A fire is…
I got…
There’s no…
He’s getting away!
Wait!
Until we meet again, young one!
He disappeared.
Black Rose Baron…
Yes?
Um, Mana-san, I have something to-
No can do.
Caliber: 7.92 mm… 1200 rpm… That’s the famous machine gun that Hitler’s palatial saw and the Allies have feared…!
I wanna touch it just once! Just let me touch it!
Why don't you just give a Diemaco about it this time and listen to her?
2 points.
Sorry for being rude again.
Looks like you got rejected!
‘Twas an honorable defeat, though!
Looks like it’s our time to be in the spotlight!
Yep!
We, the members of the Mahora Academy Cheerleading Club...
will support and heal by cheering...
Yuuna-chan’s injured heart!
Huh?
L-
O-
V-
E!
Lovely,
Yuuna!
If today
is no good,
there's always
a tomorrow!
Yeah!
Uh, um…
Yuuna’s distraught.
Well, then, let’s start with the basics.
These are beginner’s wands.
They’re so cute, desu!
I know!
Please observe.
Practi-
Bigi-
Nal.
Ardescat!
Do this as if you’re absorbing the powers of the universe, and then concentrate that into one spot.
Alright, lemme give it a shot!
Practi-Bigu-Nunu. Anununukato!
Eh?
Ane-san, that’s a terrible mispronunciation.
I’ll give it a shot now!
Me too!
And me, too!
Practi-
Bigi-
Nal.
Ardescat!
Nothing’s coming out!
Desu!
It’s normal for nothing to come out on the first try.
I guess.
Konoka, can you write that spell on paper?
Hmm? Ah, okay!
Negi-sensei!
Do you think you could model for us one more time?
Ah, okay.
Here I go.
Practi-
Bigi-
Nal.
Ardescat!
Pretty bubbles!
This is what spawns from magic energy. This light and speed is the proof of his power and technique.
You’re so amazing, Negi-sensei!
I respect you, desu!
Negi!
Negi-sensei!
Oh? That brat and the others are on special training?
Yes.
It’s a mere pretension.
And, by the way, Chachamaru.
Yes, Master?
Why are these two here?
Please don’t mind us being here.
In a good way!
In a good way, mya!
Here.
I am honored to drink your well-prepared tea.
That was very well-prepared.
What is the tea’s name?
Nekamukashi.
Even if he’s a frog…!
And because I’m a frog…!
He overworked.
I’m sure if he takes a break, he’ll feel better.
Thank goodness. I was worried there.
Geez, stupid Negi doesn’t know his own limits…
He’s a handful.
Yes. He was busy with his own troubles lately… I guess he just couldn’t feel relaxed.
And we even invited him to the camp.
We made him tag along with us for magic training,
and ended up pushing him too hard.
Negi-sensei… I’m sorry…
Nekane… oneechan?
Just rest up for now.
Okay.
Drink this.
Thanks, Oneechan…
Aniki!
Kaede-san?
You should feel better with that medicine, de gozaru.
Kaede Ane-san, why are you here?
I use this area for ninja training, de gozaru.
Ninja?
Yes.
I was watching over you and the others the whole time.
Are you saying that now you know about…?
I’ve known that Negi-bouzu is a mage for quite a while now, de gozaru.
I even know that if you’re to be exposed, you’ll have your certification revoked, as well as turn into an animal.
Even up to your battle with Evangeline-dono and how you’re making provisional contracts with the class by kissing them.
I know it all.
I also know about how you want to be a mage like your father, the Thousand Master.
Was he that great of a father, de gozaru?
Kaede-chan?
I… don’t remember much of my father, to tell you the truth.
He knew a thousand spells, and was a strong mage. Thousand Master…
Do you want to meet him, de gozaru?
Yeah. I do.
I’m sure if you try hard enough, you’ll get to meet him, de gozaru.
Kaede-san…
I may have weak abilities, but I shall assist you, de gozaru.
But you know, the more servants you have, the better, de gozaru.
Pactio!
Looks like he made another partner, huh?
Welcome back, Dean.
England’s pretty far, isn’t it?
I’m kind of tired.
Well?
The Star Crystal is indeed currently in Japan.
Even the gathered elders’ magic powers could not obtain more detailed data.
So, what about the criminal?
I see.
Do you think that has any relation to the Star Crystal?
Hmm, I see. I’ll look into it.
If you would.
Mornin’, Negi-kun!
I’m so sorry! I dozed off and ended up falling asleep on Asuna’s-!
Don’t worry about that! Just come over here for a sec!
IT’S ON FIRE! I NEED WATER! WATER!
She intended on making you breakfast.
Water!
Even though she can’t…
Asuna-san…
Negi-sensei!
Good morning, desu!
We’ve brought something good for you!
Banana flavored cod liver oil candy, desu!
It’ll pick you right back up, de gozaru!
Negi-sensei, I brought you some Super Nasty Vegetable Juice!
Ooh, you’ll cheer up from that, too, de gozaru!
Negi-sensei, I brought you a Red Viper Drink!
Well, I dunno if that’ll bring Negi-bouzu back up again, de gozaru…
Aren’t you glad? You’ve got quite a bit of things to make you better!
You guys…
EVERYONE, DUCK AND COVER!
Asuna, what did you do?
This!
Mornin’ to you all!
Morning…
Kaede has been included as a partner while Negi is standing against the mystery with the support and tenderness of his partners.
Watch carefully, and wait till next time, Amoré!
We did it!
‘Tis good manners to use the fork that’s to the very right.
Next Time: “You hid Negi-sensei from me and took him where!? I will never allow such a thing!”
By Ayaka.
I’ve done it! It’s complete!
It’s finally done!
It’s the ultimate equipment! Improved from Super Power Hand, it boosts the user’s power fighting strength higher than ever!
I call it: “Super Power Hand 2”!
You shall fight with Kuu Laozi, aru!
Ready? GO!
Two meat buns!
She’s good…
The fight will continue, will it!?