I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors.
Brought forth to fight in this
Holy Grail War as Rider!
What are you thinking, you moron?
Of course, I am your enemy
in the battle for the Holy Grail.
But first, I would ask of you both...
Would you
consider surrendering yourselves
and acquiescing the Grail to me?
Do so, and I shall
welcome you as allies!
Follow me, and you shall know the thrills
of world domination!
I'm afraid I must decline.
I made a pact to deliver the Grail
to none other than my new lord,
who summoned here.
And you are not he, Rider!
You saw fit to interrupt
Lancer and my duel,
merely to spout that gibberish?
To a knight, this is a grave insult!
I can make it worth your while.
Enough!
Moreover,
I am a monarch, as well...
The King of Britain.
No matter how exalted you may be,
I could never lower myself
to another's subject!
The King of Britain, you say?
Incredible!
To think that the King of Knights was a little girl!
Would you care to taste this little girl's steel,
King of Conquerors?
It appears negotiations have broken down.
Damn, what a shame.
Rider!
Did that oaf truly rule the world once?
Listen, you...
I see.  It was you, of all people.
I wondered who could possibly
have been mad enough to
steal my summoning relic.
But never did I expect you to have the guts
to enter the Holy Grail War yourself.
Waver Velvet.
But this is quite convenient.
It's the perfect chance
to impart a very special lesson unto you.
You will learn what it means for two mages
to fight to the death.
You will be thoroughly familiar
with all the fear and pain that it entails.
You should feel honored.
You there, mage!
It sounds as though
you were intended to be my master
instead of this boy!
Let me say, the mere idea makes me ill!
Only the man with the courage
to stand beside me on the battlefield
is fit to be my Master!
A coward, too afraid to show his face,
is not fit for the role!
And the rest of you!
I know you are hiding in the darkness,
spying on us.
What do you mean, Rider?
Saber and Lancer.
Your battle was fought fairly and with honor.
It was splendid!
I cannot imagine myself to be
the only Heroic Spirit
drawn by the ringing of
your clashing weapons.
Heroes summoned by the Grail,
let us gather!
And to those too paralyzed by fear
to show your faces,
know that Iskandar, King of Conquerors,
holds you in utter contempt!
This...
Yes.
This is bad.
Agreed.
That's...
The Servant who killed Assassin!
Not one, but two insolent dogs
disregard my majesty,
to purport themselves as kings?
That's an odd thing to quibble about.
I am Iskandar,
known throughout the world
as King of Conquerors.
Foolishness.
I am the only true king to stride this Earth.
All others are but mongrels and
peasants before me.
If you make such claims,
then state your name!
Surely a fellow king would not hesitate
to name himself to his enemies.
You dare issue demands to me, cur?
To your king?
Blessed to personally basking in my glory,
you still cannot even recognize me.
You are uncivilized animals,
unworthy of your lives!
Ah, that's the move he used to slay Assassin.
That's his Noble Phantasm.
Kill.
Berserker?
Well, King of Conquerors,
why not try recruiting him?
I would try,
but he doesn't seem the type
to sit down and negotiate.
Okay, boy.  How does he measure up as a Servant?
I don't know.  I can't tell at all.
What?
What kind of excuse for a Master are you?
Can't you even see his weaknesses,
strengths, basic things like that?
No, I can't.
That black creature is definitely a Servant,
but I can't read any of its stats!
It seems we have another
powerful opponent to confront.
That Heroic Spirit is under an enchantment
that obscures his identity and abilities.
But that isn't all.
Faced with four enemies at once,
we cannot afford the slightest mistake.
Why did he materialize now?
If his Master were rational,
I cannot imagine he would insert his Servant
directly in the middle of this chaos.
Maiya, keep Assassin in your sights.
I'll search for Berserker's Master.
Who gave you permission
to observe me, you rabid dog?
See to it that your death
amuses me, mongrel.
Is that really Berserker?
That's quite a technique for one who is
beyond rational thought.
Oh, you couldn't tell?
That black thing snatched
the sword out of the air,
then used it to knock aside the spear.
You presume to soil my treasures
with your filthy hands?
Do you desire death that badly, dog?!
Are you kidding me?
How long can your petty thievery
sustain your life?
Show me!
Ignorant fool...
You should regard me as a god.
I shall not permit you to exist
upon the same world I inhabit!
Your impudence has earned you death!
You, mongrel...
I'll destroy every last bit of your corpse!
Gilgamesh is serious.
He's about to unleash his Gate of Babylon even further.
Repeatedly using his strongest Noble Phantasm
before so many enemies...
How rash.
My lord, what will you do?
I must sacrifice a Command Spell.
King of Heroes,
quell your anger and withdraw.
You'd have the gall
to order a king's retreat?
A bold move, Tokiomi.
You've been spared this time, mad dog.
As for the rest of you mutts...
By our next encounter, I expect you rabble
to have thinned your herd.
Only true heroes are worthy
of gazing upon me.
Looks like Archer's Master
doesn't have Archer's own fortitude.
Irisviel, get back!
What?
So that's it.
Anything that black monster wields
becomes his Noble Phantasm.
Saber!
Talk to me, Maiya.
Can you locate Berserker's Master
from your position?
Negative.
This is bad.
Damn it!
What are you?
I think that's quite enough of
your demented ravings,
Berserker.
I have already claimed
this duel with Saber.
Attack her further, and you will
contend with me, as well.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is the perfect opportunity
to eliminate Saber.
Saber
will fall by my spear, upon my honor
as Diarmuid Ua Duibhne!
Allow me to slay this rabid dog first!
What say you, my Master?
I command you, by this Command Spell...
Master!
You will help Berserker,
and kill Saber.
Lancer?
Saber, I'm sorry.
Irisviel.
I shall hold them off.
While I draw their attention,
get yourself to safety.
Get as far as you can.
Irisviel, go!
It's all right, Saber.
Believe in your Master.
Is Kiritsugu here, as well?
Kiritsugu, I know you'll think
of a solution to this.
We must kill Lancer's Master.
That's the only way to get this
situation under control.
Maiya,
on my signal, shoot Assassin.
I'll need suppressive fire.
Understood.
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
You won't be easily felled, will you?
Well, it appears our friend in black has
decided to withdraw for the night.
Master of Lancer...
I know not where you hide,
but cease your pathetic meddling
in the affairs of true knights!
Call off Lancer.
Should you insist on further
sullying his name,
I shall side with Saber.
And together,
we'll massacre your Servant.
What say you?
Fall back, Lancer.
Tonight's battle is over.
You have my gratitude,
King of Conquerors.
You needn't mention it.
I simply enjoy seeing the
flowers of war in bloom.
What was your purpose in coming here,
King of Conquerors?
I cannot say I planned it out thoroughly, to be honest.
Saber, before you do anything else,
settle your score with Lancer.
I shall await the victor, be it you or Lancer.
Goodbye for now, King of Knights!
I hope our next meeting will prove
even more exciting than our first!
Hey, boy, any grand declarations
for our foes?
He really needs to get himself together.
Farewell!
Saber, your left arm!
Yes, it was a costly mistake.
As Rider says,
I must finish my fight with Lancer,
and lift his spear's curse.
Otherwise, I'll be at a disadvantage
against the other Servants.
Thank you, Saber.
It's thanks to you that
we survived this night.
I simply focused on the enemies
in front of me.
I relied on you to protect my back.
Saber...
The true war lies ahead, Irisviel.
Tonight was simply a harbinger of
the many battles that await.
You're right.
All of them are terribly powerful.
And not one could be considered
a conventional opponent.
So this is the Holy Grail War...
They all turned tail and ran at the sight
of my Berserker.
I wiped mud on that pompous ass's face!
Tokiomi, I wish I could've seen
the look on your face.
Damn you, Berserker...
You just had to flip out with Saber.
At this rate, my body won't be able
to handle the strain...
But if I'm able to control him, I can win.
Wait for me, Sakura...
Pardon me, Kirei-sama.
Yes?
I discovered something outside the church
that may interest you.
A familiar?
Yes.  It was outside the barrier,
but it had clearly been sent
to observe the church.
Incredible!  You're blowing my mind!
Sir Bluebeard, that was all real, right?
No special effects or tricks or anything!
Holy crap!
So what about that Holy Grail War?
You wanna sink your teeth
into that, too, right?
Sir Bluebeard?
At last...
At last...  Uh, what?
Look!  She is the answer!
That gallant face, that dashing figure...
She is, without a doubt, my one true soul mate!
You know her?
Of course!
She who was forsaken by God Himself,
who fell into ruin and died in shame...
Here and now, she is reborn anew!
This... This is a miracle.
What can I say, but that my
deepest wish has been granted?
Oh, my maiden...
My virgin angel...
Soon, we shall be together.
Episode 5
A Wicked Beast's Roar
I will bring you Saber's head.
Next time, I won't hold back!
Are you sure you aren't mistaken?
You would test the magic
of Kayneth El-Melloi?
Are you preaching at me?
I have come for you, my holy virgin.
Next Time:
A Night of Schemes