Will you become my friend?
Y-Your friend?
You don't want to?
See you.
Yes.
Welcome back, Chihiro.
Did you have fun?
Yes, it was very enjoyable.
Don't push yourself.
And...
And don't get too involved. Also, don't let others get too involved either.
Himura-san, is it wrong for me to tell another person about me?
I won't object if it's something that Chihiro has decided.
In my personal opinion however,  I do not support it.
Right.
If I do something wrong, I can't even regret it.
Now then. Onii-chan, it's morning.
Wake up, Onii-chan.
You'll be late if you don't wake up.
Alright, since I already did this much...
whatever happens now is Onii-chan's responsibility.
I told you to wake up!
Oww...
Isn't your method of waking up a person getting worse?
It's because your habit of oversleeping is getting worse.
I told you not to sleep on the desk because it isn't good for your body, didn't I?
I have no choice. The deadline is close so it's an emergency.
You say that every month.
Work is good, but Onii-chan's primary job is a student.
Being a manga artist is a primary job too.
Put away the excuse and quickly wash your face.
Or else everyone will find out about your job.
Onii-chan, if you don't go to school your attendance record will be in trouble.
You're not smart.
Your grades are bad as well.
You have no tenacity.
If you also lack attendance,
then it would be the same as saying, "Let me retake my second year."
Then I might be in the same class as Kei next year.
I'm telling you to go to school properly so that won't happen!
I won't tell you to stop your publications.
Just go to school.
Well, I'll think about it.
Yeah, think about it.
Are you reading my manga these days?
Of course I'm reading it.
You don't give your thoughts on it anymore.
But it's embarrassing to tell something like my thoughts now.
And also, you get letters from readers even if I don't say anything, right?
Shindou Nagi-sensei.
Don't call me by that name outside.
Yes, Onii-chan!
You can't call me "Onii-chan" either!
You can't fall asleep.
Listen to what the teacher says properly.
And listen attentively when you're called on.
What are you, my guardian?
See ya, Hirono-sempai.
Aren't you unusually early, Hirono...
Kyousuke.
And also coming to school along with your girlfriend.
As a man did you grow a bit?
She's not my girlfriend, and it is none of your business.
Listen carefully, Hirono. Even if a girl isn't your type, it's important to become friendly with her.
There might be a girl's friend that is your type.
Also, around the girl's friend might be someone that is more appealing.
Is your reason for meeting girls without discretion because of that strategy?
No, I just have a broader range.
Would there be any reliability in the words spoken by such a person?
So, are you going to classes today?
Since I'm here, I might as well get an attendance stamp.
Is that it?
I have...
always...
had the feeling of emptiness as if I'm lacking something.
I get the feeling that there's a color missing from the world that I look at.
But I don't know what color is missing.
So even if I want to find the answer, I can't find it.
The hastening heart just eats itself.
You're being very diligent.
Since I'm an idiot, I can only look forward.
You're strong.
That's not true.
I think that there is a responsibility to a human who has achieved their dream.
And that... is about who?
Myself during the days when I dreamed.
Was I sleeping?
Are you awake, Hirono-kun?
You?
Good morning. It is Miyamura Miyako.
You were a student of Otowa?
The school uniform look is pretty good, isn't it?
You were completely out.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep in places like this.
So, why are you here?
Isn't it obvious?
It's to see Hirono-kun of course.
If this car hadn't passed by, it would have been a good clip.
Hey Kyousuke.
Hmm?
The clips that you took are good, but...
they're a bit hard to connect.
Huh?
The clips are too precise so the flow between them stops.
I put my soul into every single clip.
Put your life on the line and do the editing.
Things like that cannot be accepted.
To win at the film festival,
you must aim more towards the general public.
Still, there are a lot of fans who view our work because of Kyousuke.
President?
That's the point. So wouldn't it be right to edit while extolling Kyousuke's clips?
That's true, but...
Kyousuke?
Going to the bathroom.
That's not it though.
I think it'll be the time soon.
That girl is Hirono's...
It's about time for Renji-kun to arrive. Today I'll tell him the truth.
Chihiro...
Can I go to Onii-chan's house after club activities?
Oh yeah, that deadline is close...
But I was really surprised...
that Hirono-kun and I were in the same school.
I don't really come to school, so...
Same here.
I also ditch like there's no tomorrow.
If so, it's obvious that we didn't notice each other.
When I found Hirono-kun...
I wondered if I should talk to you or not.
Why?
There are things like gathering my emotions.
I'm a girl, so...
I don't get it.
It's a reunion with the person that you spent Christmas night together with.
Don't you want to go with a romantic atmosphere?
We just stayed at family restaurants and karaoked until morning, didn't we?
Plus, I payed for everything.
But say, Hirono-kun...
I'm sorry. To tell you the truth, I saw...
that notebook.
Is it that Hirono-kun has a dream?
A dream?
Don't be shy. It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
It's good to have dreams.
Dreams or not, I'm a manga artist.
Self-proclaimed? Delusional?
Actively.
Even though I don't look like it, I'm a pro that publishes in magazines.
Seriously?
Yep, seriously.
What kind of manga do you draw?
To put it bluntly, girl manga.
Actually, if you do look at it, Hirono-kun has a girlish face.
That's the only thing you're surprised about?
That's impressive.
In another words, Hirono-kun already has a career?
Well, that's right.
You are independent at that age, right?
You're living the dream!
Well, I'm not up to there yet...
Amazing! You're at the prime of your life!
Be quiet!
If you have the leisure of praising others, try to strive so you can be praised yourself.
Arrogant.
Read my manga.
There are a lot more arrogant things in there.
Seriously?
Yep, seriously.
From yesterday's me...
to today's me...
Huh?
I wonder if Chihiro isn't here yet?
Hello.
Ah, hello. You took your time today.
By the time I noticed when I finished reading a book after lunch...
What were you reading?
That is, how should I put it...
It's an uninteresting book.
So you were immersed in an uninteresting book?
Well, not immersed...
Something that you can't even tell your friend?
Well, that is...
Asou-san is a friend, but...
But...?
You're mean.
I understand. This should be okay to tell.
But please keep it a secret.
By all means, please.
Absolutely. I won't tell anyone.
I-I am...
in truth, not reading a novel, but...
Not reading, but...?
Maybe it's that you're writing one?
You're really mean.
Then, can you show it to me?
Absolutely not.
I see.
But it's amazing, a novel that you're writing...
That's a very displeasing reaction.
It's not that, it's just that...
It's just that it is a slightly displeasing reaction?
No, it's that I was thinking about if I should write my own novel.
Asou-san too?
It's just a thought.
There was a career survey at school.
I thought maybe being a writer is okay.
Is that so?
I think it will be good, really.
Really?
Yes.
I'm curious about what kind of content the story that Asou-san writes will have.
I'm also curious about the story that Chihiro wrote-
Please don't be curious about that.
O-Okay.
From now on, please do not mention it at all.
Even in your grave or in hell, please keep silent.
So does that mean I'm going to hell?
But things like careers are difficult, right?
Are they?
It isn't difficult?
I think that doing what you like is the most important thing, but...
Looks like it. I also heard the same thing.
From who?
An adult.
What does Chihiro want to become?
I...
have a dream.
A dream?
It's not that I want to be a novelist, but I want to write just stories.
Just anything, I want myself of right now to make something.
I see.
I believe that Chihiro can do it.
Really?
Yeah.
Although it isn't so reliable even if I guarantee that.
That isn't so.
Thank you very much.
Even just hearing that makes me happy.
I need to go to school again starting tomorrow.
I don't want to go.
You don't want to go?
It's not that I don't like school...
School...
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
It's fun to hear about school...
especially since I can't go.
Really?
My twin sister tells me often about school.
When she happily does, it makes me happy just to listen.
Your twin?
Yes, her personality is opposite of mine.
If Onee-chan loiters without doing anything, she would surely die.
Her name is Shindou Kei and is a first-year student of Otowa.
But if she's a junior-high student then there won't be a chance to meet her.
She's a high school student.
She is Chihiro's twin right?
That's right.
Well... Then Chihiro also?
If I were attending school, I would be a first-year student in high school.
I see.
Oh man, I thought she was younger until now.
Um, is it okay if I call you Shindou-san from now on?
Chihiro is fine.
Everyone calls me that anyway.
Then, can you just call me Renji?
Can't it be Asou-san?
That's a bit formal, so...
Then will it be fine as Renji-san?
It sounds a bit weird with "-san," so use "-kun".
But that would be embarrassing on this side.
Well, you know, we're friends, right?
I understand. Then from now on I'll say Renji-kun.
Renji-kun.
It's a weird sensation.
It seems like it.
I go this way, so...
I see.
Well then...
Yes.
Well, good bye.
Renji-kun...!
What is it?
I-I...
Chihiro?
No, it's nothing.
Good bye.
Chihiro?
Yes?
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow...?
let's play again.
I'll go to the station right after school, so...
Tomorrow... Is that okay?
I think it would be okay.
Yes! Tomorrow again at the station.
It was you?
The one that was meeting with her...
Himura-san?
If you want to stay beside Chihiro then be prepared.
Asou-san... Renji-kun said, "Let's play again tomorrow".
Not a courtesy of, "See you next time."
But this time a real promise.
See you again tomorrow.
Onee-chan.
I can't imagine tomorrow nor happiness.
I stay here even though tomorrow comes.
If you want to stay beside Chihiro then be prepared.
"Be prepared" isn't something said under normal circumstances, is it?
Hey.
Is that Renji-kun?
Yep. It is.
Good afternoon.
What should we do today?
Do you want to visit the shops somewhere?
If it is somewhere with few people.
Somewhere outside I should say; I don't like places with lots of people.
It's very beautiful.
It is. It looks as if it was burning.
Asou Renji-san.
Am I your friend?
To be asked that again, I do wonder...
I may not even be especially conscious of it.
Then to Asou-san, what am I?
At first a subject of interest.
I guess I would say that I couldn't leave you alone.
Yeah, it's not that I was worried, but just that I always wanted to meet with you.
Is it a feeling like me being a little sister?
I think it was a feeling like that.
I also think that if I had a Onii-san, it would be someone like Asou-san.
Really?
Yes.
And so, that...
I...
Chihiro...
Yes?
Deep breaths...
Note: It is said that if you write the symbol of the thing that you're afraid of and swallow it, it is supposed to alleviate your fears.
They say that swallowing the symbol that you write on your palm is said to help also.
Yes.
I'm sorry, I tested Asou-san for a bit.
It was to see whether or not you are a person that it's okay to tell this to.
But I understood...
that from then until now and even now, Asou-san hasn't changed, right?
Um, it's not that you're another person, right?
Yes?
No, it's just that you said you had a twin sister.
It isn't something like Onee-san disguised herself and came in place of you, right?
That's true. I guess it isn't odd even if I'm asked if I'm another person.
Asou-san...
I have anterograde amnesia.
Anterograde... amnesia?
Yes. I can only retain memories for thirteen hours.
If you look at it that way, the me from yesterday and the me from today is a different person.
Even as today passes, I cannot be me of tomorrow.
I'll forever be this way.
Forever.
Even from now.
My feelings intertwine with his feelings.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Paradox
Do you have a feeling that you don't want to forget?