Thank you very much!
Thanks to you, Aisaka, we've become happy.
Yes, we have.
Did you know them?
Palm-Top Tiger of Happiness
Not in the slightest
Even if they did greet me so openly in the morning...
Taiga!
What's with these guys?
Ah, Aisaka
What's up with you guys?!
Why did you have to avoid us, Taiga?
I'm not asking to care for us as thanks but...
A bit more like this... grab the leg, and rub the heels or something...
Eww.. That's disgusting. Don't come near me. all of you!
What's up with all of this?
There is this strange jinx
But I don't know what to think it as well
How about if we do it like this
What are you doing, you stupid chihuahua?!
Ami's respectability is
Scentless
See. I knew that rumor was a fake
All I'm getting is unhappiness
Hey, don't rub it on my skirt!
But something got stuck on my finger
What should I do with this contamination?
You put that in there yourself!
What rumor?
The other day during the festival
The people who came to watch our Pro Wrestling show
Who were lariated by Taiga outside of the stage
Who were head-butted
Whoever were touched by Taiga
Seem to have found happiness one by one
Happiness?
Yes yes
Being confessed of love by others
Receiving piles of inheritances from some unknown uncle
Being looked after to the extent of being Uha-uha happy
No matter what you wish, it will be granted
And all of those happiness is all thanks to the legend of the Palm-top Tiger of Happiness
I see
Is that it?
What's with that? Being worked up all by yourselves
It's going to fine, Taiga
Just a little bi...
I wouldn't get too familiar
No matter how many times you try, I won't let you touch me
Good morning, classmates!
What's up with all of you, gathering around here?
Minorin!!!
Only Minorin can touch me
Minorin!
How's this? There there. How about this?
Whoever touches Taiga will receive happiness, eh?
On that day
During the cultural festival, Taiga was
Very far from
What you call happiness
And if Taiga were to make someone happy on that day
That is...
What is it? Hurry up with lunch
Oh yeah
What a big irony
How ironic for Takasu
Even though he's the closest to Aisaka
Aisaka was dancing so happily back there
Touching her would make you happy but he's been with her all this time
Who would've thought she'd be stolen completely by Maruo
What is with this strange rumor...
How sad for you
Yes, I was completely swept off my feet by Kitamura
And you're okay with that rumor?!
Well, it is complicated as an ex of a dog but
I am only human
But I was dumped by you, you see
And now I am with Kitamura
I'm sorry for worrying
Ah thank you
Well, if we don't take our seats
The 'single', with her bra lowered of 'single' pain won't be able to do her 'single' homeroom
Si... 'single' pain...
Wow... Takasu's lunch today also looks good
Is that a spring roll?
Ah yeah
I tried to roll the leftover tuna salad with rice paper
Really? That's great
Takasu's great and all, but isn't rice great too?
They're coming after you, Taiga
Geez, I just can't eat in peace
You don't sound convincing
Can I eat with you guys?
Aisaka, don't let the rumors from the festival get to you.
Which one?
Ah, no never mind
On that note, the festival was a complete success
True true
If I were to sum up the class exhibition, Mister Lucky, and Miss Con into one word
It was Great!
Yeah, that's true. All thanks to Aisaka
Ah that's not true
Taiga?
Hey, drink this
I don't want
Huh? But...
If it's not juice, I don't want it
Orange
You're saying that at this time?
Geez, she's always like this all the time
Seems she has returned to her old self
That's a good thing, right?
Yes
I understand
But I have a test coming soon
Okay
In the mean time, just a bit more
I understand
I'll call you again
Talk to you later then
What's up with that call?
What's this? Are you interested in my secret?
Not really, no
Let's see... Orange... orange...
Orange juice with your meal? What a childish taste
It's not for me. It's for Taiga
She said she didn't like Coffee Milk
Wha'?!
Wh... what did...
See you later
What will I do with this?
Flying...
Kick!!!
You're late
Because of you, I had to drink tap water
How will you make up for this?!
Hell if I know. You just suddenly...
Hey, you okay?
I... I'm sorry
I... It wasn't on purpose
I wanted to ask a favor from Aisaka
I thought I could go closer if I picked up the juice
I thought it was you
You've been following me since this morning
Since this morning?
Ah, is it because you will be happy if you were able to touch...
Y... yes
I like this girl, you see
And I'd like to go well with her...
Ah, yes, go.
Go to the afterlife
Geez
To be happy is to fight for survival
C'mon, let's go
Lunch break is over soon
Eh? Where to?
They said they'll put up pictures from the festival
And lunch?
I've finished it already. C'mon
But I haven't
Just start walking
Come to think of it, you touch me all the time
Huh? Don't make it sound so dirty
That's right
Being touched by Taiga this much
I should be happier than anyone else
Instead she's the one happy while she just gives me trouble
One hundred thirteen
Don't get it wrong
Oh just shut up
But at least
That's one great picture
That... and that... and that... and that... and that...
Minorin
Listen up, Taiga
It's time to check on the latest scoop on Ami
The password is:
kissiwannaknow
Being surprised by something so dirty
Oh well, if it's something done with me...
Geez, with your powers of restraint
There are times when I go beyond being shocked and just want to kill you
That's a very politician way of doing things
If you want to know about the stupid chihuahua that badly
Then I will tell you this much
She has six fathers
I saw them!
No way
If I stay too long with you, I'll just get hurt with your horniness
Minorin, I'll just look way over here
Damn that Taiga
Investigate with me, Takasu!
The duel
Of fate!!!
Out of the nineteen pictures, I now summon nine pictures
And now, I open a divas card!
And now the magic starts there
The ninety-three I just found
Send-a-ten-yen-postage-of-a-picture-with-my-softball-mates open!
End of my turn!
Excuse me...
Now it's your turn, Takasu
What? Turn?
Oh don't pretend like you don't know
I'm asking you to show me the pictures you're buying
Oh, is that so?
It's only natural for classmates to comment on each other's picks
There's no way for me to get that
C'mon, show me show me
Oh eighty-five!
Eight-five... eighty-five... eighty... five...
Ah... well this is...
Maybe, I should buy this picture too
As memory
Uh, yeah. Let's buy it
Oh what's with you?
You only picked pictures of Sudou of Class C
Shut up. Don't look
To buy pictures of a girl you like is so cheesy of you
Well can you show me yours?
To be worked up with just a picture
Everyone is so childish
Ami
As for me, it's my job to have my picture taken
And the pictures are sold all over Japan
It doesn't matter to me whoever is holding on to my pictures
And whatever I think of that picture is...
Is just a mere-picture
Yeah, a mere-picture
You're right
A mere-picture
Ah that's Master Ami for you.
So calm and mature
What shall we do on the way home?
Can we pass by the train station today?
Sure. What's there?
A single's pain
A single's love
A single's fortune
Ah, the lines are disappearing
Teacher
Do you have anything to say to this single's back, Kawashima?
I've been thinking about it since this morning
That blouse you're wearing came out in this year's winter collection, isn't it?
You noticed?
Of course, I do
You really have an eye for the high brand, don't you?
It makes you look quite the lady
It's wonderful
I think those who understand would also realize
Your mature charm, Miss Yuri
Oh, Kawashima. You're such a good good girl
I guess it's true. I'm mature
What?
Oh it's nothing
Well, shall we pass by the grocery on the way home?
Ah, let's see. Today I feel like...
Meat... A big fatty one
You always say meat
So what? I eat proper meals, don't I?
Balance. You should think about balance.
And you, just because you bought a picture with you and Minori holding hands
Aren't you letting your imagination run free?
Were you looking?
I just thought you'd definitely buy it
I thought right
How about you? You bought that
That's true
But it's not like I had to
Because I'm her girlfriend
Oh, you're from earlier
I'm s... sorry... I...
It's you again
And... and this time, you're looking down my sk...
S... sk... ski...skirt
No, I'm not!!!
Wait up!!!
Looks like she's back completely just like before the festival
Even though something like that happened
No
Because it happened
President
The calculations for the festival's accounting is finished
Let's see
To... Tomiya is being attacked!!!
What was that?
Oh that
It's probably the legend of the palm-top tiger of happiness
When you touch Taiga Aisaka, you will be granted any wish
It's just a rumor though
And you don't see it that way
Whether it's a rumor or a lie
I want to try to depend on something that has no proof
But I just don't understand that
How unexpected
That you would say something like that
Is that so?
Um, President...
Kitamura
We have to talk
In the end, I wasn't able to touch Taiga
Don't you just envy those who did
Even Taiga herself is happy with Maruo
She just danced with, you know
It's not like she likes him
What are you being so worked up on?
Like I said, it's just ridiculous to believe in a stupd jinx like that
That's easy for you to say
If it's a wish for love, it looks like yours will always be granted
That's right
You're so mature and have a good figure
There's no guy that can resist being cornered by Ami
We're talking about that again...
Ami?
One for one thousand eight hundred? What a deal.
Kawashima?
It's okay to be so lost in it but...
Takasu, you're being marked by every other housewives, you know
Can't you just buy from a meat shop or something?
Yeah, but
Pork costs four times as this, right?
If you're worried about the price, why don't you just touch Aisaka?
You might get loads of inheritance from an unknown uncle
Certainly
Hey, if you touch Taiga, you get happiness, right?
It's not likely to be real though
But what if it were to be true
What should Taiga do so that she herself can be happy?
She's happy enough already
Isn't this a matter of what she needs?
If you just feed her well enough, she won't have any problems with it
You're right. Alright! I'll get the pork then
Oh I don't need a plastic bag
Takasu, you're stocking up on points, aren't you?
Such a housewife
Shut up
Oh yeah
Here, take this
I'm giving it to you
We're only three at home and one is okay with two packs
Wa... to receive something like that
I don't even cook
It's fine. I'm telling you to eat some pork
You didn't look so good today
You might lacking from vitamin B2
Huh?
You didn't look so energetic since this morning
Even when you were by the vending machines
Wh... What're you talking about?
You're just like a worried aunt
Don't call me that
You've been probably just been eating junk food
You're really so childish
You should cook that with ginger. Ginger should be able to warm your body
See ya
Childish... huh
Really, that mongrel
So impudent to just leave his master to go home alone
Huh?
K... Kita... Kitamu...
Aisaka
W... what are you doin'
Um... doing?
I am doing... doing nothing
The palm-top tiger of happiness
I'm sorry. What was I doing?
Did something happen?
Did you drop your wallet or something?
Did that damned shit-of-a-council president bullied you or something?
No, that's not it
It's nothing
Um
You... you can touch me
I can't really say but
C'mon. Touch me anyway you like
Touch me a lot. Touch me like you've never touched before
Wh... what am I saying?
Aisaka
I'm sorry. I'm fine
Thank you
Tomiya, are you really okay?
Ah, yeah. I'm fine
Really? Really really?
Yeah, Sakura. I'm really fine now
Ah, welcome home
Geez, why did you go home without me?
Wait a minute, Ryuuji. This is a feast
What day is today?
Ah, let's see... ah...
That's right. I skipped lunch today so I'm really hungry
That smells good
Was this in your repertoire?
Yeah, it's pork prepared in western style
But the focus is to put a new miso in the sauce
I can't lose to the restaurant I went with your dad
And after that is to make a gratin...
Are you stupid?
I am really fine with it
Never mind. Just get back to work
Alright alright
The legend of the palm-top tiger of happiness?
Really. It's all just so ridiculous...
Rub... rub... rub... rub.. rub..
Yacchan?
I feel happy already
Isn't that too fast?
You know
If I just rub Taiga like this
And eat delicious food with my family
That is when I am the happiest
Family?
That's right
We're a three-person family, you know
Hey, Yacchan, I can't breathe...
To grant any wish if you touch the palm-top tiger
If that were to be true
Yeah. That is why, Mama
I think I'll just stay here for a while
Yeah
I've made some friends
And besides
It'll be fine
I'm eating properly too
Yeah. I'm told to be mature anyway
What
Did I wish for?
Right now
I can't very well see
The shape of my dreams
And it's not like
I want to see
Alrgiht. Now I'll rub Ryuuchan
Let me rub too. Here
Yuck! Don't touch me with your feet.