SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
So that's the plan.
Roger.
We'll start the mission-
Are you going out, Kana-chan?
Good morning!
Spending your first stipend right away, I see.
Not all of it.
I'm sending some to my parents, so I thought I'd include presents as well.
Also...
Something for yourself?
Yes!
Well, you didn't get paid for the first month since you were a trainee.
You must be happy.
Yeah.
But I was surprised.
I heard that paychecks are often late, or they're substituted with war notes.
Here. Thanks for the hard work.
Thank you very much!
I didn't expect I'd actually get paid.
Well of course.
That's exactly the reason our unit-
Kanata, um... you know... the flea market is today!
It's your first time, right?
Your first salary and first leave.
Perfect timing for both. You've earned it, Kana-chan.
Forget about duties today and spread your wings.
Okay!
KANATA'S DAY OFF
HAIRDRESSING
I'm going then!
I told you not to make her suspicious, didn't I?
But,
if you think about it seriously,
there's no way you'd get paid on time when everything else is delayed.
But, Kanata believed it so easily.
Kana-chan's good point is that she's very trusting.
Yeah.
She's not like both of you, who immediately asked where the money came from.
I know, right?
Now, then.
Let's forget about our duties as well.
This is well made.
It really is.
But there's only one problem.
I won't budge on the price.
I-I'm sorry!
I wasn't paying attention.
Preparations are done, I see.
Yeah.
No problems here.
There's a big one on our end.
But I have an idea for dealing with it.
Are you in?
Can you give us the details?
Sure.
This one's cute, too.
So it's you who's selling these goods?
Are you interested in them?
They're not bad.
However...
We have a bit of a problem.
Oh my, what could it be?
Selling this much'll take a lot of effort and good connections.
With that in mind, it'll probably exceed our budget.
That's why-
Our policy is no discounts.
The price comes with the flavor.
I'm not asking you to lower the price, you see.
I'll just take them all!
You'd better not!
Just try to shoot.
But before you do, I'll take this gun,
and put a hole in your head instead of your hat.
In that case...
Not too bright, are you?
This is your punishment for taking us lightly.
Good night, boys.
I told you so.
Hey.
Are you people with them?
Mishio-chan!
Th-The car!
Underboss!
Leave it!
But, the gifts for the boss...
A small price to pay for our lives!
Underboss!
No one told me they were that dangerous!
No way I'm coming back to this town!
They're gone.
I see.
Alright everyone, it's all clear now.
Oh man, that gave me the chills.
Seems that we managed to fool them.
Thanks for your cooperation.
No problem. If the central Mafias were to set up shop,
our business would be in jeopardy.
We're scratching each other's back, right?
However...
I assume you would give us something extra for our part in this little play.
Oh please, you do love to joke around, Mikhail-san.
No no, not at all.
I wasn't joking, you know?
From here, it's the world of business.
How about... I take care of that?
Was that your doing, crushing their car out back?
That wasn't you?
What happened?
Well...
Seems like someone crushed the car.
Inside, there were spoils of war bought from the flea market.
How about I "buy" it and share half the profit with you?
It's a deal, then.
Indeed.
The farce is finally over, huh?
But, I was a bit surprised.
By what?
Well, because you were so into it, Rio-senpai.
This is bootleg liquor, so there'd be no excuse under military law.
Monopoly and tax code violations,
not to mention treason, at worst.
You're right.
Our seniors entrusted this side job to us,
but Rio never opposed it even once.
I didn't expect it either.
Of course, I was surprised at first.
I didn't know this Calvados my mother loved was actually produced in the fortress.
Then maybe the reason why you're posted here,
was because your mother led you to it.
I'm going then!
Yumina onee-chan!
It's done! Look!
It's wonderful, Seiya-san.
Mishio-san.
It's time for your first visit to the church,
and the priest will be there too.
So at least for today...
No!
Don't trouble Onee-chan, Mishio.
Why don't you let her do your hair?
No! I don't wanna!
Why?! You were always bugging me to do mine!
Shut up, Seiya!
You musn't do that, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10.25 yen...
Watch it, missy.
I-I'm sorry! I wasn't paying attention.
They're the problem.
It seems they've caught wind of the trade.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But, Naomi-san...
What should I do?
Huh?
This is the first time I have all the money I need in my purse.
I can definitely buy it now if I said I wanted it, right?
Hey, what would you do if someone wanted to buy it up right now?
What?!
Did someone else say they wanted it?!
No, I meant as a, "what if?"
I see, if it were me...
Right! I'd change their mind by saying dolphins are scary creatures that eat people!
You're a genius!
Ah, about that dolphin...
I won't sell it until you say you don't want it anymore. So don't worry.
Okay then, let's go buy everyone's presents now.
Um, Dad, Mom, Grandpa, and Grandma...
Old Man Warren, his wife...
Great-grandma...
and Granny Nanae from next door.
Wow, there are so many things for sale.
Like this!
I'm sorry.
Hm? Mishio-chan?
Are you buying something?
She's looking for a box of some sort.
A box?
Like this. Have you seen it?
I'm sorry.
If you're looking for it, can I help?
Kanata, what are you doing here?
Ah, I'm here to buy some presents.
I was thinking of buying something lovely for my family back home.
But, I can help you-
I don't need it!
What happened to Mishio-chan?
Th-This is a bit much...
That's a lovely shirt.
This one's cute, too.
Yumina-san?
Um, Kanata-san.
Have you seen Mishio-san around?
A box?
Yeah.
It seemed important to her.
I see.
When her mother passed away, they took all of her belongings.
I believe that box, a memento of her mother, was also taken.
She looks for it every time there's a flea market in town.
I said something mean to her.
I got my first stipend yesterday,
and I told her I wanted to send gifts to my family.
That's not your fault.
Right now, I'm... I mean, we're trying to be her family.
If Mishio-san still envies you after all that,
it just means I wasn't good enough for her.
Hey, Mama. Which do you like more, me or this treasure box?
This!
Mama...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
That's Treize's amazing firecrackers for you!
It makes a great sound, how about it?
Onee-chan...
Yumina onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
Mishio-chan!
Th-The car!
I'm sorry I'm not Yumina-san.
Onee-chan!
Yumina onee-chan!
Thanks.
Good work.
Now then...
Um...
M-My, what's wrong?
By any chance, is that your car, Naomi-san?
Don't tell me, you two did it?!
I'm sorry!
Um, I have 150 yen here! Is that enough-
Great job you did there.
You can keep your money.
I've already got the payment for it.
N-Naomi-san, that's-
It's an ideograph that means "beautiful rice stalk".
Carve this into her seal, and she will be blessed with happiness equal
to that of a bountiful harvest of rice in the fields.
Oh, my...
Isn't it great that you received such a good name, Miho?
Did you manage to find Mishio-san?
I've put all my heart into being her family,
but I'm not good enough.
No, you've done more than enough.
Mishio-san!
Thank God. So you found it?
You should treasure it, then.
Since it's an irreplaceable memory of your mother-
That's not it!
Here.
I want you to have it, Yumina.
Mishio-san is a child the church took in after she lost her family.
First, her father was called off to war, and never returned.
And her mother?
Mishio-san's family lived at the eastern border of Vingt.
Don't tell me...
Yes. The town that was attacked by the invisible Grim Reaper.
When the two of them arrived at Seize, her mother was already bed-ridden. Shortly afterward...
Mama told me,
that she regretted she couldn't do my hair anymore.
And then, also,
I should have the one who cares about me the most do my hair.
So do it for me, Yumina.
People need to keep on living.
Even when separated from their loved ones,
and feel so much pain they'd want to die from it.
Even so, we keep on living.
We must keep on living.
That strength is very sorrowful, yet very dear.
I'm sorry,
and thank you,
Onee-chan.
Everyone's already in the bath.
Okay, I'll go soon.
You must be tired.
Yeah, I wanted to avoid washing my hair,
but a lot of things happened.
Okay, then! Lemme do it, Senpai!
Let me dry your hair.
I always wanted to touch it once.
So you didn't buy the dolphin after all?
I was pretty sure you'd get it to reward yourself.
Do you believe in fate, Rio-senpai?
Why, all of a sudden?
It just crossed my mind today, somehow.
That's all I need to reward myself.
I don't believe in it.
I'd hate to think everything was decided from the beginning.
Really?
But, yeah...
It's possible that small and unimportant actions by one,
could change the course of another's life.
If that's what you call "fate", then...
Just maybe...
D-flat.
You also had a wonderful day today, didn't you, Senpai?
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
CHIRPING CRICKETS - SPIRITS DOWN THE RIVER
Chirping Crickets - Spirits Down the River
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.