It's summer.
I want to die.
You sound so gloomy, Tooru.
It's summer! Let's go to the beach!
I don't want anyone to see this tiny body.
You worry too much.
Everyone has special traits.
You just need to bring out the best in yourself.
Run-chan...
Or so a certain kind of people say.
You don't need to say that.
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Ta-da!
I got you a swimsuit with that in mind!
I picked the smallest one they had, so let's go to the beach!
Here.
I know it'll look good on you! Try it on!
Okay.
It looks great!
But it's kind of loose...
I'm here.
I brought some ice cream.
What's this?
Tooru, we have ice cream.
I can't eat anything right now.
What's up with Tooru?
Just something.
Oh! This flavor just came out this year!
I wanted to try it!
Me too! I thought I might try it out!
What a coincidence.
Why don't we split it?
Sure!
Never mind! I can eat!
Wh-Why are you naked?
Beach
It's pool time!
Changed already?!
Honestly. You're in high school and you still get excited by the pool?
Must be nice to be you.
What are you saying? Summer is all about the pool!
Did you forget that we're in class?
The pool is the pool.
Oh? Your swimsuit is faded everywhere but here. Is it a hand-me-down?
I've been using this one since elementary school.
Hey! That's dangerous!
This floating feeling is wonderful.
Your boobs are huge, aren't they?
You think so?
You must have an easy time swimming with that fat as a flotation device.
That sounded bitter.
Are you jealous?
I-I'd never—
No fat at all?!
It's so hot...
P.E. in the summer is just too much.
The first years have the pool today.
It's Tooru!
You're right!
The pool looks so cool.
Alright. Gather 'round.
Must be nice.
I'm jealous.
What's wrong, Nagi? Didn't you hate the pool?
I hate the pool.
Or rather, I hate wearing swimsuits.
But!
Tooru!
Get water on me! Dump a bucket on me!
The heat's fried Nagi's brain!
Oh, whatever.
What? The beach?
Yeah! Summer vacation starts tomorrow! Let's go together!
Agreed!
I don't have a swimsuit for the beach.
I don't want to wear a swimsuit.
What are you two saying? That's not true!
What?
Hey, did you hear that? Just because she has a nice body!
Just because she has white skin.
Hey! What are you saying!
That's not what I meant!
My, what modesty!
Come on...
Let's go to the beach together.
Thank you very much!
Man, I'm hot from walking around.
Sorry to drag you along with me.
No, I got myself some stuff.
How about sitting down somewhere?
Nagi?
What's wrong? Do you feel alright?
This wall traps the cool air in this corner.
I'll sit right here.
Come on, Nagi! Stand up! Please!
That girl is really big!
She must be over 170 centimeters!
Everyone must think I'm too big...
They're envious.
You're thin, tall, and you've got boobs.
Don't mention the boobs.
It's pretty hard living with them.
Really?
Oh, these bras are pretty nice.
And they're cheap! Maybe I'll get one.
You're right. I want one, too.
What's wrong?
The sizes on these are up to D.
I guess smaller ones are nice sometimes.
Let's just go home.
Hey, why don't we take a look?
What? Didn't we decide we weren't going to the beach?
Come on, they're cute.
I'm not buying one.
Nagi.
How's this one?
It's good.
Really? I'll try it on. Mind seeing?
Sure.
What do you think?
It's nice.
Really? Then...
How about this?
Looks good.
Then...
This one?
Perfect.
It's too hard to choose!
Maybe I should check out a few others!
It'll only be a minute.
Okay.
Alright.
Nagi, thanks for waiting—
Oh?
It's not what you think! I was just looking...
I'll try them on.
Why did I get one?
It's a nice one, and it looks good on you.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
A text?
Yeah. I'm inviting Run and Tooru to the beach.
It'll be fun.
Just two kilograms...
Not happening.
Run says okay!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Run-chan just came by.
Did she go home already?
Yeah. She said she just wanted you to have this.
This is a swimsuit I used to wear. I think it should fit you perfectly.
Let's race to that island, Tooru!
Play hard and study hard. I look forward to seeing all your bright, shining faces next term.
Wait!
Beach! Beach! Beach! Beach! Beach!
What are you, a kid?
The beach!
It sure is pretty...
We're on the road.
Looks like it's a streetcar, too.
Yeah.
That's pretty cool. It can run on the road.
When did they switch them on?
Switch what?
Well, the tires.
It doesn't use tires.
We're here!
The beach!
Alright! Let's swim!
This beach has me all excited!
Me too!
Run-chan.
Thanks for giving me your swimsuit.
No problem. I'm glad it fit you.
Sorry the design is so kiddy.
But you know...
I used it in elementary school.
Hey! What are you doing?
Let's go!
Okay!
Elementary school...
Take that!
Now you've done it!
Hey, that tickles!
Here! Have a lift!
What are you doing?!
That looks fun, Tooru.
Let go of me!
Tooru? Nagi?
That's a nice hat!
What?
Seaweed.
Looks good on you, Nagi!
Looks good!
Seaweed.
Okay, time-out.
What, Nagi? Tired already?
I woke up at five this morning. I'm almost out of gas.
I'm still going strong.
Unlike you, I'm weak.
Then how about a break?
I'll go get some juice.
Get me a melon soda?
Sure.
Sports drink!
Okay.
She's really tired.
Welcome!
They have a lot of stuff.
What should I get?
Oh, Run-chan.
That.
I never thought I would find that legendary tortoiseshell candy juice here!
Nagi-chan, here's your drink.
Thanks.
Oh?
Yuuko sleeping.
You're right.
Honestly. She said she was going strong.
We sit down, and look at her.
She looks really relaxed.
I know.
This sure feels nice!
Not many people, and it's so quiet.
These southern islands are great!
What?
Leaves?
Stop that, Tooru. That tickles.
Heavy...
Heavy!
What?
A dream?
I fell asleep?
A castle?!
No!
Don't move.
It's almost done.
Get it off me!
There!
Attack!
Here!
Sorry!
It's okay!
What's up?
It feels like you're getting pulled in! It's fun!
Is it that much fun?
Nagi?
Me too!
Lunchtime!
The beach is all about ramen!
Yakisoba.
That southern taste, octopus rice.
Boxed lunch.
That's kind of plain.
You think?
It's okay! Leave it to me!
What are you going to do?
I mean, we're at the beach!
Fish!
What kind of scenery do you expect to see?
Look, there it is, the horizon
On the burning sand, my heart is dancing
With every blink, the sun in my eyes
Looks like my wanting to play was just hiding away,
A side of me you've never seen before, running ahead
Blue sky in your heart, the waves splashing
A feeling you can see
Let's go, sisters, the swimsuit tans
Looks like people are leaving.
Well, it is sunset.
Bring us together
It feels like we played all day.
With all the rays we catch,
I'm glad we came so early.
Right?
The beach was a lot of fun.
Let's make a rainbow
Yeah.
Yeah. It was fun.
Let's come again sometime.
Yuuko, come on!
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
We made it...
We get the car to ourselves.
Yuuko-chan, why don't you sit down?
No, I'll stand here.
We won't get back for a while.
I mean, I still have a lot of energy.
Are you okay, Yuuko?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Cuticle!
Is your cuticle okay, Yuuko-chan?
You can't see it...
I think it's fine.
Your hair is long and pretty, so you have to be careful.
And your skin is white.
Thanks...
Oh, I wonder if I tanned.
No, don't worry.
We put enough sunscreen on.
You sure?
Run, how about you?
You haven't tanned a bit.
Run, what sunscreen do you use?
I don't use any.
You don't use any, and you have this kind of skin?
I can't believe this.
That tickles!
My skin just doesn't tan.
Really?
Are you an alien or something?
No, I'm not...
Run-chan is from Earth.
You sure?
I'm sure!
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
Why do we get so sleepy after we swim?
Especially those afternoons after swimming in class!
It marks the start of a cycle of terror.
What's that?
If you sleep in the afternoon, you can't sleep at night.
But if you don't sleep at night, you'll get sleepy in the afternoon...
I know what you mean!
On the next A Channel: A Midsummer Night's...
If you sleep from afternoon until morning, it all works out!
How many hours will you sleep?!