The elders are going to be on the move.
It is dangerous over there as well.
Please hurry.
What a foolish act you have done.
The fortuneteller told us thus:
"The night of the red moon,
the snake will slither horribly quickly
to make use of its venomous fangs."
You look so pitiful, Vicious.
We have informed you of our decision
that you cannot be our successor.
The syndicate does not need
corpses who cannot even fight.
That arrogance of yours will
ruin everything in the end.
Take him to the punishment chamber.
Kill me.
Right now.
You cannot choose how you will die.
After we let you have a
good taste of humiliation,
we will send you into the underworld.
Don't forget...
...a snake's venom poisons
slowly after the bite.
Sheesh, that was the first time
we screwed up so badly.
We never had anything like that
before when we were all alone.
All told, they screwed up
our plans right to the end.
They really were like troublesome babies.
I completely understand why
you hate women and kids now.
Too much vermouth.
Who are they?
Lin?!
I'm Shin, his younger brother.
Shin...
That's right, you two were...
If you change sides, you won't be
able to return to the syndicate.
What happened?
Vicious is to be executed.
He failed to pull off the coup, and has
been put under restraints by the elders.
You are in danger as well.
And Miss Julia...
Julia is?
They're in the city of Tharsis.
I'll hold them off here.
Please go!
I'll owe you one, Shin!
I don't know what
happened to Red Dragon...
...but it's not really
your problem now, right?
Vicious, Julia...
To me, both those names
sound nothing but ominous.
Just like a magic spell that opens
a door that shouldn't be opened.
You're...
Hold still.
You are no longer a
member of the syndicate...
I know.
You, too...
Forget everything, including
the fact that we came here.
What are you talking about?
I'm just treating stray cats
that wandered into the office.
Stray cats that I can't ever get rid of...
When this is over, I'm leaving the syndicate.
You'll be killed.
I'll let them say I'm dead.
I'll be waiting at the graveyard.
Of course, I will be alive.
I... can't come with you.
Come with me.
We'll leave here...
We'll escape from this world.
And then what are we going to do?
We'll just live a life of freedom somewhere.
Just like watching a dream...
Are you going to betray me?
Are you going to leave this world...?
Vicious.
Even if it's a dream, that's an impossibility.
Are you going to kill him?
Yeah...
...with your hands.
You stay alive...
...or you both die.
You can choose.
So there is no place for me after all.
I won't go no matter who
comes to pick me up. Never.
I don't want to live a life where
I'm always in someone's way.
Mom! I've been looking for you!
A-Alfred...
I told you to wait in front
of the curry restaurant!
Sorry.
It's all right. I'm glad you came.
It sounds too good to be true
that you can take care of me now.
Mom, I want to live with you.
You found a job?
Don't worry about that.
What about your female co-host?
I heard she's getting married.
Something about this...
Where are you now?
What is it?
I'm heading out to the city of Tharsis.
You should head that way, too.
Why?
It's hard for Jet to get around on his own.
Especially after getting shot in the leg.
I'm telling ya to stop wandering
around so much, and just come back.
Don't just assume that I'm coming back!
You've got to be kidding!
I have a place to go back to!
What's with that attitude?
Like he's all high-and-mighty.
What does he mean, Jet's by himself?
He's there... Ed and Ein, too...
You saved me.
Same here.
You're a good shot.
I was getting bounties with it.
A bounty hunter...?
Although now...
...I'm kind of on a break 'cause
there's something going on.
You look like you have
something going on, too.
It might be good to pair up
with another woman.
How about it? Wanna be my partner?
I have... something to do.
Oh.
Too bad.
Do you know any bounty hunter hangouts?
I can help if you want to
put a bounty on someone.
I'm looking for a bounty hunter.
I'll drive you back.
What's your name?
Faye...
Faye...?!
Faye Valentine.
A common name.
What's yours?
Julia.
Julia...?!
It's a common name.
I'm glad I met you.
Me, too.
Um, have I seen you somewhere...?
lf... you see Spike again...
...tell him that I will be waiting there.
He'll know what I mean.
Tell him that I'll keep waiting...
Why...?
Good-bye, Faye Valentine.
Why?
Why do you know?!
Does it still hurt?
Do you know a story that goes like this?
A man injured his leg during a hunt.
In the middle of the savanna,
with no means to treat the wound,
the leg rots, and death approaches.
The man got onto the airplane
that finally arrived
and there he sees a land
of pure white below him.
The place glistening in the light was
the summit of a snow-covered mountain.
The name of the mountain was Kilimanjaro.
The man thinks... that was
where he was headed...
And...?
I hate this story.
Men only think about the past...
...right before their death, as if they were
searching frantically for
proof that they were alive.
Turn back.
You told me when we first met...
...that you were a man
who had already died once.
Just forget the past, okay?
There was a woman.
For the first time in my life,
I saw a woman that was truly alive.
That's what I believed.
She was a piece of me I had lost.
She is my other half that I had longed for.
--She's back.
--Hm? Who...?
Oh, man...
We're not a repair shop.
Don't come back just when
you broke something...
Where is he?
He?
The one with the fluffy hair.
What, can't you just say
you're looking for Spike?
Where is he?
He's in the workshop.
What are you trying to hide?
You came back here just to see Spike?
I was asked to relay a message...
...from Julia.
Hey, wait!
Jet, it's me.
What, I don't have any information now.
We're not really able to--
I'm glad you're all right.
I was worried. It's getting to
be pretty bad, you know...
About Red Dragon?
Yeah...
There was apparently
a coup two days ago
concerning who was going to
be the syndicate's successor.
In the end the elders won,
and they're now out
to annihilate anyone who
was involved in the coup.
Your partner will also...
Been there.
But why are they trying to get rid of
those that already left the syndicate?
Anything against them will be annihilated,
down to the very last seed.
That's how they do it.
That's the worst logic I've ever heard.
Just run.
The police can't handle all of it.
Leave Mars.
Too late for that.
You have something?
You look like you have some information.
How much will you pay for it?
I don't have any money.
You sure came back at the worst time...
Weren't you the one who called me here?
Or... maybe they followed you here?
Oh, well. It was gonna
happen sooner or later.
Wait!
Wait a minute!
I don't have any money.
She said she'll be waiting there.
She said you'd understand.
I don't get it.
It was from a woman named Julia.
Someone was after her...
They were chasing her...
Jet, I can go at any time.
You who caused a disturbance
in our clan's affairs.
By the will of the clan,
you shall be executed.
Let me out, too!
Wait!
Your right thruster isn't working yet!
The end is the same if
we go down ship and all!
Will you leave words?
Or leave something material?
Nothing.
You shall shed red tears.
Spike, can you still fly?
Don't worry about us. Just go!
Go grasp that thing you had lost.
Go!
As of now, the leadership
has changed hands.
From now on, I will dictate all authority
and symbolism of this syndicate.
Too much time has passed by...
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
I only want to know what true sadness is.
Sitting in muddy water...
...isn't such a bad life...
...if it ends after the first time...
A lot of things have happened,
but the next episode is the last.
It sure was long...
The past is the past
no use doing this...
and the future is the future.
So how was it, Jet?
A man is a man, and a woman is a woman.
Because of you, I ended up raising Ein.
I am who I am, and you are who you are.
Dogs are really cute after all...
Like it really matters any...
Hey, Jet. Come on, you aren't listening to what I'm saying at all!
I wonder why we gave him away...
Oh... What was it?
Never mind.
Anyway... Next episode:
"The Real Folk Blues (Part 2)."
We'll see you again, somewhere.
"The Real Folk Blues (Part 2)"
What? This is the end?