Morning, sleepyhead! Time to wake up.
Morning, sleepyhead! Time to—
I have to get up.
Taroumaru, breakfast.
Taroumaru?
Taroumaru!
It's not him...
No!
Why...
Why?!
School Living Club
Graduation Album
#5
"Meeting"
Club outing!
A fun-filled club outing!
Megu-nee, do we have any bananas?
Someone's in a good mood.
We... do!
We should be there soon.
Yay!
Oh, that's it!
We're here!
You're too hyper.
You're the type to get
overheated on outings, huh?
N-No I don't! I do not!
See? Your face is already flushed.
Now, now.
I really am worried, though.
Wh-What was that?! What about you?
Well, so far, so good.
Your presence is barely noticeable!
You could get lost!
I'm guessing there aren't many of them
out because it's a weekday.
I-I will not! I'm your teacher, you know!
And I have a perfectly
noticeable presence, okay?!
They're all probably at school, or work...
Oh, all right. I'll hold your hand.
Like they still have memories
of when they were alive.
"Oh, all right," nothing!
Well, let's keep our guard up
and try to enjoy our outing.
Aww, meanie...
It's been so long since we went shopping.
Hey, you two!
Hurry up!
You're right.
And we have to keep an eye
on that little troublemaker.
The door's open?
Are you guys closed? Hello?
Hey, don't be so loud.
Why?
Well, because...
Inugami Yasutaka Piano Concert
Looks like there's an event happening.
Event? Like a festival?
I think there's a concert going on.
Let's be quiet so we don't interrupt.
Okay!
Shh!
Thank you.
Okay, everyone, let's go.
It's so big!
So there are some in here.
This many is nothing I can't handle.
Stay close and try to keep quiet.
Okay.
Gotcha!
Shh!
Sorry.
Okay, let's go!
Looks like there are none in here.
Thanks, Rii-san.
This is J-Rock!
I wonder what they've got here.
Rii-san, I'm gonna check downstairs.
To the supermarket? But I'm sure
everything's spoiled by now.
We need canned goods, right?
Don't do anything reckless.
I know.
Hey, Rii-san, check this out!
What's up?
Don't worry. I promise I'll bring help.
Kei...
There.
All right! Jackpot, jackpot!
Ginger soy beef!
A d-dog?
What? What is it?
No fair! That's mine!
Oh, no!
I hope Kurumi's okay...
Hey, Rii-san, Kurumi-chan still isn't back.
I know. Let's wait a little longer.
Enka Corner
Wow, Rii-san, you're so refined.
Huh?
Safe...
Kurumi.
It's you!
A puppy!
They can communicate?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry. Hang on a second.
Here you go.
My ginger soy beef!
Rii-san, hurry.
Just a second...
Rii-san, no fair.
It's okay. He's not bitten.
Here, Yuki-chan.
Hi there, puppy.
Yay! It's a puppy!
Yuki-chan, settle down!
Where'd he come from?
I ran into him downstairs.
I wonder where his owner is.
If he had one, they'd be with him.
Hey, Kurumi-chan,
what do you think his name is?
No idea. Isn't it written on his collar?
Oh, you're right.
Um... Taroumaru...
Taroumaru?
Okay! Nice to meet you, Taroumaru!
Are the escalators all broken?
There aren't many on the upper floors.
I don't think they handle stairs well.
Let's try the home appliances store.
Roger.
Camping stove, gas canisters,
and...
Here!
This is it!
An emergency alarm?
Yup.
How cute!
So, when you pull the string...
Don't mess with it.
There's a concert going on, remember?
Aww, just a little...
I said no.
Understood.
What do we need that for?
To scare off bad guys. Crime prevention.
Well, we've got everything we need, right?
Yup!
Then let's go look at clothes next.
Yay!
Shh.
Sorry.
Should we really be doing this?
What better time than now?
We are girls, after all.
I-It's fine... It'll be fine...
I can still fit in these...
Hey, we're heading to the next stop.
Can we please wait a bit?
Megu-nee's fallen and she can't
get up, in more ways than one.
We'll apologize to the owner together, okay?
I couldn't still fit...
Megu-nee?
Yeah. I wanna cheer her up.
Let's see...
Why don't we get her a present?
Yeah! Let's!
Do you know what she likes?
I don't know...
That'd be this, right?
Here, Megu-nee, this is for you.
You're buying that for me?
Yup!
Are you sure?
Of course!
Thank you, Yuki-chan.
I want you to keep it, though.
What? Why?
Do you already have one?
That's part of it, yes.
I should've known.
But that's exactly why
I want you to have one, too.
I see! So we'll match!
Okay, I'll take care of him
as if he was you, Megu-nee.
Actually, he kinda looks like you.
H-How so?
This, mainly.
4th Floor Map
So in the end, you got to keep it.
Yup.
Figures...
First place!
Finally, the top floor.
Taroumaru?
What's wrong?
4th Floor Map
Taroumaru?
Taroumaru, hush.
Taroumaru, be quiet, okay?
Thank you.
Rii-san.
What is it?
I heard something. Sounded like
a chair getting knocked over.
Is it them?
But there were barely any on the floor below.
What if the reason Taroumaru was barking...
A survivor? Maybe it's Taroumaru's owner?
If that's true, we've gotta save them.
Here?
Yeah, definitely.
A movie theater.
Hello? Anyone here?
Looks like no one's here.
Stay here. I'll check inside.
We'll wait here. Be careful.
Look at this, Rii-san!
Doesn't this dog look like Taroumaru?
I-I suppose.
Run!
There's a huge group of them!
Yuki, we've gotta go!
Yuki!
Kurumi-chan? Rii-san? Megu-nee?
It'll be okay. Just run!
I guess... it was my imagination...
Hurry!
That's bad.
There are so many...
Rii-san, throw those glowsticks downstairs.
Understood.
We'll bust through. Stay behind me!
Yuki-chan, let's go.
Yuki-chan... Yuki-chan.
What?
Are you okay?
She has a fever.
I'm okay.
Is she hurt?
No, she's uninjured.
You really are the type to
get overheated on outings.
Sorry.
Just rest, okay?
Okay.
Taroumaru...
Let's let her sleep a bit.
You should rest, too.
You must be the most tired.
Yeah...
Have some water.
Thanks.
We didn't see anyone who was still alive.
That group in the theater...
A lot of them were kids.
They must've been waiting
for help the whole time.
No... The door was barricaded,
like someone was trying to keep them in.
They weren't attacked from the outside.
Someone in that room had been bitten.
I can't stand that. I hate it.
I mean, some of those people probably
retreated there to protect their loved ones!
To protect the people I care about...
If I get infected, don't hesitate for a second.
What're you saying?
Promise me.
Pinky-swear.
What's the matter, Yuki-chan?
I'm hungry.
So I see. Why don't we
head back and have dinner?
Yeah.
Let's go home... to school.
So someone was here.
I'm scared...
Is just staying alive enough?
No excuses!
We're finally out of there!
Let's head home.
We're leaving, Yuki.
Yuki?
Did you guys hear something?
No...
I heard a voice. Someone's calling for us.
You're imagining things, Yuki.
Let's hurry home.
I'm not imagining it! I really heard a voice!
Yuki-chan, calm down.
Megu-nee, you heard it too, right?
I...
Hey, Taroumaru!
I'm going with him!
No, Yuki-chan!
Yuki!
No!
Get away...
Help...
Someone!
Someone, help!
Please!
Please...
There! Over there!
Taroumaru... and...
There are others...
No! Yuki-chan, it's too dangerous!
But...
But...!
Yuki-chan!
Damn it!
They're coming to...
There are too many!
Everyone!
Cover your ears!
Come on, let's go.
Yuki, hurry!
Taroumaru...
Thank goodness you're safe.
Um... Excuse me.
Did you see another girl about my age?
No, we didn't see any others.
I see...
I'm a bit late, but I'm leaving too, Kei.
Next time!!
Shopping, shopping!
Don't waste your money.
Hmph
Manga is never a waste of money.
Do your homework.
I wonder if they have the latest volume.
Next time on Episode 6 of
SCHOOL-LIVE, "Welcome."
#6
Welcome