PROLOGUE IN HEAVEN
How awful!
There's nothing you can do.
It's too much for her to handle alone.
She knew this prior to coming.
But this is terrible! It shouldn't be happening!
It's all over if you give up.
But you have the ability to change fate.
This unavoidable destruction and sorrow...
You can change it all.
You have the power to do just that.
Can I really?
Can I do really something to stop all of this?
Can I really change this ending?
Of course you can!
So make a contract with me...
and become a magical girl!
Was it all just a dream?
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 1
I think we met in a dream...
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning, Madoka.
Is Mom up yet?
Tatsuya went to wake her.
Mind giving him a hand?
No problem!
Mommy! Mommy!
It's morning! It's morning!
Wake up! Mommy! Mommy!
Rise and shine!
Huh?
Mommy woke up!
So what's the latest gossip?
Hitomi-chan got another love letter.
That's the second one this month.
Guys who don't have the guts to confess in person are worthless.
And how's Kazuko?
It looks like her new relationship's still going strong.
She's always talking about her boyfriend during homeroom.
This week marks their three-month
anniversary, and that's a new record.
We'll see how it works out.
This is a tricky time for them.
It is?
If he's not "the one," then they'll start having some problems soon.
If they can get through that, they should be good for the first year.
I see.
All done!
Which ribbons should I wear?
You think? Aren't they too flashy?
They're supposed to be flashy.
We women must always look our best in public.
Perfect. Now your secret admirers will be stuck on you like glue.
You know I don't have any.
You need to act like you do.
That's the secret to being pretty.
Got it.
Be sure to eat it all up.
'kay!
Would you like another cup of coffee?
No, that's fine.
All right, I'm off!
Bye!
Madoka, you should hurry too.
Huh? Oh, right!
See you later!
Bye!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Madoka, you're late.
Oh, cute ribbons.
Y-You think? They're not too flashy?
They're lovely.
So, my mom said that guys who can't ask you out in person are worthless.
Your mom is just too cool, Madoka.
She's beautiful, and she's a successful businesswoman.
I wish it were that easy to reject someone.
What an enviable problem to have!
I know, right? I wish I could get a love letter too.
Oh? So you want to become a beautiful princess like Hitomi?
That's why you started wearing those ribbons, huh?
No! My mom—
I'll bet your mom taught you the secret to being popular!
You dirty girl!
A girl like you needs to be punished!
H-Hey, stop! Stop it!
You're cute, but I won't let you become popular with the guys.
You're going to be my wife!
I have something of utmost importance to discuss with you all today,
so pay very close attention!
Should sunny-side up eggs be hard or soft?!
What do you think, Nakazawa-kun?!
I, uh... I-I guess either way's fine?
That's right! Either way's fine!
And if you think a woman's value
is determined by how she cooks her eggs,
then you are horribly mistaken!
Girls, I want you all to make sure not to associate yourselves with picky men who demand soft eggs!
Guess it didn't work out.
You can say that again.
And boys, make sure you don't grow up
to be a nitpicker who demands eggs to be cooked one way, and one way only!
Now then, I'd like to introduce a transfer student who will be joining us.
You should've mentioned that first!
Please come in, Akemi-san.
She's so cute and cool-looking!
Wow, she's beautiful.
Wait... No way.
Why don't you tell the class your name?
I'm Akemi Homura.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Homura Akemi
Um, Akemi-san?
Which school did you come from?
A Christian school in Tokyo.
Were you in any clubs?
Like sports, or art?
No, I wasn't.
Your hair's so beautiful!
What kind of shampoo do you use?
She has a bit of a mysterious aura about her, don't you think?
Hey, Madoka, do you know her?
Wasn't she staring at you earlier?
Well, uh...
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm still under a bit of stress.
I'm not feeling well.
Would you mind if I went to the nurse's office?
Oh, let me show you the way.
I'll come too!
Don't worry about me.
I'll ask the person in charge.
Kaname Madoka-san, you're the
health officer for this class, right?
I, uh...
Could you take me to the nurse's office?
She's really cute!
Um, how did you know that I was the health officer?
Ms. Saotome told me.
Oh, I see. Well, the nurse's office is...
This way, right?
Huh? Yeah, but...
It's kinda like you already know the way.
A-Akemi-san?
You can call me Homura.
Homura-chan?
What is it?
I, uh... That's a unique name you have!
I-I don't mean it's weird or anything!
It sounds kinda cool!
Kaname Madoka, do you value your own life?
Do you think dearly of your family and friends?
Well... uh, I... I do.
I love my family and friends.
They mean the world to me.
Is that true?
Of course! Why wouldn't it be?
I see.
If that's true, then you must never
think about becoming someone else.
If you do, you'll lose them all.
You just need to remain Kaname Madoka,
as you always have been.
An integer divided by 14 will have an integer quotient with a remainder between 0 and 13.
a is an integer with a remainder of 6 when divided by 14, b is an integer with a remainder of 1 when divided by 14.
The quadratic equation x^2-2ax+b = 0 can be solved for an integer solution.
Find the remainder when this integer solution is divided by 14.
An integer divided by 14 will have an integer quotient with a remainder between 0 and 13.
a is an integer with a remainder of 6 when divided by 14, b is an integer with a remainder of 1 when divided by 14.
The quadratic equation x^2-2ax+b = 0 can be solved for an integer solution.
Find the remainder when this integer solution is divided by 14.
D-Did she just break the prefectural record?
Wait, she said what?!
Doesn't make any sense, does it?
I thought she was one of those smart and beautiful girls...
but it turns out she's just a nutcase.
Just how big of an impression
does she have to make on people?
Is that moe? Is that what moe is?
Madoka-san, are you sure
you've never met her before?
Well, I guess I'd have to say yes, but...
You "guess"?
Is there something weird you're not telling us?
Well, I think we met in a dream last night... or something.
That's great!
Now you're starting to make an impression!
That's mean!
I'm seriously concerned about this!
There's only one answer, then.
You must've known her in a previous life,
and were brought together by fate across time and space to meet once more.
What kind of dream was it?
Honestly, I don't really remember.
All I know is that it was a really weird dream.
Maybe you have met her somewhere before, then.
Huh?
Even though you might not remember her,
your subconscious could have taken note of her, and later brought her image out in a dream.
Isn't that a bit too far-fetched?
I mean, it's just a coincidence.
I suppose so.
Oh, look at the time.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Piano lessons? Or do you
have Japanese dance today?
Today's tea ceremony practice.
Entrance exams are right around the corner, but my mom still wants me to keep this up.
I'm glad I wasn't born rich.
Should we get going too?
Oh, Madoka?
Mind if we stop by the
music store on the way home?
Sure.
Buying another CD for Kamijou-kun?
You know how it is.
See you later.
See you!
Bye-bye!
Save me.
Save me, Madoka!
Who's there?
Save me.
Notice of Store Renovation
This floor has been CLOSED for renovations
Where are you?
Who are you?
Save me.
Was that you?
Save me...
Homura-chan?
Step away from that thing.
B-But he's hurt.
N-No! Please don't hurt him!
This has nothing to do with you.
But he was calling me!
He was begging for me to save him!
I see.
Madoka, this way!
Sayaka-chan!
Of all times...
What's with her?
Does she go around attacking
people while cosplaying?!
What's that thing?
It's not a stuffed animal, is it?
Is it alive?
I don't know.
I don't know, but...
I have to save him!
Huh? Where's the emergency exit?
Where are we?
Something is not right.
The corridor keeps changing.
Damn it!
What the hell's going on?!
I-I see something over there!
This can't be happening, right?
I mean, this has to be a bad dream or something, right?
Right, Madoka?!
Huh? What was that?
What the...
That was pretty close,
but everything's okay now.
Oh, you saved Kyubey?
Thank you.
He's a dear friend of mine.
He was calling out to me.
I heard his voice in my head.
I see.
Judging by your uniforms, I assume you're also Mitakihara students.
Are you juniors?
Who are you?
How rude of me.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
But before that...
allow me to take care of a little something first, would you?
W-Wow...
W-We're back!
The witch got away.
If you want to hunt it down,
you'll need to chase after it quickly.
I'll give you this one.
I'm here on business.
You don't seem to understand me.
I'm saying I'll let you go.
Would it not be better for both of us to avoid any unnecessary trouble?
Thank you, Mami.
You saved me.
You should thank these two.
I was just passing by.
Thank you very much.
My name is Kyubey!
Were you the one who was calling for me?
That's right, Kaname Madoka and Miki Sayaka!
H-How do you know our names?
I have a request for you two.
A request?
I want you two to make contracts
with me and become magical girls!
"sore ja mata ne" tte te wo futte
「それじゃ またね」って手を振って
I waved my hand, saying, "I'll see you next time"
muri ni waratte samishiku natte
無理に笑って さみしくなって…
I forced a smile, then I was lonely...
kousaten shingou
交差点 信号
Traffic lights at the intersection...
tooku no kurakushon
遠くのクラクション
The distant sound of a car honking...
shiranai dareka no waraiau koe
知らない誰かの笑い合う声
The voices of strangers laughing
kyou wa hitori de aruku
今日はひとりで歩く
Today, I walk alone
kayoinareta machi demo
通い慣れた街でも
Even though I'm used to the city,
itsumo yorimo nandaka
いつもよりもなんだか
I feel just a little smaller
jibun ga chotto chiisaku omoeru yo
自分がちょっと小さく思えるよ
than my usual self
"sore ja mata ne" tte te wo futte
「それじゃ またね」って手を振って
I wave my hand, saying, "I'll see you next time"
egao tsukutte samishiku natte
笑顔作って さみしくなって
I made a smile, then I was lonely...
honto wa mada hanashitarinai kedo
ホントはまだ話し足りないけど
Even though I want to talk even more with you...
"sore ja mata ne" tte kotoba tte
「それじゃ またね」って言葉って
Saying, "I'll see you next time,"
mata aeru tte uso wo tsuite
また会えるって嘘をついて…
Lying about seeing each other again
itsumo toori no egao de iu yo
いつも通りの笑顔で言うよ
I say, with my usual smile,
"mata ashita"
「また あした」
"See you tomorrow."
Illustrated by  Hanokage
I can grant each of you one wish.
Wait, really?
What kind of wish?
Anything you want.
I can fulfill any miracle you wish for.
Episode 2
I think that'd be really nice
I think that'd be really nice.