All right, all right...
This isn't working at all.
They're going to fly away.
It's sparkling.
How pretty...
That
Selection
is...
That
Selection
is...
That
Selection
is...
That
Selection
is...
Truth and reality are like the two sides of a card
shinjitsu wa hitoe ni kaado no uraomote
Forever entwined
tokenai mama
Thrust upon this chaotic stage
mekurimekuru meku
I spin around and lose my way
memagurushii suteeji de
Until I can finally sort out these mixed-up emotions
sono karamatta kanjou wo manzoku iku made nankai mo
I'll destroy it countless times
kowashite shimae
The uncertain future will be summoned by fate
unmei ni temaneki sare samayou ashita wa
Should I choose just one thing to let go of?
nani wo erande nani wo tebanashi hitotsu ni nareba iin darou
I can't afford to let my sinful hand show yet
najitta tefuda wo sarasu yoyuu nante nai yo
My days of leisurely drinking from the sea of regret are long over
kawaita koukai no umi wo nomihosu hibi wa
Will you really use your one wish to return that lost smile?
kagirareta kotoba de itsushika no egao yurushite hoshiin darou
It's no concern of mine if you avert your eyes from reality
utsutsu wo wasuretatte kamawanai yo dakara
So please just live in blissful ignorance
ima wa shiranai de itai nee
Hitoe...
That scrunchie!
To be honest, I remembered it...
The time I spent with you two.
Hitoe!
Hitoe?
Hitoe?!
It hurt.
My chest felt like it was being torn apart.
Still, I thought to myself...
I... want to remember.
Hitoe?!
Even if it meant pain and
suffering for me, I still wanted...
...to remember!
Hitoe!
B-But why did you hide that from us until n—
I wanted my wish to come true!
I wanted friends...
No, it didn't matter what my wish was.
Because as long as I win,
Yuzuki will become an Eternal Girl
and be released from the card.
Isn't that right?
What are you saying, Hitoe?!
That doesn't solve anything at all!
I'd just be stealing your—
My friends really care for me.
Just that is enough to be a dream come true.
That someone would sacrifice herself for me...
I didn't know something as beautiful as that ever existed in this world.
Rather than the existence of Selectors,
to me,
having met the two of you
is far...
far more
of a miracle.
Being able to do something for a friend...
There's no greater happiness than this.
This is the only wish I want to see granted.
Hitoe!
Friend...
Please, Tama...
Please accept my wish.
Ruu?
I want to release her from the card.
My friend...
My precious friend!
Can I...
become your friend, too?
Ruu!
Tell me what to do!
Tama needs to battle!
To make your wish come true...
I need to battle!
Thank you.
Yuzuki!
Hitoe!
Let's continue the battle.
And... I'm sorry, Hitoe!
I'm going to win this battle!
I'm going to have my wish come true!
Ruuko?
Arch Aura!
Hitoe...
Ruuko...
Did that hurt, Yuzuki?
I'm all right.
Anyway—Ruuko, about that earlier!
Right! Ruuko, your wish...
I want Yuzuki and all the other girls who
were sealed inside the cards to be released.
Ruuko...
H-Hold on!
I told you we still need to think this through.
Hitoe, Yuzuki, I feel the same way you do.
Being able to do something for a friend...
is something to be really happy about!
I'll be going now.
Wait! I'll go with you!
I'll go, too!
Hitoe... Yuzuki...
But...
I give up. No use trying to talk you out of it.
If your wish really does come true,
I should go back to normal
and you shouldn't be turned into a LRIG.
Let's go buy some pork buns at the
convenience store when we go home.
Yeah!
Tama, let's do some shopping
when we go for pork buns later.
Shopping?
I'm going to buy you a matching scrunchie.
Ruu!
It's really scary being this high up...
The place where Grandma and I live
should be somewhere around there...
Grandma...
I've been waiting for you,
Ruu.
"Ruu"?
You two came as well?
Got a problem with that?
Not like we're gonna stop you or anything!
It's all right.
An audience doesn't make any difference.
Is there anything you need?
Like a declaration of intent?
Or details of the situation here?
I don't need anything.
I only want to battle.
You're the best.
Open!
What a lonesome place...
Is this how it looks inside your heart?
You said battling is all you want?
Let's begin.
You're first, Ruu.
Grow!
They're both so strong.
But Ruuko's eyes...
They're kind of cold.
What's going on?
This battle doesn't feel fun or exciting, like the battles I had before.
It's so quiet...
I can even hear Tama drawing breath.
With this battle...
I will...
Grow!
Sword Ability!
Ulith.
She's in a league of her own!
You've already amassed enough wins to give birth to an Eternal Girl,
but the time wasn't quite ripe.
Now it's finally time.
No, not yet.
Grow.
No, still not quite yet...
This isn't all Ruuko has.
My Kominato Ruuko!
Black Desire!
Tama...
Tama!
Tama... Tama...
It's not Ruu.
Tama...
This isn't Ruu's voice.
But I know this voice even better than Ruu's.
We finally meet, Tama.
Wh-Who are you?
You poor thing...
Look at all these bruises.
Ruu is cruel, isn't she?
You even wished for it.
You wished to stay together forever.
You wished with all your heart.
Ruu must treasure her friends more than you.
No!
Ruu's not like that!
She said I was her friend!
Tama...
We're going to eat soft-serve ice cream together!
She said she'd buy me matching scrunchies!
And—
You poor, poor thing...
Ruu is doing this all for her friends.
Not for you, Tama, but for her precious friends.
She'd even become a LRIG for their sake.
No!
Ruu said we'd all go home together!
That's why I have to—
That's wrong.
It's all wrong, Tama.
Remember!
It's easy.
You don't want to fulfill Ruu's wish, right?
Then it's easy.
Just don't agree when the time comes.
Yuzuki said it herself.
A Selector's wish is only granted when her LRIG agrees to it.
B-But then, Ruu will...!
Try and win, then.
Win the battle, and you will know Ruu's true feelings.
Ruu's...
That is, if you can win the battle.
Tama...
Tama!
Tama, are you okay?
"Win... and you'll know."
Tama, don't overdo it.
Ruu... I will fight.
This is our last battle.
Tama...
Now that's a good girl.
The battle isn't over yet, right?
Draw!
Enercharge! Tama, level 4!
No matter what waits beyond my wish...
...this will be the last battle.
No matter what waits beyond this wish...
The last!
Look!
The white and black keep on colliding.
The battlefield is...!
The roof?
Were we... brought back from the battlefield?
No, look at the sky.
Tama and the others aren't done yet, either.
Ruu! What should I do next?
Hurry!
It's so pretty...
I wasn't really sure earlier,
but the place where Grandma and I live is right there.
R-Ruu...
Thank you.
You wanted to show me this before our final moment.
"Final moment"...?
Grandma...
Goodbye.
See this, Iona? She thinks she's already won.
She's...
truly the best.
Ruu...
What am I supposed to do now?
Swear an oath before the final attack.
I understand.
Right, Hanayo-san and I took an oath, too.
It's the ultimate contract with the LRIG.
But didn't Tama lose her memory?
What do I say now, Tama?
It's true...
She doesn't think she can return now.
For the sake of her friends,
Ruu is even ready to become a LRIG.
Ruu thinks she needs to become a LRIG to save everyone.
Tama?
So, what do I say?
I... accept...
I accept.
the Laws of the Selector.
The Laws of the Selector.
Tama, thank you.
Aww, they don't have any moves left and they're still taking this long.
I'm bored to hell!
Come on, let them have a nice one!
Bloody Slash!
Tama.
Okay.
White Hope!
Wh-What? What is this?
Hey, what's going on here?!
It's... finally happening...
What's the matter, Yuzuki?
Yuzuki?
Yuzuki...
I don't have any regrets.
Because no matter what happens, this is the wish I chose.
I chose it...
No...
Ruuko won, so why...?!
The oath wasn't complete.
The last part of the oath—
"And now, a new Eternal Girl will be born."
Tama?
I can't turn you into a LRIG after all...
I can't say bye-bye to you...
I just don't want this!
Tama...
Wh-What?!
It's disappearing!
Tama! The oath!
Hurry, we need to say it again!
No... Wait!
It can't be!
Why is Iona-san...
Iona was ready to have her wish granted all this time.
She's already won more than enough Selector battles.
But you know, she lacked a certain
condition to have her wish come true.
A condition?
Right. That's why her wish was on hold.
I guess the condition's met now.
Yes...
My wish will come true now.
H-Hold on...
Tama!
Please, hurry!
Hurry and make my wish come true!
Tama!
I accept
the Laws of the Selector.
No...
Don't... You can't!
I need to bring them all back!
And now, a new Eternal Girl
will be born!
Don't!
I-Iona-san...?
U-Ulith...
Let's meet again, scum.
Ruuko...
Tama! Why—
Tama...
Isn't this the very best,
Ruu?
This tastes great!
Your white sauce is just too awesome, Grandma!
Ruu-chan is pretty late, isn't she...
You should just eat already.
No...
You know,
I want to be with Ruu-chan.
I want to be with you.
Tama...
Where are you, Tama?!
Tama!
That was...
my wish.
It's been a while, scum.
So, who wants to battle us first?
Is it because Tama was a bad girl?
You're my precious friend!
Selector spread WIXOSS.
Airing this Fall!