Who's the next target?
Frank Claude.
We have traced him down, at last.
Are you intending to make use of those unknown guys again?
The decision to send them for this job should have been finalized.
They're gonna make it too flashy.
That is necessary to make our organization known.
Their abilities shall become the hellfire,
and burn hell to a crisp.
There, we will build our own world.
You're hurt.
Just a scratch.
I will...
...kill.
To keep living,
I will kill.
I'm gonna get killed...
I will die if I don't run away...
I can't run from those dark eyes.
What should I do?
If I can't outrun it, I'll have to kill it.
If I don't kill, I will be killed.
Where am I?
What is this?
What am I...
Who am I?
I can't remember my name.
What is...
Japanese?
Travel bag...
This is me.
I'm a Japanese tourist...
And then...
Why?
Why can't I remember anything?
They might still be around.
The ones who attacked me.
Don't act on your own, Clau.
What's the point of me being your bodyguard, then?
Do you really want to get in my car?
I'll pass.
It'll be fine.
I'm just gonna take a look at the situation.
I can't let that man handle it all by himself.
That snake guy...
He's probably playing with such an exceptional toy right now.
Heh, makes me want to puke.
But he's quite important to our organization.
She's McGwire's favorite, after all.
That doll-san, that is.
Using whatever means necessary to complete their objectives.
That's how Inferno does things.
I know that.
But, Clau...
You're in a dangerous spot. You're too easily predicted.
Give me a call if something happens.
I'll keep that in mind, Lizzie.
If it's not because of that driving style of hers...
Situational Decision Rate, 074.
Visibility, 087.
To be able to reach these numbers just a few minutes after he woke up...
Like I said,
he's exceptional.
I'm gonna fall straight to hell, aren't I?
No,
I might already be there.
His perception just now...
That was his animal instinct.
The animal sense of instinct hidden under his reasons.
But this isn't enough. Not yet.
He still hasn't reached the level that I want.
It's your turn now, Phantom.
However...
Don't go overboard.
Understood, Master.
If you do not wish to die,
Those eyes...
come at me with everything you got.
The crisis in one's mind,
the crisis in one's life,
the crisis in one's existence,
The only thing that can fight them all is one's survival instinct.
Relying on morals and mercy,
or thinking that one's safety is guaranteed,
means to abandon one's life.
A weak kind of human.
And this world that has turned all of that into a way of living,
I really hated it.
Well, well. Miss McCunnen.
If I had known you would be coming...
How's the situation?
The results are about to show up, I assume.
Are you coming to observe?
Yes.
Come inside, then.
Who is she?
Why is she trying to kill me?
I don't even know the reasons.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know who I am.
I can't escape.
You have nowhere to belong.
If I can't run,
You, and I...
To kill...
or be killed!
It has begun.
Begun?
Please look closely.
Why?
Come at me with all you have!
If you don't want to die, that is.
I have nothing.
A past,
a future,
nor a life.
Even so, I...
...don't want to die!
Where should I go?
I don't even know where I came from.
I don't remember anything.
What should I do to be free?
What is... the freedom to choose who to kill?
Tell me...
Please...
Where is this?
I...
Who am I?!
Zwei.
You are...
I'm Ein.
You are Zwei.
Zwei...
That is your name.
Your name...
...is Zwei from now on.
Zwei?
What does that mean?
What is...
You are me.
I am you.
What do you think?
Don't you think he has quite a talent?
But that was an outstanding result.
The boy hasn't got proper training nor any basic strategical knowledge.
He was relying only on his basic instincts.
Furthermore, he even temporarily took Ein down.
That wasn't good, Phantom.
I'm sorry.
He's a genius.
He possesses talents which were triggered by the extreme predicament of his life.
He is truly...
...as if he was born to be one of the Inferno.
Even so, is that what he really wants?
It is not about whether an egg refuses to hatch,
nor about seed that refuses to bud.
It is not about what he wants.
So it's brainwashing that you're good at, huh?
It's flawless.
By using hypnosis and drugs,
we have sealed only the memory of his own identity.
Please do understand, Miss McCunnen.
We're being merciful.
He happens to be in such an unfortunate situation, seeing the crime scene.
Normally, he would have been killed as a witness.
But I wanted to give him another chance to live a fruitful life.
A single Japanese traveler, huh?
This could mean trouble, you know?
No one can trace his footprints anymore.
The secret is perfectly hidden.
Very well.
Scythe Master,
I'm leaving this boy to you.
Thank you very much.
Ein, and Zwei.
You should think more about what you call your pupils.
How much longer can you give me orders, I wonder.
Little miss.
I am the number one woman.
Ein.
You are the second man.
Zwei.
We are...
What are you doing?
That'll be all, Ein.
Go back to your post.
Understood, Master.
We are...
...a ghost that cannot exist anywhere.
We are no one.
Phantom.
Welcome back, Master.
Yeah. Where's the others?
Yes, they are resting now.
In the middle of the day?
What's going on?
You...
Phantom.
Inferno's ultimate assassin.
A title given to the organization's top sniper.
My ultimate masterpiece.
And...
...him too.
You're overdoing it.
I see.
That bastard's organization is over now.
With this, two of the five organizations in Las Vegas have been destroyed.
Gentlemen.
This is the beginning.
We will create an era with our own hands.
The era of Inferno.
We'll create it.
...a ghost that cannot exist anywhere.
We are no one.
Phantom.
You have already...
...become an existence that cannot live without killing.