When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
A Happy New Year to you!
For the first episode of the
year, we will start with...
Hayate the Combat Butler!
Annual New Year Hidden Talent Contest
"Hayate the Combat Butler! Annual..."
Actually, "First"...
"New Year Hidden Talent Contest"!
Is it all right that the host isn't Machaaki?
Looks like we're reusing the set from
"Burst of Laughter On-Air Battle".
And now, first up is...
Red Team, a live performance
on various instruments
and leaping through a ring of fire!
Hot! Hot!
10 points! 10 points! 10
points! 10 points! 10 points!
Next up is the White Team!
Foreign language comedy routine and
leaping through a ring of fire!
"Enough's enough!"
This is unreasonable! Impossible!
This is cruel! The logic is ill!
10 points! 10 points! 10
points! 10 points! 10 points!
Head Judge
A word, please, Head Judge.
It's so idiotic.
Are there only stupid shows
like this on during New Year's?
After all, they even say, "New Year's
food is good, but have some curry, too."
Oh, as I recall, we have
a new show starting today.
Indeed?
Gale Force Squadron
Hayate the Combat Butler
Giant
"Hayate the Combat Butler - Giant"!
Animation Produced by
Synergy SP
"Giant"? Does that mean
you're going to become big?
Special Skills
Photography: Eiichi Terada
Art: Toshiko Kaizu
Editing: Keiko Onodera
Color Coordinator: Kayo Ohno
That would be like that old show
that tried to get more viewers
Director: Keiichiro Kawaguchi
Animation Director: Takashi Uchida
and pointlessly gigantified
their normal-sized hero...
Storyboards:
Episode Director: Shinichi Watanabe
Shut up!
It's Silver Mask!
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
Happy New Year.
"Hayate the Combat Butler –
Giant!" is about to begin.
Wrong!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naive and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
New Year's Food is Good,
But Have Some Hayate, Too
On the night of New Year's Eve...
The year is about to come to a close.
How about going on the year's
first trip to a shrine?
What?
Staying cooped up at home, steeped in
manga, online games, and lame anime.
That is the proud, world-renowned way
that Japan celebrates New Year's!
Well, you have a point, but...
You've regained your memory!
Oh, right. I got swallowed up
by the Bartra Space-Time Current
and got flung all the way to Kujukuri!
Look, Diomitis, it's the dawn of mankind.
Come to think of it, this is
the year's first sunrise...
"To think the first sunrise I
saw with my destined partner
"was the first sunrise of the year...
"Oh, how romantic!"
That's not bad.
Songs change with the times and
the times change the songs.
Man, I guess this year is almost over.
A lot sure has happened since
I came to this residence.
Well, it's passed without mishap and
I owe it all to the Miss taking me in.
I should be grateful.
Wow, I feel embarrassed when you
say it so candidly like that.
What?!
Whoa! M-Miss?! Where did you come from?!
Or rather, what are you doing here?
Well, uh, it's nothing big, but...
Blush
I was thinking I'd kind of like
to see the Asahi (sunrise)...
Huh? But I only have a copy
of the Tokyo Sports here...
The UFO stories on the front page
pique my curiosity sometimes.
WHAM
I see, I see. That's the head that
comes up with these stupid jokes.
Pardon me...
Darn it, you just don't get it!
I'm saying I want to go see the first
sunrise on a pretty beach somewhere!
Just you and me!
Huh? What's the point in going to see that?
Shut up, you jerk! Quit
complaining and get ready!
Yes, ma'am!
Um, could it be that we're bicycling there?
Yes! We're keeping this a secret
from Klaus and the others,
so we can't go by car or chopper, right?
Uh, you said we were going to the beach,
but where are we specifically going?
Kujukuri Beach!
Ocean
Kujukuri Beach
What's wrong?
Um, even roughly speaking,
Nerima
it's at least 100km from this
mansion to Kujukuri Beach.
Roughly 100km
Wouldn't you be able to
make it in about an hour?
A-An hour would be...
I see.
Well, we just have to get there by
sunrise, so we can take it slow.
W-Wouldn't it still be better
to take Maria and the others
and make the trip with everyone?
Hahahaha
Taking a car or a chopper?
I am saying that I want to go
with you, just the two of us.
Or what? Do you have a problem
with being alone with me?!
Goodness, no!
Riding tandem on bicycles
is against the traffic laws,
but most of Nerima Ward is the
Sanzenin family's private property,
so it's not a problem.
This anime certainly puts
convenience above all else.
It's what's called "the adult circumstances".
But to think my parents foisted
off a debt of 150 million on me
and I almost got taken to an overseas
resort by "very generous people"...
It's hard to believe it really happened.
Because they really are
unbelievable situations.
Th-That's true.
But well, we were able to
meet thanks to that, so...
Y-Yes...
B-By the way, Hayate,
d-does this bicycle have
heating or something?
Pardon?
My legs are starting to feel chilled...
Th-That's a bit...
It looks like your plan to
ride tandem on a bicycle
in the middle of this winter night
to go all the way to the beach
was a bit problematic.
What?! It is not problematic!
If I had just instrumentalized my skirt more,
the plan would have been perfect.
Now, now, you're going to catch a cold.
We still have a long way to go,
so perhaps we should come up with
a new instrumentality project.
True...
This is the legendary diamond-pearl card,
which is one step above the
black card that has no limit.
Uh, but no matter how
amazing the credit card is,
only convenience stores and Don Quixote
discount stores are open at this hour.
W-Welcome.
Welcome!
No way! I mean, this is...
Takatan Department Store
...a super prestigious high
class department store!
It's not normally open at this hour!
Put it all on this card.
With pleasure!
BAM
Miss, wh-what is this?
You sure are ignorant. Don't you
know what a covered carriage is?
I mean, aren't these usually
drawn by an ox or something?
They even hitched it up for free.
Ox?!
Nagi? Nagi?
Where could she have gone?
And Hayate isn't here, either.
Oh?
There she goes again, reading manga
and leaving it lying around...
"The Romance of Kujukuri"...
Don't tell me...
"Shiwasu", the twelfth month...
It means that everyone is
busy at the end of the year
and that even teachers are running around.
And...
ZWINNNNNNGGGGG
...the butler-in-debt was also running.
Inertial drift!
For your information, this anime
is staying within the speed limit.
Ah! You're amazing, Hayate!
You are unsurpassed on the
Metropolitan Expressway!
Yes! At this point...
...no one can catch up to me
with my boosters at full power!
But is it all right for us to be bicycling
on the Metropolitan Expressway?
Ah! I'm glad I bought up the
Metropolitan Expressway.
Adult circumstances.
Yup, yup.
Passing signal?!
At night on the Expressway, this
indicates that the race is on.
H-Hayate...
I know. The miracle is still to come!
What shall we do, Maicule?
Chitt, I have faith in you!
Not a soul...
...shall be permitted to run ahead of me!
VROOOM
I can see time!
That's 600R, the high speed turn of death!
I'll make him disappear from my
rearview mirror with this turn!
Not that he has a rearview mirror.
The probability of going in at full
throttle and clearing it is 27.8%.
Chitt, I have faith in...
Maicule, please don't spill.
Can I make it?
Secret technique, ditch hooking!
Maicule, what do you want to do?! Maicule?!
All right, Chitt! Fire the rocket boosters!
This is madness! Or rather, you're an idiot!
Are you an idiot?!
Knight Foundation
Maicule?! Maicule?!
A single man will change the world!
Maicule!
Youthful mistakes are so hard to admit to.
This anime is totally staying
within the speed limit.
Ah! It's pitch black, but we're at the beach!
It's the beach! It's the beach!
I've reached my limit...
It looks like we'll be able to watch
the first sunrise together now.
It's the beach!
I-I'll go buy something
warm for the time being.
Sure. I'll be waiting right here.
It's the beach!
Wait, now that I think about it,
I don't have my wallet with me.
Here you are.
M-Maria!
Even for you,
going at such speeds with someone
riding in the back is dangerous.
P-Pardon me. I ended up going
just under the speed limit.
Well, we'll retrieve the bicycle and
that ridiculous covered carriage,
so please use that money to
get yourselves back home.
Thank you so much for everything.
Not at all. I'm the one who
should be thanking you.
You're doing wonderfully,
protecting and guiding Nagi.
Though, that's not to say
there aren't some problems...
No, I'm still far from such...
She seems happy since you came...
I also...
Oh, also...
Happy New Year, Hayate.
H-Happy New Year.
I look forward to another year with you.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Miss! It's almost sunrise!
Here you are. Red bean soup. And Happy New...
...Year...
Happy New Year,
Miss.
Shall we play a game of karuta cards?
(Karuta-asobi demo shimashou ka?)
Karuta cards, huh? What a drag.
(Karuta ka? Kattaru.)
On the night of New Year's day...
Somewhere along the way,
we got a lot of snow...
We got silvery landscape in no time at all!
Sakuya also called to say she would
be coming for a New Year's visit.
What? Saku is coming?
Before we get to that, why are you
the only one who's dressed up?
It's fine, isn't it?
We're not doing anything
else New Year's-like anyway.
New Year's...
People are experiencing heavy
snowfall all over the world...
Freakish weather...
We live in an era where we can't
remain complacent forever.
Mankind must rethink its
culture of mass consumption
in favor of the environment...
When you say that in a comfortably
heated room, playing a portable game,
you have zero credibility.
It's portable, so it's contributing
to the environmental cause...
Oh, dear! Is it a power outage?
Um, are you two all right?
Oh, Hayate. I'm fine, but Nagi is...
I-It got dark all of a sudden, so...
I see. The snow must have
taken down some power lines.
Normally, the backup generator
should kick in, but...
Maybe the breaker's tripped on the
backup generator in the other building.
The breaker will need to be reset manually.
Then hurry up and do something
about this breaker thing.
I'm going to die if it stays this dark.
Miss...
So, would you please do something about this
before the batteries run out on the
game she's playing to distract herself?
Roger that!
The time left is approximately 3 hours.
My mission this time is to restore power.
The target location:
the generator station, approximately
1km from the main house.
Whatever the case,
I haven't had such a butler-like job in ages!
I have to do my best!
Incidentally, there's a
blizzard raging outside.
ROOOOAAAARRRR
Holy...
I-It's blustering worse than I'd thought...
Even though we're in Tokyo... in Nerima...
Could this be what they call
"tsudere (snooty softy)"?
Earth sure is a "tsudere".
That would be what they call a "tundra".
Incidentally, a "tsudere" is...
W-Well, I guess I'll see how it goes anyway.
I am not going anywhere,
so please just don't pull that, all right?
Or it'll become an "Oh, dear!" situation.
Earlier, you said something
about Saku coming?
Oh, come to think of it, she hasn't shown up.
It'd be funny if she got
stranded out there in the yard.
No, not funny. Not funny.
B-But...
...I feel like I might really get
stranded out in this blizzard!
But this is for the Miss,
cowering in the darkness.
I must restore the power at all costs!
I can't give up!
I can't allow myself to give up!
Snow like this...
Like hell this snow's going to get me down!
Wait, this is a snowmaking machine!
And what are you doing out here?!
Ah...
"Wait, this here's a snowmakin' machine!"
Nice! That was a nice jab.
Don't tell me you've been out here
in this fricking cold just for that?
Well, somethin' like that.
"Nice jab!" What point
is there in doing that?
He's good!
Where are your butlers?
Oh, when I drew power for
this guy from the power line,
they said the lights went out in the
main house, so they scurried off.
This guy is what caused the power outage?
Sorry.
At any rate, you'll catch a cold
if you say out here forever.
Please get inside the residence quickly.
Well, I'd love to,
but which way's the residence?
We might seriously die, huh?
ROOOOAAAARRRR
At any rate, this is not
some snow-covered mountain!
Things will work out!
Please come with me.
What's this? Yer more
dependable than I'd thought.
And an hour passed.
ROOOAAARRR
Um, mind if I take back
everythin' I said earlier?
M-May I ask you to wait just a little longer?
What?!
A yeti?! It's a snowman!
This is perfect!
I'll go ask him for directions real quick.
A snowman may know the snowy roads well.
He was kind enough to tell me.
What?
I take back what I said 'bout
takin' what I said back.
He's done better than I thought.
Generator Station
This be the generator station.
My coat's drenched.
I know. We've literally "gotten wet".
Oh, it's taken longer than I'd thought,
so I need to hurry up and reset the
breaker and switch to the backup.
But man, this place is shielded from
the wind, but it's still mega cold.
Oh, so it's an independent
geothermal power generator.
It looks like there's a
hot spring here as well,
so perhaps it might be a
good idea to take a dip.
A hot spring? I...
Blush
Takin' a dip in a hot spring in a
place like this, just the two of us...
It'd be too embarrassin'.
Why would that be?
Guide Map
What was that for?
Shaddup, ya moron! That one
seriously ticked me off!
As I asked before, why?
Wanna go at it for another round?!
Hot Spring
"Zapping Bath"
Hey, c'mere for a sec!
As I said, what was that for?!
Shaddup!
P-Please stop!
Shut yer mouth!
How d'ya like that? Learn yer lesson yet?
I don't mean to keep repeating
myself, but what is this about?
I might not look it, but I'm still
the eldest girl 'round here,
so don't treat me too much like a kid.
Coming from someone who does things
like this without hesitation...
What d'ya say?! I'll show ya!
I was kidding!
I'm not treating you like a kid.
Huh?
Y-Ya aren't?
This situation's definitely not good...
I feel like I'm gettin' dizzy from the heat.
But what shall we do?
The breaker is located pretty far from here.
Drenched as I am, I might freeze
to death before I get there.
But I cannot leave the
Miss waiting any longer!
Sorry. Want me to come with, too?
No, I think that might not
exactly be advisable...
I mean, you are technically a girl...
Well, I'll be going then.
Oh, is that the waterproof cell phone
that Kimutaku's been advertising?
Oh, Makita? Is Kunieda there, too?
2 hours and 50 minutes
since the mission started.
5 meters left to the breaker room!
However, the drenched butler-in-debt
was on the brink of mortal peril.
This is bad...
I'm so cold, things are
starting to look blurry.
Maybe going naked would've
been better after all.
But that would be sketchy
in terms of your appearance.
I-I'm going to die at this rate...
But... just a little longer...
I'm so close to restoring
power for the Miss...
But I'm just... Miss...
Oh, dear! The flame in the lamp...
What?!
Don't tell me Hayate's...
Could something have happened to Hayate?
My Galadriel is dead!
As I suspected, this must mean...
I believe that's simply because
you weren't paying attention.
Oh, the lights!
Ah!
Which means Hayate is fine!
But Galadriel is dead.
I managed to reset the breakers somehow,
but I've got no strength left in me...
Oh, man. I'm so cold...
I can't take another step.
Miss..
Maria...
I was so... happy...
Hayate!
Ya can't give up! Get it together!
Sakuya...
I came to save ya.
You'll be fine now.
Look at how cold ya are!
Your hands are incredibly warm...
Ya hung in there real good.
I had the wrong idea 'bout ya.
Yer quite the go-getter, aren't ya?
Yes, but...
With it being winter and all, I'm
"sleet" and tired of the cold...
Or something like that.
Generator Station
Makita! Kunieda! We're
leavin' that moron here!
Roger that.
What?!
W-Wait! Sakuya!
Oh, the lamp...
Galadriel is still totally dead.
But I wonder if Hayate really is all right.
And thus, New Year's Day came to an end.
Next time, they will fight
against a sudden farewell.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Report!
Power Come Forth! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I'm Hayate Ayasaki.
Lots of new developments this time around!
The arrival of new enemies have certainly made things intense.
There's going to be a mysterious
new rival showing up next time.
The plan is for them to be good guys by the
final episode and help fight the great evil!
Miss, did you actually watch this episode?
It was nothing like that!
Oh, it wasn't?
The new cour is supposed to be full of
stories that fans of the manga will be happy to see!
I'm not sure how much I believe that.
Seeya!
Preview
Good morning!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Hey, now, if you get too absorbed
in your chat you're gonna be late!
S-something is different about Ms. Katsura!
Something about her is radiant...
Life is tender, and full
of sudden goodbyes, y'know?
You're being so stupid!
I don't care what happens to you!
Go die in a ditch, somewhere!
Next time, "Despairing Goodbye to the Teacher
~A Graduation Special"
Be ready to Jack On with Hayate
the Combat Butler next time!