When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Tralala~~ Sploosh!
Sploosh
"My name is Britney.
"As you can see, I am a fine,
totally unremarkable florist.
Sploosh!
"Once again, I have followed
the alluring fragrance of flowers
"and today, I've come all the way
to the Sea of Japan.
"Listening to the roar
of the crashing waves,
"I'm reminded of the magical kingdom,
my homeland, 3-chome in East Nakano.
"Whoops, I just accidentally
blabbed my secret. Bloody hell.
"I'm sure you've noticed,
"but as you can see, my true identity...
End of the Century
Legend Magical Destroy
Rising star
of the universe
Nagi Sanzenin
"...is that of a magical girl!"
Today, in commemoration of our 17th episode,
we're going to show you a full
30 minutes of manga that I drew!
A stunning comic-mation even greater
than "His and Hers" and "Cat-Eyed Boy"!
You'll see your fill of talent
that surpasses even that of
the super director of the SOS Brigade...
Please stop!
They'll get the wrong idea
and think we've been canceled!
Besides, what are we commemorating
at an odd number like 17?
Darn you! Do not mock 17!
In Episode 17, Amuro steals the Gundam
and leaves the White Base!
And Captain Okita collapses
in Episode 17 and has surgery...
W-Well, then,
please enjoy your regularly
scheduled "Hayate the Combat Butler"!
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
By the way, there's also a fan service
scene with Miss Sayla, too!
That's Episode 37!
Episode 17 was Miss Mirai!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
For You, I Will Mow Them Down
with Every Ounce of My Being!
The girl knows.
That there are some things
in the world that money can't buy.
DOOM
As for what happened, please use your
imagination based on her expression.
Miss, what happened?!
Wait... Whoa...
Th-This is...
A manga magazine?
It seems I lack life experience.
It seems I can't win any manga contests,
because I lack life experience.
End of the Century Legend Magical Destroy
H-Hmm...
Wh-What do you think?
It's my greatest masterpiece.
It didn't even make it as a finalist.
No matter how you think of it,
it's messed up, right?
Well, I suppose there may be a niche
for absurd gag mangas like this...
These are not absurd gags!
Are you saying the grandeur
of it is lost on you?!
I do sense the grand aura
of a space cadet...
I swear!
It's because of such bungling judges
that droves of precious, budding
new authors end up being crushed!
"Ultimately, in order
to draw entertaining manga,
"one must have rich life experience..."
Like hell new authors can grow
on vague advice like that!
It's all fine and good
to tell me this, but...
Well, it's sort of like a chronically
pathological thing for her,
so please don't pay it any mind.
What?
She draws a manga once every
several months and submits it.
I had no idea.
What is it?
Oh, no.
I was just thinking that
if it's for something she loves,
even the Miss will occasionally work hard
to put heart and soul into something.
Well, not that she ever
gets anywhere with it.
I see.
I sort of feel a bit sorry for her.
It's not entirely so bad.
It teaches her that there are problems
that money can't solve,
so I think that it's a good thing.
I see...
It's true, I feel like
I lack in life experience.
I have few friends, I don't go to school
much, nor do I play any sports.
And yet, I don't have to
worry about making a living
and things will work out,
even if I just laze about every day.
Truly, rushing headlong down the path
to becoming a useless member of society.
I-It's this privileged environment
that's at fault to begin with!
I have no experience like Nello
and Marco, who were super poor!
Or like Sara, who plunged from
the peak of happiness to rock bottom.
That's why I can't create
super powerful stories
that can move all of America to tears.
Wait, I know someone who likely
has abundant life experience.
What? What was I doing
when I was around 13 years old?
That's right!
I want to know how different
we are in life experience.
Hmm, when I was around 13 years old?
Let me think. At that time,
I was probably...
...doing things like working
as a professional mahjong bouncer.
Huh?
Professional mahjong bouncer...
A job like that of a bodyguard,
who plays mahjong to repel
Murmur... Murmur...
the "very generous people" who come
to pick fights with the establishment.
It is a dangerous occupation,
as you absolutely cannot lose.
Isn't that like, incredibly dangerous?
It wasn't that big a deal.
I was a strong player and
I was also good at cheating, after all.
The difference in life
experience is great indeed!
But I think you have abundant
life experience, too, Miss.
What?
You're only 13, but you've skipped
grades to be in high school,
and you live in this great big mansion.
These aren't experiences
you can come by so easily.
Y-You think so?
Incidentally, what else were you doing?
Let me think. What else?
I used to get award money
by winning new manga author contests.
So, just as I expected,
the difference in experience
is the decisive different in firepower!
Miss?
In that case, I'll do things
I don't normally do
and raise my experience level, too!
Do things you don't normally do
and raise your experience level?!
That's the spirit, Miss!
Use this as your springboard
to say good-bye to your reclusive life
and leap out into the world outside!
Rejected!
What?!
The things to be found outside the residence
will amount to no more
experience than Slimes!
What I desire is the kind of experience
you get from Liquid Metal Slimes!
I see...
That's why, as the top thing
that I ordinarily don't do,
I will help Maria with her work!
What? You're going to help me?
Yes. I will be of great use to you!
Ask me to do whatever you want!
Hayate!
Well, the Miss is finally motivated
to take the initiative, so...
Now, first things first,
I'll do what you always do
and begin by helping you
clean the residence.
Oh, wait, Nagi!
Here goes! Zephyrus Broom!
Oh?
That is not the yell used
for when you clean!
R-Right. I messed up there a bit.
But I'll manage somehow next time...
Take that!
Hayate!
Miss! Wait! Stop!
Hayate, there definitely are things
you need to experience to know.
What might that be?
Cleaning makes a mess.
A rare experience...
Yes, I've mastered cleaning now.
Come, we're moving on to the next thing!
Wait, Miss!
All right! Next up,
I'm going to master shopping!
Shopping?
But there are things in this world
that cannot be bought online
or on Yahoo Auction, you know.
Don't take me for a fool!
I'm going out to town
to run a proper errand!
Th-There are too many things...
This store has the greatest selection
of goods in this area, after all.
If the equipment store
in a role playing game was like this,
you wouldn't know what to buy anymore!
For starters, check
the freshness and the price.
Also, look for where it's from and
if possible, who the producer is.
I have no need of such complicated commands.
Oh, this is...
Hey, clerk.
Yes?
I've learned yet another
thing through experience.
What is it this time?
Sold to Ms. Sanzenin
If you go shopping,
the store ceases to exist.
I didn't know that before today, either.
All right, next, we'll go back
and tidy up the storehouse.
You're still going to do more?!
Wow, it looks like the legendary
Ark could be hidden in here.
The majority of what's in here
is pretty much like garbage.
Please! I'm sure they're
all valuable works of art.
Th-This is...!
See? I find it hard to believe that
such ugly portraits have any value.
True...
Yah!
Yah
Wh-Who's there?!
That's Rodin's "The Thinker"!
No, it's not! Head Butler,
what are you doing here?!
This is my relaxation spot.
When I have few scenes, I come here
to immerse myself in the world of art
and to reinvigorate myself.
No wonder we don't see you around much.
Okay, onto the next thing!
Please wait for me, Miss!
M-Miss, let me out!
It's dark! It's scary!
Hayate the Combat Butler!
The cat laid down.
(Neko ga nekoronda.)
Harumph! It'll be fine!
(Dafunda! Daijoubu da!)
Say, Hayate, what should I do next?
Let me think... I suppose that leaves
things like showing hospitality...
Showing hospitality? All right!
Oh, Miss!
Please wait! We don't
even have any visitors.
Oh, dear, oh, dear...
Isumi...?
Isumi!
Oh, Nagi... my dear Hayate...
What are you doing out here?
So this was your home.
No wonder things looked so familiar.
What?
The truth is, I was studying
in my room until just earlier, but...
My eraser fell from the desk and...
Wait for me!
I was looking for it in my yard
and before I knew it,
I had wandered over here.
You continue to get lost in the most
spectacularly original ways.
Or rather, I wonder if there's a wormhole
that connects to our yard.
But you've appeared at the perfect moment!
I will now treat you
to super VIP hospitality!
I wonder if the Miss will be all right.
You made the tea for me, Nagi?
Yes!
I took all the high end
tea leaves in the kitchen
and threw them in one after another
to make a Nagi Sanzenin original,
the Royal Premium Hyper-Gigamax
Blend, so it'll be crazy good!
Oh! The cup is dirty!
Pardon me, I'll go get another one!
Wait... Hayate?
A blend of Darjeeling, Blue
Mountain coffee, and brown rice tea!
On top of which, I can taste a hint
of Baby Star Ramen for some reason!
We can't possibly serve such an
"Oh! My Konbu Seaweed!" sort of tea.
H-How it is?
It is very delicious, Nagi.
R-Really?!
Hayate, it seems I have a talent
for showing hospitality!
I am happy for you, Miss.
All right! I'll practice hospitality
on an even greater scale
and increase my experience level!
What?!
Hayate
Please enjoy.
Th-Thank you.
1000 yen for a fried rice
omelette with lettering.
If I eat this, will I become
a full-fledged refined young lady, too?
Everyone, it's good of you to come.
Nagi?
What's with yer getup?
It's the worst-looking
cosplay in the universe.
This is not cosplaying!
This is life experience!
Huh?
Hey, what's this 'bout life experience?
The thing is, she said she wanted
to do things she normally doesn't
to increase her experience level.
I will now put my talent
for hospitality on full display for you!
I'll cook you a dish that's so delicious,
it'll make you melt down to the core!
Wait, she's gonna start makin' it now?!
Here goes Nagi!
Hey, can she really do this?
Pardon me, I must go see to something!
Sneak, sneak, sneak, sneak, sneak.
It tastes ultra bad!
I-If we serve this to the guests,
the Miss will end up being hurt!
I cannot leave things like this!
I-It's good!
This is good!
You are right, Young Sir.
A fusion of full-bodied flavor,
richness, and simplicity!
What depth there is to this flavor!
A mellow aroma like the land
bursting forth with life!
A mild mouth-feel, similar
to the embrace of the great wide ocean!
The ingredients result
in a nuclear reaction in your mouth
and create a Big Bang of taste!
Th-This is...!
This is splendid!
How splendid!
It's YUMMY!
It's yummy!
It's delicious.
Come on, now! Bring on the seconds!
Katsy, no going on a rampage!
You are so much trouble!
Bring on the sake, too!
And while you're at it, bring me money, too!
Hayate, everyone's enjoying the dish I made!
I'm happy for you, Miss.
Thank you for the meal, Hayate.
What?!
You're the one who really
cooked this, right?
Looks like I hit it on the nose.
It shows on your face so easily.
Th-This has to be a secret from the Miss!
I know.
It must be tough being a butler.
You have to work to make sure your
mistress doesn't get embarrassed.
Nagi, that was delicious!
R-Right.
Your hospitality was quite good.
Is that right?
I'm glad I came.
Say, Hayate...
Yes?
I feel like I understand a bit
of how you and Maria feel now.
What?
It's nice to do something for other people.
I also want lots of people to read my manga
and enjoy it like these people did.
Miss...
The truth is the Miss is a good kid.
I have to continue
to protect her innocent spirit.
Where's my seconds?!
Bring me my seconds or else!
Oh? Miss Katsura,
you still hadn't gone home?
This smell!
Ta-da!
I've discovered my seconds!
Oh! I went to such trouble to hide it!
Miss Katsura?!
Miss Katsura, please get a hold of yourself!
Hayate.
M-Miss...
Why is my dish sitting here, untouched?
What? O-Oh, come on!
Those people ate every
last bit of your dish earlier!
This is a failed dish that I made...
Liar!
Then what about my signature there?!
By Nagi Sanzenin
What?! Why did you have
to sign it like a manga?!
So what everyone ate earlier was
a dish that you made, wasn't it?!
Uh, um, that is...
So it is true.
Could it be that I haven't been of any use?
What?
Was I of no use to you or Maria
or anyone from the beginning?
No, that is hardly the case!
How do I put this? Everyone has
their strengths and weaknesses,
and not everything will go their way.
In other words, you mean to say...
...that I may not have
the talent to draw manga?
What?! No, I never...
It's not as if that thought
never crossed my mind!
It's just possible...
It's just possible, that there's
a one in a million chance...
A one in a billion chance...
A chance as unlikely
as the Earth exploding...
that I can't win those contests
because I don't have the talent for it.
Miss...
Miss!
I'm just... I'm just...
Are you all right, Miss?
Leave me alone.
I have no talent and
I'm not much help to anyone...
Not to worry.
Please take a look!
Thanks to all your help,
those two both have such
satisfied looks on their faces.
Dazed~~
Don't their eyes seem lifeless?
What shall we do about the cleaning?
This was my chance to get screen time.
You think I have no talent, too, don't you?
What?!
You do, don't you?!
You've won manga contests and
in your eyes, I have no talent for it.
That's what you want to say, right?!
You do have talent, Miss.
What?
I mean, you've written many works
of manga and submitted them, right?
Yes...
There are a lot of people who never
even finish drawing one work
and fail to see the project through.
But when it comes to something you love,
you try to do your best
without losing heart.
You have a talent called passion!
A talent called passion?
Yes, I guarantee it.
I understand, Hayate!
I'll try and take a chance on my passion!
That's the spirit, Miss!
Besides, it's possible that your manga
are just too sophisticated.
Too sophisticated?
Yes!
Perhaps the richness
of your experiences is too great
for people to easily appreciate
how interesting your work is.
Th-That makes sense!
So, if I tone things down a bit...
That's right! Then next time,
you will surely win!
All right! Then I guess
I'll work hard at it one more time!
Please do, Miss!
"Black Sega Saturn?!"
"That's the surefire way to save
Earth in the 8th dimension.
"All that remains is to win
in the music contest.
"The 4th Space God Communication
Ticket Vending Vessel we need for that
"has already been successfully
bid on in Yahoo Auctions."
Man, it's as sophisticated as ever...
The next new author award
is as good as mine now.
Y-Yes...
Thus, the butler-in-debt's life
experience and suffering continue.
Next time, a dragon and a hamster
will meet in the clash of the century!
Or so we thought, but due to
the convenience of the rotation,
we have a swimsuit episode.
Notebook
Nagi
So exciting, so thrilling.
That is my Nagi.
That cured the stiffness in my shoulders.
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful,
it'll be clear again tomorrow
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
SIGN: Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Hello, I'm Yukiji Katsura.
Miss Katsura, what are you doing here?!
Well, I figured I possess
greater adult charms than Hinagiku
and that people might enjoy
my appearance somewhat more.
I don't know about that...
Besides, the boys and girls who are fans
of Hinagiku won't buy the DVDs!
You really should target single men over 20!
Miss Katsura, advertising
within the show is forbidden!
How naïve of you, Ayasaki!
I want people to buy the "Hayate
the Combat Butler" DVDs...
You're panicking way too much, Ayasaki.
Hey, Sis!
Preview
Next time, it's the summer festival,
the highly anticipated swimsuit episode!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
A luxury resort island in the tropics,
Hakuou Island and those
who go there see... see... see...!
Welcome to Hakuou Island.
I am this island's
in-house butler and manager,
Schmidt Offenbach.
I shall take it upon myself to create
happy summer memories for you.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"The Rare Cards Are Swimsuits".
The Rare Cards Are Swimsuits
I will be talking more than usual as well.
Now, how to fight through this...