Just because you couldn't get a customer, you didn't have to drink so much.
I always come to pick you up.
A service much appreciated.
You're such a reliable little sister.
Jeez.
Judy!?
Judy!!
Why?
Why?!
Is this where Judy Devens died?
Who are you?
Everyone called you Phantom.
I heard about it from Judy's friend.
You're the one who has been killing gang members all over America.
So you're a real assassin, huh?
You're an assassin, aren't you?
The Assassin, Phantom.
Yeah, I am.
Cal...
Please kill everyone with this.
The people who were there in the alley yesterday, the ones who fired guns,
and those who were supposed to receive this money.
Kill everyone who killed Judy without exception.
Will you do it?
Judy, I'm Phantom's acquaintance now.
He will definitely slay your killer...
...with those five million dollars.
Cal.
Five million dollars isn't enough, to be honest.
I see.
However, the rest of the payment isn't much more.
You can earn it by yourself.
What should I do?
Be my assistant for a while.
Awesome!
Hey,
does being your assistant mean...
...I can watch when we avenge Judy?
But before that happens, there's something you need.
Did you choose?
Wait a sec.
Just pick the one you want the most.
But I want all the clothes here equally.
If I were to choose one, I would have to discard the rest.
Don't worry.
We won't do this only once in our lives.
If you want something else as well,
I'll take you here some other time.
Really?
Yeah.
So just choose what you want to wear today for now.
Okay.
Umm, then...
Hey, hey. Is it cute?
Does it look good on me?
Yeah, it does.
This is the first time I've worn such light and smooth clothing.
Wait a second.
After I finish cleaning up, I'll start cooking.
Why are you doing this?
Because this place is dirty as hell.
Well, no problem.
An assassin who cleans up...
...sounds ridiculous, right?
Leave the chores to me.
Alright.
I have to earn what's not covered by the five million, right?
Say, Reiji. Do you have a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
I see.
Yeah.
Just like me.
Have your parents passed away?
No idea.
I ran away from the worst father there ever was.
And Judy found me.
If she hadn't, I'd probably be dead by now.
So that's why you said you're her sister?
Yes.
She was the only family I had.
But now she's dead.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What should I do now that Judy is gone?
Where should I go?
What should I do?
I don't know anything.
I didn't know.
Even death comes in many forms.
Cal.
Cal, hold out your arm.
What is it?
Today's reward.
This is...
Thank you, Reiji!
I'll cherish it.
I'll cherish it forever.
All the actors have assembled.
Playing her petty tricks, Claudia tried to manipulate me...
...and now crafts yet another scheme.
Her partner in crime is Godou Daisuke,
seeking to encroach upon Inferno's top echelons.
Wisemel unearthed the conspiracy and is trying to stop it.
A new actress has entered as well.
I will create the grandest stage.
Alright then.
It will get hectic.
Ein.
Is he Judy's killer?
Possibly.
At the very least, his organization.
Let me be there.
There he is!
There's someone behind the water tower.
Your face...
Reiji?
Let me see it!
You bastards!
Don't, Mr. Godou.
Huh?
That startled me.
I'm...
...with you...
Reiji!
Did you get hit?
No, it's just a scratch.
Reiji, you idiot.
Why did you do that?
I just wanted to confirm his identity.
You idiot!
You did great, spotter.
He was Judy's killer.
You've had your revenge.
Mission accomplished.
Good.
Move to route C and await further orders.
Yes, Master.
Hey, I heard a rumor...
...saying that Isaac of the Bloodies died.
That's right.
Then it's over...
My revenge.
I see.
By the way, how did it go?
Training me into an assassin, I mean.
If it's fine with you, can I help with other assassinations too?
The killing... is over.
It's over.
Then I'm just a nuisance now?
I wonder.
But...
I do have need of your cooking skills.
You can be a cooking maid for a while.
Really?
Yahoo, I get to be a maid.
I've always wanted to try being a maid.
Maid uniforms are soo cute!
Reiji!
What's wrong?
I... want to be your assistant.
Cal, that's...
I understand.
Your feelings about not letting me be an assassin, I mean.
You understand the sorrow of being an assassin.
Cal, you have so many paths you can walk.
You can be anything.
Why must you become an assassin?
Reiji, do you hate being an assassin?
Yeah.
Then, do you hate yourself?
Yeah, I hate myself.
I became a killer and can't stop being a killer.
I really hate myself.
But, Reiji...
I'm already broken.
Do you want to be like me?
I-I'm sorry, Reiji.
I...
Cal, I said too much.
Sorry.
But I told the truth.
I don't know how many have died because of me.
If I were not in this world, they would be alive.
They could return to their lovers and family.
It's not your fault.
If you hadn't killed, someone else would have.
It's not so simple.
Then, do you wish to kill?
Did you kill because you wanted to?
Do you like to kill?
You're different, aren't you?
But, Cal,
once you kill someone, the entire world changes.
Even the sceneries you see...
...and the sounds that reach your ear...
...will change.
The way you are now...
You won't be able to accept kindness any more.
I don't want you to be like that.
This place was not meant for you.
You shouldn't come over to my world.
But...
But you will always stay in that world, won't you?
If I step into your world, I can be beside you.
Cal...
I don't want to be separated.
I want to stay beside you.
To be useful for you.
I want to be...
...together with you.
So that's how it is.
I...
...wanted to return.
I could be with you then.
It's okay.
I'm going.
I will come to your side.
Let me go.
Let me go back...
...to Cal's world.
Reiji.
I'll be beside you.
Definitely.
Definitely, won't I?
A job at such a late hour...
I might be back late.
Go to sleep without me.
I'll stay up.
I picked up an old video recorder this afternoon.
I want to see if I can repair it.
You could just buy a new one.
That's a waste of money, the recorder might still be usable.
Still usable, huh?
I guess you're right.
I hope you return soon.
Yeah.
It's a promise then.
I promise.
Hooray, it works!
Hm...
Is the video rental store still open this late?
Reiji.
Reiji!
Don't go in.
It's dangerous here.
But, Reiji is... Reiji is...
Reiji!!
Reiji...
You will come back, won't you?
You promised, didn't you?
Liar.
You said you would never leave.
You said we would be together.
Exactly.
He is a liar.
You were being tricked the whole time.
Who...
...are you?
In these times, you can cry.
Now we can be like in the days of old.