so ra no wo to
The brilliant glow of this sky, does it carry right into your heart?
The melody you heard in your dream, it plays like the silence
Even if your hands are still far from that dream,
Come now and remember that kindly voice
Someone was there singing for you, the happiness they sang about
Sound of the sky, echo on high, break through that overwhelming sadness
Everything that shines in your eyes
Is part of the real world
Even your tears can't leave you here to stay forever
In this gentle light pouring down onto you, play tomorrow's song
There we go.
It sure feels like fall.
One Typhoon Passes - What You Really See
Oh, so your dad was a tankman?
Right. He was part of the platoon that led over a thousand civilians and soldiers out of Wardenburg when it was under siege
with just six Type-2 Millipads.
A legendary hero during that legendary escape!
That's amazing.
Isn't it?
And after he received a life-threatening injury in battle, he met my mother who was an orderly at the hospital he was sent to!
And you were born out of their love,
right, Kureha?
That's right!
Do I look like a potato to you?
My, what a wonderful potato she is!
You raised them very well, Kanata.
We can probably give some to the people in town.
And Klaus should be coming soon.
Should we give some to him as a gift?
Is he really coming?
You really love Klaus, don't you Kureha?
It's not that I like him,
I just have a lot of respect for him.
Rio...
Wow! She can even play it like this!
That's my Rio!
Yeah...
The wind is starting to pick up.
The weather might be taking a bad turn.
Should we stop here for today?
Okay!
Okay.
Noël, you too.
I mean it.
Don't you think Rio's been acting strange lately?
What part?
Like her trumpet-playing.
Isn't it wonderful? It's so smooth!
Like she's feeling blue.
She never did like making small talk.
But... Right! Dinner!
Wasn't that tempura delicious?
Yes! The potatoes were so steamy!
Wait, not that!
Here you are, Rio. Eat it while it's hot.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Really? That's good.
Bell peppers!
She was practically wolfing them down!
Rio ate them?
Right!
No matter how finely you chop them, she seeks, finds, and removes every last piece!
Rio ate them!
That... might mean something.
Wait...
Is this Klaus?
Right! It's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Klaus!
On his left breast, he has a tattoo of the insignia of Platoon 481,
the glorious Wolf Head!
Doesn't he look amazing? You can't have it.
I don't think you have to worry about it.
When the Commander looked down, it was just us worrying, after all.
And...
We're talking about Rio,
the cool, stylish, and beautiful.
Right.
I'm sure she just got over her fear of bell peppers and ate them.
You really love Rio, don't you Kureha?
I've always admired her, after all!
I admire her too, but...
What do you think, Noël?
Look out!
It's time for Noël to sleep.
There's no helping her. I'll lend her half of my bed.
Kanata, take that side.
Okay!
The fire for the bath.
You forgot to put it out.
Sorry. I forgot all about it.
Looking like you've got everything under control and forgetting one thing is the best part about you.
But you've been forgetting too many things lately.
Sorry.
Are you regretting hanging up on your father?
We can't do anything about it now.
I'll cover whatever mistakes you make.
At least try to be be a cool mentor in front of them.
Is it the wind?
Doesn't sound like it.
Sorry to come in the middle of the night. Class-one priority.
Who is it addressed to?
Platoon 1121. Master Sergeant Rio Kazumiya.
Get the receipt.
Major, please come inside for the night.
You won't be going anywhere in this weather.
Even if you're the Desert Wolf.
I told you not to call me that.
I'm sorry.
How about some hot tea and a bath as an apology?
We appreciate your diligence in completing your mission in this typhoon.
I'm sorry we only have leftovers from last night, but please do eat.
You should have woken me up when Klaus got here!
These are good! Delicious even after it's cold!
The bell peppers were raised very well too.
Do you really think so?
I picked them, and I fried them!
You'll make a good wife someday.
Is that the latest newspaper?
Yes. The Major brought it here for us.
The peace treaty?
It looks like the conferences still aren't going smoothly.
Neither side is making any compromises.
Things would be completely different if Princess Iliya were still alive.
Princess?
Iliya?
Wait, you can't not know who she is! The Hero of Binnenland!
The first daughter of Archduke Arkadia!
The Goddess of Victory of the Helvetian Army,
a tankman as legendary as the Desert Wolf, Major Klaus!
Kureha, you know...
You all here?
We've got an emergency.
Rio! Rio!
What's all the ruckus?
One of the kids at Yumina's church hasn't been seen since morning.
Help us out.
What?
Sister Yumina, who went missing?
Seiya...
Sound of the Sky
The river's water has risen quite a bit.
The fields downstream haven't been harvested yet.
If the dam breaks, they're all gone.
I'm not familiar with the city.
Show me the way, Kureha.
Yes, sir!
I am so very sorry.
I only took my eyes off him for a second...
Search and rescue is part of our duties.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
Seiya!
Amazing.
The water is so rough...
If he fell in there...
Seiya!
What are you doing?
You!
You know something, don't you.
You came out here because you know where he is.
Tell me! Where is Seiya!
The field.
Field?
Eggplants.
They're Sister Yumina's favorite.
So we all saved our allowances to buy seeds...
Seiya...
Where did you plant them?
What the hell are you doing?
In a place like this in the middle of a typhoon?
I'm protecting these eggplants!
What are you thinking? Don't you understand?
We're risking our lives for you!
You decided to come here yourself! No one asked for your help!
What did you say?
That's enough out of you!
Listen up. Kids without parents have to think harder than other kids.
If you cause trouble for people, you know who they'll blame?
It's not just you.
Yumina.
They'll go after your Sister too.
Kureha...
I'm an orphan too. I know.
Now then. Let's head back.
But...
And you still feel like whining?
Just wait.
You come to value things that you raise from nothing as much as your own life.
Once eggplants are this big, you can eat them.
They'll taste amazing if you pickle them.
Thanks, mister!
Major?
Seiya has started climbing back up.
Major, go on ahead.
N- No. You go ahead.
I'll take up the rear.
Yes, sir!
They're both safe. Thank goodness. But...
Now there's no way for them to climb back up.
The situation... is grim.
Thank you, sir.
The situation has gotten worse,
but you're here, Major.
I'm sure you'll find a way out.
No...
What? Did you say something?
No.
Listen up. No need to fear!
Right now, Miracle Klaus is here!
Yes, sir!
The ground is starting to collapse.
The water's breaking down the soil...
Dammit! This is why I hate kids!
Kids who can't listen should just be tied up and locked in a dark room!
Rio!
Nothing will come from panicking!
Those three are always watching you.
Sorry... I went too far.
B- But they'll figure something out, right?
They call Klaus a miracle worker, right?
No.
He isn't the Desert Wolf or Miracle Klaus.
They just happened to have the same name and look similar.
When they first met, Kureha got excited and decided he was.
You know how Klaus is bad with words.
He never found a way to tell her, and so...
But...
Right now, we have to find a way to rescue a courier
with only a long service history and an aspiring soldier
without a shred of experience from that ledge.
Throw them a rope.
There aren't any anchors above them.
They're too far away to throw a rope from here.
If there were a way to throw a rope over there...
I have one.
When I first met you,
I thought that maybe if my father were still alive, he would be like you.
I tell people about him like I knew him well,
but I actually heard it all from other people.
I don't really know much.
He died before I understood anything at all.
Kureha...
Left... At attention, signal?
The Takemicaduchi!
Halt!
How is it, Noël?
Anchor-use linear coil now operational.
Targeting system, E-7 to F-5 activated.
Initializing targeting system.
It can do it.
Wire anchor, standby to fire!
Kanata, do it!
Yes, sir!
It's coming.
I'll protect you just like your father would if he were alive!
Yes, sir.
Major.
Standby! Fire!
Here!
Kureha!
Major!
Reel in the anchor! Full speed!
You know, Kureha...
I'll tell you now that we made it...
I'm...
You're exactly what I thought you were.
The man I admire most.
The blue sky after a typhoon passes?
So you played the part the whole time.
Frankly, I'm surprised.
Never thought you had it in you.
When I looked into those eyes, shattering Kureha's dreams frightened me more than death. She believed in me.
That's probably how I managed.
In the end, I'm just a coward.
That's not true at all! You were wonderful, Klaus!
Listen up, young lady.
What someone watching sees and what the person front and center feels are completely different things.
The lenses we call admiration are always out of focus.
Someday, someone will see you through those lenses.
You'll know how it feels.
Can't you at least stay until Kureha wakes up?
Mind telling Kureha something for me?
This baby's the best life-threatening injury I've ever had!
Love and friendship - put these feelings together
And sing of how important they are
I was so happy that I cried
It hurt so bad that I laughed
But that all just goes to show that I'm alive
Let's just walk it slowly
Everybody singing!
Just tell me a bit of what you think
You're just my friend!
Love and friendship - even though they might waver
I know, you know, little happy
I want us to echo on forever
Can you hear my precious note?
All these words that there are can't even describe it
Our harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony
Next time: Departure - When the First Snow Falls