Don't make me laugh!
A brat like you, a debt collector?!
Well, whatever.
You're in luck.
I'm on a winning streak today.
That covers seven
interest payments. Take it and scram.
Okay, let's get started again...
Hold it.
Huh?
That wasn't the agreement.
Mr. Sugi told you to pay
him in person every day.
Huh!?
This is about more
than just paying interest.
--Don't give me your bullshit.
--Hey, kid!
Screw with me and I'll split your
head open and bleed you dry!
Pick up the money.
You little..!
No one mouths off to me!
I'll say it again...
What?
Pick up the money!
Save the tough guy act for after
you apologize to Mr. Sugi in person!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we couldn't cry
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where hopes and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga, Chandy10
We fight this fight forever more
Script/Editing:
Chandy10, Kanra
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find that place we’re not alone
So, what can I do for you?
Could you tell us where Turtle--
I mean Noboru Maeda-- is?
I'm afraid I can't.
I don't know who you are...
--Listen, old man!
--Mario!
I beg you!
Please, won't you tell us?
We need to take him to the hospital.
It sounds like this is important...
He's over in Mishuku,
collecting some money I lent.
Collecting money?
With any luck, he'll be back soon.
He's dealing with a
rather vicious sort, though...
I've agreed to lend him money if he
can successfully collect the loan.
Money? For what?
For his family.
That's what he told me.
How much would it cost to make
your little dream come true?
Could it be, that Noboru...?
--I'm going to Mishuku!
--Wait! I'm coming too!
No, Lilly! You heard him!
We're dealing with--!
Don't be stupid! He's doing this for me--!
Turtle...
Hey. Walk faster.
Right...
Oh...
Mario... Lilly...
What are you guys doing here?
What do you think? You suddenly...
Hey! What's the matter, Lilly?
Why the gloomy--
Oww...!
Lilly? Hey...?
Idiot...
Idiot..!
H-Hey, now! What's going on?
She had cried out of
sadness and frustration before,
but never out of happiness, until now.
Lilly had always struggled
to survive on her own
in this world devoid of
kindness and compassion...
But Turtle considered her family now...
He risked his life for her...
Lilly couldn't stop her tears.
Yes... It was very nice
of you to see me again.
Yeah, right. Nice, my ass.
Oh!
Kid almost bit it off!
O-Okay! I'll go! I'll go
pay the interest! Just let go!
It's not funny! That's one hell
of an animal you picked up!
It's no wonder them call him "Turtle"!
--Let's go!
--No! I refuse to get a check-up!
"The next day"
--Knock it off, Turtle!
--Shut up! Let go, Mario!
The doctor already said it was a cold!
I'm perfectly fine!
Please, Noboru!
You need to get tested.
You were in the atomic blast, after all.
Mario! You told her!
Listen, Turtle. You told Mr. Sugi
you need money for your family.
You were talking
about Lilly, weren't you?
But do you know what she was doing
while you were risking your life for her?
What do you mean?
She had to put up
with some terrible things
to get the hospital here
to take a look at you.
No, you were the one who did.
I didn't do anything.
Look, Turtle.
Lilly's in the same boat as you.
She can't stop worrying about you.
She thinks of you as a little brother.
If you're family, then you
have to listen to your big sister.
Sister...
Right, Lilly?
Hmph! I don't remember ever having
such an unreasonable little brother!
Okay! Let's go!
Jeffrey!
You came to see us? Thanks.
Noboru Maeda, yes? I'll be your
interpreter today, so you can rest easy.
O-Okay.
Okay, Mario. I'm heading out now.
Huh? Where are you going?
Just some minor business.
I leave the rest here to you!
Lilly!
Mario...
Mario. You really gave up boxing?
I know a good trainer.
If he can take a look at you, your fist might still be of some use.
How about it? You wanna go for another shot?
Listen, Jeffrey...
I don't understand a thing you're saying.
What?
All done.
How'd it go?
They said to come back in a week,
when they'll have the results.
Oh.
--Let's go.
--Yeah.
See you later, Jeffrey.
I had fun boxing.
--Where's Lilly?
--Said she had stuff to attend to.
Huh?
See you tomorrow.
Can I help you?
If not, I'll be on my way.
That child...
Please don't lend him--
Noboru-- any money...
He doesn't need it anymore.
I'm going to disappear from his sight.
So please don't give him
any more dangerous work.
I just need to go away.
I don't want to burden him.
Family...
Is that really how a family works?
I will lend him the money.
I gave him my conditions, and he fulfilled them.
This agreement is between the two of us.
But, it's for..!
It's none of your concern,
even more so if you're about
to disappear from his sight.
Good night.
Wait!
Would you...
Would you be willing to buy me?
Oh?
"One week later"
"The results of last week's tests
show nothing out of the ordinary.
Nothing requiring treatment was found.
However, we can't rule out the possibility
of future after-effects of the atomic blast.
Recommend regular tests from now on."
That's great, Turtle! What a relief!
Why the stern face? You should be happy!
How can you act so carefree?
Huh?
I'm talking about Lilly!
She's been gone for a week now...
Where could she be!?
Anyway, let's go.
--Huh? Where to?
--To see Mr. Sugi.
You promised to tell him about
your test results, remember?
Huh? Oh, yeah...
I see! I'm glad to hear it!
Well, here you are.
Thank you...
But I don't need it anymore...
Hey! Is our tea ready yet?
Coming right up!
L-Lilly!?
I heard the good news about
your test results! That's a relief!
You've really taken to your new job, Lilly!
I guess so!
What's going on here?
What's going on here, Mr. Sugi!?
Hold on, Turtle...
You old pervert!
You bought Lilly, didn't you!?
Noboru!
I came to you for help so she
wouldn't have to do this sort of thing!
You acted friendly-like and
tricked her into doing this..!
You're too old to buy women anyway!
--Calm down, Turtle!
--Shut up!
Mario! You were in on this too!?
Wh-What?
What? What are you laughing at!?
Sorry, Turtle! Don't get mad!
Your reaction was just so
close to what I expected...
I'm sorry, Noboru.
I'll explain everything now.
I came to see Mr. Sugi
the day of your check-up.
Would you be willing to buy me?
If you buy me, Noboru won't
have to go through with this.
So, please...
You truly don't understand how he feels.
He risked his life so you
wouldn't have to resort to such work.
Come with me.
I told Mr. Sugi everything after that.
About how I had made a living before...
About how I milked money from
that army officer to start my own shop...
And how he ran off with it all...
As I talked, I started to realize
how much I despised myself.
You should thank that military officer.
Thank?
Even if you had started
a business with that money,
you would have been
drowning in debt before long
and stripped of everything you have.
You can't be serious...
A business is not something
to be approached lightly, Miss.
Then, what do you suggest I do!?
What else is there for me to do!?
Having a house this
large makes it difficult
for an old man to
properly clean on his own...
I can offer you 15,000 yen a month.
Huh?
You can work as a live-in maid.
Spend a year or two here
to learn and understand
what it means to work and
what it means to run a business.
Noboru Maeda is still young,
but he has a good grasp
on what a business entails.
By the time you
master running a business,
the 300,000 yen I lent
will have grown significantly,
probably even enough
to open your own shop.
So, you're a live-in maid?
Yes.
Mr. Sugi! I'm sorry about
the terrible things I just said!
Please take good care of Lilly!
Noboru...
I'll borrow this money.
Tomorrow, I start
working hard as a 1% lender!
One more drink..!
Man, you drink too much...
But I guess it's a real relief after
your tests came back negative
and finding out Lilly's okay.
Why does Mr. Sugi live alone
in such a big house anyway?
I take it you're wondering why
I live alone in such a large house?
Yes...
Because of family.
Are these..?
My wife has already passed on,
but I built this house for our sons.
I haven't been sent their remains,
and their war buddies
didn't see them die, either.
So they will be back someday.
I have faith that they will.
Booze..!
Man, you're a lost cause.
Knock it off, will ya?
Mario...
Noboru really is in good health, right?
Yeah, I think so.
But if it ever takes a turn for the worse,
we'll make sure he survives.
I'm gonna earn a ton!
Okay, we know.
--I'll carry him now, Mario.
--Huh? No, that's okay. He's not...
I want to.
Okay.
A heavy load for one person
becomes lighter when carried by several.
Lilly, having experienced family ties
for the first time in her life,
decided to live from now
on for herself and for Turtle...
Thank you, Noboru...
same ta manazashi
What could I keep watching over
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on flying
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it; its now
a far off distance
A dream that can't be abandoned.
Mario bets everything on
a minute chance, and then...