I wonder if everyone's already asleep...
Tomorrow's the day...
It really feels like the whole school's pumped up.
I have to make good use of my time.
Let's see...
The Quiz Club starts from 1pm...
A shougi tournament? I don't know about that...
Oh! I'm definitely seeing the cooking competition.
Tomorrow's the big day!
Tomorrow, huh?
Please bless us with good fortune for the next three days,
that we may get over that mountain.
Mazui Presents
Hyouka
It's time for the cultural festival!
Practically Piled to the Ceiling
Morning.
Hey.
You're up early, Sis.
The cultural festival starts today right?
Yeah.
And you've got problems already, don't you?
How'd you know?
Just a hunch.
It's a tradition in the Classics Club never to have a cultural festival without a problem.
Don't make annoying traditions like that.
At least give me something to fix it with, Senp—
Here.
I'll give you that.
Should I thank you for this or what?
By the way, it's out of ink, and the tip is broken.
Don't give your trash to me!
You're going to be late.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll come check it out if I'm bored!
No, don't!
It's the cultural festival, Houtarou!
Looks like it.
You look the same as always.
And you look excited.
Of course!
It's the Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival, with all the clubs and everything!
Oh, isn't that Mayaka?
I'm guessing that outfit is for the Manga Society.
I guess she's on shift first.
You have something planned, too?
Well, I'm part of the Sewing Club, too.
I'll go poke her a bit.
Hey, Mayaka.
Morning.
Those clothes look good on you.
Stop it.
So, what kind of cospl—
Don't say that word in public.
Got it.
Then what are you dressed as?
Frol.
Frol?
Frolbericheri Frol?
I'm putting the gloves on later.
What's in the big bag?
Just a little something.
That sounds suspicious.
Are you with the Manga Society all day?
Yeah. I'm on the floor all day.
And at a time like this...
Well, no point thinking about that now.
We can't change the past.
Now this is a cultural festival!
Yeah.
I heard it was huge, but this is way bigger than I expected!
What's this? It's really well-made!
It really is.
It's bright.
Too bright.
Wow.
Alright! Let's do this!
Guess I'll take my leave here.
Sewing Club?
For a bit.
But I'll be up real soon!
It's quiet.
Yeah.
Don't let it bother you.
Satoshi might not mind, but if you keep this up, Chitanda is going to get curious.
I know that.
Good morning, Oreki-san, Mayaka-san!
Morning, Chii-chan.
It's finally time!
Yeah, it is.
Let's try our best!
Sure.
But I don't think that's going to help.
Think of it this way:
We don't know if trying our best will help,
but we do know that if we don't try our best, it won't help!
How right you are.
I'll buy some of them!
That's not what I meant!
But it was me who placed the order...
How many copies did we plan to order?
30 copies.
How many did we actually receive?
200 copies.
Galaxy!
My Saturn!
So you're finally here.
Good morning, Fukube-san.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Don't worry, it hasn't started yet.
I'm really sorry, everyone!
I didn't check the message from the print shop...
Everyone makes mistakes.
Don't say that with that outfit!
It's nothing to get depressed over.
We're all the same.
Don't say that in that outfit!
That's right. I should have checked it as club president.
Well, I just handed them the manuscript and didn't ask anything either.
It's a shared responsibility for the whole Classics Club.
Yes! That's right!
Okay.
Looks like you finally get it!
Stop talking in that outfit!
We don't have much time before the opening ceremony.
Does anyone have any ideas for selling as many as we can?
How much are we selling them each?
200 yen.
That's pretty cheap already.
The only other problems are the lack of branding power our club has and our location.
Which means that the first things we should do are advertise ourselves and find a better place to sell.
You mean we could make another stand?
I was only thinking about how to lead customers here...
That's a wonderful reversal in perspective, Oreki-san!
It's not really a reversal of anything...
But do you think we can get permission for that after the festival starts?
Well...
What do you think, Executive Committee?
I don't know if they'd give us special treatment like that,
but we could try asking the Executive Committee President or the Student Council President directly.
Who's the Executive Committee President?
You should at least read the brochure.
Here, look.
First I've seen it.
I wish you could have noticed my trick.
What about it?
Just look. Doesn't it stand out?
The Classics Club is the last in the whole line of clubs.
I made sure that they put us here.
The Executive Committee organized the brochure, after all.
That's amazing!
I'd call it an abuse of power.
It's fine.
If you want to meet the president, go to the meeting room.
Can't you ask him for it?
Well, I suppose I could,
but I'm not very good at negotiation.
Really?
Maybe Chitanda could do the negotiations while I act as support?
Thank you very much!
Okay. Let's do that.
She's doesn't sound exactly thrilled to do it.
Alright!
But more importantly, I want us to do some serious advertising!
Is that why you're wearing that?
That's just one part of the plan.
I have other plans, too!
Does that mean you have something in mind?
We can enter all sorts of contests and events in the cultural festival under the name of the Classics Club.
If we leave a good track record, everyone will know about us!
You just want to play around!
That's a great idea!
Right?
Yes!
You're amazing, Fukube-san!
I know, right?
Wait a second...
That's a great idea.
We each have our own roles, then.
Chitanda will negotiate for a better location,
and Satoshi will advertise.
Let's go with that for now.
But what will you do, Oreki-san?
I'll...
Yes?
...take care of the booth.
Well, I guess we need someone here.
I suppose.
Then I guess we should get going.
The opening ceremony is starting soon.
Okay!
Alright!
Let's go with the plan we have now.
Let's do everything we can to sell even one more copy.
Our goal is for all 200 copies of Hyouka...
completely sold out!
Ready, and...
Shuubun
When the light and dark are in balance
Hyouka
How about the Quiz Club first?
A rabbit?
That was amazing!
...you know?
Ladies and gentlemen, it is my great honor to declare the 54th annual Kanya Festival...
...open!
He jumped!
He's spinning!
This isn't the time to be doing this!
Some calligraphy, anyone?
Calligraphy!
Would you like to try some calligraphy?
Yes?
Growing rice is
growing earth
Chitanda Eru
Feel free to keep it.
Not good! Not good!
Tsukuba ne no...
Haru sugite...
Tachi wakare...
Karuta Club
Would you like to try?
One game?
Hisa—
Well done!
Not good! Not good!
Executive Committee Main Office
I finally made it...
Is anyone in?
What a pretty picture...
Um...
Can I help you with something?
Excuse me!
I'm looking for the Executive Committee president, Tanabe-san.
I'm Tanabe.
Oh, I see!
Please give the Classics Club a better location!
Global action! Global action!
I'm sorry!
I'm the Classics Club president, Chitanda Eru.
I have a request, you see...
Please give the Classics Club a better location!
I can't just hand out booths out of the blue like that...
I see...
Thank you for your time.
Wait!
Those are just the rules, you see.
Would you mind explaining your situation?
I see! Thank you!
Isn't Fukube-san supposed to be helping me out for this part?
When I get at that wheel, "Go!"
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stop! Stop!
That's dangerous!
Whaddya mean?
Yer gonna crash!
...so that's why.
That's quite a pickle.
I'd like to help out, but everyone's got their own issues.
I can't go around making exceptions...
So you really can't...
Sorry.
Oh, but if other clubs are willing to let you put some anthologies in their booths, there'd be no problem there.
That's a good suggestion!
I'll give that some thought!
Thank you so much!
Welcome to the Manga Society
Good morning!
Morning!
Hey, Ibara.
You finally came.
Good morning, Kouchi-senpai.
You even brought a katana?
Yep.
It's just a plastic toy.
Maybe we should have done something about your shoes, too.
So she ended up cosplaying anyway?
Even though she was all like, "No."
She could have just done what Kouchi-senpai said in the first place.
You don't have to say it like that.
Morning!
Morning, Yuasa.
Good morning, President.
Morning.
Did that cost you a lot?
I only had to pay for the belt.
I see.
You can give me the receipt later.
No, it's fine.
Anyway, President, would it be okay if...
Never mind...
It's nothing.
Really?
Yes, I'm sorry.
It's kind of difficult to ask to sell Hyouka here...
Hey, hey!
What costume is that?
This?
It's Frol.
Have you heard of "There Were Eleven"?
I've never heard of it...
It's a really old SF manga.
I think it's a masterpiece!
Can I borrow it?
Sure!
What are you borrowing now?
Manga.
Alright, everyone!
Let's do this!
Excuse me...
Are you open yet?
Welcome!
We have our first customer!
Classics Club
Anthology
Hyouka
No. 46
On sale now
It's quiet...
Best job...
...ever.
I guess I'll mark down how many will definitely sell.
I'll assume each Classics Club member buys two.
Plus one for our Supervisor, and one for archiving, makes twelve.
That's not bad, considering.
Did someone take my apple juice?
Haven't seen it.
I hadn't even touched it...
What's that paper there?
Did something happen?
What is it?
Man, I'm sleepy.
Um...
Woah, punk?
Is he a punk?
What do you do here?
Nothing...
I mean, we're selling anthologies.
All of these?
There were extenuating circumstances...
I'll take one, then.
A customer?
A real customer?
I need to smile...
That'll be 200 yen.
Damn, I can't smile.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
Yes?
Can I see that?
This?
Yeah!
This is great!
This is perfect!
Is it?
Oh, sorry.
I'm in the Fashion Club, you see...
We're doing a fashion show, but I forgot to bring something to go with my formal breast pocket!
This is seriously awesome!
You can have it.
What? Seriously?
You're giving it to me?
It'll just go into the garbage later anyway, so go ahead.
You can have this, then!
That's a backstage pass for our show.
If you come to the Fashion Club with that, we'll give you the greatest makeover ever!
Sure...
Satoshi's probably the only one who would...
Though, he has his own sense.
Don't need it.
So I guess that makes one copy sold.
Not again!
Hey, you!
Yes?
Taking commemorative pictures!
Photography Club
How about a photo?
Not good! Not good! Not good!
If I keep stopping every time something catches my eye, I'll never finish my job!
Occult Society! Occult Society!
Would you like to join us in flagging a UFO?
We're also selling ghost photos!
The Enterprise is on display now!
The launching ceremony will be held momentarily!
Global action!
Would you like a good luck charm?
Does anyone have a pair of glasses that only lets you see straight ahead?
joukyou wa hikagaku teki ni
The case seems so irrational
kanjou no monta-ju
A montage of emotions
dare ga dare wo yonderu
Just who's calling who right now?
furimukeba nigeteku shisen kanjiru
When I turn around I don't feel watched anymore
ki no sei ja tsurenai yo
I know it's not just my imagination
antena wa sainou da yuusha
A heroine's antenna is her talent
datte (datte) shiritai (kimi wa chigau no)
I mean (I mean) I want to know (Don't you want to?)
seishun ondosa ima no uchi tadashite ageru yo
I'll fix the difference in how we view our youths right now
ashita kaiketsu suru nara ima demo yokunai
If it'll be fixed tomorrow, then why not fix it right now?
kimi no misuteri-
You are a mystery
toite mitai
Detective I'll try to be
shougen no himitsumeita senaka sagase (kyou mo)
Looking for the person who makes this happen to me (Again today)
kimi wa fantaji-
You are a fantasy
hikareteyukuyo tsumui
You pull me in to see
fukuranda koukishin
I want to launch an investigation
torikku wa nai no ni
Even though there isn't a trick
ki ni naru yo
I'm curious
kyoumibukai
I'm so interested
doushite
Why is that?
Next time: A Corpse by Evening
A Corpse by Evening