Do I seriously have to wear this crap?
Quit your whining.
Hey, check this out, Yukine!
This looks cute!
Capypa
Land
That's so lame.
Capypa
Land
Fine then! I'll wear it!
Capypa
Land
Why am I still so sensitive to physical stuff...
even though...
I'm long dead?
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Let's eat here today.
Eat up.
What's this?
You said you're hungry,
so I got you some lunch.
You expect me to eat this?
You're my Regalia!
What your master says goes!
Regalia, huh...
That's right!
A Regalia respects, worships,
and serves at his master's beck and call!
You should at least go and serve some tea!
We don't even have a place to serve tea.
Talking back to me is unacceptable!
I demand obedience!
You're ripping my hair out!
Quit it, you little furball!
I never would have guessed
that being a god means drifting around town,
sleeping in the corner of some old shrine to avoid drawing attention,
and picking through trash bins for our necessities.
Delivery God Yato
What's that supposed to be anyway?
Missionary work!
Work? What work?
Are you sure you're a god?
Don't gimme that look.
I'll show you what I can do.
Chapter
Bidden Calamity
Welcome!
Hiyori's offered to treat us!
See how charismatic I am?
Looks more like extortion than charm.
Once you're done, I expect you to finally listen to my request.
Welcome!
Are you ready to order?
Three glasses of water, please!
Huh? Oh!
I-I'm so sorry!
I thought people can't see you because you're not human.
It's not like that.
It's not that we're invisible, just hard to notice.
People can still see us.
Let me ask you something.
How many waitresses are in this restaurant?
Huh?
Oh, no looking.
Uh...
Two?
Huh? Four?
It's just like that.
Yukine and I blend in with the background,
just like the two waitresses
you didn't notice before.
Once noticed, we're seen as normal people,
but we're forgotten again soon after.
My apologies!
Like...
You don't remember every single person you've passed on the street, right?
Since we're from the Far Shore, it's like that, but more extreme.
Anyone could see that
you eat a lot, that's for sure.
Never waste an offering!
An important rule!
You're going to make yourself sick.
I'll be fine!
Gods don't have to poop!
Thank you very much!
That man has some nerve!
Um... Thanks for the food.
Don't worry about it.
My name's Iki Hiyori.
You can call me Hiyori.
How do you know him, Hiyori?
Well...
I lose my body from time to time now,
I'll take the entire bowl.
It says the candy is free, after all.
so I'm hoping he can fix that.
Huh...
Well, good luck with that.
Gee, thanks.
Um, what about you? How did you...
What did you do before
you became Yato's Regalia?
I dunno.
I know that I died...
but the farthest back I can remember is when I was suddenly in his hand.
I don't remember anything
from when I was alive.
I don't know what to expect now, either.
You're that sardine thief!
Atta boy.
Do you like cats, Yukine-kun?
I think so.
Cats are cute, aren't they?
I like them, too!
Yukine!
You just had a dirty thought, didn't you?!
Listen, Yukine!
For future reference, gods and
their Regalia share mind and body!
Huh?
That means as your master,
I sense all your wicked thoughts!
Huh? What the heck are you talking about?
Uh, what do you mean you share mind and body?
Man.
Kids in puberty can be such a handful.
Shut it, you moron!
Who are you calling a moron?!
Is this what a generous god is supposed to be like?
Hello! Fast, affordable, and reliable!
Delivery God Yato, at your service!
We got a job, Yukine!
Come on, let's go!
A job?
Hey, wait!
What about the job I gave you?!
You came too?!
If you don't like it,
then just help me already!
A tail?
Who are you?
You called in a fake job as a trap?!
"When the east wind blows,
let it send your fragrance, O plum blossoms."
P-Plum blossoms...
"Although your master is gone, do not forget the spring."
Th-This is one of Sugawara-no-Michizane's poems!
Could it be?!
Tenjin-sama, the god of learning?!
Oh? You could tell?
Oh, god!
What?!
I'm impressed, little spirits.
That's quite an old classic, as far as poems go.
It's in all the schoolbooks!
That's actually quite distressing.
Aren't there copyrights and such?
They expire 50 years after the author's death!
Oh, I see.
Such a godly aura!
So godlike!
Oh my. You think so?
You're the total opposite of...
Hm? Yato-kun.
What is this little one called?
His name is Yuki.
As a Regalia, I call him Setsu.
And as a person...
Yukine.
Yukine-kun.
You've only recently become a Regalia, correct?
As a Regalia, you need not prostrate yourself.
Huh?
Tsuyu.
Indeed, young one.
'Tis disrespectful to bow to another god in the presence of the one you serve.
May you keep that in mind.
Wow!
You have a lot of shrine maidens too!
I'm Ayu!
I'm Nayu!
I'm Miyu!
I'm Moyu!
And we're...
the Tenjin Sisters!
They're all my Regalia, actually.
Providing for them is quite the task.
Real gods are on a whole different level!
I'm a real god, too!
So? What do you want?!
Oh, right.
It's exam season and my hands
are quite full, you see.
Please let all of us get into
our first choice school
Please let me get into
the school I want
Please let me pass my entrance exam
So I was hoping you could take care of some Phantoms for me.
I mean, you have nothing else to do, right?
I am aware that you sleep in my shrines without my permission, by the way.
I'm willing to let you join
my Tenman Group, you know!
I could even make you a branch manager!
But you'd much rather have your own shrine, right?
In that case, here!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I only have a large bill.
Can you make change?
Oh?
A little low on change, are we?
So income inequality is an issue for gods, too?
This must be why the world's so unfair.
You had change all along!
Now, then. Show him the way,
Makoto.
My Lord.
Mayu is still new to this area.
I would suggest another guide.
Indeed she is. However...
Mayu happens to know Yato...
very well.
Tomone?!
NORAGAMI
I am not Tomone.
I'm Mayu.
Tomone!
Y-You joined this big shot?!
My name is Mayu.
Excuse me...
I was once Yato-san's Regalia.
Oh, really?!
Wh-What was it like?!
How was the work?!
Did he actually do his jobs?!
What about food, clothing, and housing?
Is he really an unemployed,
sweats-wearing drifter, or what?!
He was a homeless and jobless guy in sweats who called himself a god.
Give your former master some credit, Tomone!
It's Mayu!
Don't call me by my old name!
It offends me!
You complained and complained about me touching you,
but now you're some geezer's pipe?!
You've been blinded by money!
I'd gladly serve anyone that wasn't you!
A-An ex-girlfriend?
No!
Ex-wife, then.
You're on pretty bad terms.
It's not like that!
Either way, there's a lot of friction between you two.
Excuse me...
You asked Yato to kill some Phantoms, right?
Are Phantoms really that bad?
Why do you need to get rid of them?
"Disorder among people means disorder in the heavens."
Huh?
Hiyori-san, was it?
I can't say I approve of you getting involved in our matters.
We and humans are too easy to meddle with.
The other day,
I really want to
get into college,
for my friends up
in heaven right now.
- Natsuki
I really want to
get into college,
for my friends up
in heaven right now.
- Natsuki
someone offered an unsettling wish plaque.
I really want to
get into college,
for my friends up
in heaven right now.
- Natsuki
I really want to
get into college,
for my friends up
in heaven right now.
- Natsuki
When I looked into it...
I learned that two people have
already ended their own lives here.
Why would they do that?
This area is often plagued by Storms.
The Phantoms they bring latch onto people and take control.
Filled with heartache,
Michizane-sama put up a barrier here,
but a spirit can still get through
if they're deeply rooted in a person.
This makes complete purification difficult.
Such a waste of precious life...
So we just need to kill these
Phantoms that are possessing people?
Yes!
Hiyori?
People are dying because of this!
Don't you want to put a stop to it?!
If someone wants to die, I say let them.
Huh?
You're as repulsive as ever!
Um...
I don't think you should be looking at it like that!
If a soul's willing to commit suicide,
it means it's already been possessed.
It can't even become a Regalia.
Already dead or still alive...
It makes no difference.
Just can't be saved.
H-How can you say that?!
Isn't this your job?!
Well, I'm outta here.
Hold it! He paid in advance!
You sure it's okay to let her run off like that?
Man, what an asshole.
Yukine.
It's time for your first job.
What do I have to do?
Come when I call for the Regalia,
and revert when I call your name.
That's all for now.
Yato...
If someone wants to die, I say let them.
You're just awful!
Express
Local
Shin-Kiba
cars
doors
Don't... wanna get... a job...
but... don't wanna go to university... either...
Sushi Roll...
Kick!
You're in big trouble for making people do bad stuff!
What... is... that?
One of us?
Almost like us...
A train will be passing by on Platform 1.
Let's take her...
Yes...
Please remain behind the yellow line.
Let's take her with us.
Come here...
Come this way...
Wait...
Jump!
You okay?
Man...
You'll die if your tail gets cut, remember?
Now just stay put!
Yukine.
Here's where the real work starts.
I got an F on my practice exam.
This sucks.
Just forget about it. F for forget! Just forget!
Come here. Relax and forget....
Forget... Forget about it.
Forget...
I just... want to forget.
Forget it... Leave it behind...
Forget...
We're taking out that Phantom!
Don't bail on me now, Yukine!
Don't need to worry about that.
Forget...
Oh no! We're not gonna make it.
Yes, we will!
Forget...
Thou who dares desecrate
this land of the rising sun!
With my advent, I, the Yato god,
lay waste with Sekki...
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
Yuki! That's enough! Revert!
You cut too well!
You said people who want to die should just die...
but it looks like you do help them after all!
It's not like that.
I just refuse to let anyone die in front of these guys, if I can help it.
"These guys"?
Even if life is painful and tough,
people should appreciate
what it means to be alive at all.
If a soul's willing to commit suicide,
it means it's been possessed.
It can't even become a Regalia.
They're all so young and innocent.
If suicide isn't how they died...
then Regalia must be people
who still wanted to live.
So having other people waste their lives in front of them...
was something Yato couldn't stand.
Hiyori?
Yukine, you perv!
What did you do to her?!
I didn't do anything!
I-I'm okay!
Some of the fragments got in my eye, that's all.
Huh?!
That's not okay at all!
No! Don't rub your eyes!
Stay calm, Hiyori!
Take deep breaths!
Will that really help her?!
Use it.
It'll warm you up a little.
Capypa
Land
You did pretty well today,
considering it was your first job.
Huh?
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
Yukine.
What's the difference between butter and margarine?
Th-Their ingredients?
Wrong! Their names!
You can't even solve a simple riddle like that?!
On the next Noragami: "Where Happiness Lies."
Yato is so obnoxious.
Next Episode
Where Happiness Lies
Hang in there, Yukine-kun!