Yo.
Mr. Ladykiller Manabe!
Huh?
Manabe
Kotoura
What were you guys thinking?
Manabe
Kotoura
How could you forget the heart?
The heart is crucial.
Don't you understand anything?!
F-Forgive us!
Kotoura
Honestly. No one grasps the deep
significance of the shared umbrella!
Um...
Let it go. I'm begging you.
One morning I realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
Don't fret now
Fret,
fret,
fret
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Is this love?
That's a really big secret, you know?
Yeah!
That's a really big secret,
isn't it?
So Happy, So Fun
What's with you?
Still mad about before?
I'm not mad.
Kotoura still doesn't know what happened the other day.
Because I like her!
Got a problem with that?!
I can't let that slip for a while.
Who knows what people would say to Kotoura?
He's worrying about me.
I'm gonna buy some bread from the school store.
Go ahead to the club room and I'll see you there.
O-Okay.
Hey, Kotoura...
Wh-What?
Well, uh...
S-Sorry!
Well, see ya.
What am I doing?
H-Hello.
Hey.
This is kind of awkward.
I still don't know what kind of person Muroto is.
Manabe isn't here yet?
Yuriko got held up,
so for now we are all alone.
No one to interfere.
This room is tucked away in the back of the old building, so not many people pass by.
It seems...
I have my chance!
How I have longed...
to vivisect a psychic!
Nooo!
'Sup?
Sorry I'm late.
Shall we have some lunch?
Hey. We've been waiting for you two.
We truly couldn't wait another moment.
He was teasing me?!
Please explain why you have done this.
You want an explanation?
You know very well why!
Only Manabe has the right to harass Kotoura!
He's the one who seriously wants her to be his girl—
Oh, that's right.
He doesn't know that you overheard his confession, does he?
Hey Manabe, know what?
Yesterday, Kotoura—
Please! No!
Why not? It's not like you hated the confession, did you?
O-Of course not!
There, there.
Let's hurry up and eat before lunch break ends.
Wait. Was there any point to keeping me quiet?
Oh my.
Did you make that lunch yourself, Kotoura?
Yes.
Did you make yours too?
Yeah.
My grandparents are getting on in years, after all.
I-I see.
Yuriko—
What?
I'm still not letting you down.
No, I just thought I'd check to see
if your cooking's gotten any better.
Big talk for someone in such a bind.
Here.
65 points.
Please. You're always such a tight-ass critic.
C-Could it be?
President Mifune, are you and Muroto...
Funny you should ask. Muroto is...
A childhood friend.
Perhaps our fates are bound together.
She, forever making trouble.
I, forever sacrificing myself to stop her.
The chains of karma are a heavy burden.
So sue me!
Make it stop!
Anyway. Manabe, it seems like you always eat bread or convenience store lunches.
Yeah, my mom's not a morning person.
Oh, really?
Then, Kotoura, why don't you make his lunch?
You could even feed it to him yourself while you're at it.
I-I'm not taking it that far!
Then you are making lunch for him?
W-Well...
I'll think about it.
Mega-score!
My first homemade lunch, and it's from a girl!
I haven't decided to make it yet!
All right.
I will now announce the details of today's ESP Society activities.
Y-Yes ma'am.
Today, after school,
we, the ESP Society, will...
sing our hearts out!
Wait. What exactly...
In order to fulfill the ESP Society's grand mission,
we must forge strong bonds between our members!
Yes, I suppose.
In other words, we must reinforce our friendship!
Thus, Kotoura...
Yes?
Your turn! Go!
No! No way! Absolutely no way!
You've never sung karaoke before?
No!
Basic karaoke proficiency is an absolute necessity for any high-school girl.
Without it, you'll run into big problems on your dates with Manabe.
Kotoura does have a cute voice.
I wonder what her singing sounds like?
O-Okay. I'll give it my best shot.
It's my first time, so it might not be very good.
Please don't laugh.
The moment has come!
Go, Kotoura!
I'll enter the song.
You're too cute!
That's a Really Big Secret, You Know?
Rock on!
One morning I realized it
Sing louder!
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love! Love! Love! Love!
Don't fret now
Fret, fret, fret...
Can't you smell my feelings on me?
But, but, but...
I want you to comfort me
Is this love?
She is...
That's a really big secret, you know?
...shockingly...
That's a really big secret, isn't it?
...staggeringly...
...unbearable!
Okay, Manabe,
make sure you see Kotoura home.
Roger!
And no feeling her up once you're there.
Hey! Aren't you going to respond?!
I'm not letting you inside!
It'll be just the two of you.
Why not simply tell him how you feel?
Would you please stop saying that?
K-Kotoura?
Eep! It's nothing!
Well, see ya.
See you tomorrow.
Are you trying to make up for letting her be bullied?
Not at all.
She's a necessary element of my master plan.
I'll play the nice upperclassman so long as it furthers my goals.
Sorry, but you don't have the talent to be an actress.
Especially in a villainous role.
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, by the way, you should come eat at my place tonight.
My mom keeps pestering me to bring you over now and then.
You'd better walk me home after.
Wow, that was really fun!
Yeah.
But I made them worry about me again.
Kotoura, it's not...
It's okay. I understand.
I know they aren't being nice to me just because I'm psychic.
They're like you.
It's just, I don't know much about the distance people should keep between each other.
Right now, I have people who care about me slowly getting closer to me.
And this time I won't let them slip through my fingers.
Because this will be the very happiest, most fun time of my life.
Stupid.
You've got so many more happy, fun things to look forward to.
Don't sell yourself short by thinking things can't get even better.
M-Manabe...
Why not simply tell him how you feel?
No! I don't want to be eaten, Mr. Wolf!
But why else would you have opened the door?
It's chow time!
Nooo!
Yup. You're not setting foot in my house, lecher.
Wild sheep?!
Moritani         School
Why, Miss Hiyori!
Mori!
It's a pleasure to see you so full of spirit this morning.
It seems the Moritani School's future is in good hands!
I just wanted a little exercise to let off steam.
Then perhaps you'd be so gracious as to spar with us?
We'll do anything we can to be of use to you.
God, they're so smothering.
This is why I hate living in a dojo.
You said you'd do anything?
Of course, Miss Hiyori!
That right?
Please excuse us.
Oh, Kotoura, come here a second.
Yes?
What is this I see?
Manabe seems to have eaten a
convenience store lunch again today.
Is that right?
Muroto, it seems like you always choose the most difficult-looking books.
What do you usually read?
Books about psychic powers, computers, and so on.
They're not that challenging.
Which means...
They must be dirty!
Are you an utter moron?
This is no good!
That moron won't notice anything unless you make a move yourself!
I tried my best!
This lunch is just too embarrassing to be!
I simply couldn't do it.
Don't overthink things like that.
That dunderhead would be moved to tears by any lunch you made for him.
I guess you're right.
Do I spy something homoerotic over there?!
Nope, just your own derangement.
Huh? What's up, Kotoura?
Uh, well...
I need to pick up some things. You can go on home.
Hey, don't try to get rid of me.
I can at least carry your bags.
That would kind of defeat the purpose.
S-So let's just say you can look forward to lunch tomorrow.
Your bread-and-convenience-store diet can't be very nutritious.
And cooking for two is just as easy as cooking for one.
You... You'll really make lunch for me?
Yahoo!
Manabe?!
Can this be true?
I really get to eat your homemade lunch?
I'm so happy I could die!
Please, calm down!
Sorry. I was just so overjoyed.
I noticed.
But I guess I can understand why you'd want to shop on your own.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Now that was mortifying.
Kotoura's homemade lunch, huh?
I'm so damn pumped!
I wonder if I bought too much.
Manabe just seemed so happy.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
No mistake. This is the guy.
Thought you could get away with it, you little bastard?
What the hell do you guys want?
He's been following me around everywhere.
At this point, I don't even know what he'll do to me.
I'm... afraid.
Have no fear!
Just leave it to us, Miss Hiyori!
Thank you.
Just rattle him a little.
On your feet!
We're not nearly finished yet!
I'm not sure what's going on.
But hey, I got this.
Miss Hiyori!
Wh-What happened to you?
He put up a pretty impressive fight.
But please don't worry yourself.
Most of the blood is the stalker's.
We're not hurt too badly.
I'm not worried about you!
What about him? Is he all right?
I don't think he's dead...
I told you just to rattle him a little!
I can't wait to see the look on his face.
Is he running late today?
Okay, everyone to your seats.
I have something important to tell you.
No!
Manabe's been hurt, so he had to go to the hospital.
Seems he was in a bit of an accident.
It was no accident.
It's not...
It's not my fault.
I didn't tell them to take it that far.
Not my fault.
It's not my fault.
What's the matter, Kotoura?
She's looking. She's looking. She's looking!
What do I do?
She knows.
Everything!
No! They'll find out everything!
I didn't mean it!
I didn't want to...
I-I'm so sorry, Manabe.
I only wanted you to...
Please. Please forgive me!
I...
It's okay.
Manabe will be okay.
Which hospital is he in?
Slow down, Kotoura. Let the doctors—
Central Hospital, right?
I'm leaving early!
Hey, wait! Kotoura!
Why? Why didn't she rat me out?
How could she give me that look of pity?
She's never once asked me for help.
She locked all her pain away inside herself.
I'm so blind.
Manabe was right about everything!
How much longer do I have to wait?
My wife won't even come visit me.
It was just a fight between some hooligans.
They deserved what they got.
Excuse me.
Manabe Yoshihisa
Manabe!
Thank God.
Thank God for these angels in white!
Miss Nurse!
I can't eat this on my own.
Feed me, please!
You're just a big baby, aren't you?
But I can't.
You have to eat it yourself.
Shucks.
But what a relief.
He doesn't seem too badly hurt.
If you want to be fed, ask your girlfriend.
Unfortunately, my love is sort of unrequited.
It was seriously lucky Kotoura wasn't with me yesterday.
She could have been dragged into the fight and gotten hurt.
Yeah. Kotoura doesn't need to get hurt anymore.
I'm really glad I was the only one involved.
Manabe, that's wrong.
It was all my fault.
I was so happy to have you looking out for me.
I thought maybe things could change for me.
But it doesn't work that way.
You just get hurt in my place.
I knew it.
I knew I'd bring nothing but unhappiness to everyone I met.
I told myself this time would be different.
But I only took advantage of you.
Even Moritani broke when I touched her.
I had sworn never to get involved with anyone again,
yet still I...
I'm sorry, Manabe.
I'm sorry, Moritani.
Please.
Forget me.
I'll just...
I got out of the hospital pretty soon.
But Kotoura wasn't here anymore.
Kotoura
She even moved out.
Where did she go?
I still don't know.
There's a lot I don't understand,
but there is one thing I'm sure of:
I couldn't...
I couldn't protect her.
When something trips you up,
how do you stand again?
Can truth be found by thinking
about the days to come?
When we are born, we all come into this world alone,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us
the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
After I met you,
my faded world began to shine in brilliant colors.
But it was only a fleeting dream.
If I could have just one more chance...
Episode 4
Changing World
With you...