Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Tomorrow's the start of a long break...
Don't forget that you're all students...
...and act with caution.
Yes, ma'am!
Precautions
for
Summer Vacation
Students feel restless around this time of year...
...and many cause societal disturbances.
I am terribly concerned.
Take extreme care to avoid causing any trouble.
Precautions
for
Summer Vacation
In short...
If you do something bad...
...it'll cut into my vacation...
...so I'm begging you!
Sh-She's hopeless...
Ace
Shooter
It's finally vacation...
When I think about how I won't have to see your face every day...
...I feel so good.
Sis...
Well, even if it is a vacation...
...I'll still see Teacher every day.
Why?
Do you have make-up classes or something?
We're in the same party on an MMO.
What's up with that?
MMO?
She plays a wizard, and I'm a tank.
So if we pair up and I pull...
...we can get crazy experience.
Uh...
Well, I'm the only one who's actually busy.
All Teacher has to do is click AoE spells.
The other day, I pulled this huge mob...
...but Teacher had fallen asleep...
It took a whole day to make up the experience lost from death.
Um...
In Japanese, okay?
Good morning.
It sure is hot this morning.
Morning.
Your hair's pretty wild.
Hey, Sis.
How about we turn on the A/C?
There you go again...
Don't be so quick to depend on that stuff.
Just use a fan or something.
Here.
A fan can make it pretty cool.
Right?
I'm hot...
You get tired from fanning yourself...
...and once you stop, you feel even hotter than before, right?
When you use a fan...
Well, I expected this.
Hang in there.
Everybody's wearing yukatas.
Well, our sashes are the pre-tied kind.
The ones you can just attach.
Even then, yukatas sure are hard to put on.
Yours is a real tied-on sash, huh?
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
No.
A clerk at the store tied it for me.
Tying a sash would be too difficult for me.
I see.
And Konata's wearing one.
Oddly enough.
Did you get also yours tied at the store?
Nope.
My dad did it for me.
Oh, really...
Come on, let's go!
How come her dad knows how to tie a sash?
Hey!
Konata-chan!
A cop?
Do you know her?
She's Cousin Yui.
Nice ta meet ya!
Hi.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Listen to your elders...
...and control yourself...
...and get home early.
No, no, no, no, no.
Elders
We're in the same year.
Don't use Konata as the standard.
We're all in the same year.
Whoa!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm amazed!
The difference in size got me.
That's okay.
Man...
Girls sure hit puberty early these days.
No.
Like I said!
Don't use Konata as the standard!
We're the normal ones!
It's a shooting game.
Cousin Yui.
Aren't you good at shooting games?
Believe it or not...
...I'm good enough to be known as Sharpshooter Yui-chan.
I can hit five bullseyes in three seconds.
With enough time to flash a peace sign.
Then show us.
Here.
Huh?
What?
You use rifles for shooting games?
What a surprise!
I use pistols.
Can't wait! Can't wait!
Narumi.
What are you so concentrated on over there?
Aren't you on duty?
What?
Okay, back to patrolling.
Let's try this again...
Hey, big guy.
We can have anything over there if we hit it?
They're all okay.
All of them?
All of them.
Whoa, miss.
I'm not a prize.
Summer festivals are all about shaved ice!
It's pretty hot.
Let's have some.
Oh, yeah.
Strawberry
Lemon
Melon
Blue Hawaii
I've been wondering...
I know what strawberry, lemon, and melon are...
Melon
Blue Hawaii
Lemon
...but what kind of fruit is a Blue Hawaii?
What does it taste like?
L-Like Blue Hawaii?
That's right..
That's what you would think.
So Miyuki-san...
Do you know anything about Blue Hawaii?
Blue Hawaii, is it?
Um, let's see...
Is it a song?
B-Blue...
No, that's not it.
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of any help.
I'll look it up in the near future.
I'm counting on you.
I don't believe there are any fruits or confections by that name.
Wait.
Shouldn't the person who wants to know...
...be looking it up instead of Miyuki?
Um...
About Blue Hawaii...
I think the name comes from...
...a cocktail with the same name and color.
The cocktail was named with the movie Blue Hawaii in mind.
You're right.
That was very informative.
When you learn something from Tsukasa...
...it feels like you've really failed.
I just realized that I barely have any money left.
The stuff at these stalls isn't cheap.
Use your money wisely.
For crying out loud...
But the whole festival atmosphere makes you wanna spend.
I guess.
It's like how you don't realize how
expensive doujinshi is when you're at Comiket.
Afterwards, you're like, "Whoa, I spent a lot."
Seriously, nobody else understands your world!
You're all exhausted from waiting in line since morning...
...and it's really far between the west gate and east gate.
We don't know what you're talking about.
I love how cotton candy is all fluffy and sweet!
You're not a child.
Eat slower.
It's not as entertaining when two girls do it.
Don't say it.
Why haven't any of us found any romance?
Summer means festivals which means yukatas!
If this was a dating sim...
...you'd probably trigger at least one flag somewhere.
Flag?
And there'd be an event scene.
Since you'd be in yukatas.
And it's outdoors.
Okay, that's far enough.
Aren't you going to play anything, Kagami-san?
Since we're here...
Might as well scoop goldfish or something.
I haven't even made a move!
Why are they running away?
Didn't they sense your barbaric nature and run away?
Guess we've finally got some hard proof.
Look!
There's one right here!
You're right.
Okay...
Gotta catch 'em all!
Yay!
I caught one!
That was amazing!
I'll take care of it.
I'll take good care of it.
Lil' Goldy.
Yo.
Y'all came together.
I heard there was a festival around here...
...so I figured I might as well come.
I love festivals.
Did you come with your boyfriend?
'Course not.
Don't have one.
There really isn't a shred of romance around us.
Figured as much.
We meet again!
Looks like you're having fun with a new friend.
Hello.
So this is the one who really hit puberty early, huh?
She's our teacher.
For homeroom.
I'm terribly sorry.
I assumed that you were a classmate.
It's okay.
This is Cousin Yui.
She's a cop.
As you can see.
Yeah...
Today's a summer festival...
...so I'm on patrol here.
Man, they make us work in such hot weather.
Work?
Looks like you're just having fun.
Are you also working?
Keeping an eye on students?
Nah.
I was bored so I figured I'd drop by.
Lucky you.
If I wasn't on duty...
...I would have come to play around.
No.
You're having plenty of fun as it is!
Are you also by yourself?
Yes, I am.
I see!
Single
Husband
works far away
Actually, I would recommend balsamic vinegar...
But the normal vinegar you may have in your kitchen works fine.
Balsamic vinegar.
Balsamic vinegar!
Vacations are kind of boring since you usually have nothing to do.
You get used to sitting around and doing nothing.
If you're going to say that...
...don't ask me to show you my homework later.
I see.
It sure is cute.
All stout and rotund.
And how the outside looks like a froggie.
Yep, yep.
Depleted uranium, huh?
That's cool!
I'll get in trouble if I'm on the phone too long.
Bye, then!
I was on the phone with Kona-chan...
...and I mentioned how much free time we have during vacation...
...but she's playing a bunch of games
that have piled up, so she has no free time.
I guess some people still enjoy a
full and satisfying summer vacation.
Maybe I should do something, too.
Well...
I suppose that's okay...
But do your homework!
Honestly...
Every single time...
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
I'll pull one.
I'll pull one
ok
lolololol
Debuff please.
debuff please
Your friend nanakon has signed on
Teacher logged on.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
hi
yo (^3^)/
You're on a lot more since it's vacation, huh?
you're on alot more since it's vacation, huh?
pretty much lol
I've got some time. Wanna go hunting?
i got some time, wanna go hunting?
I'm in the cave near Chopron Village.
i'm in the cave near chopron village
oh ya! let's do it! omw! >w<b time for some wiz action!
Then I'll be waiting by the gate.
then, i'll be waiting by the gate.
thats great.. but have you done your hw?
huh?
locked in your room the whole time? (-_-)
don't forget when school starts again (~3~)y-~~~
also, don't stay up too late just cuz it's vacation
Teacher...
Stop talking about the real world on an MMO every day...
It's like I'm getting yelled at by Kagami every day.
Yo!
Sure is hot today.
Welcome.
Come on in.
Hello.
You set up an electric fan.
Since it's hot.
Cool yourself down.
I knew it.
I knew you'd do it.
Good morning.
Kona-chan's here.
Yo.
Don't "good morning" me!
Do you have any idea what time it is?
It sure is hot.
You too?!
Well, it's the normal thing to do.
It isn't.
But Kagami also did it this morning.
See.
I was seen.
Looks like Comp Festival's pretty popular.
What's that?
If you collect the forms that come in
these magazines and send them in...
...you can get every single limited edition QUO card.
I'm constantly taking magazines to the register like I'm possessed.
You were saying the same thing about QUO cards the other day.
Japanese people are really weak when it
comes to special gifts or limited edition stuff.
That's why it's essential to buy one for
preservation, one to look at, and one extra.
Wait!
You're undeniably a special case!
There aren't many people like you.
Sometimes, I forget who I lent it to and have to buy another one.
Don't forget.
So...
I'd like to order the usual...
Homework!
Again?
I'll teach you the stuff you don't know...
...so try doing the problems yourself.
Balsamic vinegar.
Kagami.
Tell me how to do this one.
For this one...
Kagami.
I don't know how to do here through here.
That was close.
Kagami.
This one is...
You're not even trying to think it through, are you?!
I am thinking it through.
Really...
And I don't know any of the ones past this one.
You aren't thinking after all!
She ended up not telling me how to do them.
Hey!
I'm here to play!
Cousin Yui.
Perfect timing.
Teach me this part.
Math homework?
Let's see.
Leave it to me.
Well...
I must say, as a good police officer...
...my help would not be to your benefit...
...so don't depend on others!
It's such a pain when I don't understand any of the questions...
If you don't know the answer...
...just write something that sounds close.
Because you just have to turn the homework in.
I get it.
You're smart!
But this really weakens what she said before...
I doubt this will be to my benefit...
Yeah...
That's what I did!
I'm exhausted...
I'll do a little gaming for a break.
I'll do some solo hunting for thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes should be okay.
Solo hunting, right? Right?
...becomes fiction.
...what make you strong.
This isn't...
...else.
A rare drop.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Obtained Demonic Sword Laevateinn
Laevateinn!
I've never seen anyone with this!
It's ultra rare!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
found a leava sword!!!!
Found a Laeva sword!
RLY?! Σ(@@)
lolol gratz lololol
i'll be right there so show me! >w<ノ
let's celebrate! get a guild party going and go test it out!
all-nighter for sho lol. feeling it ronight roflcopter
Okay. Come on!
kk, come on!
Well, where should we try it out?
Everybody's pumped up.
That's right.
I'll buy a bunch of quality potions to pass out.
Let's go back to town first...
Gonna get busy!
Good lucky!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami!
We're already on the fifth episode of Lucky Channel!
Let's get even crazier!
Now let me introduce...
...someone who's showing up more
often in the actual show and getting full of it...
I mean...
The hardworking...
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Clap. Clap. Clap.
Well...
I didn't mean to look like I was full of it...
I'm the assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure!
Okay.
We're always receiving lots of postcards.
Today's is from U.S.S. Gatoh in Tokyo.
Occupation: NEET.
This guy sent in fifty by himself...
He must be one sorry guy!
Let's move on to the postcard.
Good day, Akira-san and Minoru-san.
In the actual show, Konata-chan seems to play MMOs.
Do you also play these games, Akira-san?
By the way, I live a happy life
playing female characters every day.
MMOs?
Online games?
I'm sorry to say that I've never tried it.
But it's better if you haven't.
Another blunt response...
R-Really?
Too many people getting addicted and giving up on the real world.
I was dumb like that once.
I would log on whenever I had time...
...and stay on forever doing stuff like PKKing.
Back when I was young.
Wh-When you were young...?
Er...
There were a bunch of words I didn't get...
You're better off not knowing.
Well, only half the audience is going to get it anyway.
A-Anyway, so you've played them before?
Then do you have any online experiences you would like to share?
Yep!
You bet I do!
When l first started...
...I didn't know what to do...
...and I got lots of help from
some really nice and experienced guys!
They gave me lots of expensive armor and rare items!
Akira was so touched!
R-Really...
It was really fun, so you should all play, too!
We're already out of time.
Bye-bee!
Then we'll see you next time.
So you're popular in those kind of games, huh?
Huh?
Akira-sama?
What's wrong?
Cut 12 on page 38.
Yes?
Who the hell is Yutaka?!
That's what you're mad about this time?!
I'm Akira!
Well, that's true...
Bring out whoever's responsible!
No! Uh...
D-Director?
Director?!
Ah, no.
The hell is Yutaka?!
A producer would be better.
Producer would be better!
Hey!
A-Akira-san!
Please calm down!
Please!
You know.
Yes?
Why don't we change Minoru Shiraishi's name...
...to something else?
Like Su-
You rocked, Kagamin!
Cut that out.
So is Tsukasa or Miyuki next?
Me.
Again?!
When did you order a song?!
They were taking too long, and it'd be a waste of time.
Sorry.
I need a little more time to decide.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We can kill some time with Konata's singing.
I know this!
Didn't expect you to go with something mainstream.
Kami rules!
Sparking!
BREAK THROUGH THE SHINING CLOUDS!
FLY AWAY!
A PANORAMA SPREADS THROUGH MY BODY!
EARTH GETS MAD AFTER A KICK IN THE FACE!
AND MAKES A VOLCANO ERUPT!
IF THE MELTED POLAR ICE...
...YIELDS A DINOSAUR...
...I WANNA TRAIN IT TO BALANCE ON A BALL!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA!
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS!
I'LL BE FEELIN' FINE!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
When you first start MH2...
...the condition for learning weapons is defeating five Gearnos.
So once you return to town...
...and get sent on a quest by the elder...
...even if you defeat five Gearnos...
...get loads of snow mountain grass...
...and lots of poponotan...
...when you can't go back to town...
...you realize for the first time that you
can't access your supply box yourself...
...and your reward is decreased since
you didn't read the instruction manual...
...and you can't save up money.
Doesn't it make you wonder about
how this applies to the real world?
Next time:
「Summer Events」
Summer Events!
Look forward to next time!