I want you to carry out another task in LA.
I thought our focus was to be shifted to the East Coast.
This operation isn't coming from McGwire and the others.
Well, this is to score points personally.
You want to unexpectedly contribute and leave the higher ups indebted to you, huh?
Yeah, that's why we need the utmost secrecy.
I don't exactly hate that type of scheming myself.
I figured as much.
Understood. I'll do everything in profound secrecy.
This operation will show Phantom's excellence, right?
The Past
That concludes the seven-day weather forecast.
Now for the latest news.
Santa Monica's new shopping mall
has grabbed the attention of the locals.
Although the West Coast has many tourists throughout the year...
Who was it?
My part-time shift changed.
They just asked for me now.
I see.
I'll drop you off... I was planning
to go out to practice driving anyway.
You don't need to.
If a couple lives together,
they'd do at least that much, right?
Yeah, you're right.
The drug market on the West Coast
has long been monopolized by the Chinese mafia.
However, lately the Japanese mafia
has been stepping in more frequently
and fights have been breaking out
in Chinatown and the surrounding areas.
Sources point out that this can grow into a large conflict...
Be careful.
Don't worry. I won't mess up and get dragged into it.
That's not what I meant.
I don't want people to find this
place because you started a small fire.
Y-yeah...
Going out?
Ms. McCunnen
Would you like to come with me?
I'm sorry, but I have to practice driving.
Then, would this car do?
I'll walk there.
Well? How does this car feel?
You feel like you'll never want to stop, right?
Does it make you feel like the king of the world?
No way. I'd just be thrown around...by this.
That was surprising.
Just a little longer and it would have been all over for you.
Over?
Nothing would be over... even if I died.
It'd only reduce the amount of assassinated a little.
You can't!
You can't die for nothing.
I'll decide the place for you to die.
A man who has won my trust has earned that much.
Now, go. Keep going, Zwei.
This is an unexpected mission, but...
just consider it a part time job.
Yes.
Claudia seems to be infatuated with Zwei.
Be sure not to let her steal him.
Even if that happens, it won't be a problem.
Always carrying out a mission with Zwei isn't required.
You're right.
Your partnership with Zwei
was stemmed from coincidence.
Go ahead and play with the car a little longer.
Come back in around an hour.
What's going on?
Get familiar with this way of handling things.
Yeah...
Enjoy your drive, Zwei...
You sure know how to make an entrance.
Is it okay to meet up so openly like this?
You don't need to worry.
I exude a fog of war.
So we can speak freely here.
That's great.
I've thought about your plan very carefully.
Essentially, you'll get the weapons, etc.
And we'll prepare the soldiers, etc.
Those are the terms, right?
Yes.
If we do that, we can have 500 kilograms of cocaine,
which is worth about 200 million, all to ourselves, huh?
Ha! If that's the case, we won't have
any problems with funding for a while.
Right?
Yes.
You think it's fishy?
I just can't see it, Ms. McCunnen.
What would you gain by suggesting such good terms for us?
I want to do you, the Godo family,
a favor in return for something else.
Oh?
So you want backing, huh?
Yes.
I'll give you 200 million dollars.
But I'll gain something that's worth more than that.
It's true that it makes sense as a business deal.
Well, that's all right...
since we've already made our decision either way.
We'll take part in our plan.
Your partnership with Zwei
was stemmed from coincidence.
I'm an INN reporter.
Wha...
I have a favor to ask. Take this and...
Huh?! What...
Just give it to the police. That's all. Please!
Ah! Wait!
Why... is this...
I've had enough of this. I'm hungry.
What day is it for god's sake?
I wanna go back... to Japan...
It's quiet... if I go now, maybe I could...
No... If I go out now, she'll find me right away.
She'll... kill me.
He gave Phantom such a hard time and he's still alive.
I'm impressed.
By suppressing even fear and hunger,
he chose to continue staying at this place.
He assessed that it was the only way to survive,
and his instinct made him continue to suppress his impulses.
Interesting... What an interesting subject.
Zwei... Zwei... Wake up.
We're going out. Get ready.
O-Okay.
We have a mission. Tonight.
We'll go check the site before it gets dark.
At 22:00 tonight, 500 kilograms
of cocaine will be brought here.
And Inferno will be taking that.
Our mission is to back up the assault unit.
Are the guys in that assault unit reliable?
Claudia seems to be infatuated with Zwei.
Be sure not to let her steal him.
I wasn't told anything about them.
So this is a mission only Phantom can carry out.
Let's get back. We have to get our weapons ready.
Ein... do you sometimes have dreams?
Dreams?
You see scenery that you've never
seen or meet people you don't know.
I wonder if... those dreams might be... my memories...
I don't know.
Haven't you had... a dream like that?
Sometimes... I have a dream about colors.
Colors, you said?
That's right. Colors.
And...
Wind...
Blue, white and green.
That's all there is. There is nothing else there.
But it's dazzlingly bright there
and there's a wind blowing. A very strong wind...
I wonder if that scenery is your homeland.
I don't know.
But...
What about it? What will we do after knowing our homeland?
Don't you want to go visit it?
The place that remains in your memory.
There's no place for us there.
The place for killers...
right here...
and nowhere else...
It's nothing. Dreams are illusions.
All they do is interfere with reality.
Hey, it's me.
Lizzie...
I've got a message for you from Clau.
Zwei, you're coming to Clau's house at 8.
So sudden. What's going on?
We're changing positions.
I have to attend a big trade tonight.
It's been decided that you'll
be Clau's guard in place of me.
Hold on a second.
We've already got orders for tonight.
What? No one told me that.
Who gave you those orders?
Scythe Master.
Humph! He must be acting on his own.
Don't bother. Clau is your boss.
But...
8 o'clock. Don't forget.
Go, Zwei.
Ein...
I'll carry out the mission given by Master, by myself.
You follow Ms. McCunnen's instructions.
But... it's dangerous.
I'll be fine.
Doing it all by yourself...
The ones who decide...
aren't us.
Yes. It seems that he's doing
quite a bit without involving me.
Scythe Master isn't a fool.
He's probably trying to act ahead of the others.
Yes.
Then humor his little ambition under your management.
Take the car that we're hiding on Fifth Avenue.
Understood.
It doesn't matter if it's money or drugs.
Just let him have his way.
But once he goes beyond those things...
Yes. At that time I'll take responsibility.
I'll bury Scythe with his puppet immediately.
Ein...
Be careful.
You too, okay?
Sudden Change
If I know my past...
I'll know about myself...
I won't be able to continue being myself.