Winter already...
Some time has passed since that incident,
and we've returned to our usual lives.
It was as if nothing had changed,
yet it felt like some things had changed a little.
But the place where I belong is still there, just as always.
Research
Society
– Yo!
– Hello.
Good, you're all here.
As of today, the ESP Research Society is disbanding.
What?!
TLC:
Tobikage
Timer:
Floris257
Editor:
Chippo
K-time:
Floris257
Karaoke:
Naruto-kun
Logo : KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter:
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC:
Robo731
Floris257
Hritham
Encoder:
Floris257
The Things I Want to Tell You
Snap out of it, Kotoura!
My place...
It's no use. She's completely out of it.
What do I do?
Don't die, Kotoura!
I'll have to give her mouth-to-mouth.
No...
Maybe a cardiac massage!
Which one do I choose?!
Hey! I can just do both!
Kotoura...
I can't let my guard down for a second around this pervert.
Feels like it's been ages since you've given me that look.
It kinda makes me tingle!
Advanced level pervert...
Is your little spousal comedy routine over yet?
S-Spousal?
What?
That's the part you react to?!
I mean...
President, what do you mean the club is disbanding?
Exactly what I said.
The activities of the ESP Society, related to scientifically proving
the existence of psychic abilities so that the general populace will acknowledge them,
will cease as of today.
Are you serious?
But...
Kotoura...
And, as of today...
I'm announcing the launch of the new ESP Research Society!
What?
Like I said, the new ESP Society.
Its activities will primarily revolve around having fun with a psychic.
A psychic?
As in...?!
Picking on Kotoura-kun and taking pleasure in her silly reactions.
That's not so different from what we did before.
Why do you have to make me the focus?
Wait, so that means it's okay for me to stay here?
Of course.
Your place isn't going away.
Jeez, President...
You should've said that in the first place...
Actually, didn't Yuriko's thoughts give it away?
You know you should never believe a word that comes from her mouth.
That was a mean thing to say.
I was so shocked, I didn't have time to see what she was thinking.
You guys didn't see through her either, right?
So I need to come up with much more lewd and lustful thoughts to get the best reactions out of you, huh?
Oh, man! Now, I'm fired up!
If I rig a hidden camera in the haunted house on Third Street
and call Kotoura-san there...
I'm burning!
I knew I could trust you two to be the first ones to grasp the new ESP Society's goal.
Hey! Don't pick on me!
You're meshing well, Manabe-kun and Moritani-kun.
You seem to be getting along better than before.
There's less hesitation, or something.
Sorry. I love Kotoura.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
Huh? Why...
I knew from the start that it...
that it would turn out this way...
Well, to celebrate the launch of the new ESP Society,
how about some karaoke?
Yahoo!
That's right. You all went to karaoke before I joined the club.
Come with us, Moritani-san.
S-Sure. Let's sing together.
You probably shouldn't do that.
Meanies!
Oh, sorry. There's something I need to do first.
Kotoura-chan, could you help me?
Okay, sure.
Then, we'll head there first and reserve a room.
Let's get going, you two.
What? I'll help, too.
Yeah, we should all...
Come on, let's get moving, Moritani.
Hey, what are you doing? Stop shoving!
Don't push yourself, Yuriko.
President, it's all right.
There was never any need for you to do this.
So please, don't apologize.
You were apologizing every time you looked at me.
Whether you were angry or laughing...
But you really don't have to apologize.
But I was trying to use you all along!
I know.
I pretended to be a good senpai,
while trying to use you to achieve my own goals!
I know.
I intentionally showed you terrible things just to evoke sympathy from you!
I put you in danger in order to avenge my mother,
when it had nothing to do with you!
Yes, I know all of that.
I am a psychic, after all.
Then how can you not hate me?!
I'm not a good senpai at all!
I'm just a dirty, calculating—
I don't have any right to condemn you.
Because I was essentially trying to use you too.
Kotoura-chan...
Thank you for giving me such a wonderful place, where I can be myself.
I let my junior see me in such an embarrassing state.
But are you really giving up on proving the existence of psychic abilities?
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't still interested in it,
but I'd be putting Muroto-kun through too much again.
I'll just take my time and do what I can to...
Why are you looking at me like that?
So that's what was going on between you and Muroto-senpai!
What do you mean, "what was going on"?
You know what I mean...
Want to hear all the details?
I just stepped on a land mine!
It's okay. You can read my mind.
Go on, read all you like.
U-Um...
Oh, yes. We need to hurry, or Manabe-kun and the others will—
Read.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Sorry you had to see that.
I'm used to it.
You're supposed to follow my lead...
So, anyway...
You said that you'd always be beside me,
that you'd stay with me until the end...
right?
Did you mean it... that way?
Well, we are childhood friends.
And I don't have any plans to move yet.
Uh... I'm really sorry.
Yeah, that's right!
That lunkhead is seriously clueless!
I've been trying to subtly win his affection for years,
and he doesn't even notice!
President, calm down!
I'm used to it, though.
I'll just take my time.
On the other hand,
you and Manabe-kun are always acting like total lovebirds.
Huh?!
Don't tease me...
Knowing Manabe-kun,
I bet he's always whispering sweet nothings to you, huh?
Not at all!
Oh, come on.
Manabe-kun has never...
He's never...
Wait...
What's wrong, Kotoura-chan?
I just realized Manabe-kun
has never directly told me that he loves me.
Well then! Everyone is waiting!
No fair, President!
Man, my throat is shot.
You sang too much.
And you're as tone deaf as ever.
That day, you taught me about
the strength and the meaning of life.
I grasped those lessons firmly in my heart.
Someday, everything will definitely bloom
like those flowers of hope.
Wh-What? Is this a joke?
It will all start from here.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?!
So tone deaf!
Look, we're here. Cheer up.
Oh... Thanks.
Well, see you tomorrow.
M-Manabe-kun!
Um... Good night.
Night!
It's okay even if he doesn't say it out loud, right?
I know how he feels.
Huh?
I must have left the lights on this morning.
I'm gonna rack up a huge electricity bill...
Don't be stingy over stupid little things like that.
Well, I live on my own.
I need to cut back where I can.
What? When did you start living like a poor person?
You could at least say I'm frugal...
Huh?!
M-Mother...
So... why are you here today?
And how did you get in here?
I came to eat at a nearby restaurant, but it was closed.
That's all.
I had the landlord unlock the door for me.
O-Oh...
You're not a very hospitable host.
At the very least, you could offer me some food and alcohol.
But... I'm not old enough to drink, so I...
I'm sorry.
I'll go buy some right now. Just wait here.
Hold it.
I'm coming too.
What are you doing? You really are a dim bulb.
It's nighttime. This child has no sense of danger.
How is everything?
Well, it's not inedible.
When did you learn how to make this?
I tried to make it taste the way you used to.
Do you remember?
You used to make it for me all the time...
I don't remember.
I... see...
What's your problem?
No, it's nothing...
Always trying to read people's expressions...
Pathetic.
But every time you open your mouth, something insensitive slips out.
You said you made friends, but I bet you're lying about that too.
I'm not lying.
They're precious friends who have always stayed beside me and supported me!
It's true!
I don't...
I don't want the person who abandoned me during the most painful period of my life
talking as if she knows me!
Wh...
What?! You think you were the only one in pain?
Don't forget about the people who were hurt because they got involved with you!
Then why didn't you just look for help?!
Could it be that you didn't have any friends to help you, Mother?
Wh...
What did you say?!
You and I are nothing alike!
You're just a little brat with a bad taste in boys!
I know Manabe-kun is a hopeless pervert...
but you're in no position to talk!
Just look at that Tsuyama-san guy you were with before!
What?!
You're just a child! Don't take that attitude with me!
What about you?! You're supposed to be an adult!
All right, come over here!
You little...
Stupid Mother!
Hey—
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
You little...
Cut it out right now!
You cut it out!
You stupid daughter!
You stupid mother!
How did you grow up like this?!
It's all your fault!
You can really dish it out these days.
My friends told me I shouldn't keep my emotions bottled up.
Friends, huh?
Anyway, what were you going to say about Tsuyama?
W-Well...
Hi there.
So, you're Kumiko-san's daughter?
A h-high school girl!
That filthy lolicon!
Why didn't you say anything back then?
You're the one who told me not to.
I did?
I suppose we both share a terrible taste in men.
You've still got me beat.
I want to drink some more.
Haruka, clean all this up and get the alcohol ready.
You could help out too, you know.
Didn't you say you'd do the cooking and cleaning when I left home?
You had to bring up the past...
Okay, Mother, I'm done cleaning.
It'll just be a little...
Honestly, Mother...
I'm sorry, Haruka...
I'm sorry...
I should have never given birth to you.
Wait! Kumiko!
K-Kumiko-san!
I'm sorry I'm such a weak mother, Haruka.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I...
I was such a child.
I only read what was on the surface,
and didn't try to understand what my mother was really feeling.
Why didn't she tell me?
I didn't know.
I never knew there were things I could only understand by being told out loud.
Mama...
I want my eggs over easy...
Mother...
Mother?
These aren't over easy at all, Mother.
They're so overcooked, they're bitter.
Sorry I'm late.
You're the one who told Kumiko about the incident, right?
Dunno. I haven't got a clue what you mean.
I just got a message from Haruka.
From Haruka-chan?
Well, look at that...
Haruka
Mom's Fried Eggs
Honestly... She used to be able to make them better than that.
Haruka
Mom's Fried Eggs
That stupid daughter of mine.
Kotoura, let's head to the club.
Manabe-kun...
Kotoura!
Please open the door! He's right behind you!
Don't include me in your wild fantasies.
I've got something to do, so you go on ahead.
Understood.
So, Moritani-san, I wanted to talk to you...
I see... So he hasn't told you outright, huh?
But you know what's in his heart, don't you?
If that's the case, I see no reason for you to worry.
I thought so too.
But then I realized...
It's sometimes better if people say what they're thinking.
I want Manabe-kun to tell me in his own words.
I see.
So you came to me for advice.
I know I'm in no position to ask you about this...
Don't worry about that. I'm over it.
Actually, it'd make me happy just to help out a friend.
Moritani-san...
Don't expect any expert advice from me though.
Manabe just gave me a serious answer because I confessed to him.
You'll have to express how you feel in your own words.
Y-Yeah...
But I've never confessed to anyone before.
How should I do it?
You'll just have to practice!
Imagine I'm Manabe and confess to me!
Y-Yes, master!
I... I l-lo—
You done, Kotoura?
I love you!
What?!
M-Manabe-kun?!
N-No way!
Moritani-san, that was amazing.
I'll make sure you never think about boys again.
My woman, stolen by another woman...
What is this sense of immorality I feel?
Why is my heart throbbing?!
I get the picture.
Let me take care of him. Carry on.
Fight!
Kotoura-kun, you tend to self-destruct,
so I think you'd be better off if you just let it come out naturally, rather than putting too much thought into it.
Well, good luck.
You're pretty sharp when it comes to the relationships of anyone but yourself, aren't you?
Huh? Are you mad about something?
How should I know?!
Sto-o-op!
So there you have it. What do you think?
I get the feeling it'll work out somehow.
Really?
I'll do my best.
Then, go for it, best friend!
Wait! We're best friends, aren't we?
Sorry... I can't.
Oh, sorry! Did I hurt you?
No.
Thanks, Moritani-san.
All right!
It's so pretty.
Christmas already? Time really flies.
Manabe-kun, it's a white Christmas—
Yahoo! It's snowing!
Kotoura! Do you think it'll stick?
Let's have a snowball fight!
And after that, let's build a giant snowman!
You really are true to your heart, aren't you?
That's why I love you, Manabe-kun.
This is a little embarrassing.
I say it all the time, so I'm used to it,
but this is the first time you've said it to me...
Huh?!
Huh?
You've never said it to me, Manabe-kun.
I've never said it before?
Sorry, Kotoura. I'm always thinking it, so I didn't realize.
Wow, I guess stuff like that does happen, huh?
Even you should know that's being too single-minded!
Do you realize how much it's been worrying me?
But that's just the way you are, Manabe-kun.
The Manabe-kun I love...
I love you too.
I've always, always loved you.
I love you like crazy.
Could you hear what's in my heart that time?
Yeah... I heard everything.
Everything!
- Kotoura!
- Kotoura-san!
Good morning, everyone!
Thank you for your support!