So you can really fulfill any wish?
Don't worry. Your wish is fine.
Go ahead.
Do it.
All right.
Accept it.
This is your fate.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 5 Absolutely no regrets
I don't know what's wrong with me!
I'm so terribly sorry.
What's wrong, Hitomi? Not enough sleep?
I was up late last night dealing with the hospital and the police.
What? Did something happen?
I had an episode of sleepwalking or something like that.
When I came to, I found myself collapsed with a group of people.
Seriously?
The doctor said it might have been a collective hallucination...
They want me to come in after school today for more tests.
It's such a pain...
You really should've stayed home today.
I can't! If I do it'll seem like I'm really sick!
My family would get even more worried.
That's our honors student! So mature!
Man, I haven't felt this great in ages.
It's exhilarating!
Aren't you scared, Sayaka?
Yeah, a little bit.
Yesterday went fine, though.
Besides, I could have lost my two best friends, you and Hitomi.
That's a lot scarier.
So!
I dunno.
Maybe it's confidence. Maybe it's relief.
And there's probably a bit of pride mixed in too.
Oh well, this is my chance to shine!
I, Magical Girl Sayaka, will protect the peace of Mitakihara City!
So you don't regret it at all?
I guess if there's anything I regret...
It's waiting so long.
After all, if I had made up my mind quicker,
I could have fought that witch alongside Mami and maybe she wouldn't have died.
I...
What are you thinking, anyway?
I... I mean, I...
I guess hindsight's twenty-twenty.
When you ask "why", that's exactly the point!
I just had to become a magical girl!
Sayaka...
I found my wish.
I have something I don't care if I have to risk my life in battle for.
I just kind of regret that it took me so long to realize it.
So you don't need to feel pressured.
It just means that you don't have to be a magical girl.
Anyway...
Anyway, I need to get going.
Do you have something you need to do?
Yeah, kind of.
Oh, so you're not being discharged yet?
My leg rehab isn't done yet. I've got to get back on my feet before I can leave.
They don't get why my hand healed all of a sudden, either.
So they want to run a few more tests.
What do you think? Does everything feel fine?
It feels almost like everything after the accident was just a scary dream.
I almost wonder why I'm in this bed.
You were right, Sayaka. It is a miracle.
What's wrong?
I was really mean to you.
I know I have a short fuse, but still...
You don't even need to remember that.
You're happy now!
Don't make that face.
I feel like I've wasted so much time.
Of course.
It's almost time.
Let's get you some fresh air, Kyosuke.
Huh? Why the roof?
You'll see.
Everyone!
We'll have the real party when you're discharged.
But since your hand healed first...
That's--!
You told me to do something with it, but I couldn't bear to throw it away.
I...
Give it a try. Don't be afraid.
Mami...
My wish has been granted.
I have absolutely no regrets.
This is the happiest moment in my life.
So that's the new magical girl in town, huh?
Are you really going to take her on?
She looks like such an amateur.
I'm gonna punch her ticket.
Or what?
You gotta problem with that?
Things may not go how you plan.
There's another magical girl in town too.
Really? Who?
I don't really know either.
What the heck? Didn't she agree to your contract to become one?
Maybe, maybe not.
She's an irregular.
I can't tell what she's going to do.
Oh well, I was getting bored anyway.
Need a little spice in my life.
What did you want to talk about?
Well, uh, it's about Sayaka...
She's hotheaded, stubborn,
she gets in a lot of arguments...
But she's really a good girl!
She's kind, she's brave, she tries to solve everyone's problems!
Those are fatal flaws for a magical girl.
Really?
With kindness comes naïveté.
Courage becomes foolhardiness.
And dedication has no reward.
Those who don't understand this are not fit to be magical girls.
That's why Mami Tomoe lost her life.
Don't talk about her like that!
Anyway, Sayaka says she'll be fine, but...
But I don't know what I'll do if something happens to her like it did to Mami.
You're worried about Sayaka Miki, then?
I can't do anything to help her, so...
So please, Homura!
Be friends with Sayaka!
Don't fight with her like you did with Mami!
It'll be safer if you work together while hunting witches!
I don't like to lie.
And I don't make promises I can't keep.
So you should give up on Sayaka Miki.
Why!?
She should not have agreed to the contract.
That was my my mistake. I should have kept as close an eye on her as I did on you.
Then--
But I'll tell you exactly what I'm responsible for.
At this point, it's a mistake I'll never be able to correct.
It's as fruitless as trying to raise the dead.
Once someone's become a magical girl, there's no hope of saving them.
The contract requires that they sacrifice everything for a single hope.
So...
You've given up?
On yourself, and all the other girls?
Yes.
I won't ask for forgiveness.
But no matter how much I sin, I must keep on fighting.
It looks like I've wasted your time.
I'm sorry.
Are you nervous?
Kind of. One mistake and I'm dead meat.
Madoka?
Sayaka, are you... Y'know...
Yeah, I'm going on patrol for wicked witches! It's a duty of all allies of justice!
You're going alone?
I'll be fine. It was Mami's job, right?
So now it's my job as her junior.
Um... I can't really do anything, and I know I'll just get in your way,
but...
I promise I'll stay out of your way if you take me along!
Aren't you trying too hard?
Sorry...
I know, I'll just be a distraction so I can't go.
Nah, I'd love to bring you!
You can tell, right? My hands have been shaking all this time.
I'm so ashamed. I'm a magical girl, but going alone made me feel so lonely...
Sayaka...
You won't be in the way at all! I'm really happy you're coming!
Just having someone there is really reassuring!
With you along, I feel like I could take on the world!
I...
I'll protect you. So don't worry, come along!
Let's go witch-hunting again!
You understand the danger you're putting yourself in, correct?
I'm kind of a ditz, so if I'm alone I'm sure I'll make all sorts of mistakes.
With Madoka at my side I'll be a lot more cautious.
I see.
As long as you've thought it through.
Kyubey...
You have your own reasons, Madoka.
I know you want to protect Sayaka.
Really, just by being there you're our ace in the hole.
I'm..
You don't have to say anything now.
Sayaka would be against it anyway.
But if you ever decide on it, I'll be ready.
Here it is.
This barrier was probably formed by a familiar, not a witch.
Don't let your guard down. You're still new at this too.
Don't get sloppy.
Gotcha!
There it is!
Got it!
Hey, what the heck are you two doing!?
Fin
Who are you!?
Can't you tell? That's a familiar, not a witch.
Those don't drop Grief Seeds.
But if I leave it be it'll kill someone!
Yeah, you wait for it to do that and grow into a witch.
That's how you get Grief Seeds.
You're killing the goose that lays the golden eggs here.
Are you saying we should just watch the witches kill people!?
You have some really messed up ideas, kid.
Haven't you ever heard of the food chain?
You should've learned it in school.
Witches eat weak humans.
Then we eat those witches.
It's a law of nature.
Just the order of things.
That's...
You... You're--
Wait, don't tell me you're going to give me that line of crap about "helping people" and "justice"?
Is that  really why you contracted with him?
What are you trying to say!?
Give it a rest, kid.
You think you're just playing around, don't you.
What a nuisance.
Sayaka!
Now go cool your heels somewhere.
I don't get it.
That should have put you out of action for months.
Sayaka, are you okay!?
It's because she came a magical girl by wishing for someone's recovery.
She has superhuman regenerative powers.
Who the hell would listen to you!?
If it wasn't for people like you, Mami would--
You tick me off.
You really  tick me off!
What the heck's your problem, anyway? That's not how you talk to your seniors.
Shut up!
Who the heck do you think you're talking to like that!?
Sayaka!
Madoka! Stay back, it's dangerous!
You don't get it when I tell you, you don't get it when I beat it into you.
Guess I'll just have to kill ya!
I won't lose!
I can't lose!
What do I do? Why is this happening!?
She's not a witch! They're on the same side! Why do they have to fight!?
It can't be stopped. Neither of them will back down.
Please, Kyubey, stop them!
This shouldn't be happening!
I can't do anything.
But...
If you want to force them to stop, there is one  way...
Only another magical girl could get between them.
But you could do that.
If you really wanted to.
That's right... If I contract...
You're finished!
I...
That will not be necessary.
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes will
(Go beyond the time)
There is but one dream, of a world rushing toward its doom
(Will it be destroyed?)
Swallow your hesitation! What do you desire?
Chasing these greedy desires, will the future fade away?
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even the darkness
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a plucked laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
Sayaka, you became a magical girl to hunt witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch! She's another magical girl!
Episode 6 This just isn't right
Illustration: Yuupon (Nitroplus)
This just isn't right!