When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
My dream.
First Year, Peach Class, Ayasaki Hayate.
My father and mother are always being bums at home, regardless of it being weekday or weekend.
Father is searching for himself.
Mother is into finding a way to beat the slot machine.
Father says he'll take me to Hawaii if he wins the money,
But Mother says "We can't get passports, so that's impossible" and laughs, so my house is always filled with laughter.
And my dream is to...
Is it because of what I was told yesterday at Milady's home?
So in other words, your life is infinitely worthless, I take it.
No, come on! Keep it together!
I made up my mind, didn't I?
I don't know the meaning in my life, but right now, I'll protect Milady.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Hello. Ayasaki Hayate here.
All right, I'll do my best today, too!
What? My dream?
Yes.
If I were pressed, there's one person whose future I'm really worried about,
so I would have to say my dream is for her to become a fine adult.
But why ask this all of a sudden?
Oh, well, how do I put it...
Dreams are like the motivation for people to live!
I-I guess.
Hold on, if you apply that theory,
my motivation to live is a little iffy.
Sakamoto Ryouma said that we should have a dream
as large as the Pacific, since we are born as humans.
And Mozart said that life has meaning because there are dreams.
A spy from England said that a person who can't come up with a huge dream must have a life worthless like trash.
Is something wrong, Maria-san?
No, I'm just going through a minor depression.
But still, Hayate-kun, you seem a little strange.
Did Nagi's grandfather say something to you?
I-It's like the idea of always remembering the mindset of a novice.
Anyway, I'm going to do my best as the butler Hayate.
Hold on...
I couldn't get a wink of sleep because of that.
I'll protect you from anyone who tries to make you cry.
Is that all right with you?
Hayate is so cool...
Hayate-kun's working hard.
He said something about the novice mind and a dream.
He did?
What dream?
He's working really hard,
like a businessman who has found meaning in life.
Could it be for the future between us?
Um, I think you have it wrong.
No, you mustn't!
Well, actually it's fine, but I'm not mentally prepared yet!
Um, how about you? Do you have a dream?
Of course. Wouldn't anyone have a lot?
Like I want to be a manga author
and sell 100 billion copies of what I publish.
Do you have something on your mind?
Nothing. You're too dazzling for me right now.
But what exactly could Hayate's dream be?
I don't know, but since he made such a big speech,
I'm sure he has something big.
But Nagi, I'm sure the dream you have in mind is different from what he has in his mind.
On another note, what could Hayate-kun's dream really be?
What? My dream?
Yes!
But that was like a kid's mistake, and it's embarrassing to say it.
Please don't worry, I won't laugh.
Um...
What is it?
Note: 3LDK is a Japanese housing term which stands for
"3 individual rooms, Living room, Dining room, and Kitchen"
3LDK.
3LDK!
And my dream is to live in an apartment with 3 separate rooms
with a living room, dining room, and a kitchen.
I want to live in a 3LDK peacefully without being chased by anyone.
Tha... That's enough. You can stop now Ayasaki-kun.
And the reason is-
I-I see. So your dream is to live in a 3LDK.
Is that too big?
It doesn't have to be in Tokyo.
I think it's good.
Really?
The bigger the dream, the better...
Hayate-kun!
Yes?
I just remembered that your cell phone is still broken.
After all, it's inconvenient,
so please go buy another one with your budget.
Yes, then right away.
Oh, and you need to take some breaks once in a while,
so you can have the day off today.
So how about strolling around the city a little?
I bought a good one since I had the chance.
So this is what the One-Seg function is.
I can have a TV-Phone with it.
Wow, I can store 1,000 email addresses. This is amazing.
But I don't need that many.
I don't have that many friends.
Oh yeah, I wonder what my friends in high school are doing now.
School, eh...
I haven't had a chance to go,
so I haven't dealt with it all this time.
I did pay the entire tuition, didn't I?
What am I thinking? Could I still...
...want to return to school?
Okay!
I came on a whim, but it's hard to enter.
But I should still be a student of this school.
I have to not act suspicious.
Um...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm not a suspicious person, at all!
You're Hayate-kun, right?
Nishizawa-san?
I-It's been since Christmas when we last met.
What have you been doing up till now?
W-Well...
Souya-kun and the rest were all worried about you, too,
since you never come to school.
Well, a lot has happened since the end of last year.
A lot?
I'm not sure how to explain.
It's like, there's a huge debt, and my parents disappeared,
and I was given to very generous people as a present because of the debt.
C-Could it be...
Well, a lot has happened,
and I'm working as a butler at a certain mansion.
Oh, so it's a joke? You're such a kidder, Hayate-kun.
But I'm really glad. I'm finally able to see your face this year.
I'm really happy.
I-It's nothing. Don't take my words so seriously.
What are you doing flirting by the gate?
S-Souya-kun.
Hey, it's Hayate!
Rumor has it you quit school!
I haven't really quit it...
Really?
Aren't you glad, Nishizawa, to have your dear Prince back?
W-What are you saying?
Are you an idiot or something, Souya-kun?
It's only natural to worry about classmates, right?
But you were about to cry when you heard he'd quit.
So you were worried about me.
Thank you, Nishizawa-san.
O-Of course, since we're classmates.
Then, maybe I should try and come back.
What are you saying, Ayasaki.
You've dropped out.
Is it all right for the teacher to say such a lie?
Stop it, Nishizawa. I'm only speaking the truth.
Ayasaki's parents came here around noon on Christmas...
...and told us to give them back
the remaining tuition since he would no longer come.
Hayate-kun, weren't you paying your own tuition
since your parents wouldn't?
Yeah.
Then it's harsh for you to consider him dropped out
because you gave his parents the money.
But they said to give the money, so-
I see, so I can't go to school anymore.
Where are you going, Hayate-kun?
Are you really going to disappear like this?
You can't do that.
If we bring this up
before the board of education, then I'm sure...
If we do that, the teachers will have to take responsibility for my parents' selfishness.
Don't worry about me.
So, this is goodbye, Nishizawa-san.
It was only for a short time, but goodbye, my high school life.
Wait, Hayate-kun!
I love you, Hayate-kun!
I don't want to say goodbye like this.
So please go out with me!
The moment she said that, I realized something.
Without thinking, her face spontaneously came to mind.
Her sad face hit me hard.
Will you date me?
Um...
I'm sorry.
I'm...
...only interested in 2-D girls.
Gahhh!!!
That was a joke.
Actually right now, I have someone I can't leave untended.
You jerk!!!
To Hayate who's not used to girls,
he thought it'd be more manly to reject her
so she would come to hate him,
but comedy anime main characters never get dumped with dignity.
I've just returned.
Hey, Hayate.
What happened to your face?
A minor thing.
By the way, you bought a cell phone, right?
Show it to me.
What are you doing to it, Milady?
There.
I registered my address in the number 1 slot.
Thank you very much, Milady.
Yup. Call or email me as much as you like.
Yes.
Hayate-kun, I haven't given up on you.
Make sure you pay, okay?
Ichigo daifuku = Bean paste with strawberry
Ichigo daifuku
Kuru kuru mawaru yume nante... = Dreams of spinning drums are...
Kuru kuru mawaru yume nante...
Here Wataru-kun, I finished these, so I brought them back.
So how were they?
60%, I'd say.
I told you they're not movies girls can understand.
But I'm at an age that I want to understand guys' minds!
You learn about guys' minds from monster movies?
But Nishizawa-san, the boy you like quit school, right?
Yes! His house was empty and there wasn't any hint of him.
I wanted to meet him at least one more time and talk to him.
You'll never find a lost person like that, idiot.
Why do you say such a hopeless thing?!
Oh, Wataru-kun.
I don't usually watch them, but are animes interesting?
Only the ones I thought were interesting are on those shelves, but I don't know if you'd find them interesting.
Stop those "ehh"!
Listen! Interesting or uninteresting is only a personal opinion!
You'll never find out until you watch and check them out yourself!
So stop whining and watch!
Think, then act.
Think if it will be really interesting for you or not.
Now that's my coach!
But since they're all rented out, start with Getsumen To Heiki.
Bamboo... Bamboo...
Damn you bamboo vendor! Always getting in my way!
I-I just remembered something I need to do, so I'll head home!
Bamboo... Bamboo...
Damn, she got away.
Let's take better care of customers.
But can you really find someone who's disappeared in this huge city?
He must have been a really nice person.
Wataru-kun, we finished these, so I'm here to return them.
Hey debt-ridden butler. How were they?
I learned a good life lesson from them, but Milady didn't like them much.
The two never manage to meet.
However-
Oh no!
Kazuki asked for me to get a tape, didn't he?
No way, is that Hayate-kun?
To be able to meet at a place like this...
Are we destined to be?
It's no time to me to lose myself in a delusion.
I need to go after him!
Hayate-kun! Hayate-kun!
Hayate-kun!
He's so fast. I can't catch up with him.
B-But I have to keep up so I don't lose sight of him.
He finally finished.
So could he be living here?
H-Huh?
W-Wait? It's more like a mansion than a house!
Why is Hayate-kun living here?
Oh yeah, Hayate-kun said something about being in debt or something.
Then this must be a yaku** house.
Hayate-kun must be going through lots of troubles in here.
Can we hear your story?
What? A suspicious girl?
We thought it might be one of Milady's friends, so we wanted to confirm.
Let me go! Let me go!
Black suits and scary faces!
They're definitely yaku**!
No!
I'm going to be treated to activities
that can't be made viewable for young audiences.
Public school?
Maybe she's from Hayate-kun's old school.
Well, it doesn't look like she's someone suspicious,
so please let her hands go.
Let me go! Let me go!
Yes.
Hey, let her hands go for now.
Yes!
She ran away!
Chance!
Um, I didn't say let her get away...
I'm sorry; we'll catch her right away.
I managed to get away, but I have no clue where Hayate-kun is.
But wow, yaku** people are amazing.
I bet Wataru-kun won't believe me
if I tell him a mansion this big exists.
Anyways, I have to find Hayate-kun fast and get out of here.
Comedic shot.
Realistic shot.
Why?!
Why is there a tiger at a house in Japan?!
I'll really die from this!
And it's chasing me!
Why am I chasing her?
Is this my hunting instinct I thought I had lost?
Oh no!
Then I shall listen to my instinct and...
...I shall...
Lick her all over!
No, that's the wrong instinct.
Hayate-kun!
Ina**ma Kick!
It's an ultimate move for only those who have overcome hardship with effort and guts.
Um, I never trained, you know.
God... He's causing trouble as always.
And thanks to the DVDs we rented from Wataru-kun, I shouted out the attack name, as well...
This isn't what I meant by a life lesson.
Hayate-kun!
Eh, Nishizawa-san?
Thank goodness you're here.
Let's hurry and escape from here.
What?
Hey, Hayate.
What are you doing?
Milady!
There are things you can tell the moment you lay eyes upon others.
Hayate, who is that woman?
Ah, she's Nishizawa-san. My former classmate.
Hayate-kun, and she is?
She's Lady Nagi, this mansion's-
It's women's intuition.
The people who are destined to fight over someone dear to them.
The moment they saw each other, they both knew it.
They are rivals.
What? My background is a hamster?
It got eaten!
My hamster's weak, so weak!
Fine, I'll step aside for today,
but I'll bring a stronger hamster next time!
Rest assured and wait for me, Hayate-kun!
Nishizawa-san!
She's a funny person, as usual.
You can't, okay.
You can't leave me and go somewhere else, okay?
Please don't worry. I don't have
anywhere to go other than here.
Because there are those who can't even if they want to.
Um, Nagi?
I've decided!
Hayate has done a lot for me.
I must answer his kindness as his master.
Lady Nagi has made up some kind of mind.
Next time, we'll fight against the huge school again.
And leaving that aside...
For today, I'll borrow these.
Thanks a lot.
Business, business.
Kendama and Carrot is rented out!
Yes, they just got rented.
Andarta!
Wataru's video shop is making business.
They're having 50%-off service, too.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Hello, I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
Starting today, the BGM will be Milady's song.
Yes. The ability to sing is an important factor as the next head of Sanzenin family.
It describes well how rough and hard to tame you are.
It's a wonderful song.
What, is that supposed to be a compliment?
Of course, it is.
You can sense your charming acts from the song.
Charming? You make me blush.
Bye bye!
Milady, some paperwork has arrived from Hakuou Academy.
It's a transfer form.
For you.
Oh mine.
What do you mean mine?!
It's paperwork for you to transfer in.
Then I'll let you hear my application process story.
I'll tell you what Hakuou's exam style and questions are like.
No thanks.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Those Who Seize the Summer Seize the Application Process.
You're the person I have faith in,
so let's go to school together.
Run up to the stage of dreams!