Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
Our country's first manned exploratory
space rocket, the Lion, was launched.
However, 72 seconds after liftoff...
The liquid fuel booster suddenly exploded...
And although the Space Control Center activated
what could be called its self-destruct system,
the flight suspension system
did not function correctly...
The Lion fell into an urban area and caused a
huge disaster with many civilian casualties.
Eleven years later...
Asumi's Cherry Blossom
For becoming a rocket driver, physical fitness is even
more important than knowledge or engineering!
Jogging everyday is fundamental.
Yuigahama Clinic
What's wrong, little one?
Just now...
It seemed like someone was watching.
Now then, the answer to question five is...
Kamogawa. Kamogawa?
Kamogawa Asumi.
How many times do I have to call you, hm?
I'm sorry.
Why are you always just gazing at the sky?
It wasn't the sky.
I was looking at space.
Space?
Fine, then. Look at space, or whatever it is,
as much as you want.
I heard...
Huh?
I heard that childhood friend
of yours really is an idiot.
Hey, wait up!
Hey, Fuchuuya!
There's a rumor floating around school
about the essay she read out
loud during Japanese class.
She said, "I have a ghost friend who used to
be an astronaut." I heard she was serious.
She's already in middle school.
Is there something wrong with her?
You know...
If you hang around her,
you'll become an idiot too.
Ow...
What are you doing?
Oh, looks like you bumped into my leg.
Idiot!
Sorry about that.
Damn it! I'll remember this!
Who's that?
I feel like I've seen him before, but...
For becoming a rocket driver, physical fitness is certainly
more important than knowledge or engineering!
But doesn't it seem like this
pace is way faster than usual?
I give up!
Go on alone, little one!
Okay! I'll wait for you up ahead.
Hey!
Huh?
I'm Shimazu Takashi.
I-I'm...
I know. You're Kamogawa Asumi, right?
Y-Yeah...
Wait there for just a second.
Here, have this.
To Space: The Human Race Stands on Earth
Utagawa Keigo
This... What's this for?
I went to Yuigahama Elementary School, too.
Huh?
I was absent a lot, so you
might not remember me.
Remember the essay presentation in the gym?
My dream is to become a rocket driver!
I knew that you were interested in space.
Besides, I don't need this book anymore.
What do you mean, you don't need it...
For now, this is enough for me.
I've been sketching every day.
Even though it's just scribbling.
I see...
Hey, he's not with you today?
Who?
The ghost of the astronaut.
Huh? Umm...
You can see him?
No way!
But you really are amazing.
You can see something that no one else can.
Hey, Takashi!
What are you doing over there?
It's time for your examination!
Oh man.
That lady is pretty scary when she gets angry.
Well, see you later.
Thank you for the book!
So you were waiting for me, little one...
Let's go, Lion-san!
Yeah...
H-Hey, little one!
Did something good happen?
Hey, Asumi, finished yet?
Yes!
Kamogawa
Bye!
Around this area, I can't keep up with her at all!
She always quickens her
pace when she gets here...
So that was it.
Hey, what are you always drawing here?
Huh?
Nah, it's not really something I can show off.
Really? I want to see!
Oh, well I was... I was drawing that.
That cherry blossom tree in the
park, on top of that hill.
I really want to draw the cherry blossoms in full bloom,
but that tree's flowers don't bloom.
Why?
It's the only cherry blossom tree that didn't
burn down during the Lion accident, but...
Since that accident, no matter how many
years pass or how many springs come...
for some reason, no flowers
will blossom anymore.
So my drawing is still incomplete.
When those cherry blossoms bloom,
I'll show you my drawing.
Okay.
But doesn't that mean you won't
show it to me for a long time?
Huh? What?
You've got a pretty sharp wit, Kamogawa!
I always thought your specialty
was being absent-minded.
That's mean! I'm not absent-minded!
Wow! Shimazu-kun, you're really good!
You can really tell it's a space shuttle!
Of course. You're making a big deal out of it.
Hey, you promised, right?
Let me see your drawing, too.
Mine is...
Hmm?
I'd rather not show you, after all.
Hey, let's stop by the arcade!
Let's go! What about you, Fuchuuya?
I'm not going to that waste of time.
But you'll laugh!
I promise I won't laugh!
What should I do...
Hey, isn't that Kamogawa
and Shimazu from class E?
What? They're going out?
We gotta tell everyone!
Let me borrow your cell phone! Cell phone!
Sure!
Huh? Fuchuuya?
Where are you going?
The arcade.
Hey, you laughed after all!
Sorry about that.
But it's just like you, Kamogawa.
Huh?
It'd be great if you could become one.
A rocket driver.
You've already read the
entire book from before?
Yeah. It was really interesting.
Then I'll bring you something else later.
Thank you!
You know what?
I'm really glad that I was able to come
to the planetarium with you.
I see.
Thank you for visiting our planetarium today.
We will now introduce you to
the world of the spring sky.
You certainly have a lot of books
about astronauts, Shimazu-kun.
I suppose.
Hey, look over there.
Hmm?
The hospital's second floor window.
When I was little, I was always a patient there.
I couldn't move much, and the only things I could see
from that window were the sky and the stars.
Before I knew it, I got interested in space.
How far does space stretch out?
Is there an end to space?
If there is, what lies beyond?
I wanted answers to those questions,
so I read as many books about it as I could.
I see...
But, the answers don't really exist anywhere.
My dream was to go and see for myself,
but it's probably impossible.
Don't say that.
Why do you say it's impossible?
It'll be over soon...
my life.
It's just a joke! A joke!
I thought you'd notice it
with your sharp wit again.
I'm just saying that I'm not very smart.
Well, see you.
You can go!
You can definitely go!
Since I'll be driving the rocket!
Let's go together. To space.
Thanks. If you're driving, I might be able to go.
Together, huh?
Hey!
Hey! Are you all right?
Get a hold of yourself, kid!
It's not like he'd be able to hear me...
I gotta call the little one...
I'm fine.
Huh?
It'll settle down quickly.
I'm used to it.
Don't tell me, you can...
I'm fine.
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Scoop!
Kiss!!
Shimazu and Kamogawa are together!!
Kamogawa, aren't you on duty today?
You should at least make sure you clean
the blackboard before class starts.
Yeah...
Hey, why would they do something like that?
It seems that by being with Shimazu-kun,
I'm causing him trouble, too.
Kamogawa.
Hmm?
You haven't come around lately.
Has something happened?
Yeah, I guess...
I still have more books about space.
"I still have some books about space,
so come to my room," huh?
What are you going to do when
you pull her into your room?
You!
Ow!
What are you getting all
serious about, Shimazu?!
Ow! Let go!
I said let go!
Dammit! Do you want to die?!
I...
I don't need any books anymore.
That's enough...
I don't have anything to do with Shimazu-kun.
Hey, Lion-san.
Why did I say something like that?
I've been acting strange these days.
I don't really know myself.
I wonder why...
What's wrong, Asumi?
Aren't you going to school?
I don't want to go today.
I see.
Make sure you go tomorrow.
Yeah...
Kamogawa!
Look, listen to me calmly.
Shimazu... died.
His last words were for you to have this book.
Seems like he was so sick
that he could barely run.
Hey, don't you think
Kamogawa-san's kind of cold?
Even though she's got a weird personality,
shouldn't she at least show some tears?
I heard she said some harsh things
to Shimazu-kun before.
Who does she think she is?
That tree's flowers don't bloom.
When those cherry blossoms bloom,
I'll show you my drawing.
What he saw from that window every
day was you running, little one.
Since a long time ago.
Lion-san...
Deep in my heart...
It really hurts...
I promise I'll go there someday.
Let's meet in space, Shimazu-kun.
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
I saw Marika-chan smiling
brightly for the first time.
But it was only in a photograph.
All I said was that it was cute,
but I ended up getting her angry at me.
I wonder why.
And to think, we have to start our next
round of training feeling like this...
Next time on Twin Spica:
Survival Training.
Survival Training
End