Finally...
We've done it!
No...
Close?!
But how?
You should know by now...
that Dysdark... will always return!
Lady Dyspear entrusted everything to me before her end.
Until every dream has been sealed...
Despair will...
never disappear!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Toward a Distant Dream,
Go! Princess Precure!
More thorns!
No... What now?
You can make your peace!
You and I can't coexist.
This endless battle of ours...
is our fate.
Guess we've gotta fight...
Wait!
Flora?
Continuing this fight won't change a thing!
What are you doing?
I don't know.
But I do know...
that I need to talk with Close!
Flora!
Go on!
What?
Don't worry.
Just trust her.
Mermaid?
Flora!
It's in your hands now!
Right!
What, you're alone now?
If you want a fight...
I'm happy to oblige!
Haruka...
How fitting that it ends with you...
Cure Flora!
The stage is set for you and me.
So... let's dance!
If defeating Dyspear wasn't enough to end the despair...
then that means...
Focus!
Was the princess you dreamed of supposed to be this weak?!
If so, you'll never defeat me!
I'll keep dragging you into despair...
until you finally break!
As long as dreams exist,
despair is sure to follow...
for all eternity.
Despair is... sure to follow?
What... is despair?
Despair...
You couldn't be a princess in a million years!
I get it!
It's over.
Yes...
despair will... always follow.
Despair is all around us.
I've faced no shortage of hardship in my path.
But I can't pretend it wasn't there...
No, I wouldn't want to!
What're you yapping about?!
Happiness and hardship are two sides of the same coin.
But...
both of them made me who I am!
It's nonsense!
Stoooop!
Freeeeze!
Both dreams and despair...
have helped me grow.
Silence!
Maybe joy and sorrow together are what dreams are made of?
Sileeeeeeence!
Despair will always follow.
Yeah.
You haven't seen the last of it.
But I'll overcome it.
I might give in from time to time, but I'll keep my chin up.
After all, we wouldn't be here...
...without a dream...
Dreams will always follow, too!
As long as we have despair,
dreams will continue to shine!
And always...
With strength, grace and beauty, huh?
All right, I'm done with you.
Any more of this will make me nauseous.
I'll disappear... for now.
See ya.
Close...
Soon...
Adieu.
Flora!
And Close?
Yeah, we talked.
I think we're fine now!
Good...
Open!
The door to your dream!
Father!
Kanata... Where have...
Towa?
The castle!
Father!
Mother!
It's really you?
Are you really Towa?
But how?
What happened?
Towa...
Welcome back!
Thank you so much!
You have our sincerest gratitude for saving our kingdom.
Same to you, little ones.
It was an honor!
I'm glad it worked out.
Yes.
What now?
I suppose the Keys are returning to their slumber having served their purpose.
Well, I guess the fight is over.
Which means we have to return the Keys and Perfumes to Hope Kingdom, right?
But once vous do, vous can no longer travel between worlds.
You can't mean...
Le two worlds were originally separate and were never meant to cross paths.
Which means...
that we've gotta say goodbye?!
I see...
That's... right.
Closing Ceremony
Marble Doughnuts are still the best!
My doughnut's good too!
I'll see about that!
Oh, is that a new flavor?
Sure is!
That's the last one.
Then shall we split it between us?
I'm in!
Bro, you've got crumbs on your face!
Er, thanks...
Kirara, isn't your flight soon?
Yeah... I should get going.
Then I shall as well.
I thank you all from the bottom of my heart!
From here on out, I'll work with my brother...
to ensure Hope Kingdom's... hopes and dreams...
always keep...
their...
flame...
Towie...
Towa!
Perf...
I promised myself I wouldn't cry...
Towa...
None of us could promise that.
Don't worry.
We'll meet again.
Even if we're apart,
we're connected in spirit.
I'm sure...
okay?
Right!
All of us...
Are always together!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
Red roses are more beautiful than I gave them credit for.
'Cause they're Cure Scarlet's color?
S-Silence!
Really, why must I put up with you?!
I can't even fly anymore since the Three Dusketeers's power disappeared, so I'm stuck with you, 'kay?
Shirogane, dorm mother.
Oh my, a guest?
Do you like roses?
Er... yes.
Sorry for the wait!
There you are!
We've got a lot of work ahead!
Bon.
Now Kuroro, le path to becoming le professeure royal is harsh!
I'll do my best!
Vous must start with le très bien tour into le excellent saut!
Perf!
Prince Kanata,
I think that should do for today's patrol.
Very well.
Now it's back to the castle!
Brother!
How fares the forest?
As quiet as can be.
For now, at least.
You've no need to worry.
I'm sure...
the next generation of princesses will stand against despair.
Yes...
they will.
It really has been a lot of fun!
It hasn't been easy,
but having this Key brought me this far.
The Key was but an opportunity.
All it did was give you a little push.
Everything after that was your own strength, Haruka.
You sure?
Well, if you say so, I guess I can't argue!
Yup, I did all right!
In that case...
I think I'll be fine from now on.
I can go forward without this key.
I'll keep chasing my dream...
to be the princess only I can be!
Thank you,
Haruka.
I'm glad I met you.
Me too!
Thank you, Kanata.
We'll meet again, right?
Yes.
If you wish...
...from the bottom of your heart...
Yes.
This is a tale of girls who never stop chasing the distant horizon!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
"And so, the princesses continued
their journey toward their dreams."
Do the princesses ever see each other again?
Oh, Mommy!
The Princess and the Key of Dreams
By Nanase Yui
Don't worry.
As long as one chases her dream...
she'll once again find the Key inside her heart.
If they have that Key...
then they will...
I'm certain.
Thanks for your support over the past year!
It's been a full bloom blast thanks to you!
Let me introduce my new friend!
I'm Cure Miracle!
I'll pick up Cure Flora's torch
and give it my own magical spin!
Curappa Rappapa!
Awesome!
For now, boys and girls...
Adieu!