ToraDora! 11 Tl by KloneDesu
It's so hot...
It's September, why is it so hot?
Guess we should hurry and finish the left over curry from yester...
Good morning Minorin!
Hey you two!
Have you been doing well?
Y-Yeah, how have you been—
Hey there everyone!
Did you guys finish your summer homework?!
Did you brush your teeth?
Did you bathe?
What gives Haruta?
Why are you so hyped up?
Aha!  I bet something happened during the summer break, am I right?
The summer break is a thing of the past!
The second semester is the new age.
The Cultural Festival is the next stage, where something new will—
How nice, a summer break with "happenings."
Y-Yori-chan sensei?
But anyway, I guess it's natural that something would happen.
It's summer for a 17 year old after all.
It's not like the summer of a single woman who's entered her thirties.
The world is so unfair isn't it...?
It seems that nothing happened for Yuri-chan sensei.
So, like last year we've been told the event will only be held for one day.
Even with the Chairman on our side...
The decision wasn't made based simply on one side's opinion.
This is an exchange.
We've yet to begin our negotiations with the teachers.
Indeed!
If things carry out as we planned,
even if we aren't able to make it last for two days, we'll be winners in the end.
I'll liven up this year's Cultural Festival no matter what.
This is the grand finale of my schooling after all.
Takasu-kun, let's look for a UFO next!
Hey, you stupid Chi!
What are you doing you slowpoke?!
I told you, I can't touch the ball right now because my nails are long.
They'll break if I do.
You stupid Chi!
What a cute smile.
Ami-chan is an angel indeed.
I'm more for palm-top Taiga.
Then I'm for Kashii.
Kihara's really good, too.
Woah, Ami-chan's riding on Taiga's back!
Ooh, I wish they would ride me too...
Ladies and zentlemen!
What now?
There are no ladies here.
And what the hell is "zentle?"
Don't you all want to see the cute non-everyday actions of the girls you secretly like?
Are you alright?
You weren't into something strange over the summer break were you?
Let me finish talking first.
The Cultural Festival is about to begin.
We have to discuss our activity for it during tomorrow's extra long homeroom session.
And I'm one of the Cultural Festival activity council members!
So what?
So-I'm-saying—
If we decide to do a maid café at the Cultural Festival, we can see the girls in maid outfits.
If all the guys get together and get it to a vote, we win by numbers and there's no complaints.
How's that?!
That sounds pretty good.
And this is Haruta, too.
Wait a second.
If that's the case. Rather than maids, I want—
China dresses!
That could work, too.
Don't you think so, too, Takasu?
Y-Yeah, I guess.
I'm already used to seeing a maid type outfit at her part-time job anyway.
I guess the tighter fitting China dress would be more…
No, I can't!
If it's a tight fit that means—
I have to prepare those fake boob pads again!
What are you talking about?
O-Oh, nothing!
I would prefer something like... the Lolita style more than a China dress.
Takasu...
...you're a genius!
In that case, I want nurses!
I want stewardesses!
You fool, call them customer-room employees!
I want shrine maidens!
Hold-hold on guys! Stop being so selfish!
Oh man, what were we talking about?
A cos-play café.
If we go with that, it'll solve all our problems.
That's it!
Taiga, I'll go ahead okay?
Yeah.
Ryuuji!
Huh?
Look at this.
W-What's with you all of the sudden.
Woah, that's terrible.
That stupid Chi ripped it.
Hey, wait a second.
Would you stop saying such misleading things?
You just stepped on your own sleeve, fell over, and tore it yourself.
It all started because you dodged the ball, stupid Chi!
I already told you, my nails are too long right now!
Enough already.
I'll fix the ripped part for you alright?
Spoiling her again...
Make sure you have it done by next week.
H-Hey!
You can't just blame it on someone else and leave!
Hey!
They sure are full of energy aren't they?
Kushieda.
Well then, I suppose we should get back to the classroom, too.
Y-Yeah.
You're right.
Oh yeah, I was wondering...
H-Have you seen a UFO since—
Instant noodles sure are fierce enemies of the dieting warrior!
How scary. Gotta avoid it, gotta avoid it.
Looks like this'll be no good without some inner support cloth.
Guess I'll slice up one of Yasuko's old undershirts.
It's ringing Taiga.
It's okay.
Seriously, that freakin' geezer.
Freakin' geezer?
What are you talking about?
Whatever, but it bothers me so would you—
Oh, shut up!
W-What's with you all of the sudden?
I told you to leave it.
He found me an apartment and just left me after remarrying, 'cause I got in the way.
He abandoned me.
He's a cold-hearted man.
He's your old man?!
He's a freakin' geezer!
No matter what kind of man he is, he is your father.
Calling him a freakin' geezer...
No matter how far apart, families are people whose hearts are—
I said he's a freakin' geezer!
Frea-kin'-kin'!
Don't remember stuff like that!
Different mother...
Ahh, Inko-chan, not again—
Diff—different— different mother...
What is it?
Are you talking about your daddy, Ryu-chan?
No, not my old man!
He was a wonderful person you know.
Just so he could be stabbed at anytime—
Not that again!
That's not wonderful at all!
Don't stay stuff like that in front of others!
But—
So, we'd like to decide our activity and our Miss High school contestant.
I don't think anyone has a problem with Ami-chan being our Miss High School contestant.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Wha—?
I'm grateful for the thought though.
I've already been chosen as the host for the Miss-Con.
So even if you choose me, I won't be able to enter it.
That's why I think—
Aisaka-san should enter it!
I mean, Aisaka-san is really tiny and cute.
Plus, everyone knows who she is!
What the hell are you saying you super stupid Chi?!
Why do I have to do something like that?
Hmm, but that might work.
Taiga definitely is famous.
She might get pretty far.
You...
Come on now.
Be good, Taiga-chan.
You're part of this class, too. You should happily participate in such events.
Damn it you stupid Chi! If you still don't get it, I'll crush the entire Culture Fes—
Now, now, calm down, just calm down.
You might really win Aisaka.
Right?
Alright.
Our Miss High School contestant is Taiga!
So next, we'll discuss the activity that our class will be do—
Me, me!
Yes, Notoku-kun!
How about a cos-play café?
What?!
That totally reeks of otakuness.
Plus other classes will definitely have something similar.
I would never want to do something like that.
Um-You know—Um-Um—My opinion—
No-Not that I really want to do it—
I hate that sort of thing, but—
But it'd be nice if everyone can have fun right?
Uh-Um-Yeah—
ha-ha-haun—ted!
Oops, my nose it bleeding.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not trying to say anything weird.
I just wanted to do a h-h-haunted house.
Kushieda, I think you should give that a rest now.
Your body won't last through it.
I won't let you...
I won't let you do it...
Yu-Yurichan?
Café? No!
Get a band together and do a live show? No that's the worst thing to do in Japan right now.
A mere one day of liveliness is just an illusion. You're going to go bad before Christmas anyway.
Did something happen to her over the summer break?
Anyway, we'll get nowhere at this rate!
It's our last resort; let's submit our ideas!
Everyone write what you want to do on a piece of paper!
No matter what the girls write, it's a waste of effort.
They're no match for the men students' alliance.
Alright, you're all done writing right?!
Let's do it then!
Shake-and-draw!
D-Draw?! What are you—
Here's the announcement!
This year's Cultural Festival activity will be pro-wrestling—
Who wrote pro-wrestling show?
And they even put "Bam" in parenthesis too!
What the hell are you writing?!
More importantly, why didn't you make it a vote?
Oh...
That stupid Chi!
I'll make her go through a new hell every time she reincarnates!
Why don't you give it up and just enjoy a class event for once?
You're too closed-minded.
What, you're the only one acting jolly here.
Jolly? You mean me?
Ever since we got back from that trip.
H-Huh, why?
What's wrong?
Weird... It won't let me withdraw money.
The balance says zero.
It can't be helped, then I'll—
That's impossible.
It must be because I kept ignoring the phone calls.
He would do something like this? I can't believe it.
You mean the phone calls from before?
He's been calling several times since a little while back.
But I've been ignoring it since he pisses me off.
And then he went and emptied my living expenses account.
That freakin' geezer...
I really want to kill him.
You shouldn't talk like that about your parents.
He's threatening me isn't he?
Just pick it up for now.
Nothing can be done until you talk.
Plus, you need money right?
So she picked up, great, but why am I here seeing him... alone?
I see.
In any case, it seems my daughter won't come see me.
Right... sorry.
I just had to see Taiga.
But I guess she just hates me more now.
Sorry about that.
Was it, Takasu-kun?
If that's the case, order whatever you'd like!
Oh, no thank you.
I'm about to have dinner.
Oh-Um-I'll take your offer!
I'll get the egg bagel!
Is that so?
Excuse me!
Can we place an order?
An egg bagel for him and I want one of these salmon bagel.
With plenty of cheese~
Put in as much as you can.
Oh yeah, before I forget, here's the money.
I just wanted to see her no matter what.
I had something important to talk to her about.
Something important?
Oh-Um-So are you... going out with Taiga?
N-No, I'm not!
We're just normal friends. We're not going out or doing anything of the sort.
She just lives next door and we just happen to get along.
I see.
Then I guess you've heard a lot about her family from her.
My new wife is too young.
So Taiga just couldn't get used to the new family.
Misunderstandings piled on top of one another and...
My current wife, her name is Yu.
Somehow they were left with the option of either Taiga or her leaving the house...
So Taiga did...
I want to live with Taiga. Together, just like before.
That's what I wanted to tell her today.
I'll never make the same mistake again.
I plan to start over with Taiga.
I'm going to be breaking up with Yu soon.
So I'll live with Taiga.
Because we're family.
Because I love her.
Oh my goodness
Your dad said that he's going to come pick you up.
What are you doing?!
Do it properly, you have to put it in the water for more than five seconds!
Oh shut up.
Keep out of this.
I promised to do the dishes in exchange for you meeting him.
Then wash it properly.
Whatever, just go away.
You know, your dad is kind of different.
He's not like the usual adult...
Didn't I tell you to go away?
Go heat up some water and prepare for tea or something.
You dad was really worried about you.
He said he wanted to live with you ag—
Are you stupid?
I'm being serious here.
Your dad said that he wanted to live with you.
Your father asked me so I—
You don't have to bother with needless things!
Keep your nose out of other peoples families!
You're the one who made me go there!
You're just going to take the money and be done?!
I am.
That's why I'm here washing your dishes.
So this ends here.
I'm never going to see him again!
Hey, stop messing around... you have to—
Shut up! Don't touch me like you're close to me or something!
Your dad was sad because you were ignoring him! He seemed really pitiful!
I'm much more pitiful!
Tai-ga?
Alright, did everyone get one?
I felt like I was responsible for that.
So I made this.
A script book for a pro-wrestling show.
Hey, maybe we should do something else.
The class's submission—
Here you go.
Everyone, please at least show some interest in it!
We can't go back.
Yuri-chan already stamped the activity form and submitted it.
Wow, this might actually be pretty interesting.
Everyone actually has a role, Haruta-kun you're actually pretty amazing.
Wow, I'm the main character!
That makes me a little happy.
Ami-chan...
Oh you're right.
This is actually alright.
Haruta-kun, let's do our best together!
Alright, let's begin practicing!
Yeah!
The setting is in the near-future.
Everyone in 2-C is living peacefully with Ami-chan as their leader!
However! There are people who look at that peace distastefully.
The hallmark of evil Palm-Top Taiga and her minion, the delinquent Takasu Ryuuji!
Wait a second...
Why am I her minion and a delinquent?
Why am I the hallmark of evil?
Don't worry, don't worry. Just listen to the rest.
Palm-top Taiga descends upon 2-C. The students get mind controlled, one by one.
However, Ami-chan's hard efforts releases them from control and—
everyone gets together in the end,
successfully driving palm-top Taiga and delinquent Takasu Ryuuji away!
That's how it goes. Happily ever after, the end!
How's that?
We listen to the rest and that's it?
But it's simple yet, dramatic.
It might be pretty good.
No way!
I'll never do something like this!
Sheesh, Aisaka-san, you're so selfish.
Hey! First it's the Miss-Con and now this?!
Why do I have to do all these weird things?!
If hitting me makes you happy, then hit me as much as you like.
Alright, I will!
But nothing will come of that.
Woah, Palm-top Taiga's really into it.
They're already practicing.
That was really realistic!
Alright, now Taiga, do your mind-control line!
Your line, you know, here.
Huh? Taiga screams—
Amin kind of changed lately didn't she?
Yeah, you're right.
W-What is that?!
Dunno, Haruta-kun said I could get a part that's especially good.
Everyone listen to me!
A decision has been made from the school side!
In this year's Cultural Festival we will compete against each class!
The winner will receive prizes!
These are the prizes:
First, the class will get their own refrigerator for the rest of the year.
Don't you want to put your juice in it?
Second, even though we're supposed to get brand-new mellifluous air conditioners next year,
you'll get one within the month!
Ooh... don't you want to keep cool?
The outlet in the toilet that is currently restricted will be open for use.
Don't you want a place to curl your hair?
Finally, sale coupons for the Supermarket, Kanooya!
Sale coupons... don't you want them?
Wait, huh?
Hey! You guys have to get it together too!
Y-Yeah.
Hey, what should we do about dinner?
Yellow-tail fish.
What do you want me to do with yellow-tail?
Glaze.
You want me to glaze them?
Sorry, I've been waiting here... for a while.
Um...
You damn stalker!
Taiga!
Stop acting so tough already!
Let me go you stupid dog!
Are you on his side?
You're horrible. I thought that at least you were on my side!
I'm saying this because I'm on your side!
It's for your sake.
Who do you think he is?
He's your father.
He's come just to pick you up!
Can't you at least listen to what he has to say?!
You're wrong, that's just a stalker!
I don't need him!
Stop acting like a fool!
You were crying, saying he abandoned you.
Be honest with yourself, be more honest!
You actually want to go with him right?!
What do you know about me?
I don't need someone like that anymore.
I wasn't abandoned, I abandoned him!
I threw him away because he was useless trash!
You...
Does he—
Does that person, really look like trash to you?!
My old man will never come back, no matter how much I wish!
It wasn't for Taiga...
I...
I'm sorry Taiga...
It's okay.
Cause it's you...
So...
...don't make that kind of face anymore.
Tai...
It's a good thing right?
I'll just pretend that I think that.
Even though I don't know if I can really think that.
But since you say so...
...I'll pretend that I think that.
Thank goodness
This is good... it's what's supposed to happen.
Right?
Koigakubo Yuri, I've entered my thirties this summer...
Give me presents everyone!
More like, someone please take me...