Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
見送った手を振った
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
So happy for them
Alright...
Is there anyone who can explain what this "AD" means?
The time has finally come.
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
What?  Is something about to start?
Oh, yeah. Uh huh.
Tenshi's assault is going to begin.
Tenshi's assault?
An assault... but why?
It's because exams are coming up.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh... why?
You'll understand if you think about it.
Getting us to go to class is important.
But getting us to score well on our tests is important to Tenshi as well.
But this test period...
could also be a good opportunity to pull one over on Tenshi.
Looks like you have something in mind, Yurippe.
Let's hear it.
Completely get in the way of Tenshi's exams, and make her get failing grades.
That'll lower her scores to the lowest of the school.
And what will that accomplish?
Her fall from grace.
The Student Council sees her as almost majestic.
And if that majesty weakens?
At the very least, her image among the teachers and regular students will change.
And with that, changes will begin to surface.
Like what?
Who knows?  I can't predict that far ahead.
Then isn't this kinda meaningless?
However...
If by some small chance she's not an Angel created by God...
If her soul isn't made of steel...
If she has a human soul just like us...
Her fall from grace will deal her an effective emotional blow.
First, we'll decide which members to use for today's operation.
Preparations to take tests alongside Tenshi have already been completed.
Then wouldn't going in with everyone be okay?
No it wouldn't "be okay"!
I won't forgive any slip-ups!
If we get caught partway through, we'd all be moved to a different classroom...
We'd lose our ability to make Tenshi fail her exams.
I see.  I'm gonna pass, then.
Stuff like this can be handled by the pansies.
In that case, today's members will be...
Takamatsu-kun.
Hinata-kun.
Ooyama-kun.
Takeyama-kun.
Otonashi-kun.
Me again?
Please, call me Christ-
I just chose the members who look the most normal.
Now, then.
Operation... start!
The test seating will be assigned by lottery that morning.
Study Building B - Classroom
If we don't manage to get close to Tenshi, it'll be difficult to interfere.
Got it?
Pick the seat in front of her.
How are we supposed to do that?
Let's see...
20.  I missed!
11.  That's pretty far from Tenshi.
33.  Haha!  Not even close!
My turn.  25.  I'm pretty far, too.
Kyaa!  I'm number 1!
Hey wait... damn you!  Damn you!
Isn't anyone close to her?
Even next to her is okay.
One seat ahead.
YES!
So, what should I do?
When they're handing out the test sheets, grab two of them.
Then when they collect them after the test, switch one with Tenshi's.
Turn in that test paper blank...
Wait, turning it in blank will seem almost too unnatural.
Just put lots of stupid answers on it.
You make that sound easy...
Just write what you'd like to be in the future or something.
But it's a Physics test...
That's fine.  Just say you wanna become a pilot...
or maybe a dolphin trainer!
That's definitely stupid, alright...
So what do we do when they're being collected?
Hinata-kun!  Choose your timing well, and do something retarded!
Something everyone will notice!
I couldn't do that...
Why do you think I put you in here?
Wait.  That was what you were planning?
So, when the moment is right, Takeyama-kun will take Tenshi's test from the pile of answer sheets he'll receive from behind him...
and swap it with the fake.
At any rate, even if the unexpected happens, don't get confused.
Just follow each other's lead.  Understood?
Ah, but hold on a minute.
What should I write for her name?
"Tenshi".
Are you stupid?
Would "Student Council President" work?
It just might.
I mean, we're making her stupid enough to write stuff like dolphin trainer in her answers...
No way.  No one's stupid enough to not write their own name!
Actually, I'm surprised you guys don't even know her name!
We never had a chance to find out.
That's not cool at all!
Fine, you go and find out.
Go check the roster in the Teacher's Lounge.
Tch... fine.
Just a minute...
Where are you going?  Testing is about to start.
Oh, um... I'm just a little nervous.
Crap... what do I do?
Isn't it too cruel to hand in her test with the name "Student Council President"?
No no, this isn't the time for that.
With the question "What is the current in amperes that will flow when 3.0 volts is applied to a 20 ohm conductor?",
are we really gonna write in "I wanna be a Train Conductor!
Are you really that worried?
Uh, no... it's not that...
Try to calm down.  You'll be fine.
Um...
Ah, uh... Otonashi.
Otonashi-kun.
I don't know your name, either...
Me?  Tachibana.
First name?
First?  Kanade.
Tachibana...Kanade.
It has a beautiful sound to it.
Like her name, like the sound of a note being played...
TL Note: "Kanaderu" means to play a musical instrument.
It was a good name, I thought.
Thank you.
I've calmed down thanks to you, Tachibana.
Okay, do your best.
Tachibana Kanade.
Oh yeah, that's what it was.
So you already knew?!
I just forgot.
Alright, we're starting.
Sit down.
How strange.
I have no memories, so how am I finishing my test so smoothly?
Don't answer the questions seriously.
There's a chance you might disappear.
Oops.
I'm not supposed to take it seriously.
Alright.  Pass them forwards starting at the back.
W-What is that ?!
There's a monstrous bamboo shoot coming up from the ground!
Stupid Hinata.
Geez.  I guess I've gotta use it.
I put a rocket engine under your chair just in case you messed up.
How did you like your taste of space flight?
All it was was me hitting the ceiling and then dropping to the floor within seconds!
And how the hell did you make a rocket engine?!
I followed up after your mistake.  Be grateful.
Operation successful, right, Takeyama-kun?
No errors at all.
Also, call me-
Well, you're next, Takamatsu-kun.
What about me?
Create a distraction.
I-Isn't that Hinata-san's role?
Do you know the story of the Boy Who Cried Wolf?
Lies told over and over become less believable-
Exactly that!
W-Wait, is that why you brought so many of us?
Who knows?
I-I refuse.
You'll do it!
Just give it up and fly, and get smashed into the ceiling.
I've got to think of something to distract everyone.
So, what should I do for the next set of answers?
You've got it easy, huh?
You just have to be sneaky, no need to fly...
What are you saying?
I'm taking on a mission with extreme risk here!
Then switch with me.
No way!
See!? Cause your job is so much easier!
Congrats for having good luck in the lottery!
This is a job that requires the finely-honed nerves that only I have.
All you need to do is act stupid and go flying.
What was that?  Are you calling me stupid?!
HEY!
STOP FIGHTING!
Sorry!
They were arguing about an answer.
It's settled now.
Turns out Hinata got zero points.
Everything's okay, now.
No problems!
Sorry about the ruckus.
It's all good now!
I see.
Idiot!
Who is?!
So... what should I do for the next set of answers?
What subject is it?
World History.
Then answer all the questions as if the Earth were under attack by aliens.
Okay, pass them forwards starting at the back.
I've gotta do it.
You there, what's wrong?
Sensei, the truth is...
I only look skinny when clothed!
How's this?
I understand.  Sit down.
Yes...
I can't believe you thought such a stupid plan would work.
I had confidence, but...
Could it be said to be surprising?
Does it not match my character?
I've been training in secret.
We get it.  Put your shirt back on.
The plan went well again, right, Takeyama-kun?
Without a hitch.
Isn't it about time you call me-
Next is Ooyama-kun.
I knew this was coming!
I can't come up with anything!
Ooyama-kun, your seat's behind hers to her left.  That's pretty close, isn't it?
That's true!  So... maybe I don't have to do any weird gags?
Sure.  Just confess to Tenshi.
Okay!  Wait, what?
Confess to Tenshi.
"I'm sorry for not picking a better time and place."
"I've always loved you.  Please go out with me."  Something like that.
If you do it just like that, you won't need to fly.
Tch.  He just has to confess?  That's almost unfair.
No way!  Put yourself in my shoes!
You got off with just damage to your body.
The damage to my mind is going to be extreme!
I mean, I've never confessed to a girl before!
And I already know I'll get turned down.
It'll be good practice for someone as naïve as you.
I'm not like you, Hinata!  I don't want practice!
I only fall in love for real!
What's that supposed to mean?
You saying that my love is fraught with insincerity?
HEY!
NO FIGHTING!
Sorry!
Yuri was feeling anxious.
It was because she had a dream about Hinata.
Don't think the me today will be the same as the me tomorrow.
You'd better watch out.
That's what he told her.
And just then, Yuri found out that it was true!
There's two Hinata-kuns?
U-Um... you took it that way?
You mean there might be 3 or more?
Um... sure...
My condolences.
Anyway, it's all calmed down, so no need to worry.
Everything's fine.
Thanks for your concern.
What do you mean there's 3 or more of me?
What do you mean I was anxious?
Hey now, I cleaned up after your mess.  What's with that response?
You guys brought it upon yourselves.
So, how should I answer the next set of questions?
What's the subject?
English.
Well then, answer everything with Katakana.
Okay, pass them forwards starting at the back.
Tachibana-san!
I'm sorry for not picking a better time and place!
I've always loved you!
Please go out with me!
Well then, pick a better time and place.
Hey you, sit down.
Yes, sir.
Ahhh, now he's done it.
He's gonna go fl-
Hey, wait a minute here!
What is it?  Don't come close!
Why did I get sent flying?!
Because Ooyama-kun had already suffered damage to his heart.
Why me though?  I don't get it!
More importantly, everyone...
Let's have lunch!
UTW Presents:
Study Building A - Rooftop
No mistakes yet, right, Takeyama-kun?
It's all perfect.  And it's Christ.
How many more times am I gonna have to get smashed through the ceiling?
All the way until the tests are over.
Let's change members tomorrow!
Matsushita-kun and TK seem too heavy.
You chose me because I'm light?!
And besides, if you keep sending me flying like that, they'll get sick of it!
"Oh, he's flying again"... they won't even look!
That's why we need to keep this up and come up with more gimmicks!
What's in store for us?  I'm scared!  We're friends, right?
And that's why you should help!
So you help, too!
I wonder if I'll need to confess again tomorrow...
Maybe I'll take my pants off too, next time.
The operation was almost perfect.
But... will anything change if we do this?
All we've done is make a big ruckus like we usually do.
And like usual, things calm down and return to normal.
I thought that's all that would happen.
And, the testing period ended...
Staff Building 1 - Hallway, Outside Teachers Lounge
Tachibana?
What's wrong?  Did something happen?
Nothing.
- The Next Day -
It's begun.
What has?
The rumor about Tenshi scoring zeros across the board.
Seriously?
And all her answers were making fun of the teachers.
We went that far?
What did you guys do?
We went flying and spinning, and even went jumping out of windows.
What's with that?
But the teachers, they should realize it wasn't Tenshi, but someone's prank, right?
How many times do I have to tell you?  The teachers wouldn't realize that.
It's the same as it would go in reality.
The Student Council President turned in joke answers.
Therefore, Tenshi herself will be called into the office and scolded.
So, that's what happened back then...
I wonder if Tachibana explained it to them.
Who knows?
But it was all of the subjects.
Just how would she explain it to every last teacher?
Well, from the perspective of the teachers, it would seem like a lone rebellion.
A lone rebellion?
Gymnasium
Then, a few days later...
We heard about it at a school-wide assembly.
And so for those reasons...
Tachibana Kanade-san will be resigning as Student Council President.
And current Vice-President Naoi-kun will be standing in as President.
That's ridiculous!
She didn't resign, but was discharged.
Yurippe...
Now that she's been demoted to a common student like us,
I wonder if she'll be able to stop us now that she's lost her authority.
We'll carry out Operation Tornado tonight.
That's the last piece Iwasawa left behind.
What?!  Is it really okay for me to write the lyrics for it?
I suppose.
Fukigen sou na kimi to sugoshite
不機嫌そうな君と過ごして
After spending time with a sullen-looking guy like you
It all depends on how everyone will react...
to this new song, "Thousand Enemies", and the second incarnation of GirlDeMo.
わかったことがひとつあるよ
There's something I've come to understand
Wakatta koto ga hitotsu aru yo
Sonna furi shite tatakau koto ni hisshi
そんなふりして戦うことに必死
You're just acting like that, and really fighting
desperately.
Say...
Hm?
Who exactly are we fighting with?
Anyone who gets in our way.
Itsumademo kaenai de koori no youni
いつまでも　変えないで　氷のように
I never want you to change. Just like ice.
Who's gonna get in our way?
If anyone's coming, it'd be Tenshi, right?
Natsu no hizashi atsukutemo tokezu ni ite ne
夏の陽射し暑くても溶けずにいてね
Even if the hot rays of Summer beat down on you,
never thaw.
Oh wait, maybe it'll be that new acting President.
Isn't he just a normal student?
We can't shoot at him.
Kitto saki ni
きっと先に
For surely beyond that
Oh, really?
Utsukushii hyouga ga aru yo
美しい氷河があるよ
There's a beautiful glacier.
Will Tenshi come?
Katachi aru sonna kokoro
形あるそんな心
A finely-shaped heart
Daredatte kizukeba motteru
誰だって気づけば持ってる
If you stop to notice it, everybody has one.
Kimi mo motteru
君も持ってる
You have one, too.
Onaka ga suite arukenakunatte
お腹が空いて歩けなくなって
Hungry and unable to keep walking
She's here!
Wakatta koto ga hitotsu aru yo
わかったことがひとつあるよ
There's something I've come to understand.
We'll get her before she uses her Guard Skills.
Here I go!
Wait!  Don't shoot!
Why?
Yaru beki koto sakiokuri ni shite
やるべきこと先送りにして
I've been putting off the things I need to do
Something's strange.
Yaritai koto bakka yatteru
やりたいことばっかやってる
And only doing what I want.
W-What's strange?
I don't know for sure...
She doesn't seem hostile...
Gohan tabete tatakau shitakushi yo
ご飯食べて戦う支度しよ
I'll eat a meal before I set out to fight.
Like she won't resist us...
It's like she's here for a different reason, this time.
What are you talking about?
Itsumademo mottetai yo hagane no you na
いつまでも　持ってたいよ　鋼のような
I want to always keep mine like this, as hard as steel.
Donna mono mo toosanai ganko na iji wo
どんなものも通さない頑固な意地を
An unshakable will, that lets nothing through.
Kitto ima mo tachitsukushite mamori no tochuu
きっと今も立ちつくして守りの途中
I'm sure even now you're still standing firm in defense.
Yukute ni wa
行く手には
Blocking all escape
Tenshi?!  What are they doing out there?
Kazoekirenai
数え切れない
Their numbers are countless.
Teki ga ite atashi wo matteru
敵がいて あたしを待ってる
Enemies are here, and waiting for me.
What should we do?
Hang on a minute.
What's going on?  Something's strange.
Kimi ni mo matteru
君にも待ってる
They're waiting for you, too.
What is she doing?
What?!
That's Szechuan Tofu, which is so legendarily spicy none of the students will touch it!
Why is she getting that?!
Is she planning to make us eat it as revenge?
Saa sa susumou ikutsumo no kakehashi
さあさ進もういくつもの架け橋
Alright, let's advance. Across these countless bridges.
Yurippe-san.  The show is almost at its apex.
Itsumademo issho dakara koibito no youni
いつまでも　一緒だから　恋人のように
We'll always be together, just like lovers.
Your instructions?
Kitto saki ni
きっと先に
Surely just ahead
Soudai na keshiki ga matsu yo
壮大な景色が待つよ
A magnificent landscape awaits us.
Yeah...
Sono toki wa tamatteita
その時は溜まっていた
When that time comes, everything that's piled up
Start it up!
Start it up, please.
Sono kimochi zenbu kiite yaru
その気持ちぜんぶ聞いてやる
All of your feelings, I'll listen to them all.
Kimi ni mo kikasu
君にも聞かす
And I'll let you listen too.
Tappuri kikasu
たっぷり聞かす
I'll let you hear them all.
Academy Dining Hall,  Food Court
Szechuan Tofu
What the hell?
That's the spicy Szechuan Tofu.  It's famous for nobody ever ordering it.
Even the tough guys have it with some white rice.
This is what I grabbed, so I don't have a choice, do I?
One bite and it's this spicy?!
But... it's good.  Hinata, try some!
Huh?  No way!
Fine, one bite...
It's spicy!  It hurts!
But... the taste that comes afterwards is...
I see, this has a pretty deep flavor to it!
See?!
I'll bet you've never had such delicious Szechuan Tofu, right?
This menu item is surprisingly good.
That's the ticket Tenshi bought.
T-This?
Yep.
All she wanted was to eat this, huh?
This must be her favorite...
I took that simple happiness away from her.
Tenshi is human.
I can't imagine an Angel who would want to eat her favorite food to drown her sorrows.
As the Student Council President, she was just trying to stop us from disrupting order.
Because we created weapons in the Guild, she devised new Guard Skills to counter us.
So, that's all it was.
What a joke.
To think we still have no thread to lead us to God...
Suppose for a minute...
Huh?
With Tenshi the way she is now... couldn't she become our ally?
HUHHH?!
What the hell are you talking about?!
Do you have any idea how many of us have fallen victim to her?!
Uh... well maybe not victim... we're all okay, but...
Do you have any idea how much pain she's put us through?!
That's right!
Sure, she was good today, but we don't know when she'll feel like going against us again!
She'll slit our throats while we're sleeping!
Not your best idea, Otonashi-kun.
Seems that way.
Where did I come up with such a ridiculous proposition?
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつもひとりで歩いてた
I've always walked alone
I guess it was because I just imagined her buying the ticket alone,
and then eating her Szechuan Tofu, all by herself.
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返るとみんなは遠く
When I turned around, everyone was far away
The image of her having lost both the trust placed on her and her duty...
mou nanimo kowaku nai
もう何も恐くない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
was so lonely...
that it was pitiful.
sou tsubuyaite miseru
そう呟いてみせる
That's what I try to tell myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Eventually, everyone will be alone
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They'll continue to live only through their memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru youni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
So I can love and laugh even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakau n da
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenai n da
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will never show you my tears
What the hell do you guys want?!
They're normal students.
That's as far as you go.
There's a number of charges I could file, but...
For the time being, for engaging in activities past curfew,
I'll be taking you all to detention.
Now that I'm the Student Council President, I won't be taking it easy on you.
Take them.
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 95] Come with me.
[c 3] What was with those guys?
[c 45] Ayato Naoi-sama.
[c 10] And that would be the acting Student Council President.
[c 29] Doradora Oyaman!
[c 222] You're just slaughtering people!
[c 135] Bring Tenshi.  We need her.
[c 216] You're going to defy me?  God?
[c 117] Hand Sonic: Version 2.
[c 296] Will you accept me?
[c 57] What are you telling me to reflect on?!
[246] Ah, it's them...
[c 286] God!
[c 262] Even your life!  It was the real thing!