The one who sails against time: Akemi Homura.
By changing the possibilities of the past, numerous parallel worlds have been traversed.
Seeking the conclusion that you desire, this one-month period has been repeated, that's certain.
Your existence has created an answer to one of my questions.
"Why does Kaname Madoka, as a magical girl, possess extraordinary characteristics to such an extent?"
If it's now, I can form a hypothesis that I can both understand and accept.
A magical girl's latent power, you know... it's decided by the weight of her karmic burden.
It'd be one thing if she were the princess of a whole country or a messiah,
but for Madoka, who was given a very ordinary life...
It was baffling why she had threads of karma to such a huge extent concentrated around her.
But... Hey, Homura.
Could it be that Madoka, every time you've repeated the same section of time, has become a stronger magical girl?
Just as I thought.
The cause was you.
To be correct, it should be called a side effect of your magic, I suppose.
What does that mean?
You have rewound time for one single reason:
Kaname Madoka's safety.
With that same reason as your motive, you've rewound time on multiple occasions,
which has probably spooled a great number of parallel worlds into a bundle.
Kaname Madoka's existence has been their central axis, you know.
As a result of that, you have indisputably entwined all of those threads of karma from parallel worlds,
linking them to the Kaname Madoka of this time axis.
I can understand and accept that ridiculous magical power she has.
The time that you have repeated...
All of the karma circulating inside of it has wound and wound,
attaching itself to Kaname Madoka.
Since she is the one whom all incidents revolve around, you know.
A great achievement, Homura.
You have raised Madoka to become the strongest witch ever.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we exchanged
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes and ascertain it
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that has closed in on me, I move forward
いつになったらなくした未来を
The future I had lost at some point...
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
will I be able to see it here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を
The overflowing shadows of distress...
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
will be cut away as many times as necessary while I walk this earth.
止めどなく刻まれた　時は今始まり告げ
The ceaseless ticking of time now announces a beginning
変わらない思いをのせ
Placing my unchanged feelings into it
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awoke to paint the future where I'll start running
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road, the sky
綺麗な青さでいつも待っててくれる
is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue
だから怖くない
so I'm not scared
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't be crushed
Episode 11
The Final Guidepost Left
After disappearing on the 12th,
Miki Sayaka's
funeral service
the corpse of a second-year student from the private Mitakihara Middle School, Miki Sayaka-san,
Miki
was found inside a local hotel at early dawn today.
The crime scene shows no signs of struggle, therefore police are investigating the cause of this incident or accident.
Next is the weather report.
This evening, there will be a breeze from the northwest and strong rain.
Welcome back.
Hey, Madoka...
Sayaka-chan's case... you really don't know anything about it, right?
Yeah.
Sayaka-chan and Kyouko-chan have both died...
That is not a surprising development.
Omens have existed since long ago.
Are you saying it doesn't matter?
And yet it's your fault that everyone has died!
As an example, do you feel that livestock are inferior compared to you?
Do you know the process by which they're lined up on your dinner table?
Stop it!
That reaction is irrational.
If you find this scene cruel, then you're completely blind to reality.
On the condition that they become food for humans, they're given protection from any struggles for existence,
and they breed with no regard for natural selection.
Cows, pigs, and birds are species that breed at an overwhelming rate compared with other wild animals.
Aren't all of you in an ideal, mutually prosperous relationship?
Are you trying to say that's the same?
Actually, we give you a much better compromise than humanity gives to livestock, don't we?
Although it is imperfect, we recognize you as sentient life forms and discuss negotiations, you know.
You don't believe me?
In that case, shall I show you?
History in which Incubators and humanity walked together.
You know, we have interfered with your civilization since before your recorded history.
To an immeasurable degree, many girls have made contracts with Incubators to have their aspirations fulfilled,
then yielded themselves to despair.
It begins with a prayer and ends with a curse.
All the way up to this moment, that cycle has been repeated by a multitude of magical girls.
Among them are girls who have marked turning points in history, guiding society to a new stage.
Stop it already!
Everyone... Everyone placed their trust in you.
They trusted you, and yet you betrayed them!
It was not we who betrayed them.
Rather, it was their very own prayers.
Regardless of the kind of aspiration, if it's one that's unsuitable to the limits of reason,
then it will always produce some kind of distortion.
From that, an ending which produces calamity is the natural course of logic.
If you want to state that an obvious conclusion like that is betrayal...
Then it would be a mistake to make something such as a wish in the first place, you know.
However, I won't call it foolish.
The fact that the sacrifices made by those girls have put a spin on human history is yet another truth, after all.
In that way, every tear they shed has become a cornerstone of the past, in order to support the current lifestyle of your people.
If you can correctly recognize that, then why after all of this time do you view the fate of merely a few people at most to be special?
While watching over those girls for so long, did you feel nothing at all?
The pain everyone was going through... did you try to understand it at all?
If we could comprehend that, we wouldn't have bothered especially coming all the way to this star, you know.
In our civilization, the phenomenon called "emotion" is an exceedingly rare mental disorder.
That's why when we discovered you, humanity, it was astonishing.
Something like a world where every single individual holds separate emotions while coexisting...
We never would have imagined it, you know.
Perhaps... if you had never come to this star...
I suppose that even now, you would all be living naked inside of caves, wouldn't you?
In the end, you know...
parting like this with a student whom I taught really is painful.
That's right.
They don't even clearly understand the situation, you know...
There's also a third-year student who is a missing child...
I think staff meetings will be a total mess...
They really don't know anything, after all?
Sayaka-chan, you know... had a little bit of relationship entanglement with a friend, and a lot went on.
That girl is also burdened with a considerable amount of damage...
If this were normal, it'd just turn out to be a bittersweet memory, but...
now that it's come to this kind of conclusion, you know...
It seems like the police will settle for saying that her cause of death was debility after running away from home.
They have no clues at all, you know...
How's Madoka-chan doing?
I don't understand.
My intuition tells me she knows something...
But I also can't see any lies that she'd be telling.
This is the first time, you know. That I can't do something like see through to her true intentions...
Pathetic, isn't it? She's my own daughter, and yet...
Junko, to think that even you're voicing complaints...
Recently, I've been thinking that she's acting unusual.
I presumed she was carrying some kind of burden alone,
but no matter how much time passed, she never came to me for consultation.
I thought she relied on me a bit more than that, you know...
Children around that age, you know...
One day they just suddenly become adults.
I believe it's a shock for parents, though.
Is that how it is?
There is no option but to place your trust in her.
Right now what Madoka-chan probably needs is time to sort out her feelings,
so you have to wait for a little while.
It's so hard, you know... being unable to do anything.
That kind of thing being your weak point... you haven't changed at all, Junko.
Akemi        Homura
May I come in?
Is this "Walpurgis Night"?
Kyouko-chan talked about it.
She said that in order to attack a witch so strong a single person could not defeat it,
she'd have to fight together with Homura-chan.
You've always been here making preparations, right?
Is the whole city in danger?
Unlike the witches so far, this one has no need to conceal herself within a barrier.
By even simply just a single incarnation, several thousand people will become sacrifices.
As usual, normal people won't be able to see it,
so the damage will be credited to something like an earthquake or a tornado...
Thinking it's a natural disaster like that is nothing but a misunderstanding.
Then, we absolutely need to beat it no matter what, right?
Kyouko-chan has died, too...
There are no magical girls who can fight anymore, Homura-chan, except for you. In that case—
I alone will suffice!
It may have been impossible for Sakura Kyouko, but if it's me, I can repel Walpurgis Night by myself.
In truth, Kyouko's support was unnecessary.
I simply just wanted to let her save face.
Really?
Why is it...?
I...
want to believe you, Homura-chan, yet...
I don't want to think you're anything like a liar, and yet...
I can't bring myself to feel like everything will be completely fine.
Homura-chan, I can't bring myself to believe the things you're saying are true...
There's no way I could convey something like my true feelings to you.
Homura-chan?
Because, I...
Madoka and I...
live in different times from each other!
You know, I've... come from the future.
Again and again, I've met you so many times, Madoka...
And just as many times, I've watched you die...
How can I save you?
How can I change your fate?
Looking for nothing but the answer to that, I've started over from the beginning so many times...
That means...
Eh?
I'm sorry.
You can't understand the reason, can you?
It's disgusting to you, isn't it?
To you, Madoka, I'm just a transfer student who you met less than a single month ago...
But to me...
To me, you're...
Each time I repeat this, and then repeat it again... the time spent between you and I slips away more.
My feelings also slip away, and my words no longer reach you...
I think I've probably... already lost myself a long time ago.
Homura-chan...
I will rescue you.
That was my first emotion...
And by now... it's the one and only final guidepost that I have left.
It's fine even if you don't understand.
It's fine even if none of this is communicated to you.
But still, please.
I'm begging you, so... let me protect you.
Akemi        Homura
The storm is developing by splitting and rotating with absurd force.
It's a clear sign of a supercell!
Issue official instructions to find shelter at once!
This is an official announcement of instruction to take refuge from abnormal weather conditions as of seven in the morning, today.
We request that everyone in the vicinity take refuge in the nearest evacuation center immediately.
This is a Mitakihara Municipal Office of Public Relations car.
This is an official announcement of instruction...
It's coming.
Is today a big sleepover?
Are we camping?
Yeah, that's right.
Today we're camping with everyone!
I'm so high up! Can we roast meat?
Homura-chan...
This time, for sure...
I will put an end to this!
Hm? What's wrong, Madoka?
I–I need to use the toilet.
Homura-chan can achieve victory even by herself, is that true?
Even if I were to deny it, would you believe my words?
At this point, there are no words I can use to persuade you.
It's fine for you to just see and confirm it with those eyes.
When put in front of Walpurgis, how far will Akemi Homura get?
Why does she go so far to fight?
Because she still seeks hope.
If it comes to it, I believe that this will become yet another inactive time axis, and Homura will continue her fight.
I believe that no matter what, she will incorrigibly repeat this futile chain, you know.
By now, "coming to a standstill" and "giving up" hold the same meaning for her.
If she finds that anything and everything was futile—
When she is confident that by no means can she change your fate, in that instant...
Akemi Homura will lose to despair, then turn into a Grief Seed.
She understands this herself.
That's why she has no other kind of alternative.
Regardless of whether she has a chance of victory, Homura has no choice but to fight.
You're saying that she can't be saved as long as she holds hope?
Yup, that's right.
It was the same for all the magical girls of the past.
Madoka, even you have seen it with me, right?
But...
But...!
But!
Where are you going? Oi.
Mama...
I... need to go save my friend—
Leave that to the firemen.
Amateurs have to sit still.
Anyone but me will be no good!
Your life isn't for the benefit of one person!
Now look, if you just decide things on your own like this, how do you think the ones surrounding you—
I understand!
I understand that very well.
Since I love both you and Papa very much, Mama.
That's why I know just how important I am to you.
I understand that I can't waste my own life.
That's why you're wrong.
Everyone is important, so I absolutely have to protect them.
For that reason, I have somewhere that I need to go right this instant!
The reason isn't something that you can explain?
In that case, take me with you.
That's no good.
Mama, stay by Papa and Tatsuya's sides.
Give comfort to both of them.
Mama, you said I grew up to be a good girl, right?
You said that I don't tell lies, and I don't do bad things.
Do you still have faith in that now?
Will you believe that I'm correct?
You definitely won't strike carelessly, right?
You're not dancing around to someone's lies, right?
Right.
Thank you, Mama.
If it advances any farther than this...
It'll attack the evacuation center!
By any means necessary, I have to stop it here!
That's...
Why...?
Why is this...?
No matter how many times I try, I can't win against it...
If I repeat this... That alone would increase Madoka's karma...
In the end... all I've done is...
It's okay now.
It's okay now, Homura-chan.
Madoka...
You couldn't be...!
Homura-chan, I'm sorry.
Someday, the light of love that has lit within your eyes
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
(will pass through time)
(時を超えて)
A single dream belonging to the ruined world will certainly
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ
(be destroyed, I hope)
(壊すだろう)
Drinking every last drop of hesitation, what is the thing that you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Does such a greedy aspiration have course in an evanescent tomorrow?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
Like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was a child
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
I want to meet you, with the power to crush even darkness with a smile
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Inside these frightened hands lies the courage of a plucked flower
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
I rely only on my emotions for everything
想いだけが頼る全て
The light will awaken the wish.
光を呼び覚ます願い
If I were told something like "embracing hope is a mistake," I'd say that such a thing is wrong.
I would repeatedly say that any number of times.
I would surely insist on saying it forever.
Final Episode
My Best Friend
My best friend.