WARNING: this commentary contains spoilers. Watch after completing the series.
Also, commentary tracks are not held to the same translation standard as regular dialogue tracks. This is a rough TL.
The guest this time is everyone.
Please pardon missed background dialogue in this episode. We'll use this neutral white color for subs if we aren't sure who's talking/laughing. Thanks for understanding.
Hello everyone! Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika episode 11,
The Final Guidepost Left audio commentary shall begin now!
This time, you know, it's going to be extremely noisy! With the role of Madoka, it's Yuuki Aoi!
And—Yes! With the role of QB, it's Katou Emiri!
And—Yes! With the role of Sayaka, it's Kitamura Eri!
And—Yes! With the role of Sakura Kyouko, it's Nonaka Ai!
And—With the role of Tomoe Mami, it's Mizuhashi Kaori.
And—With the role of Akemi Homura, it's Saitou Chiwa!
Ao-chan, you're far away today!
(lol)
Ahhh, Chii-samaaa!
Yes, so then...
Yes!
Mahou shoujo... plus...
Yes...
White thing.
White thing!
White demon.
(lol)
Not a demon, just an Incubator!
That's right.
Today is going to be noisy.
Yes!
Ne? Amazing, these six people talking at the same time doesn't happen too often!
Ne~?
It's amazing, huh.
Amazing.
Somehow, um, the special included on volume 3,
Somehow, fffum, th special! included on volume 3,
it's going to be like that tea party with everyone.
That's right, ne.
That noisy thing had quite a favorable reputation, so...
For episode 11, we have everyone.
Oh!
Ohhh.
From here on out, everyone will be constantly talking over each other.
يفعلون هذا لي عن قصد
يا إلهي لماذا أعتقد أن التعليق كان فكرة جيدة
يرجى فقط قتل لي الآن
أريد فقط أن تلعب المعبود الرئيسي
أعتقد أن أربعة تشان سوف يسخر من هذا
لكن أربعة تشان هو مثلي الجنس حتى مهما
(lol) Awful.
(lol)
(lol) It'll be just like that.
Amazing~
But we have so many people, and...
We don't have too much time.
The amount of time we have.
That's right, ne.
If you have something you want to say, please secure your right to speak. Raise your hand.
(lol)
Nah, it's fine.
This is school.
(lol)
Right, right, right.
That's right, but actually, coming this far, we have everyone who's been on before...
Yes, yes.
Right.
Yes.
But the mahou shoujo never really gather together like this, so...
So everyone, please be sure to voice the feelings of your heart.
Yes.
What do we do, Ao-chan?
What do we do?
Then, QB can be the last person to talk...
(lol)
That's right! Then...
Umm...
How about Mami-san?
Eh? Me!? Surprising.
(lol)
لا أعتقد أن هذا سيحد لول آسف وبأعقاب ديكس
What is it, ne...
I thought "I want to watch this normally, though..."
I was given the shiropake, but...
Somehow, um, a lot of things happened, and then there was a continuous broadcast of three episodes, right?
That's right, episode 10-12 were broadcast continuously.
The night episodes 11-12 aired, TBS also aired ep10.
Right, right, right.
Ne?
Somehow, I was able to watch it like that.
It seemed sort of like watching a movie, seeing it like that.
That's right, ne~
Seeing it from a customer's point was a lot of fun.
Yes...
For Kaori-san, during episode 3, a little bit of a sad thing happened to Mami-san...
(lol) a little bit.
But then you also did the little brother.
Yes, yes.
That's right, ne.
Tatsuya.
Yes.
You did the role for Takkun.
You actually did many things, so...
Yes. Yes, yes.
Then, the one that comes in just a little bit, Walpurgis, too...
That's right.
You're saying that here, Ao-chan? It's too soon!
(lol)
This cast has almost no males in it.
That's right, ne.
I had a really bad premonition, because at the time I was taking Takkun...
At that time, Tsuruoka-san had just stopped me.
And when I lifted my head, he was niyaniya'ing.
(lol)
"Eh? So basically, does this mean—"
"It means that."
(lol)
"Please enjoy your new role."
He had a lot of "kyaa– kyaa–"'s written for his script, ne?
That's right.
Ne~?
That comes after this.
Really, it's quite a wide range.
Ne~?
Truly!
Yes. I do the little brother to the last boss.
(lol)
A wide range.
You might be the one with the most different roles!
That's right.
Ne?
Ah, okay, then, next is...
Yes.
Order...
Ai-cha!
Yes!
Mm!
Ah, me?
Ah, actually, this... since right here is...
That's right, we had an order.
Does it go in order of seating?
(lol)
Ah, so it's me?
Well, it's got a bit of a sorrowful feeling now.
Ahhh, well, well.
This atmosphere now is a bit...
(lol)
Yes! Eh... Ah, with the role of Miki Sayaka, it's Kitamura.
It's been awhile, hasn't it?
Eh...
I'm in a pretty place, aren't I?
(lol)
Actually, in different workplaces, where Eri wasn't at, I was told "Somehow..."
"It's depressing, isn't it? The funeral house scene."
(lol) It was some amazing content.
"Somehow, it seems it was on the news."
seems so!
Somehow—
It crossed over to other places, huh?
Ne? Like "It seems you were found at a local hotel."
I have Kyouko-chan to thank for that.
Really, she was doing this...
She was keeping me so important to her.
Keeping it fresh.
Right, she was keeping it fresh.
That's friendship, right?
Right. It was sort of like she was a fellow traveler for a little bit or something, you know?
Kyouko-chan was also in the same place. Makes me think "Sorry for the trouble!"
But really, even if I wasn't in this part [of the anime] myself, really...
What is it, looking at this overall...
Somehow it's like this piece of work is always on your mind, so...
Amazing. Well, I also did يرجى أي مربع القبيح, though...
Really, um... For the people in the office, my friends, and even people in the same office who were working on this...
This is a piece of work that everyone views as if they were a fan.
I really feel that in my life, this was a really big piece of work.
Sayaka... well, having the role of Sayaka is...
Extraordinarily... Well, Mami-san is the first big shock.
So Sayaka is the second big shock.
But I really feel like I was able to give meaning to this piece of work myself, too. That kind of role!
Yes.
"Thank you!" for that. I have many feelings of gratitude!
Sayaka ;_;
Yes.
Sayaka... ;_;
Somehow... ;_;
Well then ;_;...
Kyouko-tan.
Kyouko-tan~!
I'm the "Third Impact"
Third Impact = Neon Genesis Evangelion reference
Third Impact (lol)
So cool!
Cool image, there.
Yes. With the role of Sakura Kyouko, it's Nonaka Ai.
For me too, certainly, regarding Sayaka... It was surprising, but...
Still, I come in when Mami-san is no longer around...
That's when my entrance is, so...
We never got to talk, huh?
That's right, they never talked to each other!
We never had a proper conversation.
That's right...
That's right, ne~
"That Mami girl!"
Ne?
But it's like you knew her, right?
That kind of thing was there, yes...
And, they were able to talk a little bit in episode 10's different worlds.
Right, you two fought side by side.
desu yo ne.
I wanted to talk about more things with you ;_;
That face you're making! (lol)
During those different worlds, I'd certainly say...
...
"Please give me some tea."
...Yes.
I wanted to see everyone over there drinking tea.
Ah, but you see, that table can seat three people around it, but...
Yes.
If there were any more people, where would they sit?
(lol) Oh.
Ah, I'll go buy a round table.
(lol)
But I could use some bribes.
Ah, why don't they just sit at the edges?
(lol)
That'd hurt, you know.
Then, now, let's hear from this person with the close-up.
Yes~
Ohh!
Don't look this way.
QB?
(lol)
Ehh, well, as for QB... I was constantly thinking that I took a cute character at the auditions, so...
When I took him, and found out I got that role, I was extremely happy...
I've had a dream of being able to do something like a mascot-chara.
So I felt extremely happy, then...
For QB... in the outline, it didn't really say much about QB at all, so...
I had absolutely no idea what kind of character he was.
Ahh, certainly.
Right. So then.
During the conversations while after recording...
I gradually came to understand the truth behind him.
During after recording—
There's that shadow again.
(lol) Right!
During after recording...
Scary.
Somehow, I finally came to sort of understand QB.
Somehow, his style of thinking.
That's why, originally, I didn't think he'd be a character with such a huge role in the story.
Personally I thought it was amazing, something like a godsend.
(lol)
Really, for it to be this good of a role. And to think I was able to add my own voice to it.
That's right, and he's in all of it, ne.
Mm!
Right, amazing... I was truly happy. With just my voice, it gave everyone such a reaction...
Mou.
And everyone just loves QB.
Right, right, no one said anything like "Don't look this way!", I was happy.
(lol)
Don't look this way!
Don't look!
(lol)
"No, no, no!"
He's too close, too close!
(lol)
When this close-up comes, everyone says "There it is again! There it is again!"
THERE HE IS!!!
That's right, it was like that in after recording...
Ne? Well, the fact I got such a nice role really made happy.
Well, we got to talk with everyone this time, huh, Ao-chan?
Yes.
Yeah!
That's right, just before this we did episode 10. We were able to have a chat about our feelings.
Like how everyone is able to influence this work.
And now it's perfectly timed that everyone is here!
So since we're here, ne, I have some stuff to ask.
Somehow, Mami-san is here and she talks a lot, but she had that fairly shocking event.
That's right, ne.
And you say that you even knew that at the auditions, too...
Yes.
That's right, yes.
But I had no idea how she died, so...
It's just, what is it... It didn't really turn me off from the role too much.
Somehow, generally speaking, it sort of sucks when your own character dies, right?
I didn't feel that way at all. Then I still didn't know in what way she died, so...
She had a lot of effect on things afterward too, right, right.
Right, right. A character's life is quite mysterious, and...
Somehow, it was a bit different from how real people die. It was like "So there's death and then there's life."
So, Mami-sama felt a lot like that sort of thing to me... because she died, she was able to live.
Ohhh.
You could say it left an impression on me.
Up until that point, this had relatively good artistic sense, but afterward it was like true pure literature!
Mou, it's amazing. That shock, you know.
It wasn't rushed.
But for me, I was satisfied.
Ah.
That type of death.
Uwaaah.
Yes.
Then in episode 10 and such, she sort of came back in business, didn't she?
What sort of feeling did that have?
Ahh...
But I didn't think she'd be in it. Originally I was told she'd only be in 3 episodes.
"3 episodes, is it?" is what I thought.
Um, then when I appeared in episode 10, I thought it might be for one of my different roles...
When I saw the script, "Eh!?"
(lol)
Huh!?
Right, surprising, "Mami-san is here!" is what I thought. Very surprising.
Really, I was happy.  Somehow, um...
There was this, right? The musket's sound...
Mm!
When they saved Homura. She wrapped it up.
She wrapped up the witch, and there was that musket sound, which was emotionally moving to me.
(lol) Yes, I was a bit touched by it.
(lol)
Yes.
Amazing, huh?
Then, Sayaka?
Mm.
Well, um... Really, Sayaka's... well, what is it...
This Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika, overall, at the core, it's...
For when she was alive, even when she was a mahou shoujo, the one called Miki Sayaka was a very ordinary person.
As a magical user and as a school student, both of those were really quite...
Um, what to call it...
She was a girl who was quite inexperienced.
青い(Aoi) - Blue, green, inexperienced.
"Aoi" has quite a few meanings, the ones relevant to this conversation being the color blue, the color green, and the concept of being inexperienced (same as "green" in English). When Kitamura Eri uses this word to describe Sayaka's lack of life experience, it has the double meaning of lining up with her image color.
(lol) Well she has a blue image, but...
(lol)
Well, she's blue, though...
In the sense of her being youthful, she had the feeling of being an extremely inexperienced child.
Conversely though, I really thought she was worth doing.
On the flip side, there's a character like Homura who 100% doesn't think of herself.
Upon seeing that, it's like really, Sayaka is...
I can't say this in an exact, straight manner, but...
This presentation was executed well. There are many sides, you see them laughing, crying, really...
You see the origin, right? From the beginning, she starts as a regular girl, then halfway through becomes a mahou shoujo...
The presentation is—
Right, right.
Right, all the until she's a witch. (lol)
Mm!
She went through quite a few various experiences, so...
For acting, it was very interesting, doing a character with such development... Really,
there's also the fact that she felt Mami-san's existence so strongly, she kept it very close to her heart...
Ne, umm...
Then the precious Kyouko's existence, too, really...
She also had proud and impatient points to her,
she went about things eagerly even without knowing everything about them.
Then, Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika is a work where it's hard to comprehend conversations when watching it chronologically, so...
When you see it you really want to just start from the beginning again, but...
During after recording stages, really...
For around episode 8 or episode 9... when I say about myself "I'm really an idiot,"
that part... I thought some nice writing was done, ne?
You were able to do a character no one dislikes.
Yes I did. That also gave me ton of moral support.
While Hitomi-san was laughing as she pleased, all of the girls were like "No, that's not right!"
(lol)
Since that was there, I got support from everyone.
Also, um, really... this is a bit of a different topic, but...
Mami-san has Tiro Finale, but...
I want my own special technique, you know~
Ne~?
Ahhhh!
Ne?
That's right, ne.
Well, rather than having a technique such as Tiro Finale or anything like that, it was like "You can't do anything! Ahahaha!"
"Doing nothing is your special technique!"
Right, right, right.
"So it was like that."
But I thought that also had its own really nice spice, and it satisfied me personally. Yes.
But really when I saw the pictures, sounds, and then furthermore, the dialogue lines come to life...
It made me happy.
The part where Sayaka deeply shocks you is amazing!
Ne? That's right.
Ne?
I cried.
Then also, on the train... that groaning Mikishin-san, though.
ミキシン(Mikishin) - Affectionate name for Miki Shinichirou.
(lol)
Personally I really like that part where she's talking while covered in shadow...
It was extremely fun, ne~
And now we're at an amazing part.
Ne?
That's right.
Right, I have one small thought to say. This episode 11, I...
This is the most—Actually, looking at the whole series... I recently had the interview for the Official Guidebook with Ao-chan...
I said this there, but...
For me, looking at the whole series, this is what I'd choose as the most touching scene...
Um, this is the first time Homura talks about all the painful things she's been through until now. She has some long lines here, but...
This confession scene left a huge impression on me, I just remembered to say that a little bit ago.
That's right. Mou...
Ne~?
She said so many things, and while doing the acting, when it may have been thought that she might not accept all of it...
Surely Madoka would accept those feelings, and it'd fill her with so much [emotion],
and it filled me with so, so much too.
Somehow, it was amazing. I felt like in that scene Madoka and I were synchronized.
I really cried, you know.
That's right, ne...
Right, I just remembered to say that now.
Nah.
The curtain on Homura-chan has been lifted, hasn't it?
This... starting from episode 10,
it's so "guwaa!"
When she comes now, it's like "Homura has come–!"
Then you know... Conversely, umm, I said this during a different interview, but...
Really, Chiwa-chan's fine details in that Homura "coming out" scene, the lines one by one...
I've said this to Chiwa-chan before, um...
Surprisingly, when you see her poker face, Homura is actually shaken up.
Without knowing about spoilers you wouldn't see that...
After you see the "coming out" scene and hear her lines,
it's like she seems properly aggravated.
Every time at the after recording workplace, I feel like you and Tsuruoka-san really did it...
I had major attachment to Homura.
This part is amazing, that part just now... I feel like it is very like her, so personally it is the scene I choose as the best.
Then Takkun comes, ne?
Takkun comes~
When Takkun comes it really calms you down!
It's sad!
Right, then afterward, you know...
I wanna hug him~
From this part on the fight will begin, though.
Then also, during our interview times, Ao-chan was just like "Kyouko-tan! Kyouko-tan!"
That's right.
Kyouko is super popular, isn't she, Ai-chan?
No way, no way...
Somehow, when I started, I hadn't done many girls like her...
So I was really nervous, though...
It's somehow amazingly relieving to me.
Amazingly, um...
Kyouko-tan is... very Kyouko-tan-ish, but...
She's very popular among girls, isn't she?
It's like girls hold a lot of empathy towards really cool girls.
She's cool, na~
Mmm.
Somehow, in that way... she has that rough feeling, but in reality she's very warm...
I think that for girls, you'd definitely you want her as a friend!
She has a feeling of being so light-footed, it's like girls can really be cool in that way!
Kyouko-chan!
Right, right, right.
She's seriously cool, I think!
Ah, really, Kyo—
Kyouko-tan~!
(lol)
During episode 9, during Kyouko's scene that has a sorrowful feeling, when watching with Ao-chan and Emiri-chan, we cried. (lol)
I really cried!
Ehhh~
Mou, umm, when she's with Sayaka, I truly think that it's amazing that someone would sacrifice themselves that much for a friend...
Really! I seriously cried, ne...
Right.
She's magnificent, isn't she? Kyouko is.
I really think this right now among us, but everyone and everyone loves this piece of work...
That's why this is true for me too, but...
Doing this piece of work, I already loved all you actors involved in it to begin with, and now...
It always makes me think "What's with everyone!? You're too genius!"
Amazing, coming to love everyone that you already loved even more...
And this really applies to all of you.
I had this conversation during an interview with Ao-chan earlier, but everyone was very wonderful...
No matter what chara, they're all truly wonderful.
Somehow... I'm glad I did this! It was fun.
You can say that about everyone.
It's even true for QB, you know!
Ahh, truly...
Somehow, all the way up until the end, QB actually never gets shaken up even once.
Right, right, that... I think it gave me a little bit of relief personally.
Somehow, you know from the beginning to the end...
He never gets shaken up. At the very end he might have changed just a little bit, but...
Somehow... if QB [him]self had ever changed, somehow it seems like that'd have given me a lonely feeling.
I feel that way, so...
Ne? Um...
Since QB was constantly unshakeable,
because of that, now that the program is over, it's like I can get more into the personality of everyone else.
That's what I think, ne!
Then, this is the DVD with both episode 11 and 12 included, starting now there's going to be some ep12 spoilers, so...
People who haven't it watched it yet, "WAAAAAAA!" your ears.
(lol)
The finale, what do you think about the ending?
Ending!?
Right.
It was surprising, though!
Homura and Kyubey, we... had a HomuKyu end (lol)
(lol)
What do you think of that?
That was really surprising, but...
But when you think about it, QB was just doing what QB thought was the number one most efficient thing, so...
When all is said and done, um, that is...
QB [him]self is what Homura was fighting against, he was just the biggest antagonist to her goal, so...
So without witches, that alone changed QB [him]self's actions, but...
His thinking style was still never shaken up...
But somehow, up until now everyone has sort of been like:
"QB, QB, this jerk!"
(lol)
That's because of Homura's indiscretion in 8!
Right!
That's right, ne.
At the very end, even though, sort of...
Well, I was killed a number of times. (lol)
Right, right, right.
Even though I was killed a lot, at the very end we were able to be together, which was a bit shocking, but I was very happy.
Mm, I thought "Hurray!"
"I became a mahou shoujo mascot!"
(lol)
Right, right!
And you could really say that, couldn't you.
Right, right, right.
Somehow for me, Katou-san's acting of QB, he does sort of bring out emotion when talking about other people, yet...
It's still like he has no emotions at all in the end, it's really very QB-like.
I really love that!
Ah, thank you very much.
Super—
Super dangerous QB (lol)
(lol)
That was there... I really love it.
It's an amazingly delicate balance, isn't it?
The fact that I couldn't allow emotion to come out... around ep1 and ep2, I didn't know that.
It was like "Be cute! be cute!"
No emotions—
Right, right, right, right, I was told to please act cutely, so...
Learning he had no emotions was a surprise.
Mm. But,
I thought "I'm glad I didn't put out too emotion from the beginning."
Mmm!
Yes, then now we're going to have more conversation about the ending, so...
Um, for people who have not seen it, please watch all of it then listen to this.
There will be spoilers!
Um, the ending style, it was quite a shocking style regarding many things, but...
So I think everyone has seen up to the very end, and I'm interested in your impressions regarding the very end.
This piece of work's ending-style!
Yes.
I'd like your opinions.
Um, then... Mami-san!
Yes...
Well, Madoka is not around anymore, isn't that right...?
That makes me really think, just at what point did Madoka decide on that?
I think she must've considered many different types of wishes, but...
"With this wish, you're going to possibly disappear yourself."
It's that sort of wish, isn't it?
So it's like she actually understood that, I think...
Everyone... If you want to erase all witches, then the fact that it'd mean erasing yourself too...
"I wonder if she understood that," or something.
But if she wasn't already resolved to do that, then it wouldn't have been able to happen, so...
Somehow, in the end she was erased from everyone's memory...
Homura-chan is the only one who retained a bit of those memories.
That's right, ne.
Somehow I thought that was really deep.
Because, remembering is actually painful, isn't it?
That is right.
Right, right.
If it was her mother who was the one to not forget about her, I think she'd certainly regret that.
Right, if it's a parent who remembered that, she might not be able to go on living, so...
Yeah, it'd be hard to go on.
But, she really did want someone to remember, and she choose Homura. Somehow...
Mm, "That's quite deep," I think.
You're in the most painful spot, aren't you?
شيء ط ط التخلي عن هذا دونو
Right, right, right.
I'll always remember, and have to continue fighting. With that white person.
(lol)
That white face.
Fighting with that white thing, you know... Mou.
Really though, it's amazing, isn't it? And deep, too.
Right.
There's so much content, but it's worth thinking about.
Mm!
You can think about it, you can think about it endlessly.
Ne?
Then, Sayaka? How is it?
Yes.
Um well, somehow...
Really, this work went through a complete changing.
Then, it has the feeling of "So there's this kind of conversation and this kind of world, too."
Somehow, a different dimension?
Like with the times of Homura at school and such.
Somehow, I felt like I really wanted to see the world from the opening with Madoka.
The settei feels like there is a bit of hope for salvation in it.
That completely includes the fate of my own Sayaka too.
It has a feeling of "It isn't just purely painful things" as well.
Then, as an actress too, this was touched on a bit earlier, but...
Various people, and various—It was a gathering of really talented people...
Um, at the workplace, there was great cooperation. Everyone was watching each other's back.
I was able to study that and learn.
Thank you very much!
Haaa~
For you, Aipon?
Yes.
Since before, I've been watching this now...
I want her to defeat Walpurgis Night!
(lol)
It hurts, huh!?
I left Homuhomu all by herself, though...
If Kyouko was here, she'd surely do some javelin throwing at that thing, you know~
(lol)
I want everyone to fight it, you know.
Everyone help Homura!
!ما يوكي الهيئة
Kyouko-chan ;_;
With all 5 mahou shoujo.
Well Homura likes Madoka a bit too much, so for everyone to come...
(lol)
Everyone can be an ally.
Ne?
That's right, and then at the launch time, there was a lot of staff, and all sorts of people.
Somehow, this became the best.
I really felt the voice.
Thank you very much!
Somehow, we didn't talk enough, did we?
We didn't talk enough, truly...
It feels like our time was extremely short, but...
Last up is QB-sama.
Yes!
QB-sama, how was participating in this piece of work?
Mou... It was truly greatly satisfying.
(lol)
Mou, what is it...
I feel like I was able to accomplish everything that I personally wanted to in doing this Madoka.
Since I did a mascot-chara, that sort of...
Well, he might seem a bit like a villain, but QB [him]self isn't.
He was more of a villain than anyone else!
Ne?
(lol)
Right... but somehow it's like "I was able to do a character like that too..."
It's greatly satisfying for myself.
But I feel like it was a short amount of time.
But, I think if this piece of work continues on from here, that'd be nice.
Yes.
I'd be really happy if there was another expansion, you know~
Ne?
Truly.
I want to see, I want to see.
I'm really hoping for that kind of thing.
Yes!
Yes~
Well then, well then... That's Mahou Shoujo Madoka☆ Magika episode 11 audio commentary. Sending you off:
With the role of Madoka, Yuuki Aoi and...
With the role of QB, Katou Emiri, and...
With the role of Miki Sayaka, Kitamura Eri, and...
With the role of Sakura Kyouko, Nonaka Ai, and...
With the role of Tomoe Mami, Mizuhashi Kaori, and...
With the role of Akemi Homura, Saitou Chiwa. That's all!
Well then!
Goodbye!