Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
I'll never let you!
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
You've been at that for a while, you know.
Aren't they all the same?
Eh?
Isn't it common sense to do this?
Otherwise, you would never have enough money to get what you want.
Your common sense has quite a limited strike-zone.
At the very least, a normal person wouldn't have that kind of common sense.
How to Spend
Summer
There are people that don't go for just the figures,
they try to go for specific cards, too, you know.
How can you distinguish between cards?
Don't they all weigh the same?
There have been many legends and myths about this ever since they were introduced.
Like how certain areas have better cards,
or how there are specific marks or patterns you can look for.
Just so you know, I can usually get the special cards I want,
when it comes to little food packs like this.
There's a certain pattern if the box was just opened.
A-HA
That's pretty crazy if you think about it,
but I just can't bring myself to praise her for something like this!
But if people have ways of knowing these things,
don't the good ones get taken right away?
That's true.
If you live in an area with a master,
all the rare cards and secret figures are gone in a flash.
When I go to the store to find it looks like a leaf devoured by bugs,
I'm left in despair.
But then I always keep that sliver of hope, thinking, "Maybe this time!"
It's quite troublesome at times.
Troublesome indeed.
Aren't there also collectors who just buy the whole box in bulk?
Ah.
Yeah, there are.
When you buy in bulk, it's a lot easier to complete the set.
And it's easier to read the distribution patterns that way.
Is that a fact?
But they call this the "adult purchasing method" since it's a strain on your budget.
Not something a part-timer like me can pull off.
Is that so?
It might be called the "adult purchasing method",
but what they're doing seems pretty childish.
Like how they want to be unique,
or exhibit selfish behavior.
Then maybe a "large kid purchasing method" would be a better option?
Am I the only one who thinks it would be better...
...to direct that passion towards something more productive?
Lately,
topics on Akihabara have gotten a lot more media attention.
Yeah, and not for the best of reasons.
I don't see any problems with covering Akihabara,
but it's just that their depiction isn't the most flattering or accurate.
Well, they probably exaggerate some stuff,
but the stories had to originate from somewhere, right?
That doesn't explain how TV dramas and music,
that were first popularized by the otaku-culture, have caught on.
Even news programs and variety shows use anime and game music all the time.
Well,
maybe they thought normal people wouldn't make the connection when they used it.
Speaking of otaku.
Male otaku...
...are always talking about how they would prefer to have a girl otaku as a girlfriend.
On message boards and stuff.
But you never hear a girl otaku wanting to go out with a male otaku.
I wonder why that is?
Maybe girls are more vulnerable to the 2D images than guys are.
Maybe they're just worried about their future?
Though I'm sure most of them have jobs and stuff.
Wait, why are you asking me?
Now that it's gotten hot, more of them have started to appear.
They're so noisy and quick to escape, I can't stand them!
And they're dirty, too.
It is said that Miyamoto Musashi...
...could catch flies with his chopsticks.
For real!?
How can you touch those things with your eating utensils?
That's disgusting.
That's your concern?
Though I kind of understand what you mean.
Abeshi!
That was amazing!
I could never smack a mosquito.
Why not?
It's just gross when you squish it and get blood all over your hands.
That's true...
Hey, that's my blood.
Then what would you do if a mosquito landed on your arm?
I'd go, "Shoo! Shoo!"
Or try to blow it away.
Did you know?
If you contract your muscles when a mosquito bites you,
it can't pull out its stinger.
No way!
Watch this.
You are already dead.
And you've already been bitten.
And if you contract even more,
the mosquito explodes!
Stop! Stop!
It itches!
You should've just smacked it when you had the chance.
It itches so much!
Miyuki-san, are you going overseas again this summer?
No, not this year.
But I think we'll be visiting our relatives in the country.
I also often go to the summer festival with the neighbor's daughter from Ryouou.
She's like a little sister to me.
I see...
I see.
So you're going to the summer festival, Iwasaki-san.
You probably look dazzling in a yukata.
Not true...
I know that you're trying to compliment me,
but somehow I can't appreciate it.
It's like you're telling me I don't have any.
Izumi
Be right there...
Yo...
Morning...
You just woke up!?
What a slob!
Well, something's been on my mind lately.
What is it?
Like, did my alarm go off?
Or is someone else turning it off?
Oh, I know what you mean!
When you notice it, the switch's turned off.
Though when noon comes around, it gets so hot that you just can't stay in bed anymore.
It's way past noon.
"Kona-chan."
"It's morning."
"Wake up."
"Izumi-kun."
"Let's have lunch together."
"I was thinking about walking home with you, Konata-kun."
Hey, Konata.
Yeah?
Why are the main characters in these games...
...so popular for no apparent reason?
Beats me.
Probably because it would be hard to make a game otherwise.
"Geez!"
"You'd better do your homework!"
"I-It's not like I'm worried about you or anything..."
"Fine."
"If you say so, I'll do it."
Hey, Konata.
Yeah?
Why are the heroines in these games...
...always so cute with good personalities, but lack boyfriends?
Guys should be all over them!
Beats me.
Probably because if they had boyfriends, there wouldn't be a game to play.
Yo, Konata!
I came over to play!
Since I was here to check up on Yutaka, anyway!
Nee-san, good evening.
Konata?
Your father is calling you.
Okay.
Yutaka started on her homework, so can I borrow some manga?
Err...
Konata, don't you have to study?
Haven't you been playing this entire time?
No!
This isn't what you think!
You just have a bad timing and happen to come every time I'm taking a break.
GRIN
Oh, really?
But that just means you take a lot of breaks.
And so,
I'm a little worried about my image around the house.
I keep trying to stay at my desk,
but I can't help taking a break in the end.
Honestly.
It's because you don't have good study habits.
But I guess,
it's not like I don't understand how you feel.
You've had a similar experience, Kagami?
Well,
if I start a book that I'm really interested in during break,
and then try to study again, I can't get my mind off the book and end up taking another break.
It's hard to stop in the middle of something.
Like with manga.
You tell yourself that you'll stop after just one more volume,
but before you realize it, you've read through dozens of volumes.
Or when you borrow the DVDs for a drama so you can watch the episodes you missed,
you can't resist watching the next episode, and then it's downhill from there.
And when you actually watch it, it ends up being pretty stupid.
"I see."
"Director, about this doll..."
Onee-chan, can I change the channel?
Sure.
I wasn't really watching, anyway.
"Where did it come from?"
Is there something you wanted to watch?
They're having a special on sweets from all around the world.
You have quite the sweet tooth, don't you?
I bet Kagami and Tsukasa will be watching, too.
"It's like the Hare Hare Dance of sweets!"
That looks delicious!
But most of the time, with these shows,
even if you see something good,
it ends up being sold somewhere far away, so you're left disappointed.
We live in Saitama, so Nagoya is kind of...
It's like that most of the time,
but I still end up watching it.
It's sad.
Summer Classes-
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
Um, what's the matter?
I went to the dentist yesterday, but...
You were still going to the dentist?
I ran away in the middle of it.
"Let me know if it hurts."
"It'll be over soon."
It was something like that...
Yeah, they just don't stop!
It hurts just hearing about it!
We already have summer classes,
but for them to assign homework on top of that,
that's going too far!
What a waste of my summer vacation.
It's not like you ever do it yourself in the first place.
Besides,
unlike elementary school or middle school,
there aren't any independent study projects or book reports.
So we're better off, right?
You just have to answer questions.
Yeah, we had to make crafts and posters.
For stuff like that,
you had your parents to help you out with them.
And then they would get so into it that they'd finish it for you.
I've won an award with something like that before.
It was for one of my posters.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
It was all thanks to Dad.
I told him I was really impressed and he was really happy about it.
Isn't that when they're supposed to get mad at you?
"You'd better buy at least five at a time!"
Recommended by the Brigade Chief !!
Quenching the world's thirst
Super-sized Haruhi Cola
Only on sale for a limited time!
Whenever I see this commercial,
Super-sized Haruhi Cola
Only on sale for a limited time!
I always get jealous.
When I was little,
and read that story about a house made of gingerbread,
I wanted to eat as much candy as I could!
I know what you mean.
But when you actually get so much of your favorite thing,
you tend to lose interest in it.
Is that so!
Yeah, it stunk all year round!
So I was thinking,
summer homework is such a pain...
...because I always tell myself to do it all at once in the latter half.
That was random.
And I thought that was obvious.
If I worked at it a little at a time over the entire summer,
then maybe I wouldn't have to panic near the end.
And you just realized that?
You're a third-year now.
Take care of it while you've still got that mindset, okay?
I'll be coming over tomorrow,
and bring you a little something, too, so let's do our best!
Is that what you meant by "a little at a time"?
Did you intend to come over all summer?
I'd say about once a week.
Shut up!
Yo...
It's hot...
Yo.
I couldn't agree more.
The A/C is on in my room.
Oh, this is heaven!
You sure are making yourself at home.
Every year it's like this.
I don't feel like doing anything, and summer just passes by.
And before I know it, summer vacation is over.
Stop saying such depressing things.
Why don't you actually set some goals for this summer and get your homework done.
Well,
every year before summer vacation starts, I always tell myself that I'm going to work hard.
Really now?
Even in manga,
the "I didn't do my homework" plot is used a lot this time of year.
I guess so.
When you look at it like that,
it makes you think that it's the norm,
and you start to question whether you should even do your homework.
Since that's what everyone else is doing.
Of course it's not okay!
Just do it!
If you're going to have that kind of attitude, don't come over in the first place!
I'm thirsty!
I'm going to go get some barley tea.
Oh, Onee-chan!
Could you grab the math problem sets on my desk while you're at it, please?
Okay, okay.
Whoa, hot!
It's quite unpleasant to leave an air-conditioned room,
so when someone's about to leave the room, you try to get them to take care of your errands, too.
But then everyone ends up not wanting to step outside.
And in winter you don't want to leave the kotasu,
so you ask someone else to do stuff for you when they get up.
Hey...
Yo!
Sure is hot!
Welcome.
I brought some ice cream!
Choose whichever one you want.
And take it off my hands.
Since I won't really be much help with the homework.
And the Marimokkori's eyes were just...
Really?
Why is it that at times like this...
...you always wish you had the one that someone else chose?
I'm reading this manga right now about getting into Tokyo U.
Ah, that one?
Reading something like that...
...makes me think that even I could make it into Tokyo U!
If I try hard like them.
That's quite simpleminded of you.
Even if that method could get you into Tokyo U,
you'd need friends who will ditch their classes to help you out.
Teachers who hold classes like that.
Someone who will take charge.
And a bunch of other things for it to work, right?
You're right.
I guess it wouldn't work out that nicely.
There are quite a few of them.
People who get influenced by manga or TV dramas,
and then think they can easily change themselves.
Well,
I do try to work hard and study,
but I keep on falling asleep.
Do you know any good ways to stay awake?
I hear it's better to take a quick nap, rather than forcing yourself to stay awake.
Oh, yeah?
I heard that one before, too, so I tried it out for myself,
But my quick naps always turn into good night's sleep.
No willpower.
Hello!
Yutaka-chan, hello!
Hello.
Um, do you have a minute?
What's the matter, Yu-chan?
You can ask us anything.
One of my friends from middle school apparently has a boyfriend now.
And so she asked me what she should give him as a present for his birthday.
But I had no idea...
What should I do...
The atmosphere is so heavy...
A-Anyway, Yu-chan,
there are places on the Internet where people discuss stuff like this.
Why don't you check them out?
There might be a thread about it.
You can use my computer!
I-I guess I'll do that.
I know about Dens** Otoko,
but I didn't know they had threads for stuff like this, too.
It's pretty common, nowadays.
Anything goes these days, doesn't it?
That's right.
I wouldn't be surprised if I found answers to questions in textbooks as well.
It makes me think how easy elementary and middle school kids have it, nowadays.
As technology and the community advances,
the users' mindset and willpower become worse.
Just look at her.
Huh, that's weird...
I was just supposed to copy the homework...
But unlike before,
in the presence of an audience, it's like my pride is...
Speaking of which, what about the summer festival at your place, Kagami?
What are you talking about?
It's already over.
What!?
It was just like last year.
Why didn't you tell me?
We had to study for exams,
and if we told you, we knew you would want to come,
so we didn't participate either.
You don't have to come all the way to our festival.
Can't you just go to the one where you live?
Or is that one over, too?
My local one...
Yeah, when was that again...
Oh, yeah,
there are people who make a big fuss about festivals in other places,
but are completely oblivious to the ones where they live.
Are you also the type of person who doesn't want to meet their local friends?
Ah!
Just because we're college applicants doesn't mean we can study for exams 24/7!
Speaking of which,
there is going to be a fireworks festival near my house tomorrow.
That's it!
Why don't we all go out and have fun for once!
I guess so.
We could use a break.
Speaking of which,
tsn't there going to be a fireworks festival near your house tomorrow, Minami-chan?
Yeah.
I want to see Japanese fireworks.
Let's all go together and check it out, Minami.
Minami-chan, are you free tomorrow?
I'm fine.
Then it's decided, Minami.
Let's go, Iwasaki-san.
Okay.
Huh?
Iwasaki-san?
It's a pretty famous fireworks festival,
Mi-
Iwasaki-san.
Once you call someone a certain way, it's hard to give it up.
But it's pretty far away and famous, so I'm sure a lot of people will come.
Yu-chan, will you be okay?
Didn't you have a cold until just recently?
Oh!
It's supposed to be pretty hot tomorrow, so do you want to wait for the next one?
Don't worry about me.
It happens all the time.
I, the nurse's assistant, will be with her,
so there's nothing to worry about.
Yutaka.
I see now.
You're right!
Thanks, Minami-chan!
And so we decided to go see the fireworks.
With all this college exam preparation, there hasn't been much time to do fun stuff.
Because Kagami and the others are all serious.
Well, I can understand that.
You should just do what you want, Konata.
I used to drag Kanata around with me everywhere.
And we made lots of memories.
Though she got pretty mad at me.
You just can't let your youth slip by!
Then maybe I should get a boyfriend and make some memories myself.
Absolutely not!
I'll never accept a boyfriend!
You're not making any sense, Dad.
That's right.
Do you want to come watch the fireworks with us, Yu-chan?
To hear something like that from Konata...
The truth is, I'm going, too.
As a father, this hurts!
We're meeting at Minami-chan's house.
I don't want her to follow in our footsteps...
Is that so?
Kanata!
We're leaving!
Have fun.
The train's here!
You're late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yutaka-chan came along.
Ah, um...
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Over here!
Hi there!
Hey!
Hiya!
Patricia-san!
Are you guys here for the fireworks, too?
You look really good in a yutaka.
What the heck!?
Iwasaki
So Miyuki-san's neighbor was Minami-chan.
What a coincidence.
Yeah, what a surprise.
Welcome.
Help yourselves.
Thank you very much!
Oh?
Did we miss someone?
There should be enough.
Mom.
Did you count yourself, by any chance?
9.
Oh my, you're right.
I get it now...
Thank you for having us!
Ah!
So this is Minami-chan's house.
Whoa.
A huge dog!
Scary.
Don't worry.
It doesn't bark at all, and it's pretty friendly.
I see.
Even if they're big, if they're like that, then they seem so much cuter.
Huh?
I think he's growling at me...
Maybe she's the type who just gets barked at for no reason?
When you were little,
did you ever wonder if fireworks still looked round from the side?
Huh?
They don't look flat?
Come on now...
Sometimes they show fireworks displays on TV,
but it definitely feels different when you see them in person.
Yeah, definitely.
But you know, I've been thinking.
Every time they fire a huge one,
and announce, "This was brought to you by,"
followed by the name of some business or store,
doesn't that ruin the mood for you guys?
T-That's true...
Huh?
Yu-chan, you look a little pale.
I'm okay.
I'm fine, so you guys go watch.
But...
I'll...
Stay behind.
Minami-chan!
BALSAMIC
That was wonderful.
This is what summer is all about.
But...
They're not all beautiful memories like in a manga.
I got bitten everywhere.
It's so itchy!
They say it itches more if you scratch it.
And when you take off your yukata,
the belt mark on your stomach gets really itchy, too!
Yeah, it does!
Beautiful.
Yeah, it really was.
But I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble.
Oh, there you are!
Hey!
Did you guys get bitten by mosquitoes, too?
Huh?
We didn't get bitten at all.
Oh!
So some people get bitten by mosquitoes more easily than others?
I'm jealous.
Or maybe the mosquito could read the atmosphere...
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
I'm your navigator, Kogami Akira!
I'm the assistant,
Ono Daisuke.
It's been fast, but Lucky Channel is on its 20th episode!
You're not a crow today.
And you're not a dog today.
Piko.
Then let us have a look at the live feed.
Forest
Studio
Hm... I wonder where he is right now,
that Shiroishi-kun.
Mt. Fuji is so pretty!
Whatever.
Bye-bii!
Shiraishi-kun?
Piko piko.
Shiraishi-kun!?
Ma'am!
This is what you wanted, right?
Hello, Shiraishi Minoru here!
Now, please listen to me!
Bridegroom Rumba!
One, two, three, four!
Shiawase no koe hibiku...
Merry voices ring through the air...
Rokugatsu no kyoukai
...at a church in June.
Shiawase no zecchou wa...
The phrase "happiest moment of my life" was...
Masa ni kono toki
...made for such a time.
Ah, konna koto ni naru no naru...
If I'd known this would happen...
Ikko date nante kawanakya yokatta
...I wouldn't have bought that new house.
Hanayome ni nigerareru nante...
Getting jilted by the bride...
Manga mitai na situation
...is like something out of manga.
Awatete Omuko Rumba
All worked up, I break into the Bridegroom Rumba.
Dare ka tasukete...
Somebody save me.
Oh my God!
Oh, my God!
Kore kara dou suru no?
What am I going to do now!?
Joushi mo kiteru no ni!
Even my boss is here!
1 . 2 . 3
2 . 2 . 3
Omuko Rumba!
Bridegroom Rumba!
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Misao here.
Ayano here.
Hey, Ayano.
Isn't Hiiragi so cold?
She always runs off to that shorty's class, too.
There, there.
Does our love not reach her?
「 Pandora's Box 」
Next week: "Pandora's Box"
Ayano's cold, too...