Throughout Kyoto, the pants and underwear of males went missing, and everybody ran around in confusion.
"Land Submarine, to the Women's Bath"
~Bed Chamber Investigation Team's Rose-Colored Search~
I, of course, haven't taken
a single step out of my home.
Because it's awkward, right?
There's no way I'd do such a thing.
No!
There aren't any pants or underwear left.
Just what exactly is going on?
While I'm asleep, my pants and underwear
that I'm wearing disappear.
I can't leave the room like this.
The man with the hobby of taking
people's pants is currently bedridden.
I'll drop by as a visitor.
I couldn't find them.
Gross...
It's over. I've searched all over Rakuyou,
but there's no pants or a single pair of underwear to be found.
Hey, you.
Your underclassman is Akashi-san, right?
Know her address?
I have a bit of business with her.
Hey now, it's not like
you won't be compensated.
O-Ouch...
Who are you guys?!
Nobody suspicious, don't worry.
We just want to know Akashi-san's address.
Who would give out the address of a female underclassman after being kidnapped?!
Hey, don't be like that.
What is this?
Or rather, aren't you leaving out too much in your explanation?
I will not give out the address of a maiden!
You're a man, right?
She's so innocent, we...
Anyway, this submarine will get to her place unnoticed,
and then it's possible to leave at once.
And then naturally...
Are you a pervert? That's a crime!
As I thought, it's better that you don't know it.
So you know it, then?
I don't know it, really.
At last, Rihaku-shi fell ill,
and we were able to put this to good use.
Until now...
I've burned all the pants and underwear.
They don't wear underwear in Scotland, nor pants.
Since ancient Japan,
it's been kimono or loincloth.
Originally, a man's radiator, so to speak, not having
a regional function to keep under wraps was outrageous.
Then I found an interesting book.
Creating a scrubbing brush by mixing
white fiber and fern together
results in something called Van der Waals interaction.
Rather, it was written that matter
drives into the back of primitive matter.
That's how I found this blueprint.
A quick buy at the used book market?
You can only find good books at the start of the market.
God will be angry.
For some reason, what's written in this book cannot be remembered.
There appears to be contrivances to prevent transcription.
It cannot be photocopied,
and pictures cannot be taken.
It had to be built while keeping an eye on it.
I see, you've made up your mind.
I will create a breezy "free hanging" world!
That's an interesting and superfluous story.
It's no good. I've contracted some kind of virus after handling his underwear.
The man who claimed he wouldn't change his underwear until he reunited with the apple girl?
It was an inevitable dilemma I tried to avoid,
but after we had taken them, he was able to meet with her.
I was able to grant his wish.
That's a convenient way of thinking.
If the energy of his distress
devised a mysterious energy,
it wouldn't be strange, but...
Now, about the submarine?
It'd be great if the Bed Chamber Investigation Team members weren't riding it around,
but they're so bothersome
about putting it to "good use."
Get well soon
Please take care of yourself.
Was it your group who stole the pants and underwear? Perverts!
Don't say strange things, that's something Rihaku-shi made happen.
That's something I have no interest in.
Right? So Akashi-san's address!
Akashi-san wouldn't even tell us her address.
She's probably been targeted by stalkers like you before.
Akashi-san has been spotted with the sonar!
Oh, we did it? We won't let her go this time.
Hey, stop this!
We don't need you anymore!
Akashi-san!
Hurry!
Hey, she's not here!
She's nearby.
Where? Where's she hiding?
Where?! Where is she?!
What happened?
A harpoon!
Bed Chamber Investigation Team?
A club of men with the interest of
collecting erotic art and secret treasures.
Can't we lure them?
Akashi-kun and Hanuki
will go to Sakura Yu at eight.
We'll go too.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
To Master Higuchi,
Went to Sakura Yu
to work up a sweat.
Sakura Yu
Welco—
Men are that way.
We have important business. It's a crime.
There's no greater crime than men
going into the women's bath.
What do we do? It's not like
I don't understand, but...
I can get in the women's bath
because I'm still small.
You're just going to grow soon anyway.
To think you didn't call me to a public bath.
You'll need my help.
It looks more like the women's bath
is a need to you.
It's because you like
stripping off your clothes.
Give back the used book.
Every used book deserves to be passed on.
Okay.
What's this about?
Rihaku-shi got a hold of a used book
with a secret technique and angered God.
God?
The god of the used books market.
Men go that way.
Hanuki! Call us anytime.
All right.
Well, how are my muscles?
The setting sun!
Thanks.
Let's get in.
Ah, a moth.
A moth?!
It's here.
Wait till it gets into the bathtub.
Hanuki-san!
All right!
It's too much!
Hold on!
( Electrically Heated Bath )
Perverts!
You all right, Hanuki?
Akashi-san! Aren't we able to do anything?
Clearing one's mind of all mundane thoughts
makes walls like curtains do.
Let's go.
Yeah!
It was an amazing—a single-towel
showdown with Hanuki.
Still can't see, even after slowing down the video.
Akashi-san was completely naked.
It's unbelievable.
Kaori-san was so cool.
Thanks to Jougasaki, their life was forfeit.
We sure cleaned them up.
Hmm, it's unbelievable.