When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Spring's right around the corner.
The third semester flew by, didn't it?
Yeah? It felt like it took forever to me.
But the only days you came to school were when we thought Katsura-sensei was quitting and last episode.
I'm the main heroine, so when the story takes place at Hakuou, I have no choice but to show up.
There you go mumbling nonsense again.
Let's go home, Hayate.
Seriously, why is school such a big pain?
But then, it'd be a different story if this were Hou**ka Academy or Ku***.
Oh, I would like to try the Ashi**do Academy's uniform once.
Milady's hatred of school is really over the top.
Why, why. Who do we have here?
If it isn't Hayata-kun and Nagi-chan.
What a coincidence.
How may I help you all?
We thought we'd take part in our club activity for once.
Club?
Oh, I always assumed that none of you were involved in any clubs.
Are you interested, Hayata-kun?
What?!
No, not really.
What? "I'd love to participate", you said?
Then stop by our club room.
Come, come.
H-Hey!
Just as planned.
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
This story takes place when hu**** were still able to fly.
Motion Picture Research Club?
You really have a unique club room.
The building is made according to the club founder's taste.
This is a 16mm film!
This is a super HARP camera!
I got it. You're basically a MC!
A Movie Club!
What are you talking about...
...Little bunny?
It isn't?
We don't have any intention of shooting movies.
We can't do anything that difficult.
Then what do you do here?
That's obvious!
We film and gather all sorts of funny movies and laugh at them with everyone!
That's why we're also called Niko **** Movie Club.
In short-
You-To-be~
"In short?"
So basically a boredom killing club.
Who are you calling the boredom killing club?!
Motion Picture Research Club, huh?
It sounds a little interesting.
Wh-What's this? Milady has an interest in getting involved with people.
I think she's interested in the motion pictures.
Speaking of it, Nagi-chan, are you in any clubs?
I'm not in any right now.
Then give this one a try.
We're a really lax club originally made to take shots of cute girls.
So it'll work as a way of making memories.
What should I do...
This is a chance.
It's a great opportunity for Milady, who tends to be a hikikomori, to enjoy regular school life.
Who would ever call me a butler if I don't support her being in it?!
Okay.
Wow, it sounds very interesting!
So, what kind of footage do you actually shoot?
The works are lying around there.
Then let me see some.
You said you shoot footage of cute girls, right?
Hello, I'm Ayasaki Hayako.
A little mischievous sixteen year old.
Some nice-looking men out there take me out on dates!
No! There goes our work!
What was that spy shot about?!
You even dubbed over it!
What's wrong? It's funny.
By the way, cameras are set everywhere.
From the pinnacle of Chomolungma to Shi**ka-chan's shower room over at Minamoto-san's.
No, you can't film! Stop!
Then how about this?
Sensei! I... I can't hold myself back anymore!
Y-You can't, Ayasaki-kun. We're student and teacher.
But I want to stay like this with you.
You fool. Don't trouble me like that.
Being able to cheat is a sign that a guy's dependable.
Girls are around for you.
You're making me look like the biggest flirt in the world!
Hey, Hayate. What was all of that about?
Th-They're accidents! They were all purely accidents!
Milady.
Let's take our leave now.
What? You're going to leave, Hayata-kun?
You just got here.
I don't want to see any other sketchy footage.
Don't say that.
Please, help us.
Help? What do you mean?
You all seem to be having fun.
Superintendent!
Wh-What brings you here?
Today's club investigation day run personally	by Kuzuha-sama!
Investigation?
I'm checking to make sure nothing has strayed from what students should be doing.
Exactly.
So she does some normal stuff once in a while.
Don't be deceived, Hayata-kun.
How could she be normal?
Do you have any clue how much suffering stems from her investigations?
For example, in the Tennis Club.
No one can hit a Boomerang S***e here?
Closed down.
In the American Football Club-
They can't even do a ***bat Dive in midair?
Closed down.
Furthermore, in the Doll Club-
"To wind or not to wind?"
It doesn't run on *****?
Closed down.
Like that, there are countless clubs that got destroyed.
I don't want us to be closed down.
That's why we were planning on getting you into our club as one of the Superintendent's favorite men on campus...
...and show her footage of how much economical adversity you're in.
And yet...
I don't think the Superintendent would have enjoyed watching that.
Wh-What? This was Ayasaki Hayate's embarrassing moment collection?
Yeah.
I wanted to see them!
I so wanted to see them!
Kuzuha-sama.
Okay. I order the Motion Picture Research Club closed down this instant.
Starting tomorrow, start the Onono Imoko Research Club or the Eat Udon up the Nose Research Club.
Can't it be a little more normal club?
What a waste. We were just about to start shooting amazing footage.
What? Amazing footage?
We were planning on showing it to you, too.
What exactly will it be like?
Staff credit NG collection!
Staff credit?
You've seen them in Jac*** **** movies.
In those staff credits, they play NG shots, remember?
That stuff.
"That" you say, but...
I see.
I do like them.
I don't mind Jac*** **** either.
Oh my. Milady is showing interest in something that's not 2D.
As her butler, I must do this.
Hey.
This is your only chance to stop.
Good luck, Hayate!
This is amazing.
I can't miss a frame of this.
I really think he should stop.
Ready, everyone?!
You will, Jac***?
Jump, Jac***!
Meanwhile...
Makimura-san, you can't take footage like this.
I said you can't!
I never imagined I'd find film this old.
In this networked world, it's hard to recall movies that once got distributed.
Watch out.
Su-Sukinan dakara, mou.
Su-Sukinan dakara, mou. = Y-You really like this kind of stuff.
Ureshinakijya, boke!
Ureshinakijya, boke! = We're crying because we're happy, you idiot!
Hakuou Academy Motion Picture Research Club. The First...
...Exciting...
...Normal Story Competition!
What is this out of the blue?
What are you asking? It's obviously...
...Just as the title reads!
The Motion Picture Research Club must consider safety first.
We decided to reflect upon our acts and take footage that can be enjoyed by everyone in front of the screen.
Yay.
Uh...
I won't let you say you're leaving after coming this far.
We already have a contract with the Superintendent that
if we present her with funny footage featuring Hayata-kun,
then she'll give us 30% more funding next term.
When did you do that?
Plus, Nagi-chan agreed to help as a club member.
What's wrong?
Anyway, what is this Normal Story Competition?
Thank you for asking, Nagi-pon.
You see, Nagi-rin...
...This is how it goes, Nagi Springfield.
Um, can you just call me Nagi like normal?
This was back when I was in elementary school.
Excuse me...
I was at a really rundown fishing village.
That village seemed as though time had stopped.
It was pretty creepy at first, but at the inn we stayed at, a really worn out statue of Ninomiya Kinjirou stood facing the ocean.
From what the landlady of the inn said...
At night, that statue turns around to make sure no kids staying at this inn are staying up late.
So you mustn't stay up too late, okay?
Yeah, I've heard those kinds of stories before.
I see. So we're going to gather those common stories.
No!
The story continues.
When you hear something like that, you have to confirm it, right?
At night, we snuck out with a few kids to check.
The time was 2 AM.
Looking back, we really shouldn't have.
It was pitch dark out.
It was a windy night, too, with a sound like human groaning.
We waited for ten minutes, then twenty minutes.
It was summer, yet it was strangely chilly.
The next moment, we couldn't believe what we saw!
We had all fallen asleep at some point, and morning had come.
Whatever happened to the statue of Kinjirou?
Everyone was asleep, so no one confirmed it.
You used seventeen cuts for that worthless story?!
Just like that we collect normal stories where nothing happens that can't be used in any kind of context...
...and want to make a collection of footage that makes viewers feel, "Ah, that was a waste of time."
We don't need a collection like that.
However, all humans have one or two worthless stories like that.
Come on. I know you have one, too.
A really worthless story that you have sealed away.
Well. Um, I...
I used to live in a really crappy house as a kid.
You do have one to share?
That house was really crappy.
At night, the windows would always rattle.
One night, I was staying at home alone.
At the time, we didn't have electricity, so it was pitch dark inside.
I tried to go to bed, curled up in my futon,
but I realized something.
"Hey, the rattling noise is louder than usual."
I was scared, but as though I was drawn by something, I walked towards the window.
I slowly opened the curtain,
and took a look outside the window,
and I noticed that...
...the wind was stronger than usual.
So what?!
Nothing happened.
But that's exactly what we're looking for.
Good job, Hayata-kun. You know how things go.
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes! I want to tell my story, too!
Katsura-sensei! Where did you come from?
At noon, I leave the POD room, right?
One day after work, I felt this
the moment I stepped into the room:
"Something's not right."
At first glance, the room hadn't changed.
But I could tell that something important was gone.
I thoroughly checked the room.
Then I finally realized what I was missing.
I was missing...
Missing what?
...cash from my wallet!
What the heck was that?!
I'm 500,000,000% sure it's because you used it all.
Hey, where's the mike?
If I may, can you listen to my story, as well?
Klaus-san?
This is school, you know?
At this point, I'll enter any possible scenes given the opportunity.
So.
At the Sanzenin's, we used to have a dog named Lucky out in the yard.
Oh yeah, we did have a dumb dog like that, didn't we?
He was indeed a dumb dog, but by around six in the evening, he'd always be back and be sleeping in his place.
But one day, he didn't come back even after the sun was starting to set.
We didn't have him on a leash,
but it didn't look like he had left the premises.
But, no matter how dumb he's been, it was hard to think that he could get lost in his own yard.
I searched for Lucky the entire night.
But I couldn't find him, and a day passed.
A second day went by, as well...
...but Lucky wouldn't come back.
However, on the third day!
Lucky was back in his home!
Wh-Why?
That was the end of this story.
Thank you for being a good audience.
What happened during Lucky's three days?
I wouldn't know.
Push.
Can I tell my story, too?
When we were cleaning our house,
Kotetsu-kun found a really old wooden box.
Inside the box was a mummified Kappa's hand.
And on the inside back of the box was some scripture.
It said that this hand will grant any three wishes of the owner.
So, did you make your wishes?
No, I bet there was a fearsome curse instead.
Well, you see...
We ended up...
...tossing it out as noncombustible trash the next day.
Hey, wouldn't a Kappa's hand be combustible?
She's right. It's combustible.
Oh, it is? Oopsies.
It's now become a story about trash...
Right, I'm up next.
Do you all know the word "doppelganger"?
It's about meeting an individual who's like a copy of yourself.
It's said whoever sees a doppelganger will soon die after that.
It's said that Lincoln saw one the day before he was assassinated, too.
A Japanese poet, Murou Saisei, also saw a doppelganger.
This time, it's starting to sound like an urban legend.
Doesn't the name Murou Saisei sound just like Slow Saisei?
Note: Slow Saisei = The slow play setting on video players
Also, toudai motogurashi and
taishou democracy sounds similar, too.
Plus, Jura*** Park and Ju**ke ni nisanpaku sounds similar, too.
Those really are things no one cares about.
It's all up to you to believe it or not.
Um...
May I share my story from home?
Saki-san.
My home is really old, and whenever someone uses the stairwell, it makes creaking noises.
One day, the whole family was eating on the first floor, but we heard the creaking noise from the stairs.
So Mom said, "Wow, our house must really be getting old", and so we renovated.
That really was a normal story.
My god. Those were all really boring stories.
Wataru-kun?
Oh, if it isn't him; you're...
President! Our club president!
President?
Yup, that's right.
The boy standing there is the current
Motion Picture Research Club's president,
Tachibana Wataru-kun!
Tada.
You just forced me to be the president.
When did this happen?
Just so you know, the president's amazing.
He makes MAD anime openings that could fool the eyes of people who don't watch anime.
Note: A MAD movie is a Japanese fan-made video, much like AMVs (Anime Music Videos)
Also, all the OreVoice series are made by him!
No, they're making that up.
Besides, come on. None of them have any punch lines.
As expected of our President.
Then what, you can tell a story with a punch line?
I don't know.
But what I'm saying is, I want to hear a more touching normal story that strikes one's heart.
"A normal story that strikes one's heart?"
Yeah, for example.
This is regarding outer space.
You know how space is expanding at great speed, right?
Y-Yes.
Also, you know that light is the fastest thing in the universe, right?
Well, since it's common sense.
However, the rate of expansion is greater the further you are from Earth.
Therefore, the stars further away from Earth will distance themselves from Earth more quickly,
and eventually, they will go past the speed of light!
Why?!
It's a mystery, isn't it?
P-President...
Was that the end?
So that ends one worthless day.
I wonder if anything good happens.
A p-peach?!
Why?
Th-This is...
I can't reach it!
Oh yeah, I know what I can do.
I'll go buy a can of peaches.
Ring ring. Ring ring.
There was another normal story for you.
Next week, we'll fight against quiz tournaments.
Right now, we are in front of Yukiji's room.
Let's go check out her sleeping face.
Oh, but before we do that...
All those who are watching Hayate no Gotoku.
This will probably be the last episode where we'll be featured as main characters.
Looking back, there was this and that and many things that happened.
I feel a little sentimental.
But an ending is a start of a new ending that will lead to a beginning.
Let us meet again somewhere.
Ready?
Bye bye!
Come, come and wake me up already!
Hey! Hey!
You can easily play my wake up reaction
300,000 times and get 100,000 comments!
I did it!
You're kidding me!
Nagi and,
Hayate and,
Maria, a seventeen years-old's
Butler Network!
You idiot! I'm Sanzenin Nagi!
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Maria, a seventeen year-old.
The cold days continue, but are you all doing well?
On a cold day like this, it's better to stay inside
and play MMOs rather than to force oneself outside.
If you say things like that, you won't get to master your life like Maria-san.
Oh please, Hayate-kun. But remember, I'm only a YEAR older than you.
I'm sorry, Maria-san. But you're very mature, and some times appear like an ol-
Time for today's service shot.
Please keep supporting Hayate no Gotoku.
Shine! Jump! Shake you booty.
The 4256th High School Girl Ultra Quiz!
Your host will be me, Mikiri Teruo and,
Abe Maou ~tima.
There are tens of thousands of pairs that have gathered from all over the country ~tima.
Who will be victorious?
Can't wait ~tima.
Next time: Quiz! Written as "Rival" and Read as "Friend"!!
Why do I have to pair up with the Hamster?
Next time, strike your special pose as you watch Hayate no Gotoku.
Bring it on!