HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
P-Precure?!
It's a Precure!
Precure! Precure!
A super strong Precure!
Pretty, pretty, Precure!
Cure Blossom!
Blossom!
All right!
Precuuuuure!
Clap, clap, clap.
In that case, we'll take them down, Precure and all!
Doll!
Huh?
What?!
Why the heck can I jump this hiiiigh?!
Allow us to explain!
Huh?
It's because you're a Precure!
But I'm... afraid of heights!
Blossom!
Was it really a good idea to make her a Precure?
I'm the Weakest
Precure in History?!
Doll! Doll!
Cure Blossom, watch out!
Huh?!
You can't run away!
But...
Hey, look where you're going!
I'm running so fast that I can't stop myself!
Cure Blossom!
Huh?!
Doll!
My eyes are spinning...
Get a hold of yourself!
This is the legendary warrior, Precure?
How pathetic can you get?
I'm just so powerful I can't control it...
Now's your chance to finish them!
Doll!
Nooooooo!
Stop!
You can't just keep running away!
You're a Precure! You have to fight!
Let go of me! You'll pull my skirt off!
What an idiot.
You might be the weakest Precure in history!
Just finish them already.
Dammit, why won't you hold still?!
Now crush her!
Cure Blossom!
What do we do? What do we do?
It's no use!
Hmm?
Wh-What on earth?!
Thank goodness you're fine, Blossom!
I don't know who you are, but thank you so much!
Oh wow, what a hottie...
Wait, I mean... Who the hell are you?!
Doll!
They vanished?! What's going on here?!
Dammit, even the fairies got away!
Desertrian, find them, no matter what!
Tsubomi.
Grandma?!
How did I end up... here?
When I came in here, you were just lying there.
Oh! Blossom!
Oh, it's Cure Flower!
Huh?!
Chypre! And Coffret, too! It's been a while.
What?!
Wait, Grandma, you know these two?!
Indeed I do.
So the "Cure Flower" these two mentioned...
Is actually me.
I used to be a Precure!
Wha—?!
You did?!
I thought you've always been in charge of the botanical gardens here!
I have been.
And while I was doing research on the Great Heart Tree, I met Coupe.
The legendary fairy!
It's Master Coupe!
Legendary fairy?
Master Coupe?
Coupe was my partner back when I was a Precure.
He's Chypre and Coffret's predecessor.
That's a fairy?
He doesn't look like one at all...
You're so cool!
I hope I become like you soon!
Huh?! What on earth about him is cool?!
That's very rude, Tsubomi!
Master Coupe is an idol to us fairies!
The weakest Precure in history has no right to say such things.
Exactly.
Huh?
Wait, you mean... Tsubomi is a Precure?!
That's right!
Tsubomi said she'd seen the Great Heart Tree in her dreams, so we gave her the Heart Perfume...
And she transformed into Cure Blossom!
Tsubomi, could the dream you had be of Cure Moonlight being defeated?
Yes.
I saw it so many times.
And then I met these two, and they just made me into a Precure.
We were being chased by Sasorina, one of the commanders of the Desert Apostles.
And then Sasorina and her Desertrian attacked us!
I see... That must've been tough for you.
Still, I can hardly believe my ears about Tsubomi becoming a Precure...
However, Tsubomi, your love of flowers makes you perfectly suited to the role.
Hey, Grandma... what exactly is the Great Heart Tree?
The Great Heart Tree is...
the origin of the Flower of the Heart.
The Flower of the Heart?
Yes.
Everyone has their very own Flower of the Heart within their heart.
And each flower is its own variety and color.
No two are the same.
So I have one too?
Of course you do!
The Great Heart Tree is connected to the Flower of the Heart by an unseen force.
And if the Flower of the Heart is
saddened or changed for the worse,
the Great Heart Tree is weakened.
That reminds me. These two said the flower of Erika's heart had turned red...
That's right! What happened to Erika?!
Don't worry!
Erika!
The poor girl.
Her Flower of the Heart was pulled out, wasn't it?
It was Sasorina and her cronies!
And it looks like they're nearby!
Huh?
It's a Desertrian!
I found you, fairies!
Someone spoiled our fun earlier,
but you won't escape this time.
Erika...
I was only trying to help Tsubomi by making her more fashionable!
And still Momo had to make it her business!
Erika!
The white cyclamen Flower of her Heart will soon turn entirely red!
In the language of flowers, a white cyclamen means "purity"...
If it turns red, it will become "jealousy"!
And then what'll happen?
The only thing left will be for it to wilt...
And once it wilts, her heart will be consumed, and she'll sleep within this sphere for all eternity!
No way...
To save your friend, you'll have to become a
Precure and defeat the Desertrian, Tsubomi!
Quickly, transform into a Precure!
G-Got it!
Huh?
It's gone. Gone. Gone!
What?
That thingy I have to spray to transform... is gone!
Whaaaaat?!
Now, Desertrian! Beat them to a pulp!
Where did you leave the Heart Perfume?!
It's not that easy to remember...
It's the Heart Perfume!
It was lying next to you when you collapsed.
Thank you, Grandma!
Just hold on a little longer...
I'm definitely going to rescue you, Erika!
Go forth, Seed of the Precure!
Precure! Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
This is the power of Precure?
What the hell are you doing?!
You've gotta do better than that!
Doll!
Whaaaaat?!
Blossom!
Not only do you make Erika suffer, but the flowers too.
I...
I've had it up to here with this!
Huh?
I sorta feel... stronger than before.
Feelings of wanting to protect your friend and those flowers strengthen your abilities as a Precure.
I see!
This isn't the time to admire yourself!
You're right!
I'm afraid your luck has run out.
Once my poison stinger gets you... you're finished.
For someone like you, who tramples on people's hearts...
I won't budge a single inch!
What?!
Precure sure are strong, aren't they?
Cure Blossom, use this chance to defeat the Desertrian and take back the Flower of your friend's Heart!
D-Defeat it?!
How am I supposed to do that?!
Use the Blossom Tact!
Shout out "Gather, Floral Power! Blossom Tact!"
Got it!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
And then shout "Flowers, shine forth! Precure Pink Forte Wave!"
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Curse you, Precure!
Next time we meet, I'll strike you down with my poison stinger!
Blossom!
You must return the Flower of her Heart to her!
Wh-What?!
Erika!
Thank goodness...
Where am I?
The greenhouse at my grandma's botanical gardens!
How did I end up here?
We found you collapsed outside the park, so we brought you here.
So that's what happened...
Wh-What's wrong, Erika?
While I was asleep, I had this really realistic dream.
Someone pulled a flower out of my heart,
then put it into a doll, which went berserk!
Huh?!
And this Cure Something-or-other appeared...
Th-That's...
What an interesting dream.
I know, right?
All right! Tsubomi!
Well... um...
I'm sorry!
Huh?
I only think about myself and keep imposing what I want on others, unlike Momo...
That's not true!
You thought so hard about how to help me change, after all.
Then you're not mad at me?!
Not at all!
And more importantly, Erika...
No need to be so formal. We're friends now!
Gotcha, Erika!
If I join the Fashion Club, will we be able to make this doll even cuter?
You're gonna join the Fashion Club?!
If you don't mind sharing me with the Gardening Club...
Thanks so much! Glad to have you!
That's right, I was in the middle of going shopping!
I'll have this guy fixed up by tomorrow!
Tsubomi, Tsubomi's grandma,
thanks for helping me when I collapsed!
See ya!
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born!
What the heck is this?
It's a Heart Seed.
It was created because Erika's
Flower of the Heart was purified.
Now it's my turn!
And this is?
The Heart Pot!
If we gather a lot of Heart Seeds within the Heart Pot,
we'll be able to revive the Great Heart Tree!
Now, place the seed in here!
O-Okay...
Tsubomi,
as they attempt to eliminate the human heart, and with it the Great Heart Tree,
the Desert Apostles' attacks will only become fiercer.
It'll be all right!
My partner, Tsubomi, will become a Precure and protect us!
You're my partner?
That's right!
I bring forth the Seed of the
Precure and offer you advice!
I'm Chypre! Once again, it's
good to be working with you!
Same for me.
I'd be worried if it was just Tsubomi on her own.
You are the weakest Precure in history, after all.
What's with that?!
I beat that Desertrian, didn't I?
I need to find a partner who'll become a Precure too!
I'm sure you'll find one!
We'll look after Chypre and Coffret at our place.
Won't this surprise Mom and Dad?
It'll be fine!
We'll just pretend to be plushies!
All right then, shall we head home?
Tsubomi.
Being a Precure grants immense power, so you must be careful how you fight.
I understand.
For some reason, I feel like becoming a Precure has changed me a little.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
I didn't want to put you in danger, Tsubomi.
Grandma?
But... protecting the Great Heart Tree is the mission entrusted to all Precure.
Becoming a Precure means you'll have to stand up to the chaos that lies ahead.
Just like the meaning of your name, you're still a bud waiting to bloom, Tsubomi.
By becoming a Precure and working hard, you'll bloom into a fantastic flower.
Really?!
I'm gonna do my best!
Tsubomi?!
That hurt...
How worrying...
What am I going to do with you, Tsubomi?
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Become a Precure with me!
I'm busy! I just don't have the time!
Then just try it with me! Just try it, okay?
One, two!
Precure! Open My Heart!
See, you wanna do it now! Right?! Right?!
I said I wouldn't, so I'm not gonna!
HeartCatch Precure:
The Second Precure
is Raring to go!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!