Hey, when were the Taika Reforms?
You're in 3rd Grade, and you still don't know?
You sure are stupid.
We haven't learned it.
Here's an easy way to remember it:
just call them the Uneventful Reforms.
TL Note:
6-2-5 can also be pronounced as mu-ji-ko, and in this case, mujiko means "uneventful."
Uneventful?
Nothing really happened during the Taika Reforms.
Uneventful, the year 625.
Don't forget it.
I've imprinted it into my heart.
I won't ever forget it.
Here at Fumizuki Academy, academic ability equals battle power,
and test scores equal justice.
What is it, Himeji? You have something for me?
There's something I want to ask you.
It'll be real quick!
That's all.
The first second year Summoned Being Exam War of the semester
concluded with Class F defeating Class E.
Oh? Not bad.
The losing class must be quite mad since their facilities has now turned to trash.
Tell them that if they're unsatisfied, they should work hard to improve their grades and then try to win back their class.
Life is a series of battles!
Actually, based on the students' decision, they didn't exchange classroom setups.
Hm? What's with that?
As expected of superglue.
You can fix everything in a flash.
This is great, Akihisa.
This glue's much better.
We went through so much to win. The least they could do was to improve our supplies.
We should be sitting in the Class E desks.
Yuuji! Why did you turn down exchanging classrooms?
Dude, seriously? You want to use those busted up tables?
They're better than these flimsy Japanese tables!
Eh? What the heck? How did...
It's not like you study,
so the desks shouldn't matter to you anyway.
They matter!
You can use desks to eat lunch on, sleep on, and write graffiti on!
It's an important partner in every student's school life.
You and that desk are inseparable.
We'll only be using these Japanese tables for today, anyway.
Class A declared war against us, hm?
Right.
If we win this next one, then we can have Class A's setup.
It messes up my plans a bit, but it shouldn't be much of a problem.
Everything is going as I planned.
Right, Himeji?
Eh? Y-Yeah.
Well, let's head to Class A.
So this is Class A.
It's like a luxury hotel.
This setup suits me very well.
Look, Yoshii! An unlimited drink and snack bar.
You'll be laughed at for making such a big deal out of it.
Have some class!
What you do and what you say are completely different things.
Oh? Isn't the battle tomorrow?
Sister!
You want to surrender already?
We just wanted to see what's about to be ours.
How confident.
I'm here to negotiate.
Let's decide the outcome of the war with a one-on-one between class reps.
Are you stupid?
How the hell can you beat the one with the highest grades in the second year class?
You scared?
As expected of the cowards who attack weak classes that have just been to war.
Wanna go now?
Wait.
If one fight decides all of it, I'll accept it.
Rep!
But I have a condition.
The losing side must comply to one order from the winning side.
Is this the reason you declared war on Class F?
Don't be mistaken.
We of Class A are obligated to protect the school's order and peace.
It's retribution for the lazy idiots who declared war in the first semester without working hard.
All right. I'll accept your class rep's condition.
Not one versus one, but five versus five.
Yuuko.
Although I don't believe that our class rep will lose,
it's best to take precaution.
Okay, five versus five is fine too.
But we get to choose the subject to fight about.
Very well.
Negotiations complete.
What are we going to do now? Why did you do that?
We'll win, so it doesn't matter.
The only difference now is that they'll be at our beck and call when we do.
Is that really okay?
There's a weird rumor about the class rep, Kirishima Shouko.
Rumor?
She has perfect grades and is gifted in both brains and beauty.
But that beauty has constantly rejected surrounding men who want to go out with her.
Eh? She's popular, isn't she?
It is said that she has no interest in guys.
Not interested in guys...
Don't tell me Kirishima-san's intention was to...
I-It's definitely not like that.
That would be too weird.
No way something like that'll happen to someone we know.
Right? Shimada-san.
There is.
Someone who's that weird is right here!
I found you, onee-sama!
Miharu!
You're so cruel, onee-sama!
You left me all alone to chat with these filthy, good-for-nothing men.
Let me go! Piss off!
I surrender, I surrender!
Who is that?
Shimizu Miharu of second year Class D.
Hurry and get off me!
Don't be shy, onee-sama.
You do love me, don't you? Don't be shy!
I'm normal; I like guys!
Yoshii, hurry up and say something.
She's right, Shimizu-san. You're wrong.
While Shimada-san may be indiscernible from a man in terms of her looks, personality, and chest size,
She is, in fact, most satisfactor—
No matter how you look at me, I'm still a girl!
That's right. I love onee-sama as a girl!
I surrender... I surrender!
I won't let you off!
I can see... can see...
I surrender. Shimada-san, I'll abide to your every order.
Really? Then I want you to treat me to crepes from Lapelle next time we're off.
Huh? What about my living expenses?
I'll gladly treat you!
Also, you must call me Minami-sama.
I'll call you Aki.
I will, Minami-sama.
And... And...
Say you love me!
Yes ma'am, I'll say it!
I'm not lettin' you!
Say it!
I can see... can see...
Hurry and say you love me!
Yes ma'am!
"Hurry and say you love me!"
You idiot!
What an unfortunate incident...
Himeji-san?
Watcha' doing, Himeji-san?
Ah! Yoshii-kun!
It's just like a love letter.
Don't tell me she's writing a love letter in class.
N-No, it's not what you think!
No, it might also be it!
It's not!
TL Note: 幸の手紙 literally translates to "letter of misfortune." In common context, however, it refers to chain letters which are believed to bring curses on those who do not spread them.
This is a weird chain letter.
That's a very troubling misunderstanding.
Is that guy in our class?
Yes.
Is that so?
Okay, I'll teach you how to write a chain letter properly. How about it?
No. This isn't one of those.
No. This is one!
Sign: Sweat
Aren't I feeling really unfortunate right now?
That's not it.
I see. What's good about this guy, anyway?
It's not his appearance.
Not that I don't like his looks!
My friend said that when she sees the beautiful Yoshii-kun
and tough Sakamoto-kun walking together,
it's like looking at a painting.
She's a good friend.
You should be good to her.
She also said that Yoshii-kun is the one on the bottom.
Please sever all ties to her right now.
But it's not just his appearance. He's also very nice on the inside.
His liver indeed looks very nice.
I'm not talking about his internal organs.
You can't be talking about his personality, right?
I am. He's kind, easy-going, and always seems cheerful.
He's the man I've always admired.
I see.
This letter...
Yes.
I hope it gets a good response.
Yup.
You're here, eh? Our strategy meeting is about to begin.
Hey, where are you going, Akihisa?
Don't come near me, and don't walk with me.
What is it, Akihisa? What happened?
I...
am not the receiver!
What?
The first battle shall begin.
Why am I the round girl?
Round One.
What are you babbling about?
Who in the world besides you can be the round girl?
I told you. I'm not a girl.
All right then. The contestant of each class, go forth.
It's all yours, Shimada.
Then I'll be going.
Let's hurry and get this over with.
Not like it's even a "match."
Don't look down on us just because we're from Class F.
Begin match.
Summoned Being,
summon!
I'm as good as Class B when it comes to math.
That's amazing...
Summon!
H-How...
But I'm Class A level, of course.
Winner: Kinoshita Yuuko.
It was inevitable.
You didn't realize that Class B's level was nowhere near Class A's? Is your brain lacking oxygen?
It's quite comfortable in this position.
I can see... see...
Round two.
Begin battle two.
Contestants, step forth.
I am Satou Miho of Class A.
Okay. Akihisa, you're up.
Me? If we lose this match, there'll be no way out.
Don't worry. I have faith in you.
I see. You want me to get serious, eh?
There's no need to hide it anymore, right?
Let everyone see your true strength.
Oh, you... I guess I'll have to comply.
You... could it be...?
Precisely. Up until now, I've never really tried before.
Then that means you're—
Exactly, just as you think.
Although I've been hiding my true strength all this time,
I'm actually
left-handed!
Winner, Satou Miho of Class A.
What the hell do test scores and being left-handed have to do with each other?!
I can see... see... see.
We've only just started. Time to get serious.
Yuuji, you bastard! Didn't you have faith in me?
I didn't have faith that you'd win.
I want to use my left hand on you!
Round three will now start.
Round three.
Class A: Kudou Aiko.
Class F: Tsuchiya Kouta.
Which subject?
Health and physical education.
So you're good at health and Phys Ed, eh?
I'm also good at those but in a different way.
I learned by doing.
Doing?
Ninja Pervert!
How dare you do such a cruel thing to Ninja Pervert!?
Despicable!
You want to replace him?
But you seem to do bad academically.
If you don't mind, I can teach you health and Phys Ed.
Physically, of course.
Yoshii-kun! Aki!
Leave him alone. Aki will never have that chance!
Exactly. Yoshii-kun doesn't need that kind of education!
Why do you guys say such cruel things...
Ninja Pervert.
Don't worry. This is nothing.
Well then, begin match.
Summon.
Summon!
446!?
Practical vs Theoretical.
I'll show you which side is stronger.
Bye Bye, Ninja Pervert-kun.
Speed increase.
Speed increase complete.
What the hell? I actually...
Winner is Tsuchiya Kouta of Class F.
He's so strong!
His score in health and physical education alone is almost the same as my total score in all subjects!
Round four will begin now.
Round four.
I'll be going now.
Good luck, Himeji-san.
Will do.
Well then, I'll take this one on.
Kubo Toshimitsu, eh?
He's the one that I was the most worried about.
Why?
He's the salutatorian of our year.
It'll be tough if we don't choose his weak subjects.
How?
Which subject?
Please choose All Subjects.
He chose on his own... We're the ones with the right to choose.
It's fine.
Himeji-san.
Crap. Strength in general knowledge and class rank are directly related.
Then...
Begin match.
Summon.
What an amazing score.
Our school's number two already has a score that high?
Himeji-san!
Summoned Being,
summon!
It's over 4000?!
It's a score that can match our valedictorian's.
Since when did you get that high of a score?
Go!
I've already decided to do my best!
I've heard about why we started this Summoned Being Exam War.
I like this class.
In this class, everyone tries their best for others.
The person I like is also in this class.
That's why I'll also do my best!
Winner: Himeji Mizuki of Class F.
This is amazing, Aki!
With that win, it's two to two now.
Himeji-san!
Now the next battle will determine the outcome.
The fifth and the last round will now begin.
Round Five
All right. It's my turn now.
Yuuji...
Watch and observe.
Class F representative. Sakamoto Yuuji.
Class A representative. Kirishima Shouko.
Which subject?
Please use a test limited to Japanese History.
Use the one at the elementary level.
Full score is a hundred.
Using a test!?
Not fighting with Summoned Beings?
The Summoned Being Exam War is a war that uses test scores to battle.
As long as it utilizes tests and the teacher approves,
there is no other regulation.
I understand.
Then, prepare to be tested.
Contestants, please head to the classroom.
What's with that, Yuuji?
If they're elementary questions, wouldn't you both get a hundred?
Wouldn't that end in a tie?
Probably not. If there's even the tiniest mistake, one loses.
Exactly. It isn't about academic ability
but rather concentration and attentiveness.
Yuuji...
Chill. I've got it handled.
When Shouka memorizes something, she never forgets it.
Isn't that a disadvantage for you?
No. That's what I'm betting on.
She incorrectly memorized that the Taika Reforms, the Uneventful Reforms,
happened in the year 625.
If this question comes up, then I can win.
Wait, Yuuji!
Didn't the Taika Reforms occur in year 625?
The Uneventful Reforms happened in the year 645!
This is the truth. Trust me, Akihisa.
Yuuji.
This class's system desk
is going to be in our palms.
Please begin.
Finally, eh?
What happens if that question doesn't come up?
If he lacks concentration or attentiveness, then Yuuji will probably lose.
But if this question comes up.
Here it is!
Well then, I'll announce the results of the limited test.
Class A representative, Kirishima Shouko.
97.
Awesome!
Class A's rep didn't get a full score.
From now on, this facility is ours.
Yoshii-kun!
Next, Class F representative, Sakamoto Yuuji.
53.
Class F's Japanese tables
mmmmmmm became tangerine boxes
Class F's Japanese tables became tangerine boxes.
It's worse than before!
What's with that score, Yuuji?
Indeed, that was the limit of my ability.
You knew that if you didn't get 100 points, the plan wouldn't work!
I wasn't expecting such an ambush.
You're the one who ambushed us!
Yuuji.
Our deal.
Deal... Comply to any order.
I know. Shoot it.
No, you can't! Kirishima-san!
Homosexuality is not the way to go!
Yuuji, go out with me.
You still haven't given up?
I will never give up.
I've always liked you.
Can I reject?
Nope. Because you promised.
We'll go on a date now.
Eh. Wait—
What was that?
I wonder...
So the reason Kirishima-san looked at Himeji-san like that
was because she was bothered by the girls around Yuuji.
I'm sorry, Himeji-san.
The situation's worse than before.
It's a good class.
I love Class F.
And...
Well then, Aki, it's time to get some crepes, right?
Wasn't that supposed to be over the weekend!?
Weekends are weekends. Today is today.
What?
If I treat you twice, I'll run out of living expenses before I get my next allowance.
No way, Yoshii-kun is going to go watch a movie with me.
Eh?
Himeji-san, I didn't know that.
I know; I just decided.
Come on! Let's go eat crepes.
What kind of movie will you take me to?
What the hell! No!
Save me. Stop! Save me!
That guy must be a real idiot.
The third question.
What is the portion of a household's expenses that covers food costs called?
I'll only have salt and water this week!
I did not ask for the breakdown of meals.
Next week:  Food Expenses, Dates, and Stun Guns.
This will be on the test.