SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
Honestly, this snow is so annoying.
Especially on days that HQ orders us to do thorough patrols.
Yeah.
So, you haven't given up on Jacott-san?
That's not what I...
Well, it's okay, I guess.
Although you looked everywhere,
as long as you haven't found her, there's still hope.
What?
You remind me a bit of Rio-senpai, Kureha-chan.
What is it?
Under the cliff.
11 o'clock.
About 400 meters.
Wake up! Get a hold of yourself!
Even her clothes are frozen!
Kanata, take off her coat.
Huh?
She can use mine.
Ah, okay!
She's...
A Roman soldier.
A VISITOR
A BURNING FIELD OF SNOW
To actually restore this facility...
Now that's what I call the greatest girl-genius
in the history of academia.
Victory will be ours with this.
It's all thanks to you, Kannagi Noel-kun.
Noel-chan!
They found her during their patrol.
She's a Roman soldier.
It looks like her left leg is fractured.
Hey, all her fingers are dark-red.
It's frostbite.
If you don't treat it properly, she could lose her fingers.
Helvetian witch...
Leave her to me!
Looks like she's finally stabilized.
Her fingers are okay, too.
Thank goodness.
What about Noel-chan?
She said she'll stay a bit longer.
But, I wonder...
The way she focuses on her is as if
she's working on the Takemikazuchi.
I see.
A trumpet?
She must be a scout.
But I didn't expect this.
Well, of course.
No one would've imagined finding a Roman soldier-
That's not it.
This is my first time seeing a Roman.
Everyone just calls them the enemy.
So I thought they'd be more like a demon or something.
The Romans probably think the same way about us.
But now that I've seen her,
I'm starting to think the Romans are just like us.
Hey, Kanata! You-
Say, Kana-chan,
it's almost time for the evening call.
Ah!
The peace talks are still going poorly, aren't they?
It seems so.
Are you going to report her?
If I do that, she'll be taken to the
central government and interrogated.
We can't do anything about it!
She infiltrated enemy territory during this unstable period.
She'd be ready for torture-
It's interrogation.
I'll decide how to deal with her.
Please, give me time, Kureha-chan.
Please don't forget, Captain.
We are soldiers.
Can I ask one more thing?
When you brought her here, did anyone see you?
I'm not sure. We were too busy with her.
I see.
Thank you.
Say, Rio...
What would you do?
A Helvetian soldier!
What would you do with this?
Where is this?! Am I a hostage of the Helvetians now?!
I don't speak Roman.
So, you took me host-
What was that scream?!
What happened?
She woke up.
Thank goodness.
Ground Forces of the Roman Empire.
First Tank Division,
Thirteenth Tank Batallion,
Company B, Sergeant Aisha Ardora.
ID number, 1031021.
Why are you here?
Army of the Roman Empire, Sergeant Aisha Ardora.
What is your mission?
ID number, 1031021.
You've got guts...
How is it? Did you get anything?
Nothing at all!
She doesn't seem to understand any Helvetian.
We only got her ID number and her name, Aisha.
I'm Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann,
the commanding officer of this Fortress.
I see you have big boobs. That's just my type.
Would you mind if I fondled them?
Can I feel you up as well?
What are you saying, Captain?!
So she truly doesn't understand Helvetian, it seems.
But, this is troubling.
We can't interrogate her like this.
We need to find someone who can speak Roman right away.
So...
Until we can properly interrogate her and file an
official report, we'll keep her under our unit.
But...!
It's just... I thought of placing a bet.
Don't blame me, whatever happens.
Aisha-chan, welcome to the Timekeeping Fortress.
Timekeeping Fortress?
That's right, Timekeeping Fortress.
So I actually made it here...
Grandmother...
Say "ah"...
Hm? Is it too hot?
She ate it!
Is it good?
You need stamina to escape, so I'm going to eat now.
I'm sure she said it was good.
I wonder...
Kanata is her usual self, but Noel getting attached to her...
It might be her way to atone for her sins.
Huh?
Listen, have you ever seen a fossilized angel?
"Engel"?
Oh right, you don't understand anything.
I should have learned Roman.
I guess you're right, if we could communicate...
Working hard, I see.
Oh, Yumina-chan.
Do you have enough hands to clear the snow at the church?
Yes.
The kids are working hard.
That's good to hear.
That means they won't be kids forever.
Indeed.
People grow day by day.
Like Kanata-san's trumpet.
I bet Rio would say she still had a long way to go.
Oh?
Weren't you going to Treize for supplies?
Stuff happened, so I came back empty-handed.
Sorry to hear that.
Oh, speaking of the Fortress...
I heard a bad rumor.
Thank you for listening.
Your trumpet is great!
I didn't think there were still trumpets like these.
May I?
I think Rio-senpai would do the same.
A great trumpet.
To get to see something like this-
Hey, that song you just played!
Amazing! This is so wonderful!
Iliya-san's note resounds in me!
And it resounds in Rio-senpai too!
And the same song resounds
not just in Helvetia, but Rome as well!
Notes do resound, don't they?
Be it Rome or Helvetia, they're the same.
First-aid treatment.
Thanks!
"Danke"?
Yes, thanks!
What's "danke"?
It means, "thank you".
So somebody saw us after all.
This town never experienced the brunt of war,
but almost all the residents, in one way or another,
have lost someone they knew,
including parents, siblings, or relatives in the war.
They're usually calm, but when things happen...
Mikhail, the one who owns that liquor store,
remember him?
I went to his place yesterday.
It seems that Helvetian Army is mobilizing on a large scale.
And they're heading this way.
If it has anything to do with that Roman soldier here,
it'll be bad.
Anyway, we need to ask her.
Naomi-san, do you know anyone who understands Roman?
More than just know, actually.
I'm Yumina.
I serve the Helvetian Orthodox Church.
May luck be with you always.
So, you're one of the heretics!
There is only one God. Such a greeting is blasphemy.
What did she say?
It's just a light greeting.
We don't need that, just ask her already!
Why are you here?
If you don't talk, everyone here
will wind up with extra work.
If you feel the slightest bit of gratitude,
you should speak the truth.
I can't talk about my mission,
but I'm here to see the fossilized angel
that's supposedly in this town.
She said she's here to see the fossil of the angel.
Fossil of the angel?
What's that?
My grandmother once was in this guard fortress.
"My grandmother was a soldier of the Timekeeping Fortress."
She was taken as a POW on the Eastern Front.
She met my grandfather there.
"She was captured and held prisoner on the
Eastern Front, and met my grandfather."
When I was a child, she would often tell me about it.
"I was raised listening to her stories."
I wanted to see it, no matter what.
The angel my grandmother had seen.
The Angel of the Apocalypse that
brought retribution unto the world long ago.
That's the wrong teaching!
The one who destroyed the world was a demon!
Just tell us exactly what she said!
She wanted to see the
Angel of Apocalypse that destroyed the world.
That's why she came here.
The marching call!
This signal...
Royal Guard Platoon, 9th Independent Mobile Division.
The 9th?! Don't tell me...
Colonel Hopkins!
Is he famous?
They called him the "Knight of Vingt".
He activated a weapon from the old era
and obliterated three towns overnight.
It's okay.
He doesn't know you're here.
It'll be all right.
Either way, it seems you no longer have time to think.
You need to decide now or you'll be in deep trouble.
Hand her over or-
There's nothing to think about!
We're the Helvetian Army.
I lost the bet.
It means you didn't make it, did you Rio?
Please wait!
Rio-senpai said she didn't want anyone else to suffer anymore.
That's why she'll do what she can.
That's why she left, isn't it?
But...
I don't like this.
Everyone's the same!
Everyone's together!
As the commanding officer of
Platoon 1121, these are my orders.
This order will be based on my own judgement.
I will take full responsibility for it.
Everyone understand?
I'm the Captain of Platoon 1121.
Lieutenant Filicia Heidemann.
A Roman scout was captured in Treize a few days ago.
Unfortunately, there was an accident during the
interrogation process, so we couldn't confirm anything.
Coincidently, I received an eye-witness report
stating there was a Roman soldier here.
Would you know about that?
Negative, Colonel.
Very well then.
From now, the 1121st Fortress will be under the
command of the 9th Independent Mobile Division.
Don't make loud noises!
I'm sorry.
Aisha-san told me about the legend of the Fire Maidens just now,
but it's weird.
According to her-
Search thoroughly!
Found anything?
How about over there?
Nothing here!
Find her no matter what!
Break down the door!
Should be around here somewhere.
Seal the exits!
Oh, she said she hasn't heard your name yet.
Noel.
Her name is Noel.
Noel?
Noel Kannagi?
Yes.
The one who released the Invisible Reaper-
The Invisible Reaper?!
Oh? Was that a rat?
Noel-san!
H-Hello.
1121st Platoon speaking.
A large battalion of the Roman Army
appeared on the border of Seize?!
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
ECHO IN THE BLUE SKY
Next episode: Echo in the Blue Sky
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.