This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki.
She's twelve and dreams of becoming a singer.
But unfortunately, she only has one year left to live.
Her manager has been selected
and we went to Dr. Wakaouji's
place to meet her, but...
...we have to keep her secret
from being exposed. It's terrible!
But hey, it's my job
to get her through all these problems.
Well then...
I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Stop that at once, it's unladylike.
How can you...
...be so rude as to only worry about your skirt?
You should be more attentive while eating.
What is that sound?
I-It's nothing!
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful.
Good night.
Ah. Wait a minute.
I haven't finished talking to...
Honestly, I really have to keep her on a short leash.
That was close.
H-Hello?
Ah. Mitsuki-chan? This is Ooshige.
Ooshige-san!
It's short notice, but
your debut single has been
selected to go on the market.
Eh?
Eh?!
Debut?!
The Feelings In Your Song
Mitsuki-chan.
This is your producer, Takasu-sensei.
I'm Kouyama Mitsuki.
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
The debut concept is...
...the trouble of coming up with a cool and elite name.
Eh?
Um... could you repeat that?
If it's regarding that matter...
...there is no question about my supporting you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What?
There's no need for you to worry.
Together, we'll be sure to...
...turn you into a sexy singer.
S-Sexy you said?
What... you're going to be late?
Okay.
Here...
This is a song written just for your debut.
A tempting kiss
The two of us are already a Non-Stop
Love Hurricane
Love... me... do...?
"Love me do Forever".
You're a high school student, aren't you?
Don't you recognize English?
Uh, yes!
Sorry about that!
A tempting kiss...
The two of us are already
a Non-Stop Love Hurricane?
For now...
...we're concentrating on your debut.
Um...
Huh?
You want me to sing this?
Are you unsatisfied with it?
To say unsatisfied... well...
This is...
P-Please excuse us for a second!
You mustn't, Mitsuki-chan.
You have to be more happy about it.
Takasu-san is...
...the one who produced Matsushita Genki's and...
...Kobayashi's debut.
He's an amazing record producer.
Okay...
But...
...that song won't... be able to reach Eichi-kun.
Eichi-kun?
Why don't you try writing one yourself then?
You just said that you wanted to put
your own feelings into your song, right?
So then, you'll have to try writing it yourself.
My feelings in my song...?
Why don't you try doing it... songwriting?
I'm leaving this to you, Mitsuki-chan.
Man... these new artist nowadays are all so spoiled.
Well...
...it's okay as long as you understand how futile it is.
I'll try songwriting.
Eh?!
It's just like you said.
I'll try to put my feelings in it.
Thank you very much for the advice.
That wasn't supposed to be advice...
What? That's bad...
Got it. I'll be right there.
It's fine. This'll be interesting.
However, the time limit is three days.
Just how far can you go in three days.
I want you to show me that.
I... I'm very sorry!
Mitsuki-chan.
Yes?
As your manager, there's something I want to ask you.
Y-Yes?
Who's Eichi-kun?
Tell me!
I see...
So you have someone you like.
Yes.
But he left for America, and I
haven't had any contact with him.
My desire to become a singer is because...
...if he heard me...
...then maybe he'd notice me.
That's what I think.
All right!
Huh?
If that's the case, then I'll be rooting for you.
Really?
Yep.
That song just now...
...had no musical sense or good points to it at all.
But... it'll be popular, right?
You don't need to restrict yourself
to only song that will be popular.
I want you... to debut with a good song.
Ooshige-san...
Write a good song...
...and open Takasu-san's eyes!
Okay!
All right...
...let's start writing!
What's wrong? Hurry up and write.
I'd like to do that, but...
I wonder how I'm supposed
to go about songwriting...
Don't tell me...
...you don't know how to write songs!
Yeah...
Then why did you say you were going to write a song?!
That's because...
You have to be more upbeat when you're
songwriting instead of suffering like you are now.
What should I do?
I have to finish it in three days...
Just leave it to me.
Do you have any CDs of a song anthology?
Yup. Just a sec.
Do you always keep it there?
Yup, it's easier for me to find them this way.
See.
That looks like it, but it's so worn out...
This is the only thing I have that's music-related.
I've read it over and over again.
You're really so... valiant!
By the way, Meroko...
...what do you plan on doing about your song?
Well, that's...
Eh?
Meroko, what the hell are doing all of a sudden?!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Anyways...
...let go of my ha-...!
What I just did was a hint.
Eh?
So then, what was it?
What the hell do you mean, "What is it?"
All you did back there was clamp
your big mouth over my hand!
Exactly.
You should just shut your mouth.
But... I wonder if I'll be okay doing something like that.
Of course not, there's no way you'll be okay!
It'll be fine.
You're doing this to see the
person you like, after all.
I guess so...
Huh?
Do whatever you want!
W-What was that for?
Now Takuto will be all lovey-dovey with me.
Man...
You said to leave the songwriting to you...
and you're already sick of it.
Huh?
She's...
I guess it can't be helped.
You're up early.
Ah, Takuto.
Good morning.
By the way, are you okay in just your pajamas?
Yeah. I seem fine.
I guess I forgot about my sickness.
Forgot...?
It's the first time I've ever
forgotten about my sickness.
Doing what I want to, with all my heart...
...it feels so good.
And... it was you, right?
Huh?
This.
That's why I'm fine.
Thank you!
A-Anyways, did you finish writing?
Yeah. I finished writing, but...
What is it?
Meroko.
Let's see.
H-How is it?
Well...
How should I put it...
Huh? If you don't get it, then let me have a look at it.
If you're smiling... it's like a clear day.
If you're crying... it's like a great flood.
As long as I am by your side,
it'll always be smiles and peace.
What's this suppose to be?
As I thought... they're no good, huh.
I-I wouldn't say that they're no good...
Y-Yeah.
The first time's probably like this.
It's okay.
I know that I can't do it by myself.
I've never done it before, after all.
There isn't time to learn.
Why don't you go on a date once, then?
Eh?!
Sure.
If you do that, you'll be able to write something.
But... how?
There's no one to go with.
T-That's right...
I thought it was a good idea...
Good morning, Mitsuki-chan!
How are you feeling this morning?
There he is!
The person who you're going on a date with!
Eh?!
A date with Wakaouji-sensei?!
Wow!
This is the first time I've ever been to Harajuku!
You're this happy about coming here... I'm glad.
I was really surprised when you
asked me on a date, though.
Well, as long as you're this
happy, your body will get better.
Okay!
All right!
Let's start our date.
Okay!
Wow!
This is really good!
Isn't it?
I was sure that you would like it.
Just what you would expect from a little girl's escort.
Heh. He's not doing much.
So... how's the date?
This is more fun than your job, right?
Yep!
I had lots of fun!
It's almost as if I was on a date with Eichi-kun.
Ah!
Sometimes when you're staring at the sky...
...you're thinking about Eichi-kun, aren't you?
Eichi-kun, Eichi-kun...
She's so cute!
Not really...
Well...
...it's about time.
Shall we head back?
Okay!
Mitsuki-chan!
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Mitsuki-chan!
Mitsuki-chan, hold on!
The medicine's taken effect, right?
Your fever's gone down,
and you don't seem like coughing anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's because I was thinking selfishly.
No.
It was my fault for being careless.
That's not it.
Last night... I stayed up.
You stayed up?
It couldn't have been because of your job.
I certainly agreed to your working, but...
...if you do such unreasonable things,
I can't allow you to continue being a model.
Sensei! Please stop saying that!
I want to debut no matter what!
If I don't debut...
...I won't be able to let Eichi-kun know that I'm here.
I... I...
I understand.
You don't need to say any more.
If I oppose you, I'll just be the bad guy.
Don't worry.
I'll still back you up.
Really?!
Of course.
But don't do anything unreasonable from now on.
Okay!
Eichi again, huh?
To be thought about this much... Eichi must be happy.
I also won't do anything like... giving up on Takuto!
Let me go already!
I'll excuse myself, then.
What are you doing?
The medicine's working, so I'll...
Stop it.
Go to sleep.
I can't fall asleep.
There's only one day left to write a song.
Hey, Takuto.
Can you turn me into a sixteen year old again?
Then you won't have to worry about my health, right?
That's true, but...
Why do you have to do such unreasonable things?!
Isn't it fine?!
That producer Takasu's songs...
...they'll be a hit, right?
I don't want a song that's just a hit.
I have to send my feelings to Eichi-kun properly.
Just stop it already.
Huh?
Takuto?
Stop trying to write songs like that!
What do you mean by that?
Just give up already.
Besides, writing a song is impossible for you.
W-Wait... Hold up,
Takuto!
My voice won't come out.
If Takuto isn't here, I...
...won't ever again... like that...
What should I do?
Man.. what's with her?
Everything she says is Eichi, Eichi, Eichi.
It's so annoying!
Takuto, wait up!
Wait up, I said!
What's wrong with you, saying something like that...
Huh?
What's with you... stopping so suddenly...
Meroko.
Huh?
It kinda looks like they're arguing.
Let's check it out.
Okay.
What is the meaning of this?
Huh?
What's "the song is already done" supposed to mean?
Just what I said.
The songs have been altered.
That can't be.
Back there you promised Mitsuki-chan
she could write her own so-...!
If this project fails...
...do you understand how much will be lost?
Leaving it to an amateur...
...did you really think that I'd do that?
T-That's...
But, a promise is a promise!
How naive.
You can't think like that in this world.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Good job, you.
Open your eyes.
There's no way someone like you could
ever understand Mitsuki's feelings.
That's right.
She... always remembers her
promises, no matter who they're with.
Even thought I knew that...
I... what did I do..?!
I'm going back.
What are you doing to my head?!
Wait!
Geez... what's with you?
This is very sensitive!
Ow! That place hurts!
Ow!
Mitsuki...
Back there, I...
What are you doing?
Hurry up and stop that.
Back there, I...
Takuto...?
Huh?
Then... this is...
While I was writing my song...
...Grandma kept coming in and checking on me.
So I pretended that I was under my blanket.
Wh-What in the..?!
Takuto.
I'm sorry about earlier.
E-Er... that's supposed to be my line.
I've been only depending on you guys for everything.
Wanting to debut... and wanting to see Eichi-kun...
...those are all part of my dream.
If I don't work hard myself...
...that'd be wrong, right?
You've been writing the whole time since then?
Yeah.
I've thrown away a lot of drafts.
But it was fun to think this much about a song.
Eh?
I really do love singing!
Earlier, when I thought about
never being able to sing again...
...I was really sad.
It was painful...
I want to see Eichi-kun, of course, but...
...I want to sing just as much!
This feeling makes my heart skip!
I can't make it stop!
That's it.
Eh? That's it?
Use the true words that came from your heart...
...try singing with those.
Put these feelings into my song?
Yeah.
But...
I wonder if I can say it well.
You told me just fine.
Me, too.
Okay!
I got it! I'll try it!
That's it.
That's the spirit!
Work hard!
Okay!
This is the best I can do towards expressing my feelings.
Please take a look at them.
Well. I'll at least take a look at it.
Well, it can't be helped.
This is Takasu.
For Kouyama Mitsuki's song,
I've selected a different one.
Huh?
That means...
I lost.
Writing with such will...
...the concept and the feeling... it's all there.
That means...
You did it!
It's been accepted!
Your song's been chosen!
Eh? Really?!
Yes, even though you have a tight schedule.
It's all due to your rash actions.
Prepare yourself.
It's going to be busy.
Yes! We'll do our best!
By the way...
...what are you going to use for a stage name?
Huh?
That's right...
What should we use?
Do you want to just go with your real name?
N-No, that'll be bad...
Um...
Hey, Mitsuki.
If by chance the two of us are separated...
...there's no need to worry.
Why?
Even if we're at the ends of the world...
...the moon will be in the sky.
So, I'll look in the sky for the moon...
That's why you have to shine even brighter...
...so that I can find you sooner.
I've decided.
I've chosen Full Moon.
Tatta hitotsu kawaranai mono
Ta
There's just one thing that's never gonna change
Zutto egaiteta yume
Zu
the dream that I have always been drawing
Ima no jibun wa dou utsuru no
I
How would I, as I am right now...
Ano koro no chiisana hitomi ni
A
...look to those young eyes I used to have?
Say, look up... The night sky stretches so far
Nee miagete konna ni hiroi yozora dakara
Sou sugu ni wakaru you ni
Yes, very soon, you will understand
Seiippai kagayaku kara hayaku
I'm shining with all of my might, so hurry up
Full Moon wo sagashite
and find the full moon
Full
Moon
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi no tame ima no watashi ni dekiru subete
I
Together, forever! I'm doing everything I can for you right now
Day by Day
Day
by
Kyou made no unmei ashita kara no kibou kono mune ni kakae
Kyo
I hold the past fate dealt and the hope tomorrow brings here in my heart
Let's sing a song!
Let's
sing
a
song!
Itsudemo issho kimi to nara tsurai koto norikoerareru yo
Together, forever! As long as I am with you, I can make it through any pain
More and more
More
and
more
Motto motto motto chika tsukitai ima koko ni itekurete
Mo
More, more, and more, to be closer to you, I stand here now and give
Many Thanks for You!
Many
Thanks
for
You!
Preview
Yo-re-i-ho!
What was that all of a sudden?!
That's because... look, look...
...at this setting.
A blue sky. Green mountains.
The air is so fresh...
We didn't come to play around!
This is her first job, after all.
We have to keep an eye on her.
I get it.
But I wonder if that girl can pull it off.
When you say that...
Inside, she's still a twelve year old...
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
The First Job.
The First Job
Look forward to it!