Hey Hideyoshi, what are today's supplementary lessons-
Huh?
W-What is it... Akihisa?
Suspicion
There's something...
different about you today.
You think so?
Aren't I... always like this?
My appearance and behavior are the same as usual, right?
It's just that you're usually more cute and girly...
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
So, Professor Takahashi...
things are progressing well, I take it?
Yes, Headmaster.
Question 3
『 Me and That Girl and A Doll! 』
Because of her high grades and sociability,
what do you think about using Kinoshita Yuuko-san from Class A?
Her twin brother, Kinoshita Hideyoshi-kun, has already performed well as an opera singer,
so we can expect great things from Yuuko-san.
That's good to hear.
Having students who are multi-talented is something that a Headmaster can truly be proud of.
Yes, to have a second-year student of such irreproachable behavior and beauty,
paired with such good grades and
exemplary social conduct is a real rarity.
Pretty boys really are the best!  Especially the way that Yuuichi hits on Shinji so bluntly...
But this isn't the time to think about that.
I'm home.
Sister...
Holding you under the
legendary tree 2
What's wrong? Why would just just toss your favorite story away like that?
Absolute Favorite
How is it possible that there is a skill that you possess that I do not?
What are you talking about?
Professor Takahashi asked me,
Please
to sing the school song for the Fumizuki High School promotional video today.
Fumizuki Academy
Please
Promotional
Video
School
Song
Sing
What?!
Even though your musical ability and rhythm are...
basically non-existent.
Non-existent
Solar Plexus
Fist
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you looking for a fight?
If it was going to cause such a problem for you, you could have just refused.
Absolutely not!
Not after I've spent so much time,
going through the trouble of playing the unmatchable model student who can do anything!
Well your vanity is certainly unmatchable, isn't it, sister?
Vanity
Unmatchable
Clap
This is the role that a Kinoshita plays.
You are the master of acting on stage, and I play the part of the model student.
Come to think of it, we're actually pretty alike in that respect aren't we?
Of course we are!
As much as I don't want to admit it, you're my-
Twin...
What's wrong?
What is it, sister?
You're good at fooling other people, right?
I'd prefer to call it "acting"...
Don't tell me!
Hideyoshi, your big sister has a favor that she'd like to request of you, okay?
Violent
Negotiations
That's more of a threat than it is a request!
Making a request
Fist
Are we really going to do this, sister?
It seems only fair considering that I'm taking your supplementary lessons for you, right?
But if my classmates ever find out about this...
So what if they do?
They'll keep on treating me like a girl forever.
With me filling in for you, I doubt that they'll figure it out.
Here, take this with you.
What's this?
A microphone. With this I can listen in on everything that you're doing.
Where did you get this thing, sister?
From a classmate of yours.
New material...
This classroom is as miserable as ever...
Remaining Time
Health
Mid-escape
Sugawa has escaped!!!
Sugawa has broken his contract and contacted a woman!
He's a traitor!
After him!
Yuuko (Freaked out...)
Curse
Yuuko      (really freaked out)
Hey, Hideyoshi.
We have printouts to do for our supplementary lessons today.
Oh, I see.
But Sugawa just did something pretty stupid...
Emergency report! Emergency report!
Remaining Time
Health
Mid-escape
We have obtained testimony from a girl who was approached by Sugawa.
She's stated that she has no interest in Sugawa, but was interested to know how Aki-san was doing.
Akihisa
Really
disgusted
I repeat, the female was interested in Akihisa-san!
I'm out!
All Alone
Idiots, all of them.
Well then, let's see how Hideyoshi is doing on his end.
Thank you, Kinoshita-san.
This voice is... Kubo-kun?
I have the courage now because of you.
It's really nothing.
What is it? What are they talking about?
Kubo
No...
Knowing that I have a classmate who understands me is very comforting.
I never thought that you...
would be interested in same-sex relationships too.
Hey, Hideyoshi. What's going on?
Can I borrow you for a minute, sister?!
Hang on, Hideyoshi... sis-
Hideyoshi!
Would you like to elaborate on what the two of you have been discussing?
We were just chatting.
And how exactly did it turn into a situation where I'm
supposed to be interested in same-sex relationships?!
But, the stories you read are-
Idiot!!! Super Idiot!!!
It's not the same thing!
You've gone and made it sound like I'm interested in dating girls!
That's not what I mea-
If you cause any more misunderstandings...
I get it! I get it!
Does he really "get it", I wonder?
Yuuko, come here.
What's wrong?
Class Rep?
Shouko
Hideyoshi, do not  mess this up...
Yuuko, your skirt is rolled up.
Shouko
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
That idiot!
Thank you Class Rep, but it's okay.
But, your skirt...
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
It's because...
Because?
I'm wearing underwear today.
Sister!!!
What's your excuse this time?
I meant that it was okay because I was
wearing my sports shorts under my skirt.
Okay how?!
Crack
Now you've made it look like
I usually don't wear any underwear at all!
Crack
But sports shorts are a kind of-
Stop being such an idiot and just wear the skirt normally!
But your skirt fits really loose around my waist...
I'll be careful! I'll be really careful!
Hooray for eavesdropping!
Geez...
Kinoshita-san!
Who's this?
Yokomizo
I'm Yokomizo Kouji.
Yokomizo Kouji?
I don't know him.
I-I love you.
P-Please go out with me!
A confession?
What should I do?
I don't want to hurt his feelings, but...
I'm sorry. I appreciate your feelings, but...
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
Yes, good answer!
Yokomizo
Well then, can you tell me what your type is?
I'm sorry. I...
I?
I'm... only interested in pretty little boys.
I am...
not  a girl-loving, panty-less, pedophile!
I just said what I thought was right based upon your preferences, sister.
That's just a preference in fiction, you know!
I've never mentioned it in public, have I?!
I'll keep that in mind. This time I'll imitate your character perfectly!
Sigh...
Hey, Hideyoshi.
All right.
Akihisa, they've stopped chasing you?
Yeah.
Ever since we heard that Yokomizo-kun confessed to your sister, they've all been focusing on him.
I-Is that so?
Yokomizo-kun,
Yuuko
other than myself, you've probably suffered the most today.
Yokomizo-kun never learns, does he?
Yuuko
You turned him down once before, and now he's going after your sister!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
I take it back!
Yuuko
He's pitiful!
Speaking of your sister, by the way...
I take it back!
He's pitiful!
Yuuko
I take it back!
He's pitiful!
Huh!
Your sister is really awesome, isn't she?
What do you mean?
It's just that...
she's cute, gets good grades, is good at sports... she's like the perfect sister.
You think so?
And just look at her.
She always looks so pretty.
Pretty... huh?
It's such a shame about her...
Huh?
I heard that your sister's a girl-loving pedophile who never wears panties.
Octopus Hold
Forget about that!
What?! Why?!
Am I just imagining it, or is there a slight new softness to your chest?
Slight
What do you mean slight? I'll have you know that things are developing exactly as they should be!
I'm not sure why, but there's is a rumor going around all of a sudden that my chest is developing.
What a coincidence.
I've heard a rumor that I'm actually a girl-loving
pedophile who goes to school without panties on.
How did this happen?
Now I'm treated like a girl even more.
Well, not that much has changed for you then, has it?
Where as I'm a triple-duty pervert.
This is all your fault for suggesting that we change places!
It's yours because you're a bad actor!
I guess that all we can do is ignore it.
Yeah, worrying about it won't help matters any.
Our school is just full of interesting rumors, it seems.
【Question 3】
Please indicate the syllable that is
accented when pronouncing the
underlined word below.
『Don't mind. It's your imagination.
He had stayed on business in New York yesterday.』
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『It's your imagination 』
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Generally, when words end
with "-tion", the vowel before the "-tion"
gets accented.
This is a good rule of thumb.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
『It's your  imagination 』
Teacher's comment:
Nice try, but you won't get it right
by just choosing all of them.
´ ´  ´ ´  ´ ´  ´  ´ ´ ´ ´
´
.
!
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
『It's your  imagination  』
Teacher's comment:
Baka to Test!
Every once in a while I wonder if you're actually a genius.
Let's go back in time, one year...
Let's go back in
time, one year...
Nobody move!
Inspection!
Open your bags and put them on your desks so that I can see what's inside them.
Futile
Resistance is futile!
Sakamoto, turn out your pockets as well.
Damn!
I'll be taking this mp3 player.
Damn! Why's it just me?!
Yoshii!
Take off your uniform and change into your gym clothes.
Why?! Now you're just going overboard!
Why can't you just trust-
Hey, Akihisa. You dropped your PSP.
Thank you, Yuuji.
Why can't you just trust me?!
Just change into the gym clothes.
Summoned Being...
Summon!
Today is the joint summoning
training for all first year students.
I just haven't had any luck at all today...
Damn, I just bought that mp3 player last month.
He confiscated a bunch of things from me as well.
Well, I lost my PSP, games, DVDs, CDs, manga,
Why do you even bother coming to school at all?
trading cards, celebrity photos, a spinning top-
Look, Himeji's up next.
Aren't you gonna take pictures, Muttsurini?
My digital camera was confiscated.
That's a shame.
She's not in our class, so it's not every day
that we get to see her in her gym clothes.
Summoned Being...
Summon!
As cute and smart as she is, it's
no wonder that she's so popular.
Oh yeah, you and Himeji go way back, don't you?
Yeah. We were in the same class in elementary school, but...
We haven't really spoken in a while.
Next, Yoshii Akihisa.
Huh? Okay.
Yoshii's opponent will be...
Shimada.
Shimada!
Shimada Minami!
Huh? Yes.
Yoshii?!
What's wrong, Shimada-san? You're seriously spaced out.
Are you hungry or something?
I'm not anything like you, okay?
Huh?
Oh, I've got it!
You're disappointed with how lame your Summoned Being is.
I'm glad that I'm up against you, Yoshii.
Because I'm really going to enjoy kicking your ass.
Crack
Wai-
It's supposed to be our Summoned Beings that are fighting, not us!
I guess you're right. We're not going to be fighting each other.
I'm glad that you get it.
After all, I'm  going to be the one giving you  a beatdown.
Shimada!
See, even the teacher doesn't-
Just this once, okay?
Okay!
What?!
It's just been one bad thing after another today.
It's H-Himeji-san.
All right.
I'll use this opportunity to go in and talk to her.
There's no way that I'll clear this hurdle! No choice but to... run away!
Please, I beg you.
I really have to have that plushie!
I beg you.
I really can't do that...
Um, what's the matter?
Well, this little girl really wants the plushie over there,
but she doesn't seem to have enough money.
Hey, why do you want that plushie so badly?
My big sister has been kind of depressed recently.
Your sister?
Yes.
She told me once that she'd like to have that plushie, so...
That's why...
I see.
You want to give her a present so you can cheer her up, right?
We just moved here, so she's been having a tough time at school.
But in spite of all that...
My sister still does all the housework
and even finds time to play with me.
Don't cry!
Maybe I can do something to help you!
Really?
Mister... thank you!
So, how much does it cost?
Tax included
,
It's twenty-five thousand yen.
I'm sorry...
I've done my best... but there's nothing that I can do.
Shock
But... I have ten-thousand here.
Well, if we add that to the thousand yen that I have... we'll still only have eleven-thousand yen.
So that means that we've got about half of the twenty-five thousand that we need.
It's still not enough, though.
Well then, how about we cut off the plushie's head,
and only buy half!
Are you really in high school?
You're an idiot, mister...
Reserved
Don't worry, it'll be okay for now.
But, without the money...
That's true...
Twenty-five thousand, huh?
That's just about what all of the stuff that was
confiscated from me this morning was worth.
That's it!
What is it?
Hazuki-chan, meet me back here at the park tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes.
Got it.
All right!
Getting your stuff back?!
Yeah.
I'm gonna need your help too, guys.
Then you're gonna need to get the key to Iron Man's locker.
The key'll be in Iron Man's coat pocket.
In that case...
Why don't you just throw a bucket of water on Iron Man,
and then take the key from him while he's changing?
Yep, that'll do it. Good luck, Akihisa.
Me?
He's coming!
Don't mess it up!
Hurry!
Aren't you guys gonna help me at all?
In that case...
Sorry, I slipped!
What?!
Like hell I'm going to let you escape!
I'm sorry, I slipp-
I could swear that I heard something about "not letting me escape"...
It sure wasn't easy... but here's the key.
Good!  Let's open up Iron Man's locker while we still can.
Confiscated stuff
Found it!
All right. Let's get out of here, then.
Okay.
Huh? Old books?
Well, if they're just trash anyway...
That was a close one.
Without those old books I wouldn't have had the full twenty-five thousand yen.
Hey, Mr. Idiot!
Sorry I'm late.
No problem.
Hey, that's...
Um...
Before you got here, a pretty lady came over to me.
Pretty lady?
Yes!
"Please take this plushie and give it to your sister.
But if that boy comes and brings the big plushie, then please keep this one for yourself."
...is what she said to me.
So this one is yours then, Hazuki-chan.
Mine?
Yep.
And also, take this one... and give it to your sister.
The plushie!
I hope that it cheers your sister up.
Um... mister?
Could you bend down for me, please?
Like this?
Thanks, mister!
You know... you might be an idiot,
but you're really nice, so I love you.
When I grow up, we're going to get married!
Yesterday, an unfortunate incident occurred.
Problem
All of the confiscated items, along with a few old books that belonged to me, were taken by someone.
And that person actually had the nerve to use their own student ID when selling everything.
What do you think about that, Yoshii?
Takes real guts, doesn't it?
Absolutely.
AHAHAHAHA!
Yoshii, stop laughing!
Sorry! There were extenuating...
Yoshii, I'm going to present you with a title worthy of your stupidity.
Please accept this.
Yoshii Akihisa, from today forward you are...
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
the Punishment Inspector!
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Punishment
Inspector
Reflect upon
your actions
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Here you go, sis!
This is...
Does this make you feel better?
Thank you, Hazuki.
I feel so much better now!
Speaking Japanese is hard, and there are other issues as well, but...
Yeah! We can do our best, together!
And also...
And also?
I've just met a guy that I'm kind of...
Interested in...
Huh? What's he like?
He's a guy in my class...
And he's a huge idiot!
【Question 4】
Answer the following
question.
What is the sum of all the
numbers on a set of
52 playing cards?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
『364』
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done as always, Himeji.
There are several ways to calculate this.
For example, if you laid out and matched
up each of the 13 Spades from 1 to 13,
with the Hearts from 13-1, you would have
13 pairs that each add up to 14.
The same is true of the Diamonds and Clubs,
so you have 14x13x2 = 364.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
Teacher's comment:
Next Episode
Question #4...
What is the sum of all the numbers on a set of 52 playing cards?
『1 plus 2 plus 3 plus...』
1 plus 2 plus 3 plus...
Good luck with that.
『1 plus 2 plus 3 plus...』
Next episode!
"Me and True Intentions and a Man's Dignity!"
Me and True Intentions and
a Man's Dignity!
This will be on your test.