A sudden incident has befallen me,
Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
Feelings that miss each other,
words that don't link together...
Is fighting the only thing that I
can do to link them together?
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
I'm sure it all started
from one coincidence.
But many coincidences
overlap each other.
I was choosing my path, being
careful not to make mistakes.
I think that's how everyone
spends their days.
The current days of my life may
have begun just by coincidence.
That's why I want to keep moving
ahead, without making any mistakes.
By my own will, according
to my own feelings.
Episode 5: This is a Town of Hot Water,
Uminari Hot Springs!
Okay!
It's vacation season all over Japan!
Café Midoriya is always open,
but during vacation season,
sometimes we entrust the
café to the employees
and go off on small family vacations.
This time, we're on a trip
with all of my friends.
My big brother, his girlfriend
Shinobu Tsukimura,
and the maids from the Tsukimura
family, are with us as well.
For two nights we'll be soaking
in hot springs, close to home.
The usual Takamachi vacation plan,
to ease the fatigue of everyday life.
Look, look, so much green!
You're so right!
It's just like the gardens in my house!
Nanoha!
You have to unwind during
a vacation, if nowhere else!
I know that.
It's okay!
That mage in black
that I met last week...
And not having been able to find
any Jewel Seeds since then...
I've been thinking
too much about them,
so Yuuno recommended that I
should take time off and rest a bit.
So big!
At least for the next two days,
I'm going to act like
all the other kids my age.
I'm planning to play as much as I can!
Ladies’ Bath
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Shall we go?
Have you ever soaked
in a hot spring, Yuuno?
Uh... Well... I've been to
a public bath before, but...
Hot springs are wonderful!
Really?
Nanoha!
I think, after all...
I think I'll go to the men's bath
with Kyouya and Shiro.
It's okay! Let's go in together!
Fantastic!
Amazing! It's so spacious!
It is amazing!
Really!
Sis, let me wash your back!
Thank you, Suzuka.
Then I will too!
Thanks.
Then I'll give you a wash!
No need to worry!
I'm really good at washing things!
Holidays like this are so nice.
Yeah, you're right.
o Tt e L ungsters
And our kids are all so full of energy.
And you too.
Yes, I guess I am.
It took quite a while.
I'm sure I won't be worrying you
or our kids anymore, Momoko.
Right, from now on, Midoriya's
owner is what I'll always be.
Yes. Thank you, honey.
Here you go.
Thanks.
But Noel, you're not on duty today,
so you can relax, you know?
Right, I am relaxing right now!
Then, big sister, Miss Shinobu,
we're going to go on ahead!
Okay!
I'm going to go roam around the inn
a bit with Nanoha and the others!
Okay. See you later.
Now, let's go, Yuuno!
That really felt good!
Since we've washed off the sweat,
shall we play some ping-pong?
Ping-pong?
Oh, I wanted to go see
what souvenirs they had.
What should we do?
Which should we do first?
Why not play
paper-rock-scissors to decide?
Hi, kiddies!
Are you the one that did the
you-know-what to my girl?
You don't look too smart or strong.
You look like an ordinary kid.
Nanoha, do you know her?
No.
It seems she doesn't know you.
Who are you?!
Uh-huh...
Sorry, sorry!
I guess I was thinking
of the wrong person.
You really look like a girl I know.
Oh, I see, that's what it was.
That's such a cute ferret!
Yes!
There, there! Pet, pet!
For now, I'm just going to say hello.
Let me warn you.
Kids should behave themselves
and play at home!
If you're being a bad girl,
you'll get bitten, got that?
Well then, I think I'll
go take another bath!
Nanoha...
Yeah.
Yeah?
What was that?
Well... That was a really
strange person.
Is she drunk this early in the day?!
She's creepy!
Arisa...
Now, now, this is a place to relax,
so there's all sorts of people here!
But you should know how
to be modest! Modesty, I say!
Oh, hello, Fate?
This is Aruf.
I went and took a look
at that girl in white.
I see. How was she?
Well, she's not much of anything.
She's no match for you, Fate.
I see. I've gotten a small lead too.
I've determined the general
location of the next Jewel Seed.
I think we'll be able
to capture it tonight.
Nice going, Fate!
Nothing less from my master!
Thanks, Aruf.
Let's meet up again tonight.
Sure!
Relax, relax!
Whoops.
Oh, no!
You think this will be fine?
And they lived happily ever after.
Oh, Falin. Are all the kids
asleep already?
Yes, Mrs. Momoko.
They're sound asleep.
Thank you, Falin.
No, it's something I'm doing
because I want to.
Yuuno, are you awake?
Yeah.
That woman from this afternoon...
Does she have something to do
with that girl from the other day?
Probably.
Are things going to end up like
what happened the other day?
Probably...
Nanoha, you know, I've thought
about it since that day.
And I think, after all, I should...
Stop!
If you finish that sentence,
I'll get mad!
You were going to say, "I should
do the rest from here by myself."
"I can't get you involved in this
any further, Nanoha," right?
Yeah.
Collecting the Jewel Seeds...
At first I was just
helping you out, Yuuno.
But now it's different.
It's something that I'm doing
because I want to do it.
If you tell me you want to leave
me behind and do it by yourself,
I'll get mad at you.
Yeah.
Let's get some sleep.
There might be something
going on again tonight.
Yeah...
Bingo!
I've found it, Fate!
Nanoha...
It's all right! Let's hurry, Yuuno!
Raging Heart, please!
Stand by ready. Set up.
Wow, this is an amazing one!
Is this what you call the power
of the Lost Logia?
Though its condition is very
incomplete and unstable, yes.
Why does your mom want
something like that, anyway?
Who knows?
I have no idea, but the
reason doesn't matter.
Mother wants them,
so I need to obtain them.
Bardiche, wake up.
Yes, sir.
Sealing form, set up.
I'm going to seal it. Aruf, back me up.
Sure thing.
That's...
That's two.
Oh, my, my, my!
Didn't I tell you that
kids should behave?
What are you going to do
with that Jewel Seed?!
It's a dangerous item!
Who knows?
I don't see any reason to answer that.
Besides, I was nice
and told you, right?
That if you didn't behave,
you'll get bitten!
Just as I thought!
She's that girl's familiar!
A familiar?
That's right, I'm a magical
lifeform that this girl created.
In return for living on through
the creator's magical powers,
I use my life and all my
power to protect her!
Go home ahead of me.
I'll catch up to you soon.
Don't be reckless.
Okay!
Nanoha, please go after the girl!
You think I'd allow that to happen?
I'll make sure it happens!
Transportation magic?! Not good!
A barrier, and a forced transfer spell...
You have a good familiar with you.
Yuuno isn't what you call a familiar!
He's a dear friend of mine!
Well, what are you going to do?
Isn't there a way that we can
somehow talk this out?
I must collect the shards of the
Lost Logia, the Jewel Seeds.
And if you have the
same objective as I do,
then we are enemies, who must fight
over the Jewel Seeds as a prize.
That's why!
So that we don't quickly
jump to that conclusion,
I think we need to talk
everything out first!
Just talking it out...
I'm sure mere words
won't change anything.
You wouldn't get it!
Flier Fin.
But that doesn't mean that...
Let's make a bet.
We'll each stake one Jewel Seed.
Photon Lancer, get set.
Don't just scurry and sneak away!
What is a mage powerful enough
to create a familiar
doing in this world?!
And what does she know about the
Jewel Seeds... the Lost Logia?!
Stop babbling!
Thunder Smasher.
Divine Buster.
Please, Raging Heart!
All right.
Nanoha is powerful!
But she's too soft.
Scythe Slash.
Nanoha!
Put out.
Raging Heart, what are you doing?!
I'm sure it's a good one that
cares greatly for its master.
Let's go home, Aruf.
Nothing less from my master!
See you later, kiddo!
Wait!
If it's at all possible,
never appear before us again.
If there's a next time, I might
not be able to stop myself.
Your name...
What is your name?
Fate.
Fate Testarossa.
Um... I'm...
Bye-bye!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of
cellophane and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying
inside a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining on
the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something I
can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Nanoha is hiding something from us.
We can't do anything about that.
There are things that you can't
tell even your friends about.
The events of the past
are coming to light.
What are the destinies
of the two magical girls
that meet one another once again?!
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode é:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode é:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Episode 6: Feelings That
Can't Be Understood?
Episode é:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?
Lyrical, magical, in hopes
that I can reach...
Episode é:
Feelings That Can't Be Understood?