Good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
I'll keep this as a member of the Dollars.
Hey, haven't you gotten a bit cocky ever since Harima Mika disappeared?
How is it possible for her to die?
Did you hear about it?
There was another slasher incident in Ikebukuro.
Then maybe I'll start a war that only I can fight.
Right?
Enough is enough!
Come one, come all!
We have Russian sushi!
It's yummy! It's cheap!
Come eat sushi.
"Slasher"?
It appeared again.
How many did it get?
I'm standing at the location of last night's slasher incident.
A large meeting had been abruptly called in Ikebukuro's business district.
The slasher incident also began around that time.
Young people are talking about a legendary "headless rider"...
American organizations are contacting the headless rider to determine the technologies used—
The slasher?
The headless rider...
So scary...
Every day, something new appears, and something else disappears.
No way!
Yet nothing happens.
Nothing changes.
That's her normal life.
Our love is completely fake.
But it's stronger than real love.
I'm in love with the scar on your neck.
And this love is connected to a real one through this scar.
I love you.
I will love all of you with all of myself!
Looking at them fills me with envy.
Then stop looking.
We look if we see a pretty girl!
And then we go talk to her!
That's our destiny as members of Team Boys, since it's engraved in our DNA!
Don't group me with you.
But don't worry.
My body belongs to everyone,
while my heart belongs only to you, Anri.
I've always wondered...
Why are you so erotic and cute?
Not erotic, Masaomi!
I see.
You don't see her as erotic, but you do agree on the cute part.
Well, um...
Are you saying Anri isn't cute?
Sh-She is!
She is, but...
Ah ha! So you do admit that she's cute.
But I also admit that she's erotic.
So I understand and love her more, since I love the erotic part too.
Thus, I win!
Six months ago, there was an incident.
Everyone in town and at school talked about it then.
But it has nothing to do with her.
She's not interested in it.
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah. Thanks.
Nothing happens.
And nothing changes.
That's her normal life.
Thank god we had enough points saved up!
Hurry up.
Yumacchi, whatcha gonna do with that poster?
She's going pretty fast today.
Isn't she driving around more boldly than ever?
Yeah.
I wish someone like her was more secretive.
It'd be much better if only we knew the truth, like a lady's secret.
That must be like Nogizaka Haruka's "Secret."
Guys...
Don't blame her.
She must have her reasons.
Hey, check it out!
It's the headless rider!
This is Celty Sturluson's normal life.
This is an everyday occurrence.
People panic when they face an extraordinary situation.
She flees from the scene using that.
That's how Celty Sturluson usually handles such situations.
However...
I've always thought...
In movies and comics with monsters like you, we're always the dying pawns.
When a superhero appears,
we're always the dead bodies lying in pools of water to show how strong the monster is.
But that's fine.
It means that we're normally considered pretty strong.
It's an unavoidable part of the plot.
But I've always wanted to tell your kind...
If a monster, evil telekinetic, android, or ninja makes their appearance...
Just one thing...
I only have one thing to say to you:
Don't take the traffic police unit lightly, you fucking monster.
Let me say it again, you damn monster.
Don't take the traffic police unit lightly.
Celty!
Welcome hom—
What? What's going on?
Getting hugged by you makes me feel like the Supreme Being.
Wait, I didn't say that quite right.
Hey, you're shivering.
Seriously, what's going on, Celty?
I-It was scary.
So scary, Shinra!
Th-The police these days are like monsters!
The police?
About ten police bikes and cruisers were chasing me like they were a single living organism!
Actually, I remember hearing about this biker cop being transfered here just to deal with you.
I think his name is Kuzuhara Kinnosuke.
He's a troublemaker who forces the target into an accident.
It was scary.
So scary.
I've been too conceited.
I'll be more modest from now on, so please forgive me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Who are you apologizing to?
This isn't like you at all.
You should only show your feminine side in bed—
Stop saying embarrassing things in this situation.
Yeah, that's it.
A-Anyway, I know you've been through a lot,
but can you go pick someone up?
It's not a job.
He's back...
My dad, that is.
Seriously, he should catch a taxi.
He's always picked on me.
Hey man.
Come on.
Say something.
You're so white.
Don't tell me...
What the fuck's wrong with him?
You like his dress, Horada-san?
Gentlemen, Tokyo's air is ugly.
Don't you agree?
Actually, your ugly faces are perfect as camouflage in this ugly air.
Hey, this dude's got a screw loose somewhere.
Who cares?
Looks like it's time to show you the power of grown ups.
You must think that because you're protected by the Juvenile Law, you can kill anyone anytime.
But remember this:
When you try to kill someone, you better be prepared for the possibility of being killed by your targ—
You're fucking crazy, man.
I'm over twenty.
Hold on a minute.
That seriously hurts.
And you're stepping on my shoe, so I can't flee.
The finger's stabbing me!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Don't just stand and watch, Celty-kun!
Come on, save me!
I don't want to...
Don't you realize that I acted tough because I saw you and thought that there wasn't anything to worry about?!
Hey, Horada-san, this is the black biker dude.
What? You serious, Higa?
Dead serious. I saw it on TV.
I heard you were at the Dollars' meeting six months ago.
Man, you're all trying to take away our area.
Come on, say something.
What the hell's this?!
W-W-Wait up!
Yeah, this is how people are supposed to react.
Good, it's not broken.
This is a precious device that Shinra gave me.
Take that!
This is the power of grown-ups!
I just can't grow to like him.
Is this really good for anything?
And seriously, how are you supposed to play like this?
Russian sushi! Russian sushi!
President!
Hey, Izaya!
Hey, working hard as usual?
You've been around Ikebukuro a lot lately.
Why don't you stop by my place?
I just opened a fresh can of fish.
It's still fresh.
Sorry, but I'm actually kinda busy.
I'll stop by some other time.
Hey.
You can't hide a gimlet in a bag.
Don't talk about ropes in a house where a man hung himself.
Right?
Let's take turns and list what's good about Anri.
I'll start.
She's erotic.
You're starting with that?
Let's stay away from that topic.
Those who underestimate sex will cry about sex.
Start making more sense.
This was her first time being friends with guys.
Then, Mikado, say something good about Anri.
Well, I think...
More accurately,
"There is nothing good about Anri. Bleh." Right?
she probably had never been friends with anyone before this.
I didn't say that!
Then say it.
Say it now.
Come on, say it.
W-Well, um...
Once, she was merely someone who enhanced Harima Mika's presence.
3, 2, 1... Bzzt! You lose!
But it was fine with her.
That was where she belonged.
But...
now that she'd lost that place,
she was unable to find where she stood.
Fine.
Let's all go hit on some chicks so I can prove how ero-cute Anri is.
What kind of excuse is that?
B-But... hit on girls?
Don't you worry.
You're just bait to make them to relax by thinking, "He's with another girl, so he should be safe."
You don't need to do anything.
Hold on, Masaomi!
Let's go!
Follow me, gang!
Ready, set, go!
Here I come!
K-Kida-kun?
Masaomi!
Was that really okay?
It's fine.
He'll go hit on girls anyway, even if we don't tag along.
Seriously.
He's such a handful.
I need to give Mr. Shy at least this much handicap.
I'm such a badass.
Hey...
She was aware that the two boys had feelings for her.
But...
Oh, it's a pretty sunset.
But there's an ominous-looking cloud over there.
It might rain later, so let's be careful.
Yes, we should.
Um...
Yes?
I'll excuse myself here.
See you tomorrow.
Y-Yeah, see ya.
Using the sunset was way too cheesy.
She probably couldn't give a reply if either one of them confessed his love to her.
She still liked Harima Mika, even to this day.
And she liked those two just as much.
She wasn't aware of the difference between friendly love and romantic love.
To her, Harima Mika is...
Ryugamine Mikado is...
Kida Masaomi is...
You really won't?
We're really not the same without you.
I already told you, I have nothing to do with you anymore.
I don't belong here.
I have zero desire to return to that life.
I've been seeing more yellow people recently.
Yellow?
I know.
And because they're very visible, they stand out more than the Dollars.
Oh, you mean the Yellow Napkins?
You know about them too, Setton?
Well, yeah...
They've been around for a while.
Yellow Napkins?
They're the gang that used to hang around Ikebukuro before.
They went missing after they had a fight with another gang.
Oh yeah, I heard about that.
Does this mean they're back?
Ikebukuro is getting to be pretty scary.
I know.
The police are scary too.
Seriously.
Please don't take the police lightly.
The police?
Shit, she's on her knees.
So lame.
We only tapped you.
You're so clumsy.
Because you're a parasite.
What are you looking at?
And the slasher incident still isn't resolved.
By the way, have you heard...
that the slasher is actually the work of the Dollars?
There's also a rumor that it's the headless rider.
What?! Who said?!
I really doubt it.
All joking aside,
you should really be careful about the Yellow Napkins.
Some members hold a grudge against the Dollars for getting big while they were gone.
I see...
All right, I'll be careful.
You whore.
You're going after Ryugamine and Kida after getting dumped by Harima.
And now Nasujima.
How many more people are you gonna whore out to?
Dating whore.
You're always depending on someone.
Parasite!
Parasite! Parasite!
The girl knew that their accusations were true.
She was dependent on Harima Mika.
And she probably still is.
Don't just sit there!
Say something.
Or is a parasite unable to even speak?
Or maybe she's depending on those two boys.
Like trying to find her place among them.
You fucking stink, parasite.
Stop coming to school.
We've already lost two boyfriends because of you!
Don't just sit there, bitch!
And like this, she's been protecting her own body and mind.
Nothing will happen.
Nothing will change.
This is her normal life.
You live around here, don't you?
Let's see it.
We'll check it out.
Come on, show us.
Here he is!
Oh.
Huh?
I'm the one who wants to slash!
He's the one who's been spamming Ikebukuro-related BBS and channels since about six months ago, right?
You haven't banned him?
I did!
But it never works!
Oh, I see.
I ban him by remote host name, but he just joins from another one.
Is he using a proxy?
I don't think he is.
That's kinda creepy.
Nothing will happen.
Nothing will change.
That's her...
There's a slasher somewhere in this town.
And each time there's an incident,
the fear and anxiety creates countless rumors in the heavy, stagnant breeze of the night.
But...
Next time: Reigning Turmoil.