< sign : Incinerator >
- Angel area}
- Connecting Corridor}
<sign: Study Block A - Classroom >
< sign: Study Block A - Stairway >
< sign: Gymnasium >
< sign: Library >
< sign: PC Room 1 >
< sign: Library Interior - PC Room 1 >
< preview >
Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
It's time, huh...
I'd better head over there.
Now then, who should be next?
Study Block - Inner Garden
I guess I'll see what Kanade thinks.
Yo.
Hinata!
Otonashi-san.
Naoi?
What are you doing here?
Same to you, where did you crawl out from?
So... did you two have some business with me?
Oh that's right! Where are you going, Otonashi?
It doesn't matter where he's going!
This has nothing to do with you!
I have to talk to Otonashi so I can help out with what he's trying to do!
That should be my role.
You're just in the way.
Hurry up and vanish.
Now, look into my eyes.
You are toilet paper.
You will realize the splendor of how easily toilet paper is flushed—
Hey, stop it!
Hey, Hinata!
Please allow me to assist you!
Do you guys understand what I'm trying to do?
I understand.
Of course I understand.
You're erasing everyone one by one, right?
It sounds evil when you say it...
Anyway Naoi, shouldn't you be free of regrets at this point?
I want to be together with you!
And I don't want to disappear before this guy.
Don't stay for such a petty reason!
Then what should I do?
Disappear.
I wasn't asking you.
Come on Otonashi-san, you need a partner, don't you?
Make use of me, Otonashi-san!
Is something wrong?
What...
Did you do something again?
What are you talking about?
I haven't done anyth—
What the hell is that?!
An enemy? Do we shoot it??
It's entering me...
Something is entering me!
Otonashi-san!
Dammit!
Hinata!
Will this thing even die?!
Did we get it?
What was that?
Hinata-san and Otonashi-san confronted and defeated a second one.
Nobody was harmed.
So a second one appeared...
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
The natural assumption is that this is some new skill Angel came up with, but...
Something doesn't feel right?
Yeah...
Relay this to all Battlefront members.
Henceforth, it is forbidden to move solo.
Stay in groups of at least two.
We'll treat the shadow as a separate enemy from Angel.
Be sure to stay on full alert at all times.
Acknowledged.
What now, Yurippe-san?
"Yurippe-san" will think through all the possibilities.
Student Council President Tachibana Kanade-san,
Incinerator
please come to the student council office immediately.
Isn't that Yurippe's voice?
I repeat...
What's going on?
This is bad, she might find out about what we're doing.
That would be bad.
Let's go!
Yeah.
Student Council Office
Why are you guys here?
Allow us to sit in on this.
As the former acting student council president and current vice-president, I gave him permission.
How is this your jurisdiction?
This is the student council office.
Well whatever.
So what's with this shadow?
I don't know anything.
Didn't you program it?
No.
Then there's a chance it's a bug.
When did you last write a program?
The day before yesterday.
The timing fits...
We'll be intruding on your room, is that okay?
I'm leaving it to you, Takeyama-kun.
Understood.
And call me Chri—
So, what kind of program was it?
Wings.
Wings?
You added wings?
So you can fly?
No, it's a decoration.
A decoration?
Yes, a decoration.
Why?
I was told it would be more angel-like.
You were told?
By who?
This is bad...
That was me.
I believed it would give her more impact as the president,
so in my position as the former acting president and current vice-president, I made the suggestion to her.
If the student council president had wings, she'd have more impact?
Correct.
I believed that for the president,
wings
would be suitable.
Idiot.
You're surprisingly obedient though.
I don't sense one bit of cruelty in you.
You seem like the way you always were.
No, she is cruel.
As the vice-president, I get stabbed everyday.
Er... why?
When she's in a bad mood, she stabs anyone nearby.
In my position as vice-president, I am often near her, so I get stabbed quite a lot.
Just this morning, she stabbed me till my guts were hanging out.
Though, it appears she's in a very good mood right now.
Idiot.
Can you hear me?
Please respond.
Takeyama-kun? How was it?
Girl's Dormitary - Angel Area
I couldn't find any bugs.
I looked into the most recent program, but it's a simple decorative program.
There's no way a bug that might have its own will and attacks people could come from this.
And call me Chri—
What about the other programs?
Passive, Overdrive, Active, and Hand Sonic.
They're all programs from before, though there are minor changes to them.
What should I do?
Is she going to make him erase them?
We'd have to start from fresh...
Hey, did you just hear gunfire?
What are you talking about? What gunfire?
From outside!
Look, over there!
Those monsters!
Why are there so many?
Kanade, go!
Yurippe!
Wow...
I'm going too!
Hey!!
Otonashi-san!
Are you okay Yuri?
Otonashi-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Bow before me!
I don't need backup!
Come on, don't say that.
How shallow-minded.
Woah! Dancing in the shadow!
I kiss you.
I wouldn't want to be on the receiving end of that...
Hey, are you trying to cut your own team?!
It's in the plan.
Don't put that in the plan! Leave it out!
Stop messing about and help out!
That was...
Is everyone alright?
What were those? Monsters?
What were those creepy things?
They weren't in this world before.
Is this a nightmare?
It's a carnival and everyone's invited.
Did we stay in this world for too long?
What do you mean?
You get this in games, don't you?
Invincible monsters that appear to prevent infinite play time.
That's not funny.
Seriously though...
She's just like an ally.
Hey! hey!!
Fujimaki!
This is bad...
Takamatsu...
Takamatsu got done in!
His glasses...
Study Block - Connecting Corridor
I saw it...
I saw that shadow eating him!
Eating?
When I ran into him, his whole body was already covered by the shadow...
I tried to save him!
But I couldn't do anything!
In the end, his glasses fell off...
For him to leave behind his glasses...
This is serious.
And then?
The ground absorbed him.
The ground?
This is too irregular.
What is this...
Some other will besides ours is at work here.
What on earth's happening?
Takamatsu's here!
Takamatsu!
Study Block A - Classroom
What do you think you're doing?
Everyone was worried about you!
Worried?
About what?
"About what"?
You were eaten by the shadow, weren't you?
I don't understand what you're talking about...
You didn't realize it?
A shadow ate you!
And then you were swallowed by the ground.
What happened after that?
I'm not sure what you mean...
I woke up in the dorms and headed to school as usual.
To school?
You put on that uniform and came here to attend classes?
Well, yes...
You're going to disappear! Don't you get that?
Disappear?
What will?
This looks bad.
He's become strange.
Well, he was always strange, but...
Takamatsu...
That's enough, Hinata-kun.
What do you mean "enough"?
I'm sorry, but you're interfering with my class.
Let's go.
We're just going to leave him?
He'll disappear!!
I said let's go.
Oyama-kun!
That conversation just now was enough.
Study Block A - Stairway
I know what's happening now.
He...
...has become an NPC.
W-Wait a second...
How could that be?
I don't get it at all!
By NPC, you mean he doesn't have a soul?
Then where did his soul go?
It was eaten.
What do you mean by that?
Are you saying he can't disappear anymore, and is doomed to take classes for eternity?
That's how it is.
No way...
That's worse than death...
To be stuck in this place for eternity...
What the hell's that?!
Dammit!
That's terrible...
So this kind of thing is possible in this world...
Being erased by Angel would be better than that.
On top of that, it seems that the shadows are multiplying.
What are we supposed to do now?
Yurippe!
Gymnasium
This world is developing an abnormality —
the arrival of an opponent other than Angel.
It's not very imaginative, but we're calling it "shadow".
Unlike Angel, it appears and vanishes without warning, and attacks indiscriminately.
Anyone who gets eaten by the shadow loses their soul and turns into a normal NPC who attends classes.
It is currently multiplying in unlimited numbers.
Its origin is unknown,
and we don't have any countermeasures.
As I had Yusa-san broadcast, the only way to defend ourselves is to move as a group.
Now, even while we face this danger,
some individuals within the Afterlife Battlefront have formed new ideals and are trying to take us in a new direction.
That path could be a viable choice to avoid the danger we are currently facing.
Therefore, as their representative, Otonashi-kun...
Can we hear your point of view on that, straight up in front of everyone here?
Seems she found out.
Go.
Don't screw with us!
How can you say that?!
There’s no way it can be that convenient!
Yeah!
Like hell there’s a choice like that in this world!
There is.
Yui found it.
Even someone like me, who died like human trash...
Even I was able to grant that to her.
Me too.
I may be God,
but even so, Otonashi restored my human soul.
Just by saying one thing to me...
by encouraging me.
It is up to each one of you which road you take.
What about you?
What'll you do, Yurippe?
Me?
I'm always doing my own thing.
I won't be protecting you guys.
I just do whatever I want.
Time is running out.
Think carefully about it for yourself.
That's all.
Dismissed!
Got a moment?
What is it, Yuri?
Get her to intercept the shadow.
Kanade?
Why?
She's more useful fighting without thinking, rather than pondering over a plan.
From what I've seen, anyway.
You were watching us?
I guess we can’t fool Yurippe.
But Kanade's our friend.
We should do it together.
The other members are also your companions.
To protect them, we'll need her power...
That overwhelming power that she's been fighting against the Battlefront with for so long.
I guess only an angel can stand up to that thing.
She's not an angel, you know?
What?!
What was that?!
I said she's not an angel.
She's a human, like us.
Didn't you notice?
As God, I knew all along.
You're seriously disturbed...
Wait, you aren't an angel?
I'm not an angel.
I gave you the same answer when we first met.
They said you were an angel or something...
I'm not an angel.
It's true!
A lot's happened since then...
It's because of you guys!
So why is Kanade here?
She's the student council president, so why hasn't she disappeared?
She has a reason to be here, obviously.
I see...
So you're carrying some burden, just like us?
I guess we'll have to lift that off you too,
right?
So Yuri,
what'll you do now?
There's something I want to check.
You're going to fight the shadow?
Depending on how it turns out.
It's too dangerous alone!
There's no choice.
I gave everyone the freedom to choose what to do.
There are people who will follow you!
They need time to think.
It's an important decision.
That's... true.
When I return, if everyone's gone and safely left this world,
I'll assume you managed to send them all off.
But...
I'll wait for you!
Don't be dumb.
If you wait alone, the shadow will get you.
You need to get out of this world before that happens.
Don't worry about me.
No, we'll worry.
Hinata-kun...
What are you saying, all of a sudden?
Didn't we form this Battlefront together?
We've spent a long time here together,
so we'll leave together too.
I won't leave you here.
You're such an idiot, like always.
Nothing's going to be solved with emotional speeches.
An attack!
We're under attack!
Kanade-chan, I'm counting on you.
Hand Sonic, version 5.
Well, if we can, we'll meet again.
Yurippe!
What a terrible nickname.
But it might have been why everyone followed me.
Thank you.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
Alright! I guess this is the last one.
Christ of the Front Diary
Today's weather was good too.
It seems I've been in this world too long.
I've had a change of heart.
I repeat,
Today's weather was good too.
Tomorrow onwards I'm sure I'll get to see even clearer skies.
That transformation...
If it’s possible for NPCs to be reprogrammed, like Kanade does to herself...
That software must be being used to transform the NPCs and attack us.
And there must be a whole load of computers wherever that is.
There has to be a large number of computers wherever that is.
If that's the case, there can be only one place.
Library
PC Room 1
Library Interior - PC Room 1
Checkmate.
Put up your hands.
What did you checkmate?
Do you play chess?
This is the culprit?
So in this age of computers, people still play with those?
You have a good hobby for such a young person.
Wait!
Hmm? Me?
What were you doing?
Here?
Yes.
Setting up new computers.
What for?
They have good specs, so they get stolen.
When there's not enough we have to replace them.
Any leads on the culprit?
Nothing at this stage.
Is that all?
Thanks.
Sorry for stopping you.
There's no doubt about it.
The one stealing the computers is currently playing God of this world.
He's using the stolen computers to interfere with the NPCs.
But how do I catch him?
I don't have the time to relax and think.
Even now, the shadows are multiplying.
And these aren't exactly easy to just make off with.
Does he sneak in at night, put them on a cart, then take them out?
Or does he use a window?
Found you.
Wait...
No way...
Guild again?!
We're breaking through!
What's with this world?
"I wonder if we can surprise God"??
Because it doesn't seem anyone would notice if I disappeared!
Disappear!
Disappear like miserable toilet paper!
I only move to save Yurippe!
I'll also play in a band in the next life!
Think of it like it's gained the fighting strength of 100 people.
You've done well to reach here.
Give me your hand!
If I disappear now... can I start over?