WORLD DOMINATION
JOURNAL,
JOU EDOGAWA.
World Domination Journal, Jou Edogawa:
A perfect plot with absolutely
no loopholes was completed.
In order to carry out the plot,
I conducted the ceremony to summon
Kuzuryu, the nine-headed dragon.
That was when...
That was when night and morning switched
and also when she and I switched...
My name is Awashima-sama.
I'm the personality in charge of this body at night
when the divine spirit of Jou Edogawa sleeps.
I'm also one of the gods that was consumed by her once.
My body somehow grows a penis every now and then!
Oh, no! I should've made a better excuse than that.
It... grows somehow?
She believed me?
That's right! It grows...
It just comes out every now and then
but disappears before you know it!
So you're a girl, right, Edogawa?
That's right. Please don't tell that to anyone.
Okay.
It's a secret only between us.
Yeah. Thanks.
But it, um, isn't contagious, is it?
What?
I'm not going to get one, right?
You'll be fine!
It looks like I got away with it.
Year 1-Class Arahabaki
Tamamo-no-Mae
I think it was pretty suspicious.
Were you watching, Tamamo-no-Mae?
The way you talk is just
the male version of how Milady talks.
We'll switch again soon.
Jou is better at conducting the ceremony.
That's right. The sun has already risen, Awashima-sama!
What did you think you were doing?!
Sasami came so close to finding out about it!
There was nothing I could do about it.
I'll conduct the ceremony.
Wing Commander Garuda!
Garuda will be standing by on alert.
Tamamo-no-Mae, you set up the barrier
and keep people away.
Understood.
I HEREBY
I hereby commence the unified world domination
operation of Arahabaki, the evil occult society!
All is for my happiness.
In other words, all is for my personal desires!
Kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
At the fingertip of God
Watashi no kisetsu tachi
My seasons are made
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
It's much longer than the starry sky
Nemuri wo yusaburu uta
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
It felt like my existence got wiped out
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
Kokoro wo enjiru niwa
To play what's in my heart
Zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otonaja nai
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
Deatta kouya no hana
The flower that I found in the wilderness
Kowakute yasashikute
It's scary yet gentle
Fureta shunkan ni diorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta watashino miraichizu
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
Because the thousands of melodies echo
Oikakete kuru ashita wo kowasu
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
Nukumori ga mieta yo
I saw the warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
The bond that's born from the pain
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasamisan @
Ganbaranai
FINAL EPISODE                                      Ganbaranai
"I WON'T DO MY BEST TOMORROW, EITHER"
She says, "So can I call you 'Jou-chan'?"
That moment it caused me to have a slight expectation...
Big Sister Kagami...
I welcome you to the organization!
You'll be my servant and use your power for me!
Big Sister Kagami!
Hey, what's going on?
Big Sister Kagami... Big Sister Kagami!
Just explain what's going on!
You're going to be my servant, aren't you?
I'm really sorry, Edogawa!
I've got to go! I'll call you later!
Hey, wait up, Sasami!
I don't care! You don't have to come!
That's right. The expectation is to be betrayed...
Especially when it's coming from a human...
I was kinda looking forward
to going to the festival with you...
How come things don't go the way I want them to?
That's why I hate humans!
I hate them because I don't understand them!
It's pointless to interact with humans! I don't get them!
Milady, everything's prepared for the plot.
Fine. This is my destiny.
Even if it means solitude I'll still accept it
and keep going forward laughing!
The evil occult society Arahabaki
will launch an all-out attack!
Run!
I beat the old man! Can I get that thing?
But we have Meat at home! I can't have any more!
Why don't we keep it at Mama-lin's house?
TAMA, WAIT HERE.
Tama, wait here. I'll be right back.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
What's going on?
I'm sure it's nothing to worry about,
I'M SURE IT'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT,
BUT EXCUSE ME
FOR A MOMENT.
but excuse me for a moment.
Are you going to get that old man?
I don't think that's it.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S IT.
What? What is this?
Mama-lin! Help me!
MAMA-LIN! HELP ME!
Tama! Tama!
Tama has been drugged?
And I feel it, too?
Another lightning strike?
The shrine gates, the temple forests,
the roadside guardian shrines...
The giant trees and unique rocks...
Every single spiritual spot has been destroyed.
Those people who randomly popped up
in the chatroom earlier were suspicious too.
This could be serious...
What's the matter, Miss Tsurugi?
It's a barrier. We're locked in this island.
Hey, what are you doing?
The tide started to come in, so...
I'm no kid!
But I don't want to get my nice yukata wet, so...
I wanted to be alone with you and find out
exactly who you really are, but oh well...
Just for a little while...
Big Brother...
It's been a while, God of Flame Kagutsuchi!
Oops, I forgot that you're
Kagami Yagami right now.
My sister told me that she ran into you,
but who knew that you were still alive?
Wing Commander Garuda
is also very much alive and well!
I'm sure you're delighted to know that
as a former colleague.
So the evil occult society Arahabaki still exists!
The Iwakusa Sword on my right
and the Nekusa Sword on my left!
These are the godly embodiments of the sword
that struck down Kagutsuchi, the God of Flame!
Note: In myth, the fire god Kagutsuchi was struck down by his father
Izanagi for killing his mother Izanami in birth.
Indian irregular sword techniques,
Chinese strategic sword techniques
or Japanese ceremonial sword techniques...
Which do you like?
The most beautiful girl of
all three countries is going to kill you!
Good morning, Tama.
Edogawa?
Mama-lin? Where's Mama-lin? Mama-lin!
She's not responding!
This island has been completely sealed within a barrier.
You can no longer communicate with Sasami Tsukuyomi
from here in Amenonuboko.
Note: Amenonuboko is the primordial land mass created by the gods.
What are they doing?
The "other" festival. You're going to give me your hand.
This shrine's secret ceremony is the re-enactment of
the extermination of the nine-headed dragon Kuzuryu.
You play the role of the hero,
who came to defeat the evil dragon.
What?
The new god defeats the old.
Isn't that the perfect role for you?
New God Tama Yagami.
I'm a forgotten old god. The Prideful One, Arahabaki.
Isn't it perfect for the role of
the nine-headed dragon Kuzuryu?
Now, kill me with that sword!
No!
Come on! Kill me!
I won't!
Can't you do it?
Because that's... not... nice.
I'm saved because you're sweet and foolish.
The secret ceremony is the
reenactment of the past.
In other words, what takes place here
will actually take place in the past.
With the power of Tamamo-no-Mae,
we will mislead the world!
We will Alter history so that
Kuzuryu defeats the Yamato Dynasty!
Does it hurt? Is it painful?
You feel pain even though you're a god?
Why are you doing this to me?
I thought you were Mama-lin's friend!
Only the God Arahabaki is complete and mighty!
Arahabaki needs no family, no friend,
no subordinate! Nothing!
The secret ceremony is complete!
History will be Altered and Kuzuryu will seize victory!
As the present stands at the edge of history,
Kuzuryu will regain its true appearance!
Deny the eight million gods and their history!
Cast aside the eight million gods and their myths!
All is for my happiness.
In other words, all is for my personal desires!
Tama! Tama!
TAMA!
Mama-lin, you're back.
What happened to you, Tama?
This island has perished.
Listen. Tama has been consumed.
A very scary god has destroyed everything.
Don't cry, Tama.
DON'T CRY, TAMA.
At any rate we have to do something about this.
AT ANY RATE WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS...
You can't! It ate everything.
Don't give up, Tama! Please!
There's still something we can do.
That is true. I can still make use of you.
You are...
...Tamamo-no-Mae, she who toys with the balance!
YOU WERE TOO LATE,
SASAMI TSUKUYOMI.
You were too late, Sasami Tsukuyomi.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR
YOU TO CONTACT ME,
LEAVING THE WINDOW
OPEN IN THE BARRIER.
I've been waiting for you to contact me,
leaving the window open in the barrier.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
What have you done?
AS YOU CAN SEE, I
As you can see, I resurrected the old god
Kuzuryu and destroyed the island.
RESURRECTED THE OLD GOD
KUZURYU AND DESTROYED
THE ISLAND.
We'll declare war against the world as we turn
the enormous strength of Kuzuryu into a weapon.
WE'LL DECLARE WAR AGAINST
THE WORLD AS WE TURN THE
ENORMOUS STRENGTH OF
KUZURYU INTO A WEAPON.
No way...
NO WAY...
You should be proud, Sasami Tsukuyomi!
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD,
SASAMI TSUKUYOMI!
My Master highly appreciates you and
appoints you the priestess of the new world,
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD,
SASAMI TSUKUYOMI!
MY MASTER HIGHLY
APPRECIATES YOU AND
THE PRIESTESS OF THE NEW WORLD
in other words, the ruler of this humanity!
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD,
SASAMI TSUKUYOMI!
IN OTHER WORDS...
THE RULER OF THIS HUMANITY
What?
An infiltration is considered a failure
if you completely wipe everything out.
AN INFILTRATION IS
CONSIDERED A FAILURE
IF YOU COMPLETELY
WIPE EVERYTHING OUT.
Humanity is a precious resource.
HUMANITY IS A
PRECIOUS RESOURCE
TO UTILIZE THAT RESOURCE
WE NEED A PRIESTESS WHO
CAN MEDIATE...
To utilize that resource we need a priestess who
can mediate between the humans and the gods.
PRIESTESS
Don't listen to her.
They're bad people.
THEY'RE BAD PEOPLE...
They're going to trick you...
THEY'RE GOING TO TRICK YOU...
I'm making a concession.
I'M MAKING A
CONCESSION.
IF I UNLEASH THE ENERGY
OF KUZURYU, I COULD
If I unleash the energy of Kuzuryu, I could easily
vaporize this Amenonuboko instantly.
EASILY VAPORIZE THIS
AMENONUBOKO INSTANTLY.
Can I trust you?
CAN I TRUST YOU?
Of course.
OF COURSE.
We lost.
We couldn't stop you and many innocents
were dragged into it along the way.
It's pointless to fight until everything's wiped out
completely. So if you say you need me...
Mama-lin!
Then you must swear here. To the god!
Say, "I, Sasami Tsukuyomi, will
become the priestess of Arahabaki"!
To the god?
An oath to the god is absolute. Nothing will change that.
If you're willing to go that far
I can finally trust you.
Mama-lin, no!
It's okay, Tama. It's okay...
No way...
Because I just...
BECAUSE I JUST...
...finished buying time!
What did you just say?
You should never let your guard down,
Tamamo-no-Mae!
This is impossible! I thought I killed you!
That sword was my nemesis.
I figured I had no chance against it,
so I pretended to be dead.
You were pretending?! You fooled me, a fox?
I'm a spiritual robot with a divine spirit.
If I am ever defeated, all I have to do
is to find a new body. That's all.
That's why you're inside this Killing Stone Golem?
I'm sorry, everyone. I've kept
something secret from you all.
I'M SORRY, EVERYONE.
Mama-lin...
I wanted to join you guys as soon as I got over this cold.
So I transferred my entire house into Tama's body
and came here with her body.
Basically I've been controlling Tama from inside,
using this house as a cockpit.
You mean to tell me you've been inside the barrier
on this island this whole time?
My senses were a little off at first,
though, because of the medicine I took.
But I stepped outside and got to enjoy
a hot spring bath with Edogawa.
You thought you defeated the three sisters,
and opened a hole in the barrier in order
to communicate with me on the outside.
That was your mistake! I'm sure Tsurugi is out
of the barrier and plotting her strategy by now.
They're alive? I must contact Milady!
You think we'll let you go?
Burn it to the core, Flame Emperor Ikazuchi!
Now I'm the one who owns this body.
Are you okay, Tama?
Big Sister Kagami! Kagami!
Tama...
THAT HURTS!
It's no time to be laid back.
First things first, let's do something
about this strange space.
I'm going to use the Eight Hands Mirror, Yata no Kagami.
Tama, you must defend yourself.
O human world... be restored to the way it should be!
Ouch...
I didn't know this was a desert island...
It looked like the world had perished,
but was it just an illusion?
It seems that Kuzuryu didn't resurrect
completely for some reason.
If it was just an illusion, everyone may still
be alive and well... Edogawa, too...
Is that my sister?
You know what?
I only came here to check on things,
so why am I running errands for you?
Note: This is Susano-o, Amaterasu's brother and rival.
Kuzuryu was resurrected because you failed
to keep the lid of the Underworld sealed properly!
Hey, in Japan an island
is identified with a god, right?
Yes. A god could become an island
and an island could become a god.
So that means, this island, too...
That is Kuzuryu.
Haven't seen one this big since Yamata no Orochi!
Bring punishment from Heaven, Amenohabakiri!
You idiot!
Why don't you hold back a little, Moron?!
Sasami and the others are on the island!
I'm sorry...
What?
I couldn't visit the festival with you.
I'm not worried about stuff like that.
I'm sorry.
Suddenly I felt scared.
Scared?
Once I acquired everything and became
the supreme being in this world...
I wouldn't be able to take trips
or laugh or eat with everyone.
I'd be alone...
I know that's expected,
and I even wanted it that way, but...
I understand. It's scary to be alone.
How could you possibly know what I'm talking about?
Ever since I was little, I'd worked so hard,
so very, very hard,
trying to meet everyone's high expectations
as the head of the organization, but...
You're right. Maybe I don't know anything...
But things could be so much easier if you just run away.
One day I will kill you.
Then we'll be friends until that one day comes.
You are so weird.
You're so stubborn, Jou-chan!
I'll get some sleep until help gets here. I feel exhausted.
Okay. Me too.
Sniff, sniff. I can smell Sasami from over there.
Seriously?
My spiritual powers are worn out right now,
so his sense of smell is the only thing we can rely on.
Papa-lin! Move forward at full-speed!
Sasami, I'm coming for you right now!
I understand that the situation was extremely desperate,
but I'm still shocked how they ruined themselves.
Especially the depths to which Ruza fell;
simply unacceptable.
I can't argue that.
It is absolutely foolish to look away
from your duty and lead a life of leisure.
I'm going to straighten that out!
Of course.
But...
You're cute when you're jealous!
We're not going to do our best today.
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
Mata ashita ne
See you tomorrow!
Bai bai shitemo nanka suguni aitaku naru
I already miss you right after I say goodbye
Densha ni norumade zutto koe wo kiitetai yo
Until I get on the train I want to keep hearing your voice
Akiregao kimi ga warau
You look fed up, but you're still smiling
Nee issho ni kaerou
Hey, let's go home together!
Kikoeru yo
I can hear it
Kimi no koe ga
Your voice
Dokomade mo hibiku symphony
That's a symphony that echoes far away
Hikari sasu koi iro
Light shines with the color of love
Zutto te wo tsunagou
I want to feel the press of your hand over mine
Kasanari au shintoatsu
Kanjitainda
For a long time