Hyouka
However, if your theory is true,
then Kanya Fest is being held at the price of at least one student's high school life.
Still, I'm surprised.
At what?
The fact that you even tried to solve the mystery.
I was too.
You solved a few mysteries since we've enrolled in Kami High.
I understand why you're doing something so strenuous.
It's for Chitanda, right?
It's Chitanda's fault.
If you say so,
but that wasn't the case today.
You could've taken the easy way out.
We were all helping solve the mystery.
No one would've complained if you said you didn't know.
So why did you lock yourself in the bathroom and think about it?
Did you do that for Chitanda too?
I'm tired of being a gray person.
Chitanda's energy efficiency couldn't be any worse.
She's working as a club leader, on the anthology, on exams,
and now solving mysteries of the past.
I'm surprised she doesn't get tired.
Same goes for you and Ibara.
You guys live such an inefficient life.
Maybe so.
Still, the grass is always greener on the other side.
I get restless when I watch you all.
I want to be able to rest.
But I still...
don't find excitement in it.
That's why I thought...
I should at least participate and test the waters.
By trying out your way of life.
Say something.
Houtarou...
Did you envy those with a rosy lifestyle?
Perhaps.
A rosy lifestyle, huh?
Is that what "rosy" means?
I don't get it.
Like Chitanda, who is pursuing the past,
or Sekitani Jun, who protected Kanya Fest.
Did I want to be like them?
Do I really want my life to be rosy?
I don't get it.
What defines "rosy" anyway?
Speaking of which, I suppose my sister is the same.
"I'm certain that I won't regret these days when I look back in ten years," huh?
When I'm 25, how will I look back at myself from ten years ago?
I'm sure Sekitani Jun never regretted it.
As for me...
Hello, it's Oreki.
Oh, Houtarou?
You're still alive?
How rude!
Did you really think one or two robbers could kill me?
I knew something like that happened to you.
I landed in Pristina yesterday.
My funds and travel documents are both fine.
I'll write you when I get to Sarajevo.
That's the end of my status report.
What about you?
We're making the anthology now. On Hyouka.
Oh, Hyouka!
We researched about Sekitani Jun.
Sekitani Jun?
That name brings back memories.
His name is still being passed down, huh?
The term Kanya Fest  is still taboo, then?
What did you just say?
It was such a tragedy!
I can't believe it happened!
Taboo? Tragedy?
Can't believe it?
Hold on.
We're talking about Sekitani Jun, right?
Yeah. The Gentle Hero, right?
You know about it, right?
No, I guess I don't.
Tell me about Sekitani Jun, Sis.
I've got no time for that!
Ciao!
Y-You... You idiot!
So we're still not done.
The theory I presented to everyone...
was either wrong or incomplete.
If Sekitani Jun was still alive, would he not regret anything?
I thought there'd be no doubting it.
The hero who left high school for he and his comrades' passion...
couldn't possibly regret that sacrifice.
I was fixated on that idea for some reason.
But is that really true?
If you were kicked out of a school over the cultural festival,
and your entire course of life had been altered.
High school life is very rosy.
But if it gets so rosy enough to terminates high school life...
Can you still say that's "rosy"?
No, you can't.
To forgive everything for the sake of his comrades?
There's no way every hero is like that.
Not to mention that my sister called it a tragedy.
Was Sekitani Jun's high school life all that rosy?
I'll get to the bottom of this.
Hi, Fuku.
Hey.
Did Houtarou ask you to come too?
Yeah.
He said, "I have to tell you something. Meet me at club room after school."
Houtarou actually arranging a meeting...
I can't remember him ever doing that.
I'm busy with Manga Club too...
Good evening.
Thank you so much for your help yesterday.
Don't worry about it. I had fun.
Anyway, where's Houtarou?
Well-
There he is.
Everyone here?
What did you want to tell us?
There's some supplementary information for the solution yesterday.
I think it will conclude the case.
Huh? What are you...
Oreki, I think there's still something I need to know about this case.
Don't worry.
I think I can explain most of the questions you might have.
Okay.
What do you mean, Oreki? What do you mean by supplementary information?
It's exactly what I said.
A follow-up meeting to fill in all the blanks.
Fill in the blanks? So your theory was wrong?
I don't know.
I either looked at it from the wrong perspective, or I didn't look too deep into it.
You don't know?
Yet you still called us out here?
Unbelievable!
Just listen.
We should've taken Hyouka more seriously.
What happened to Sekitani Jun wasn't a heroic tale.
It's clearly written in the preface.
We talked about it, and decided to ignore it.
We said it was just the author's state of mind.
Yeah.
But it may have misled us.
But how can we-
In addition,
this line, "all our disputes and sacrifices, and even his smile."
Is this really the kanji for sacrifice ?
It can be read as offering  too, right?
You would write offering  differently.
They're entirely different.
No, it's possible to read it both ways.
Both terms meant the same thing in ancient times.
You're not a top student for nothing. You catch on quickly.
I see there's another way of reading it.
But only the person who wrote it knows which one is correct.
That's right.
We just have to ask the person.
The person?
The person who wrote the preface.
Kouriyama Youko.
She was a tenth grader 45 years ago, and she's 60 or 61 years old now.
You looked for her?
I didn't have to look for her.
She's right in this building.
Isn't that right, library assistant?
It's her?
Yes.
What?
Who is it?
The librarian, Itoigawa?
Itoigawa Youko.
Her maiden name is Kouriyama.
Yes.
The kanji for her last name is pretty rare.
Not to mention that her age is perfect.
Furthermore, her reaction when she found out we were in the Classic Literature Club.
You're such a weirdo.
I'm with her all the time, but I still didn't notice.
You really should have Chii cut your head open and see what's inside.
I've told you before, there's luck involved in this.
No way I'm getting unjustifiably dissected for that.
If we ask the librarian, Itoigawa, then...
...we'll know what happened 45 years ago.
About why it wasn't a heroic tale.
Why they use such a strange cover image.
Why they chose a weird a title like Hyouka.
And about what happened to your uncle.
But how can you be so sure that it's her?
There's no doubt about it. I already confirmed it.
You talked to her?
Yeah.
She was the club leader when she was grade 11.
I booked an appointment with her too.
It's almost time. Let's go to the library.
You're really excited about this.
I guess so.
Geshi
The season of utmost heat, as the daytime get longer.
Hyouka
Hi, Itoigawa-
Oh, you're the Classic Literature Club.
I'm sorry, I still have some work to do.
Is it all right if we talked here?
I'll help you.
Thank you, Ibara.
You said there's something you want to ask me?
Yes.
But before that, I'd like to confirm it in front of everyone.
Your maiden name is Kouriyama, correct?
Yes.
So, you're the one who wrote this.
Yes, I did.
I'm surprised you managed to find this.
I kind of know what you want to ask.
You want to know about the protest that happened 45 years ago, right?
Bingo.
She really knows.
Why would you want to know something that happened so long ago?
I thought it was forgotten already.
Well,
we wouldn't have noticed it, if Chitanda here wasn't a gremlin for curiosity.
Gremlin for curiosity?
Oops. I meant a glutton.
Wh-What? I'm a glutton?
What piqued your interest about that protest?
It's because Sekitani Jun is my uncle.
Oh, I see.
Sekitani Jun. That name brings me back.
Is he doing well?
I don't know.
He's gone missing in India.
I see. I wanted to see him again.
So do I.
Please tell me, what happened to him 45 years ago?
Why wasn't my uncle's incident a heroic tale?
Why is our club's anthology named Hyouka?
How accurate was Oreki's solution?
Oreki's solution? What is that?
Miss! Oreki put fragmentary documents together,
and came up with a solution for what happened 45 years ago.
Please listen to his theory.
Okay.
Let's hear that in librarian's room.
Librarian's Room
I see.
That's why you think his expulsion was moved to October.
Yes.
That's all for my theory.
You were able to come up with this with only those documents?
I only summarized their hypotheses.
I'm speechless.
Was I wrong?
No. It's like you were there yourself.
What you said was practically everything that happened.
What did you want to ask me after knowing all this?
I don't know, but Houtarou says something is missing.
There's one thing I want to ask.
Did Sekitani Jun willingly become a shield for all students?
Was he proud to be a hero for the entire school,
and left the school as part of have a "rosy" school life?
You really see right through everything.
It happened so long ago, but I still remember like it was yesterday.
Kamiyama High's cultural festival was something akin to our goal in life.
I guess it felt as if all the active energy in Japan was materialized in Kami High as the cultural festival.
However, the year I enrolled, our activity had gone too far, and it was closer to a riot.
On that year, the principal put his foot down,
"Don't think of this as a party in school."
I'm sure everyone thought that they were trying to ruin the cultural festival.
We were told the schedule for our cultural festival was shortened from five days to two.
That triggered a huge mess.
The entire school was in tension.
Posters and public meetings everywhere,
and it eventually reached a point where we decided to demonstrate the students' collective opinion.
They were all so serious.
It's something students today wouldn't think of doing.
It wasn't as admirable as you think.
Simply put, our toy was taken away, and we were whining.
But...
Nobody thought of it like that.
Finally, a retaliatory organization was formed to oppose shortening of cultural festival,
but no one volunteered to be the leader.
We were all afraid of the consequences.
I know it sounds pathetic.
Chitanda's uncle, Sekitani Jun, was the one who was selected for this unwanted role.
Another person was leading the group behind the scene,
but he never made his name public.
In the end, we stopped the teachers' plan to shorten the cultural festival.
However, we went too far when our protesting intensified.
We were planning to boycott all classes as part of the protest,
and at the peak of everything, we set up a campfire to show our spirits.
That's when the incident occurred.
The fire spread to the dojo.
The building was nearly wrecked from fire and water.
That was the only thing the students couldn't justify.
The school didn't ask the police to intervene,
but when they put the issue on the table,
no students could offer a rebuttal.
As a result, the student they chose to expel as an example,
was the public leader of the protest,
Sekitani.
We students just watched it happen without trying to help.
Yet, Sekitani kept silent about it.
You asked if he willingly became a shield for the students,
and now you know.
A few years after that,
the cultural festival was shortened by one day in two occasions.
It's a three-day event now.
That's about all there is to it.
Is there anything else you wanted to ask?
So the anthology's cover put that event into a picture.
The hound represents the school.
Rabbits for students,
and the rabbit that took the hound with it was Sekitani Jun.
The dojo alone is exceptionally old in Kami High,
because it was rebuilt after that incident?
Yes.
When they rebuilt the school 20 years ago,
the dojo wasn't very old yet, so they didn't rebuild it.
Uh, Miss?
You don't use the term Kanya Fest.
Is Kanya written Sekitani  in kanji instead of Kamiyama?
What do you mean, Fuku?
The origin of Kanya Fest.
It was named after the hero, Sekitani Fest.
They changed the way kanji was read, to Kanya Fest.
Oh.
But that name is deceptive.
Sekitani Jun didn't become a hero by choice.
If people knew that, they wouldn't have called it Kanya Fest.
Is that true?
Yes.
That nickname became taboo in the Classic Literature Club.
Miss Itoigawa,
why did my uncle name our anthologies Hyouka?
Do you know?
No.
That name was coined by Sekitani, when he sensed his expulsion.
He wasn't usually the type to decide things on his own.
He said, "This is all I can do."
But I'm sorry, I don't really know what it means.
You don't know?
Did they really not understand? Or was no one capable of accepting the truth?
About that silly message of his...
What is it, Oreki?
Don't you get it?
Everything is so clear now.
Hyouka is a silly pun.
A pun?
Sekitani Jun made sure even the descendents of the club like us would know his feelings.
He put his message in the anthology's name.
What do you mean?
Did you figure out the meaning of Hyouka?
Did you really figure it out?
Tell us, Houtarou.
Houtarou?
What would Hyouka translate to in English?
Is it ice cream?
Ice cream? Is that the message?
I told you, it's a pun.
Um, everyone?
These are the true words left by Sekitani Jun.
I remember it now.
I asked my uncle what Hyouka meant.
Then he told me...
Yes... he told me to be strong.
That if I was weak, then...
there will be a day... when I won't even be able to scream.
If that happens, I'll be eaten...
I was scared of being eaten alive.
I'm so glad.
I remember it.
Now I can send my uncle off.
It's all thanks to you, Oreki.
Thank you, Oreki.
Um... I just got lucky.
Right!
You got lucky.
I scream.
I will not remain silent, huh?
So I made a rough draft and schedule for the anthology.
I didn't know that was the kanji for draft.
You're so smart, Mayaka.
Really?
Where did you learn it, anyway?
Why does it matter?
Hey,
this featured article, "Gentle Hero Story: The hidden truths behind the incident 45 years ago..."
What?
Why am I in charge of writing it?
You're the one who solved the mystery, so obviously you're writing it.
It has most number of pages.
Of course. It's the featured article, after all.
Are you okay, Oreki?
I can try writing it if it's too hard.
Good ide-
No, Chii!
This is the only time he can be useful.
Yeah, you have to order him around.
Stop complaining, and come up with a structure for the article, got it?
Anyway, the plan for Fuku's part is...
It was pretty surprising.
What was?
Our anthology's article.
You ended up accepting it.
More like I couldn't escape, so I had to.
Well, it'll at least be a tribute to Sekitani Jun.
Kamiyama High School
Speaking of surprising...
Yes?
I said you should ask Satoshi and Ibara for help earlier, right?
You were against it at first.
What changed your mind?
Oh, that...
You said back then, that even if we couldn't solve my uncle's mystery,
it'd become a thing of past.
It's true that the "me" in ten years might not care,
but these feelings I hold now...
becoming something I don't care about in the future...
is not what I want right now.
I'm living in the present.
So...
I'm sorry. I don't really get it myself.
That's all right.
I feel the same way.
Oh well, see you.
Bye.
"Dear Oreki Tomoe,
"I'm writing this letter because there's something I want to ask you.
"How much did you know about the Classic Literature Club?
"What was your intention when you made me join this club?
"You know my style...
"That's right. Energy consumption.
"If I never joined the club, I would've never even reflected about my lifestyle.
"Did you predict my joining the Classic Literature Club would be a catalyst for that?
"And then there's Hyouka.
"Ever since I found out about Sekitani Jun's incident through those anthologies,
"well, I've come to think my style isn't all that bad.
"Well, relatively speaking, I mean."
Now it seems as if my big sister...
Nah, no way.
"Just think of what I wrote as a status report.
"Have a nice trip.
"Thank you for the advice,
"Oreki Houtarou."
Next week: "Committing a Grave Crime"
Committing a Grave Crime