Sasami report.
Chapter 3, draft 2.
Gods reside in everything in this world.
They as a collection are referred to as the Myriad Gods.
They reside in pebbles on the street, buildings, artworks, animals, grass...
They even reside in the weather, physical laws, and the like, bending them to their will.
These gods can be divided into groups based on their divinity.
Gods with higher divinity can control gods with lower divinity and change them at will.
Those changes are referred to as alterations.
Amaterasu is the highest divine god and holds every other god under Her control.
All gods change forms as Amaterasu demands, and make alterations to fit Her world.
Alterations
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
What would you like to
search?
Options
Search
That great power was once something I had
inherited, maintained, and kept under control.
Options
Search
How I can get rid
of you
Idiot
However...
At the moment, inconceivable as it may be, Amaterasu's power resides in my brother.
For now, it would be correct to assume that my brother is Amaterasu.
So if my brother wishes for something, the Myriad Gods try to make him happy,
and so alterations may occur.
That is what caused the incident on Valentine's Day.
The gods altered themselves into chocolate and begged my brother to eat them.
Luckily, the three Yagami sisters, Tsurugi,
Kagami, and Tama stopped the alterations.
Who or what those three sisters are is still uncertain.
However, they are undoubtedly psychics with high divinity.
It appears to be necessary to expand my
surveillance to include them from now on.
That is all.
Tsukuyomi Sasami.
kamisama no yubisaki de dekiagaru
It all starts at the tips of gods' fingers
watashi no kisetsu tachi
They are where my seasons begin
hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
This is a song much longer than the stars
nemuri wo yusaburu uta
A song that will wake you from your sleep
Sasami@Unmotivated
mimi wo fusaide hito ni magireru to
When I covered my ears walking in the crowd
watashi ga kieta mitai datta
It felt as if I had disappeared
kokoro wo enjiru ni wa
Yes, I want to express my true feelings,
zatsuon wo eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm too immature to use pretty words
deatta kouya no hana
I see flowers blooming in the wild
kowakute yasashikute
They're fearful and gentle
fureta shunkan ni jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I brush through them,
it turns dioramas into realities
kamisama no itazura de egakareta
The map of my future is drawn by the gods
watashi no miraichizu
Drawn by mere whims of the gods
ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
It rings with thousands of sounds
oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
And breaks through tomorrow, chasing after today
hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
When we tightened our bonds under the watch of the stars
nukumori ga mieta yo
I found your warmth
kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our bond forms with the blood we shed
mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
But it's the kind of bond I'm compelled to keep
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 2
In-House Security Guard
Yay! I win.
Shut up, dum-dum!
Shows how immature you are if winning a game makes you this happy, dum-dum!
You are too loud. Be quiet.
We are in the middle of class.
As a student and as your sister, I am
embarrassed by your frivolous attitude.
As a teacher and as your sister, I don't want to hear that from someone who was sleeping in class.
I have already completed my work.
I just don't have someone to check my answers with.
You know, there are an awful lot of students absent.
It's been like this for a while now.
Oh, really?
Please pay more attention. You're the teacher, after all.
We teachers don't care about you
students as much as you think we do.
Please don't expose me to such harsh reality.
You guys frustrate me so much!
Talk faster!
There is obviously something strange about this!
Why are there so many students absent?
Chat log
Take a look at this.
What is it?
This is the Yamatano Orochi SNS that has been popular among the young people.
Yamatano Orochi SNS?
In other words, it's a school fantasy social
network system featuring swords and magic.
Furthermore, this person here, here, and here are all students who are absent today.
They play in this internet reality all day long.
Is it really all that interesting?
Who knows.
The game balance was initially poor,
and their game system was unpopular. They were about to shut it down due to a lack of revenue.
But three years ago, it suddenly became popular for no apparent reason,
and that is how we arrived at the present situation.
Maybe I'll try it just to see what it's like.
Oh?
Judging by your sudden interest, would this be an alteration?
Tsukuyomi, your sister has a computer, right?
Yes, she does.
I think she has about ten?
So...
Lend us your computers.
Look at these stuffed animals!
This bed is great...
Look, I won't lecture you about missing school, so cooperate a little. 'Kay?
How many computers do you have?
Do you even need this many?
I do.
One for games, one for internet, one for anime, one for music,
one for games, one for games, one for—
That's too many for games!
They're for different games.
Anyway, it's my first time playing this type of game.
You're good with the internet, right?
Sasami, why don't you play with us?
Huh? N-No thanks.
I'm one of those people who doesn't see the point of those games.
What? So you're antisocial even on the internet?
I can't...
I can't tell them that I'm a game addict who has spent countless hours on this game,
and that my character is the strongest in this game and has the rarest set of items.
S-So what's going on with this Yamatano whatever game?
I dunno.
But we gotta stop anything that seems suspicious.
We don't want to wait till it's too late.
It would be horrible if something similar to the Valentine's Day incident happened again.
This isn't good.
If they find something strange in this game, they'll shut it down,
and all of my EXP, gold, my Orochi Rank, items, and the hours I spent on the game will be gone!
I must stop them at all cost!
All righty, I'm done.
Let's start.
Welcome to Takamagahara Academy.
Will you tell us about yourself
before the entrance ceremony?
What do I do?
First, you have to make your character.
I just want to get through this game fast, so I'll be a fighter.
No, this one is your real job!
What?
You're in luck.
That's a rare message that grants you a rare job.
Really?
Tsurugi, your real job is this:
Name      Tsurugi
Sex        Female
Age           16
Race       Human
Occupation
Delinquent
Leader
Armor  Biker Overcoat
Right Hand Wooden Sword
Beginner  Items   3x cigarettes
Special Ability      Extortion
a delinquent leader!
What the hell?
Is being a delinquent leader even a job?
Enjoy your time at the academy!
Oh no, my hand slipped.
Whoops! I broke my router.
Connection lost
Please check your internet connection.
Hey, what are you doing?
Sorry.
We won't have internet access for the rest of today.
Not a problem.
I have my own high speed network.
I'm done as well.
I figured we'd need a healer.
Oh, you're nurse?
A veterinarian.
I have no interest in ordinary humans.
Name      Kagami
Sex        Female
Age           16
Race          Elf
Job           Vet
Armor
Nurse Uniform
Nurse Cap
Right Hand      Syringe
Beginner  Items   3x Anaesthesia
Packs
Special Ability Anaesthesia
Are you sure you can heal humans?
You always fall asleep when something's not in your favor.
Oh no!
Whoops, there goes the power.
You guys didn't save yet, right?
I think you should just give up today.
I'm done too!
Name       Tama
Sex        Female
Age           16
Race       Demon
Job     Pastry Chef
Armor    Maid Outfit
Right Hand  Kitchen Knife
Beginner  Items            N/A
Special Ability  Julienning
I'm a pastry chef!
I'm going to bake all the snacks I want to eat!
Shoot!
They were all using laptops...
No!
I haven't saved my report yet!
Hey, Tsukuyomi!
Go fix the circuit breaker.
Okay, right away!
Hurry up! We're waiting!
Yes, right away!
Oh, you ran out of time.
You can't even make a simple decision in a game?
I bet you're a piece of indecisive trash in the real world too.
I'm sure you're trying to make up for your lonely life with this game,
but the internet isn't that simple, you retard.
What did I do to deserve all this verbal abuse?
Here's a perfect job for a loser like you!
Name      Kamiomi
Sex          Male
Age           16
Race      Human
Job           Loser
Armor         N/A
Right Hand        N/A
Beginner Weapons            N/A
Special Ability     Being a servant
Your job is...
a loser?
I'm not even wearing clothes...
Brother, things don't work out for you even in video games.
Enjoy your time at the academy!
Chat log
Okay, the game officially starts now.
Guys, keep a lookout for any alternations.
I couldn't stop them...
The power outage, the birdlime, and the wobbling madam all failed.
So what do we do next?
Nothing in particular.
You just do whatever you want in this world.
How is this any fun?
You can do that in the real world.
Not everyone can do that.
More importantly, you should serve tea to your guests.
Stop doing as you please in my house.
I'll bring you tea right away.
I'd like some chips too.
You're asking for too much.
I want a chocolate parfait!
Make your own! You're a pastry chef!
potato chips
Here you go.
Thanks! I didn't mean to be so demanding.
You totally did!
What's wrong?
Don't touch the laptop with that hand!
The keyboard's going to get dirty!
It's fine.
No it's not!
Use chopsticks!
That's too much effort.
You shouldn't be like that, Sis.
Shut-ins have their own way of doing things.
If you crush the chips like this and eat straight out of the bag,
your hands won't get dirty.
Wow, you're a genius!
We're good.
What the hell are you doing?!
Don't worry, there's the 30-second rule.
I'm not talking about the chips!
The chopsticks came in handy.
I need a vacuum!
Hey...
You're awfully quiet.
Nothing's wrong.
What did you do?
Nothing at all.
Show me the laptop!
No, don't look!
I told you not to look.
Just turn it off!
You own this manga?
I've always wanted to read it!
Wash your oily hands before reading it!
It's fine.
It's the first edition, so treat it with care!
Relax, it won't make a difference.
Don't throw the ribbon away!
Oh? I haven't seen this movie yet.
Don't open the package! It's brand new and I haven't opened it yet!
Hey, what should I do?
What does "Do you want to format the system?" mean?
Formatting the system. Please wait.
Formatting complete.
My party!
It's hopeless...
I can't deal with terrorism on multiple fronts all by myself.
Crap!
I had already lost the moment I let them in!
Chat log
Hey, you! Be quiet during class!
It hit me!
I was quietly listening to the lecture!
Kamiomi received 2 damage
Chat log
Kamiomi
Kamiomi died.
And I died?!
Oh, no. Kamiomi died?
Someone take him to the nurse's office.
That's a light reaction.
Let's revive you, Mr. Tsukuyomi.
So how do we do that?
Mini Game
Mini game: "Not in the Nurse's Office" has started.
Not in the
Nurse's Office
Chat log
What?
You have until the time limit to do anything you can to revive him.
How about this?
Tama cooled Kamiomi's head.
That's for treating a cold.
Kamiomi has been revived.
How?!
Oh, thank you, Tama.
Kamiomi's likability has increased by 20.
Likability? What's that?
High likability allows characters to get
married and make offspring characters.
What? You can make kids?
Now this is my type of game!
With a bed, a nurse's office is the perfect place for sex events.
Tsukuyomi, you get naked too!
What? Me too?
Just stay still and stop acting like an innocent young woman!
Well, I'm certainly not an innocent young
woman, but I don't think that's the problem.
I'm so scared! This is scary!
Tsurugi and Paparin are naked and doing weird things together!
Please don't traumatize a gradeschooler.
It's all good! It's all good!
Virtual Miss Tsurugi, even though it's a game, please stop!
Resistance only enhances the experience!
How's this?
What the hell are you doing to my brother?
What's that?
Is this you?
Wow! You look strong!
And are you for real?!
You need to outright refuse even if it's inside a video game!
You stupid pervert!
Know what? Go fall in love with a video game character and get married or something!
You're just a piece of insensitive blockheaded trash that's horny all year long!
Sasami is inside the game!
And she's cursing at me so adorably!
Trash!
Chat log
Stay away from me!
Kamioimi takes 9999
damage.
Chat log
Kamioimi takes 9999
damage.
Kamiomi
Kamiomi died.
Oops.
So you've been skipping school to play this Yamatano Orochi SNS game.
No, I've been doing other things like shopping online, watching anime, and reading blogs on net idols.
Same difference!
But I'm not the only one addicted to this game...
I hacked into their system.
It appears that about 10,000 people are online.
I wonder what their objective is.
Who knows?
I, for one, can't seem take a grasp on what they're thinking.
Tsurugi...
I just realized something terrible!
What is it?
I... I...
I need to pee.
You should've gone earlier.
Tsurugi, please come with me!
You're in elementary school, so you can use the potty by yourself just fine.
I know this is sad, but humanity has yet to evolve to that point.
Oh, just shut up!
I'll be right back, so try to make some progress.
So what do we do now?
Well, let's start by making some progress in the game.
Let's return to the classroom first.
What is this?
What happened here?
Look at this.
Those light dots...
Are those the players' spirits?
Is that the army of the dark lord that's absorbing the spirits?
I sense a powerful force.
One of a very high divinity...
K-Kagami?
Ouch, that hurt.
Huh, where am I?
What happened?
Crap.
Brother, get awa—
Ow...
Well, this was unexpected.
It appears that our minds have been
absorbed into the Yamatano Orochi SNS.
Then it really is an alteration...
Yamatano Orochi...
Its divinity is insanely high.
It must have grown from the
consumption of the players' spirits.
No...
But I don't understand.
It's grown so big, but why isn't it doing anything else?
If this god carried malicious intentions, it could quite easily control the players' bodies and invade the real world.
However, it's only consuming the sacrifices and it isn't doing anything beyond that.
How puzzling.
With this much power, it could invade the real world and create its own kingdom.
It doesn't care about the real world.
It just wants to maintain this world.
Its only desire is to keep this world in existence.
That's why it exists.
What do you mean?
That god smells like us.
Its level of divinity is on par with that of Amaterasu.
In other words, that is the monster Sasami created unconsciously.
I figured it out by looking at your profile.
You started playing this game 3 years ago.
In order to escape from the harsh reality and from your strenuous studies, you played this game.
And you made a wish.
From the brink of being shut down 3 years ago, this game suddenly became popular.
The timing matches perfectly.
That thing has been protecting your playground from being shut down.
That's... what I wished for?
Is that what I had wished for and created when I still held the power of Amaterasu?
Really?
I see...
You've been protecting this world all along.
You know what to do, right?
Its job is done.
You should tell it that.
In the name of Tsukuyomi Sasami, I command you.
O savage god...
rest in peace!
Diffuse and melt into the world as you sleep.
I am okay now.
I'm living a pretty happy life now.
So... you don't have to...
try so hard anymore.
Make sure you
get in bed
once you
wake up.
Important Announcements
to Our Customers
Due to glitches in the system,
Yamatano Orochi SNS will be down for the meanwhile.
Sasami@Unmotivated
And it's that time again Sasami comes on stage!
Let's hear you sing for us this time, okay?
Go grab a mic and are you ready?
Hey, come on!
Hello?
Not even a reply?
You're really not interested at all, are you?
The song's already started!
We're going to have broadcasting issues at this rate!
For your sake Sasami, as your brother,
I will do my best to entertain in your place!
Yay!
Come on!
Cha cha cha!
Ya!
Hoo!
Hoo, oh yeah!
I tried my best.
I put all my heart into those cheers!
But Sasami still doesn't seem interested at all.
If we don't do something to fix this,
this show is going to run into problems!
Oh, I've got it!
Next time, let's have the three Yagami sisters give us a hand!
Weather Forecast
It's time for the unmotivated weather forecast.
I'll be staying at home from morning until evening, so it doesn't really what the weather is.
Today's Weather
Nagasaki
Osaka
Nagoya
Tokyo
Sapporo
0~12  hours/12-24 hours
I'll still be home at night, at midnight, and all the way until the next morning, so it doesn't matter.
But if it's too sunny, I won't be able to sleep, so hopefully it won't be sunny.
People who invented curtains are so smart.
Next time, episode three:
Next Time
Episode Three
If you work, you lose.
If You Work, You Lose