Ow... Hm?
So how long are you going to sleep? School's already over.
Man... There are other ways of waking me up, you know.
What?
Actually... I need you for something.
Is that how you should talk when you ask a favor of others?
What's the fuss? This is a very good thing for you too.
What's with the skeptical look?
Tell me what this is about.
To do so, first I want you to come to the rooftop.
Huh?
Old Home
So why did you have to bring me here?
What do you want?
Just wait and see.
Hm?
Ah...
Uhm... If I remember correctly, you're from the class next door.
Uhm, Sanae... I really...
Ahh! Ahh! I can't hear you!
Well then, goodbye!
Ah!
You're Elen's friend, right?
Fujiwara, was it?
It's Fujieda. I'm Mio Fujieda.
So you know Sanae as well, huh?
Yes.
Well.... I was in the same class as her the first year.
I see. By the way, is there something you wanted?
Uhm... well... actually, there's something I want to ask you.
Did you want to ask something about Elen?
No, that's not it.
Uhm... what I'd like to ask is... about you.
Hm?
Is there someone...
you like?
Huh?!
But you wouldn't want to go out with me, right?
Th-That's... you mean... Uhm... well...
Mio?
Elen!
Brother... what're you doing...
in a place like this?
I was wondering who you were talking to. Did you know Mio?
Well, uhm...
What're you doing here?
I was looking for Mio. I've got a craving for Kanekoya's waffles,
so I wondered if she wanted to join me.
Hey, do you wanna go?
I... have errands to do today, so...
See you later.
Ah... Yeah.
Did I interrupt something?
Yeah, big time.
Did something happen?
She said she likes me.
Huh?
Like I said, Fujiwara told me...
Fujieda, you mean. But hey, really? Mio said she likes you?
Y... yeah... sort of.
Whoa... she's got unusual tastes.
What do you mean by that?
So... what did you tell her?
You came in before I said anything. So...
Go after her!
What?!
I think she wants to hear your response.
I know I'm the one who interrupted,
but there's no way you should leave things like this!
But what should I tell her?
Decide for yourself.
But...
Just go!
After I went to all the trouble to arrange it?
How can you be such a bungler?
Sorry.
You should have done as we discussed...
You should have just said "I like you. Be my boyfriend."
After that, get him to nod even if it means you have to choke him. That's it.
It takes 5 seconds. When confessing love, shock and awe is the way to go.
Why are you dragging your feet like this?
But... I...
I can't do it after all.
Geez, come on! This is the last spring of your high school life!
Are you going to ruin it?!
Sanae!
Oh, good timing! I was about to go look for you.
Good you found me, then. I wanna talk to Fujieda.
Hurry up and leave.
What?!
Oh... I see.
In that case, Good Sir, I'll just disappear as you told me.
I'll leave the rest to your discretion.
Ah... What re you doing, Sanae?
Oh nothing...
Fujieda... uhm...
Yes!
About the response to what you said earlier...
since it was out of the blue...
how should I put it...
Don't peek!
Okay.
So...
Yes.
Well...
So what did you tell her?
I said I wanted to start as a friend for now.
What a typical response. You have no sense at all.
It's none of your business.
So have you made any plans with that friend?
We decided to go into town tomorrow.
Brother.
What?
Do a good job escorting Mio.
She's my friend. If you do things to embarrass her...
Bang!
That's disturbing.
I'm giving you support, too. Mio is a nice girl.
Yeah. I realized that just from what little we talked.
Yep.
So... give me emergency allowance.
I've already given you this month's allowance!
What?
Oh, is that right?
Getting a promise to go out on a date already...
That's a big achievement for a late bloomer like you.
Good for you!
What are you girls talking about?
Oh, Ms. Fujieda! Hello!
Hi!
Hi, you two.
Ms. Fujieda, something major happened! It's big news!
What is it?
Tomorrow, Mio is going to...
Ah!
You can't tell her.
Oh... it must be a date.
What? How did you guess?
Do you have your lunch?
Yeah. Well then, see you later.
Hold on.
Okay. Now I'd give you 40%.
That's a low score.
Repeat what I taught you last night.
I like you!
I love you.
It's not money that matters.
You sound like a gigolo.
Thanks for the lunch. It was very delicious.
Normally, I would invite you to a restaurant or something, but...
You live alone with Elen, right?
Both of my parents died in an accident.
Ah... I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it. It happened when we were small... so I'm over it.
You're strong. I live alone with my mother, too.
But seeing her busy with work...
makes me wish... my father was around.
Then you should support your mom.
When you need a guys help, I'll give you a hand.
Yes! Thanks!
Let's see... what's next?
Meet up at the train station
Take train to destination
Art Museum
Relax at a café
Have lunch at the park
Shopping
Movie
What's that?
What?
That looks like Sanae's handwriting.
Movie
Go to the kind of place
you don't talk about
"Go to the kind of place you don't talk about"...
Reiji...
What's this "place you don't talk about"?
Eh?
Climb the stairs to adulthood and now you're Cinderella.
I'm a guy.
If you clear all the schedules I created,
today's date will be perfect!
That darn Sanae!
That's a woman, isn't it?
It's amazing that she's riding such a big motorcycle.
Always being poor, such an amazing bike is...
Oh? When did that happen?
Reiji?
The sound of a 9mm Parabellum fired with a silencer...
awoke me... from a dream.
We traveled from Mexico to Peru via land...
and then to the Philippines via Palau.
And it's been 6 months since we came to Japan.
We were supposed to live on here... in this town, leaving our past behind.
This is your homeland.
Ever since we came to this country, you've... really changed.
I could see that your heart was rapidly opening up.
I bet that's how... a homeland is.
But it's over.
A pursuer has come.
Inferno?
I don't know. But I received a silent warning.
I see. The time we awake from this dream has come, then.
If possible, I wanted you to stay in the dream forever...
leaving the past behind.
What about you?
I'm not... I'm not done with my penance yet, so...
Your penance? Who are you repenting to?
Directly to God... since I should be able to see him someday.
Elen...
So Inferno... has finally come.
I didn't want to do this, but I'll take advantage of Mio's feelings.
Mio's feelings?
What do you mean by that, Elen?
Mio's parents got separated right after she was born.
Yeah, she told me that.
Her father disappeared and is still missing.
Mio grew up being told that and still believes that lie.
Lie?
Her father is a big shot who even appears in the newspapers.
Who is he?
Kaiten Godo.
The head of the Godo Family, a crime syndicate that covers a wide area.
The Godo Family?!
That's right. "Fujieda" is her mother's maiden name.
That Godo Family...
Does she know about it?
No, she doesn't.
Even within the Godo Family, only a handful people have been told about it.
Kaiten Godo wanted to protect his divorced wife and his daughter
from the power struggle, so...
Then Mio is Daisuke Godo's...
Yes, his half sister.
Kaiten Godo absolutely never lets his daughter get dragged into violence.
And yet he can't openly protect her, either.
Mio is Kaiten's biggest weakness.
How did you come across such information?
Scythe Master told me...
Scythe Master?
Though it was quite a long time ago.
After Master ran away from Inferno, he hid here in Japan.
I told you about it before, right?
Yeah.
Around that time, Master investigated the Godo Family thoroughly.
Since he too intended to take advantage of their weakness when push came to shove.
Weakness? Don't tell me, Elen...
Are you going to use Mio for...
She can be at least a trump card in an emergency.
The senior member who holds the real power in the Family now is Toru Shiga.
He's a member of Inferno.
Humph.
Now you know the situation.
Even if the one who appeared in front of you was Inferno,
as long as we have Mio...
Why... didn't you tell me?
Yeah... I should have told you before.
If I had known Mio would come to have feelings for you...
If I had known our pursuers would come this soon.
This life didn't last as long as I hoped.
We also have to get ready... to run.
Yeah, I guess you're right. We have to run.
Don't push yourself.
It's okay to cry at a time like this.
You can go back to being your old self now.
That's too selfish.
It's a matter of course that I should be prepared for little things like this
as we're being pursued.
No... You had forgotten about it.
But it was okay,
and I was... happy about it.
Elen...
During this 6 months, your smile... your face while you were sleeping at night...
you really looked happy.
I was able to feel happy by just looking at you being happy.
If one's birthplace can heal them this much...
I thought someday, I, too, would...
I dreamed about it by thinking that way...
because you promised me
that you'll find a homeland for me someday.
I don't want the happiness you've felt up until now to be a sham.
We can return someday.
Even if we leave, it's not like this country will disappear.
The day we can come back again will definitely come one day.
The day we can get a normal life back in a real sense will come.
It's just that it's not that time right now.
What?! Reiji went home in the middle of your date?!
It wasn't a date.
And also he did say an urgent matter arose.
To the young who celebrate the joys of youth,
there's nothing more important than romance!
K-Keep it down.
Geez...
after I went to the trouble of coming up with a schedule for you guys...
That might be none of your business.
That was unfortunate.
Hmm... I guess.
Oh? "I guess"?
Ah... Speak of the devil... the very man who ran off.
Take this!
Hey, hey, that hurts!
S-Sanae...
Geez, Sanae...
Reiji, I had a good time yesterday.
Yeah... me, too.
Did you take care of the urgent matter okay?
Yeah... I did.
You dodged my attack. You're quite good... But I'm better.
I've got to talk to Elen, so I'm going on ahead.
Later.
What?! Where're you going, leaving your girlfriend here?
Ah... did that bother you?
He's different somehow.
What?
He seems different... from usual.
Huh?
Wh... Why? Why is she in a place like this?
No... More importantly, is that really you?
You didn't die?
Cal!
Next episode
Anger
How do you do, Ein?
Or... should I say ex-Phantom?