This place is like a maze.
Try not to get separated.
All right.
Gahhh!
- [WINRY] Owww.
- Winry! Are you okay?
[WINRY]
I'm fine.
What's this stuff?
Dynamite!
Take it from me, take it
from me, take it from me...!
Nahhhh. These are
all sopping wet...
Relax. They wouldn't blow up
even if we wanted 'em to.
Enough... Quit dawdling...
They could already be after us.
Right... Sorry.
[MILES]
The storm has finally passed.
Start preparing.
[MICK and LIAM]
Yes, sir.
We can't take any risks
with Kimblee and his men,
so first chance you get...
take out all three of them.
[LIAM] Right. Yes, sir.
[MICK] Understood, sir.
You're the only ones to
know of this mission...
Don't mention it
outside of this room.
Hey, hold on a minute...
You're not planning on
killing them, are you Major?
Of course we are.
No, I'm not gonna
have any part of that...
I say we should
take Kimblee prisoner
and try to get some answers.
[MILES] Do you really think
he'll tell us anything...?
He's too dangerous to live.
But we don't know
about his men.
I mean for all we know,
he could be
manipulating them somehow...
Forcing
them to obey.
You could be right...
But we can't take such
a risk on a possibility.
And yet you're still
willing to kill them for one...
This isn't like it was
with General Raven...
There might be another way!
Have you forgotten the
first law of Briggs...?
The careless are
the first to die.
You show mercy in this place...
And I guarantee that
it's going to get you
or your friends killed.
[MILES]
We aren't going to be careless.
We're killing Kimblee...
And the two men with him.
I had almost forgotten
that he's just a kid.
Indeed he is...
Especially if he's naÃ ̄ve enough
to think he won't
have to kill anyone.
Well I have to admit that
I used to think the same thing.
So did I.
But once you've lived
through a couple wars
ike we have, you
learn some things...
Like sometimes,
killing someone isn't as
hard as letting them live.
The Elric brothers
have certainly chosen
the more difficult path.
[MILES] I guess they like
to go against the grain.
Yeah...
But in a way, I envy
their conviction.
[MARCOH] What's this
"Rasayana" term here?
[SCAR] It's a miracle
drug used for longevity.
[MARCOH] Could that be the
Philosopher's Stone...?
It says here...
that it can transform...
all metals into gold and
restore youth to the elderly...
And what does this term
mean...? "Aurelian"?
[SCAR]
It's another term for gold.
[MARCOH] So these
notes are centered around
immortality and gold.
I'm guessing that it's
because Mr. Scar's brother was
influenced by Xingese alkahestry
whenever he wrote them.
And why is that?
We refer to an
immortal as a shinhito...
It means a "a true being"...
These "true beings" are
considered to be perfect souls.
And since gold is
considered the perfect metal...
these beings are also
sometimes called "Aurelian."
[MARCOH]
So in other words...
An immortal person is
seen as a "golden being."
[MAY CHANG]
In a sense.
It comes from the man who
brought alchemy to Xing...
The legend says
he was an immortal
with golden hair and eyes.
And that's where the
term first originated.
An alchemist with golden
hair and golden eyes, huh...
Sounds like Ed and Al.
[YOKI]
Hey...! Over here...! The exit!
Oh, wow...! It's so bright!
[MARCOH] I was starting
to wonder if we'd make it.
[GERSO]
The weather's clear.
[ZAMPANO]
For now...
Let's head to Briggs
before it turns again.
Alright, everyone...
Follow my lea--
[YOKI]
Hey...!
[GERSO] Looks like the
snow is pretty deep.
You should hop on my back Miss,
just to be safe.
We'll walk ahead to
stomp down the snow
and make a clear path for
the rest of you to follow.
Thank you very much.
[AL]
Helllllp!
Hey...! Is someone there...?!
Help me, please!
Help!
That's Al!
My Alphonse?!
[MAY CHANG]
No, no!
[WINRY] Just hold on,
we'll get you out of there!
[AL]
You saved me!
I got stuck in the snow...
And then a blizzard buried me.
[WINRY]
What are you doing out here, Al?
[AL] I crossed the
mountain to warn you guys.
You crossed over...?
In the middle of that snowstorm?
[YOKI]
So you cut straight through
bypassing the mine's
twists and turns.
[MARCOH]
Why would you even risk that?
[AL] It was the
only way to warn you.
[WINRY]
Warn us about what?
[AL] Briggs has been taken
over by troops from Central.
General Armstrong's gone.
They summoned her to
Central Headquarters.
You'll be walking
right into their hands
if you go there.
[GERSO] Well, then what
are we supposed to do...?
We can't just hide in the mines.
[AL]
I don't know...
We'll have to
find someplace else.
But there isn't anyplace else!
Just follow me.
[MARCOH]
Where are you taking us?
There's a mountain
village called Asbeck nearby.
It shouldn't take
us long to get there.
I have been told
that some of my people
have taken refuge
in the slums there.
An Ishvalan refugee camp?
It's not like we really
have any other options.
Great idea, sir...!
Let's get going!
Are you sure about this, Al?
[AL]
About what?
Well, isn't Mr. Kimblee
gonna be suspicious
if you just suddenly disappear?
[AL]
It's okay, don't worry.
Brother's got it
all taken care of.
[SOLDIER A]
Three men in this squad.
[SOLDIER B]
There are five men in mine, sir.
Each squad is ready then...
Spread out and carefully
search your designated sector.
[SOLDIER B]
Sir.
[SOLDIER A]
Yes, sir.
Let's get going.
[MICK]
Yes, sir.
Don't get carried
away, Alphonse.
There's no reason to
call the Major "sir."
It's hard to move
around in here...
Couldn't you have
made this thing lighter?
[ED] You're strong,
you can handle it...
C'mon... Kimblee's watching.
[MICK]
Hold on, Brother!
[ED]
Hurry up... c'mon.
Did you overhear Kimblee say
where his squad is searching?
You saw that mineshaft in
the center of town, didn't you?
They're headed down there...
To search the tunnels.
I heard him mention
that he couldn't trust
the Northern soldiers,
so he's only taking the men
that he brought with him, sir.
[MILES] I guess he's
figured us out, then.
We'll head them off...
Position snipers near the
opening of the mine shaft.
Yes, Sir.
[KIMBLEE] Check the entrance
for tracks in the snow...
We'll follow them in if
you find multiple sets.
[DARIUS and HEINKEL]
Yes, sir.
[MILES]
Is it clear?
[MICK]
Yes, sir... He's in my sights.
[MILES]
What's wrong?
[MICK]
It's Edward.
[MILES]
What?
Hey, Kimblee...
You should probably
let the Briggs soldiers
check the tunnels instead...
You could get lost in
there pretty easily.
The mere fact that
you're stopping me
is proof that we're
in the right place...
Now I know that
they're down there.
And how is that...?
Look, I wanna
catch Scar just as--
You're trying to buy some time
for your snipers to
get into position,
aren't you?
You knew about that?
I can practically smell
the murderous intent
in the air around here...
It's like a sixth sense
I picked up while in Ishval.
They're just standing
there, talking...
What should I do?
Can you still target Kimblee?
[MICK]
Yes, sir.
[MILES]
Then aim carefully... and fire.
[MICK]
Yes, sir.
That bastard!
He's using the snow
to block our view!
[ED]
Dammit.
Kimblee!
[ED]
Sonnuva--
[ED] I should've guessed
you guys were chimeras!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ED]
Damn you, Kimblee.
I can't see anything...
But on the bright side,
they can't see me either.
The odds are eve--
[HEINKEL] There's no
point in trying to run,
Fullmetal Alchemist.
You can't hide from us here...
We may not see you,
but we can smell you.
[ED]
Shut up.
[MILES]
Fullmetal!
What's going on in there...?
Edward...! Answer me!
Major Miles!
These guys are Chimeras!
And they know how to
fight in low visibility.
Stay outta here...! Trust me!
[ED]
Owwww...
Falling like that's gonna
stunt my growth even more.
[ED]
Dynamite, huh?
There's one perk to
fighting in a mine.
Whoa, you might want to
keep your distance guys.
These aren't exactly
cigars I'm holding.
[HEINKEL]
You idiot.
[DARIUS] That stuff isn't gonna
do you any good, it's too damp.
[ED]
You sure about that...?
Do you happen to know
what dynamite's made of?
It's Nitroglycerin, isn't it?
And Nitroglycol...
And there's sawdust...
Isn't there ammonium
nitrate in it too?
[ED]
Yeeess, there is.
And what's ammonium
nitrate made out of?
[HEINKEL] That's easy!
Nitric acid and ammonia.
[HEINKEL and DARIUS]
Ammoniaaaa!
Pee-yew!
[KIMBLEE]
What's that disgusing smell?!
[ED]
That's ammonia...
There're downsides to
having a sharp nose...
I doubt that they'll be
much use to you now.
Your attitude changed
rather quickly,
now that I've lost my hostage.
What'd you expect to happen?
Let's make this easy.
All I want here is for you to
tell me everything you know...
[KIMBLEE] Oh, is that
all you want from me...?
I just got out of the hospital
and I don't feel like
getting banged up fighting
a youngster like you...
Not to mention that I don't
really have the time either.
I guess I'll have to
speed things up with this.
[ED] At least I won't
have to search for it now.
[KIMBLEE]
He's fast!
[ED]
Too slow!
He's lost his stone...
And he can't transmute now.
[ED]
And now I've-
[KIMBLEE]
Now you've what?
You think you've won?
So you're determined
not to kill...
How admirable of you...
You do realize the advantage
that it gives your
opponent though,
now don't you?
Instead of finishing me off,
you've given me a
second chance to kill you.
That sense of mercy is about
to get you in a lot of trouble.
[ED]
Aughh!!!
[explosions]
[groans; gasping]
[ED] I must've fallen
down the mine shaft.
Kim... blee...
[groans]
Dammit... I can't
let Kimblee get away.
[ED]
You're kidding... No.
[gasp]
[thud]
[WINRY]
Al...! What's wrong?!
[MAY CHANG]
Alphonse!
[WINRY]
Al!
[AL] Oh, no... I'm
being pulled back again.
[WINRY]
What...? Pulled back...?
What do you mean, Al...? Al?!
[AL]
My body...
It's pulling my soul.
Al! Al!
[SCAR]
His soul is being pulled away?
[MARCOH] Do you know
if anything like this
has ever happened before, Winry?
[WINRY]
I don't know...
[MAY CHANG]
Can you hear me, Alphonse?
Al...! Please wake up!
[WINRY]
No... Al...! Al!
What do we do...?
What do we do?
[WINRY]
Ed!!!
[ED]
I won't make her cry...
Especially not over
something this stupid.
[HEINKEL]
Damn... Kimblee's gonna pay.
[DARIUS] Hey, Fullmetal kid...
You still alive...?
What made you
decide to rescue us?
[HEINKEL]
You're more injured than we are.
[ED]
Don't get the wrong idea.
I can't pull this out of
my stomach on my own...
I could use...
a little bit of help.
[DARIUS] We were enemies
just five minutes ago
and now you're asking
us to save your life.
[ED]
Yeah... Basically.
[DARIUS] Well...
It's not like we were
given orders to kill you.
C'mon.
[HEINKEL]
Y'know, kid...
You're gonna bleed to
death pretty quickly
once I pull this out.
Not if I heal it...
As soon as it's out of me,
I'll close up the wound...
with alchemy.
[HEINKEL]
What?
Have you ever performed any
kind of medical alchemy before?
Sort of... I did
some research on it...
when I tried
human transmutation.
Just some research...?
Your guts've gotta
be all messed up...
You're gonna need a
Philosopher's Stone
to make this work.
I'm gonna have to use
my own life force...
the same way
I would use a stone.
It'll probably take a few
years off my lifespan, though.
[HEINKEL]
You're positive?
I don't really have
time to think about it...
If this is really what
showing mercy is gonna cost me,
then I'm gonna have to learn
to pay the price... right?
I don't know what
you're talkin' about,
but it sounds like you're sure.
[HEINKEL]
Ready?
Yeah, I'm ready.
[ED]
I've gotta picture myself...
as a single mass of energy.
[painfully]
Yaahhh!! Rghhh!!
[ED]
Use the energy...
Just like the Stone!
[painfully]
Rrrrghh!! Yaaggghh!!
[ED]
That's it...
I'm a Philosopher's Stone
that's powered by a single soul.
[painfully]
Aaaaaaaaagggh!!!
[ED]
Remember...
What it felt like...
At that moment.
Remember...
How it felt to use souls!
To harness liiiife!
[HEINKEL]
Did he make it?
Ya can't kill me that easily.
Whoa... You mean it worked!?
Well, I wouldn't exactly
say that I'm healed...
I rejoined my
undamaged organs...
And I managed to
stop the bleeding...
But it won't last for long.
[HEINKEL] Oh... Then
you need a real doctor.
No... I don't have
time... for that.
[DARIUS]
What...? Hey!
[ED] I've gotta stop Kimblee...
Before he gets...
to... them...
[DARIUS]
Oh, man.
[HEINKEL]
Idiot...
There's no way you can fight
Kimblee in your condition.
What is it?
[HEINKEL]
Whoa...
The Stone, huh...?
I guess Mr. Kimblee
must've lost it.
Quit callin' that
freak "Mister"...
He's not our boss...
Not since he almost killed us.
That's a good point...
How about we make our
resignation official?
Let's just hold
onto our freedom
and let the bastard think
we died in the rubble.
Well... What do we do with him?
[HEINKEL] We can't just
leave him here to die.
We do owe him
our lives, after all.
[DARIUS] Very true...
First things first...
We gotta find him a doctor.
[HEINKEL]
Right.
[NARRATOR] The situation
may seem to be unstoppable,
but the unexpected
lies in wait,
planning to forge its own
path and alter the outcome.
Victory only promises itself
to the one who's capable
of seeing the truth,
and patient enough to
understand its meaning.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 42,
"Signs of a Counteroffensive."
This is how the war begins.