Someone from Raira Academy
was attacked by the Slasher!
Instead, you should get the others caught
up in fighting over her body.
You eat OK?
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yeah, the strongest.
If I weren't headless, I'd be dead.
I'll kill them. I'll kill them dead!
I'll kill them deader than dead!
Shizuo!
I flew.
Flew?
All that I wanted was to know...
Even a stopped clock is
right twice a day.
Ikebukuro...
The source of this junktown's energy.
The truth about its greed,
growing greater by the day.
It's mine!
And the strongest man in the city...
About six months ago, when I was doing an
article on the strongest man in Ikebukuro
for a "Tokyo Year in Review"
article, I met him.
The air...
The air around him was different.
That was the only way to put it.
You bastard...
You made me violent!
You think you're God?
Do you think you're God, huh?
Hey, Shizuo, let's go.
Gotcha.
What's the next place?
The teacher who can't keep
his hands off his students.
OK.
W-Wow...
He brought back the purity that
I felt when I was young,
back before I started spending my days
writing for third-rate gossip magazines.
Curiosity...
Yes, a strong sense of curiosity was what
made me want to know everything
about the strongest man.
But the mess afterward made
me postpone my article.
I don't know the incident's details,
but the whole town felt like it was
haunted with little demons.
Something was about to happen.
And the strongest man would
somehow be involved.
When I started my article on 'bukuro again,
I decided to gather information
from the people around him.
Oh, Shizuo!
I'm his friend!
Want some salmon roe?
I didn't order it.
Shizuo is friend! He is friends with me.
Thank you very much!
Is he talking like this deliberately?
My Conversation with Russian
Sushi Employee, Simon
Strongest?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You've never seen him fighting or anything?
Fighting is bad!
Peace is good!
Observe, don't clam up.
Oh, clam sounds nice.
One order of clam!
Um, well...
Come on, mister.
Simon's a pacifist, so you can't
talk with him about fighting.
No, I just wanted to know
who the strongest is.
Then you should ask a specialist.
If you really want to know...
Shiki of the Medei Awakusu
The strongest in Ikebukuro?
Yes. I was told you might
know something about it.
You know, the age of street-fighting is over.
We use our heads now, not our bodies.
That's right.
We work clean.
Clean.
Of course, if you let them
screw with you, it's over.
So if someone screws with us
or threatens our families,
whether they're a little kid,
or they pull a knife or a gun,
we erase 'em.
But you know,
the ones who fight in this
town aren't pros like us.
They're all little kids.
Yeah, like the Dollars and
the Yellow Scarves.
Well, as long as they don't
screw with our business,
we leave them alone.
Lately, there's been some weird
urban legend shit out there,
like the Slasher and
the Headless Rider...
Lemme see... The strongest in
Ikebukuro would probably be...
Heiwajima Shizuo.
You think so, too, huh?
I'm told he fights straight.
Either way, there's an information broker
who knows more than we do.
Really?
Would you introduce me?
While we're on the subject, big guy,
this article of yours...
You know how it is.
So, who told you about me?
Conversation with Shinjuku Information Broker,
Orihara Izaya
Well, um... I can't really
reveal my sources...
Whatever.
"Tokyo Year in Review," right?
You guys do reports on weird crimes and gangs,
and your next issue's on Ikebukuro.
If you know that much already,
then that makes this easier.
Actually, I'm planning on writing about
the strongest person in Ikebukuro.
The strongest, huh?
There are a bunch of strong
people in that town.
The sushi-seller Simon would be the
strongest in a hand-to-hand fight.
Shizu-chan would be the strongest
in a street fight.
Sh-Shizu-chan?
Heiwajima Shizuo. You came
to ask about him, right?
Yes. Well, this Shizuo-san...
I don't like it.
I'm the only one who needs
to know about him.
I try to know about him 'cause
he's trouble for me.
And that bugs me,
and I don't want to talk to him.
Is there any way...
By the way, Niekawa-san,
how's your daughter?
As a parent, you must be worried that
she transferred over such a thing.
Wha-
Six months ago, you talked
to Shizuo and ended up
flying through the air with
the greatest of lampposts.
You sniff around too much, and it might
cause problems with my work.
What are you...
I'm sure you know this,
but right now, a lot of dangerous
stuff's going down in Ikebukuro.
Like the war between the Dollars
and the Yellow Scarves.
There's that, and then there are the
Slasher attacks that brought it on.
The Slasher...
There's an uncontrollable urban legend
out there that I don't need anymore...
Oh, I know.
Talking about Heiwajima Shizuo...
I'll introduce you to a friend of his.
The information broker, Orihara, introduced
me to a surprising person.
Oh, and here's a warning for you.
Don't talk about Shizu-chan's
brother in front of him.
Wish you'd told me that six months ago.
His mention of my daughter
caught me off-guard.
I have a daughter who's in her
second year of high school.
I've lived with her since my wife ran off.
To be honest, I don't believe
she thinks much of me.
She's the reason I started writing
articles just for the money.
Hello, I'm the transporter, Celty.
Conversation with Transporter Celty
Um...
Yes, Shizuo is a good friend of mine.
But he'd be scary if you got him mad.
Actually, I'm researching who'd be
the town's strongest in a fight.
Your magazine seems to like that kind
of thing. Ranking gangs and stuff.
Ah, I suppose so.
Anyway, there are some people
who say you're the strongest...
You're laughing, aren't you?
No way. Shizuo's way stronger than I am.
It's pretty scary how dangerous he is.
I dunno. It's not really any kind of skill.
He's like a wolfman or a
devil or something.
An alien?
Oh, no...
I've got little grey trauma.
Anyhow, it's like the way that, no matter
how good the martial artist,
a shot to the head and it's over.
He's like that handgun.
It's impossible to compare him to anything.
I was moved.
This urban legend put what I'd felt, meeting
Heiwajima Shizuo, into words perfectly.
That's right. His strength
is on another level.
The adrenaline in his brain probably
brings out incredible power.
For a single instant, his power surpasses
human limits. It's truly incredible.
I understand.
By the way, this is just
me being curious...
What's up?
Could you show me what's
under your helmet?
Um, you don't really have to...
No, that's impossible.
That's right.
Miss Celty must be a magician.
Once I got my nerves together,
I continued my interviews.
All I heard about was the Dollars
and the Yellow Scarves.
The Dollars continued to ignore
the Yellow Scarves.
People said that the Yellow Scarves's leader,
the "General," might make a move.
Who is he, I wonder.
We dunno.
I doubt even the young turks
of the Yellow Scarves know.
The rumors say that only the
veterans have seen him.
The leader of the Yellow Scarves
gave his men strict orders to do one thing,
to stay away from Orihara Izaya.
Could he be the strongest man?
The Yellow Scarves seemed to attribute
the Slasher attacks to the Dollars.
A few days ago, one high school
girl was unharmed in an attack.
She made me think of my own daughter.
A father, protecting his daughter from
the Slasher, risking his life...
But...
I'm an alien who doesn't understand
her right now.
No.
Today, I'll face my beloved daughter...
<Kanra> Did you hear?
The guy the Slasher attacked was a
reporter writing a "Year In Review"
article for Tokyo Warrior.
<Tanaka Tarou> A magazine writer?
<Setton> Really?
<Kanra> Have I ever lied to you?
<Setton> Is he okay?
<Tanaka Tarou> Setton-san, do you know him?
<Setton> No...
I'm a fan of his.
<Tanaka Tarou> Really? I'll check him out.
Scary, though.
<Setton> The cops need to do their job.
<Saika-san has joined the channel>
<Kanra> They're here!!
<Tanaka Tarou> Hu-
<Setton> h?
<Saika> Cut
<Saika> Cut!
<Saika> Cut today
<Kanra> I'm the one who wants to cut you.
<Saika> But, no... I still love strong people
<Setton> How ya doing, Saika-san?
<Kanra> It's useless, Setton-san.
Saika won't respond to us.
<Saika> I'm sure I have to cut.
<Tanaka Tarou> Creepy.
Talking about cutting people and stuff...
Maybe she's the Slasher!
<Kanra> That's funny.
<Saika> Strong people
I want to love them
I found it.
My goal
To love
I found it
<Saika> Shizuo.
<Setton> What?
<Saika> Heiwajima Shizuo.
<Tanaka> What?
You know Shizuo-san?
<Saika> Heiwajima Heiwajima Heiwajima
Shizuo
Love
Cut
I and Shizuo
Cut Shizuo
Love
Mother's wish, Heiwajima
Heiwajima, mother's wish, cut
Love, Heiwajima
Love, Shizuo, mother's wish
Shizuo
<Saika-san has left the channel>
"Happy Birthday, Anri"
Eat up, Anri.
You'll get fat, Anri.
It's fine. I'll exercise.
I'm kidding.
Eat all you want.
Now we'll be together forever,
mother, father...
Every night, the girl had a dream.
A happy family, a perfect family.
But it was a failed illusion.
Five years ago, her parents
died in a horrible incident.
But even now, alone,
she still dreams...
Of the happy family
she'll never have.
Of the tragedy in which she lost her family.
It was the first time the Slasher
appeared in this town.
Anri, you sure it's OK to be
getting ready for field day?
Y-Yeah.
She knew she was an unfair person.
She knew exactly what the teacher was
up to, but she didn't stand up to him.
She simply withdrew into herself
and waited for it to pass.
The Slasher might come after you again.
It's dangerous to go alone!
More sexual harassment?
She knew that she was a parasite,
feeding off them.
Here's the coward.
Sorry. You were waiting?
Waiting so long, we thought we'd fossilize!
Sqrt 3.
Square root?
What do you mean, square root?
Give me a -20 or something
I can understand.
Next thing I knew, I was in a hospital bed.
It's OK.
If you stay still for a while, you'll be fine.
You need about a week in the hospital...
I couldn't remember things.
No, you can't get up yet!
I don't have time.
Niekawa-san!
See you!
See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
I would watch her.
The voice inside me said to.
Niekawa-san, in room five, isn't back yet!
What a problem...
I hope his wounds don't reopen.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Shizuo, I appreciate it, but you
don't have to come with me.
This is my problem.
There's no guarantee the Slasher
will show up tonight, at all.
Man, I hate that goddamn Slasher!
Who cares if it's a cursed
blade or whatever...
If it's a sword, it'll die if I snap it in two.
I'll kill it, whether it dies or not.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Calm down, Shizuo... There's no need
to deal with these guys right now.
You need something, pill bug?
We're talking to the cockroach over there.
Listen, looks can kill.
Huh?
There's at least a 0.0000000000000000000675%
chance that a curse or a stare can kill someone.
The hell you say?
Huh, bartender?
Bartender...
No way.
So if you glare at someone, you
can't complain if they kill you!
Niekawa Haruna...
Why did he respond that way...
Hey, you.
It's eleven o'clock.
You're a student, so go home.
I'm sorry.
I'll go straight home.
You OK?
Want us to take you home?
Um, well... Uh...
110 call, reporting several youths involved
in a fight, in East Ikebukuro Central Park.
Head straight to the scene. Over.
Roger.
Responding now.
Kuzuhara-san, let's go.
Sorry, miss.
If you want, you can wait at the police
box, and I'll take you home.
Stop it!
Stop using random kanji for things
and thinking it makes you badass!
You're at the age when you want to look at
things differently than others,
aren't you, Yumacchi?
And stop thinking that if you try doing
things in a way that most adults hate,
that kids in their rebellious
phase will like it!
It's so silly how people try to look cool
by criticizing society or ideologies.
You don't often say bad things about books.
Whatcha reading?
A book he once published on his own.
I was asleep, so I shouldn't talk, but
one of our guys was taken down.
Pay attention and gather information.
But this time, unlike with Kazutawno,
it was someone we don't know,
even if it was someone from the Dollars.
You should have some empathy, damn it.
I want to cry, but it's closed.
I want to hate the Slasher,
but it's closed.
Why'd you guys join the Dollars, anyway?
You want to live a peaceful life?
I'm going to get a green-haired
foreign daughter and
then come back and live happily,
next to three beautiful sisters.
What a wonderful life that would be.
Yotsuba&!? Yotsuba&!?
Come to think of it, this is where
the Slasher showed up.
Yeah. She's being careless.
Girls like that will get attacked.
Yeah, might be bad.
What's wrong?
That guy had red eyes.
No, it's nothing.
Just a bit of trauma coming back.
What am I doing?
Togusa!
Yeah!
Ram 'em.
What's wrong?
Where are you going, Celty?
He dead?
You're awful, Kadota-san!
I just said I wanted a peaceful life!
It was our only choice.
Self-defense, anyway.
Run!
The Headless Rider... And Shizuo?
Dotachin, look!
Is he a monster?
You're Heiwajima Shizuo?
I've wanted to meet you, Shizuo.
Heiwajima Shizuo.
I love you so, so, so much, Shizuo!
Fine.
I'll kill you.
That's right, Heiwajima Shizuo.
I'll interview him and write this article,
and everything will be fine.
My daughter will come back,
and things will be fine
between us again.
Just like they used to-
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
That should have ended
the Slasher incidents.
But they weren't over.
Instead, it was the beginning of her fate.
It was a long, long night.
Next time:
Mutual Love.