When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Hey! Nagi!
I'm here to visit ya!
Jump! Jump, Tama!
What the heck are you doing?
Oh, Saku. As you see, I'm giving Tama exercise.
Exercise?
She just saw a circus on TV,
where animals jump through a ring of fire.
And she says it's a perfect exercise for Tama.
There you have it.
Now jump! If a cat in a circus can do it,
then there's no reason you can't!
You moron!
What was that for?
There's no way he can possibly jump through that small ring!
And, animal abuse is more of a problem than copyright violation stuff.
Don't you know that it's constantly discussed during plot meetings?
Even if one or two scriptwriters were sacked,
it's not like the main heroine would get her seat taken away.
Um, both of you, borderline conversation like that is not appreciated.
There, there. You don't have to be scared anymore.
Hey! Don't side with Saku!
You're my pet!
Wow, I didn't know Sakuya-san
was good at taking care of animals.
Not just animals.
Right, Nagi?
Wh-Why are you asking me?
She's right. Nagi likes Sakuya-san like a real older sis-
Stop it Maria!
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
Is it one of those youthful indiscretions?
Shut up!
So you used to call Sakuya-san "Saku-neechan" when you were little, Milady?
It's a horrid past.
I have lots of younger siblings.
So I used to take care of Nagi along with them.
She used to be very cute when she was little.
She would always have Sakuya-san-
I told you not to say anything!
Nagi never took care of little kids,
so she's a brat no matter how much she grows.
Don't make fun of me.
If I had younger siblings, then I could take care of them better than Saku.
Are you sure? Then prove it.
You got it.
Hey, Hayate!
Yes?
W-Why did I end up in one of these getups again?
He's adorable!
Be glad. You look great, Hayate.
I'm not happy at all!
And first of all, why am I dressed in girl's clothes?
Don't worry about that detail.
I will take care of you from now on.
Take your chance to be spoiled by me.
But what exactly can I do?
You don't get it, do you?
All you have to do is say,
"Nagi-oneesama," and come cling to me.
Nagi-oneesama!
What's wrong?
Y-You...
Pervert!
How dare you do that and take advantage of the situation!
I don't remember raising you like that!
Forgive me, Milady.
I mean, Nagi-oneesama.
So, debt-ridden butler. It's not easy taking care of Nagi, is it?
It's as usual.
It didn't go right because we don't have an actual kid.
A real child, you say?
Yes. And there are forests and jungles
in this property that kids may have gotten lost in.
Hayate! Go find some at once!
That's a little...
I have something like this, too.
R-Right away!
She's a spoiled brat.
But what's Hayate-kun going to do?
She asked for a real child, but...
It might boil down to him having to kidnap someone.
Here they are.
Eh?!
SFX: EH?!
What does this mean?
You didn't really go kidnap them, did you?
You got it wrong. Please calm down, Sakuya-san.
Lost children?
Yes. They were walking around the gate,
so I took them into custody.
They are here on a family trip and got separated from their family.
It's not Isumi-san we're talking about, so how did they get lost here?
We need to contact the police.
No, we don't want to go there!
Even if they say no...
You don't have to be afraid.
They wouldn't come attacking on I*grams all of a sudden.
The Special ******* Section wouldn't mobilize for lost kids!
Don't bother.
Milady?
We were in need of children.
We'll take care of them here for a while.
Don't be an idiot! It's not like getting a pet, so you can't do that.
Thank you, very rich Onee-chan.
Rich Onee-chan.
Look, they're so cute.
What are your names?
I'm Itsuki.
I'm Shunji.
Nice to meet you, very rich Onee-chan.
Hayate! Looks like I have the tendency to be liked by children.
But their parents must be worried about them right now.
Don't worry about that.
SPs! Come!
Listen! In the name of the Sanzenin SPs,
find these children's parents!
Yes, Ma'am!
Don't worry. I'll get you two back with your parents right away.
T-Thank you.
But take your time.
We're not in that big of a rush.
You two are my little brothers from now on.
So I'll take good care of both of you.
Really?
What will you do for us, rich Onee-chan?
Come on, now. Call me Nagi-oneesama.
Yes, Nagi-oneesama.
What's the matter, Sakuya-san?
Wha-
Why?
I was thinking about something.
You didn't have to smack me.
Now...
I said I'd take care of them, but what exactly should I do?
Nagi-oneesama, how much is the vase?
That's only ¥10,000,000.
What about this picture?
That's got to be under ¥30,000,000.
Wow!
Hey, Nagi!
What do you want, Saku?
I just wanted to drop off my stuff.
Sure, go ahead, I don't care.
It's my more-expensive-than-junk valuables that were just lying around, so don't you dare touch them.
I'm not interested in your stuff.
All right then.
Okay. I'll show you two even more amazing treasure!
Treasure?
We want to see it!
Read anything you want!
This is the treasure?
What's wrong? They're all valuable rare doujinshi.
It doesn't seem that different from what she does when she's alone.
You're right.
Looks like you two still don't get it.
Look! There are only 200 copies of this in this world.
It contains *******'s final episode-
You idiot!
What was that for, Saku?!
How do you call this taking care of them?
You're dealing with kids, so there's got to be other things to do!
Like reading books to them.
That's a pain.
Get rid of the face! The kids'll copy it.
Besides, this room is for doujinshi.
There are no books for kids here!
You're wrong to begin with then!
Give something more entertaining for them!
Something kids enjoy?
I know!
Do you two like animals?
Animals?
We do!
What's wrong? You said you like animals, so I brought him.
Get to playing with him.
There's a danger of them getting eaten before they get to play.
You're right.
You idiot!
What's your problem, Saku?!
You two want to get out of this room ASAP, right?
We do! We do!
What selfish kids.
Then I'll take them to the game room next.
Hold on!
It's better for the kids to play outside rather than staying inside.
You're not the one to make a decision.
I said I'll take care of them.
I want to go outside!
I want to play outside!
Majority wins.
Takoute kanawan wa.
Takoute kanawan wa. = It's so damn expensive.
Wahhoi! Wahhoi!
Wahhoi! Wahhoi! = Wahoo! Wahoo!
Hey!
I'm the king of MMOs, so why must I play such a retro game?
She doesn't have any stamina, does she?
Shut up! Besides, it's your idea, so why are you taking a seat?
Hey!
Slow poke Nagi!
Come get us if you can!
Damn those brats. Repaying kindness with ingratitude...
Call me Onee-sama!
Milady, do you want me to switch places?
Butt out!
I will catch them no matter what it takes.
One...
Two...
She really hates to lose, doesn't she.
Three...
Four...
It is very like her.
Five...
Six...
She hasn't changed at all from when she was little.
Seven...
Eight...
She was afraid of strangers.
Nine...
She hardly spoke with me in the beginning.
Ten...
She was surrounded with adults who just wanted the estate, so I understand her situation.
Hey!
Wanna go off on an adventure?
I'm okay.
Just come.
It was little by little, but she started to hang out with others.
I see.
Ninety-nine...
One hundred!
All right...
Wh-What's going on?
Excuse me.
Would you happen to be these children's mother?
Mother?
I don't have children!
Not only can I not take the next step with the boy I like...
I only held his hand...
Oh, the lap pillow, too.
Hold on.
What are you making me say?!
Th-This is from Ogikubo station.
Still unable to find anyone like them.
Over.
Negative around Mitaka station.
Negative around Ooizumi Gakuen.
Negative at Anime Town Kamiigusa.
Keep searching!
Search around every station out there!
I'm beat.
That was so much fun.
It feels good to play outside, too, doesn't it?
I wasn't playing.
I was only taking care of them.
But...
It's nice to have siblings.
Nagi...
All right.
Let's do this! I think I can do it this time!
You're not thinking...
I will now make a special meal for you!
Are you sure, Milady?
Maybe we should lend a hand, too.
No. Don't worry.
I won't make the mistakes I made before.
Be good boys and wait, okay?
Yeah.
Okay, it's ready.
Sorry for the wait, Itsuki, Shunji.
Hold on a moment.
Say "Ahh".
Ahh.
I knew it.
Are you all right, Milady?
I am, Hayate.
I can't let it end like this.
With the next Sanzenin's leader's pride on the line!
Hey, let's go.
You can't improve cooking through willpower, alone.
Y-Yeah.
I'll help you, too.
Yes. Thank you.
Oh boy.
Hey, where did they go?
She said this is a valuable treasure.
Onii-chan, let's stop this.
This is wrong.
What are you saying now?
We snuck into a rich family for this.
B-But...
I knew it was something like this.
You two smelled really suspicious from the beginning.
It doesn't hurt me at all for you to steal something that insignificant.
But...
If you do anything to make
my buddy cry, I won't forgive you.
She's scary.
Hey!
What's going on?
Stop you two!
What's the matter, Sakuya-san?
I'll fill in the details later! We need to chase them!
Yes.
How is it?
Maria!
You did well.
Hey. It's really ready this time.
Where did Itsuki and Shunji go?
Now that you mention it, Hayate-kun's missing, too.
Those two were...
I bet there's a story behind it,
but they got away before I could ask.
Maria-san!
What's the rush, both of you?
Well...
Did something happen, Saku?
N-Nagi!
Well, those two turned out-
You moron! Don't say it!
Those two? Is something wrong with Itsuki and Shunji?
They're...
A robber just snuck in.
And took the two away.
What?
Maria. Itsuki and Shunji are safe, right?
They'll come back, right?
Don't worry. The security robots will find the robber.
We need to find them before the security robots get them.
Sakuya-san, why did you tell them that?
If Nagi hears the truth, she'll get hurt.
Sakuya-san...
And I'm worried about them, too.
What should we do... This is turning out to be a big mess.
They're going to take us to the cops.
Intruders in sight!
Nii-chan!
We're done for.
Stop it!
Makita! Kunieda!
Are you two safe?
Y-Yeah.
Good grief.
You two better not go telling this to the others.
We're sorry. We'll give this back to you.
So don't turn us in to the police.
Don't worry. We won't hand you over to the police.
Really?
Yeah. And I'll give that to you two, too.
Take it as a gift.
But...
This is a real treasure, right?
Open it.
Saku! What happened?
Did you find the two?
No, I was seeing things.
They didn't get kidnapped.
Then...
Their parents came to pick them up.
What?
Apparently they had to go home immediately.
They wanted to say goodbye to you,
but they didn't even have the time for that.
My, what a rush.
I see.
But they were able to meet their parents.
Thank goodness.
Milady.
Cheer up, Nagi.
Saku.
You've got us.
Yeah!
It all took place on an autumn night when we thought the Sanzenin lady would never have to face a lonely moment again.
Next week, we'll fight against a super butler that looks familiar.
Why the heck?!
That's enough!
Strive to be bigshot comedians!
Why the heck?!
Make big bucks and become free of poverty!
That's enough!
Why the...
Kuzuha-sama. It is now autumn.
Indeed.
I can't control my appetite.
I agree, Kuzuha-sama.
Come, Mysterious Dark Butler Three!
Bring-
Ayasaki Hayate to us!
It's a dead heat!
It's getting exciting!
The speed!
The liveliness!
The four tires heat up the motor!
That's all there is to the fastest hobby in the world, Minicar *******.
Don't lose! Keep going, my Emp****!
The next corner's where it's decided!
I must find out the mystery behind these strange situations.
Um, who are you?
Dash.
I'm the Mysterious Butler, Mini Yon.
Due to a certain person's request, I'm here to defeat you.
"M-Mysterious"?
Oh I get it. That's the situation they're setting up.
And so, who is this certain person?
Are you curious?
That person is...
Oh no! We have trouble up ahead!
We have a storm blowing into the race!
Will both cars be blown off of the course?
At this rate...
Go!
Goal!
First in is Ayasaki Hayate-kun's machine!
Hayate Magnum!
I did it!
Damn it.
The next race is mine!
Congratulations, Ayasaki Hayate-kun.
Thank you very much.
Wait. I got carried away by the flow again.
But I did find one thing out.
Someone is after me.
What are you saying now?
Nishizawa Ayumu's Butler Network!
Hey there. It's Nishizawa Ayumu.
How are you all?
I'm in charge of this section for a while now.
The song you're hearing right now, don't you think it's nice?
It's fitting for a maiden in love, don't you think?
I want you all to remember it
and sing it when you go out for karaoke.
I'm not sure if it'll be in the machine to play though.
You're the burglar hamster!
Right, you were today's guest, weren't you?
I heard I could meet Hayate-kun if I came here.
I heard he'll be late today.
Too bad for you.
Gahhh!
Bye bye.
I heard Isumi is on her way to the mansion.
Alone, too.
Alone?
Please save us!
No! I can't! I can't hallucinate in the middle of a city.
Calm down, Sakuya.
This fish is not an entity from your hallucinations.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Welcome Demon Hunter Isumi, and Nabeshin.
Who is that afro man?
Did you know that Nabeshin can't handle hot food?