What? How to lose weight?
I wouldn't know, since I really haven't done any dieting.
No way! How come? You're so thin!
Let's do this.
Yeah.
I guess I just have a good metabolism.
Wow, metabolism...
I'm so jealous.
Kawashima has really become the
centre of attention among the girls.
Yeah.
If you push yourself too hard, you'll just be piling up stress.
Maintaining a good balance between eating what
you want and eating healthily is probably the best.
Now that I just can't ignore!
What's going on?!
What are you-
H-Hey! Let me go!
What's going on?
Take that, and that! And some of this!
Teacher! Kawashima-san's hiding her flab!
It's customary to bring only up to 300 yen's worth of meat for trips!
Is this only 300 yen's worth of excess flab?
Bananas like these don't fit in the meat category!
This here is from meat buns!
Here is the expensive ice cream!
And here's the American dark cherry!
Take this! Divine fist of convenience stores!
High...!
...calo...!
...ries!
I dedicate this to the tears of the dieting warriors that have vanished along with the stardust.
Bye, then.
We really did it! The divine fist of convenience stores!
My, she was quite an admirable foe.
Those bastards!
A-Are you okay, Ami-chan?
That was really mean of them.
You poor thing.
Ah, um...
That was the first of many storms to come.
I see...
Coming out of nowhere, those two were so mean!
If you go about it like that, Ami ends up like this, huh?
Huh?
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
True Colours
That felt so good! Just what I'd expect from you, Minorin. Your performance was superb!
Girls are way too scary.
As a dieting warrior, I wasn't able to hold myself back.
As long as you face the fat head on,
you will obtain the grace of the god of weight loss.
I'm sure she'll understand this someday too.
Is that really how it works?
What's that guy doing here?
Oh, right.
Ryuuji, want me to make some salad for dinner tonight?
You make salad?
I learned how in primary school.
I can even make the dressing on my own.
First you buy the lettuce, right?
Then you separate the leaves and slice them up, right?
And then you put it on a plate. Pow, and it's done!
You didn't wash the lettuce, you didn't put it under running water,
and where did the dressing go?
Shut up about the trivial things, you nosy sister-in-law.
Sister-in-la-!
Takasu-kun!
What's wrong, Kawashima?
Please, can I stay with you for a moment?
That's the guy from earlier.
Hey, Kawashi-
You're-
Hey, how long do you intend to cling to him?
Completely ignoring my existence, sticking closely to him,
clinging onto him...!
Wait, Taiga! Now is not a-!
I'm scared, Takasu-kun!
You lewd exhibitionist woman!
Hey Kawashima, who was that?
It's not someone you know, right?
Ah, yeah. When you're a model, things like this happen sometimes.
It's like getting entangled with your fans, or well...
And here I even went and changed schools...
Huh?
Hey, you're going home now, right?
Well, yeah.
Could you hide me in your house for a little while?
Meeting him again would be scary...
So that's how it is.
If that's the case, then just leave it to me.
What?
Between a draughty, wooden, rented house, and an auto-locked,
high-security, expensive apartment, which would you prefer?
The expensive apartment!
It's decided, then.
Come to my place.
Why? Wait a minute, why does Ami-chan have to go to your place?
It's okay, I won't force you.
But keep in mind that Ryuuji's place is so
vulnerable that even I could easily sneak in.
Wha-?
Fine then, it's none of my business anyway.
W-Wait! Aisaka-san!
I'm telling you to wait already!
Oh well, whatever.
Here you go.
Way too sweet!
This is the honey-preserved kumquat that Ryuuji has been making a lot of.
I tried mixing it with soda.
Isn't it too thick?
Sheesh, making me drink this. Who's the dieting warrior, huh?
It's like your brain is the same size you are.
Man, you sure do change when you're like that.
It makes me want to show the people in our class how you really are.
Like I would ever show my true self to anyone.
I see.
Now, when you drink honey-preserved kumquat, your throat becomes nice and clear.
Huh?
You don't intend to show your true self?
Well then,
let's have you show off your fake self instead.
Thoroughly...
What?
Hey, good morning.
Good morning.
Kawashima, you look worn out.
Yeah, I couldn't shake off my exhaustion from yesterday...
Right, you went through a scary situation there.
Not that.
For roughly five hours in Aisaka Taiga's apartment... no, six hours...
Did Taiga do something to you?
Jackson.
Uganda.
Uganda?
Falcon.
Akechi Mitsuhide.
Matsumoto Seichou.
Oda Nobunaga singing French songs with enthusiasm...
Dazai Osamu cheering on Japan...
Huh?
Susano-o, Amaterasu, Uzume, Quetzalcóatl, Matthew, Judas!
H-Hey, are you okay, Kawashima?
Oh yes, I made her do a medley of 150 different imitations!
It was an incredible blast!
I can't even begin to guess how to imitate Akechi Mitsuhide.
I told her I'd throw her out if she didn't do what I told her to.
Then she frantically did my every bidding.
So cruel.
No, I'm thankful, Aisaka!
Kitamura?
K-Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, I have a favour to ask of you!
Ami-chan, you don't look so good.
Are you sure you shouldn't go to the infirmary?
I'm fine, really.
H-Hey.
Come, Stupid Chihuahua. It's feeding time.
"Stupid Chihuahua"?
Yes, you. Putting on a sweet and innocent act,
yelping all the time, and you're always in heat...
Either way, just come along.
Like I ever would.
Why should I come with you, huh?! I got plans with my frie-
Michael Jackson guiding a bus.
Mona Lisa attacking a corner at 200 kilometres an hour.
A happy 'The Thinker'.
I've already made copies of the pictures I took.
There's a chance they might accidentally get spread around.
Wha- Stop that!
Okay, fine! I just have to come along, right?! Damn you!
Um, Ami-chan?
I-I'm sorry!
I forgot I was going to eat lunch with Aisaka-san today.
I'm really sorry!
Hey you! Wait up!
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
What's this supposed to be?
If she keeps interacting with people just using her façade,
Ami won't make any real friends.
So I'm asking you two, who know her
true colours already, to take care of her.
You say that... I wouldn't mind,
but no matter how you look at it, the chemistry between Taiga and Kawashima's not really...
Aisaka!
Please! You're one of the very few
female friends that I can ask favours of!
Like I sai-
What?!
Oh, thank you, Aisaka!
That Kitamura... Pushing the trouble onto us and running off to the student council on his own...
W-Wow! Kushieda's lunch box is amazing!
It might look large, but this lunch box is super low on calories.
Look, these are king trumpet mushrooms, this here's konjac, and this is thread-konjac rice!
Sheesh, why do I have to do this?
Hey, Ami. I'll share some konbu with you.
I don't want the damn thing.
Aw, is that so...
How nice.
What?
Um, no... Right, lunch, gotta eat my lunch box.
Why does Takasu-kun's lunch box have the same side-dishes as Aisaka-san's?
Hey, why?
Um, you see, this is...
Now there's no problem, right?
My lunch box is a omelette and fried food lunch box, while Ryuuji's is a just a seaweed and rice lunch box.
Ah! My side-dishes!
Here, now Takasu-kun has a meatball-lunch box.
Thank you.
But why do you let Aisaka-san do whatever she wants all the time?
Do I really?
You see, Ryuuji was my dog in his previous life.
A dog's happiness is measured by how useful he is to his master.
Yes! These two are meant for one another, you see!
No, no way.
Geez, why do you do this, Minorin?
Sorry, I was kidding! Just kidding!
Geez.
Hey!
Everyone, please listen to me for a moment!
Today, we're having the customary neighbourhood volunteer cleaning rally that the student council organises every month,
but this time we're a bit short on hands.
Could any brave heroes that would like to participate, please come forward?
I'm sorry, Kitamura. Today, Super Kanoya has a special sale-
Oh, Takasu! You'll come along?!
Huh?
Go change and meet up in the school yard.
Sheesh, why do I have to?
Look, I'm taking responsibility and
coming along to participate with you.
That's what you're saying, but you just wanted to spend some more time with Kitamura, right?
You could say that.
How honest of you.
Takasu-kun!
I'm participating too. I just transferred, so I want to get more familiar with the school.
Huh?
Minorin.
As a dieting warrior, I just can't help but want to cheer on girls
who are desperately working up a sweat, trying to lose weight.
I never said that I wanted to lose weight or anything like that.
Let's do our best together, Takasu-kun!
Uh, okay.
All right, you punks! Put some heart into it, and let's move out!
Don't even dare to skip out on this, you bunch of scum!
Whoa there, calm down.
Are your work gloves on?!
Got your trash bag?!
Confirmed your assigned cleaning area?!
Yeah!
Don't take the town lightly.
With that level of guts you'll get tossed off this trip, you maggots!
Put some spunk into that reply, you cowards!
Yeah!
That's our president for sure.
All right, I'll explain the program. First...
After all that, Kitamura ended up going with the student council.
Sorry, the council staff is going a different way!
So why did I even...
Hey, doesn't this piece of trash look just like Aisaka-san?
I mean, look at it. It's so helplessly small!
Well, this piece of trash here looks just like Kawashima-san.
It's just as sodden, sloppy, and flabby as you.
Let's go the other way, Minorin.
Oh, we're eloping? Fine by me.
Let's get away from here.
Yeah! The trash is awaiting us!
Those two just bailed, didn't they?
The ones left behind should get along well, right?
Um...
Picking up trash can be pretty fun too.
Or maybe it's because I'm together with Takasu-kun?
Kawashima, look, I...
Hey, let's go that way next.
Watch ou-!
Hey, are you oka-?
Oh man, that's so filthy! What is this?!
What the hell is this?!
K-Kawashima?
Wow, that scared me. Geez, my shoe's all drench-
No!
Kawashima!
Ew, ew! Get it away!
Don't move!
Aah! It's climbing upwards!
Don't kick my face!
Ew! Ew!
Damn it!
Okay, salvaged!
Right, it's all okay now.
Look, the frog has gone back home. See?
I don't want to do this any more!
K-Kawashima?
Just kidding!
Did I fool you?
It's starting to rain.
Ew, I'll get wet.
We've got to find shelter from the rain. Right, Takas-?
Hey.
It's enough already, stop doing that.
Huh?
What are you talking about? I don't understand.
I'm the one who doesn't get it.
Why did you even bother coming out here to do this troublesome work?
You don't get it? I see...
So this approach doesn't work on Takasu-kun.
I've known about the act for a while now, you know.
You should be more, uh...
With a face like that-
You see, I...
I can't get by without this façade.
You really don't understand my feelings, do you?
Well, frankly...
That's okay.
I mean, I'm an airhead after all!
Kawashima?
What's wrong? Hey, Kawashima!
Hey, what's up all of a sudden?
If we're going to take shelter, we sho-
What are you doi-?
That's yesterday's...
Why is he here?
Well, to be honest,
that guy's a stalker.
Sta- Why didn't you say anything?!
It...
It's frustrating.
Frustrating?
I don't want to admit it...
That my life is being thrown into chaos by guys like him...
I moved away because of him.
I didn't want to cause trouble for my parents.
So I moved here on my own to live with my relatives.
I took a short break from my modelling job, yet...
Now I've been chased all the way to this town!
Hey! Hey! Takasu-kun! Kawashima-san!
Hey!
That's strange... They told us they went this way...
I don't care any more. Let's just go home, Minorin.
Whoa!
Cute, mini-sized monster spotted!
Wow, so cute! Lucky me!
"Monster"?
Taiga!
Watch ou-!
I don't recall having to be called
"monster" by suspicious people like you.
What is she doing? He's a stalker!
And besides, with whose permission are you taking pictures in the first place?
You're being really disgusting!
Why can't I? It's not like it's the end of the world.
Of course you can't.
I'll destroy that camera and its owner!
Why are you running away, huh?!
I told you to stop running!
W-Wait, Taiga!
That idiot...
Why?
Why isn't she scared?
I mean, that guy's a pervert!
Kawashima?
Why did I...
Why did I take a break from work, move out,
even change schools, all because of that bastard?
Getting all nervous, piling up stress, eating tons of candy...
This means that...
...Ami-chan's losing to that worthless bastard,
and to Aisaka Taiga.
Takasu-kun.
It's like you were saying earlier...
That I should stop putting on this façade.
You told me I should do that, didn't you?
Well, yes...
I got it now.
I got it.
I'm quitting the "Ami-chan" act.
I'll quit it, I'll quit it! And then...!
K-Kawashima?
And then I'll live on with this mean look!
I won't keep on getting beaten, either!
Hey!
Kawashima...
After that, Kawashima was amazing.
She ran through the town with a form that would've put even the track club to shame.
And then she recklessly smashed the
frightened stalker's camera to pieces.
The stalker was terrified by the extreme change.
And then...
You liar! With this demonic appearance...
You're not the Ami-chan that I know!
You're not an angel! Your personality is horrible!
What of it?
Ami-chan's cute either way.
Who cares about personalities?
Kawashima! Hey, are you all right?
Hey! Kawashima!
I did it, Takasu-kun.
I see.
But...
That was so scary.
Here, this'll warm you up.
This is honey-preserved kumquat.
I'm amazed you knew that. Taiga loves it.
"Taiga"? You call her by her first name, right?
You're still suspicious of that?
Isn't she great?
Self-centred, always in a mess,
and yet not even attempting to hide it...
And even so, she has friends. She's got Takasu-kun.
Takasu-kun, what would you do if I showed you the real me?
Huh?
Would you fall in love with me?
K-Kawashima...
Would you?
W-Wait just a moment...
I...
Taiga? Were they there?
Taiga?
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
Pool Opening Day
"Water-proof,
water-repellent design."
"Delicate gradation."
"One-touch
installation is possible."
How about this one, Taiga?!
Fake breast special force.