Why don't you tell the class your name?
Umm... I-I'm Akemi Homura...
I, uh... I-It's nice to meet all of you.
Homura Akemi
Akemi-san's been in hospital for some time due to a heart condition.
She hasn't been to school in quite a while,
so I'm sure she'll run into a lot of difficulties.
Make sure you all help her out, okay?
Which school did you come from?
Were you in any clubs?
Like sports, or art?
Your hair's really long.
It must be tough braiding it every morning.
I, uh...
Akemi-san, you need to go
to the nurse's office, right?
Do you know where it is?
Huh?
No...
I'll take you there, then.
I'm the health officer for this class.
Sorry, everyone,
but Akemi-san has to go to the nurse's office during recess to take her medicine.
Oh, really? Sorry for keeping you.
Talk to you later, Akemi-san.
Sorry about that.
They don't mean any harm.
They're just excited because we don't get many transfer students.
No, it's okay...
Thank you very much.
Hey, don't be so nervous.
We're classmates, after all.
My name's Kaname Madoka.
Call me Madoka.
I...
It's fine, really.
Do you mind if I call you Homura-chan?
People don't call me by my first name very often.
It's a really weird name.
What? That's not true.
It feels really exciting and cool.
I guess I don't live up to my own name.
You shouldn't say that!
You already have such
a wonderful name.
You should be cool to match it!
Find f(x).
Given that p is a prime number, and n an arbitrary natural
number, prove that (1+p)^p - n^p -1 is divisible by p.
All right, why don't you
try solving this one?
Given that p is a prime number, and n an arbitrary natural
number, prove that (1+p)^p - n^p -1 is divisible by p.
Oh, you've been away
from school, haven't you?
Why don't you ask a friend
.to let you copy their notes?
She got light-headed just from doing warm-ups? That's pretty bad.
She's been bedridden for half a year.
It's no surprise.
You should be cool to match it!
I can't do that. I'm not good at anything.
All I ever do is make trouble for others and embarrass myself.
Why?
Will I always be like this... forever?
It'd be better if you just
.died right now, wouldn't it?
Maybe it would.
Yeah. You should just die right now.
I should just... die...
Wh-Where... am I?
Izadel
What?
What is that?!
No!
That was a close one.
It's okay now, Homura-chan!
Yo-You're...
They're magical girls.
They hunt witches.
Our secret didn't last very long, huh?
Don't tell anyone else in class, okay?
Mami      Tomoe
Kaname-san, do you always fight those things?
Always? Well, Mami-san's the veteran here.
I actually just made my contract
with Kyubey last week.
But your performance today was a big
.improvement over before, Kaname-san.
Isn't it dangerous? You're not scared?
Well, it certainly is dangerous,
and we do get scared,
but the more witches we defeat, the more people we can save.
So it's worth it, right?
We need Kaname-san to become a full-fledged
magical girl before the Walpurgisnacht gets here.
I'll be going, then.
But...
But Tomoe-san just died.
That's why I have to go.
I'm the only one left who
.can stop the Walpurgisnacht.
But it's impossible! Nobody
could fight that thing alone!
You'll die too, Kaname-san!
I'm still a magical girl.
I have to protect everyone.
Please... let's just run away.
There's nothing else we can do.
No one would ever blame you.
Homura-chan, I'm really glad we became friends.
Even now, the fact that we made it in time to save you from that witch
is one of my proudest accomplishments.
So I'm glad I became a magical girl.
I don't regret it at all.
Kaname-san...
Goodbye, Homura-chan.
Take care of yourself.
No! Don't go, Kaname-san!
Why...
You knew you were going to die.
I wish you could have lived...
instead of saving someone like me...
Do you truly mean those
.words, Akemi Homura?
Would you be willing to trade
your soul for that wish?
If there's something you want badly enough
.to commit yourself to a life of battle, then...
I can be of help to you.
If I make a contract with you, can you really grant any wish I want?
That's correct.
It seems that you qualify.
Now tell me, what is the wish that will make your Soul Gem shine?
I...
I want to redo my first
.encounter with Kaname-san.
But this time, instead of
her protecting me,
I want to become strong
enough to protect her!
The contract has been made.
Your wish has prevailed over entropy.
Now, release your new power!
Where am I?
Leave
Hospital
Go to
School
I'm still in the hospital?
It wasn't a dream!
Why don't you tell the class your name?
I'm Akemi Homura.
.Nice to meet you all!
Akemi-san's been in hospital for some—
Homura Akemi
Kaname-san, I became a magical girl too!
So let's do our best together from now on!
Uh...
Here I go!
What do you think, Mami-san?
Time magic, huh?
It's pretty amazing,
but you're not using it right.
O-Okay...
How to Make Bombs
Patricia
Mami-san, now's our chance!
Okay!
Akemi-san, your turn!
R-Right!
I did it?
I did it!
You did it!
Well done.
Amazing!
That was amazing, Homura-chan!
What's wrong?
Hey, Kaname-san! Hang on!
Why...
What?
How...
How could this happen?
Leave
Hospital
Go to
School
I have to warn them.
We've all been fooled by Kyubey!
Uh, what would Kyubey gain by lying about something like that?
Well, um...
Are you trying to turn us against each other or something?
Wait, you're not working together with that Kyouko girl, are you?
N-No!
Sayaka-chan, now you're the one who's turning us against each other.
Either way, I'm against teaming up with her.
Mami-san and Madoka-san use
long-range weapons, so they're fine,
but I fight up close, and having bombs go off in my face is something I can live without.
How many's it gonna take
.before I get blown up too?
Akemi-san, do you have any other weapons besides explosives?
Shaft
Industries
I'll think of something.
Oktavia von
Seckendorff
What the hell are you?
What have you done with Sayaka?!
Sayaka-chan, stop it!
Please remember!
I know you never wanted to hurt anyone!
I'm sorry, Miki-san.
Sayaka... Damn it...
This is...
This is terrible.
It's too much.
Tomoe-san?!
If the Soul Gems give birth to witches...
then we have no choice but to die!
You, me, all of us!
Stop it!
No...
I can't take this any more!
It's okay.
We can do this together.
We'll beat the Walpurgisnacht,
just the two of us!
Okay.
I guess... this is the end for us too.
Do you have any Grief Seeds?
I see.
Hey... How about we become monsters together...
and lay waste to this awful world?
We'll wipe out everything...
all traces of evil or sadness...
and just destroy, destroy, destroy... until there's nothing left but dust.
Don't you think... that sounds nice?
I lied before.
I had one left.
You can't...
Why did you use it on me?
Because I need you to do something I can't.
You can travel back in time, right, Homura-chan?
You can change history so it doesn't end like this, right?
Yeah.
Could you save me from my stupidity...
before I get fooled by Kyubey?
I promise.
I'll save you, no matter what.
No matter how many times I have to try,
I swear I will protect you!
I'm glad...
Could I ask you... for one more thing?
Yeah.
I don't want to become a witch.
There are so many awful, sad things in this world...
but there are lots of things... worth protecting... too...
Madoka!
Homura-chan...
You finally called me by my first name...
I'm happy...
No one will believe the future.
No one can accept the future.
So I will...
Wh-Who's there?
Madoka, if someone should ever appear before you, promising you a miracle,
you must not succumb to temptation.
Huh?
Um...
I will never depend on anyone again.
I will never need anyone
.to understand me again.
I will never let Madoka fight again.
I will destroy all the witches by myself.
And this time, I will stop the
Walpurgisnacht with my own hands.
How awful!
There's nothing you can do.
It's too much for her to handle alone.
But this is terrible! It shouldn't be happening!
Madoka, don't listen to him!
It's all over if you give up.
But you have the ability to change fate.
This unavoidable destruction and sorrow...
You can change it all.
You have the power to do just that.
Can I really?
Don't be fooled! You're falling right into his trap!
Can I really do something to stop all of this?
Can I really change this ending?
Of course you can!
So, make a contract with me...
and become a magical girl!
No!
Madoka really was amazing when she transformed, wasn't she?
I had predicted she'd become the most powerful magical girl,
but I never would have imagined she'd
destroy the Walpurgisnacht with just one shot.
And did you know what would happen to her as a result?
It would've happened sooner or later.
As the strongest magical girl,
she took down her greatest enemy.
Naturally, after that, all that was left was for her to become the most terrible witch.
Kriemhild
Gretchen
In this form, I imagine it will only take her
.around ten days to destroy the entire planet.
Oh, well. What happens next is mankind's problem, not ours.
We've pretty much met our
.energy quota at this point.
Aren't you going to fight her?
No.
This is not my battlefield.
Akemi Homura, are you...
I'll do it over...
as many times as it takes.
I'll relive the same time over and over, searching for the one way out.
I'll find the one path that will save you from your fate of boundless despair.
Madoka... my one and only friend.
Homura-chan?
If it's... If it's for you,
I don't mind being trapped in this endless maze...
for all eternity!
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I still see it when I close my eyes
oshiyoseta yami
押し寄せた闇
I'll move forward as I cast off
furiharattesusumu yo
振り払って進むよ
this darkness engulfing me
MEGUCA
PRESENTS
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
How long will it be before
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I see that lost future again?
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
I'll walk upon this Earth,
nandodemo saite
何度でも裂いて
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
kono sekai ayundekou
この世界歩んでこう
as many times as necessary
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
toki wa ima hajimaritsuge
時は今始まり告げ
now tells of the beginning
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Let's open the once-closed door,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
with these unwavering feelings
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
muzukashii michi de tachidomatte mo
難しい道で立ち止まっても
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
sora wa kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
dakara kowakunai
だから怖くない
So I won't be afraid
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
Episode 10
I will never depend on anyone again
Illustrated by   Kuroe Mura
Did you really feel nothing while watching over those girls this whole time?
Didn't you at least try to understand how much they were suffering?
Episode 11
The one thing I have left to guide me
The one thing I have left to guide me.