Takasu-kun!
I'm...
going after her!
You go left!
I'll go right!
- Let's do this!
- Right!
Mr. President.
They're running in the halls.
I'll let it slide this once.
I'll chase her down...
and say what, exactly?
I don't know...
I haven't figured that out, but...
She's gone?
The entrance!
Taiga, can you hear me!?
Answer me, Taiga!
I'll tell you what you've
always wanted to know!
I'm also...
I'm also in love...
...with Takasu Ryuji!
And I've been in love with him
from the very beginning!
But...!
I felt I should let you have him!
'Cuz my best friend needed him so much!
But that was just my
pride getting in the way!
I...wasn't respecting you!
I already said no one but me
decides what'll make me happy!
But the same goes for you! Only you
can decide what makes you happy!
So!
So, Taiga!
Show me how you'd do things!
Kushieda!
I-I tripped...
Nurse's Office
Did it stop?
Uh-huh.
You scared me.
I thought you were crying.
You expected me to cry?
Well yeah, under normal circumstances...
Then I guess it was worth it.
Remember what I said about
working on what I can see?
Yeah, sure...
Well...
That determination is what keeps me going.
Determination?
Remember when I mentioned how I have
a brother who plays baseball?
I used to play, too.
Quite frankly, I have more talent.
But I couldn't continue because I'm a girl.
That's why I plan to save up money,
go to a college with a
good athletics program,
and then play softball on
an international level.
And then, I can declare
to the entire world—
"This is the happiness I chose
and achieved on my own!"
Maybe I'm just being stubborn.
Kushieda...
It gave me the determination to stop crying.
Because I decided to do my best,
no matter how difficult
or painful things get.
Still...
When someone sees me
struggle, suffer, or cry,
that helps to make this all feel worth it.
What happened to the hair clip?
Oh, it—
It was meant to be a present for
me on Christmas Eve, right?
- Well...
- Sorry.
At first, I had no idea.
I thought it was a present from Taiga.
I'd made up my mind to not
accept any gifts from you,
even if it meant I had to hurt your feelings.
I'm really sorry for wearing it in
front of you. Please forgive me.
Where is it right now?
In my room.
- But—
- It's okay.
I can't accept it.
You know...
There's one other thing I can see.
You love Taiga.
Yeah.
Good, Takasu-kun.
Then this is a giant...
good-bye.
Run toward what you can see!
Right!
Go, Takasu!
Ta-ka-su! Hey!
Ta-ka-su! Yes!
Ta-ka-su!
I knew you'd come.
H-How?
You have a pretty strong
sense of responsibility.
I knew you'd still come to work.
So...
About what happened...
I'm, uh—
I heard Minorin.
Don't laugh!
I'm not.
Please don't laugh.
I have something to tell you after work.
If...
If I try to run away, you have to catch me.
Please.
Right...
That job paid pretty well.
Yeah...
Uh...
You lied to me!
Ya-Yasuko...
Taiga!
What are you doing here?
Don't touch me!
Stop being so difficult!
What can you possibly
accomplish on your own!?
H-Hey...
Taiga?
You must be Takasu-kun.
Um, yes...
You have my gratitude for
taking care of her for so long.
She'll be staying with us—
I'll never stay with you!
Or your man!
Or that brat!
Wh-What's...?
What's going on?
I don't get it.
I'm the one who's confused!
You promised you wouldn't work!
But you lied and broke that promise!
That kind of behavior is unacceptable!
Unacceptable?
You're the one who took a
new job to pay my tuition!
And then you collapsed...
Of course I have to work!
What's wrong with that!?
We're family!
We're supposed to help each other!
I don't care what other families do!
I want you to focus on studying!
So you can figure out what you want
to do and live a respectable life!
Which one of us didn't study!?
Which one of us did whatever they wanted,
and failed to become a respectable person!?
That sounds like you, to me!
Ryu-chan...
Don't blame me for your mistakes!
I'm...
Taiga...
Taiga!?
Taiga!
Come back here, Taiga!
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Confession
My stupid old man's business
failed and he skipped town.
Seriously?
My mom said she'll take care of me.
But she has a new family of her own.
She's even pregnant.
Since her new man is tall,
they'll probably have a child
with really long legs,
leaving me to be the lone midget.
It...
It would be too hard for me to fit in.
My presence would make
everyone uncomfortable.
It was the same when I lived
with my stupid father.
Whenever I'm around, everybody gets...
That's how I've always felt, too...
If I'd never been born, Yasuko's life
would've been so much better.
She's still young.
She could go back to school...
Ryuji?
Grown-ups are so selfish.
Always forcing their
expectations onto others...
Though, maybe I was the one
taking advantage of Yasuko...
Because I'm just a kid.
Yeah...
If I didn't exist—
Ryuji!
Stop that, pighead!
Don't do anything rash!
H-Huh!?
Wh-What?
I think you're really confused here!
Stupid, idiotic moron!
Bald-headed freak!
What would that accomplish!?
It's idiotic to blame
yourself for everything!
Y-You were doing the same
thing a moment ago!
But I'm alive!
And it's because...you were there for me!
It didn't matter to me who you loved,
or who you decided to spend
the rest of your life with...
I didn't mind!
Because...all I wanted was
to be by your side!
That's why...
That's why you can never, ever talk
about wishing you'd never been born!
What happened!?
What are you doing!?
Wh-What happened, my ass!
Are you trying to kill me!?
Oh jeez, I would never.
I-It's freezing...
Like I said!
I'm sorry!
You never said that!
You're so hung up on the little things.
What's your blood type?
I'm a Taurus!
Oh, I don't know anything about horoscopes.
But Mongolian barbecue is good stuff.
Whatever!
In two months...
I'll be eighteen!
We can run away from Yasuko!
From everyone!
We can run far away, stopping only to sleep,
and we can keep running until my birthday!
And then!
You can marry me!
Then we'll be considered adults,
and no one can get in our way!
I'll give you the rest of my life!
I lo—
Hold it right there!
That's not fair!
Didn't I say I had something to tell you!?
You sneaky mongrel!
What's your problem!?
You're supposed to let the guy do the—
Let me go first!
I promised Minorin.
I'm going to show her my
way of doing things!
Th-Then let's...say it together.
I...
...lo—
Who would call at such an important time?
Just ignore it.
Let's continue.
It's really cold.
What are you talking about!?
You're ruining the moment!
Hurry up and answer it!
Y-Yeah, okay.
Hey, Takasu!
What're you guys up to?
Kitamura?
Your mothers have been calling all
over the place looking for you two!
Oh, forget it!
Just come to the place I tell you!
H-Hold on, Kitamura!
You got snot all over my hair!
Wha—
What happened to you?
Why are we meeting up at your place?
Your moms don't know about this place.
Plus, my relatives are out tonight.
Come in.
You'll catch colds if you stay wet like that.
Go shower.
End of the hall, on the right.
Here, take these.
Never expected you to
care so much about me.
Please...
Thanks.
Wait, Taiga!
Your shoes!
Man...
Kawashima?
Oh, nothing.
Yusaku said he's bringing
a change of clothes for you.
Sorry about all this...
And thanks.
Hey...
You're in love with Taiga, right?
Wh-What are you talking about!?
Well, aren't you?
Y-Yeah...
Say it.
Wh-What's up with you?
Why should...?
Say it.
I love Taiga.
Look at you, bragging!
You forced me to say it!
Taiga!
You had me so worried!
You itty bitty, teensy weensy fool!
Minorin! Minorin! I'm so sorry!
Sorry about all the trouble we've caused.
No worries.
Anyway, what's your plan now?
Well...
We...
We're going to elope.
Huh?
We're completely serious.
Whaaaaaaaat!?
I see...
You just have to hold out for two months...
Why are you going along with this!?
You can't run off and get married!
You're being too dramatic!
It's only till Ryuji turns eighteen...
Then we can—
And where are you going to stay?
U-Uh, well...
Business hotels or manga cafes, to start.
And what, you'll live like that forever!?
No, we plan on coming back...
You think you'll be able to?
If they send out search parties,
the whole school will know.
You might get expelled.
Well...
You see...
Everything I've ever wanted has fallen apart,
so I decided long ago that
I didn't want anything at all.
But now my feelings are being reciprocated...
My wish came true.
So I want to break that jinx.
No, I have to break it.
That's why... That's why...
This passbook is nice and warm.
It holds all the money I've earned
from working odd jobs.
What's this?
Takasu-kun. Taiga.
I don't think you're doing the
right thing, by any means.
I can't support your actions.
Minorin...
But if this is your way of doing things,
I won't object to it.
Please take this.
You can pay me back one day.
Here.
It's the key to my beach house.
You've been to it before, so you
should know how to get there.
Kawashima...
Don't forget me.
Rice Voucher
Please accept these.
Thanks, guys.
Well, Ami...
Thanks for all your help today.
Heya, good show!
I need to have a little chat with Amin.
Why would I chat with you?
Oh, you made up!
That's great, Dumb-chi!
Get out of here.
You should, too...
Well, Minorin, Dumb-chi.
Bye for now.
We'll definitely see you again!
Yep.
Bye.
Oh, wait...
What do you want to talk about?
- Man...
- And get your hands off of me!
I'm so drained I can't even stand...
Hey, what are you...?
What?
You wanted me to watch you cry?
Tears just mean that your
heart's got a nosebleed.
But why are you crying?
Because Takasu-kun took Taiga from you?
- Or is it...?
- I don't know...
I had...
I had decided not to cry anymore...
Pathetic.
But I've learned something.
If you trip as you run through
the halls, your nose bleeds.
If you trip as you run through life, you cry.
Are you stupid?
We're way too young to wax
philosophic about life.
We still have at least ten, twenty,
or sixty years ahead of us.
Run out as soon as you've got everything.
Don't let Ya-chan—
Don't worry, I can handle this.
- Later.
- Wait!
Um...
Yeah!
Bring a hair dryer.
My stuff will be heavy enough as it is.
Yeah, I got it.
Don't bring too many frilly clothes, then.
They'll just take up space.
I know that!
Come out as soon as you're done.
Call me right away if anything happens.
I will. In a heartbeat.
I'm home!
She's not back yet?
In—
Inko-chan!?
Yasuko...
For Ryu-chan
This is where your grandparents live.
If you show them this watch,
they're sure to take you in.
Hmm? Mirano-san?
Vaisravaṇa Bar
She called earlier this evening to say
she won't be coming in for a while.
She...ran away.
What is she, a kid?
If I run away, it won't matter when
my birthday comes around.
I'll still be a kid on the inside.
Woo-hoo!
Check it out!
Chocolates!
Weren't you showing those off yesterday?
Eat the damn things.
How long are you gonna
wave that in front of us?
Uh, right up to the expiration date?
Honestly, weren't you the one who said
school isn't for exchanging chocolates?
There isn't any exchanging going on.
I brought this with me.
Right, Taiga?
Er, what?
She's absent.
So is Takasu-kun.
What?
They catch a cold together?
More like a fever, I'd say.
Fight on! Fight on! Fight on! Fight on!
- Ohashi! Fight on! Fight on!
- Hey there.
You sure about not sending them off?
Pardon me?
I can't hear you!
Not even Little Miss Musclehead can bear...
being dumped by both
Taiga and Takasu-kun.
Hey!
Do I look like I want to
have a snowball fight?
Damn you...
Taste my Pure and Innocent Ball attack!
Damn it!
I'm putting a rock in mine!
Since we're eloping and all,
I went with big-boy snacks.
See?
Chocolate cigarettes and
extra-spicy rice crackers.
- And even...
- Same here.
I made lunch.
See?
You're supposed to buy train station
boxed lunches when you elope.
I'll still eat it, though.
Did your mom say anything?
She only cares about what other people think.
Doubt she'll make any fuss.
And what about Ya-chan?
Nope...
Nothing much.
I should've said this before...
When Ya-chan called me a member of
your family, I got all warm and fuzzy inside.
You know how my family is...
So I was ready to become part of yours...
Think Ya-chan will cry?
Oh, but it's not going to be that bad!
This isn't good-bye!
I'm not saying I don't want to elope...
I think it's a wonderful idea...
- But...
- Yeah, you're right.
Hey, Taiga...
D-D-Dear!
Takasu
D-D-D-D-D-Dear!
I certainly recognize this...
Then you must be...
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I am your grandson, Takasu Ryuji!
And this is my bride!
I have a favor to ask!
We aren't going to run away...
Ryuji showed me his way of doing things.
Now it's my turn.
Hey, Ryuji?
Don't laugh.
And don't get mad.