It's about to leak out.
Telephone
Emergency announced!
The mission of Confir... ming the Protection of Circuits for Direct Communication of Orders to Head... quarters under Highly Ur... gent Circum... stances.
W-What a long name!
It's a very important mission.
If failed, every one of us may be punished.
Under certain conditions, a level-1 warning will be issued and the whole military will be put on alert.
Right, right. We have a super-important responsibility.
W-What is the mission?
It is...
...answering the phone.
You know that this phone is connected to Headquarters in the capital, right?
Has it rung yet?
Not yet.
Right. Luckily, it rarely rings.
Could it be...?
Right. Though we'll be in trouble if it rings,
if it doesn't ring when we really need it to, we'll be in even more trouble, right?
That is why the phone is tested every half year; to see if it's connected properly.
It's called...
C-Con... well...
Please remember it, okay?
The command communications line for high-level... What was it?
That is wrong.
The mission of Confirming the Protection of Circuits for Direct...umm?
The mission of Confirming the Protection of Circuits for Direct Communication of Orders to Headquarters under Highly Urgent Circumstances.
Yeah.
Yes, yes yes yes!
Please, let me accept this mission!
I've always wanted to try to make a call on the phone!
You're that excited?
The basic operation is the same as the Takemicaduchi intercom system.
The only difference is the longer distance.
But it's so great!
It's so wonderful to be able to talk with people that far away!
Well, yeah. It feels unbelievable to talk to people that you can't even see.
Well, it's nothing if you're used to it.
But unfortunately, we don't know when they are going to call today.
Do you still want to accept the mission?
Of course!
Good.
Then you should stick by the phone today.
Ring ring...
This is Private Sorami Kanata of Fortress 1121, Helvetia Army!
Then, when the phone call is over, return it to its original position, on top.
Good.
F-Feli...
Wow, you are so adorable!
Felicia-san.
What on earth are you two doing? That's so hot!
The trains are leaving!
Trains?
There are documents which must be delivered as quickly as possible to Headquarters.
Klaus-san is coming next week, right?
So, we're going to the station.
The mission of answering the phone really depends on you!
Yes.
If you miss it, the worst-case scenario is that they might assume this place to be under attack.
Take it seriously!
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Y-Yes!
I'm not asleep. I'm not asleep at all!
Have you seen Noël?
She's not in her room.
W-Well...
Not the hangar again...
Well, alright.
Then, Kanata.
What do you want for lunch?
Ah... I-I will cook!
Don't worry. It's my turn.
But...
Come on. Not only Kureha, but you too.
Whenever it's my turn to cook, why do you two never want me to do anything?
Before you two arrived, I did a lot of cooking!
That's because...
The taste shouldn't be bad.
W-Well, right, the taste is okay.
But the way it looks...
What?
No. The taste is very clear. It's great.
Right.
Then today, I'll do my best.
Hey! Is anyone there?
Yes!
Senpai! It's Naomi-san.
I'm busy.
But, I must be by the phone.
Hey! I'm a customer!
Damn, I have to go.
Yes. I'm coming.
I don't want to eat sandwiches with bits of cutting board mixed in.
This is...?
Drink up.
This is apple cider.
I heard it's hand-made by the farmer that delivers our apple juice.
Wow!
Then, this is a relative to our calvados!
Er?
Ah, right.
The secret has been exposed.
What?
I will get two presents for you.
Er? Ah, right.
Present?
There will be a town gathering for commercial and industrial guilds.
We can benefit from a lot of discounts since giving presents is a tradition.
Remember that.
Yes.
What? What?
Those girls have been trying so hard to keep it.
Why was it exposed?
T-That's because... well...
If there's the possibility, then someday...
Instead of talking about that, Naomi-san, do you want to have lunch together?
What? You mean I'm going to be on it?
Well, according to this week's newspaper, people want to hear a good explanation from the military.
News?
The meeting for the armistice agreement has turned into a difficult situation.
Really.
The decisions regarding the amount of reparations and the drawing of the border line are both progressing slowly.
Drawing things out is always the strategy...
Well, I guess what these bosses really want is to meet you.
Anyway, because you acted as a Maiden of Flame during the Water Festival, you've got a lot more fans.
That troubles me. Really...
Because of that, it seems that I have to go out...
I am already a Maiden of the Fortress in body and soul!
I will perform the mission by myself!
I see. I will leave it to you.
Yes!
Kanata, please try this.
Sorry that it's a used copy of mine.
This is... for the trumpet!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
Thank you very much!
Because you are getting a lot better at horns!
This is a reward for practicing hard.
And if you have this, you won't fall asleep.
Hmm, this is C, D, E, F, G...
A.
Summer is already over, isn't it?
Iliya?
Did I drink too much?
Noël-chan, are you there?
It's raining! The laundry will get wet!
The courtyard is a high-level war-zone!
Ka-na-ta, let's play~
Y-e-s!
H-Help me!
I'm saved!
It's nothing. I'm so glad the laundry is fine.
It's really great...
S-sorry!
I asked for you to help me suddenly...
Don't mind it, we were the ones who came to visit you all of a sudden. Really sorry about this.
We must return to Treize, so we are here to say goodbye.
T-That's really kind of you.
We don't really need to say goodbye to the military at all.
It's not like that, Seiya-san.
This kid isn't polite to the people from the base, so please accept my apology.
Where are the others?
They're out.
Was it Rio-san?
TL note: Yes... this priest has color blindness... so does Kanata.
The one with black hair.
Yes.
I got it.
I really wanted to see... uh?
This book is... yours?
What, what?
A book about trumpets. I got it from Rio-senpai.
I see.
So yeah...
Nothing, nothing. Excuse me. I'm talking to myself.
Kanata, are you watching the place by yourself?
Right.
Well... I'm in the middle of the Confirming the Protection of Circuits for Direct Communication of Orders to the Headquarters under Highly Urgent Circumstances mission.
So that is, waiting for this thing to ring?
Yes.
But this will be my first time using it. I'm a little nervous.
Can I answer it correctly? Something like that.
Then, shall we practice?
Then, is Yumina-san also gone for the gathering of guilds?
Yeah... she went to receive the endowments from everybody.
Here you go.
Delicious!
Right?
Seiya-kun, please drink some too.
I'll drink it, but I won't be conciliated by this.
Can you do anything for this?
Mishio-san, you kids know this?
It's a telephone!
Is this really...
Right. A telephone.
Kids like them, so I sometimes make some for them.
Then, Seiya-san...
Yes.
This is a telephone... right?
Hello! Hello~!
Great! Great, Seiya-kun!
I can hear you loud and clear.
You're wrong. You should say "hello" first.
That is how you make phone calls.
He... Hello.
Hello.
Ah. It's so great.
I really, really can hear your voice!
It's good to practice like this.
Yes.
Well, this is...
Hello.
H-Hello.
This is Private Sorami Kanata of Fortress 1121, Helvetia Army!
Yup. It's not so tough.
I-It's so kind of you to call me on the phone at this time.
And then, well...
Wait, birdie!
Mishio-san!
No!
Mishio-chan!
What happened?
The telephone!
Excuse me. Is the priest and my...
Yes?
Oh my goodness!
What happened?
You are here to show your appreciation and apologize for all the things that happened before.
I can't believe you are playing and causing trouble.
No dinner tonight.
Yes.
Does that include me?
It's no problem. Thank you.
But, your clothes are wet.
No problem. Spare clothes...
Fate does exist!
This is... embarrassing!
Not at all!
You look radiant!
But, thank you Yumina-san.
I will return it to you after it's washed.
No. I'll give it to you.
It's too big for the kids.
I don't think I know any other people who it'd fit better!
Sorry, Kanata.
Are you still gonna play with us?
Seiya-kun, you too. Please come again.
I-I...
If I am free, I'll come and play.
Then, we're leaving.
We wish God bestows a lot of happiness upon you.
T-Thank you very much.
Then, let me get everything back in order.
I forgot. Toilet.
It's about to leak out.
Someone... hurry... hurry!
Good grief. What's with that guy...
What is wrong with you, Kanata?
Senpai.
Please! Please save me!
What's... wrong, Kanata?
I can't... hold... any longer.
It's about to leak!
Go now! Or you'll get sick!
Thank you very much.
She has been holding it in all this time?
Should I say that it's obedient, or just stupid?
What's wrong!?
N-No problem!
Kanata!
I... can't!
I can't even move an inch!
These people... What terrible timing!
Hello. This is Staff-Sergeant Rio Kazumiya of Fortress 1121, Helvetia Army.
Long time no see.
I heard they were confirming your circuits. Though they said "It's useless!"...
Are you going to escape?
No! I'm not escaping!
I know. You can never forgive me.
What do you have to do now?
Please. Please, save the country. Save Helvetia.
Good morning, Kanata.
Noël-chan, I can't believe you've been sleeping since morning.
Hmm. I can sleep well on the toilet.
How can that be!?
We're bac... Wow! What a lovely dress, Kana-chan.
But... What are you two doing in the corridor?
Kanata has tripped. She can't stand back up.
You got hurt?
Then stand!
Hmm. I have to do this...
My spoiled little child.
No... Stop...
One, two...
Stop!
After the Typhoon - Visual and Real Images
Next Time :
After the Typhoon
Virtual and Real Images