Girls' Musical Revue Starlight
Just one more month until the performance!
Time sure flies!
Kagura-san?
You don't understand at all, Kagura Hikari!
I do understand.
Understand what?
Days until
Seisho Festival:
Seisho Festival
"If you pluck a large star, you will obtain a great wealth."
Her noble spirit, refusing to relent and facing the tower,
even after losing her memories and being cast into darkness...
That strength of Claire's is what mesmerizes the audience and spurs them to face life!
She is the very soul of the tale that is Starlight!
During the 99th Seisho Festival last year,
I kept the glimmer of her soul at the forefront of my mind.
In acting, singing, and dancing—at all times.
However, Kagura Hikari-san!
I feel none of that from your Claire.
Yes, she's right.
You didn't see the Starlight we put on back then.
It's true: both the script and direction are different from last year.
I'm well aware of that!
Even so...
Even so, I...
"Let's go, to pluck that star together!"
"If you pluck a small star,
you will gain a small amount of happiness."
Even having lost her memories, she still remembered the promise she made with her friend.
That is Claire's strength.
That's important.
However, even in the darkness when I had lost everything,
she never abandoned me for a moment.
She led me by my empty hands.
She waited for me and accepted me.
I want to express my gratitude.
Amazing...
Tendo-san? Kagura-san?!
I see.
It was so obvious that it didn't occur to me.
I can accept your way of constructing the character.
Um, both of you, calm—
It pains me to admit...
Huh?
It seems...
I was more emotionally invested in Claire than I had thought.
Not in the lead role?
Oh, I mean...
This will be my first time seeing you in something other than a lead role.
I thought that might be why...
That's not...
This isn't my first time.
There have been plays where I couldn't get a lead role.
However...
I thought I'd taken that frustration to heart,
to sing and dance the boldest, so as to not lose to anyone.
Yes...
I'm frustrated.
I must...
be frustrated.
At not getting a lead role.
I'd forgotten the very thing I was trying not to forget.
Where were we taking these?
The prep room, right?
I-I'm frustrated!
This is so frustrating!
Putting tacks in your shoes, hiding your costumes, ignoring you on purpose...
Huh?
...is what I feel like doing.
Kagura Hikari-san...
Are you going to?
Hold up, both you, right now—
No, I won't.
You won't?
But I've had it done to me.
You have?!
So I do understand that feeling.
I understand.
You do?
Please forgive me, Kagura Hikari-san.
I've been egotistical, forcing my feelings on you.
And it seems I care more deeply than I'd realized
for Claire and for Starlight.
I understand.
Because I love them too.
I've never seen Tendo-san so frustrated before.
Or seen Kagura-san talk about herself so much, for that matter.
I'm jealous of you both, getting to play a lead role.
Oh, I'm not begrudging you or anything.
Even if I'm not a lead character,
there's nothing that exceeds the joy of being on stage.
"We may not have the same amount of time on stage, but we have the same glimmer."
That one's by me.
Did you just laugh?
I think that's a great saying, Hoshimi-san.
Did you just say my...
I'm most grateful, Kagura Hikari-san.
Thank you for stealing the lead role from me.
If your acting is not up to par, I will steal my Claire back.
This is Tendo Maya.
Bring it on.
"Bring it on", huh?
The strong Claire...
and the thankful Claire.
If it were me...
Yeah.
I think I'll get some udon.