Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
On your mark!
Get set!
You've done it again, Kona-chan.
That was amazing.
How come you aren't on any sports teams...
...when you're so athletic?
'Cause if I join a team...
...I'll miss my prime time anime.
Speedy
Lady
Say, Tsukasa.
Which end of a chocolate cornet do you start from?
The head, I suppose.
I see.
By the way...
Which side's the head?
The fat end or the thin end?
I would guess the thin end.
Oh.
I thought it was the fat end.
But why would the thin end be the head?
Well, doesn't it look like a seashell?
Why did you think it was the fat end, Kona-chan?
'Cause, you know...
It looks like a caterpillar?
A caterpillar?
But I guess it works better if you picture a seashell.
U-Um...
You could cut off the thin end...
...and eat it with the excess chocolate.
Now I get it.
Good thinking, Miyuki-san.
You're so smart.
Not at all.
Everyone has their own approach to eating.
How do you eat cream puffs?
Cream puffs, you ask?
Well...
I start by splitting it in half...
...and eating the lid after dipping it in the cream from the bottom...
And then I eat the bottom half.
This way, I don't have to worry about any cream spilling out...
...while maintaining a balance between cream and puff.
What about the ones that have both custard and cream inside?
How do you eat those?
Do you mix them up?
No.
I wouldn't do such a thing.
But how would you mix them?
Just asking.
When do you eat the strawberry on a strawberry shortcake...
...or the chestnut on top of a Mont Blanc?
Let's see...
There are also strawberries tucked between layers of sponge cake.
I follow a normal distribution of strawberry, cream, and cake as I eat.
So there isn't a set time for eating the strawberry.
You really know your stuff.
I always save the strawberry for last.
But then I get full sometimes...
...so I end up not eating it...
...or someone in my family takes it.
Your favorites gotta come first.
Actually, I don't think I've ever seen anyone take a strawberry from Sis.
That's Kagami for you.
Doesn't miss a step.
Are you able to eat the last bite of a popsicle without dropping it?
Dropping it?
If you aren't careful...
...you drop the last bit, right?
What do you do, Kona-chan?
Suck it down to nothing.
You could rotate the popsicle as you eat.
That's a good idea.
I'm not very fond of ice cream cones.
Why?
I can't stand it when only the cone is left.
That's right.
You always end up with some cone left.
I push the ice cream into the cone as I eat.
How do you push the ice cream?
I do a little ~gui gui~ action as I eat.
~gui gui~, is it?
Yuki-chan prioritizes balance, right?
That's right.
Then what do you do with curry rice?
Do you mix the sauce with the rice?
No.
I don't mix them...
...but I make sure that they're equally proportioned.
I mix mine up.
What about you, Kona-chan?
Depends on the curry.
If there's any Worcester sauce or raw egg in it...
...I guess I do a little mixy-wixy.
Worcester sauce in curry?
It's good stuff.
Do you also put Worcester sauce on your fried eggs?
I put soy sauce on fried eggs.
I use mayonnaise.
On your fried eggs?
I don't mean boiled eggs.
You see, mayonnaise...
...goes well with most egg dishes.
Do you put it on your curry?
It's a must on white rice.
But the sweetness also goes well with beef bowls.
It's also good with parent-child bowls.
You know how eggs and chicken meat are child and parent.
So once I add mayonnaise, which is made from eggs...
...I call it an expanded family bowl.
Also...
I usually can't stand natto...
...but I was able to eat it once I added mayonnaise.
Can't imagine it.
But...
...putting mayonnaise on soft-boiled eggs might be best.
The fried eggs at my house are also half-done.
It's how my dad likes them.
He likes to suck out the yolk.
And if it's overcooked, he can't suck the yolk.
What about yakitori?
What about it?
Do you leave it on the spit?
Or do you use chopsticks to take it off?
Let's see...
If I'm eating one by myself, I'll leave it on the spit.
But if I'm with other people, I'll take it off.
Yeah, yeah.
Isn't it a little awkward when there's only one left?
I can't bring myself to take the last one.
As time goes by without anyone eating it...
It starts getting dry...
...and looking anything but appetizing...
...and no one's willing to make a move...
...but when the busboy takes it, you go...
"Wait, we're not done with that yet."
...kinda on reflex.
But then you end up leaving without eating it.
Such a waste.
I feel sorry for it.
And when you grill meat...
...I feel sorry for the meat that's all charred and stuck to the grill.
You have to eat while you're grilling and chatting...
...so it's a busy ordeal.
It's even worse with onion beef tongue slices since they're done in'no time.
You're right.
They're done after just one flip.
Flip?
Onion beef tongue slices?
You can't flip those.
Really?
If you flip them over...
...the onions on top will fall off.
Oh, yeah.
They'll finish cooking without any flipping.
I see...
I'll do that from now on.
You can never flip them.
Really...
By the way, is the head of a chocolate cornet the fat or thin end?
Locked up for two months
"I wanted to make her my slave
Super bad boy.
There've been a bunch of kidnapping cases recently.
Guys forcing girls to address them as "Master" and stuff.
Isn't that less...
...an issue of morals...
...and more an issue of playing too many dating sims and adult games?
It's a commonly used scenario.
Aren't you talking about yourself?!
Er, wait a tick.
Why are you so well versed in the adult game scenarios...
...Miss High School Second-year?
First Semester Midterm Grades
Miyuki Takara
Your grades are always so good.
Don't you have any faults, Miyuki-san?
I'm ashamed to say...
...that I have a tendency to brood over things...
...or space out.
I've cut my finger while using a slicer.
Ow!
And tripped over myself while in a hurry.
And gotten my bag stuck in the door on a train.
Miyuki-san.
Those aren't faults, but elements of moe.
Moe?
The clumsy factor.
What was going on inside Kona-chan's head during all that?!
Miyuki-san, why do you wear glasses when you're actually attractive?
You'll only nab a niche audience.
Nab's a little...
Setting aside the issue of popularity...
...why don't you wear contacts?
I heard that glasses make your vision worse.
Um...
I'm ashamed to be saying this in high school...
B-But...
I'm...
Scared!
Of contacts!
Or to be specific...
...putting things in my eyes.
I can never open my eyes when I'm underwater.
Damn!
She's cute to the core!
Must be innate.
Isn't that Miyuki-san?
YOSHIMIZU
OPTOMETRY
Is she here for an eye examination?
To get contacts?
YOSHIMIZU
OPTOMETRY
Miyuki-san's probably better off this way forever.
That looked painful...
A pillar of evolution.
Kagami's at home with a cold?
It looks like she doesn't have the flu though.
I'm stupid, so I don't have to worry about getting the flu.
I've heard that applies to colds...
...but it also applies to the flu?
There's a difference between a cold and the flu?
I thought the flu was like a super cold.
I-I think they're different...
But now I'm not sure anymore...
The difference between the flu and a cold?
Well...
The flu is caused by a virus.
The symptoms are a fever and aching throughout the body.
And there is a risk of complications.
On the other hand...
...the symptoms of a cold are a sore throat and runny nose...
...and the fever doesn't run as high.
And there are a number of other minute differences.
Which is why...
...they are different illnesses.
I see...
H-However...
Well, they share many similarities...
...so you could possibly say that the flu is an upgraded version of a cold...
I see!
Kona-chan.
What's with the pensive face?
Oh, nothing big.
I was just curious about something after our conversation this morning.
About a cold and the flu?
You didn't disagree when I said I was dumb.
N-No!
It's not like that!
Konata-chan.
Welcome.
She's here to visit Sis.
Thank you for visiting.
It's nothing.
Sorry to intrude.
Kagami actually looks pretty cute when she's asleep.
What is it?!
Why are you here?!
She's up. She's up.
Get out!
Visiting?
You?
For my sake?
That's right.
B-But I don't want you to catch the flu from me.
I appreciate the thought though.
Hah.
You know you're happy about it.
Is she worried about me...
...because of the new virus going around?
I figured she only ever had games and anime on her mind.
I'm a little touched.
Well...
I wanted to see your homework from the other day.
And I got to see your face while you were sleeping...
...so don't sweat it.
Get out!
Kagami!
Miyuki-chan's here to visit you!
Okay!
I'm sorry to intrude.
Sorry you had to come on a day off.
Is it all right for you to be up?
This is a little something.
Thanks.
I'm a lot better now.
My fever went down after I took some medicine.
Here.
Flowers and fruits! I'm overjoyed!
Have a seat.
Thank you very much.
I intended to visit earlier with Izumi-san and everyone...
...but my schedule hasn't been very forgiving.
It's okay.
I brought some materials from the student council meeting.
Thanks!
If you could take a quick glance without straining yourself...
Also, here are the budgets for each club.
And what else was there...
Um...
If I'm tiring you out...
...I'll leave.
This is how a visit's supposed to be!
D-Did something happen?
Actually, Konata showed up yesterday...
It was like, good grief.
That may just be how Izumi-san expresses herself.
The homework may have been an attempt at humor...
...in order to cheer you up.
And perhaps she saw how your face looked while you were sleeping...
...because she didn't want to wake you up.
Is this woman a saint?!
That would've never occurred to me.
Come to think of it...
Is Tsukasa-san not here today?
Good morning.
Are you feeling better, Sis?
As you can see...
She's more laid-back than the person who's sick.
U-Um...
I'm not like this every morning...
Just that I haven't really adjusted to daylight savings...
It's a little late, but welcome.
I completely understand.
I've been having a hard time waking up as well.
Th-That's right.
You get so sleepy these days.
Indeed.
And it's especially warm today.
That's the truth!
It can't be helped.
And you know how our last day off was also warm?
When I woke up, it was already evening.
I spent most of the time sleeping.
It's good to rest when you have a day off.
So I ended up wearing my pajamas the whole day.
I guess I still am.
Those are pajamas?
That's right.
They're quite adorable.
I can't tell that they're pajamas.
Really?
I wonder if I can just stay in them.
You could walk outside in them.
Could I go into a convenience store in these?
It's like an endless loop of dumb and dumber!
Nobody would blink an eye.
NURSE'S OFFICE
It's gone up a little...
No.
That might not be the case.
I'm wearing a wired bra with extra padding...
...which means extra weight.
That has to be it.
I wonder how many grams that adds.
Once you subtract that...
NURSE'S OFFICE
It's over...
I totally screwed up.
I forgot we had examinations today...
...so I wore my character print underwear.
I'm so embarrassed!
I haven't grown at all...
Damn it!
You get to look all happy by yourself!
Yo.
I'm here.
Sis.
I was wondering.
Kagami comes here a lot.
Do you have no friends in your class?
Don't put me on your level.
Are you trying to pick a fight?
Oh.
I thought you were being ostracized or something.
Worry less about me...
...and more about your lack of a social life.
You don't have to worry about that.
Believe it or not, I have around a hundred friends.
And I'm pretty good at social dealings.
And I'm in a party every night.
My comrades and I strive to recover the light stolen from the crystals...
...to save the world from oblivion...
...and rescue kidnapped princesses...
Aren't you talking about a game?!
I haven't seen that person in a while.
Who?
She's probably talking about some friend from a game.
He plays a warrior.
He went somewhere with a lot of monsters to train his battle skills, and I haven't seen him since.
I heard from someone else...
...that he was lying low in the sewers.
I wonder if he's okay.
Everyone's worried since he hasn't come out.
He isolated himself in the game?
I don't know the details...
...but his log-in info implies that he's been online the whole time.
So he's isolated in both the real and virtual world?!
Well, it's the same person in both cases.
That's right...
How did you two become friends?
A huge fishy-looking foreigner was about to take Tsukasa away...
...when I happened to show up.
Using my special fists of fury...
...and beautiful hurricane kick...
...I saved her.
Why do we always end up talking about games?
Well, that's what happens when you run into an experienced fighter.
I'm not sure you should've resorted to violence so quickly...
...but you did a good thing.
The foreigner was actually just asking me for directions...
...but I was having a hard time understanding him when Kona-chan showed up...
Hey!
You were totally at fault there!
And why do you look so proud about it?!
It's that time of year again...
Is something going to happen?
No.
I was thinking that the Tigers' season had started...
You don't like watching sports, Kona-chan?
You're really athletic...
...so I thought you might enjoy it.
Because if the game goes into extra innings...
...the schedule for new anime gets all messed up.
Sometimes, the show gets cancelled altogether.
It sucks when you lose something you like.
When do you eat the strawberry on a strawberry shortcake, Kagami?
Why you asking?
I was wondering if you were the type to save your favorite for last.
I usually eat my favorite stuff last...
...but with strawberries, it depends on the situation.
Then do you grill both sides of an onion beef tongue?
Onion beef tongues?
It's done in no time anyway...
...but it'd go even faster if you did both sides.
You can't.
The onions will fall off.
Don't you add the onions after the meat's done?
Then the onions won't be grilled.
But aren't the onions just a topping?
You have no idea...
W-Well...
Wouldn't they both work...?
Do you think the head of a chocolate cornet is the fat or thin end?
The fat end?
We think the same.
Seriously?
Then which end do you start eating from?
Don't you cut off the thin end...
...and eat it with the excess chocolate?
Have you ever made any real-life friends besides us?
I guess I had a really close friend back in middle school.
So you had one.
I haven't been in touch for a while...
Wonder what she's up to...
She wrote in our graduation book...
...that her dream was to become a wizard.
So she was one of your kind?!
Good lucky!
It's finally time for Lucky Channel!
Now being broadcast on TV!
Okay!
Hello to everyone who's meeting us for the first time!
I'll be your navigator, Akira Kogami.
I'm Shiraishi.
Who're you?
Just kidding!
This person will be helping me out from now on.
Minoru Shiraishi-san!
Da-dada-dum!
Uh...
I'll be serving as Akira-sama's assistant.
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Nice to meet you.
Say what?
You're such a stick-in-the-mud.
Come on.
We're on TV now.
Be more crazy!
Just kidding!
Sorry.
I'm not used to this.
Okay!
Let's get rollin'!
We've received commemorative postcards from lots of people!
Ah, right.
Um...
This is from Berryz Lover in Osaka.
Congratulations on Lucky Channel making it to TV.
Thanks!
By the way, I have a question for Akira-san.
You are a well-known super idol.
How much exactly is an idol paid?
Please let me know.
Pay?
That's a rather direct question.
Y'know...
What's the point in even asking that?
A-Akira-sama?
Well, if you really want to know, I'll tell you.
To be frank, it jumps all over.
Sometimes, it's just cheap pay...
...and then there's your agency.
I'm still on a fixed salary...
...so who knows how much they're skimming off.
And I've been working since I was three...
...so all the money still goes to my parents.
They, like, give me an allowance.
And boy, do they skimp.
Come to think of it, Mama's been buying a bunch of name brand purses recently.
Is she paying for that with the money from this show?
Don't mess with me!
Am I supposed to be Cinderella?!
Wait...
Just because Papa hasn't sent you any money recently...
Hold on!
...doesn't make me your piggy bank!
You don't have to bring that up!
Oh no!
It's time to say goodbye!
Akira's so sad!
And so...
Send us any questions or comments about the show, please☆!
Shiraishi-san, ask them with a please☆!
Then we hope you'll be back next time.
See ya!
Oh, yeah.
Are you seriously going to show up in the actual show?
Who told you that?
The four of us don't karaoke together very often.
I rarely come to these places.
C'mon. C'mon.
We only have two hours, so start singing!
You don't need to rush us.
We still have time.
This is kind of exciting.
It's really fun.
It feels really good when you sing.
Huh?
Where's the catalog?
Catalog?
The catalog.
The catalog, is it?
You know.
The thing with all the song numbers in it.
This?
Yes.
Then I'll start!
You move fast!
And she already queued up three songs!
It'll be a waste if you don't load up the list.
What's this song?
Space Ironmen Kyodain!
You've gotta start with this one!
Never heard of it.
From Da! Da! Da-Da-Da-Da Planet Dada!
Go for it, Kona-chan!
Konata!
Comes the Earth Invasion Robot Army!
You're too loud!
Turn it down!
Take to the sky, big brother!
Why does she know this song?
Skyzel!
Run, little brother!
Granzel!
Two arms of Scrum-metal!
With a flash, it's a galaxy of fireworks!
Go! Go! Jet! Go! Go! Car!
Space Ironmen Kyodain!
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Konata.
So sleepy...
Why am I always so sleepy...
...the day after I get a lot of sleep?
Doesn't that defeat the purpose of sleeping a lot?
Next time:
Effort and Results.
「Effort and Results」
Look forward to next time!