When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Man, I'm full.
No matter how many times I eat it, Maria-san's cooking's great.
You're eating too much even for that.
Listen. You need energy to do comedy.
You need to have strength.
If you don't eat well, you can never get people to laugh.
I never intend to make people laugh.
If you're done eating, then get yourself out of here.
I will without needing you to tell me.
Unlike you, I properly go to school.
Makita! Kunieda!
I'm off to school now!
"School", "school". Whatever.
If you don't start getting ready, you'll be late.
Don't be ridiculous; Isumi's still sleeping.
I can't leave a guest behind and go to school.
Oh, so that's your excuse today?
It must be hard to have so many reasons why you can't go to school.
Why do you want to make me go to school so badly?
If I go to school...
...I can't spend time with you...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Come to think of it, I had forgotten that Nagi was fond of Hayate-kun.
Oh no!
Seriously, why is Hayate so...
Why doesn't he understand that I want to stay with him as much as time allows?
He's so dense.
Cleaning~ Cleaning~ It's so fun~
So you like cleaning, Hayate-kun?
Huh? Ah, yes.
Then is your type older or younger girls?
Um...
You mean my ideal type?
Yes.
Since Nagi and Hayate-kun's relationship started with a misunderstanding,
I need to clearly confirm Hayate-kun's feelings once.
Does this mean the path to the Maria-san ending
in this anime has opened?
Definitely older girls.
I think younger girls are cute,
but they won't be the target of any relationships.
Oh, really?
Her reaction seems rather disappointed.
What's going on?
Hey, Hayate!
Come up here for a second!
Yes, right away!
I'm sorry; we'll talk about this later.
So Nagi-chan's absent today, too.
That reminds me. The intruder in black
from the other day was the new Sanzenin butler.
I only got a glimpse, but he was a young guy, wasn't he?
Yup. He was handsome.
You think?
I don't recall that.
Then let's go check him out again.
Could you put these clothes on?
That's, without any mistake, for girls, right?
Don't worry; the size is correct.
That's not what I'm worried about.
Why am I going to wear a girl's outfit?
Why?
Because you'll probably look good in it.
So it's on your whim?!
Yes, it is on a whim, but if I don't come up
with an excuse, I can't be with you.
Augh!
Stop whining and put this on already!
No! Please stop! No!
You're so mean to make me wear this sailor uniform.
You look great in it.
It doesn't make me happy at all!
Oh right! Camera!
No, please!
You can't take pictures of this!
What's wrong about it! Got to put it in the album.
Why?
Besides, if the head butler sees me in this, I'll get fired!
What do you mean?
Allow me to explain.
It turns out that Hayate was taught
the heart of butlering by Klaus a few days ago again.
A butler must act like a man.
Do you understand? As a Sanzenin butler,
you must always be a gentleman and manly.
Because the world seeks for equality between
men and women, we have to be manly to fill the gap.
If you can't do that, I will have you out of here instantly.
Oh, Klaus said that?
So I can't have Klaus-san see me in this!
Not only Klaus-san.
Maria-san, too...
If she sees me in this, I'll die from embarrassment.
Oh my, what should I do then?
Having you die because of me is a bit of a problem.
M-Maria-san!
I was wondering what you two were up to, but...
No! Milady forced this on me!
Hayate insisted on trying it on.
No, I didn't!
Don't worry; I don't believe that you have a secret hobby of cross dressing.
Thank goodness. I was worried that you'd misunderstand me.
Anyways, you're so mischievous.
But I thought Hayate would look good in it.
Even so, a sailor uniform?
She's right! I'm a guy!
Hayate-kun would look better in this frill.
Maria-san!
Maria! Then how about coordinating it with this skirt?
What? Wouldn't it be cuter to put pink with this?
How about red then?
Actually, this blue one looks good, too.
Oh no. They're both in high school girl mode.
My purity is in jeopardy.
What do you think about this, Maria?
That looks good.
Slowly...
Where are you going?
You can't walk around the house in that sailor uniform, can you?
But... I have work to do.
How admirable.
But let's say that this is part of your work, too.
Let's try these clothes on, too.
You're horrible.
Th-This is...
It's beyond a joke.
If Klaus-san sees me in this, I'll really get fired!
Don't worry about it.
And stop looking at me with those eyes.
Really, you're embarrassing me.
I'm the one that's embarrassed!
But you really do look great in it.
You think so, too, don't you, Tama?
T-Tama, no, don't!
Even if you're an animal, you can't engage in something we can't show in anime!
Stop it! You weigh 300kg! You'll kill me!
Allow me to explain for the kids who are watching this anime for the first time.
This tiger, referred to as Tama, can speak the human language.
And don't ask why he can.
Maria, is Tama on Hayate thinking he's a cute feline?
Or is Tama on him knowing he's a cute guy?
I'm not sure.
Depending on how it is, I'm thinking of changing Tama's training program.
But I think Hayate-kun is going to die while we discuss this.
Tama, stop it.
Oh come on! Just a little!
That's enough out of you!
You stupid tiger.
He took out Tama in one move.
He may look like a girl, but he's a monster inside.
Anyway, I must get changed immediately.
If Klaus-san sees me in this-
What a nice weather out today.
On a day like this, the best thing to do is to give
the original language of flowers to the flowers in the yard.
What is that about?
Forget that, I need to get out of here.
Who is this stranger walking in
the Sanzenin yard without permission?
Can't possibly say, "It's me, Hayate."
All that's left is...
How foolish. You think you can get away from me in this mansion?
Now that's the Klaus I know.
He's keeping up with Hayate-kun's speed.
Oh no, he'll eventually catch up with me at this rate.
I'll have to hide my face with the ribbon and fight back.
Crap, I can't see anything.
But in emergencies, humans can awaken their hidden powers.
Don't try to look. Believe the mind's eye!
Klaus Kick!
That was impossible, after all.
Die, intruder.
What do you think you're doing going into heat all of a sudden?!
I'm sorry, Klaus-san. I'm really sorry.
Change into these while you can.
Thank you very much.
No, I'm sorry for getting carried away, as well.
No, you're so kind, Maria-san.
I'm very grateful to you.
Thank you very much, Maria-san.
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't be here.
What's wrong with him saying, "Maria-san", "Maria-san"?
Hayate, get changed already!
Otherwise, I'll throw the pictures we took earlier into the air.
What? Please, no.
I'm only joking.
Looks like Nagi-chan has a new maid, as well.
Now that's the Sanzenin family for you.
But that's a really cute maid.
And they look occupied, so let's go home.
Yeah, besides lunch break is almost over.
Forget about afternoon classes.
How the student council trio were able to get inside the high security Sanzenin territory is a mystery.
Who was that beautiful girl?
If I could see her again, I want to tell her how I feel.
Hayate's misfortunes continue.
Mucchini Sukebe = Passive Pervert
Mucchiri Sukebe!
Betsu ni sawatta dakejya nai = I only touched you
Betsu ni sawatta dakejya nai.
Ooh, so hot.
Come to think of it, I wonder how Ayasaki-kun's doing.
Oww.
Man, Tama jumps on top of me... and Klaus-san kicks me...
I'm covered with scratches.
I'm sorry for you.
Isumi-san! What are you doing here?
Well, when I woke up, I was lost.
Thanks to that, I am exhausted now.
I'm sorry for you, too.
Your lack of a sense of direction is amazing.
How many times have you come to my house?
Sanzenin Mansion, the fearful labyrinth where you get lost no matter how many times you visit.
Don't treat us like a haunted house.
Well, the night has fallen,
so how about staying over another night?
I'll give a call to your house.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Isumi-san didn't see me cross-dressing, did she?
Mustn't worry. Mustn't worry.
I'll just go to bed.
Not going to bed yet?
No, I usually sleep with Nagi, as she typically won't go to bed alone because she's scared...
...but since Isumi-san is here tonight, too...
So you're relieved of your usual role.
Yes.
So you play billiards?
Well, yes.
Would you like to play a game?
Besides, I think I can have a good conversation with him right now.
This following the conversation in the morning...
Did the path to the Maria-san ending really open?
And the reason why today was filled with misfortune was a build up to this moment of happiness?
And Hayate will be regretting his optimistic illusion in a while.
Then let us begin.
Yes.
Milady is really close with Isumi-san, isn't she?
Isumi-san is special to Nagi.
The two met at a party eight years ago.
What's this doodle?
It's not a doodle, Saku Nee-chan!
It's a manga that I'm working on.
A manga?
Is this Ri***man-like figure the enemy?
That's Helnia-chan, the mascot character!
Are these ancient words from the Inca?
That's the special move, Death Slicer!
Either way, stop drawing this boring thing
and come play with us outside.
I'm never going to write another manga.
H-Hey! What are you doing reading it?!
Give it back! Haven't you had enough of a laugh, yet?
Where's the rest?
What's going to happen next?
It was very interesting.
That's how they met.
And few seconds later, she goes...
Please marry me!
What?
That's how they became best friends.
I see.
But Isumi-san's amazing to be able to understand that manga.
Really.
I'm sure, right now, Nagi's telling a story that only those two understand.
That's when the infinite-ant-creating machine hidden under Ayers Rock activates.
With the ants spreading all over the surface of the world, all the sugar is brought to the Dead General living underground,
And the heroes all around the world engage in a battle.
It worries me about her future a little.
By the way, Hayate-kun, where did you pick up billiards?
When I was in middle school,
I was working part time at a pool bar.
Is it allowed for underaged children to work at a pool bar?
I guess I shouldn't ask.
Oh yeah, how about we bet something?
That sounds good.
I only intended that as a joke.
Oh why not.
Okay, then what should we bet?
How about the loser listens to anything the winner asks for?
Are you sure? This anime is intended for a young audience, mind you.
Um, Hayate-kun, what do you intend to make me do?
Nothing... much...
Besides, Hayate-kun, you think you even have a 0.1% chance of winning against me?
Shall we begin?
B-By the way, if I lose, what are you going to make me do?
Oh, let's see...
Don't you think the remaining debt of ¥155,823,975 is a bit of a mouthful?
Huh?
¥155,823,975 is a bit of a mouthful to say, so wouldn't 200 million be easier?
Today's been a horrible day, but judging from where this is going, is Maria-san the last boss of the day?
I can't lose this match!
However, with the extreme difference in skill,
Hayate had absolutely no chance.
Um, quick question. If I do lose,
how do I pay the 200 million back?
You're right; it's impossible, isn't it?
Right, so you're joking about 200 million, right?
Do I look like a kind of person that jokes?
No.
But there is a way to pay it back.
What?
Don't mind. It's your turn.
Ah, y-yes.
I must make a comeback.
By the way, the easy way to pay the debt back is...
...marrying Nagi.
What?! Me? Marry Milady?
Oops, you missed.
What, you can't count that...
No stops in a serious match.
Now, if I make this, your debt will become 200 million, and you'll have to start hitting on Nagi seriously.
Um, I can't ever marry Milady.
You don't like her?
No, that's not the reason.
If I marry Milady and pay the debt off like that,
then that looks as if I married Milady for the sake of money.
It's only a hypothetical story!
It's impossible for her to fall in love with lowly me!
And even if she did, as a human being, I can't lay my hands on a child!
Seriously!
Milady is my life savior and a very important person.
So I can't ever do that.
Hayate-kun's a really good boy.
And here I am, trying to scout his feelings.
It might be for the best to leave it to the two of them.
Um, is something wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here I go.
Oh my.
All right, looks like I still have a chance.
Yay!
Congratulations! You win.
Then, I can really ask for anything?
Yes, of course.
Okay, then I'll ask something on the borderline, considering the kids in the audience.
But...
I think you have to deal with the monster standing behind you first.
Milady...
What's with that loose face you've got?
N-No, this really is nothing...
Listen Hayate! If you ever lay your hands on Maria, I won't forgive you!
Seriously, when he already has me...
Let's go Isumi!
Good night.
Milday turned out to be the last boss of the day filled with misfortune.
So Hayate-kun, what did you want me to do for you?
I was hoping you'd forgive me for ruining that expensive coat.
Oh, something so simple?
Yes.
The debt-ridden butler has a weak mind.
Next week, we'll fight against "it" in the science lab.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
This week's Hayate no Gotoku was hilarious, too.
Yeah? But the cels didn't have colors during the dubbing, so I can't say much about it.
It's fine. It'll be colored by the time it goes on air.
I sure hope so.
Rather than that, isn't this a nice song?
It contains my resolution to protect-
We heard that last time, so we know.
Instead, wear this for me.
Wh-What is this outfit?
Manly Hayate is good, but it's hard to give up on this, too.
*Sob* I'm ruined for marriage!
I'll take you, so don't worry.
Bye bye!
What, this is strange.
What's wrong, Milady?
Looks like I left my notebook at school.
What?
Then I'll go get it right away.
No, it's not that important.
I'm off!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Eloim Essaim. Mr. Cow, Mr. Cow! What is it, Mr. Frog?
What? Hayate-kun from Sanzenin went into that old building?
3x3 Eyes! We shall meet in the land of the Triclops.