Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Put the sakura color behind you and follow the rainbow
And we'll whisper secrets to each other all the way
Oh, Haruka. You watching TV right now?
We wore matching rings and headed towards the same dream
Your favorite artist is on right now.
Let's sing along!
I held you softly in my arms as we shared a kiss.
I'm surprised you can sing lyrics
like that out loud, Haruka.
What?! I thought you liked this song!
Let's sing together!
No.
Meanie.
Fine, then...
Are you eating anything right now, Yuu-chan?
Nope, not a thing.
Great. Here's a riddle for you.
Try to guess what I'm eating right now.
Crunch
Scary! The heck is that?!
Doesn't the sound make it obvious? It's a rice cracker.
How would I know?! It sounded like you were crunching on bones!
Bone
Bones?!
Bone?
Hey, Haruka.
Yeah?
What do you even want so late at night?
I just got the urge to hear your voice.
I-Is that the only reason you called me?
Yeah...
Did you not want to hear my voice too?
No, I...
...wanted to hear you too.
I can't believe you said that!
Knock it off!
Mitsuki, could you go get Yuu for me?
I'm on it.
"Year-end Debut S.B.J.K."
Yeah, yeah! And then...
Big Sister
Sure sounds like a good time in there.
I started thinking about whether the red string of fate really exists.
No way, that's too embarrassing!
Yeah?
Yuu, Mom wanted me to call you down for New Year's soba.
Okay.
Alright, Haruka. They need me, so I'm cutting off now.
No, it can't be cut!
What are you talking about?
The red string of fate that binds us won't break even if you cut it!
I'm just talking about the phone call!
But I wanna talk to you more.
Just call me back later then.
That's impossible!
So many people will be calling for the New Year that I won't get through!
I wanna be the first to wish you a happy New Year!
And that's why you don't want to hang up?
Felicitations
I wish you a happy New Year.
Happy New Year
New Year
There, now you're my very first.
But the date hasn't changed yet!
I'm ending this call before my
New Year's soba gets cold.
Yuu-chan, you're having soba?
Yep, my mom makes it herself.
It's the best!
What's more important to you? New Year's soba or me?!
My mom's New Year's soba ten times out of ten!
No way!
Don't you eat it with your family too?
You can't talk and eat at the same time.
We never have New Year's soba.
Seriously? Then what do you eat?
We just finished up the leftovers from Christmas!
We even made the expiration date!
Expiration Date
For someone who eats leftovers, you sure care a lot about New Year's greetings.
Wh-What's wrong with me caring?
The New Year's greeting is important.
If your call can't get through then just say it to me tomorrow.
I can't!
In the meantime, won't you have said it to your parents and President Mitsuki?
Probably.
Then that's no good at all! I want to be your first!
To think that your jealousy would
finally reach this level...
Little Sister
Mother
Father
Big Sister
Jelaously
Father
Mother
Jelaously
Not even my family is safe.
Th-That's different...
If you don't hang up right now, I'll start calling you Super Jealous Girl.
No, spare me!
Super Bad Jealous Kid, S.B.J.K. for short.
Happy New Year!
No, please stop!
Good morning to you, S.B.J.K.
Stop!
S.B.J.K, are you having a good time?
Yuu, your New Year's soba is getting soggy. Are you still not done?
I fell right into your trap, S.B.J.K!
Fidget
You dug your own grave.
Are you on the phone with Haruka-san?
Yeah.
Big Sister
Little Sister
I'm so jealous!
I want to at least talk to her a little before the year ends.
That's right, it's not strange for me to want to wish her a happy New Year or anything!
Y-Yuu, it's not good to stay on the phone so long!
Don't worry, Haruka's footing the bill.
Everything's fine, President Mitsuki.
That's not the problem here!
I know!
How about I talk with President Mitsuki while you go and finish your soba?
No can do. We eat our soba together as a family.
Keep your selfishness in check.
Aren't you getting hungry too, Onee-chan?
I...
I already finished eating.
You were taking too long to come.
Where did that lie come from?!
You already ate?
I-I sure did.
Say what? You ate without me?!
Little Sister
Big Sister
Argh!
Haruka
Hello? Is that President Mitsuki?
Now that I'm actually on the phone, I have no idea what to say.
Hello?
G
u
lp
H-Haruka-san? Good evening.
Good evening, President.
The year's nearly over.
Right. It sure went by quickly.
Wh-What plans do you have for New Year's Eve?
See? I knew I could talk to her if I tried.
New Year's Eve?
That's a really funny joke!
I messed up after all! I meant New Year's Day!
When I think about how you graduate in just three short months,
I feel lonely.
That's not the right way to say that. There are three whole months left.
You can't get sad until the day actually comes.
You'll be upperclassmen before you know it, so pull yourself together.
There won't be anyone under us though.
Then act as if there will be! Got it?
Y-Yes!
Things will be different for your year.
In addition to graduation, there'll also be a closing ceremony.
A closing ceremony?
Not even I know what the school plans to do for it.
But in exchange for all the
activities you won't get to do,
you need to make that one a blast.
Mikan
I'll be coming back for it too, so don't let me down.
I won't!
Onee-chan!
What?!
You didn't eat your New Year's soba yet either!
Why'd you lie to me?!
Because you weren't coming down! And besides, how'd you know I was lying?
Because Mom and Dad are waiting for you!
Oh...
Still not ready?
Your parents were waiting for you?
That's right, and it's all your fault!
Little Sister
Big Sister
I-I'll go back down first.
Haruka
Got it... then I'll hang up.
Sorry for being so needy, Yuu-chan.
Haruka
Sonoda Yuu
Wait!
To tell you the truth, I... well...
I want to keep talking to you, too.
You'll always be number one in my heart, Haruka.
I-I know that.
I know... but I can't help it.
And I knew you'd be like that, too.
You're the super jealous type, after all!
So... I want you to listen closely.
Yuu-chan?
Huh? What was that sound?
It was the sound of me giving you a kiss.
Aren't you going to kiss me back?
I've really gotta go now.
Okay.
Thanks, Yuu-chan.
Happy New Year.
"Year-end Debut S.B.J.K."
The end
When I think about how you graduate in just three short months,
I feel lonely.
I wonder why Haruka-san said she wanted to talk to me back then.
I'm sure there was no deeper meaning to it.
She was just feeling lonely
thinking about me graduating...
When I think about you graduating, I feel lonely.
I feel lonely...
Haruka-san's feeling lonely!
"A Sour Plan?! Take Two"
I know it must have sounded like I was patronizing her,
but is it possible that she was actually trying to say...
I'm lonely.
I want to see you, President Mitsuki.
No, that's definitely not possible.
Big Sister
Wait, but then why did she ask for me?
I don't get it!
Ah, President Mitsuki!
Little Sister
Haru
Good morning! It sure is cold today.
Yeah...
Onee-chan, you didn't get to school yet?
Haruka
Yuu
We'll leave you behind.
It's so chilly!
Yuu-chan!
You're so warm.
Let go, Haruka. It's hard to walk.
irritated
Nope! This is what you get for always being so blunt.
How lucky.
Yuu gets to link arms with her without a care in the world.
What's that supposed to mean?
Big Sister
Was I jealous of Yuu just now?!
I call a mulligan! I wasn't thinking that at all!
Oh, President. Good morning.
Are you having fun down there?
Big Sister
U-Um, sorry, I didn't mean to pull that hard...
What do you need?
I was watching Yuu and Haruka-san just now...
A-And I got this weird feeling all of a sudden...
I-I think I want to try it too.
Try what?
squeeze
This! Linking arms!
Well good for you, you got to try it.
Let's back up here, President Mitsuki.
Is there a specific person you want to link arms with?
Well...
Haruka-s—whoa, not what I meant.
scary
Y-Yuu...
Then you don't really need us.
You can do it as much as you want at home.
It'd be really awkward, seeing how we're sisters.
I don't think Yuu'd care all that much.
Do sisters usually keep their distance like that?
Not usually, but my case might be different since I'm much older.
Why don't you go over and stick your arm in there?
But she's long out of sight by now.
I'm pretty sure I saw them go down a back alley together.
To do what?!
Was this way a shortcut?
No, I'm pretty sure this is a big detour.
What reason could they
possibly have to go this way?
Kaede, time?
Plenty. We have spades of it until homeroom.
You heard her, President Mitsuki. Let's go tail—
Let's go link arms with them!
Onwards!
She was definitely starting to say "tail them".
Kaede, you remember what's down this road?
I think there was a park.
A park? This is making less and less sense.
Other than that, it's just a residential area.
Perhaps they went off to do a secret arm link they can't let anybody else know about.
Big Sister
Little Sister
What are you implying? You can't be serious.
It can't be!
West Misato Park
Made it!
I don't see them.
They might be in there.
Haruka, Yuu?
What were you two doing in there?
Ah, you know...
We were actually planning to tell you two later today.
President Mitsuki's graduating soon, right?
I was thinking it'd be nice if we could show her how thankful we...
P-President Mitsuki?!
She heard us!
I'm awful at hiding surprises.
It's the same thing that happened with Yuu-chan!
I didn't hear anything.
President Mitsuki...
I'd like you all to take care not to arrive at school late.
That's all I wanted to say.
I'd better be going now.
Big Sister
What happened to linking arms with Yuu?
I'm fine now. That weird feeling from before is all but gone.
Look out!
Onee-chan!
That's so uncool!
Big Sister
Oh no!
Man, that stings... President Mitsuki, are you all...
Huh?
She just sped off at top speed.
The rest of us should get a move on too.
Sure.
It feels like you could've just had that conversation in our classroom,
so the fact that you went to the park...
"A Sour Plan?! Take Two"
The end
Yuzu-chan Becomes One With The Wind!
Must be sweet to ride to school on a scooter.
What's with you so early in the morning?
You said you finally got a scooter, so I camped myself out here to see what it was like.
Didn't you get cold waiting?
Not at all. I'm actually burning up.
Why?
keikaku
I wanted to stuff this inside Haruka's desk.
The heck's that?!
I found it in a subculture shop.
Man, I was so excited I ran all the way here.
You amaze me...
Aren't you going to get your license?
My birthday's not until February.
Oh, so you're still too young.
What kind of stuff did you need to learn?
Y-You're getting a license too, right? You'll find out on your own.
You must have done something unspeakable.
Don't tell me...
You ran someone over?!
I did not!
Well, not technically...
Technically?
It's kind of a long story...
Driving School
Start your engines, everyone.
We'll start off by having you ride slowly one at a time.
As I instructed earlier, your right handle controls the acceleration.
Hey! Who said you could start moving?!
I'm sorry!
blocked
The instructor's freaking amazing...
That was kinda scary, but it's pretty fun now that I've got the hang of it.
That was such a smooth turn!
It feels like I could ride out beyond the horizon like this.
Is probably what you thought, right?
No!
She read me!
First melody!
Second melody!
Now then, Yuzu my friend...
Yeah, yeah, here's my math homework.
That's not what I want!
What, you need English today?
I didn't say anything about your homework!
Then tell me what you want.
You're stressing me out here.
Help me figure out what to do with this.
What's that?
woosh
My math notebook.
I was doing the homework when my younger
siblings came and demanded I play with them.
And then...
What method of play could lead to such a mess?!
Kaede-oneechan, I wanna play house.
Then I'll be the high schooler drowning in homework.
Here you are, Dear.
Father
Mother
Here you are, Dear
Father
Mother
Thanks.
Thanks
Kaede, dinner's ready.
I'm too busy with homework.
So you're saying your mother's cooking isn't good enough for you?
Go punish her!
Dear, you've forgotten your tie.
Oh, thanks for that.
"Dear"? But you were just treating him like an attack dog!
Come down, Kaede!
Pops, let your daughter study in peace.
Your dinner's getting cold!
Then help me with my homework.
We'll help!
I spilled the juice, Onee-chan.
Don't let it get on the floor! They only just gave me my own room!
The pages are all stuck together, Onee-chan.
Peel them really carefully.
They ripped off, Onee-chan!
Something like that.
I'm not sure what to say... were they seriously planning on doing high school work?
Well, whatever. Let's hit up the convenience store.
Get a loose-leaf notebook this time.
I call riding on the back!
※Illegal Traffic Maneuver!
No you don't!
What about the thing that the
neighborhood punks look like they'd do?
※Illegal Traffic Maneuver!
You got a death wish? We're walking.
I bet it would've been really fun.
Well, get it out of your mind. You're not gonna get a license thinking like that.
You have to be able to follow traffic laws before you can get one.
Darn, I'll have to reflect on my thoughts.
Kaede, you're not teaching your siblings anything weird, are you?
You bet I am.
Hey.
Do not fear, my little brother and sister are good kids at heart!
I hope your silliness doesn't rub off on them.
Thank you very much.
Nice, all that's left is to copy everything from Yuzu.
Hey.
Just joking.
Here.
touch
That's for you.
This thing's freezing!
It's Haruka and Yuu.
Hey!
Geez, you shook that around, didn't you?
I accidentally gave you the wrong one.
You...
Good morning, Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan.
Morning!
Morning.
Kaede-chan, what happened there?
Nothing really.
Kaede-chan!
There's something sticking out of your pocket.
Though my plans got messed up, I still got the reaction I was looking for.
Extra
Yuzu-Chan Becomes One With The Wind!
The End
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!
Next Episode
Hey, Yuzu-chan.
What's up?
Why does my sister call you "Mikan-san"?
That's what I want to know.
Huh? You're not the one who told her to do that?
Why would I?!
But Onee-chan has a really good memory... ah.
What?
Uh, i-it's nothing.
There's something you're not telling me!
Next time, Trick 10:
"A Snowy Day, Memories, and an Impact"
"Usual Shenanigans in the Gym Storage Shed"
and "Usual Shenanigans in the Gym Storage Shed".
Look forward to it, 'kay?
Spill the beans!