Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
Why is Nishiyama here?
Why is Hayama here?
Hayama is moved to tears?
Were those flashes of my life?
She is still alone.
That's...
Here!
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
"Cat Café"
"Tricky Cat"
Now, now, no fighting. Let's all be fwiends.
Nishiyama, your drink's ready.
Oh, okay!
Kono's gotten so big.
She's quite the troublemaker now.
Welcome! Is a counter seat okay?
Yup.
Wha--
What?!
"You've Got Them Hooked"
Teru!
Are you awake? Let's go out.
"Central Shopping Arcade"
I found a shop that you might like.
Oh, like a boutique?
Oh, right here. I heard it's new. Let's go in.
"Cat Café" "Tricky Cat"
N-No. I'd be cheating on Bel! I can't!
You've already been going to other places!
"Tricky Cat Coupon" "30 min 600 yen→ 300 yen"
Here's a coupon.
You were planning on coming here.
I've heard about this place. I wish you'd
told me we were coming here.
I wanted to surprise you.
--My phone camera's not that great.
--Welcome. Is a counter seat okay?
--Sorry.
Why is Nishiyama here?
Why is Hayama here?
Just my luck. She'll ruin
my cat café experience.
Oh, isn't this your friend?
H-Hello. Nice to see you again.
It's Nishiyama. She's just a classmate.
Oh, you were the one who took in
the last of the cats Teru picked up.
Oh, yes.
Oh, oh. What did you name her?
Oh yeah, I never asked.
Her name is...
Ours is "Bel" after "Beelzebub,"
because she was swarming with flies when we took her in.
"Bel"
I gave her a name that will give her a long life,
"Eternal"
"Eternal" or "El" for short.
"El"
What?!
Oh, it's nothing. Eternal? It's just
obvious that you used the dictionary.
By the way,
the names of the kitties here are "Princess Konohana Sakuya,"
"Princess Konohana Sakuya"
"Lakshmi," "Viracocha," and "Teutates."
That's a little much.
All of their names are so refined.
Nishiyama, think about it. You'd be using
those names at the vet or out in public.
Oh. Anyway, I didn't come here to talk to you.
Right, Mi? I've missed you!
Oh, Nishiyama, thanks for always coming.
Hello! Mi is here today. I was worried
since she wasn't here last time.
--Sorry to make you worry.
--What a pro. You can tell she's a regular.
--She wasn't feeling well.
--Not like I care! I'm not angry at all!
Really? I didn't know
Nishiyama goes to cat cafés.
It sounds like something she would like.
I wonder if she'll send those pictures to me.
If you just went to the cat café,
maybe you don't need this.
Don't need what?
A ticket for the petting zoo, Animal Town.
What?! I need that!
Okay, okay.
"Animal Town" "Free Entrance"
I got them from Sakura's mom,
and I thought you'd want it more than me.
Wow, thanks! It's good for two people.
When should we go?
What?
It's good until Sunday. We have three people,
so we can split the last ticket.
--I'm not going.
--Huh?
I don't really like animals...
What?!
And I have work.
Wait, what?!
Oh, you can go with your sister.
With my sister?
All right! Let's have some fun!
H-Hey!
Wow. So cute!
Be gentler with the small ones.
--That one is cute. But, this one is cute, too.
--Calm down. Adore them one at a time! Big Sis!
--That one, too!
I feel like it'd be tiring, and I
wouldn't have the time to have fun.
Oh, yeah!
Animal Town?
"Animal Town" "Free Entrance"
Yup, Miss Yoko and I can't go. How about it?
--What, really?!
--Hey!
Why are you inviting Nishiyama?
Don't you think she'd like it?
You went to the cat café together.
We didn't go together!
I have a bad feeling about this.
"Animal Town"
Morning.
Morning!
I didn't think Nishiyama was going
to come because of Hayama.
Her love of animals was stronger, then.
Kondo! You were worried, too?
Yeah, you know how they are.
They went in!
Let's go in, too!
"Animal Town"
"Welcome"
Welcome!
They're still at the entrance...
Yes, over here.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Oh, you're in charge of sales.
Are you always working here?
When will they go in?
It's been ten minutes already.
Nishiyama, you'll run out
of memory at this rate!
Honestly, I don't want to stay with Hayama.
We can split up or something from here.
First, I'll go see the small animals that are closest,
"Small Animal House"
then go to the dog show.
"Dog Run" "Dog Show"
Then, to the cat room, small dog petting corner,
"Doggie Petting House"
watch the animal show, then the horse park.
"Horse Park"
Okay, Hayama. We can split up from here.
Oh, really?
No way. Did she have the same plan in mind?
Jump and catch!
"Animal Town Doggie Show"
Jack succeeded!
Wow, that was amazing!
Hayama is moved to tears?
Despite the increasing number of unruly
human children, dogs are amazing!
Actually, dogs are better!
Don't think about it like that!
I guess they're going around together.
Will they be okay? They might
fight or something...
Well, I don't think Hayama will get angry today.
Really?
She vowed to exercise self-discipline.
Self-discipline?
To broaden her experiences by
getting to know all kinds of people.
Freedom from worldly attachments or something.
I see... I don't really get it.
But, if Nishiyama keeps
picking a fight with her...
There! Over here!
Wow, Nishiyama. You've got them hooked.
Oh? Well, it's natural if you own a cat.
Maybe you're just not good at it?
Yeah, I'm not that good at it.
Oh, are you drinking juice?
I'm being healthy and got tea.
Cold juices have too much sugar.
You're good. I should follow your example.
"Doggie Petting House"
That's a Weimaraner.
In America, it's known as the "Grey Ghost."
You don't even know that?
You sure know a lot
about animals. You're amazing.
Of course!
Hm, I don't know why, but she's
in a good mood today.
It's like she's another person entirely.
N-Nishiyama's going at full throttle!
The dam might break soon...
Nishiyama!
Today was more fun than expected.
I guess I could thank you.
Nishiyama...
Huh? Wh-What?
That Hayama! I was nice enough
to go with her and she... she--!
Will you cheer me up?
Thanks, El.
How was Animal Town?
It was fun! I want to go again.
And Nishiyama? How was she?
Same as usual. She got angry
half way and left, though.
What?
The petting houses and shows were fun, too.
Maybe she left because I said that her getting
carried away with herself was the funniest.
Those two just don't get along.
Quite right.
"Stuffed Hut"
But you know, I really thought it was a good chance!
For what?
You know how Hayama and Nishiyama
went to Animal Town together?
What...
I thought it was a good chance for them
to understand each other better.
Futaba...
And maybe they'd reach a point where it
wouldn't be as awkward in class anymore.
Oh...
You like the same things.
You should be able to get along.
Didn't I say the same exact thing to you?
Finished the Mega Ogre Omelet Rice!
And time's up!
Aw, I lost.
I couldn't finish.
Don't think you've won just yet, Futaba Odagiri!
"Stuffed Hut"
I'll remember this!
Thanks for coming.
Can you get along with him even
though you have similar interests?
Sorry, not happening.
Hayama!
Let's start a band!
You took way too long to say that.
It's the autumn of the arts.
What is going on?
Oh, Miss Yoko. You should join our band!
Nishiyama, Kondo! You look like
you want to be in a band!
What?!
Big Sis.
♪ River of Three Crossings ♪
♪ I cannot cross, but still...  ♪
--My, what a wonderful voice.
--♪ The tears trail down ♪
♪ I disappear with the foam, om ♪
--Oh, I feel dizzy.
--♪ Om, om, om. ♪
--She's slightly out of tune.
♪ River of Three Crossings in the beautiful spring ♪
I want to pick that flower.
Yamaji, be my ladder.
There!
Get it, Yu!
♪ River of Three Crossings that Kou sings ♪
♪ Om, om, om ♪
Miss Yoko!
Wake up, Miss Yoko!
G-Good. You're awake, Miss Yoko.
You scared me, because you suddenly fainted.
Were those flashes of my life?
And that was "River of Three Crossings"
by Kou Hayama.
So grim!
The River of Three Crossings
is like the River Styx, right?
People tend to start singing
without thinking about it.
Like when you're alone or
trying to calm a baby down.
Nishiyama, you always sing songs dedicated
to Eternal in your room, right?
I do not!
Oh, I want to hear it.
I told you there's no such thing!
♪ Nishiyama! Nishiyama! ♪
--Hey, cut it out!
--♪ Nishiyama! Nishiyama! ♪
♪ Nishiyama, yeah! Nishiyama, whoo! ♪
♪ Nishyama, yeah! Nishiyama, go! ♪
Nishiyama got super mad yesterday, huh?
Come on, I feel sorry for her.
You can't say that after what
happened at Animal Town.
Oh?
That's...
It's Kondo.
She is usually with Nishiyama.
It's strange to see her alone.
She is still alone. Did she get into a fight
with Nishiyama because of yesterday?
She is all alone, even though she
is always usually with her friend.
Come on, bread is better.
Rice is the best!
Kondo...
Is it okay if Kondo joins us for lunch today?
When I saw her alone, I couldn't
help but invite her.
I do not mind.
Do not worry over that nobody who
gets mad over such trivial matters.
Huh?
Miss Yoko is being excessively welcoming.
She understands what it's like to be a loner.
What? Nishiyama's not a nobody!
She's actually really
hardworking and a nice girl.
She's just intolerant of others.
Anyway, let's eat lunch. Come on!
I see. So you've known Nishiyama
since elementary school.
Yup. We were in the same group
during a field trip in third grade.
She was our group leader, and she helped
me out when I was a little slow on things.
And she's liked roles that end
with "leader" ever since?
Exactly.
And she wasn't always like this.
You know how things don't always
go the way you want in high school.
There's someone who's always in her way here.
Oh no, is it my fault?
Nishiyama could get along so nicely
with Hayama if she weren't so crotchety.
They like the same things, too.
If she were reasonably nice
on the outside like Hayama,
she could be the next class representative.
--Huh? Hey--
--Same goes for you, Nishikawa.
What?
Stop being so prickly and snobby
and talk to people around you.
You're pretty, so I'm sure there
are people who admire you.
Y-You think so?
--Yeah! When pretty girls aren't friendly,
--I can't tell...
--people won't want to approach them.
--...if she's complimenting, belittling, or just plain insensitive.
So why not try harder to talk to people?
R-Right...
Thanks for today.
Oh, it was nothing.
Futaba Odagiri!
You beat my brother in a
challenge again, didn't you?!
I didn't mean for it to be a competition.
And you're always eating lunch with
Nishikawa, always just the three of you!
Huh?
Oh, I'm just special.
Special?!
She's so interesting.
You're up there with her, too.
At ramen, you've just got to get veggies
piled high, dumplings, and a pork rice bowl, right?
Um, will you come with me somewhere?
Oh?
Let's see. You're...
Hello, auntie.
Nishiyama's friend who has no tact.
Kondo is here to buy a cake Nishiyama
likes so they can make up.
Make up?
Oh, I know!
Here!
What in the world is that?
Something that Nishiyama likes.
Oh, that's Nishiyama's uniform
from when she worked here.
I said cake, did I not?
That's funny.
I'm glad you're amused.
Oh, auntie, you used to be one
of Nishikawa's servants, right?
Yes.
So Nishikawa really was a rich girl.
She can be intimidating and overbearing.
Kondo is pretty amazing.
She's as scary as a final boss.
I really do admire you.
Huh? What about me?
She should be apologizing after getting
mad about something so small,
but you bought an apology gift.
Uh, Miss Yoko. I think you misunderstand.
Huh?
Kondo wasn't alone today because
she got into a fight with Nishiyama.
Nishiyama was absent, because she was sick.
Wh-What?! I-I just thought...
See? I sent a ton of emails to her to see how she's doing.
"To: Selina Nishiyama" "How are you feeling? Get better~!"
What?! A-All this time I thought...
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
It was kind of your fault, too.
"Asako Kondo"
What? She suddenly stopped emailing me after lunch.
She sent so many in the morning,
I couldn't sleep.
Thanks. You're so nice, El.
♪ "E" in "Eternal" is for your
cuteness that can't be expressed. ♪
--She's actually singing a song dedicated to Eternal.
--♪ "T" is for your tremendous overflowing love. ♪
--So there really is such a song.
--♪ "R" is for reaching beyond hyperspace. ♪
--When should we enter?
--Let's listen until the end. It's such a nice song.
--♪ "N" is for the nameless blooming flower. ♪
--What?!
♪ "L" is for...  ♪
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life
is so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
It's Asako...
...and Selina's preview for the next episode.
I've had enough! Just do whatever!
Oh, really? Then, why don't you sing
a character song or something?
What?!
♪ Character song! ♪
"clap"
I-I guess I have no choice.
"Next time: Curry Tastes Better on the Second Day"