Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Hey, Kagami.
Do you like chocolate wafers?
I do, but...
Really.
Then here you go.
Enjoy!
Oh, thank you.
Let's enjoy our meal!
There's still more.
I have even more, so help yourselves!
Wait, why do you have so much?
Well, you know those toys that come with snacks...
I can never seem to get the one I want,
so I ended up buying a bunch.
Yeah, there are people like that...
Just go for the prize and forget about the food.
To Each Her Own
A fox.
Hmm...
A squirrel.
A dog.
What's with you all of a sudden?
Oh.
I was just wondering what kind of animals you guys would be.
I like pulling pranks, so I'd be a fox.
Based on her image, Tsukasa just seems like a dog.
Yu-chan is like a small animal, so she'd be a squirrel.
I see.
And I bet you want to call me a tiger or wolf or something, right?
Nah.
You tend to get lonely easily, so you'd probably be a little bunny.
Plus your twintails look like bunny ears.
That's kind of embarrassing, so cut it out.
That's really interesting.
M-Me?
A bunny?
What about everyone else?
Yui-neesan is really energetic, so I would say a leopard.
Iwasaki-san is cool and graceful, so maybe a hawk.
Yuki-chan has that pure white atmosphere,
and just seems to shout fluffy for some reason,
so probably a sheep.
Fumoffu.
Nah.
Miyuki-san has to be a cow!
Especially around "there".
And you're just like an old man...
Yesterday we were at Konata's house...
...and looked at some of her writing from elementary school.
Is that so?
But you know,
Konata may look like a sloppy person,
but she actually takes good care of things like that.
My dad told me to keep that stuff safe.
But what was really a surprise,
was her list of future aspirations.
A veterinarian, or a lawyer...
Normal jobs like those.
Is that so?
Well, the way her dreams changed every year...
Definitely seemed like something Konata would do.
When you look at those,
you can tell what kind of games and manga I was into at the time.
Oh, I get it...
I see now...
So that's how it was.
Then again, some people put down bride as their ideal career.
That's not even a job.
That's really cute.
No.
And besides,
I was referring to you, Tsukasa.
D-Did I really?
This is why dopey people are so...
A dopey person tends to not realize they are dopey.
I don't think being dopey is the issue here...
That may be true.
Just for your information,
you're one was well, Miyuki-san.
Eh? Is something the matter?
Miyuki-san, how bad are your eyes?
Not even 20/200.
Really...
I heard somewhere that eating blueberries is good for your eyes.
That's true.
There are also carrots, which contain vitamin A.
Green-yellow vegetables, such as spinach.
Also pork, which contains vitamin B groups.
And items containing protein, such as sesame seeds and liver,
are also supposed to improve eyesight.
Also, laser eye surgery is quite popular.
But I don't think I am brave enough to try it.
And I've seen a lot of shows about eyesight training on TV.
Wow... you sure know a lot.
Well, that was only a few of the many options available.
But then why hasn't your eyesight gotten better, even though you know so much?
I may know a lot, but I haven't actually tried any of them.
Why not?
Well...
I wonder why?
Why don't you try a couple!
Like the eyesight training one.
Right now?
Well...
First, you close your eyes...
Then open them really quickly!
And then you face straight and move your eyes from side to side.
Then up and down like this, without moving your head.
Miyuki-san!
Your head!
Your head is moving!
U-Umm...
W-What...
T-That's strange...
I think you can stop now...
My eyes feel more exhausted now than when I started.
Won't that make your eyesight even worse?
Hey, Kona-chan.
What's moe?
Well...
When you put it that way...
I'd say it's a word used to express your liking of something...
But I'm not sure I can put my finger on the specifics.
What's this?
So you've been tossing it around without even knowing what it means?
My take on it is that, if you can use the word in a sentence properly, you're an otaku.
Not that I care, but I think I understand what you're saying.
"We've got dogs from all around the world!"
"Here we go!"
Puppies are so cute!
Dad, let's get a dog!
Hey now, Tsukasa.
You make it sound so easy.
But you have to walk it, feed it, clean after it.
Can you do that?
And puppies and full-grown dogs aren't the same.
Are you prepared to take care of a living being instead of an object?
Y-Yeah, you're right...
I should think it through...
B-But Onee-chan, you seem to know quite a bit.
Well, that's because...
Well, I guess that just means I thought about it, too.
So I went and did the research.
Look, Konata!
You like this artist, right?
Why don't you read it?
Okay, fine.
I will.
Don't get so close.
*stare*
Stare
Um...
Do you need something?
I was wondering how far you'd gotten.
Did that Osano person show up yet?
No,
I don't think I've reached that level yet.
Now, now...
Read faster.
There sure are a lot of elections this year.
It's killin' me.
You think so?
Oh, what's with the long faces?
Seniors should go home and study.
Ah, Sensei.
We were just talking about how there have been too many elections.
That was out of the blue.
Election coverage delays the schedule for regular programming!
Last time the first airing of a show was delayed by four hours!
On top of that, they try to show updates on the election during the show!
And the L-shaped ticker crops the screen!
But you know,
election coverage is educational, so it teaches you about current events.
You shouldn't go on about anime all the time!
Besides, air times change regardless of elections.
K-1, for example,
pushes back regular programming.
I thought you liked martial arts, Izumi.
Konata
I have experience, but I'm not that interested!
Nanako
Even anime has special programs sometimes, right-?
My honey-!
Konata
But they don't run overtime and create problems for
the following show so it's okay!
Nanako
Bah, a college applicant should worry less about that
and study-!!
Konata
Gotta finish with a power attack-
Sorry for the wait.
Kona-chan doesn't have her umbrella.
You could at least check the weather forecast.
Maybe I should be like the guys and just not care if I get wet and go home.
But I wonder why boys don't care about getting wet?
Probably because they don't have to worry about their bra showing through white shirts.
I see.
That might have something to do with it,
but don't just say it so loudly!
Have you no shame?
So, can one of you lend me your umbrella?
Well, we're going to the same place,
so I guess we could make do with one.
Thanks a bunch!
You don't leave an umbrella at school?
But you leave all your books and things here.
Well, I had one until the other day...
But I used it once and forgot to bring it back since then.
It's not something I do daily.
So if it's not a habit, you don't learn.
Hey, Suzume!
Wait up!
Oh, yeah.
Do you guys ever think you look lame when you're wearing a raincoat and galoshes?
I suppose so.
It just seems so childish.
Then how come it's so moe when you see it in art?
How should I know?
Yo, Konata!
Good morning!
What's the matter, Tsukasa?
I got in trouble because my cell phone bill was too high this month!
I hardly ever use my cell phone so I almost always get charged just the monthly access fee.
Monthly Access Charge
Is that so...
Economical, isn't it?
So you say,
but if you barely use your cell phone,
isn't the monthly access fee itself a waste?
Don't sweat the details, Kagami.
Ah, I have mail.
"Please buy some eggs on the way home."
Understood.
I will buy some...
...with Onee-chan...
...on the way home.
Was that mail from your parents?
Don't you start talking more politely when you're sending text messages?
Well, I can kind of understand what you mean...
It'll change once you get used to it.
How long have you had this?
About a year, I think?
How often do you guys change phones?
Isn't two years about the average for getting a new phone?
That's around the time when the battery starts dying.
I'm going to make it last twice.
No, three times longer than that!
Just you watch!
I don't get why, though...
I take good care of my belongings.
I make them last.
You just leave it somewhere and never use it.
Yeah...
Some people splurge on their hobbies...
But for everything else, they couldn't possibly be any more stingy.
Onee-chan, I'm sorry.
But can you loan me your world history textbook?
Again?
Geez, you're so hopeless...
Here.
Be more careful next time, okay?
I'll return it later, okay?
Your little sister is pretty klutzy, isn't she?
She sure is...
That's why I need to be the responsible one.
But do you think that's helping her?
Maybe she loosens up because she has someone to rely on.
In other words, your existence is what makes her klutzy!
That sounds quite convincing.
Hiiragi.
What time is it?
There's an alarm clock right in front of you, isn't there?
Oh, so there is.
A-A victim of Hiiragi's legendary morning violence!
For your information,
it just fell and broke.
Book Title: Lagoon Engine
Tsukasa.
Manga is fine,
but why don't you read the newspaper every once in a while, and learn up on current events?
Y-Yes!
Um...
N-Newspapers are pretty hard to read...
I can't tell which line to go to next.
I figured it was something like that.
Hey you, right there.
What's up?
Could you call Kobayakawa-san for me?
Tell her the third-year, Izumi, is here.
Y-Yes.
Kobayakawa!
A third-year, Izumi-senpai, is here to see you!
What is it, Onee-chan?
Man...
It's so fun how they suddenly start talking politely when they realize you're older.
It's so cute.
I wish I could be as tall as you, Iwasaki-san.
I wonder why there's such a big difference?
I can't say for sure,
but it may be because I drink lots of milk.
I see!
So it's the result of years of hard work, then?
No...
Life isn't quite that simple.
PAT
I was hoping for some growth in other parts, not just my height...
Since it's raining today,
we're gonna play dodgeball in the gym for PE.
Iwasaki-san, I imagine you to be one of the last ones standing in a game like this.
Because you're so good.
I tend to be one of the last to the end, too, for some reason...
I wonder if it's because I'm hard to hit since I'm small?
I'm not all that good at throwing the ball either.
They can both survive till the end...
But for completely different reasons.
I'd also feel bad if I hit Kobayakawa-san with the ball...
I don't really understand it myself.
That's too bad.
We're on different teams.
But it looks like we're together.
Yeah!
Iwasaki-san seems to be good at sports,
so I'm afraid she'll show no mercy.
Head........Out of the question
Upper Body....A strong hit might make her feel sick
Lower Body....She might fall and get hurt
But what if I let someone else do it-
I got placed on the outer side, so you don't have to worry.
That's good to hear.
Iwasaki-san is such a good person.
So Kobayakwa-san, you're on offense?
Yeah.
And Iwasaki-san is on the inside?
So I'm recei-
I mean, defending.
I was attacked by the nurse's assistant...
You okay?
You're amazing, Iwasaki-san.
You accurately nail one person after another.
Really?
Your movement and reflexes must be really good, plus, you're athletic as well.
Not particularly.
Oops...
Did she get mad because I made a big deal about it?
No, that's her being embarrassed.
Really?
If that's the case, then it's okay...
But it's hard to tell...
I see...
So she's the type that is easily misunderstood.
People who don't really know her,
get a different impression...
Have you gone sightseeing anywhere since you came here?
Yes, I went on a pilgrimage to all the sacred places.
Sacred places?
Yes, I visited Japan's three most sacred places.
You mean like Kamakura, Kyoto and Nara?
Nope, Akiba in Tokyo.
Nipponbashi in Osaka.
And Osu in Nagoya.
I also checked out some famous places around here, too.
You mean like the Tokyo Tower and Asakusa?
No, that's wrong!
Nakano and Kichijyoji!
Um...
What's the matter?
I think I got some dust in my eyes.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Tell me if it becomes too much to bear.
Okay.
I'm fine.
This is a good situation, isn't it!?
I can't...
I can't look at my friends in such a perverted way!
Hello!
Please come in!
I'll get some drinks.
Whoa, there are so many books...
This is all we have, but...
I guess Hiyorin went through such a phase, too...
Just kill me...
Just kill me now.
And this is now...
Oh cra-
Quite an improvement.
You're right.
She's really good!
Yeah.
These drawings kinda resemble Iwasaki-san.
Oh, Takarazuka Revue, huh?
Huh?
Is this me?
Is this like a fairy tale or something?
Yeah.
Show it to me when you're finished, okay?
I can't!
I can't look and draw my friends with such perverted eyes!
Tamura-san, do you want to go to Otome Road?
Yeah, that was my intention.
What's Otome Road?
You don't know!?
No...
Neither do I.
Good grief.
Otome Road, huh...
Otome Road,
lies west of the Sunshine 60 building in Ikebukuro, Tokyo.
You can find many stores that sell manga, anime, and character goods.
It's as popular as Akiba in attracting otaku.
However, unlike Akiba,
the customers are mostly female, thus the name "Otome Road".
In other words, it's a gathering place for fujoshi.
Fujoshi?
Written as "rotten girl".
Pronounced as fujoshi.
They're rotten?
W-Well, that's one way of looking at it...
H-Hey!
C'mon, the 3-second rule! The 3-second rule!
If it's under 5 seconds, the bacteria can't get on it!
We didn't even say anything.
Ah!
My beloved meatball...
What happened to the 3-second rule?
W-Well, let's just say it's situational.
Smirk
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
Okay!
We're coming at you full of energy today once again!
Through the ups and downs, Lucky Channel has made it to the 18th episode!
All right!
And you all know who the navigator is by now!
Kogami Akira!
And...
Yes!
Akira-sama's assistant,
diligently fulfilling my duties today as well,
Shiraishi Minoru!
And for today's theme,
I think we would like to introduce all the new characters...
...who have joined the regular cast!
All of them!
So many!
First, a recent addition to the Izumi family...
Konata-san's cousin, Kobayakawa Yutaka-san.
And her classmates...
Iwasaki Minami-san.
Tamura Hiyori-san.
Patricia Martin-san.
In addition!
Kagami-san's classmates, Kusakabe Misao-san,
and Minegishi Ayano-san.
This show's really firing up!
I'm sure you've all realized,
It's in the way.
but these new members...
Hey.
...have already made their appearance in the opening-
I'm tellin' you it's in the way!
Whoa! it flew!
How many more characters are they going to introduce?
We're already on the eighteenth episode!
Whatever happened to my appearance?
Ah, speaking of which,
didn't you just make an appearance?
You looked so cute in those raincoat and galoshes!
Huh?
Yeah, yeah.
What was it...
Last week I spoke with our guest, Anizawa-san,
and he told me that an actor needs to bloom!
And have a strong presence!
And honestly,
your appearance today,
brief as it was,
Made me say, "This is Kogami Akir-"
Is that so.
Hey.
Yes?
Hey!
It's nothing!
Oh!
What a shame, it's time to say goodbye.
So there you have it.
Don't hesitate to send any questions,
Hey.
opinions, or comments about the show!
Who is it?
You can send them to our homepage or to the radio show!
Bye-bii!
Turn that thing off!
Good work today!
Was it an email?
Eh?
No, it's not!
Was it a message?
N-No, of course it wasn't!
Who was it from?
W-Well, it was from my parents.
What for?
Um... well, they said I should visit once in a while...
What was your reply?
W-Well, that's...
Tell me.
Well, basically...
Zutto sagashitetanda...
I've always been looking...
Unmei no hitotte yatsu wo
...for my partner in destiny.
Sore wa kitto kimi sa
I'm sure you're the one.
Konkyo nanka wa nai keredo
Though, I've got no proof to show.
Kimi no egao wo mireba...
When I see your smile...
Arifureta nichijou datte
...this ordinary life...
Kagayaku kara fushigi sa
...magically starts to shine.
Maurde mahou kaketa mitai
Like you cast a spell on me.
Itoshisa mo setsunasa mo...
You're the one who taught me...
Kimi ga oshiete kureta ne
...the joy and suffering of love.
Donna nagai michinori mo...
No matter how long the road ahead may be...
Futari nara kowakunai
...the two of us need not fear.
Kyou to iu tokubetsu na hi ga...
I'm so very happy...
Kimi to issho de yokatta
...I could spend this special day with you.
Kono boku no subete de kimi wo...
I'll protect you for eternity...
Eien ni mamoru yo
...with everything I have...
I promise you...
There.
I think I screwed up a little on the falsetto...
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It was touching!
Thanks.
Touched!
That's so old!
Next Episode
John Lennon
「 Coolest man in the world 」
「 Shoot, coward...
You are only going to kill a man 」
Che Guevara
And next week on Lucky Star:
Hiyori here!
Patricia here!
Rely on the Nurse's Office
Reality
Patty, are you used to your part-time job yet?
Yes!
I'm good!
With Patty working there,
even first-timers can probably enjoy themselves without getting nervous.
No, I don't handle first-timers.
Is that so?
I only serve groups that have visited often and leave big tips!
It's store policy.
That's pretty harsh.
Next time: "2D has Substance."
「 2D has Substance 」
Look forward to it!