Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Hey, Kagami.
Do you like chocolate wafers?
I do...
Really.
Then here.
Enjoy!
Oh, thanks.
Thanks a lot!
I have more!
I have even more, so help yourself!
Wait a sec.
Why do you have so much?
Well, you know those toys that come with snacks.
I can never seem to get the one I want, so I end up buying a whole bunch.
Yeah...
Some people just want the toys and ignore the snacks.
To Each Her Own
Fox.
Um...
Squirrel.
Dog.
What are you babbling about?
Oh.
Just wondering what kind of animals everybody might be.
I like to play tricks, so I'd be a fox.
Based on her image, Tsukasa would be a dog.
Yu-chan's like a small animal, so she'd be a squirrel.
I see.
So you probably want to say that I'm a tiger or wolf or something.
Nah.
You get lonely really easily, so you'd probably be a bunny.
Plus, your twintails look like bunny ears.
That kinda feels embarrassing, so stop.
This is fun!
Me?
What about everyone else?
A bunny?
Yui-neesan is hyperactive, so maybe a leopard.
Iwasaki-san is all cool and suave, so maybe a hawk.
Yuki-chan has that whole white feel,
and then she just shouts fluffy for some reason,
so probably a sheep.
Fumoffu.
Nah...
Miyuki-san has to be a cow!
Around there...
That's what an old man would say...
We were at Konata's place yesterday,
and saw some of her writing from grade school.
My...
Is that so?
But you know...
Konata may look like a sloppy person,
but she actually saved that stuff.
Dad told me to keep that stuff safe.
But the real surprise...
...was the list of her dreams for the future.
Veterinarian and lawyer...
Regular jobs like those.
Really.
Well...
The way her dream changed every year was definitely Konata-esque.
When you look at those,
you can tell what kind of games and manga I liked at the time.
I get it.
That's what it was...
Back to that again.
Then again, some people put down bride for their ideal job.
That's not even a job.
That's cute!
No.
And like, Tsukasa...
I'm talking about you.
R-Really?
This is why airheads are hopeless.
Airheads tend to not realize they're airheads.
It's not an issue of being an airhead!
That may be true.
Just so you know...
That includes you, Miyuki-san...
Is something the matter?
Miyuki-san.
How bad is your eyesight without glasses?
Under 20/200.
Really...
I heard somewhere that eating blueberries is good for your eyes.
Indeed.
There are also carrots, which contain vitamin A.
Green-yellow vegetables such as spinach.
Pork, which contains vitamin B.
And items containing protein, such as sesame seeds and liver...
...are said to be good for your eyes.
Also, laser surgery is the subject of much attention.
But I'm not brave enough to try it.
And I've seen shows about eyesight training on TV.
You know a lot.
Well, I've only named a few of the many options.
But why hasn't your eyesight gotten better if you know so much?
I haven't actually used any of the methods I know.
Why not?
Well...
I wonder why...
You should give it a try!
Like that eyesight training thing.
Right now?
Well...
First, you close your eyes.
And open them really quickly!
Then you look left, right...
...up, and down...
...without moving your head.
Miyuki-san!
Your head!
Your head is moving!
Wh-Wha-
Huh?
H-Huh?
T-That's strange...
You can stop now...
I may have ended up exhausting my eyes...
Won't that make your eyesight even worse?
Hey, Kona-chan.
What's moe?
When you put it that way...
It's definitely used to express that you like something,
but I don't really know the specifics.
What?
So you use it without knowing the meaning?
I'll just say that to anyone who understands the general meaning is hardcore.
Not that it really matters,
but I kinda understand.
We've got dogs from all around the world!
Okay!
Puppies are so cute!
Dad.
Let's get a dog!
Hey, Tsukasa.
That's easy to say,
but can you train it, walk it, feed it,
and take care of all the other things?
Puppies and adult dogs look pretty different.
Are you prepared to care for a living being instead of an object?
Y-You're right...
I need to think it through...
B-But you sure know a lot about it, Onee-chan.
That's 'cause, yeah...
I'm also pretty simple...
So I went and looked stuff up.
Look, Konata!
You like this artist, right?
Read it.
Fine.
You're such a pain.
Your face is really close.
Stare
Um...
Do you need something?
I was wondering how far you'd gotten.
Did that Osano person already show up?
No.
That's still beyond my limits.
Come on.
Read faster.
There sure are a lot of elections this year.
It's killing me.
Really?
What's with the gloomy faces?
Students should go home and study.
Sensei.
We were talking about how there have been too many elections.
Where did that come from?
Election coverage messes up the schedule for regular programming!
The first airing of this one show was late by four hours!
And then they have updates in the middle of the program!
And the L-shaped ticker just makes the screen smaller!
But you know...
Election coverage is educational in terms of current events...
You shouldn't keep going on about anime.
Besides, air times change even without elections.
Stuff like K-1...
...pushes back the regular programming.
Don't you like martial arts?
Konata
I have experience, but I'm not that interested!
Nanako
Even anime has special programs sometimes, right-?
My honey-!
Konata
But they don't run overtime and create problems for
the following show so it's okay!
Nanako
Bah, a college applicant should worry less about that
and study-!!
Konata
Gotta finish with a power attack-
Sorry for the wait.
Kona-chan doesn't have an umbrella.
You could at least check the weather forecast.
Maybe I should be like guys and just not care and go home.
But I wonder why boys don't mind getting wet.
Because they don't have to worry about bras showing through.
I get it.
It makes sense...
...but don't just blurt it out loud.
Don't you have any shame?
So...
One of you lend me an umbrella.
Well...
We go home together,
so I guess we can make do with one.
Thanks so much.
You don't leave an umbrella at school?
But you leave all your textbooks here.
Well...
I had one here...
But I used it once, and I haven't remembered to bring it back.
It's not a daily routine or anything.
So you only remember if you've made a habit of it.
Hey, Suzume!
Wait up!
Oh, yeah.
When you wear a raincoat and galoshes,
you look pretty lame.
That's true.
It makes you look like a kid.
So why is it so attractive in art?
Like I would know.
Yo, Konata!
Good morning!
Er...
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
I got in trouble 'cause my cell phone bill was too high!
I rarely use my phone, so I only have to pay the monthly access charge.
Monthly Access Charge
Really...
Economical, isn't it?
So you say,
but if you barely use it,
the monthly access charge is already a waste.
Don't sweat the small stuff, Kagami.
I got a message.
Please buy eggs on the way home.
Understood.
I'll go buy some...
...on the way home...
...with Onee-chan.
Hey.
You're talking with your parents, right?
Doesn't it end up more polite when you're using text messaging?
Well, I pretty much know what you mean.
It'll change once you get used to it.
How long have you used this?
Maybe a year.
How long before you usually replace it?
Isn't two years about right?
That's around when the battery starts dying.
I'm going to double...
No, triple that time!
Just you watch!
I don't get the point.
I take good care of my possessions.
I make them last.
You're not even using it.
Yeah...
Some people splurge on their hobbies,
but pinch on everything else.
Sorry, Onee-chan.
Can I borrow your world history textbook?
Again?
Geez, you're hopeless...
Here.
Be more careful next time.
I'll return it later.
Your sister's pretty careless.
She sure is.
That's why I have to be the responsible one.
But maybe it's that...
She has somebody to rely on...
...so she lets loose.
In other words, your existence allows her to be that way!
That sounds really convincing...
Hiiragi.
What time is it?
There's an alarm clock right in front of you.
There is.
A-A victim of Hiiragi's legendary morning violence!
Just to be clear...
It fell and broke.
Book Title: Lagoon Engine
Tsukasa.
You can read manga,
but you should read the newspaper every once in a while.
It's good to know what's going on in the world.
Um...
T-The newspaper's hard to read...
I can't tell where the next line starts.
Thought it might be something like that.
You there.
What is it?
Could you call Kobayakawa-san for me?
Tell her the third-year, Izumi, is here.
Y-Yes.
Kobayakawa!
A third-year, Izumi-senpai, is here!
What is it, Onee-chan?
Man...
It's so fun how they're suddenly polite when they realize you're older.
So cute.
I wish I could be tall like you, Iwasaki-san.
I wonder why there's such a big difference.
I can't say for sure,
but it may be because I drink lots of milk.
I see!
So it's the result of your daily efforts!
No...
Life isn't so simple...
PAT
I was trying for growth of a different kind...
Since it's raining...
...we're gonna play dodgeball in the gym today.
You seem to be the last person standing type, Iwasaki-san.
Since you look strong.
I actually end up being one of the last ones left if I'm on the near side.
Maybe it's 'cause I'm hard to hit since I'm small.
I'm not even that good at dodgeball.
They both survive...
...but for very different reasons...
I'd kinda feel bad if I hit Kobayakawa-san.
But I don't really understand it myself.
That's too bad.
We're on different teams.
Looks like we're together.
Iwasaki-san looks like she's good at sports,
and she won't hold back, so it's scary.
Head........Out of the question
Upper Body....A strong hit might make her feel sick
Lower Body....She might fall and get hurt
But what if I let someone else do it-
I got placed on the outer side...
...so it's okay.
That's good to hear.
Iwasaki-san's a really nice person.
So Kobayakawa-san is attacking?
And Iwasaki-san is on the inner side?
So I'm recei-
Er...
I mean defending.
I was attacked by infirmary staff...
Are you okay?
You sure are amazing, Iwasaki-san...
You hit one target after another.
Really?
Your movement and reflexes are great.
Not particularly.
Oops...
Is she mad I made a big deal about it?
No.
She's embarrassed.
Really?
That makes me feel better...
But it's hard to tell...
I see...
So she's the type that's easily misunderstood.
People who don't really know her,
get a different impression...
Have you gone on any trips after you got here?
I went on a pilgrimage to all the sacred places.
Sacred places?
Yes.
I visited Japan's three most sacred places.
You mean like Kamakura, Kyoto and Nara?
No.
Akiba in Tokyo.
Nipponbashi in Osaka.
And Osu in Nagoya!
And I also visited some sites around here.
You mean like Tokyo Tower and Asakusa?
That's wrong!
Nakano...
...and Kichijoji!
Um...
What's wrong?
I think some dust got in my eyes...
Are you okay?
Tell me if gets unbearable.
I'm okay.
Good situation, isn't it!?
No!
I shouldn't look at my friends with perverted eyes!
Hello!
Hey!
Come on in!
I'll go get drinks.
So many books...
This is all we have...
So Hiyorin once had such a phase...
Kill me now...
Really, just kill me...
And this would be now.
Oh, shi-
You can tell she's improved.
You're right.
She's really good!
This picture kinda resembles Iwasaki-san.
Takarazuka Revue, huh?
Huh?
Is that me?
Is this like a fairy tale?
Please let me see it when it's done.
No!
I shouldn't draw my friends in perverted ways!
Tamura-san.
Shall we go to Maiden Road?
That was the plan.
What's Maiden Road like?
You don't know!?
Neither do I.
Good grief.
Maiden Road, huh...
Maiden Road...
...is a street west of Sunshine 60 in Ikebukuro, Tokyo.
Many stores sell manga, anime, and character goods.
It's as popular as Akiba in terms of attracting hardcore fans.
However, unlike Akiba,
the customers are mostly female,
which is why it was named Maiden Road.
In other words, it's a gathering place for fujoshi.
Fujoshi?
Written as rotten girl...
Pronounced fujoshi.
They're rotten!?
Well...
That's one way to look at it...
Y-Y'know!
The three-second-rule! The three-second-rule!
If it's under five seconds,
there won't be any bacteria!
What?
We didn't say anything.
My beloved meatball...
What happened to the three-second-rule?
Well...
Just let me say that it depends on the situation.
Smirk
Good lucky!
Okay!
Let's have another blast today!
We've managed to make it to the eighteenth episode of Lucky Channel!
Okay!
You all know who the navigator is by now!
Kogami Akira!
And...
Yes!
Akira-sama's assistant...
...working hard again today...
Shiraishi Minoru!
Well, today's theme...
...is the introduction for all the new characters...
...who have joined the regular cast!
All of them!
Too many!
First, the addition to the Izumi family...
Konata-san's cousin.
Kobayakawa Yutaka-san.
And her classmates...
Iwasaki Minami-san.
Tamura Hiyori-san.
Patricia Martin-san.
In addition!
We have Kagami-san's classmates.
Kusakabe Misao-san...
...and Minegishi Ayano-san.
It's gotten rather lively!
As you may have already noticed...
It's blocking me.
...the new characters have been appearing in the opening...
Hey.
I said that it's blocking me!
It went flying!
How many more characters are they going to introduce!?
We're on the eighteenth episode!
What happened to my appearance!?
That's right, Akira-sama.
Didn't you just make an appearance?
That adorable image of you in a raincoat and galoshes.
Yeah.
What to say...
Last week,
I was able to talk with our guest, Anizawa-san,
and he told me that an actor needs initiative!
And presence!
Indeed.
Your appearance today,
brief as it was,
was screaming to me: "Kogami Akira is here-
You sound passionate.
Hey.
Yes?
Hey!
Ah, no.
It's nothing.
Oh, no!
It's time to say goodbye.
So there you have it.
We're waiting for you to send us any questions or comments about the show!
Hey.
Who is it?
You can direct them to our home page or the radio show!
Then bye-bee!
Turn that thing off!
Then good work!
Was it a message?
No.
No, it wasn't!
Was it a message?
N-No way!
Of course not!
Who's it from?
Uh, it was from my parents.
About what?
Well, they wanted me to go visit...
What was your reply?
Uh, you know...
Say it.
Well, basically...
Zutto sagashitetanda...
I've always been looking...
Unmei no hitotte yatsu wo
...for my partner in destiny.
Sore wa kitto kimi sa
I'm sure you're the one.
Konkyo nanka wa nai keredo
Though, I've got no proof to show.
Kimi no egao wo mireba...
When I see your smile...
Arifureta nichijou datte
...this ordinary life...
Kagayaku kara fushigi sa
...magically starts to shine.
Maurde mahou kaketa mitai
Like you cast a spell on me.
Itoshisa mo setsunasa mo...
You're the one who taught me...
Kimi ga oshiete kureta ne
...the joy and suffering of love.
Donna nagai michinori mo...
No matter how long the road ahead may be...
Futari nara kowakunai
...the two of us need not fear.
Kyou to iu tokubetsu na hi ga...
I'm so very happy...
Kimi to issho de yokatta
...I could spend this special day with you.
Kono boku no subete de kimi wo...
I'll protect you for eternity...
Eien ni mamoru yo
...with everything I have...
I promise you...
Okay.
Kinda screwed up on the falsetto.
Sorry.
It was touching!
Touching!
Shankya.
That's so old!
Next Episode
John Lennon
「 Coolest man in the world 」
「 Shoot, coward...
You are only going to kill a man 」
Che Guevara
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Hiyori here!
Patricia here!
Rely on the Nurse's Office
Reality
Patty.
Are you used to your job yet?
Yes!
Perfectly!
With Patty around,
first-timers can probably have a fun time without being nervous.
No.
I don't handle first-timers.
Really?
I only serve people who've visited lots and paid lots!
It's store policy.
T-That's pretty harsh...
Next time:
「 2D has Substance 」
"2D has Substance."
Look forward to next time!