Summer break will be over soon, right?
Yeah.
Then school will start, right?
I can't wait!
You can't wait?
Because we'll see all of our classmates again.
Classmates?
Toorun!
Hey, Yutaka!
Ah, another blank.
Listen, Run-chan.
A lot of boys tend to crowd around you. Why's that?
Really? I don't think that's even the case.
I wonder why...
Has anybody a-asked you out yet?
Asked out?
That reminds me...
Of what?
I got this from Sato-sensei.
He said he liked this kind of thing, and gave it to me.
It's unusual for someone to like candles, isn't it?
I don't think it's the candle that he likes.
fuwa fuwa fuyuushite
フワ・フワ・フユウして
I float lightly in the air,
kirameku tooku no sora to
キラメク遠くの空と
becoming one with...
hitotsu ni naru
ひとつになる
...the distant, glittering sky.
kazeyomi, kimama na
風読み、気ままな
I read the wind, and wander away,
watashi no yukue wa kanata
わたしのゆくえは彼方
To a far off destination.
issho ni ikou?
一緒に行こう?
Do you want to come with me?
shinkokyuu hazundeku
深呼吸はずんでく
I fill my lungs and set off,
sekai no Spring Breath
世界のSpring Breath
Taking in the world's spring breath.
taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
太陽にあつまるの みんなの笑顔
While at the sun above, everyone's smiles are gathering.
ohayou to sayonara no aida wa
オハヨウとサヨナラの間は
In between our hellos and goodbyes,
watashitachi dake
わたし達だけ
There is only us.
nandemo dekiru ne!
なんでもできるね！
We can accomplish anything!
sukitooru hizashi
透き通る日差し
The rays of the sun pass through,
umaretate no sora
うまれたての空
Creating a newborn sky.
machiawaseta yakusoku no morning Arch
待ちあわせた 約束のMorning Arch
The promised morning arch that we were waiting for.
te wo furu kimi e to
手を振るキミへと
As you wave to me,
totteoki no kyou wo watasou
とっておきの今日を渡そう
I decide to share with you a special day,
oshaberi ga hajimaru
お喋りがはじまる
And our idle chatter begins.
Summer Festival
Hey, hey. Look at this!
Sign: Summer Fireworks Display
Let's all go together!
What is it?
They showcase a fireworks display every year, if I remember correctly.
Is that right?
There are lots of stands with plenty of commotion.
It's this weekend.
And summer break is going to be over soon, so I'd really like to go with all of you.
Right.
Let's all wear yukatas.
Let's do that!
Yeah.
Well, it'll be nice for a change.
That's that then.
Hey, what are you guys doing later today?
Haven't thought about it.
It's hot. I don't want to move around.
Then let's go to karaoke!
Karaoke, huh?
Karaoke is good; I love karaoke!
Yuuko, are you into that?
Yeah, I can sing most of the popular songs.
Run, which ones do you like?
Let me see, that place has really amazing Jambalaya.
Their ramen is unexpectedly good, and their parfaits have large portions of ice cream.
Weren't we going to karaoke?
Yes, we are.
Karaoke
This is a little cramped.
It is. I'll order drinks and food.
What do you guys want?
Melon soda.
Grapefruit juice.
Tooru, what do you want to drink?
I-Iced tea.
My pleasure.
Hello, I'd like to order.
Hey, they have the newest songs from this month.
I'd like two iced teas, one melon soda, and one grapefruit juice.
I'll put mine in first.
...also Jambalaya and potato chips please.
Yes. Yes, please do.
Well, here I go.
Take me summer breeze.
Take me away, take me summer breeze.
My love is feeling the breeze.
Catch me summer breeze.
Gently, touch me summer breeze.
One summer's dream, taking you home.
Yuuko is really good at this.
She really has some talent.
Taking you home.
Take me summer breeze.
Thank you.
I gotta put another one in.
Tooru is looking pretty serious over there.
Is she stressed out over something?
Take your time picking.
Why is she staring at me like that?
Ocha melodical beauty ban ban (Intro)
Well then, I'll be going next.
A gallant awakening, gravity pulling back to sleep.
Sneaking out of those days of weeping and cuddling.
Best friends fighting off an innocent obsession.
The ultimate word is "Love", I say.
Let's tell everyone,
the oracle of our magic,
mixed up with some trendy words.
Ocha melodical beauty ban ban,
with a big smile.
Are you done staring down the song catalogue?
Ah, that song?
I'll put it in for you.
And "send".
Nicely done.
There.
It's starting.
Give it your best, Tooru!
Erm...
The mic!
What is it, Tooru?
Beyond the clouds
(Intro)
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
The Jambalaya is here!
This is hot, so please be careful.
The grapefruit juice is for me!
There you go, Nagi-chan.
Thank you.
The melon soda is mine.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Huh?
She doesn't want to sing at all.
I'm sorry for forcing it on her.
Touching in the twilight, it's a maiden's naiveté.
A fruitless love is fine with me, if I could meet you just once more.
Wow.
You really put some feeling into that.
Two songs to go.
You have lost 10 kilocalories
If I sing two more songs, I'll be able to eat eight chips!
A diet?
Quit worrying and eat.
Hey Tooru, isn't that the song you like?
Tomodachi
There. Right?
But I've never sung before, so I might not be able to do it.
It's gonna be fine.
Tooru, it's turned off.
I'll start it off.
Run-chan.
Let's hold hands,
beyond the vast hill.
Like 1, 2, 3, there's going to be more fun.
A white blanket, a puppet with large eyes
A polkadot skirt, but we can't share that.
Even if we trip, or almost cry, we're still together.
And when the excitement expands, that must be happiness.
Let's hold hands,
walking straight ahead.
Like 1, 2, 3, there's going to be more fun.
Only three left...
That wasn't very nice of them.
Nobody has anything queued up?
Then I'll put one in.
Do that after you're done eating.
And now for the next song...
The next stall over?
There was nobody inside before.
Did they arrive just now?
They seem to be pretty good.
But it's a somewhat stifling song.
It's starting!
Run-chan, don't sing.
Why?
Just do it.
Huh?
Tooru?
No way...
This voice...
What? What is it?
I really want to sing some karaoke with Run-chan.
Anyway, let's go for another one!
I really enjoyed that.
We've got to go again.
I want to learn to sing.
Hey, I remember seeing a TV show recently about learning how to sing.
Training for next time
Number 1
It's been a while since I wore a yukata to a festival.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've got a few of them. Which ones should we wear?
This colour on this one is stylish.
It's mature-looking.
Let me see.
Did I even have one like this?
This is mouldy, and that's why it changed colours...
You can't wear these just yet.
Some of my older ones might fit.
I'll go get them.
These look grown-up.
They probably belong to Run-chan's mother.
With these, I might become as tall as 1*0 cm.
I'll never become an adult like this...
Mum!
Hm?
Look at you.
We put them on. How are they?
Today is the festival, right?
Flowers suit you both.
You look great.
Thank you.
But the festival starts in the evening, right?
It's only 10 AM.
We were a little overexcited.
There they are.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
That makes all of us then.
You look cute whatever you wear, Yuuko-chan.
Nagi-chan, you've... curled up your hair!
You're right.
Right.
It's cute.
Well, I... do it once in a while.
There won't be fireworks for a while, so let's go visit the stands and kill some time.
Can we go to the mask stand first?
Yeah.
Huh, so you're into anime for kids?
No.
Because I always get handouts from stands run by the shopping district, so I feel bad.
I see.
Candy apple!
Candy apple...
Yuuko-chan, may I have a bite?
Sure, there you go.
It's delicious.
What's up, you want some too?
Not really.
I see.
Let me have some of your cotton candy, Run.
Sure.
This is good too.
Huh?
Yuuko and Nagi are tossing rings.
I hit number 3!
Congratulations, that wins you a set of fireworks.
To have fireworks as a prize at a fireworks display...
Here we go, I'm next!
I'm shooting for the first prize!
Wow...
Wow, I've already spent this much.
The stands are expensive, so you can't go about wasting your money.
You might not be able to buy anything else later on.
But seeing all this stuff sure makes me want to have it.
You have to be smart and choose things you can enjoy longer.
Shape-cutting?
Nagi, why don't we do something we can all do together?
Have you ever played shape-cutting? It's pretty fun.
Really?
Let's try it then.
Yeah.
I've never done it before.
Then let's go with something easy.
It broke!
Mister, another one!
Here you go.
This is pretty difficult.
Hurry up!
Let me finish my yakisoba!
Thank you for your patience; the fireworks display will commence shortly.
The fireworks have started already!
Let's hurry!
It's crowded.
I know a nice place!
Let's run up there, and we'll be able to see!
Nagi, we're done with shape-cutting.
My gourd!
It's right up these stairs.
I don't think I care about the fireworks anymore.
Nagi, let's go.
Heh?
I can't...
Keep it up, Nagi-chan.
Please let us get there in time!
We're here.
It's the finale!
A-Awesome.
As of now, the fireworks display is over.
Please take your trash home with you or dispose of it in the proper places.
It's over.
No way...
Just seeing the end feels lacking.
It's a little sad.
I know! I won these fireworks at that stand!
Right. Nice one, Yuuko.
But we don't have fire.
Don't fret!
Matches?
A candle?
You brought those?
Why is there nothing but sparklers in there?
This is plain.
But I like these somewhat.
You're right.
They are pretty.
Delicious.
You eat too much.
Ah.
Satou-sensei? Why are you here?
Why, you ask?
Don't get too close to me!
That's my line.
Speaking of which, you're here alone?
I'm not alone!
Get me another beer.
But you are alone.
I'm telling you, I'm not!
There you go again.
Summer break was nice.
I guess.
We also went to the beach.
Let's watch the fireworks next year, too.
Right.
Next time, I'll complete my shape-cutting.
What's up with that?
What do you mean? It was fun, no?
It was unexpectedly immersing.
Right, Tooru?
Yeah, it was fun.
akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
茜に並ぶ背高かげぼうし
Lined up in the sunset are our tall shadows.
tanoshii ichinichi no owari
たのしい１日のおわり
It's the end of an exciting day.
tsukinai oshaberi
尽きないお喋り
Chatting without end,
mada mada aru keredo
まだまだあるけれど
but there's still so much to say,
sorosoro ouchi ni kaeranakucha
そろそろおうちに帰らなくちゃ
But we'll have to be heading home soon.
ja ne, ashita ne  meeru suru kara
じゃね、明日ね メールするから
Bye, see you tomorrow. I'll send you a text tonight.
kyou no peeji ni minna osoroi no egao
今日のページにみんなおそろいの笑顔
Today's chapter ends with us all smiling.
ja ne, ashita ne  itsumo arigatou
じゃね、明日ね いつもありがとう
Bye, see you tomorrow. Thank you for everything.
kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
今日も一緒に居れてヨカッタな
Isn't it wonderful that we can be together every day?
rururun, kaze to, kokoro hamingu suru
ル.ル.ルン. 風とこころ ハミングする
Lu lu lu, our hearts hum with the breeze,
tsugi no kado de furimuki nagara bai bai
つぎの角で振り向きながらバイバイ
At the next crossing, we'll look back at one another as we say goodbye.
Preview
If you're talking about the end of August, you're thinking about...
...the sound of cicadas, typhoons...
...summer homework....
...Dad, who will finish your handicraft for you...
...peeing in front of an abandoned house...
...accidentally get caught while taking photos...
I hastily drew the picture diary, but I don't remember what the weather was!
...the newspaper that is being recycled before your very eyes...
Even though it's like this, I still want to see this episode, Bibi-sensei!
Next Time!
New Term
Next time, on A Channel, New Term.
Though we're not in elementary school anymore...