When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Then we'll see you later, Maria.
See you later.
Oh, yeah, Maria.
If you have time, go rent the DVDs
listed here from Wataru's store.
I understand.
It's cold, so please be careful.
It's not a problem!
I have that taken care of!
It really is cold.
Huh? What the? Where's the Miss?
Hey, don't turn around!
I'll be directly in the wind!
What?!
You're very resourceful, Miss.
Good morning, Hinagiku.
What's wrong? You're all spaced out.
Hinagiku!
Oh!
I'm sorry. There's
something on my mind, so...
What?!
Could it be that walking disaster
sprinkler of a superintendent
has been up to no good again?!
Oh, that woman should
be enjoying her vacation
on a tropical island right about now.
Here you are, Mistress Kuzuha. Say, "Ah!"
But surely we didn't have to do
the New Year's Breaking of the Mochi
all the way out here...
Well, it's for good luck, after all.
Th-Then, what in the world...
Actually, my sis gave me New Year's money.
What?!
Miss Katsura gave you New Year's money?!
New Year's Money
To Hinagiku From Sis
She came over to the house yesterday
and left this on my desk.
I mean, it was just 500 yen in there, but...
500 yen?!
Oh, that's all?
Th-That's a fortune!
All I ever got every year
was red beans or peanuts.
Morning!
Now, now. You're going to be late
if you're too caught up in chitchat.
You're under arrest!
There, a knock to your noggin.
Sh-She's not her usual self!
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of
the wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
M-Miss Katsura's acting
differently than usual!
She's sparkling somehow!
What in the world happened, Sis?!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naive and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Despairing Goodbye to the Teacher
~A Graduation Special
What's wrong, you guys?
Well, it's not really anything,
but your Gigantor-esque change
in personality has us shocked...
Could it be that you went
and ate some plants
or maybe laughing mushrooms
from the side of the road?
Oh? Why do you ask?
Wh-Why? Well, because...
It's just...
It's just that today is a very
special day for me.
A special day?!
Well, it's almost time for the faculty
morning meeting, so later!
This is...!
What?!
Katsy's quitting being a teacher?!
Yes, that appears to be the case.
What should we do?
Wh-What is so funny?
Because that's just bananas!
Yujiki quitting being
a teacher is inconceivable.
Yeah, that's right. If she quit,
where would she live?
But she's clearly been
acting strangely since morning
and she said today was
a special day or something.
On top of which, she even
gave Hinagiku New Year's money.
Perhaps she plans to quit Hakuou
and go somewhere far away...
Yeah, right!
If that turns out to be true,
I'll shave my head bald!
I'll change my name to Spicysaltedcodroe!
Then I'll change the title of this anime
to "Yamabiko the Combat Butler"!
Don't change it without permission!
Well, for example, if you actually
saw her letter of resignation,
then I'd be convinced.
Yup, yup.
Letter of Resignation
What?!
N-No way!
I never imagined it could be true!
More like, if you found it,
tell us that first!
K-Katsy!
Oh? Can I help you with something?
Is the story about quitting true?!
It's a joke, right?!
Tell us it's a joke!
Yes, it's true.
What?!
R-Really?!
Yes, today's the last day.
Today?!
Isn't that sudden?!
I'm sorry.
I don't know, it was just hard
to bring it up to you guys.
Tell me it's not true, Sis!
Hina.
Come on! What's there to do
if not teaching?!
There are plenty of things to do out there.
Traveling, starting over in life...
Why?! Why did you keep quiet
about such an important thing?!
That's right! Don't be
such a stranger, Katsy!
So true, so true, sauce true!
Why wasn't there any discussion of this?!
As an adult, there's no need
to discuss every little move like that.
Don't worry. Plenty of thought
went into this decision.
Miss Katsura!
I'm sorry about catching you
all unawares, but you see...
Goodbyes have a way of suddenly
sneaking up on you one day.
It's sad, but life is full
of sudden goodbyes.
There are no dandelions in winter.
Oh, Marilla, I guess when you're
truly sad, the tears just won't come.
Sudden goodbyes...
But in exchange,
I'll never say goodbye to you.
I'm sorry, Matthew,
but I can't even must a single tear!
Sis, you jerk!
See if I care about you anymore!
Just go die in some ditch somewhere!
H-Hinagiku!
Hina...
Hina, let's go home soon.
Look! Awesome, huh?
I got all this New Year's money!
Me, too!
Um, this was from Daddy.
And this one's from Mommy.
This was from Granny.
And this one was Grandpa!
Hina.
Oh, Sis!
Come to think of it, I still hadn't
given you your New Year's money, right?
Hold out your hand.
Huh?
Here.
You'll have to let me off
with that for this year.
But in exchange,
I'll never say goodbye to you.
Really?!
Of course, by all Maeda's Crackers!
Come on. I'll give you a piggyback ride,
so let's hurry on home.
Okay!
Sis, you liar!
Oof, off we go.
(Rukkorase tto.)
I guess ages trumps all.
(Toshi ni wa katenai no ne.)
I never thought Katsy would seriously quit.
It doesn't seem real.
When all's said and done, she's
been there for us in so many ways.
How are we to survive the homework
assignments and tests from now on?
This seems to have come as a great shock...
But something about this bugs me.
What?
She may be capricious,
but this is on a whole another level.
Perhaps, but there's no disputing the facts.
Aw, man,
I wish we could've had at least one
more class of Katsy's world history.
Yup, yup.
Oh, yeah.
With the 6th period homeroom next,
it's goodbye Miss Katsura.
That's it! Homeroom!
Um, then let's get homeroom started.
Um... um... Today's topic is...
Me! Miss Katsura!
There's parts of the rise
and fall of the Frankish Empire
that I don't understand, so could
you give us a lecture on that?
What?!
I want an encore of the Reconquista
during Spain's middle ages!
What were the four apples
that go down in history again?
Is it true that Pythagoras
was allergic to broad beans?
Is it true that the inventor
of instant curry was British?
We have lots of other questions,
too, so please teach it all to us!
You guys...
All right! You got it!
Yes!
Since it's come to this, we better
fully enjoy Yukiji's final lecture.
Okay, are you listening?
This part is key. Key, I tell you.
1806, the Berlin Decree!
Make sure you get that in your heads!
Mm, Miss Katsura's lectures always
did move along at a good clip.
She seems irresponsible,
but she's actually a good teacher.
By the way, did you know
that Napoleon was into fortune telling?
And she teaches us stuff
that's not in the textbooks, too.
It was a simple method,
where he held a coin in his left hand
and flipped a crêpe in a frying pan.
But he did it five times
and he messed up on the fifth try.
That was the year 1812!
Yup! The year he failed
in his invasion of Russia!
But I guess we'll never get to attend...
...these lectures again...
Got it? This part is key, too.
Make sure you check it out
in your textbooks later.
Oh, by the way,
the reason Napoleon always has his
right hand in his pocket is because...
Uh, wait. Why are you crying, Miss Segawa?
You idiot! Don't cry!
Th-These aren't tears! They're
leftover water from last night's bath!
Good!
Huh?
I see, so you guys finally understand.
That history is built
on layers upon layers of tears!
Saying hello and goodbye,
and then saying hello again!
It's those connections between
people that make history!
Yes, ma'am!
The kanji for "man" depicts two
people leaning on each other!
Man
Yes! Man cannot live life alone, you see!
We can't live...
...life alone...
Once Sis is gone, I'll also...
There isn't a soul out there
who goes through life alone.
Even when people are apart,
in their hearts, they remain connected.
That's what I believe.
I want you all to understand that, too.
And please don't forget.
The tears are the sweat of the heart!
And that love is the labor of the heart!
That concludes our class.
Thank you, everyone!
Don't go, Sis!
Please don't quit!
There's still lots more
that we want to learn!
And lots more fun we want to have!
Ma'am!
Without you, my life would be
in less danger and it'll be boring!
Wh-What are you all talking about?
Even after all this, are you still
going to quit and leave us behind?
At least stay with us until we graduate!
Please promise!
Promise?
Could it be that this was...?
Uh, um, you guys...
Please don't quit!
Thank you, everyone!
I had no idea you cared so much
about me! It makes me so happy!
What?!
Working as a teacher was a lot
harder than I ever imagined and...
Sorry about this. We've
got one more place to go to.
What?!
Please get up!
That's why I handed my letter
of resignation to Miss Katsura.
Letter of resignation?
You don't mean... this?
Oh, that's it!
Oh, uh, sorry about that.
I forgot to give it to the superintendent.
Thank you very much!
Observing your lecture,
I was able to realize something.
To realize just how wonderful the bond
between teacher and student is!
Everyone, please forgive me
for not seeing how deeply you love me!
Wh-What's going on?
Oh, how touching this is!
Um...
Huh? What?
Um, um, there's a huge storm
of "why" brewing here...
So, you're not quitting, Yukiji?
Huh? There's no way I'd quit.
What?!
Then what about that unnaturally
sparkling smiley aura from this morning?
Oh!
Because today's been a super
lucky day for me since morning!
Shut up!
Here's Mistress Nobuko
Saeki's fortune for today!
Congratulations! In first
place come the Scorpios!
Particularly for those of you
with blood type B, who love to drink,
and whose pinky toe nails are long,
this is a once in a dozen
years super lucky day!
As if stuff like that's ever accurate.
A l-lucky standing tea leaf!
The egg!
The eyebrows!
Rhapsody of the Koalas
Choco-balls
The angel!
R-Red snappers!
That's what happened!
Don't you think it's amazing?!
Uber happy! Super happy!
I'm totally on a roll!
Wh-What?!
Look, look! These are the actual goods!
No wonder even Napoleon
believed in fortune telling!
For my stupid sister's numerous
misleading, bothersome reactions,
I am truly sorry
for the trouble she's caused!
It seems we jumped to conclusions, too.
I thought it was strange from the start.
What did we cry all those tears for?
We'll make sure to get back at you for this!
Yeah! Give us a free pass
for 50 years' worth of homework!
Wh-What did I ever do?
I'm never going to
believe in fortunes again!
And thus, the spinster teacher
grew ever more dispirited.
Oh?
Then what meaning was there in Miss
Katsura giving you New Year's money?
That mystery's already been solved.
Damn it. Come at me with everything
you got. You sons of bitches.
She's so utterly hopeless.
I'll give you real, proper
New Year's money someday, okay?
When is someday?
Hmm, next year...
No, I'm not quite sure I can make that.
In three years...
Err, well... In ten years...?
I'll get it to you for sure
by New Year's ten years from now.
Okay!
Video Rental V Tachibana
Let's see, "Pirates of Sanriku Coast"
and "Spider Guy 3", right?
Here!
Thank you, as always.
Tell Nagi to make sure she
returns them by the due date.
Yes, I understand.
Maria!
Um, if you don't mind,
please take this with you.
Urusai People
Oh, my! But...
Please think nothing of it.
My grandma sent me a massive shipment.
Th-These are...
They're still available?
Or rather, where in the world
is Saki's grandmother from...?
Oh?
What should I do?
The New Year's card I wrote for Hayate...
I've been trying to decide
whether to send it or not
and now the New Year's here already.
More like, didn't I decide
that my resolution for this year
was to become a mature woman,
brimming with courage?!
Happy New Year! Here's to another
great year! Ayumu Nishizawa
I can't do it! I'll come again tomorrow!
Ow!
What the hell was that?
Trying to pick a fight, bitch?
What should I do?! What should I do?!
I think I might get killed!
You listening?!
I'll beat the crap outta you!
Mess with us and we'll get you good!
Or actually, why do I always get
into trouble like this?!
You've got some nerve tackling me like that!
Oh, yes, Miss Nishizawa, isn't it?
It is, right? Hayate's friend, as I recall.
You were of great assistance last year
when you let Nagi stay the night.
Oh, no, um...
As you saw, she can be
a difficult child in many ways,
but I hope you'll continue
to be friends with her.
Uh, okay...
Oh? Who are these gentlemen?
Are they your friends?
Wh-Why would you think that?
Who the hell are you?!
You're a maid!
Just 'cause you're a maid
with some cute looks,
you better not ignore us, you moron!
I'm so sorry. I don't understand Klingon.
That was Japanese, ya moron!
You keep giving us lip
and you won't get away with it,
no matter how cute a maid you are!
What a boorish man to suddenly attempt
to grab a woman by the collar.
Wh-What the hell was that?!
That was just Xing Yi Quan.
Though, I only know enough for self-defense
and it's only useful
for catching someone by surprise.
Damn it!
You're not gonna get away with this!
I would advise you against that.
Or getting injured will be
the least of your worries.
Shut up!
See?
No! Help!
Were you hurt in any way?
N-No. Thank you very much.
Not at all.
More importantly, about this...
You dropped it.
Th-This is n-n-nothing! Nothing at all!
I will pray that this turns out to be
a good year for you, Miss Nishizawa.
What?
Oh, yes, if you'd like... Here.
See you then.
"I want to become a woman like her
this year," thought Miss Nishizawa.
Did anything unusual happen at school?
Not really.
Did anything happen during your day, Maria?
No, nothing of particular
note for me, either.
But why is it? I suddenly have
a craving for marshmallows.
Next time, they will battle
against sine, cosine, and tangent.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Yukiji Katsura's
Lettering by Hitomi Nabatame
Yukiji Katsura's...
...Butler Report!
Butler Report
Hello! I'm the charming
female teacher, Yukiji Katsura.
Hey, listen to this, everyone.
My character song's finally complete!
I was a bit nervous about
recording for the first time,
but I did my best for my fans!
Hey, Sis, what are you doing?!
Oh, Hina, I didn't know you were here.
Don't tell me you didn't know!
We're doing this segment together,
so we even had a rehearsal
yesterday, remember?!
Did we?
Well, anyway, Hina even joins me
on the second song on the disc,
so please make sure you get it.
Oh, the royalty's all mine, okay?
Bye-bye!
Preview
Doesn't he have any weaknesses or anything?
Weaknesses?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
For the heroes of manga and anime,
they tend to come with
weaknesses by default, you know?
I see... Is that how it works?
The butler-in-debt's weakness, huh?
All right, leave it to me!
Guys like him sometimes have
the most unexpected weaknesses!
Next time, "Like a Dog,
a Mouse and a Bulldog".
I have a good idea.
What's this good idea?
That is...
Like a Dog, a Mouse, and a Bulldog
Borg Get On to "Hayate
the Combat Butler" again next time!