Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemuri asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Come on, senpai!
Let me test out my new move on you!
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
I call it the "120-Hour Beating"!
One, two, hey, yo, let's dance!
Hey come on, it'll be fine!
New move! New move!
They're so cute, aren't they Shiina-san?
How shallow...
Are you ignoring me?
Seriously?
What is this, an elementary school?
Fine, I'll go ask Oyama-senpai!
All we do is take on more brats.
Are you talking to me, scum?
I am your God.
What? You still on about that?
You were clinging onto Otonashi and crying like a baby.
Who was crying?
The one crying will be you.
Now, you will realize the greatness of clothespins,
and in comparison, your worthlessness, and despair.
A clothespin...
You pin it...
You pin it and it doesn't fall...
The laundry doesn't get dirty!
So beautiful!
You can use it instead of a paper clip or just about anything else!
I'm nothing compared to it!
I'm so worthless!
Hey, don't use hypnotism to fight back.
There's no hope for me at all!
Otonashi-san, good morning!
What did you do to him?
He came at me first.
I tried to be gentle.
What part of that is gentle?
You have a grown man on his knees crying like a baby.
Otonashi-kun, Naoi-kun.
I have something to discuss.
Come with me for a bit.
Staff Building 3rd Floor — Empty room
What is it?
Why did you call us all the way out here?
Naoi-kun, I want you to try to recover Otonashi-kun's lost memories.
Are you giving me orders?
Who do you think you are—
Your leader!
And your superior.
Just do what she says.
Wait...
My memories?
Yes, your memories.
Naoi-kun's hypnotism is the real deal.
He can make you regain your memories.
I see.
I'd love to give that a try.
Wait a second!
Don't just go ahead and decide that!
Why not?
Don't tell me you don't want them back?
Well, I...
Of course I want to remember.
But why do I feel so insecure?
Is it because I might not be able to live like this if I regain my memories?
What?
I...
Do I enjoy living with everyone like this?
If I get my memories back, will I still be able to go on like this?
But even so...
Otonashi-kun?
Y-Yeah...
Okay.
No matter what kind of past you had, don't lose sight of yourself.
No matter what happens, I'll be here by your side.
Please say something...
I'll be here too, so don't worry.
Great!
That's reassuring.
Hey! What's with this difference?
Well, fine.
Please sit down.
Now then, I'll begin.
Onii-chan, is school fun?
It's not fun.
I haven't even gone.
It might be fun if you go.
Maybe if I was smart.
But I'm an idiot.
There's no place for kids with bad grades.
It's called studying.
There's no way it could be fun.
It is called studying.
What about your friends?
Is playing with your friends fun?
It's more fun watching TV or playing games by myself.
It's a pain getting dragged around for other people's hobbies and laughing at jokes that aren't even funny.
Really?
I'd love to study.
I'd love to make friends too.
Oh, right.
Here.
Thank you, Onii-chan!
Idiot!
I don't know what I'm living for.
I don't know my purpose.
I don't care about anyone else,
because it's easier to live without caring about anyone else.
Just working enough to eat and get into a daily routine...
That was all I wanted.
Even so, I kept going to see my sister.
I would buy her comics with what little money I had.
I always got her whatever I picked up first at the bookstore, so I didn't even know if I gave her the same one.
For all I knew, it might have been a different one, and the next part of the story wasn't in it.
But...
Thank you, Onii-chan!
My sister would always say that.
She would be happy with whatever I got her.
She was different from me.
She had hope in life.
She could find her purpose in life.
But she hadn't been discharged for the last two years.
It was sad...
If only I could change places with her...
I, who didn't have a purpose or meaning in life.
That compassion was what kept me visiting her.
Winter came.
Working during the summer is hard, but working in the winter is worse.
Your fingers go numb, like they're going to fall off.
But...
I kept going so I could live.
Live?
What for?
Don't think about it.
If I think about it, I might stop working.
I have to keep working.
To eat.
And to buy presents for my sister.
Oh yeah!
I'll ask the doctor if I can take her outside on Christmas.
But she can't use a wheelchair if there's snow on the ground...
I'll carry her then.
If it's just her, I can carry her anywhere.
Then I'll buy whatever she wants from any store she likes.
I want to give her a cake from a good store too.
In that case I'll have to save more money.
If you could go outside on Christmas, where would you like to go?
The main street!
You'd be fine with just that?
But they put lights on all the trees you know!
Didn't you know?
No, I don't go there on Christmas anyway.
They say it's really pretty.
They started doing it last year.
The doctor was talking about it.
Then how about we go there?
Can I go?
I'll ask if you can go.
Even if they say no, I'll sneak you out and take you there.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Yay!
Thank you, Onii-chan!
That was the biggest thank you she gave me.
What are you doing?
Sorry!
I started working multiple jobs.
I would come home only to sleep.
I was working so hard because I had a goal.
My only concern was that her condition was getting worse.
They didn't give her permission to leave.
So I snuck in after visiting hours ended and took her into town at night.
Amazing!
Hey, can you see it?
It's amazing!
Yes...
It's very pretty.
It is, right?
It's so pretty.
I'm glad I came to see this too.
Thanks to you!
We'll have even more fun from now on!
First I'll get you a present.
I'll buy anything you want.
I've saved up lots of spending money just for this day,
so I'll get you anything, no matter how expensive.
What do you want?
How about we start by going to the store?
We could even go to a jewelers!
Or maybe you'd prefer a normal department store?
Onii-chan...
Thank you.
Yeah...
And there's even more after we go shopping!
Look forward to it!
We'll do dinner for now!
I don't know much about this stuff, but I got a reservation for a great restaurant I saw in a magazine.
They make a set meal for you.
A full course dinner!
Amazing, right?
After that, I continued to walk and talk by myself.
I'll be off then.
Are you sure you'll be okay staying by yourself there?
You'll be lonely.
I'll be fine.
I'm used to it.
Really?
I worry about you though...
If you run into any problems, tell me anytime.
You can eat here anytime you like.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for taking care of me all this time.
There was a purpose I'd been living for.
I had a reason for living close by to me.
I'd just never noticed.
All I wanted to hear was "thank you".
That was all it took for me to continue living.
I felt alive when she expressed her gratitude.
I was happy.
I'm such an idiot...
I'd never noticed until now.
She was such a special person to me, and I did nothing for her.
She spent all her time in that hospital, with nothing but the comics I brought her to read.
With just that...
That meager existence...
She was probably happy.
And now that I've lost her, is my life over?
Days full of happiness that I never noticed.
I've lost that time,
and now there's nothing left for me.
Thank you for taking care of her.
Congratulations on your recovery!
Thank you very much!
Take care now!
I might be able to find another purpose in life.
Book: Medical Encyclopedia
I might discover a new meaning in living.
Devoting this life to help someone else...
Card: University Enrollment Selection Form — Otonashi Yuzuru
Have your memories returned?
Yeah...
It doesn't seem like it was exactly a wonderful life.
Can you leave me alone for a while?
You taught me the meaning to the pointless, worthless life I was living...
And after I found it, I died trying to reach my dream...
Without accomplishing a single thing...
That can't be...
No way!
How could I die like that...
Hatsune!
Have you calmed down a bit?
Yeah...
It's normal to become unsteady after recovering your memories.
It's not just you.
I'm so weak.
I've realized again how strong you are.
I'm really not.
So has anything changed?
Your feelings.
Do you think you can carry on fighting with the Battlefront?
Definitely.
I can't die like this.
I see.
So you've found a purpose?
Yeah.
Once again, I'll be in your care.
Principal's Office
So, what's your report?
We're short on meal tickets today.
What should we do?
Go with Tornado?
No, today's operation will be Monster Stream.
We're actually going to do it?!
Carnival of despair!
What is this operation?
There are monsters here in this world?!
Yes, the master of the river.
Master of the river?
There's a river a short walk from here, right?
We're going to pick up food from there.
D-Don't tell me you just mean river fishing?
Yes?
What about it?
Ah, nothing.
I got tricked into imagining something stupid again...
I wonder who'll win this time?
Botanical Garden
I'm looking forward to it!
What are you doing here?
Weeding, among other things.
I see...
Oh yeah!
Why don't you come too?
Right now we're all going river fishing.
River?
It's against regulations to go down there.
It's dangerous.
It's fine!
You're not the student council president anymore so break a rule for once!
But I'm still a student...
What do you think you're doing, bringing her along...
It's fine, right?
Let her join us.
She's the enemy!
The archnemesis of the Battlefront!
What an idiot.
How shallow-minded.
Listen, she's harmless now!
She's not our enemy!
But she was still originally the student council president!
Incidentally, the current acting president is also here with us...
Indeed.
However, my position as God comes first.
I told you, you're not God!
What do we do, Yurippe?
She's not the student council president anymore so it's fine.
Is this really okay?
We're taking on some crazy members...
I just noticed, did no one bring any equipment?
We already contacted Guild, so it's fine.
There's someone crazy about this stuff in Guild.
Below Contact Bridge 2 — Riverbank
Crazy?
Who's he?
He's called Saitou.
He also knows about guns, but he's crazy about fishing so we call him Fish Saitou at Guild.
For this operation, he brings loads of fishing gear up with him on that cart.
He brings them all the way here?
Just how much does he like fishing...
So basically he's an idiot.
Alright, let's start!
Idiot.
Maybe I'd be your friend in this world.
There's no one like that.
It's fine if there are, right?
There are none.
Even if there were, they'd all disappear.
Tachibana.
We won't disappear,
so it's okay to be friends with us.
Here, join in fishing with everyone.
What do I do next?
That's now how you do it...
First you put a lure or bait on the hook.
You're not bothered by insects, are you...
What's next?
Face the river and swing the rod with all your might!
Takeyama!!
Call me Christ!
You have some monstrous strength...
It's because Overdrive works passively.
Passively?
You might just...
You might just be able to pull it off.
What?
Reel in the master of the river!
It's a monster, like the operation name suggests.
Something's tugging.
M-Monster Stream!
What is this...
Normally we take Monster Stream as proof of the master's anger.
When this happens we all evacuate.
But with her, just maybe...
We're seriously going to do this?
Just how big is it?
The rod's going to break!
Don't underestimate my skills!
It's made to withstand even the master of the river!
Even so, it'll be impossible like this!
What, you're going to fight with the master?
You're insane.
Matsushita 5th Dan!
I'll give you a bowl of meat udon, so help us out!
Right!
Oh my, Hinata-senpai, you're an open target!
Alright, how about I kick you with all my might?
Stop thinking up stupid things and help out!
We need more of you in the battle!
What's up?
What a wimp.
Come on you runts, can't you pull any harder?!
Pull! Pull!
Now!
She reeled it in!
And pulled us up too!
Which one's the monster?
This is...
..a bad situation.
If we fall like this, we'll be eaten!
Crazy for you!
God doesn't fall.
How shallow minded...
We're gonna get swallowed!
Must save them.
Hey, with all this, we won't have to use Tornado for a while, right?
We're going to eat this every day?
More importantly, how are we going to preserve it?
It wouldn't be good to waste it either...
No choice, I guess.
How about we prepare it all at once and serve it to the ordinary students too?
Yeah, I guess.
Let's do that then.
This is almost like we're doing charity work.
We've gone from being a battlefront to some kind of volunteer group.
But we don't have an opponent to fight against anymore, so won't we stop being a battlefront?
So what will we be?
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
The "Slack so we don't vanish team"?
What the heck is that?
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
Chop chop chop chop.
I never thought we'd end up doing this.
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
Hey Tachibana, mind if I call you by your first name?
Why?
We've become friends now.
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
We have?
Of course we have!
We fished together, cooked together,
and I've always thought from the start...
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
You have such a pretty name.
I like that name.
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
Kanade means "to play a tune" right?
If you want to take it like that, go ahead.
My name's Yuzuru, written like "tie a bow".
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
You can call me that.
So Kanade, I want you to do something for me.
What?
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
Please stay with us from now on.
Why?
Because I don't want you to fight with anyone anymore.
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
I want you to enjoy your time with everyone.
And, well...
Because I want to be with you too.
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
Really?
If you say so, I'll do that.
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
It's a promise, okay?
Okay.
By the way, where's Yurippe?
Now that you mention it, she hasn't been around...
She's probably just watching over us from somewhere.
It's not like she's the type to participate in this kind of volunteer work.
Hey, help us out here!
Yurippe!
Yurippe, who got you?!
Angel.
Angel?
Wait, Kanade's been with me the entire time!
Matsushita 5th Dan!
Which means we're closed in...
I pray we can meet again.
I can't take on something that scary!
A trap...
What's the meaning of this!?
Distraction.
Is Kanade okay?
ANGEL PLAYER...
I'll tell you one possibility.
So shallow minded...
I'll persuade them by force.
It appears the time has come to show you!
Leave the one's we don't make it in time for!
You seem busy...
Please be okay, Kanade!