When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Mister Ayasaki.
I will give these ¥150,000,000 as a gift to you.
Who could this mysterious man be?
Continues on to next week's final episode!
Hey, this week's just starting!
The story flashes back to several hours ago.
Everyone, rise!
Listen! Make sure to fill this S-Ward in Tokyo with astonishment.
Ready to sing the school anthem?
Yeah!
Suginami no chi wo shihai suru
It rules the city of Suginami
It was a long, yet short, year.
Shiroki manabiya
The white academic building
But I'm really glad I was able to move on to the next grade.
Yes. With all the studying he did,
Hayate managed to pass his final exams.
Waga bokou
My school
Muneno enjin hi wo tsukete
Get the engine in your heart working.
What a shame.
Tama, step back.
Chief Butler, please don't play nasty jokes.
Let me repeat myself, Ayasaki.
The amount of debt you paid back to
the young miss in this past year is still trivial.
If you fail at any point, you will be out on
the street with a debt of ¥150,000,000 again.
Never forget that fact.
Yes, Chief Butler!
Hakuou!
All right, I'll keep up what I'm doing next year, too.
Rokumega mainichi koushin.
6MB marching down every day.
Let's go home, Hayate.
Hakuou Gakuin!
Hakuou Academy!
Wh- Please wait. Milady!
Marvelous.
Honestly, it's just more work for me, but let's all meet again in April.
End of closing ceremony!
Come on, Hayate! Get moving!
If you dilly-dally, I'll leave you behind!
Um, why are you in such a hurry?
Why not enjoy the sense of freedom a little more?
I just want to get home fast and continue playing Mon*** Portable Second G!
Huh?
That's really the only reason why I'm hurrying.
Please wait, Milady.
Looks like Hayate's puzzled.
But this is just the start.
It's my turn again.
What? Milady's important online shopping merchandise?
Yes. Can you go pick it up from that shop?
You must not look at what's inside.
Yes, ma'am. Right away.
Don't rush so much!
Go stroll out and about and waste some time.
To be specific, until around the evening.
Why?
Wh-Why...
I... I all of a sudden don't want to see your face.
Don't make me repeat myself!
Okay...
Then I will take my time and slowly come back around evening.
N-Nagi.
L-Looks like I was able to trick him well.
I bet Hayate wouldn't guess what he is off to pick up.
Nagi, wasn't that too harsh on him?
Yeah. That debt-ridden butler looked seriously depressed.
D-Don't look at me like that!
Come on everyone! Let's get the preparations started.
Nagi's traps are being set behind the scene.
Meanwhile, at Hakuou Academy...
Yukiji's snoring as usual.
What? Seriously? You'll trade me with Ma***i for ¥50,000,000,000?
Kaoru-sensei, who has appeared after eighteen episodes of absence, is making Gun*** models as always.
And, ten thousand meters above the ground...
Kuzuha-sama, we'll be arriving at our destination by tomorrow noon as scheduled.
Good. We must get our hands on this rumored item no matter what.
What exactly is the legendary item?
A mask made in ancient times by a sorcerer.
If you put it on, a strange power takes effect and one grows taller.
You're nice short,
but I would like to see your handsome version again.
Kuzuha-sama~
Shion.
Africa, eh?
I hope they come home safely before the new school year starts.
Chiharu-san, are you saying that for real?
Don't say things like that.
Even if she is like that, she is
an indispensable person at the school.
How exactly?
In what way?
Right, let's go have some tea.
I'll treat you to cake if you want.
With pleasure.
Then let us have a little party with just the three of us.
Come to think of it, I didn't see Hayate-kun today.
Looks like he was able to move on to the next grade,
so I wanted to congratulate him.
What could this be?
Judging from Milady's attitude... Did I mess something up again?
H-Hey! What? What is this?
Let me go!
Welcome, Mister Ayasaki.
I'm sorry for the rough handling.
Who are these people?
Could they be after what Milady ordered?
Victoria Elizabeth Steward Dispatch Company?
Yes. We are the largest international butler dispatch company.
I've never heard of such a company!
We have been observing you through a certain source.
When were these filmed?
The ones who filmed these were...
Ready?
Us!
Did you enjoy them?
The Hakuou Academy Motion Picture Research Club lives forever!
I see...
Mister Ayasaki.
I will give you these ¥150,000,000 as a gift to you.
The story finally returns to where we started the episode.
I am here to headhunt you into our company.
This is your hiring bonus.
Take it so you can pay off your debt to the Sanzenin family.
You even went as far as researching that?
No, thank you!
I already promised Milady
I would pay the debt back by working.
Are you sure? You may never get a chance like this again.
If you truly care about your Lady, shouldn't you use this money to pay the debt off as soon as possible?
Well...
Contact me anytime.
I'll be waiting to hear a favorable answer from you.
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
What, Tama? More to the right?
God... Why do we have to help out?
A-Are you all right, Isumi?
Oops, my hands slipped.
Hey! You!
Man, accidents are scary.
What a merry day.
Continuing to part B.
Nagi da zo!
Nagi da zo~! = I'm Nagi!
Ojyou-sama, honto ha ato ikura desuka, bokuno shakkin?
Ojyou-sama, honto ha ato ikura desuka, bokuno shakkin? = Milady, how much more do I owe you, exactly?
May never have another chance like this, eh?
He's right. For me to continue to stay with the Sanzenin family...
It might just be my selfishness.
Heck, it's no time for me to brood!
Right now, I must take this to Milady.
Eh?!
Okay! It's perfect this time!
Oh my.
This is...
It's good, isn't it?
Iffy.
Yes. It's not good per se, but it's not inedible.
Gosh! What's that reaction!
I put everything I had into making it!
But Nagi, why are you holding this large event?
Because now might be the only chance to do it.
Maria! Get me that maximum tomato!
That thing fully recovers one's health,
so I want to let Hayate have it.
Yes, yes.
I worked hard on my finals, too.
Stop complaining. Just celebrate
a fellow member who studied with you.
Hey, Sakuya.
Thanks for giving me the spot in Hakuou.
I always wanted to say it.
I-I will pay this favor back when I become a bigshot!
Stop acting like a different character!
You're just a brat!
I don't need anything! Just keep it!
Damn, the debt-ridden butler's slow.
What's taking him so long?
Itadakimasu!
There's nothing inside!
Is this a form of a lucky choice?
If so, I might be able to meet Hayate-kun.
Hayate-kun!
Nishizawa-san.
May I borrow that bicycle?
I promise to return it later.
Y-Yes!
All right, I caught up.
Ready, Eight?
There!
The dream has spoken to me! I'll become a major leaguer!
Go!
Sir, this is how you hold it.
Okay, I get it, Nonohara.
Cha! Shuu! Men!
Sir's not around today, so I guess I'll make something simple for dinner.
Hello, it's been a while since we met.
Yes...
Ah, this is... It's the 100th Master Gr*de series.
I totally thought they were Gun*** V or V2, so I could never get myself to buy these.
Saki-san!
Hello, Hayate-san.
Did you see a small box around here?
What?
Saki-san?
What's this?
Hayata-kun.
Hello all.
Can I have that box back?!
It belongs to him?
Then I can't imagine anything good's inside.
All right.
Catch!
Right here.
Ah, sorry.
I met Hayate-kun, but couldn't talk very much.
Perfect. Nishizawa-san, let me return you the bike now.
Thank you very much. It was very helpful.
Excuse me!
Hayate-kun... I'll be able to meet you again, won't I?
I look forward to working with you all next school year, too.
Yes. Good job to all.
Chiharu-san, if you're happy, you should show it on your face.
H-Hayate-kun?
What's happening?
Why did you come falling from the sky?
Ah, Hinagiku-san. I tried to jump onto
the next building, but my foot slipped.
The cake... My cake... My cake's squashed...
Huh?
Oh well. Um, Hayate-kun.
Congratulations on being able to move up a grade.
I'm sorry. I'm in a little hurry.
I'll see you when the new semester starts!
The cake...
I guess that's a penalty for him.
We'll have to bill him later.
Gosh! What's wrong with him?!
Wh-What is this series of misfortunes that hasn't happened in a while?
It's as if I'm being tested by something.
This is bad. That was a flock of geese.
Geese are large water birds categorized as anatidae, anseriformes.
They usually come down south from Siberia in autumn to spend the winter and head back north in spring.
At this rate, Milady's important item will get taken to Siberia.
All right, I guess I'll have to try it.
H-Himuro! I'm looking forward to learning Samba over the break!
You're already very good at it, Sir Taiga.
Himuro-san... That box...
Please give that box back to me...
I will depending on the situation, but are you sure about this?
This ship's heading for Brazil.
I was about to get taken away to the other side of the Earth.
But I can finally give this to Milady.
Wait, Tama!
Come, follow me!
Wait!
Now! Do it, Tama!
Banners: Ayasaki Hayate-kun!!  Congratulations on moving up a grade!!
Th-This is...
Go up already, Ayasaki. Everyone's waiting.
Um, what is this?
You're pretty dense, eh?
The effort was worth it if he's that surprised.
But, why the triumphal arch?
Where did it come from?
Nagi.
Looks like it worked.
Milady.
Maria, bring the item.
Here.
Th-That's!
Hayate, you've done well on your final exams.
This is a present from me.
So, this was all a surprise event set up by Nagi.
Open it already.
Nagi asked us about it, and we chose it together.
I did my best for the final exam, too, but I didn't get anything.
You'd better feel grateful about this!
Everyone...
I can't accept something this expensive!
What?!
I have a debt of ¥150,000,000 to you.
Not only that, but you're even letting me stay at the mansion.
Don't be such a stranger, Hayate!
Milady?
You're right. It'll take approximately another forty years to pay off your debt.
I know that!
That's why I chose that as the present!
It's famous for not breaking even after a hundred years.
Milady...
Hayate! I want to be with you all the time.
Not just forty years, but a hundred or two hundred years!
After all, money isn't the only thing that's keeping us together, is it?
Milady!
H-Hey, everyone's watching!
You spat out much more embarrassing lines.
I can't take this.
I see. That is a shame.
Well then, I wish you the best luck.
It's as you heard.
He turned down our offer. What will you do?
I guess he passes.
I was planning on kicking him out of that place if he took the offer.
Looks like he's still qualified to hold on to that.
But, of course, who knows how long it'll last.
How's the stew, Hayate?
Well, I guess it's good.
But you could say it's average.
Hey, I can feel my health getting charged.
HP max!
I didn't use that much effort to make your HP max!
Who cares!
Banners: Ayasaki Hayate-kun!!  Congratulations on moving up a grade!!
Please wake up, Milady.
Last night was fun, wasn't it, Hayate?
Yes, thank you very much, Milady.
But hmm, today's the first day of spring break.
Okay. Let's all go sakura gazing today.
H-How does this place look?
I've wanted to ride a boat every now and then.
Spring is when people's hearts start to frolic.
Today, I shall step on to a new stage with Hayate.
I'm really good with boats.
I used to work at a marina.
Oh boy. These two don't change at all even after a whole year.
Okay, let's go, Hayate!
We need to get a bicycle ready!
Yes, Milady.
Enjoy your trip.
Ready, Milady?
I'm counting on you, Hayate.
The story of the two will continue.
Next week, we'll fight against the Aegean Sea.
Nagi and,
Hayate's
Butler Network! Final Network!
How do you do? I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
So with all that's going to happen, this is the last Butler Network.
So many things have happened up to this day.
And Hayate has grown to become a great butler.
Thank you very much. I think you've grown, too, Milady.
D-Don't be ridiculous, you pervert!
What's the matter?
Someone who says stuff like that deserves this!
It's maid Hayate to commemorate the last.
The next extra series will be Hayate's Maid Network.
So until we meet again!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
The final episode.
Radical Dreamers.
Hayate, please stay with me always.
Yes! I hope you take good care of me, too.