It's hot...
It's already September, so why is it so hot in the morning?
But you finished the leftover curry from yesterday-
Good morning, Minorin!
How are you guys doing today?
G-Good...
What about you-
Hi, everyone!
Did you finish your summer homework?
Did you brush your teeth? Take a shower?
Haruta, why are you in such a good mood?
Did something good happen to you over the summer holidays?
The summer holidays are in the past!
The second semester is the present!
We are now aiming towards our next stage: the Cultural Festival!
Something new will...
It must have been nice to have an eventful summer holiday...
Yurichan-sensei?
But I guess something would happen for you guys.
It's a 17 year old's summer after all...
It's a lot different than a summer for a single woman in her mid thirties...
Man, there's so much misery in this life...
I guess nothing happened over Yurichan-sensei's summer...
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed that and I've won
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
Oubashi High School Cultural
Festival・Part 1
It's the same as last year...
The festival has been shortened to a single day again.
Even the President's powers are...
This isn't just a matter of it being shortened.
This is business.
Board: Victory is with us!!
Negotiations with the teaching staff have just begun.
Exactly.
If this goes according to our plan,
giving up two days will make it worth more.
We have to make the best out of this year's Cultural Festival.
Because this is my last large-scale school event.
Takasu-kun, let's go UFO hunting next time.
Hey, stupid Chihuahua!
What the hell are you doing?!
I told you already, my nails are too long to play ball.
They'll break.
You stupid Chihuahua!
Such a cute smile...
Ami-chan really is an angel.
I'm in the Palmtop Tiger faction.
If that's the case, I like Kashii better.
Kihara isn't bad either.
Oh, Taiga is riding on Ami-chan's back!
I want to be ridden on, too...
Ladies and zentlemen!
What the heck are you doing?
There are no ladies in here.
And what the hell does "zentle" mean?
Does everyone want to see their favorite girl's unusually cute side?
Are you all right?
Nothing weird got into you over the summer holidays, right?
Just let me finish talking!
The Cultural Festival is nearly here.
In the long homeroom session tomorrow, we're going to discuss what our class is going to do.
I also happen to be the executive member for the Cultural Festival!
So what?
So...
If for example, we choose to do a Maid Café for the Cultural Festival...
We will be able to see the girls in maid costumes!
If we concentrate our votes, we'll definitely get a majority!
How about that?
Not a bad idea...
You even thought of that...
Wait a second.
In that case, I'd rather see Chinese dresses than maid costumes!
That isn't bad either.
You feel the same way, right?
Yeah, I guess so...
Maid costumes are similar to work uniforms, so they're quite common.
But if it's a tight Chinese dress...
No, no!
If we choose tight Chinese dresses, I'll have to make breast pads again...
What are you talking about?
No, it's nothing.
Instead of Chinese dresses, let me see...
How about Lolita costumes?
Takasu...
You're a genius!
I want nurse costumes!
I want Japanese dresses!
Idiots, animal costumes are the obvious choice!
Witch costumes...
Wait, everyone! Stop branching off ideas!
Wait, what was I going to say?
Cosplay Café.
Wouldn't that solve everything?
That's it!
Taiga, I'm leaving first.
Ryuuji!
Look at this.
What is this?
Whoa, this is pretty cruel.
The stupid Chihuahua did it.
Hey...
Can you stop talking behind people's backs?
Wasn't it because you got mad and tripped over yourself?
It all started because you dodged the ball!
I told you, it was because my nails were...
Stop it.
I'll fix it up.
You're sticking up for her again...
Get it done before next week.
Hey!
Don't blame others and run away!
They sure have a lot of energy.
Kushieda?
Let's get back to class, too.
Yeah, I guess...
Oh, right...
About the UFOs...
Instant noodles are truly enemies to warriors on diets!
Huh?
Oh, may God bless us...
This place needs patching up.
I'll borrow some fabric from Yasuko's old wooly shirt.
It's ringing, Taiga.
Just ignore it.
Seriously, that damned old man...
Damned old man?
Who's that?
Anyhow, I'm worried about it...
Your cell phone-
Shut up!
Why are you suddenly so...
I told you to ignore it, didn't I?
He's the man who threw me into an apartment because he thought I'd hurt his new marriage.
He abandoned me.
He's a cold person.
Wait, isn't that your father?!
No, he's a damned old man.
Regardless of what he's like, he's still your father.
Don't call him a damned old man...
Being a family means that even if you're split apart, somewhere in your heart...
...there should be...
I said he's a damned old man!
Damned... Damned...
Don't say stuff like that!
Different mother...
Diff... Different... Different mother...
Inko-chan is...
What? Are you talking about your daddy?
No, not my dad!
He was an amazing person!
In order to avoid getting stabbed...
Again with those stories?! They aren't amazing at all!
And don't talk about those stories in front of others!
But...
So, we're going to decide on what we're going to do and who's going to participate in the beauty contest!
Discussion Topic
Cultural Festival
Cultural Festival Executive Member - Haruta Kouji
I don't think anyone has a problem with entering Ami-chan into the beauty contest...
So our problem now is what exactly we should-
Class Member - Kawashima Ami
I'm sorry, I'm afraid that's impossible.
I appreciate your feelings, but I've already been selected as the host for the beauty contest.
That's why even if you pick me, I won't be able to go.
That's why I...
...nominate Aisaka-san!
Because you see, she's so small and cute.
She's also really famous within the school.
What are you saying, you super stupid Chihuahua?!
Why should I do something like that?
But that's a good idea.
It's true that Taiga is famous.
Maybe that'll cause an unexpected turn of events.
You bastards...
Hey, hey!
You can't do that, Taiga-chan.
You're part of this class, so you should participate in these events enthusiastically!
You stupid Chihuahua!
If you don't get it, I'll just destroy this whole Cultural Festival...
Now, now.
Calm down.
Aisaka, you really might be able to win.
Don't you think so?
All right! It's decided that our participant is Taiga!
Next...
We'll be discussing what our class is going to do...
Here! Here!
Yes, Noto-kun?
How about a Cosplay Café?!
Isn't that a bit too geeky?
Other classes will be doing it, too...
I don't want to do that...
Um, well...
This is just an idea...
It doesn't necessarily mean I want to do it...
I'm not really fond of the idea...
But I think we'll have lots of fun doing it together...
Umm... Ehh...
Haun- Haunte-
My nose is bleeding...
Please don't be mistaken, it's not like I want to say something weird...
I want to do...
A-A haunted house...
Kushieda, stop it.
Your body won't be able to stand it anymore.
Don't even think about it.
I won't let you guys do as you want...
Yurichan?
No selling stuff.
A band performance?
That's like the worst thing to do in Japan right now.
It's just an illusion behind the one day of the festival.
Nothing will happen before Christmas anyway.
Did something happen to her over the summer?
Anyhow, we're not finished yet!
Be prepared to vote!
Everyone, hurry up and write an idea down on a piece of paper!
Regardless of what the girls want, it's useless against the union of the male students.
So is everyone done?
Let's begin now!
Shake and...
Pick!
A lottery? You bastard...
I shall now announce the results!
For this Cultural Festival, our class will be doing pro-wrestling...
Who the hell wrote pro-wrestling show?!
They even put "serious match" inside the parenthesis!
Speaking of which, why didn't you do a majority pick?
Oh...
That stupid Chihuahua...
I'll send her to a different level of hell in every single round!
Just drop it. You should just enjoy the class events...
You're too introverted.
What?
You've only been enjoying yourself.
Enjoying myself? Are you talking about me?
After the trip, you've always been...
Wait... Why?
What's wrong?
This is weird. I can't withdraw any money.
It says I don't have any money left.
I guess it can't be helped, I'll...
Impossible!
Is it because I've been ignoring his phone calls?
I can't believe he did this.
The call from before?
He called a few times before that.
But I ignored all of them because I couldn't stand him.
So he took away my living expenses...
That damned old man... I really want to kill him!
You shouldn't say that about your parent.
Incoming Call - Damned Old Man
This is a threat...
Just pick up.
Nothing will happen if you don't talk to him.
It'll be troublesome if you don't have any money, right?
So...
She picked it up...
But why am I the one who's meeting him?
I see, I get it.
So my daughter will not be coming, right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I really wanted to see Taiga.
But that just made her hate me more...
I'm really sorry...
You're Takasu-kun, right?
Order whatever you want, it's all on me.
No, I'm fine.
Dinner is coming up...
No, umm...
Well, I'll help myself, then.
I'll have an egg bagel.
Oh, I see.
Excuse me.
May I order?
I'll have an egg bagel and a salmon bagel.
I'd like a lot of cheese.
Just give as much as you can.
Oh, before I forget.
The money.
I really wanted to see her, since I have something important to discuss...
Something important?
Umm...
Are you and Taiga, uh...
Going out?
N-No!
We're just normal friends.
We're not going out or anything.
We just live next to each other...
And we get along well...
I see.
So you must've heard a lot about our family from her, right?
My new wife is too young.
That's why Taiga couldn't adapt to her new life.
Then a lot of misunderstandings happened...
My wife now is called Yuu.
Somehow, it became that one side had to leave no matter what...
So Taiga...
I want to live with Taiga again!
That's what I wanted to tell her today.
I'll do everything correctly this time!
I plan to start life anew with Taiga.
I plan to break up with Yuu and live with Taiga again...
It's because we're father and daughter.
It's all because I love her.
This is serious...
Your father is coming back for you.
What are you doing?
You should slow down...
You have to wash it for 5 seconds or more!
Shut up, just let me be.
I promised that if you go and see him, I'd do the dishes.
Then do them properly!
Whatever, just go away.
How should I put it...
Your father is a bit weird.
He's not just any ordinary adult...
I told you to go away!
Go prepare hot water to brew the tea or something...
Your father is very worried about you.
He said he wanted to live with yo-
Are you retarded?
I'm taking this seriously.
Your father said that he wanted to live with you again.
I'm saying this because your father asked me-
Mind your own business!
Don't stick your nose into other people's business!
What?
Didn't you tell me to go see him for you?
You just plan to ignore it after you've taken the money?
Correct.
That's why I'm doing the dishes, that's why I want it to end.
I don't want to see him ever again!
Hey, don't joke around...
You should-
Shut up! Don't touch me!
Your father is very upset because you're ignoring him!
I feel bad for him!
I'm the one who you should feel bad for!
Taiga?
All right!
Did everyone get one?
I can feel how much responsibility I've got!
That's why I made this: a pro-wrestling script.
I don't think we should do this...
Let's just focus on the beauty contest...
Take this.
Everyone, just enjoy yourselves!
We can't go back!
Yurichan has already stamped and handed in the form!
Oh, isn't this interesting?
Everyone has a role.
Haruta-kun, you're surprisingly good.
I'm the main character!
That makes me a bit happy.
Ami-chan...
Oh, she's right.
This is amazingly professional!
Haruta-kun, let's do our best!
All right!
Let's start rehearsing!
It's set in the future.
Under the class-leader, Ami-chan, everyone of Class 2-C coexists in harmony.
But!
There are people who hate this harmony.
They are the devil incarnate, the Palmtop Tiger,
and her henchman, the delinquent, Takasu Ryuuji.
Hold it right there.
Why am I her henchman? Moreover, why am I a delinquent?
Why am I the devil incarnate?
Well, just listen until the end, okay?
The Palmtop Tiger attacks Class 2-C and brainwashes everyone!
But thanks to Ami-chan, everyone snaps out of the brainwash,
and then everyone works together to defeat the Palmtop Tiger and the delinquent, Takasu Ryuuji!
That is a truly beautiful happy ending!
What do you think?
The end is just as expected.
It's simple and dramatic, though.
It's interesting, isn't it?
No!
Like hell I'm doing this!
Gosh, Aisaka-san, don't be so selfish.
What the hell?!
It's the same as the beauty contest.
Why do I have to do such weird shit?
If beating me up will solve everything, then beat me up however you want!
Fine!
But it won't solve anything.
What?
Oh, the Palmtop Tiger is so enthusiastic!
They're rehearsing already.
Such amazing motivation!
All right!
Taiga, say the brainwashing lines now!
Your lines, look here.
"The tiger screams something and appears".
Ami has changed recently, hasn't she?
Yeah, you're right.
What the heck is that?
I don't know.
Haruta-kun said it's for a special character.
Everyone, listen!
The school has announced something!
This year's Cultural Festival is also an inter-class competition.
The number one class will receive grand prizes.
Eh...
These are the prizes:
First, refrigerators will be installed in their class.
Don't you guys want cold juice?
Second, the newest moistening air conditioners, which are supposed to be installed next year,
will be installed this month!
Don't you guys want moistening?
The bathroom power outlets will be opened for use.
Don't you guys want to do your hair?
Also, you will receive Kanouyano Supermarket coupons!
Don't you guys want coupons?
Huh?
Hey! The guys should work harder, too!
Oh...
What should we have for dinner?
Yellowtail.
How should it be cooked?
Grilled.
Grilled, huh?
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for you.
Umm...
You stalking bastard.
Taiga!
Stop being so selfish!
Let go of me, you stupid dog!
Are you on his side or what?
You're cruel!
I thought you were on my side!
I'm saying this because I am on your side!
It's for your sake!
Do you know who that is?
He's your father!
He came to get you!
You should at least listen to what he has to say!
No!
That guy is a stalker!
I don't need someone like him!
Don't say that!
Wai-
Didn't you cry after you got abandoned?
Be honest with yourself!
You actually want to go back, don't you?!
How could someone like you understand?
I don't need him anymore.
I didn't get abandoned.
I abandoned him.
I abandoned him because he's just a piece of trash!
You bitch...
Did you really treat him like a piece of trash?
My father will never come back no matter how much I wish for it!
I'm not doing this for Taiga, I...
I'm sorry, Taiga.
I...
It's enough.
If you say so...
That's why don't put that face on anymore.
Tai...
It's something good, isn't it?
I'll just pretend that it's something good.
I don't know if I can do that...
But if you say so...
I'll just pretend, then.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness... It has to be...
...right?
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
Oubashi High School Cultural Festival・Part 2
Koigakubo Yuri...
She's entered her mid-thirties this summer.
Everyone, please give me a present.
Rather, someone marry me.