[HATSU] Okay, okay,
let's all calm down!
You're not getting away this
time, you naughty laundry.
Hmm...?
I wonder what that is...
It's awfully beautiful.
[RUKO] Her scrunchie...
She still has it!
You remember...
To tell you the truth...
...I've known for a while now.
Ever since... our last battle.
[HITOE screams]
[YUZUKI] Hitoe!
Hitoe!
[HITOE sobs]
Mama is here.
Hang on, Hitoe.
[HITOE] It hurt so much...
Like my heart was being torn
into a thousand pieces.
But even through
all that pain...
I kept thinking:
I won't... forget them.
[HITOE'S MOTHER gasps]
[HITOE'S MOTHER] Hitoe...?
[HITOE] But I knew what
it meant to lose you
and I knew that pain
would be even worse.
I won't be alone!
Welcome back!
But wait, if you remembered,
then why didn't you
tell us sooner?
[HITOE] Because I wanted
my wish to come true!
Because I wanted to win...
The wish itself
didn't matter...
If I won enough, Yuzuki
would complete the oath again
like she did with Hanayo.
And then she'd be
freed from the card!
That's right, isn't it?
[YUZUKI] What're you
saying, Hitoe?!
That wouldn't solve anything!
You'd end up like me!
I'm flattered you care
so much, but please,
don't worry about me.
I don't see this
as a bad thing.
In fact, it's more like
a dream come true.
Being with friends, making a
noble sacrifice to save them...
It's all just
so romantic...
I'm happy such a
beautiful thing even exists.
Of course, the battles
and stuff are incredible.
But meeting
the two of you...
Seeing what real
friendship is like...
To me, that's...
I guess...
It's like a miracle...
[HITOE] Finding a friend who can
do something important for you,
and being able to give
something back to that friend.
If I have that,
then there's not a single
wish in the world I need.
Hitoe!
[RUKO sobs]
Doing something
for a friend...
[RUKO] Please, Tama...
[TAMA gasps]
Will you finally
listen to my wish?
Ru, no.
We have to free
Yuzuki from the card.
There's a chance
to save my friends.
Nothing's more
important than that.
Huh...?
[TAMA whimpers]
I don't want you
to be so sad...
If I help, will you be
friends with me, too?
[RUKO] Uh-huh...
Okay!
You tell Tama what to do!
[RUKO gasps]
[TAMA] Battling's about
all I'm good for.
But if that can make
your wish come true.
I'll battle and battle
as much as it takes!
Thank you, Tama.
All right, guys!
You ready?!
Let's continue the match.
Oh, but Hitoe.
One last thing:
I'm sorry.
But there's no way I'll lose!
I've made my wish,
and it's coming true!
Ruko!
Attack: Arc Aura!
[TAMA yells]
Good game.
[HITOE groans]
[HITOE] I lost...
[RUKO] Hope that
didn't hurt, Yuzuki.
Only my pride...
Oh, hey.
What about your wish?
Oh yeah!
You finally figured it out?
It's clear now.
I want Yuzuki and all the
other girls trapped in cards
to be free...
Ruko, that's--
[YUZUKI] Whoa-whoa-whoa.
Slow down.
We need to talk about this.
[RUKO] But we did.
You're the ones who made me
realize what I needed to do.
If there's something I can do
for my friends, I should do it.
Nothing would make me
happier and that's final.
I'd better be going...
Wait a sec!
I'm coming with you!
[YUZUKI] Meaning we're coming!
[RUKO] Then-- you're
okay with my wish?
You're sure?
I guess so...
Not like I could
change your mind.
Just make sure you get
your wish right, huh?
I mean, yeah, duh, I want
to get out of this card.
But this'll be all for nothing
if you end up as
a LRIG yourself.
We're getting dumplings on the
way home and I want you there!
[RUKO gasps]
So, hey...
I can't wait to go
shopping with you, Tama.
You know, in person.
Can we eat dumplings?
I was thinking I'd buy
you some scrunchies.
So you can match the rest of us.
Sounds great!
[RUKO grunts]
[HITOE] Oh, boy...
Not good with heights...
I'd feel better about it if
I could pick out my apartment.
Huh?
Grandma...
[RUKO gasps]
[IONA] I've been expecting you.
Hi, Ru.
Okay...?
And you brought
your little friends.
[HITOE gasps]
Yeah? What's it to you?
She is our friend, and we're
here to support her!
[IONA] Fine with me.
A cheering section won't
make any difference.
[YUZUKI gasps]
Anything else, Ru?
A rousing speech, perhaps?
Or something you'd
like to ask me?
No questions. No speeches.
All I want is to battle you.
You really are the best.
[IONA & RUKO] Open!
[RUKO] What a dark
and lonely place...
Is it always so
scary when you fight?
[IONA] I'm sorry.
I thought you were
all out of questions.
Ready when you are.
You're up first, Ru.
Tama, Grow!
[TAMA shouts]
[URITH chuckles]
Grow!
[URITH yells]
[BOTH grunting]
They're both so strong.
[YUZUKI] But look at Ruko.
[HITOE] I know.
[YUZUKI] Something's off...
Her eyes are so cold.
[RUKO] I don't get this.
Battles before were always fun,
or exciting, or something.
This is just... hollow.
[RUKO] It's so quiet...
[TAMA breathing]
[RUKO] I can even
hear Tama breathing...
[RUKO] This may
be my final battle.
I can't have any doubts.
Tama, Grow!
Use: Sword Ability!
[TAMA] Haah!
[URITH grunts]
[URITH pants]
Focus...
She's one of a kind.
Gotta give her that!
[URITH] Of course, you have
more than enough wins
to have your wish granted.
It's just the time
wasn't quite ripe.
This might give it the
"push" you need, though.
Assuming you're ready, that is.
Not just yet...
Now, Grow.
Trust me, it won't
be much longer.
This isn't for my sake,
but for Ru's.
My Dear Ruko Kominato!
Black Desire!
[MAYU] Tama...
[TAMA gasps]
[TAMA whimpers]
[RUKO] Tama!
[TAMA grunts]
[RUKO gasps]
[MAYU] Tama...
Can you hear me?
[TAMA] That's not Ru.
[MAYU] Tama.
[TAMA] But I know that voice...
...better than Ru's.
Maybe better than my own...
It must've been from
a long time ago...
[MAYU] You've finally
come to see me.
[TAMA] Who...
Who are you?
[MAYU giggles]
[MAYU] You poor thing.
All the pain she's
put you through.
[TAMA] Huh...?
[MAYU] Ru is... so cruel.
[TAMA gasps]
A wish to be together...
To never draw apart,
no matter what.
A dream that you believed in
with all your heart...
[MAYU] I know you love Ru,
but she cares for her
friends more than you.
[TAMA gasps]
[TAMA] No!
You got it all wrong!
Ru's not like that.
She said she'd be
friends with me too!
[MAYU] Tama...
After this, we were gonna go
eat ice cream and dumplings.
And then I was gonna
get a matching scrunchie
so I could be like
her other friends!
[MAYU] I'm so sorry.
[TAMA gasps]
[MAYU] It's true that
Ru loves her friends.
She loves them so much
that she lied to you.
And now she's going to
become an LRIG for them.
[TAMA] That's wrong!
We're all going home
together after this!
So I have to win!
[MAYU] That won't happen.
Please listen to me.
Tama, try to remember!
[GIRLS crying & moaning]
[MAYU] The solution is easy.
[TAMA gasps]
[MAYU] You want to stop Ru from
becoming an LRIG, don't you?
You don't have
to lose the fight.
You can refuse the
wish at the very end.
[TAMA] Huh...?
[MAYU] Yuzuki said the
same thing, right.
For a Selector's wish
to be fulfilled,
the LRIG must be in agreement.
[TAMA] But then, what will
happen to Ru's wish?
[MAYU] Win the battle and see.
Huh?
Then you'll know
her true feelings,
and you'll see why I'm
trying to protect you.
[TAMA] Protect me?
[MAYU] But only if you win.
[RUKO] Tama...
Tama!
Are you able
to get back up?
[TAMA] I'll find out
her true feelings.
If you're still hurt,
don't overdo it.
[TAMA] I'll fight and
I'll win the battle.
And then, it
will all be over.
Tama...
[URITH] That's a good girl.
Hate to see you give up
when it's just getting fun!
[IONA laughs]
Drawing!
Ener Charge.
Tama to Level 4!
[RUKO] No matter what
happens after my wish...
[TAMA] ...this is
the last battle.
[RUKO] I don't know
if it'll come true,
or if everything
will fall apart.
[TAMA] But we have to win!
[RUKO & TAMA] This is the end!
What's that?!
It's not an attack...
What's happening?!
[HITOE] The battlefield's
coming apart!
[HITOE] The roof...?
Were we kicked out of the
battlefield for some reason?
No, look.
The sky...
And it seems like
they're still fighting.
[URITH giggles]
Okay, Ru, what should
I do for my next attack?
Hurry!
It's so beautiful...
[RUKO] And I just noticed... you
can see our apartment from here.
That does make me feel better.
Ru?
What're you...?
[RUKO] Thanks, Tama.
Huh?
[RUKO] You wanted me
to see it one last time
before the end, didn't you?
The end?
Bye, Grandma...
I love you.
[TAMA gasps]
[URITH laughs]
[URITH] Can you
believe it, Iona?!
She thinks she's
already won this!
She's the best.
She honestly is...
My Ru...
[RUKO] What's the
next step, Tama?
Huh...?
[TAMA] Before the
last attack, an oath...
'Kay, I'm ready.
[YUZUKI] That's right,
before my wish was granted,
I took an oath with Hanayo, too.
It seals the final contract
between you and your LRIG.
But wait, if Tama lost her
memory, how does she know this?
Tell me what to say
and I'll say it.
[TAMA] Maybe...
she was lying to me.
She's not thinking
about going back.
She never was...
[MAYU] She thinks the only way
she can save her friends
is to become an LRIG.
[TAMA] She knew I
wouldn't agree with this
if she told me the truth...
She wants to
sacrifice herself...
[RUKO] Tama?
Please. Just tell
me what to say.
I accept the laws,
the laws of--
I accept the laws of?
The laws of the... Selector...
[RUKO] I accept the
laws of the Selector.
And...
[YUZUKI gasps]
Huh?
Tama, thank you.
[TAMA whimpers]
[URITH] Ugh! This
is taking forever!
The battle's almost over!
Can't we do something?
It's our turn, right?
Let's just finish 'em off!
[IONA] Urith, Bloody Slash.
Ready?
Yeah.
[BOTH] Use White Hope!
[URITH whimpers]
[crashing]
[GIRLS screaming]
[SELECTOR D] Uh-oh.
What's going on?!
Hang on,
is this normal?
[MIDORIKO] It's happening...
I knew it...
Yuzuki, what're
you looking at?
What's wrong?
[HANAYO (Y) sobs]
[KAZUKI] You okay?
[RUKO] Don't worry...
I don't have a single regret.
Because no matter what happens,
this was the wish that
I chose for myself.
I'm happy to make it...
[RUKO gasps]
[RUKO whimpers]
[HITOE] But why?
Ruko won, didn't she?
But the contract
wasn't completed.
Huh?
They skipped
the last part.
It goes: "And upon
this sacred oath,
a new Eternal Girl
shall be born!"
What's wrong?
[TAMA] I can't do it...
Even if you earned your wish...
I can't let you
turn into an LRIG!
I can't let you!
Tama...
What's happening?!
[RUKO] Stop it!
Tama, it's going away!
Finish the oath! Please!
No! Wait!
This is wrong!
[RUKO] But... I won
the battle, didn't I?
[URITH] Aww, don't
look so surprised.
Iona's been ready to have her
wish granted for some time now.
She's won a whole ton of
Selector battles, after all.
It's just we had to wait
for a certain "condition"
to fall into place before
we could seal the deal.
"Condition"?
[URITH] That's right.
But now the condition
has been met.
Hope you're happy, you've
been waiting long enough.
[IONA] That I have...
Not that I'm complaining.
But, what about me?
[RUKO screams]
[RUKO sobs]
Tama!
Snap out of it! Why
won't you grant my wish?
Did something happen?
Tama!
[IONA & URITH] I accept...
the laws of the Selector.
[RUKO] No, You can't!
Damn it! Please,
just listen to me.
We have to turn everyone
back to normal!
[IONA & URITH] "And upon
this sacred oath,
a new Eternal Girl
shall be born!"
Iona!
Wait... Iona, you're...?
[URITH (I) chuckles]
No, Urith...
Let's do this again sometime,
Miss Pain-in-the-ass.
Ruko...
Tama, why did--
[RUKO gasps]
Where did she--
[IONA] Oh, this
is gonna be fun...
Hi, Ru...
[RUKO whimpers]
[AYUMU] Ah, so good!
You really outdid yourself on
the sauce this time, Grandma!
[HATSU chuckles]
Ru must be having fun
and lost track of time.
She'll be fine.
Just eat already.
Not yet, I made
this just for her.
When we eat, we do it together.
[TAMA] You told me... we'd
do everything together, Ru...
[RUKO gasps]
Tama!
Where did you go?
Tamaaa!
[TAMA] Being with
you... is my wish.
[URITH (I)] Ah, we meet again,
Miss Pain-in-the-ass.
[IONA] So, Ru, who's
our first opponent.
I'm ready to fight.
[TAMA] Was it because
I did something bad?
[RUKO
'Cause you're my friend, okay?
That's why!
[RUKO] Next:
"Selector Spread WIXOSS."