When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
After a quick bit of fan service,
we begin with a summary of the last episode.
Accompanied by his maid,
a mysterious boy has come to see Nagi.
What might his true identity be?
This boy is Wataru Tachibana
and he is Nagi's... betrothed.
Huh?
That is all. End of summary.
That's no good, mister.
Ya gotta get over yer bashfulness!
Ya can't win scenes for yerself like this.
I-I see...
Listen up. What yer character
lacks is punch, Mr. Klaus.
The comedic drive to step forward,
even if ya hafta push people aside.
Okay, here goes.
Oh, my glasses, my glasses...
My glasses, my glasses,
my glasses, my glasses...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
I hope I get more screen time.
That's all for today.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
A Man's Fight
Um, betrothed, as in...
Like a husband-to-be
determined by her parents...?
Yes, that makes him her fiancé.
I see.
But Miss, I had no idea you had
an official boyfriend.
Y-You're wrong! Don't misunderstand!
He's not my boyfriend,
but my betrothed! My betrothed!
In other words, it's something
our families decided on their own,
so... um...
No, really, I'm so surprised
that you're betrothed.
A young lady of the upper class
certainly has it different.
To Nagi, his smile...
You never told me you were betrothed!
Was our relationship just a game to you?!
...apparently looked like that.
Hayate's pretty angry.
I must resolve the
misunderstanding, no matter what!
But are they sure about this?
If the Miss marries into his family,
won't that be the end of the Sanzenin name?
There is no problem in that regard.
Since Nagi will not be the one
to marry into his family.
Oh, so the Miss will receive Wataru
into the family as her husband.
Like hell I'm being received
as Nagi's husband!
But such a thing does not happen often.
An opportunity to marry
an adorable girl like Miss Nagi...
Hayate...
Hah! A selfish, spoiled,
irresponsible manga nerd,
who thinks she's the boss of this world!
Like anyone would want her!
Wh-What?!
Like hell I'm taking that
from a brat like you,
you stupid, stupid, stupid!
That's my like, you ugly, ugly, ugly!
Wow, I guess people who are
betrothed really do get along.
Ugly! Ugly!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
If that looks like they're
getting along to you,
you should go see an eye
doctor or brain surgeon.
And you! Can't you be
at least a little more ladylike?!
Wataru.
Th-That voice... Don't tell me...
Good morning, Wataru.
What are you doing so early in the morning?
Well... uh... Isumi...
Could it be because you also heard
that Nagi had a new butler?
W-Well, I myself was of a similar mind.
I Myself
"I myself"?!
But I just heard some loud noises...
Could it be that you were
fighting with Nagi?
N-Not at all! We would never fight!
Nagi and I always get along famously!
What's with the drastic
change in his persona?
Well, basically...
It means that Wataru likes Isumi.
What?! He likes someone else
when he's betrothed?!
Well, it's not a betrothal
that they wanted for themselves.
Then, does the Miss want to
break off her betrothal to Wataru?
Of course, I do!
As if we could marry when
we don't even like each other!
If Isumi comes to like Wataru,
it would solve everything,
but regrettably, Wataru doesn't
register on Isumi's radar at all.
So, whatever the case,
if Wataru and Isumi become an item,
the betrothal will be off, correct?
Yes! It seems you finally understand!
Everyone, we haven't eaten this morning,
so how about some breakfast?
Would you prefer
a Japanese breakfast, Isumi?
What?
W-Well...
Then, whichever you prefer,
my dear Hayate...
I-Isumi! Don't tell me
you have feelings for him?!
Then everyone, please head
towards the dining room.
Hold it right there!
You're Nagi's new butler, right?
RROOAARR
Uh, yes, my name is Hayate Ayasaki...
Since we're here, how about
a little duel before breakfast?
Um, is it the norm for the rich and
famous to have duels in the morning?
Who knows?
I don't really get it,
but he probably wants to
show off how cool he is to Isumi.
Even though it's a waste of time.
Well, if he loses really badly,
he may gain Isumi's sympathy,
so beat the crap out of him.
Uh, right...
All right, ready to meet your fate,
you stupid butler?!
I'll warn you, though. Hayate's strong.
After all, he can catch up
to a car on a bicycle.
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way a poor-looking
guy like him is strong!
Do you have any experience with sabers?
Hmm, let's see...
Well, that's about
the best I can do with it.
Hey, what do you want to do?
Sh-Shut up!
O-Once a man's decided to do something,
there's no going back!
Oh, boy...
I know what the Miss asked me to do, but...
Hold on.
If I can neatly bring the two of them
to an understanding...
Wind Scar!
Isumi, be with me...
Yes, I will marry you!
Yay! The betrothal's off!
Excellent work, Hayate!
All right, it's settled then!
Here I come!
Please watch this, Miss!
Hayate Ayasaki's greatest
performance of his life!
Take this!
But...
Sharp instruments are dangerous,
so let's still get that out of the way...
Whoa, he got me!
Thud.
Huh? That's odd.
That should've set the flag
for a happy ending...
Oh, my dear Hayate...
To think you would lose on purpose,
so as not to hurt the pride
of the violent and weak Wataru.
How kind of you...
N-Not at all!
Wataru is truly strong
and I didn't stand a chance!
Huh? Oh, wait...
I'm... never... letting you
get away with that...
I'll defeat you for sure someday!
Remember this! You idiot!
Th-This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
Goodness. To think he psychologically
beat the crap out of him...
Hayate really is good.
Or rather, that cheap performance...
Is he still angry that I didn't
tell him that I was betrothed?
Wataru has left the estate by himself.
Incidentally, as for his maid's bath...
The water was quite fine.
She was in there so long,
the first half has already ended.
Tell me you love me.
(Aishiteiru to itte kure)
Love beam! (Renai biimu)
I still think it would be better
if I went to apologize to him.
What I did to Wataru was inexcusable.
Well, certainly,
I do feel a little sorry for him
to leave things like this, but...
Leave it, leave it.
Besides, for a boy
to cry in front of others...
How weak could he be?
My, that is awful! Calling him weak...
It is the truth, but since he made
Wataru cry, he should apologize.
You're the one who made him cry, though.
S-So, given that I am going to apologize,
where will I be able to
find Wataru's estate?
What? Isn't that more
of a building than an estate?
Yes, because Wataru lives
at the top of the Tachibana
Group's Shinjuku Headquarters.
Wow, he's in the middle of downtown?
Then, the roads will be congested
at this hour in the morning...
I suppose taking the train
would be faster than driving.
Huh? Did I say something wrong?
The train... Isumi, have you
ever been on one?
I have ridden the Orient Express
and the Siberian Express, but...
Not any in Japan...
Right?
Besides, there aren't all
that many trains running, right?
Then, what's that?
This is a game. A game.
Could it be that you have
never ridden a train, Miss?!
No, she hasn't.
But were there that many
bullet train stations in Tokyo?
Huh?! The bullet train?!
What?! By train, you weren't
referring to the bullet train?
Um, excuse my abrupt question,
but do you ladies know what the "subway" is?
The subway?
Yes, like the Oedo Line
or the Marunouchi Line.
They are trains that run underground.
Murmur
So, there are bullet trains
running underground in Tokyo?
No, there are trains other
than bullet trains!
So, underground, what kind
of scenery do you see outside?
No, there is nothing to see!
I thought they're only
for transporting Koubu
and ordinary people couldn't ride them!
That was just during the Taisho era!
Ah, that sounds interesting.
I had no intention
of going to Wataru's place,
but I'd like to take a ride
on this so-called subway.
All right, we are going to ride
this subway thing, Hayate!
Sanzenin
B-But will it be all right?
Getting on such a strange vehicle
with just the children...
At Shinjuku Station alone,
approximately 570,000 people get
on this strange vehicle every day.
*Research by Hayate
Incidentally, the breakdown of that is...
...230,000 people
on the Metro Shinjuku Line,
100,000 people on the Oedo Line,
and 240,000 people on the Marunouchi Line.
That is all for the explanation.
Ah, you're so knowledgeable, Hayate!
You see that? Nothing to worry about.
Besides, we may get to see
subterranean people or living dinosaurs!
Th-That is why I'm saying it's dangerous!
W-Well, we have Isumi along with us also,
so I will escort them carefully
to keep from getting lost.
Speaking of Isumi,
where in the world is she?
What?
Could she have gotten lost already?!
Oh, no! We only looked away
for just a moment!
I underestimated Isumi's abilities.
To start with, Maria, contact security.
Hayate and I will search nearby!
Right!
Oh, wait, Nagi!
I think Isumi probably headed
for that so-called subway, but...
That's terrible! There are numerous
subway stations in Tokyo alone!
No, the "subway" in this case
is Isumi's idea of the "subway".
So, I'd give it a 90 chance that
she hasn't made it to the real subway.
Rum raisin! Triple on a regular cone!
I-Is that so?
Yeah, Isumi never makes it
to her destination on her own!
So there will be no mistake
if you follow me.
Where Isumi has gone
will be the closest place around
that resembles the subway!
Wait, no, no, no.
Where in the world are we, Miss?
Wh-Who knows?
Earlier, I found a construction guy
who sounded like he'd seen Isumi...
A While Ago
Um, is this the entrance to the subway?
Eh?
The subway, where they transport
dinosaurs using bullet trains...
Oh sure, it's definitely underground, but...
Well, there are all kinds of unknown
worlds sprawled under Tokyo
that even the government
doesn't know everything about,
so you just might find...
Wait, huh?! Missy?!
So, I bought out the construction site
and we went underground with security.
I think that part went fine, but...
Th-That's a Griffon!
A trick of the light...
Part of me almost wishes it was
and part of me doesn't...
Miss, where are you?!
At any rate, we should go back for now.
Or we'll get lost for real, too.
M-Miss?
Y-You fool! Don't change
directions so suddenly!
I thought you were leaving me behind!
I don't handle dark places
like this too well...
So please don't make any sudden moves.
But Miss...
Then, what do you do at night?
Might you have trouble
sleeping alone at night?
No, wait... it's not...
I-It's not as if I can't sleep alone...
I'm not a child, after all.
I just have a hard time
falling asleep sometimes...
And if there's a power outage,
it gets pitch dark,
so it's kind of dangerous,
you know... like...
Well, what does it matter?
It's cuter when you
have qualities like that.
But that was a bit of a mistake.
You see, you shouldn't yell
in underground spaces like this.
When you yell, they get scared
and come leaping out...
I-Isumi!
Thank goodness! Let's run together!
If we don't hurry, they'll...
Oh, dear...
You are making a bit of a ruckus...
Stopped
Huh?
My, how smart you are.
Huh?! What?!
Wh-What was that just now?!
Thus, our dreams of the subway were crushed.
That's so stupid!
Dinosaurs? Subterranean men?
Like they exist.
I see...
Listen to me. The subway
actually leads to Brazil.
What? Brazil?
That's right. That place is on
the other side of Japan, right?
So it connects us to 'em.
Only thing ya gotta be careful of is
that Brazil's a foreign country, right?
So, ya gotta show yer passport.
Next time ya have occasion
to ride the subway,
show yer passport to the station staff
and say, "One child's ticket
to Rio de Janeiro please."
Got it?
I understand, Sakuya. Thank you.
Hayate, if you're still going to
insist on apologizing to Wataru,
I want you to give this to him.
What? What is this?
You mustn't open it on your
way there, no matter what.
Since there's no knowing
who may be watching.
What?
Wow...
It's the city...
But still...
What is this?
It's not something to get rid
of her betrothed, is it?
Like a bomb or something...?
Oh? If it isn't the Sanzenin family butler.
Oh, Saki.
Fancy meeting you here.
Have you come to see the Young Sir?
Oh, yes, just dropping by.
Also, I'm delivering
something from the Miss.
In that case, I shall show you the way.
What? Really? Thank you very much.
Huh?
Oh, our headquarters is this way,
so please be sure to follow me.
Oh, right...
I don't really get it,
but is Saki avoiding me?
Um, Saki...
What... the?
P-Pardon me! Um, it's not
that I'm avoiding you!
So, um, you know...
I'd never been held like
that by a man before,
so I sort of end up shying away by reflex...
Oh, no, I don't mean you!
I mean men in general!
It doesn't really bother me.
I'm used to people hating me anyway...
No... uh... I'm sorry!
We're here. This is it.
What?
Video Rental Video Tachibana
Um, isn't this a video rental store?
It is.
Young Sir, I have returned.
Ah, Saki, thanks.
What the hell are you here for?!
N-No, I brought this to you from the Miss.
Oh, the videos that I lent Nagi.
Videos?
Yeah, this is the Entertainment
Division of the Tachibana Group.
The Shinjuku flagship store
of Rental Video Tachibana.
The Tachibana Group itself
is almost dead due to
the recent economic downturn.
This rental store chain
is their last holdout now.
Saki, don't say such unnecessary things.
Then, the fact you're betrothed is...
Yeah, it means my parents
are counting on Nagi's family fortune.
They're used to being wealthy,
so they're scared of no
longer having a fortune.
But where's the point in thinking
about things so negatively?
Just watch!
I'll make this store huge
and amass a fortune that'll
dwarf the Sanzenin family!
Like hell I'm being taken
into the family as a husband!
If I do that, I'm sure Isumi will also...
This boy has a foul mouth,
but he's a really good kid.
That's why I can't just let him be.
Saki, don't just stand there! Get to work!
Oh, yes, sir!
Rental video... So, is what
I just delivered also...?
Yeah, our goods.
But as rich as the Miss is,
surely she could just buy it
instead of bothering to rent it.
You're so naive!
There're some extra-rare titles in
this world that aren't on the market.
Th-Then, are those DVDs also...?
Yeah, this is Gurren Lag...
Tachibana
Bamboo! Bamboo poles!
So you see, we've got
a collection of treasures
that we can't mention out loud.
The genres are anime
and special effects, of course!
B-But isn't it illegal to rent them out
in exchange for payment?
No problem. I'm only showing
off to Nagi privately.
Wataru Only
But someday, I'm going to surpass her
with the power of money.
Um, I'm really sorry about the other day.
By way of apology, please allow me
to become a member of this store.
Well, a customer's a customer.
Ayasaki, was it? I'll waive the sign-up fee.
Huh?
You're already registered as a member.
What?
Th-That can't be!
I mean, I've never joined
a rental membership before!
But this photo's you, right?
Shun Ayasaki...
Huh? The name's different...
Name
Shun Ayasaki
Legal Domicile
Tokyo
Address
Issued
June 2, Heisei Year 17
My old man?!
There are a total of 158 videos
that haven't been returned.
At 200 yen per video per day...
Um, the late fees come out
to exactly 1.58 million yen...
I have returned.
Ah, good work.
Wait, what happened? You look so pale.
For now, I settled things so
I pay him back for the tapes...
In installments.
Huh?
Right around the time
when Hayate's debt increased...
There were yet more people
having a miserable experience.
One child's ticket to Rio de Janeiro please.
Pardon?
To Rio de Janeiro in Brazil.
Um...
For someone unable to discern
when they are being lied to,
it is difficult to survive
in our modern society.
But let's just say that as people,
it's best to have an honest attitude,
so see you again next time.
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Sign: Butler Report
Hayate, you've settled into
your role as a butler pretty nicely.
Thank you very much, Miss.
Having said that,
you still need more training.
This is no time to be singing, all carefree.
R-Right...
To start with, let's do special training,
so you're ready no matter
when some ancient supermen
or diabolical supermen come attacking.
What?! Supermen original to the anime?!
That's right!
You never know when the anime
version of "Hayate the Combat Butler"
will get its own original
supermen, after all!
What?! Really?!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Say, Hayate, I have a favor to ask.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Yes, what might that be?
Would you try these clothes on for me?
Um, no matter how you look at it,
that's a sailor uniform, right?
Oh, Nagi! And here I was
wondering what you were up to.
Maria!
This frilly outfit is sure
to look good on Hayate!
NOOO!!!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Going to Hell in Cat-Ear Mode".
Going to Hell in Cat-Ear Mode
For the future of Earth,
I am at your service, meow!