SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
That sound could wake even the dead.
THE SQUAD'S DAY
RIO RUNS
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's a nice flavor.
Yes, it's delicious.
I-It's average, I guess.
That's great.
This is a special dish from my village.
Is this "miso" made the same way as soy sauce?
Yes, it is.
I brought a bit of the miso my mom made.
There's still a lot more, so don't hold back and eat up.
You're going to Treize?
Yes.
I've finally received notice that supplies are arriving.
Kureha-chan and I are going to pick them up.
Munitions, medicine, and other necessities.
We're running low, right?
We'll finally be able to restock them all.
And you, Noel?
She's going to Carl-san's workshop, right?
Yeah.
Got it.
Kanata!
We'll spend the afternoon practicing the trumpet!
Really?
Our meals.
My...
Where are your manners?
If your dad saw this, he'd cry.
See if I care.
Here, have some tea-cakes.
Fortune Rice Crackers?
You still hate them, I see.
Those children from the church are innocent, you know?
Raising money by imbuing useless superstitions... They're all the same.
Well, that's not necessarily true.
These crackers really are delicious.
Oh?
Great Luck
But Kana-chan seems to have adapted to living here.
She works so hard it's adorable.
Really?
I do acknowledge her passion and seriousness,
but I'm not so naive as to think everything will just work out.
What's with that look?
It's a secret.
Whatever. You're getting on my nerves.
Very Bad Luck
We'll be going, then.
We might come back later tonight.
Okay.
Be careful.
Don't trouble Rio-senpai!
I won't.
Proceeding to depart.
Have a safe trip!
I don't expect you to do that yet,
but controlling the notes with the mouthpiece is essential.
Try it.
O-Okay!
How do you like living at the base?
It's fun!
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
I'm a bit jealous of your relaxed temperament.
Now that I think of it, why did you join the military?
That's, um...
I heard that I could learn to play instruments for free...
Ah! But, um...
I think protecting our country is important, too!
I don't mind.
Whether it's for money or something else,
Those who know what they want tend to last longer here than those who don't.
Um...
I'm grateful.
So, how about you, Rio-senpai?
I...
Well...
I'm the complete opposite of you, I guess.
But it's really rare these days.
Especially brass. You hardly hear it outside of the military.
I heard it a long time ago.
Just... Like your...
Kanata?
Sound... Of the sky...
What's wrong? Get yourself together!
Come on, Kanata!
Talk to me!
No!
Please, stay still.
It's hot...
It's hot, mommy.
Is it?
I see. It's okay, it's okay.
Mom-
Mommy...
What's wrong, Kanata?
Kanata!
I want to eat some snow...
What?
Okay, wait for a bit!
Snow, snow, where's the snow-
Wait...
Like hell I'd find it!
Calm down... Calm down...
The medicine!
No, that's the last resort!
Medicine... Medicine...
Medicine! Where's the medicine?!
Found it!
We're running low, right?
Those Logistics idiots!
Dammit! What should I do?
What should I...
DAMMIT!
U-Um...
Is there something I can help you with?
Did the kids give you trouble again?
I apologize for having been so rude.
So, um...
I need your help.
Drink this.
Good girl.
Her fever's quite high,
but this should bring it down.
Is her illness serious?
I think it's tertian malaria.
Malaria?
Don't kids get that?
Even adults can get it if they are overworked and exhausted.
Kids often get it right after they come to our church.
They seem absolutely fine, but suddenly develop a high fever.
She must have endured it the whole time, I'm sure.
T-Then...
Will she recover?
She won't die, right?
I think she'll be fine.
Thank goodness...
Thank... you.
Um...
I'm Yumina.
This is a tea made from medicinal herbs.
Please have her drink it again later.
Well... I apologize for everything.
Don't worry about it.
Serving the people of this town is our duty, and our joy.
May all of you be blessed with great happiness.
I thank you for your assistance.
I-I'm sorry!
Feeling better?
I'm so sorry.
I'm a miso.
Hm? From this morning?
No, I mean...
The bean lees. When you make the soup, you filter the miso.
It's the bean lees left in the filter.
They're called "leftovers" or "hindrances,"
like me...
That's how I've been, ever since I was little.
That's why...
I told myself I'd do my best and not be a burden to everyone.
Even so...
You're more delicate than you look, huh?
Selfish and spoiled, at that.
Did I say anything?
Lots of things.
Ah, senpai.
W-What is it?
The song you just sang...
What are you talking about?
This song.
That's surprising,
you heard it just once.
Not just once.
I heard it a long time ago.
I wished I was able to play that song myself.
That's why... I...
I want to play the song that resounds from the sky.
But, I guess a miso will be a miso wherever it goes.
Kanata.
We can't rely on the church all the time.
The Takemikazuchi is a relic from a past era.
And lots of things are hidden inside it.
Lots of things?
Yeah.
Ask Noel about the details later.
Okay, this'll do.
It's starting!
This... This song-
This is probably the complete form of the song.
Various instruments, each resounding their parts,
combining into a song.
It's just like operating a tank.
The commander, gunner, driver, and signaller.
Everyone combines their ability to move a single tank.
Nobody's useless.
There's no note that isn't necessary.
Don't look at me like that.
Those aren't my words.
They're from the one I adore, and look up to the most.
I'm going to borrow her words...
Kanata, for what reason do you think seniors exist?
It's so they can be troubled by their juniors.
It's fine if you can't do it right now.
Just remember the feelings of frustration and helplessness,
and the feeling of happiness when you were protected.
It'll be useful when it's your turn to protect, someday.
So, go ahead and be as troublesome as you want.
That's what I did myself.
Of course, you'll be scolded when you make mistakes. And you'll be punished.
But, tell me if you're hurt, or suffering.
Okay?
Understood!
I'll make sure I cause you a lot of trouble from now on!
N-No, I meant...
Restrain yourself a bit, though.
Ah, jeez! I knew I should have stayed back after all.
I can't believe Kanata made Rio-senpai nurse her...
What're you saying? It wasn't a big deal.
She was just worn out, it seems.
Just needs a little rest.
The Takemikazuchi was on.
Ah, sorry. I used it for a bit.
Was there a problem?
No.
So you listened to that song?
Yeah.
But you said you'd never listen to it again.
I just felt like it, okay?
And then?
It's a secret.
Pile up the feelings of love and friendship
Performing is also important
I cried happily
I laughed eagerly
But all of them make me alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me why we dance
You just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I want them to echo forever
Speaking endless words touched by love
Our harmony
I can hear our harmony
SKY OF THE RAINY SEASON - QUARTZ RAINBOW
Next episode: Sky of the Rainy Season - Quartz Rainbow
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.