Rider?
Idiot!
What were you thinking, breaking the shutter open like that?
Why aren't you in spirit form, like when you entered?
I cannot carry these while I'm in spirit form.
Don't whine so much.
You look like a thief.
If you aren't a thief, what are you?
Something else entirely.
A thief breaks away with his loot under the cover of the night.
But if you walk away triumphantly, then you are a conquering king!
Just what I needed...
Get lost... Get lost now. Out of my sight!
Very well! Then I shall leave you to bear the spoils.
Do not drop them.
Why is this happening to me?!
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
The summoning worked, so why do I have to do this?
What's the big deal about these books, anyway?
I told you... We prepare for war.
And you cannot wage a war without maps.
Hey, boy.
Where are Macedonia and Persia?
Y-You can't talk to me like that!
I'm your Master...
I am well aware of your status as my Master.
We forged a contract, did we not?
Yes.
But I'm more interested in learning what has become of my territories.
I think it's over here.
Pathetic! I spent my life conquering that land, and behold how puny it truly is!
Very well! I can't wait!
And where on the map are we now, boy?
Here.
So, the other side of the round land?
Pleasing news indeed!
This will guide us in the coming battles.
Guide us?
First, we journey halfway around the globe.
Westward. We head west...
And we shall conquer every land we pass through!
I shall return to Macedonia in triumph.
And my people will hold a festival in honor of my revival.
That will be splendid, will it not?
Why the hell do you think you're here?
Don't forget about the Holy Grail War!
Oh right!
That reminds me... Speaking of the Grail, I have neglected to ask...
What will you do with the Grail?
Wh-What's it to you?
What do you care?
If you are also intent on world conquest,
that would make you my enemy.
This world's too small for two supreme rulers.
World conquest?
I-I'll tell you what I want...
I just want people to treat me fairly.
I want to make all those at the Clock Tower who never acknowledged my talent realize their fault!
Small!
That's puny! And narrow minded. And stupid.
You go into battle, and you're only concerned about your reputation?
And you call yourself my Master?
What a disappointment!
If you wish so desperately for others to respect you,
perhaps you should use the Grail to grow another thirty centimeters.
He's supposed to be my Servant...
How dare he talk to me that way!?
I'll show him!
By this Command Seal,
in accordance with the Grail's laws, I order this man, King Iskandar,
Calm down, Waver...
A Master can only use his Command Seals to compel his Servant's obedience three times.
If I use all my Command Seals, I won't be able to control him.
As long as I get the Grail, I have no complaints.
I don't care what you do after that.
I shall acquire the Grail for you.
You seem confident. Have you made any plans?
So, you wish to see my power. Is that correct?
N-Naturally!
You need to prove to me that I can rely on you!
I am Iskandar the Great!
By this one strike, I declare my supremacy!
This is the ox-chariot that King Gordius once offered Zeus.
Its renown must be the source of my designation as Rider class.
If you want to find the Grail, then go locate a Heroic Spirit or two!
Until then, I shall entertain myself with these maps.
I am certain that will not pose a problem...
All right... I won't lose today.
There's one.
What? Where is it? There's no way I missed it!
That's the first walnut bud today.
You lose a point.
I-I'm not going to lose!
There it is!
I found one, too!
I found two.
That's not a walnut branch...
No, Ilya. This is called a wingnut.
It's a variety of walnut.
So it still counts as a one.
No fair!
No fair! No fair!
Kiritsugu's been cheating this whole time!
But Daddy can't win otherwise.
If you keep cheating, I won't play with you, Kiritsugu!
I don't want that! I'm sorry! I apologize...
Do you promise not to cheat anymore?
Okay, okay, I promise.
Very well. Then I'll challenge you again.
A champion must take on all challengers!
Indeed. I am honored.
Princess...
So high!
What are you looking at, Saber?
Your daughter and Kiritsugu are playing outside.
Surprised?
I was under the impression that my Master was a more cold-hearted person.
Well, I can see how you might think that.
If this is Kiritsugu's true face...
I must have gravely offended him.
Irisviel! This is no laughing matter!
I'm sorry...
I was wondering if you still bore a grudge over what happened during your summoning.
Somewhat.
I did conceal my gender...
But you two needn't have been so taken aback.
But you know... You can't really blame us.
Your legend... King Arthur's legend... It's simply too famous.
Do you suppose Kiritsugu might underestimate my ability because I'm a woman?
That's not possible. But...
That's right... If he's upset, there must be another reason.
Another?
He's probably angry at the people who were around you.
The ones cruel enough to force the duty of a king upon a small girl.
It was inevitable.
I'd resolved myself to that fate when I drew forth the sword from the stone.
That upsets him even more,
how you passively accepted your fate.
Then he's overstepping his bounds.
It is not his place to question decisions made by those of my time, including myself.
That is why he remains silent.
Emiya Kiritsugu and the hero Arturia will never meet face to face.
That is what he has resolved himself to.
He wants to use the Grail's power to save the world.
That is his ambition. Yours as well, correct?
Yes. But I'm only mimicking things he's said.
I desire the Grail for similar reasons.
I wish to save Britain, the country I let down.
I think what you and Kiritsugu seek is just.
I believe it is something you can be proud of.
Fill, fill, fill 'er up, fill...
Repeat... Four times...
Or was it five?
Um, break it up once it's full...
Right?
Fill, fill, fill, fill, and fill.
That's five times!
Okay.
At all three murder scenes,
a mysterious pentagram was found, drawn in the victims' blood.
Maybe I went a bit too far...
The symbol's purpose remains unclear
Today, we've invited a professor who specializes in criminal psychology...
Hey kiddo, do you believe in demons?
All the papers and magazines call me a demon.
What if demons really did exist?
Wouldn't that be rude to them?
You've gotta be clear about these things.
Yo! I'm Uryuu Ryuunosuke, and I'm a demon!
I dunno if that's exactly the right way to go about it.
And then, I found this.
It's some old book from the storehouse.
Looks like my ancestors were researching how to summon demons.
Like, so I've just gotta find out if demons are real!
But you know...
If I do end up summoning a demon,
it'd be pretty silly, chatting with it and then sending it back.
So, kiddo...
If a demon does show up, you think you could let it kill you?
I wonder what it's like, being killed by a demon...
Not many people get to find out! Ow!
What is this?
I ask of you...
You who calls to me... You who seeks me...
Summoner who manifests me within the vessel of a Caster...
I ask your name.
Who...
are you?
Um...
Uryuu Ryuunosuke...
Currently unemployed. My hobby is murder. Murder, and stabbing.
I like kids and young women.
Very well. The contract is sealed.
I desire the Grail, as do you.
The vessel of paradise will be ours.
The gray what?
Anyway, how about a sacrifice?
Wanna eat this kid?
Cool... That's human skin, isn't it?
Cthulhu fhtagn...
Don't be scared, my boy.
Can you stand?
Now, boy, you'll find the exit through that door.
You can manage by yourself, right?
Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing?
Some forms of terror are fresher than others.
People go numb inside when they are afraid.
Terror, in its truest sense,
is not a static state, but a dynamic one.
It is the moment when hope turns to despair...
Did you enjoy that?
The freshness of terror and death?
Cool!
You're awesome! You're so cool!
Okay!
I don't know about this Grail thing, but from now on, I'll follow you!
Let's go kill some people.
I want you to show me some cool ways to kill people!
Ryuunosuke, wasn't it?
What a magnificent omen, to be blessed with an understanding Master such as yourself.
I feel my dream is nearly within my grasp.
Oh, hey. I didn't get your name.
My name?
Let's see. In this era, what would I be most commonly know as?
I suppose you can call me Bluebeard.
The Church contacted me.
They said that the seventh Servant, Caster, has appeared.
The final Servant has been summoned? Then it's time.
Indeed.
You are to head immediately for the Tohsaka household.
And once I arrive?
The house's powerful magical barriers should be child's play for you.
Are you sure about this?
Supposedly, you're allied with Tohsaka Tokiomi.
Don't worry about that.
Even if you must face Archer, there's no need to fear.
No need to fear Archer, one of the three Knight classes?
I'll leave the rest to you.
Your first mission is to slay Tohsaka Tokiomi.
This will be easy.
You lowly worm.
Who gave you permission to come here?
No need...
to fear him,
he said...
You are not worthy to gaze upon me.
A worm should be facing the ground
when it dies.
Episode 2
False Start
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
At last, it's time for the Fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
Unspeakably ugly.
Where is the thing I gave you?
This will be fun.
Welcome.
Grant me victory!
Yes, certain victory.
Next Time
Land of Winter Trees