Kamiyama
Shrine
Fri.
"Dear Oreki Houtarou,
"I'm currently in Varanasi.
"A belated congratulations on your graduation!
"So you've passed Kamiyami High's entrance exam, huh?
"As your big sister, I'll give your high school student self a piece of advice.
"Join the Classic Literature Club.
"It's a club with a lot of history.
"I was a member too!
"From what I was told, our Classic Literature Club has no members.
"If nobody joins this year, the club will be disbanded.
"As an alumni of the Classic Literature Club, it breaks my heart to hear that.
"Houtarou,
"protect your sister's history, the Classic Literature Club.
"All you have to do is sign up.
"It's not like you're interested in anything else, right?
"Best regards,
"Oreki Tomoe."
退屈な窓辺に吹き込む風に
The wind blew into the boring classroom
顔を顰めたのは照れくささの裏返し
That grimace on my face hides my tiny bit of joy
Hyouka
曖昧に頷く　手のひらの現在
I just nod my way through the life designed for me
描いてる自分は少し大げさで
Maybe I'm a little too pretentious
何か変わりそうな気がしているよ
It feels like something is about to change
心に呼びかける君のせいだね
You're probably to blame, for calling out to my heart
曇り空覗いた予感
It's as if I saw a glimpse of color through the clouds
手を伸ばそういつよりも力強い勇気で
Let's reach out with more courage than usual
光も影もまだ遠くて
Light and shadow are still so far beyond our reach
それでも僕らは優しさの理由が知りたい
But we still want to know the source of your kindness
今は誰の名前でもない
Your name doesn't define you
輝きの彼方へ 全部過去になる前に
Let's go find what lies beyond the light
見つけに行こう
Before everything turns into the past
It's been a month since the revival of the Classic Literature Club.
Activities of the Glorious Classic Literature Club
Geography Lab
I've grown accustomed to the Geography Lab.
I just stop by if I'm bored after school.
Here.
Someone gave these to us as a gift.
Take whichever one you'd like.
Thank you.
So long as I'm not wasting energy, I don't mind her company.
After all, I don't hate being around others.
It's a waste.
If you don't harvest twice a year?
That's double-cropping.
Was that a bad joke?
Don't ask me.
That's not what I meant!
So, it's a waste?
Yes, it's a waste!
What is?
This right here!
It's a waste of our time if we have no goals!
That's true.
So you want to take something away from this club?
Yes.
Oh?
It's a bit personal, though.
She said that before, didn't she?
I'm talking about the Classic Literature Club!
It's a club, so we need to have activities!
We don't have any goals.
Of course we do.
We'll collect an anthology of books for the culture festival in October.
An anthology?
Yes!
How about no? That's too much work.
No! It has to be an anthology!
Isn't there something else we
can do for the culture festival?
Let's set up a booth.
The Kami High Culture Festival prohibits the use of booths.
Besides, we were already given a budget for the anthology,
and our club advisor also asked us to make one.
Anthologies have been around for over 40 years too,
so they want to keep the tradition going.
You should've told me all that earlier.
Fine, I'll do it.
Great!
So how do we go about making one?
I have no idea!
Hey...
I'm sorry. I thought we could research it now.
Once we find the archives, I'm sure we'll know what to do.
Let's look for them!
I can't find them.
Maybe they're in the library.
Let's go!
What are you doing?
You're coming with me.
Come on.
What a drag.
It's Friday, so it's probably her  shift...
Library
Well, if it isn't Oreki.
Long time no see. I'm not glad to see you.
Hey, Ibara. I came to see you.
This is a sanctuary of sharing.
No place for the likes of you.
So you belong here?
You have my respect.
I see you're still a jerk.
If you're here to see me, then I'd like you to meet the door.
Excuse me...
Hey, Houtarou!
What a coincidence.
I see you two are as close as ever.
No wonder you were the best
couple at Kaburaya Junior High!
Yeah, right.
Me? With this gloomy loser?
I'd rather deal with a slug.
A slug...
And you, Fuku!
I can't believe you'd say something that mean even though you know how I feel.
My bad, Mayaka.
I'm such a heartbreaker.
There you go again, using jokes to change the subject.
Seriously, just forget about it.
What's with them?
She's been in love with Satoshi since middle school.
My!
Ahem.
Chitanda, this is Ibara Mayaka.
She's an alumni of Kaburaya Junior High too.
Nice to meet you.
Mayaka, this is Chitanda Eru.
She's the president of the Classic
Literature Club I joined a while back.
Nice to meet you too.
So, why are you two here?
Oh, right!
I wanted to ask you something.
Yes?
Do you have the Classic Literature Club's anthologies?
The Classic Literature Club?
I don't think so.
If they're not on the shelves, then they might be in storage.
I see.
Why are you looking for them?
We'll be making an anthology for the cultural festival,
so we wanted to look at the previous ones as a reference.
Oh, you're putting it on display for Kanya Fest?
I'm surprised Houtarou agreed to that.
She pretty much decided it without me.
What's Kanya Fest?
You haven't heard of it?
It's the nickname for Kami High's Culture Festival.
I bet you came up with that nickname.
No, I'm serious!
All my upperclassmen in the
Sewing Club call it the Kanya Fest.
Have you heard it before?
The Manga Society calls it Kanya Fest too.
Kanya?
How do you write it?
No idea.
I tried asking around, but no one told me.
Well, Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival became Kamiyama Fest,
then Kanyama Fest,
and finally Kanya Fest...
That's what I think, at least.
Anyway, Chitanda.
You might find the anthologies in the storage room,
but the librarian is in a meeting, so we can't go in right now.
She should be back in 30 minutes, though.
Do you want to wait?
What should we do?
Let's wait.
You  can leave.
Sure, whatever.
Wait up, Houtarou!
Why don't you tell them the story you told me earlier?
What?
I guess so.
Oreki, wanna use your brain for once in your life?
Nope.
What are you talking about?
It's the story of an unpopular popular book.
An unpopular popular book?
It's a really mysterious story.
It doesn't add up, no matter how you think about it.
Mayaka and I were puzzled by it.
Please tell us!
For five Fridays in a row now,
I've found a certain book in the return box
when I began my after school shift.
It already sounds strange, doesn't it?
This is the book.
What a beautiful book!
Kamiyama High School
50 Years of Journey
It's huge.
May I look inside?
Go ahead.
Take a look, Oreki!
It's just a history of the school.
It seems a bit difficult to read.
I wouldn't be surprised if
someone borrowed this every week.
You've never borrowed a book from here, have you?
You can borrow a book from our library for up to two weeks.
So there's no reason to return it every week.
And yet, someone returns it every single week.
Can you tell who's borrowed it?
Of course.
Look at the checkout card in the back.
Look, Oreki.
Class
Name
Returned
Suzuki Yoshie
Shima Saori
Yamaguchi
Ryouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Machida Kyouko
A different person has borrowed it every week.
They all returned it on the same day too!
That's right.
It was borrowed and returned within the same day for five weeks straight.
We know the time too.
They all borrow it during lunch break, and return it after school.
Well? Are you curious?
Yes.
I'm curious!
Let's try to figure it out, Oreki!
Dammit, Satoshi. You knew this was going to happen!
Oreki, you solved the mysteries of the locked door and the secret club in such a brilliant manner!
What's she talking about?
It's an interesting side of Houtarou.
Don't make it sound so creepy.
At any rate, it makes me very curious!
Not me.
I'm curious!
I'm not!
Oreki.
Quiet down.
You too, Chitanda.
Okay.
I screwed up.
If I keep turning her down, I'm only
going to decrease my energy efficiency.
If that's the case...
Fine. Let me see what I can come up with.
Okay!
Hey, Fuku,
was Oreki always that smart?
Nope, but he can be useful for these useless things.
I'm sitting right here, you know.
Rikka
This is the beginning of the summer
Hyouka
So, five different people came to
borrow this book five weeks in a row,
and they all returned it on the very same day.
Saying it's just a coincidence would be the easy route,
but Chitanda wouldn't accept it.
The truth is not important.
It's all about making her believe my story.
Let's see...
If you borrowed this book during lunch break and
returned it after school, you wouldn't have time to read it.
If you're not going to take it home,
then you'd just read it in the library.
Thus, whoever borrowed it had no intentions of reading it.
But if that's the case...
Are there any other ways to use a book without reading it?
You can use it as a pillow if you stack it with another book.
You can use it as a shield if you tie it to your arm.
Wanna give me a serious answer?
He's right.
There must be a unique use for a book like this.
What's your take on it, then?
Let's see...
You can use it to seal a pickle jar!
You're all useless...
Does Chitanda really get good grades?
It's like she has the mindset of a child.
Let's look a this from another perspective.
Suzuki Yoshie
Shima Saori
Yamaguchi
Ryouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Machida Kyouko
Why does a different person borrow it every week?
These are all girl names.
I can think of two possibilities.
One: They have nothing in common, but this book has some popular use on Friday.
Two: They're part of a group that uses this book,
and these girls take turns borrowing it.
Popular, huh?
Maybe fortune-telling?
Something like, "Your lucky item for the week is... a school's history record!
"If you borrow it on a Friday,
and return it on the same day...
"things might go well with your boyfriend!"
Right?
That's absurd.
It's five weeks straight too.
It was only a suggestion.
They're all female, and all in the 11th grade.
They're in different classes.
I wonder why only females are borrowing this book.
That's hard to say.
It's possible that a random selection of five
people from this school all turn out to be girls.
It's not unusual for girls to group together either.
Could it be some sort of code?
Maybe "yes" if it was returned with the front side up.
And "no" if it was returned with the back side up.
I doubt they used front and back as a code.
See?
Return Box
I see.
It's impossible to tell which side is up.
It's hardly surprising that Oreki can't come up with anything.
Fuku and I were thinking about it for a long... time...
What is it?
I smell something.
You do?
I don't smell anything.
No, I'm certain of it.
It's a pungent smell.
Almost like paint thinner...
I'm certain of it.
A dog?
If Chitanda insists, then she must be right.
If that's true...
You figured something out, didn't you?
Really?
Pretty much.
I can't be too sure, though.
Chitanda, you wanna take a walk?
There's somewhere I want you to go.
Okay!
Hold on... I wanted you to go by yourself.
By myself?
Why?
Well...
That's right, Chitanda!
Don't let Houtarou boss you around!
He's only useful when you use  him!
That's a harsh way of putting it.
No, I just thought we would be going everywhere together.
Oh, I see.
Let's get going, then,
Oreki!
Welcome to the restaurant.
We have prepared two courses for you.
Gray Course
Escape Hors D'Oeuvres
Terrine of Laziness and Indolence
Armchair Meunière with Energy Conservation Sauce
Penne of Lies, Black Widow Style
Slow-Boiled Delay with a Touch of Fallacy
Rejection and Peace Tiramisu
Rose Course
Troublesome Hors D'Oeuvres
Sauteed Effort and Work
Tagliatelle of Wasted Effort
Interest Troffie with
Satisfaction Sauce
la Provence Roasted Curiosity
and Hard Work Mille-feuille
Which would you like?
I highly recommend this one.
Today's mistake might cost you more in the long run.
Oreki?
Fine.
Gym was canceled today,
so I have some spare energy left.
Good!
Just how low is your energy reserve?
None of your business.
Let's go.
Yes!
Wait.
I'm coming with you.
I'm a bit curious too.
Fuku, take over for a bit.
I can't just leave the front desk unattended, you know.
See ya, Satoshi.
Have fun waiting.
So, Oreki, where are we going?
The art room.
That's in the other building.
Yep. Very far away.
That's why I didn't want to go.
You are so  lazy.
What's over there?
Let's see what we have so far.
I doubt there's any girl who would
use such a large book during break.
That being said, we can assume it's for a class.
Which school classes are shared by different homeroom classes of the same grade?
Gym and... and various art classes?
Yep.
Those five girls must've taken turns borrowing the book for each class.
I still don't understand why they'd borrow it every week.
You can borrow books for up to two weeks.
It's easier to return a book that large
every week than drag it around with you.
That's true.
What is it?
This is the smell that book had!
Really?
It'll make sense when we go inside.
That's what they used the book for.
A class shared by Class 2-D, E, and F.
They're painting for a fine arts class.
The book's size was perfect for a still life painting.
So that smell was paint!
How did you know?
How?
It just came to me. It was probably luck.
Library
Well done.
I never would've guessed it was used for a still life painting.
How on Earth did you know that?
You're a weirdo, Oreki.
What are you talking about?
I'm as average as they come.
I don't know about that.
But you really surprised me there.
I'm curious as to what's going on inside your head.
You are?
Yes.
I almost want to cut your head open and see what's inside!
My brain isn't that special.
A top student like yourself wouldn't learn anything from it.
You're a top student?
Yeah, the midterms are still weeks away,
but I'm sure she'll rank near the top of our grade!
No.
Even if I get good grades, it's nothing more than an aggregation of parts.
I'm much more interested in the entire thought process system than the individual parts.
Right...
The bigger mystery is her sense of smell.
Oreki might just...
Oh. Never mind.
Anyway, that was fun.
Did you enjoy it too, Chitanda?
It was very fun!
Time just flew by!
I couldn't figure it out even
though I thought about it for hours.
It's so frustrating!
Didn't I tell you?
He's useful sometimes.
But I can't stand losing to Oreki!
It's just frustrating!
We're different...
We live in different worlds.
I can never be like them.
What makes us so different?
What is it?
That's right.
It's like a rare glimpse of brilliance.
Or...
Oreki, don't go.
Why not?
Oh, the anthology.
That's right.
We have to wait for the librarian.
He's silly like that sometimes.
Sometimes?
I think you're overestimating him.
Ibara.
Good work.
You can go home now.
Okay. I didn't know you were back.
Hello, I'm Fukube Satoshi,
part of the Classic Literature Club.
We're looking for the archives to use as a reference for our anthology.
May we search in the storage room?
The Classic Literature Club's anthology?
You're all in the Classic Literature Club?
I'm sorry, but we don't have the archives in the storage room.
Could you have missed them somehow?
I would remember if I saw them.
Please excuse me.
Thank you for your help.
There you go, Chitanda.
That's not good.
Don't worry. We'll find them.
How do you feel?
Are you ready to solve another mystery?
Not really.
Fine.
We have no choice.
Let's go.
We're not going back empty-handed.
What do you mean?
Nothing. It's a bit personal.
Again with that?
Yes.
Oreki might just be...
Hello, Oreki speaking.
Hello?
I-It's Chitanda.
Chitanda?
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
Kind of.
I thought it was my sister calling.
So, why are you calling me on a Sunday?
I'm sorry, but could we meet up today?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
She's late.
S-Sorry for calling you all the way out here.
Well?
What did you want to talk about?
Excuse me?
Why did you call me out to this café?
You're the one who chose this café.
I'm leaving.
W-Wait!
It's Sunday.
I can't waste my energy on this comedy act.
I-I'm sorry...
I'm just nervous.
You're nervous?
Are you confessing your love to me or something?
In a sense, it is a confession.
Huh?
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね　見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
芽生えてた温もり　暖かくて戸惑う
I'm at a loss to this warmth growing inside me
こんな気持ちをまだ　あなたは分からないの
You're still oblivious to my feelings
その視線には意味なんて別にないはず
I'm sure your gaze doesn't mean anything
だって友達にしてるのと同じ
Because you look the same way at your friends
明け方に消えてく　小さな願い星
The tiny wishing stars disappears into the dawn.
夜の間だけの魔法
This magic only works at night
今夜恋に変わる　幸せな夢で会おう
I'll see you tonight in a happy dream, where it turns into love
きっとね見つけてね
Please come find me
微睡みの約束
It's a dreamy promise
Next week: "Troubled Descendants of the Classic Literature Club."
Troubled Descendants
of the Classic Literature Club