This is easy once you know the trick.
I don't think I'll ever lose this way.
Here.
You're after that, right?
Hey...
I don't want to owe you any favors.
We're even, okay?
Let's go, Madoka.
Sayaka...
Sorry.
I'm a little bit worn out.
Don't push yourself. I'll carry you.
That idiot...
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 8 I've been such a fool
Sayaka...
You're not supposed to fight like that...
Don't lie and say it doesn't hurt!
I can tell how bad you're hurting just watching you!
Don't act like it's okay to get hurt just because you can't feel it!
If I don't do that, I can't win.
I'm no good.
Even if you win fighting that way, it's not good for you!
Good for me? What is good for me?
How is anything good for me with my body like this?
Sayaka...
I'm just a lump of stone put here to defeat witches.
A walking corpse pretending it's alive.
What can anyone do for me?
There's no point even thinking about it.
But I want to make you happy somehow...
Then you fight them.
Kyubey told me you have more potential than anyone.
You can take out witches without getting yourself beat up like that.
I...
That's...
If you want do something for me, then go ahead and see what my life is really like.
Nah, of course you won't.
You're not just going to throw away your humanity out of sympathy.
Sympathy? Sayaka...
I'm like this because even though you could do anything you're doing nothing!
So don't just play innocent while giving me lectures!
Sayaka...
Stay away from me.
I'm a total moron! Why did I say that to her!?
I'm hopeless.
I predict that Walpurgisnacht will appear in this area.
Where's it based?
The clock tower.
The clock tower!?
I haven't heard of Walpurgisnacht appearing in this city before.
So how are you so sure about the clock tower?
This isn't exactly a line of business where you can blindly trust your colleagues, you know.
Why don't you show me a bit more of what you're really after?
I'd like to ask that, too.
Homura Akemi.
You've got a lot of guts showing your face here, rat.
Oh, so I'm an uninvited guest?
And here I am tonight trying to give you some important information.
Sayaka Miki is exhausting herself faster than I expected.
Not only in terms of magic use, but her body itself exudes a cursed air.
And whose fault is that?
If she keeps this up, something unfortunate will happen before Walpurgisnacht arrives.
You should be careful.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why don't you ask her instead of me?
You already know, don't you, Homura Akemi?
I wonder where you picked up that little fact.
I'm very, very curious.
Are you...
You've asked your questions. Now begone.
You're letting him go?
Killing it would solve nothing.
Anyway, what about Sayaka Miki? What's this 'something unfortunate' he's talking about?
Her Soul Gem has become too corrupted.
If it isn't cleansed soon, something will happen that cannot be undone.
The auxiliary verb 'must' denotes something which one is obligated to do, but...
Compared to 'have to', which—
I should have said something to her then...
Wait, Shizuki, you live over here?
I've never seen you walk home this way before.
Well, honestly, it's completely out of the way.
So what did you want me for today?
Kamijo...
There's something I want to talk with you about.
She didn't come home last night?
Of course.
Um... Okay.
Yes. Goodbye.
Sayaka...
I need to find her.
Why don't you understand? We wouldn't have time for this even in normal circumstances.
Hunt only witches.
Gee, thanks a ton for the advice.
Your Soul Gem is at its limits.
If you don't cleanse it...
Use this.
What are you plotting now?
Grow up.
This is no time to be suspicious.
Do you hate being saved that much?
I'm going to be a different kind of magical girl than you lot. I'm sure of it.
I hate people who'd just use and abandon someone.
I need no reward. I'll never use magic for my own benefit!
You're dying.
Once I'm dead, that means I don't have to kill any more witches.
I'll finally have completed my task.
I'm okay with that.
I can't even beat a witch! I have no reason to exist!
So why are you doing this?
I just want to help you. Why won't you believe me?
I'm not sure.
I think it's just intuition.
I can tell you're a liar.
You always look like you've given up on everything.
You're always speaking empty words.
And right now, you say you're doing it for my sake,
but I bet you're really after something completely different.
Don't think you can fool me.
Don't you see how much you're hurting Madoka?
Madoka? She has nothing to do with this.
No... Everything revolves around her.
You're sharp.
In fact, you're exactly correct.
I don't want to help you.
I simply don't want Madoka to have to watch your fall.
If you refuse my aid, only death awaits you.
If you hurt Madoka any more...
I'll kill you myself right now, Sayaka Miki.
Quick! Run away!
What's wrong with you!? You were supposed to be saving her!
Let me go.
Oh, I get it. If I've got a grip on you, you can't use that technique of yours.
Damn it...
eb wanted me to add this ad
a kind of evening rescue
unless japan's "9% in a can" is far better than america's
i think i share sayaka's philosophy of not wanting to be saved
what is over? the ad ofc
I'll protect you even if it costs me my life.
Sheryl loves Alto...
We have only one chance!
I'm just a princess captured by some monster.
Playtime's over.
Gimme a fuckin' break!
She already blew all the cash I gave her!
Dumb bitches don't know how to hold onto money, I tell ya.
Women may as well not even be human.
They're like dogs or something.
They get excited like a goddamn puppy.
But all you need to do to shut 'em up is give 'em a good smacking.
Slacken the leash a little bit, and they're all over the damn couch.
Can't let 'em get too comfortable.
What, you think a bar slut like you is gonna he doing that well ten years from now?
Know your fuckin' place.
Right?
Man, you're good at dumping them when they end up more trouble than you're worth.
I need to learn your tricks.
Tell me more about her.
What?
About the woman you're talking about.
I want to hear more about her.
Hey, babe, you're too young to be out this late.
She cares about you. She works hard to make you happy.
You understand that, don't you?
But you treat her like a dog. You don't even thank her.
When she does something you don't like, you dump her.
What, you know her or somethin'?
No...
Is this world worth protecting? What have I been fighting for? Tell me!
Tell me right away.
Otherwise...
Sayaka... Where are you?
You must blame me too.
If I blame you, will that bring Sayaka back?
No. It's beyond my power.
You told me that I could be an amazing magical girl. Is that true?
Amazing doesn't begin to describe it.
You'd be completely unrivaled.
Probably the strongest in this world.
If i had accepted that, Sayaka wouldn't have had to become a magical girl.
Sayaka chose her own wish. Madoka, you have nothing to do with that.
Why am I...
I don't know either.
To put it frankly, your hidden potential is an unimaginable hope.
I want an explanation as much as you do.
I see...
If you set your power loose, you could cause miracles, or rewrite the laws of nature.
Why are you the only one who has that potential?
I don't understand.
I've always thought that I'm worthless.
That I'd go through life not being able to do anything or help anybody.
That my life would have no meaning.
I resented it, and I felt lonely.
But I resigned myself to it.
The reality is quite different.
Madoka. If you will it, you can become an omnipotent Goddess.
I can do things even you can't, Kyubey?
So if I contract with you, I'll be able to return Sayaka's body to how it was?
That would be no difficulty at all.
Is that wish worth your soul to you?
If it's for Sayaka's sake, yes.
I want to become a magical—
That's terrible! I thought you weren't going to kill anyone!
Why... Why must you always sacrifice yourself?
Don't throw yourself away thinking you're useless or your life's meaningless!
Think about the people who care for you!
Grow up!
Why don't you realize there are people who'll be sad if you're gone!?
What's going to happen to the people trying to protect you!?
Homura...
Did we...
Have we ever met somewhere? You and I?
We...
I'm sorry.
I need to find Sayaka.
Wait...
Sayaka Miki is already—
Sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
Come on, you knew that wouldn't do you any good.
You never learn your lesson.
I have many, many replacements, even if it does form a slight inconvenience.
It's just a waste.
This is the second time you've killed me. I'm learned how you attack now.
That was time control magic, wasn't it?
Oh, wait, I just realized.
You're not from this timeline, are you?
I know your true form, and what you're plotting.
Very well. And that's why you've been such a thorn in my paw?
Is your desire to change Madoka Kaname's fate that strong?
Yes.
I'll never allow your plan to succeed.
Kyubey...
No.
Incubator.
I finally found ya.
How long are you gonna keep blowing off your friends?
Sorry to bother you.
What's wrong? You're not acting like yourself.
I just don't care anymore.
What do I even care about anymore? Who do I want to protect?
I don't even know anymore.
Hey...
The balance of hope and despair is always zero.
You said so yourself.
I understand what you meant now.
I've saved plenty of people.
But in exchange, resentment and pain took root in my own heart.
I'm even hurting my dearest friend now.
Sayaka! Are you—!?
As much as I wished for the happiness of one...
Someone else must be equally cursed.
That's how the story of a magical girl goes...
I've been such a fool.
Sayaka!
In this country, growing young women are called girls.
So it's only proper that you, turning into witches, should be called magical girls.
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes will
(Go beyond the time)
There is but one dream, of a world rushing toward its doom
(Will it be destroyed?)
Swallow your hesitation! What do you desire?
Chasing these greedy desires, will the future fade away?
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even the darkness
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a plucked laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
Remembering it, I feel all tingly.
My songs are my life.
I'll soar! Until I can end this war!
Alto! Wake up!
Illustration: Takuya Fujima/Kentaro Tanaka
You might think I'm stupid for this,
but I don't want to give up as long as there's any hope of saving her.
Episode 9 I'll never forgive that
Episode 9 I'll never forgive that.
I'll never forgive that.