I'm home.
Everyone is out again.
Nekane-san!
Yeah! I'm fine!
How's Negi?
He's crying because his job is too hard, isn't he?
Eh?
Oh. I see. So things are going well.
And he has lots of friends. Is... that so?
I was so worried.
Eh? Here?
Yeah! Of course everything is fine!
Everything's going well.
Divination is really thriving these days.
I also made friends with everyone on stage!
Et Clio Illios!
The magical item that even the Thousand Master cannot use...
If I can use this...
What if I fail?
But... At this rate, I'll lose!
For me to lose...
Anything but that!
I will beat Negi!
The devil's gem—that is the Star Crystal.
Amoris!
The last of the fairy fragments suddenly appeared...
and combined with the other fragments to turn into the Shriek of the Soul.
Finally! The Star Crystal has been awakened!
And so, Evangeline, possessed by the Darkness, addresses Negi.
Eva-san!
Negi, it's me.
Anya!
I will not lose! I will not lose to you!
Never...
Anya...
Note: There is a second subtitle stream with translation notes.
"Hold on, that's not what I meant Negi-kun!"
by Yuuna.
"That's right! I'm your parter after all!"
by Ako.
Stop it, Anya!
It's useless, Nekane-kun.
I won't let you get in my way.
They turned to stone!
Anya, how could you...?!
Master!
Chachamaru-san!
Mas...ter...
Anya, stop this!
Anya!
Aniki! Look out!
Asuna-san!
Negi, let me transform!
I'll fight!
But...
Believe in your partner!
She’s going to shoot again! Aniki!
Negi!
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna.
Show me the power... within you!
Contract...
Activate!
It's an Armor Card!
You... You... You!
Asuna-san, be careful.
She disappeared!
A kiss?!
It broke! The contract is broken!
Ane-san...
No way...
Now this girl will be my servant.
Now, defeat Negi for me.
Aniki!
Asuna-san!
Negi-kun!
She's possessed by the Darkness, de gozaru!
Nekane-san and Takahata-sensei are…
....turned to stone!
Why?!
Everyone! Please get out of here!
It's good to have lots of friends, huh, Negi?
Please run!
We know, but...
I’ll be fine.
So just hurry!
Everyone! Seriously, we have to run!
But I don't want to ditch him like that!
I... I'm hit!
Chamo-kun!
Ojou-sama, this place is...
We must leave this instant, de gozaru!
NO!!
Please forgive me.
Nin!
Fleeing is futile.
Anya!
Negi...
I'll make you lonely too.
Lonely like me!
Amoris!
Asuna-san, I'm sorry.
Aniki!
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine!
Aniki...
It's alright!
If you cancel the magic, everyone will return to normal!
The class student list...
Everyone, please hear me out.
Evangeline-san is currently controlled by the Darkness.
She is currently targeting all of you.
And she wants to petrify you using magic.
It's dangerous, so please hide in any nooks or crannies you can find!
I will definitely defeat the Darkness...
...so that everyone can come with me back to the real world!
All 31 of you from class 3-A, let's go home together!
So until then, please hide yourselves!
Aniki…
Even if he tells us to hide...
We can't just leave Negi-sensei like that.
Alright! Let’s go to Negi-sensei!
Okay... Oh!
Evangeline!
What should we do?
She looks like she’s in pain.
Sakurako!
She fainted.
Has the Darkness left her body?
Maybe...
That's why she fainted...
Let's take her to be examined!
Just kidding.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Let's go Chamo-kun.
Yeah.
Mana.
What?
Maybe we shouldn't be hiding after all, aru!
Let's go save Negi-bouzu, aru!
Don't say that now!
No feeling at all...
Who was it that told us to hide quickly?
It's not "Who".
It's Kuu Laozi, aru!
Kuu Laozi will always be black.
That's funny, aru!
Silence! We'll be discovered!
Ho ho!
All of them became stone.
The parents would certainly be happy about this.
That’s right.
By the way, haven’t you received a response for that emergency call, ~mya?
You don’t have to look so surprised, ~mya.
We've been petrified!
We’re hit!
In a good way!
Aniki...
At this rate, everyone in the class will be...
Anya...
It's going to the Science Lab.
Hello, this is Yuuna.
Got it.
We will now pursue and observe.
Please be careful.
Eva-san is currently on her way to the Science Lab.
Haruna-san, found it yet?
♪ Tokimeki Fanfare~
I haven't found it yet...
♪ Fanfare~
...even though we should have seen it by now.
Chizuru-san, what's the status on Hakase-san and Chao-san? What do you think?
♪ Tokimeki fanfare~
I sent them a text, but they haven’t replied.
♪ Fanfare~
Maybe it just means they're working hard?
Um...
Negi-sensei, we are cooperating to do whatever we can in this situation.
♪ Tokimeki fanfare~
♪ Fanfare~
So, don't try to make it hard for yourself!
♪ Tokimeki fanfare~
This is Yukihiro.
Ah. Misora-san?
We have another occurrence of petrification.
Understood. Eva-san seems like she is in the Science Lab now.
And when you add a ribbon to it... it turns into something really cool!
Please be careful when you return.
Makie-san?
Hmm?
Add these to the list of petrified people:
Kuu Fei-san, Zazie-san, Shichimi-san...
and... Motsu.
Ah! Okie dokie...
Kuu Fe-i...
Ma-na...
Zazie... Shichimi-chan...
And Motsu...
Hmm? Why's it all in Hiragana?
Eh? Something wrong with that?
Chiu-chiu-san, do not use such a loud voice on Makie-san!
Don't call me "Chiu-chiu!"
Makie-san can't write in Kanji?
Chizu-nee, that is a bit too blunt.
Well, it's not like I CAN'T write it...
I just can't write it off the top of my head!
What an ordinary answer.
Fuuka-san, Fumika-san.
Any response from Kaede-san?
Not yet...
Looks like she can't find Negi-sensei, desu!
Is that so...
Kono-chan hasn't spoken since just now.
Maybe she is really angry after all.
Uh... um...
SO SHE IS MAD!
What should I do?!
Gather your courage!
I'm terribly sorry!
Huh?
Since it was an emergency, I did not want you to get involved...
Ah, that thing!
I'm not worried about that.
Huh? I-If that's the case...
Hey, you think I got fatter?
Huh?
Were you thinking about that?
Yeah... See, feel!
Well?
N-No...
Y-You haven’t...
Really?
Yesh! Really!
You over there! This is an emergency, what kind of comedic stunt are you trying to pull off, anyway?!
Comedic?
Satsuki-san...
Have some tea, Iinchou.
Wahaa, it smells good!
It's herbal tea, to calm yourself.
Myself...
Ah! I also want to serve Negi-sensei a drink!
Got it!
We found it!
Ooh, no mistake about it!
Ah! It's this! This spell!
Come over here and explain it to me!
AH! That was my masterpiece!
Shut up, failure-at-life!
Failure…
Good grief.
It's Kaede-nee.
Negi-bouzu sighted. Looks like he's heading for the Science Lab, de gozaru.
Ever since it came in here... it hasn't come out.
That's right...
Why don't we look inside?
Everyone, please get away from there!
Negi-kun!
Curious little girls, aren't they?
Anya...
You finally decided to fight, huh, Negi?
Tel Ma
Aniki!
I wanted to turn everyone in the class into stone but...
Oh well, I'll just finish things off with you.
Practei beginnar! Arerearis!
W-What's this?!
Everyone!
Beginner's magic?
“If there are lots of people, beginners can also release a great deal of magic.”
That's what's written inside the book.
Thank goodness it went well!
It could be beginner’s luck.
No, this is no accident.
Our strong feelings for Negi-sensei guided the magic down the path of success!
Stop exaggerating! It's embarrassing...
Now that we have done this, we can really be your partners now!
Are you surprised, Anya-san?
We all...
love Negi-sensei!
You guys...
Come, Negi-sensei.
We'll leave the rest to you!
Here, sensei.
Alright.
Sensei! Watch out!
Negi-sensei!
Negi-kun!
Chachamaru-san!
It looks like we made it.
In the nick of time!
Hakase!
Lingshen!
Now's the time, Negi-sensei!
Right!
Amoris!
I will take Eva-san back!
AWESOME! The provisional contract is complete!
Ah! She’s back to normal!
Desu!
C-Chachamaru-san!
Negi-sensei, in this case, please do it with me as well.
Contract complete!
With this, Class A is ALL COMPLETE!
Yay.
I-Idiot! What the hell are you doing, Chachamaru?!
Making a contract with Negi-sensei.
Why?!
What do you mean why? You did it, too.
Though I doubt you remember.
We’re now partner-buddies, right, Eva-san?
What the hell!?
Anya!
Ah! This is bad, Negi-sensei!
The Star Crystal is...
Anya!
Negi-kun!
Don't touch the stone!!
Negi!
Negi-sensei has been taken by the Star Crystal!
No way...
Negi!!!
Everyone! Look outside!
It's the forest, desu!
That is...
The forest of Wales.
Negi got sucked in by the Star Crystal,
and suddenly the forest of Wales appears in front of everyone!
Next is the climax! Keep your eyes open for the next episode!
We might have something interesting here!
With full mental concentration in Yoga,
even fire can turn cold.
Next time, “Negi-sensei, looks like it's the climax now,” by Akira.
"Let's all go home together, okay, Negi-kun?"
by Misora.
Alright, now it's time!
Oh, so that was just for the ramen.
I've got a cat's tongue that's why!
After falling into the trap of Doctor Pooh, the helpless Baka Rangers died an honorable death.
But, the heavens did not abandon them.
Baka Red!
Baka Black!
Baka Blue!
Baka Yellow!
Everyone gets along! Baka Pi-