I think this is a sure sign she's
turning into the sparky heroine.
You're...
Help me!
The head's living on its own.
What will you do with it?
I want to meet her, no matter what.
They're probably from
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
It's OK. Leave it all to me.
Honestly, I only half believed it.
I have all the pawns I need.
I have to go.
I have to go and get her back.
My sister can't do it.
I have to do it.
I have to do it myself!
She wasn't there?
Correct. It seems,
when they arrived, she was gone.
The student who lives there...
Ryuugamine, yes?
What about him?
They heard what he said
when he got back,
and they were prepared
to take him with them.
But there was someone else with them.
Should have just brought them, too.
Useless.
What should we do?
Hello?
Yagiri Namie-san?
Who is this?
My name is Ryuugamine Mikado.
Would you like to make a trade?
Storm and
Stress
It's my...
Welcome! Welcome!
Russian sushi?
It's good!
It's cheap!
What is life?
To what end do we live?
A man once asked me that, and I beat
him within an inch of his life.
I can understand an emo middle-school kid,
but a 20-something yakuza? Should be illegal.
Yeah.
Simon-san, you don't really understand
what I'm getting at, do you?
Yeah.
After living here twenty
years, have I changed?
It wasn't useless at all.
The twenty years you've lived
here weren't useless.
If you apply them to your life
from here on, nothing is useless.
Apply them?
Apply them how?
For example...
Marry me?
Shinra...
You're Mikado-kun?
You're a much quieter
kid than I'd imagined.
Or maybe kids like you are
much more dangerous nowadays...
So, what's this trade?
I have the person you're looking for.
I see.
Then how much do you want?
I don't want money.
What do you want?
The truth.
What did you say?
I want you to admit what your brother
did to Harima Mika-san
and what you did to Mika-san's body.
Unfortunately, all I have
is circumstantial evidence.
I'll be brief. Turn yourselves in.
I see... So you're that type.
I won't let you stand in my brother's way.
People who do that are wrong, you know?
They can't be allowed to exist.
I see. She's... She's that type of person...
Hey, tell me.
Where's my sister?
I have to go.
She needs me.
I have to be there!
Hey, tell me!
That's the reason, huh?
Someone died for it. And she did that
horrible thing to her body...
And now she's after me!
That's why you took someone's life?
Are you going to make Yagiri-kun miserable
for the sake of your own self-satisfaction?
Isn't a bit late for that?
If, at your age, you've gotten caught up
in the underworld
but all you can do is shout platitudes,
It'll be OK, right?
then you need to shut your mouth.
It might be a platitude.
But so what?
You're the one who can't understand something
as simple as feeling guilt over a murder!
You've seen too much TV.
This isn't a clichéd script
written by a hack.
It's reality.
This isn't TV or a magazine.
It'll be OK, right?
You're no hero, either.
Know your role.
What's wrong with that?
I love clichés!
I love predictable scripts.
I love it when they paste over problems,
and I love it when they force a happy end, too!
What's wrong with working toward that?!
I won't say I'm doing this for humanity
or for the world's sake.
I just want to see it!
I want to believe.
That's right.
I believe.
I will believe!
Everyone will, I'm sure.
It may be a cliché.
But if it's a cliché, that just means
its something everyone believes!
Is that all you wanted to say?
I have neither the power nor wisdom
to oppose a foe who won't listen to reason.
You won't even give me time to try.
And so...
I'll rely on numbers!
Sending
--> Sent
What?
Wow!
They're all in on this?
Amazing! It's like something
out of Missing!
Care to give death a try?
It's here!
You serious?
Now, then...
Togusa, you take care of the rest.
Here we go.
How many are there?
Oh, man! Our first meeting,
I didn't think we'd get so many!
This is the Dollars?
Hey, Isaac?
What is it, Milia?
These people are part
of the Dollars, right?
That's right, Milia!
Listen up, people!
We're now the most current, the most young,
the most popular and connected, 24/7!
What is this?
They can't all...
Impossible!
This is impossible!
What? We've just met today
for the first time!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing...
Back home, the sky was big and wide.
But...
There wasn't anything there.
When I was a kid, this town
overflowed with adventure.
When did it end up like this?
I wanted to change something.
But I had no reason to leave
or courage to do so.
And then, one day...
Double click, double click...
There were all kinds of worlds out there.
Worlds I'd never seen, worlds
I couldn't reach.
I started talking with Kida-kun,
who had moved to Tokyo.
And one time, I had an idea.
At first, it was more of a joke
than anything else.
A gang?
Yeah. I've heard there are
lots of them in Tokyo.
<GG>
Make an online gang?
No. Make it real.
<Tanaka Tarou>
Say it's a gang in Ikebukuro.
We'll spread that rumor
all over the internet.
The Dollars caused that mess in Ikebukuro.
We didn't identify ourselves
as Dollars members.
What, you've never heard of the Dollars?
Our front was that we'd heard of the BBS from
somewhere else and just spread the name.
They say the leader is a former CIA
Special Agent and Arabian oil king.
We made a password-protected
site for the gang.
We spread the password via
e-mail and various forums.
Lots of our "members" posted on the BBS.
There's no gang like that in Ikebukuro.
Of course, a lot of people
didn't believe us.
It's a fake!
What's your source?
Shut up, troll.
Eventually, people started defending us.
You've never even been to Ikebukuro.
Everyone was so happy.
Man, everyone's buying it!
Idiots! Man they're all idiots!
I had a bad feeling...
I heard the Dollars were behind it.
Yesterday, the Dollars mugged
me on Sunshine Street!
People calling themselves Dollars began
appearing in the real world.
Me, too!
The Dollars made me buy this ring.
And that wasn't all.
I saw some "The Dollars are Here!" graffiti.
Total # of Members
Before we knew it,
the member count kept increasing,
even though we'd stopped
giving out the password.
It was like someone was
leaking information.
Everyone, you all here?
<Tanaka Tarou>
Hello!
I don't know if they got scared or what, but the others
who helped me make the Dollars vanished.
I didn't stop, though.
No. I couldn't.
A kid I knew got beaten up by the Dollars.
I don't know why.
They're a bunch of shitheads.
That's not true.
There may have some bad people,
but there are lots of
good people, too. I know it.
Why don't we make the
Dollars a good group?
Like, maybe do enough good things to negate
the bad impressions those others leave?
Like?
Like, picking up garbage
or erasing graffiti.
Platitudes.
Kid.
Don't be a bitch.
The neighbors are mystified!
The graffiti, which was on the walls
until last night, disappeared.
"The Dollars are here!"
Who could've done this?
Wipe the graffiti on a wall
off, in just one night...
It's impossible to believe that one person alone
could have cleaned so much graffiti.
No way, huh?
At Kida-kun's invitation, I went to Tokyo.
Dollars?
I don't know details,
but there are lots of them.
And they're all a little nuts...
Seems they're a color gang,
but no one knows what color, etc.
You shouldn't go near
them just for fun.
Don't ask questions.
But the Dollars would be the
strongest in town right now?
So, what are they like?
I dunno. Probably the best word to describe
them is "colorless and invisible."
The Dollars?
I know them.
I'm one of them.
I got a girlfriend after I joined the Dollars.
You write silly stuff on a BBS...
...and someone responds.
At this age, it's hard to meet
people outside of work.
Did you know
the Dollars saved someone who was
almost caught by those Manhunters?
The Dollars are great!
Not really.
It's fun, so why not?
It's more than I thought.
It's fun.
Orders - Everyone not looking at their cell
right now is an enemy.
Don't attack them.
Just watch quietly.
It's fun, isn't it?
What?
What's going on?
Who are these people?
Hey, who do you think the founder is?
See any Arabian oil sheiks?
Nope.
Togusa-san,
the real founder was the one who
responded to us, right?
Yeah... That's what I think.
Togusa!
The light's red! Red! Red!
She's not saying a thing...
Dotachin! Dotachin!
I told you not to call me that.
Look! There's a response
on the Dollar's BBS!
We have a girl with a scar on her neck.
Anyone knowing her, please contact us.
"Please give me the details."
Everything's ready.
I'll let you meet her.
In exchange, I want you to help me.
What's your name?
Celty.
He's not here!
What are you doing?
Find him!
Right!
Move!
Where did he go?
Move! Move it!
Screw it all!
Who said that?
I don't have a head!
I'm a monster!
I don't have a mouth to speak with,
or eyes to express my passion!
Do you hear something?
What's that voice?
But so what?!
So what?!
Celty...
I am here.
I exist!
For if I have no eyes to see,
then behold all that I do!
Hear the cries of those
who enraged the monster!
Th-The Headless Rider!
The Headless Rider!
What? The Headless Rider?
I am here.
I'm right here.
I'm right here!
I shout already, "Here am I born!"
To carve my existence
into this town!
Are you Ryuugamine Mikado?
Celty...
Give Celty back to me!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Yin and
Yang
I discovered a truth in this town.
A simple, common thing.
I think that that boy, too...
Next time:
Yin and Yang.