A large battalion of the Roman Army
appeared on the border of Seize?!
Aisha!
What was that gunshot just now?
The Roman soldier has been captured.
Is she dead?
No, she's still breathing.
Very good.
Our unit will now rendezvous with the 1st and 3rd Divisions
that are heading to the border.
What are you-
Don't move!
If you move, I'll shoot.
Captain!
Colonel, order your men to retreat from the fortress.
ECHO IN THE BLUE SKY
What in the world is going on here?
It's treason!
The girls in the fortress took our commander hostage
and locked themselves in.
What'd you say?!
Luckily, it didn't hit her internal organs.
So...
I don't think her life is in danger.
Thank you, Yumina-san.
Well done.
That girl was to be a sacrifice for the battle, after all.
She'd be worth less if she died.
What's that supposed to mean?!
We've been trailing the Roman Army moving along
the rear border of our country for the past month.
It's probably their way of putting pressure on the peace talks.
They underestimated us.
But the Archduke was being a coward,
telling us not to do anything to them.
That's why we need a way to force them
to make the first move.
For example, the execution of a
crying captive in front of their eyes.
You couldn't possibly-
The peace talks are a joke!
We must burn Rome to the ground!
Isn't that right, Kannagi Noel?
Or rather, our famous "Helvetian Witch".
Did you really think I didn't recognize you?
Stop it! Noel was just used by you people!
Noel-san...
So you really had something to do
with that Invisible Reaper after all?
The Invisible Reaper?
Known as the genius born only once in a century,
the one who revived the Invisible Reaper
at a bioweapons facility from the old era,
is that girl over there.
Your talent is valuable.
Come back to my side.
Kureha-chan,
take this man to the underground distillery.
My armies should be deploying
to confront the Romans as I speak.
The situation just needs a small spark.
So we're back to the battlefield again, huh?
Just when I thought it was all over.
Our luck sucks, eh?
I have confined the Colonel in the distillery.
Sorry for the trouble, Kureha-chan.
Why don't you have some of these.
I bought these baked sweets from Treize.
They're good, you know?
Naomi-san, you're still here?
I'll get out if it gets really bad.
This all is just messed up, really.
The fire maidens are supposed to protect the town,
but we end up getting the town involved in our war.
About that...
While we were hiding, Aisha-san told me
about the legend of the fire maidens.
And she said, according to the Roman literature,
they tell a completely different version of it.
How does it go?
The fire maidens protect lives.
Wh-What?!
It's my turn to take watch.
No, it's okay.
Can you even handle it?
Do you have the resolution to shoot someone?
If I believe it's the right thing to do, I think I can do it.
Are you sure?
Well, I am a girl of the fortress after all.
Just like our great seniors, the fire maidens.
What? You really believe that fairy-tale story
created by the Romans?
Yeah.
Somehow, I can understand it.
The fire maidens protect lives.
I think that might be the case, after all.
What is it?!
I can hear it.
Huh? Hear what?
Kanata!
There's no way she can hear that all the way out here,
no matter how good her ears are.
A ceasefire call?
Yes, I heard it.
Are you sure?
I'm certain of it.
It's still early to rejoice.
She might have misheard.
And even if she's right, it's still unclear
whether the peace treaty was signed.
Anyway, we need to inform Colonel Hopkins-
This is bad!
When I brought the Colonel his meal, he wasn't there!
I'm glad you're safe.
We will begin our assault in ten minutes.
Colonel!
Do you really think the Colonel will listen to us?
It wouldn't hurt to try.
Roger that.
It's impossible.
The Colonel... was laughing.
Seeing the death and destruction caused by the Reaper I revived,
he laughed hard.
He... will kill.
He will fight until no one is left alive.
But, I helped him with it...
It's all my fault...
If that's what you think,
then please, save more people than you have killed, Noel-san.
Aisha...
Ceasefire you say?
Don't make me laugh.
But we can trust her ears.
That's right! We can guarantee that!
She's such a scatterbrain, she forgets stuff,
acts like a kid, and isn't sexy at all,
but she wouldn't lie!
Detain this old woman!
Do you really want war that badly?!
Civilization and science progress through war.
I just want to recreate the past glory of mankind.
What?!
It seems the Roman Army is planning to attack tomorrow morning!
So, we can no longer avoid battle.
Naomi-san has been detained.
Let's go, then.
That's reckless!
We're up against The Demon of Vingt!
But I want the notes that have been entrusted to me get through!
That's just you! You're being selfish!
Why are you deciding everything yourself?
We're soldiers, you know?!
Someone once told me that the world has already come to an end.
But, I love his world.
I love this town.
I love all of you here.
I can't...
give up!
Kanata...
I beg of you.
Please stop the war.
That's what Aisha-san wants as well.
But... I...
I've killed other people too, as a soldier.
Just like you, Noel.
I'm...
Just... Like you...
You've suffered enough.
That's why I forgive you...
...even if no one else will forgive you.
That's why, it's enough...
Will you...
forgive me?
Thank you,
Aisha.
If we go, there's no turning back.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Then... there's nothing more for me to say.
Do whatever you want.
Thank you, Kureha-chan.
You've been holding out for our sake, haven't you?
I just don't want a girl my age... to go through... torture too.
But, Rio-senpai's gone!
And Noel and Kanata are such slackers...
That's why... I need to be strong!
I'm sorry I couldn't be a reliable Captain for you.
Kureha-chan.
Let's go, everyone.
Right.
Please God,
give your blessings to these fire maidens.
Raising the main conversion reactor output.
FAP, FAC, DMR, ECP operational.
Superconductor circuit is stabilizing.
The fire control system is normal.
The main cannon as well as secondary cannon are functional.
Release all joint locks!
W-Weight reduction system, operational.
Coefficient minus, around five.
Preparations complete.
Do it just like we practiced and we'll be fine.
Let's go, my darlings!
Roger!
Prepare the main cannon!
Load AP round!
AP round loaded!
Target ready!
Kana-chan, the call please.
Roger.
"Commence assault"?!
Fire!
It's Kanata nee-chan!
The Takemikazuchi...
They've rebuilt that much of the old era technology...
Signal to all tanks!
Move out and stop them at all costs!
Launch the assault!
We won't let you through!
No more war!
Don't get in their way!
The only way you'll get through is over our dead bodies!
Yeah!
So, what's your next move, Mr. Demon of Vingt?
Circle around! Rendezvous with the rear forces!
The fire maidens protect lives.
I'll leave the rest to you, Kanata-san.
Long ago,
before the world became what it is today,
an angel was sent down by God
to deliver punishment unto the world.
It got injured and rested its wings at the western end of town.
The ones who saved the angel were maidens
living in the fortress on the outskirts of town.
They knew it was sent to destroy them,
but, upon seeing the pitiful wounded angel,
the maidens, with the help of a giant spider,
gave the angel shelter at the bottom of the valley.
The maidens took turns holding the angel's neck,
laboring to suppress the flowing blood.
And so, the angel gave to the maidens
a golden horn in return.
But, in the end, the townspeople found out about the angel,
and set fire to the valley.
The maidens were engulfed in flames, the angel beheaded and killed.
But then, the angel's army descended and shrouded the sky over the town.
It may have been a miracle,
but a note resounded through the sky,
and the angels drew back.
Saving all the human lives,
was the sound of a golden horn,
blown by the last maiden, in exchange for her life.
Hey, do you remember that Missy?
The one you gave your caramel to?
She'll be dragged into this, won't she?
All hands, prepare for attack!
We're all soldiers. It's our job.
Attack!
Huh?
What's that?!
It's a tank of an ally.
The unit is...
Platoon 1121.
It's a ceasefire call!
Yes...
It's the Roman military's call!
Commander!
Like hell we'll stop here! Prepare the main cannon!
No, they're not stopping...
Captain!
Kana-chan!
It's her!
What are you doing?! Start firing!
Fire! Fire at once!
Everyone, lower your weapons!
I am the second heir of the Helvetian Royal Republic,
and the fiancée of the Holy Roman Emperor,
Rio Kazumiya Arkadia!
I command you in the name of my father, the Archduke of Helvetia, and the Roman Emperor.
The treaty is signed.
You shall not fight!
Both sides shall disengage!
This is an imperial order!
Those who act in defiance shall be punished by the First Helvetian Royal Guard in the name of both leaders!
No way...
So, we...
We don't have to fight!
Missy!
Sergeants!
It's very much spring now, isn't it?
Oh yeah, Noel...
What did Aisha write in her letter the other day?
My wounds have healed well, and now each day I practice-
Translate, please!
She's all better now and practicing her trumpet.
Really? Good for her.
We get a letter from Rome, but not from the Government Center, huh?
She must be busy.
Since she's a princess and all.
But you know, she was completely surrounded by guards on the battlefield,
so we couldn't talk to her at all.
Ah, I hear the sound of Claus-san's bike.
She's here! She's here!
I've been waiting for this new recruit!
I'm gonna be strict and-
As of today, I am assigned to Platoon 1121.
Lieutenant Rio Kazumiya Arkadia.
Captain Filicia Heidemann, permission to be posted.
Permission granted.
We don't use ranks here, Rio.
Um, the Roman emperor turned out to be quite understanding.
He said he'd grant me one wish as a reward for stopping the war.
So...
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Senpai!
Welcome home, Rio.