Starlight.
This is the story of goddesses
guided by the light of the stars.
They collide and clash.
They grow closer even as they pass each other by.
However,
it is a tragedy where an eternal parting awaits.
Let's go, to pluck that star together!
They fail to achieve their dream.
That stage and that song...
hopelessly stir us.
Let us go to that stage.
To become shining stars,
together!
Girls' Musical
Revue Starlight
Who will be the one to claim that star?
At the top of that tower
A silent flame lit up inside of me
And now a burning longing fills my chest
We're not puppets on a stage
Being made to dance by fate
Go, take flight!
I know I saw it on that day
The glimmer of an exploding star
Until we have our promise from so long ago in hand
It begins before the curtain rises
The story plays out before my very eyes
In this new life of mine
I got to meet you
Once again
Dear Kagura Hikari,
It has been cold here lately,
but how are things on your end?
The stage girl Aijo Karen is feeling great as usual.
Huh?
Oh, right. The 99th Seisho Festival's Starlight.
It went off without a hitch.
It was our first performance at the Seisho Music Academy,
but we all worked together,
and I think it turned out really well!
But I can't get complacent.
I'll definitely snag the Flora role next year.
And when that happens I'd love it if you came to watch.
Or something.
Every day, I'm getting one step closer to the promise we made. I think.
So I really hope you too...
Oh, but overexerting yourself is a definite non, non!
Until my next letter.
Love, Aijo Karen.
I'm off.
Karen, thank you for all your letters.
I'm busy with lessons every day, but I'm running too.
Towards our promised stage.
So that I can become a star here.
The Royal Academy of Theatrical Actors.
Acting, directing,
playwriting, stage design, lighting, sound design...
This is a drama school where people gather who are aiming to work in the theater.
We're divided into classes, each with a custom curriculum.
From cutting edge acting theory,
all the way to production,
professionals guide us as our teachers
in high-level and specialized lessons.
We're all classmates gathered from around the world, fighting for the same dream.
You can't relax for even a second.
Every day feels like competing in earnest on the stage.
A supporting role in a regularly-scheduled play is not enough.
I have to become better, even more refined.
To aim for that promised stage...
Hikari-chan, don't go!
Karen, you can't become a star if you're a crybaby.
What?
B-But...
If you go to Dondon...
London!
I can't Starlight by myself!
I've made up my mind.
You won't go to Dondon?
I won't come back until I've become a star.
And I won't see you, either.
Why? Why?
Why, why?
Why?!
If I'm around, you'll depend on me too much.
No way... Can I call you?
Nope.
Um, well, then...
Can I write you letters?
You don't need to write anything back.
I'll just send you them one way.
Okay?
O-Okay...
Karen.
Hikari-chan?
We'll meet on the stage.
Yeah! It's a promise!
No, that's not right.
It's our destiny!
Destiny?
Yeah!
Tokyo        Gift       City
I acted cool in front of you, Karen,
but it was actually for my own sake.
If I didn't push you away like that,
I'd end up wanting to see you.
You love the stage, and you love Starlight.
That's what you told me, Karen.
And that's why I'm running.
We'll reunite beneath the spotlight.
On top of the stage where you are waiting for me.
So that we can become stars together.
I can't be satisfied with just this.
Even greater...
Even greater heights!
What's this place?
Revues are enchanting stage performances with songs and dances.
A-A giraffe?
You would prefer Japanese?
I understand.
A revue consists of song and dance woven into a mesmerizing play.
We will now be holding auditions,
and to whoever puts on the brightest-shining revue
the Star Tiara will be bestowed,
and the path to becoming the top star will open up.
Top star?
The one who will stand on the stage of destiny.
Emitting an infinite glimmer,
unleashing their full potential,
they will transcend time to shine on.
The eternal lead.
The stage of destiny...
Will you participate in the auditions?
I understand.
Karen, I'll be waiting for you...
on the stage of destiny!
No way!
This marks the end of the final audition.
Huh?
What happened with Judy? It's ridiculous how good she's become suddenly.
That jump and grand fouetté were really beautiful.
What in the world were those auditions?
Oppression of the people, frequent wars.
We cannot overlook the tyranny of the emperor any longer!
What's wrong with me?
We, the Brotherhood of the Sword, will carry out justice with God as our witness!
I should be emotionally invested in the play,
but I don't feel a thing.
Neither the nervousness from standing on the stage,
nor the exaltation from singing.
My right hand—my son's sworn friend—
must even you betray me?
The glimmer I felt on stage...
Why...
is it all...
Even if I must fight him one day...
...gone?
130g lost in weight.
One jar of the usual hand cream.
A salmon sandwich from Cross Town.
A Macbeth paperback.
Eleven two-pound coins.
The weight of one kidney.
What is it that I've lost?
What's wrong with me?
I can't feel a thing.
I was in a hurry to do something.
I feel as though I was really frantic,
yet now... I can't remember a single thing.
Why was I standing on the stage again?
What was I aiming for when I entered that school?
Oh, that's right, that thing.
The promise I made with Kare—
Karen...
I can't believe it. Just now, I...
I referred to our promise as "that thing".
What's wrong with me?
What happened?
The auditions?
No, no...
Pick up already.
I said pick up.
Pick up, giraffe!
I won't stand for this.
At this rate, I'll...
Girls' Musical Revue Starlight
To whoever puts on the brightest-shining revue
the Star Tiara will be bestowed,
and the path to becoming the top star will open up.
But if we lose, we'll have it all stolen from us.
Our precious glimmer and everything else.
I understand.
You tricked me.
The birth of a top star requires a fair amount of fuel, you see.
You mean that's the glimmer you stole from me?
I failed to predict that this much glimmer would remain.
So I present you with a new opportunity.
What?
For the next auditions...
They will be held in Japan.
To whoever puts on the brightest-shining revue,
the path to becoming the top star will open up.
You'll let me participate again?
Why?
A stage girl who has lost everything.
A stage of destiny where no one can predict what will happen.
I want to witness that.
I'll participate.
I will take care of the arrangements.
Where in Japan?
Even if you must fight that girl one day...
Hey!
I asked you a question!
Revue of Solitude
Slipping through my firmly raised hands,
the vow we made that day fell into the abyss.
I once again climb towards my stage of destiny.
Even if it must end in tragedy...
99th generation, Kagura Hikari.
It is all for the sake of Starlight!
Today is the sixth day of auditions.
The Revue of Solitude is starting.
Aim to become the top star,
sing, dance, and fight to win.
For the sake of the promise we made
It'll be fine, don't be afraid
The sword you hold is trembling
I feel so bad for you, using such a small sword.
You must have been through a lot of pain.
Even a small glimmer
But it's all over now.
I'll shoulder...
it all for you!
I bid farewell to this world steeped in sorrow
I'll protect the people who matter to me
Don't be afraid.
You're already one of us now.
And
Again
And again
I'll turn back in the face of despair
Sadness, partings, setback...
I'll protect you from everything that torments stage girls
using my reenactment!
Karen, what drives you so?
I made a promise with Hikari-chan!
Why, Hikari-chan?
What makes you fight this hard?
Karen... My destiny is waiting for me!
I just wanted to brag a little to Karen.
The stage, plays, musicals...
I wanted to show her that I knew more than others about a slightly different world.
I wanted to see her in awe.
Hikari-chan, let's go to that stage.
Huh?
We'll become stars together,
and Starlight everyone!
That's the moment I was born.
As the stage girl, Kagura Hikari.
I won't ever...
lose again!
Having lost everything,
my promise with Karen kept me bound to the stage.
I'll become a stage girl once again.
It all started unexpectedly
To do so, I have no choice but to beat all the other participants and become the top star.
Before I knew it, my fate had changed
I thought that was the only way to fulfill my promise with Karen.
I awoke the moment we made that promise
But then that stupid Karen...
The girls
Are starting anew
These auditions are winner-takes-all, and yet...
Even if I can't do it alone
she sought to protect me.
We will definitely become stars together!
I can't deprive Karen of her glimmer.
But...
If I don't beat everyone, my glimmer...
In that case, we just need to pass together!
If we shine the strongest together...
We can pass together, I'm sure.
If we shine together...
I'd never even considered that before!
But!
Even so, I could feel it!
Our dream is taking shape
Our shared...
Starlight!
Act Two
Remaking of glimmer...
When we were young, we planted a small seed together
And now it has started to bloom in full
Guided by the star
I won't lose again, I won't give up
I'm reaching out towards where you are
I won't run away, I won't cry
Heading for our promised place
I wanted see you all this time
We are once again connected by the stars
We can make a miracle happen
Position zero!
This marks the end of the sixth day of auditions.
Do you understand, Hikari-chan?
The play Starlight is a tragedy.
You can't avoid parting in the end.
Will you fight on, even if Karen-chan...
Even if you must fight her one day...
Even so, I will...
Together with Karen...
I was always gazing at you
watashi zutto anata wo miteta
It's like I left my loneliness behind
kodoku wo oitekita mitai
The moon smiles at me tonight
koyoi tsuki mo waraikakeru
Please look this way, oh fly me to the star
kocchi wo muite oh fly me to the star
Unable to tell you how I feel
kimochi tsutaeru koto dekinakute
I imagine all kinds of lives
ironna jinsei wo ukabe
I act them out to attract your attention
enjite miru no anata no ki wo
Please notice me, oh fly me to the star
hikitai kara oh fly me to the star
Quickly climbing up, I see.
The destined two, is it?
I understand.
Next Time
On the Night of the Star Festival
Girls' Musical Revue Starlight.
I see.
On the Night of the Star Festival