When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
What?
Sion, is this true?
Yes. Though, it is just a rumor.
I have more money than I know what to do
with and I do not even especially want it, but...
I love cream puffs.
by Kirika Kuzuha
Eat pumpkin flan every day.
I want the Earth.
by Kirika Kuzuha
I want to eat millefeuille.
I want Hayate Ayasaki.
Kirika Kuzuha
As a way to stave off boredom, it
will be worth seeing if it is true.
Um, Mistress Kuzuha, those are
for the Tanabata Festival...
Whosoever commands the
butlers, commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Now, today, the episode will have
to do with the Milky Way...
Enough already! It's Christmas!
Part one of the advance
final episode is starting!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Hayate in Peril! All Functions Shut Down!!
The Miss certainly is taking a long time.
Might she be playing games
in her room or something?
No, she made sure to attend last
yet, so I think that is unlikely.
Besides, this was the invitation...
Invitation
"If you do not attend, I will spread
around an embarrassing photo of you.
By Mikado Sanzenin."
The Miss?
True, the Miss may find this
an embarrassing photograph.
She fell for a trap set by Grandfather
Mikado and this was her penalty for losing.
A... "trap"?
I think it involved investing in
a game company on that occasion.
He fed her false information about the
release of the Dreamcast 100 Mega CD Master System.
Well, the loss was limited
to about 20 billion, though.
Th-That's the kind of trap a grandfather
lays for his young granddaughter?
Um, who is this butler-looking person?
Oh, that's Himegami.
Nagi's previous butler.
Wow, so this is him.
But what in the world is he doing?
Who knows? Perhaps he's looking
for UFOs or something.
Also, he seemed to like high
places for some reason.
I see...
Sorry to keep you two waiting.
Miss...
That's the coat I lent you long ago...
Well, I wasn't sure what I wanted to wear
and I just happened to see it when
I was looking through my closet.
It's true!
Now... Ahem.
I am truly happy to see you
all again here this year.
As you can see, I am still alive and kicking.
My condolences to those of you
waiting for your inheritances.
Now, to even longer life for me. And
prosperity for the Sanzenin family.
And prosperity for the Sanzenin family.
Merry Christmas!
So, all of these people are
related to the Sanzenin family...
Yes, everyone comes together
like this every year.
To pay their respect to Grandfather Mikado.
It was also after I had escaped from this
party that I met you for the first time last year.
I see, so that's how it was.
What's this, Nagi? Stayin'
in a corner like that?
This is a party, after all.
Try to look like yer sufferin' more!
Merry...
...Stigmas!
Please, Sakuya, that's a Showa Era gag.
A brilliant jab.
You've grown.
Thank you very much, master!
Ya just keep on devotin'
yerself to the art like that.
Hey, Hayate Ayasaki.
This voice...
Please be defeated by me next year for sure!
I will be counting sorrowfully on you.
Hey, Bro, where'd ya sneak in from?
You certainly don't get discouraged easily.
I'd completely forgotten
about it recently, but...
Tell this to the other
potential heirs as well!
If you want the Sanzenin fortune, first,
defeat their butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
I'm really glad we've made it to
the end of the year without mishap.
Hayate...
You're shabby-looking as ever, boy.
There's no sense of what you're made of.
Incidentally, this is a can made of steel.
When did you get over here?!
That wasn't funny one bit, Gramps.
I dumbed myself down to your level.
What's the big idea anyway?! It's
a party, so dress like yer at one!
Oh, great Mikado! Please give me your fortune! I'm begging you!
So how about it? Have you found
the meaning of life since then?
Come on, you could just give it to me!
What? Well...
Please stop!
Yes! Protecting the Miss is my life's...
I am a concerned party!
To what purpose?
Well, that is...
I owe the Miss a great deal, after all.
And I also have a debt of
150 million to begin with.
Hey, you old geezer!
Don't appear for the first time
after so long and criticize Hayate!
Oh, my god!
Miss...
Why does this always happen?!
Go train with Senjinmaru
somewhere or something!
Let's go, Hayate.
Oh... What? Um, but...
Oh, Grandfather.
Maria, my granddaughter is being mean to me!
Yes, yes.
Oh, that's right.
Hold on for a second.
Maria!
Here.
To Maria
Happy Birthday Maria
I'll continue to count on you.
Nagi
I'm going out for a bit.
You make sure you babysit that guy.
Thank you, Nagi.
She could've just said it to your face.
That darn shy granddaughter.
Maria, what's your perspective on this?
Are you referring to Hayate?
He's done very well for us.
Nagi adores him, too.
But...
Nagi, your true feelings
have yet to reach Hayate...
Hayate, don't you pay any attention
to what that bastard says.
Loser Park
That old geezer lives for making
other people's lives difficult.
Is that so?
But anyway, I guess it hasn't
snowed yet this year.
It's already been a year
since then, hasn't it?
Yes, the days go by so fast.
Won't you go with me?
What?
I want you!
I-It's about time we took
things to the next level.
I even wore the coat that
holds our memories, after all.
This is where I should
casually take the initiative!
A-Aren't the stars pretty, Hayate?
Yes, they certainly are.
It's quite the romantic Christmas Eve.
I'm sure that right about
now, all across the city,
l-lovers are looking up at the
night sky, deep in conversation.
E-Especially since the stars
are sparkling so brightly.
Miss, you have an interest
in celestial bodies?
Then I shall tell you about
the winter constellations.
Then, first, please look
towards the northern sky.
Let us look for the North Star, a fundamental in stargazing.
Hayate must be feeling self-conscious.
Darn shy bastard!
The popular method of looking for the North Star is to find the Big Dipper,
but that is actually only for the spring and summer.
It's winter right now, so we'll use the Cassiopeia constellation.
Oh, incidentally, as to why I'm
familiar with explaining such things,
I worked on the 60th floor
of the Nikko building...
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Things were just getting good!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Could it be a construction
worker or something?
I'm Cyborg Butler!
I am a butler who was reborn
in order to fight you!
Hayate, what is it that
I'm looking at right now?
Explain it to me so I can understand.
What? Well...
Stop calling me "old mister"! I
might not look it, but I'm still 20!
Wait, I haven't even said anything yet!
This odd development of a battle...
I had no idea it was still continuing.
Drill Knee!
Hayate...
What are you doing?!
Broken Bullet!
You leave me no choice.
I will be your opponent!
H-Hey, Hayate!
It's dangerous, so please stay back.
Here we go, mystery-person!
Look over here.
Hayate?!
M-My body...
Merry Christmas, Hayate Ayasaki.
Ms. Superintendent?!
So this was your doing, as I suspected!
Um, I don't know what you're up to here,
but could you at least leave
us alone during Christmas?
Gotcha!
Let go, you pipsqueak!
You settle down, you pipsqueaky pipsqueak!
White Serpent Magic, Seventh
Spell. Butler Killer!
Hayate! Hayate!
Are you all right, Hayate?!
Yes, Miss...
Do it.
Are you really all right?
Yes, I'm perfectly fine.
Here goes!
Drill Knee!
For a butler, a technique
he's already seen is...
Broken Bullet!
H-Hayate...
Miss...
Hell and Heaven!
Hayate!
Hayate...
Sion!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Yeah!
Hayate Ayasaki, this photograph will...
Sweet crêpes. Tasty crêpes.
It's Mister Crêpe's Japan's
tastiest mobile crêpe vendor!
Ooh!
Oh, Mistress Kuzuha!
Hayate!
Finish him off, just to be safe!
Final Hammer approved!
Drive!
Hayate, pull yourself together! Hey!
Miss, please do not mind me. Just run.
Don't be ridiculous! Running and
leaving you behind would be...
Goldion Giant Mallet!
D-Don't you dare touch Hayate!
Miss...
Turn to light!
Who the hell are you?!
Bastard! Are you with them?!
Well, whatever. This is a good opportunity.
I'll show you the greatest and
final weapon that I've got left!
And that's...
Courage!
You are...
Hayate!
Himegami, you...
Himegami? Who might that be?
I am the mysterious hero,
Princess God.
(hime = princess, gami/kami = god)
That's a literal translation...
Great explosion!
(Dai bakuhatsu!)
Tsumagoi Village.
(Tsumagoi-mura)
Huh? Where am I?
Hello, there, Hayate. Long time no see!
Hey!
Mother
Father
Mom! Dad!
I thought you foisted off your debt
on me a year ago and went into hiding.
What about you? What's with that outfit?
What?
I-I'm currently working as Miss Nagi's
butler at the Sanzenin household.
So? What in the world do you want?
How rude of you after all this time.
But I mean, a butler?
Hayate, there's no way you're qualified
for such a respectable job.
What?
After all, you're our son!
Th-That can't be...
Y-You okay, Hayate?
So you have finally come to.
A d-dream...
Are you really all right?
Yes, pretty much...
I am so sorry.
My duty is to protect the Miss, and yet...
I-It's fine. Everyone has their bad days.
Besides, you know...
Recovering from defeat is a standard
plot device in hero manga.
R-Right...
I swear! Where have you been and what
have you been doing all this time?!
Showing up shamelessly after all this time!
Himegami!
Besides, you were fired from the
Sanzenin household a long time ago!
So this is Himegami...
And what is with that mask?!
Is it that thing?
But I wonder what that mask is about...
That mysterious white thing that's
been crucified in the basement?!
Then get a spear! Get a spear to go with it!
Hey, wake up!
My head hurts. Why is that?
It's because I hit you.
Want me to hit you again?
What?!
Himegami! You bastard! How dare
you lay a hand on the Miss!
You do it to me, I do it back to
you. I live by that principle.
Why you!
And I am not this Himegami person.
Princess God.
A mysterious hero just passing by.
Enough already, Himegami!
I am not Himegami.
I've long told you that there's to
be no hitting, haven't I, Himegami?
As I said, I am Princess...
No, no. Akane Himegami.
Akane Himegami
Uh, um, why was he fired?
Because he's an idiot!
I see...
I fired him because he was
an unbelievable idiot.
Humph! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Do you think you look cool or
something with that mask on?
I know what the Miss said,
but he's not the previous butler for nothing.
I already have Hayate,
so there's no point in you coming back now!
There's a kind of polished aura about him.
Nagi and Himegami have always
been like that, so...
Oh, i-is that right?
W-Well, how about some tea to start with?
Miss. Himegami.
Please drink this for now
and compose yourselves.
S-Sure, thanks.
Hot!
H-Hayate, what's with this tea?
It's hot enough to burn my tongue.
What? That's not right.
Hayate...
H-Hey, Ayasaki, what are you doing?!
At that rate, you are a failure as a butler!
I am so very sorry!
Um, p-please pardon me!
Wh-What the? That's strange. I was
sure I did everything right...
However, that was not the
last of Hayate's mistakes.
Wh-What the?
Ayasaki!
Furuya Station Police Box
It seems he got lost while running errands.
What in the...
A-ya-sa-ki...
Ayasaki, what the hell are you doing?!
P-Pardon me!
Christmas Cakes
How would you like a Christmas cake?!
I-Is it just my imagination?
I have a feeling that something
bad's happening to Hayate...
And to me, too!
Well, leaving that aside, once
again back at the estate...
Hayate, what in the world
has gotten into you?
This isn't like you at all.
Y-Yes...
Why don't you take a little time off?
Oh, no, please!
I agree, that may be a good idea.
I-I am fine!
I can't be the only one to take time
off during the busy year-end period!
Nah, don't worry. I've also got
Maria, after all. Rest easy.
I understand.
What could have happened to Hayate?
He's been unable to accomplish
any of his duties as a butler.
Say, Maria, could it be
that I'm a poor mistress?
What?
I want to be encouraging to Hayate,
but the words just don't seem
to come out quite right.
Even if he makes some mistakes or loses
in fights, Hayate is still Hayate.
But a part of me had always thought
of him as an invincible hero, so...
Miss...
What in the world has happened to me?
You're that way because your butler
abilities were sucked out of you.
By that woman.
What?!
Himegami...
A banana?
I'm not giving it to you.
Wh-What's with this person?
Never mind that. Um, about
what you just said...
Right now, you have lost
your powers as a butler.
Because of the curse laid down by that woman,
the superintendent of Hakuou Academy.
How would you know such a thing?
End of the Century Legend
Magical Destroy
Nagi Sanzenin
This is from the school festival...
Don't tell me...
Have you been watching over
the Miss all this time?
Please answer me!
Nagi is heavy of heart.
Because she had faith in you and you lost.
And now, you are no longer
capable of protecting Nagi.
That is not...!
See? There you go.
Let me give you some friendly advice.
Leave this place.
There's no stamp on it or anything.
Someone hand-delivered this.
Hayate? Um, if you'd like, how
about some tea with everyone?
This is...!
Letter of Resignation
This is how it should be.
To protect the Miss, this is the
only course of action for me.
Hayate disappears alone. What
could he mean by those words?
Next time, at long last, they will
fight against the final episode.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
Wataru & Saki's
Wataru and...
Saki's...
And Nagi's!
Butler Report!
Butler Report
I'm back! Nagi Sanzenin here.
Wataru Tachibana!
I'm Saki Kijima.
What's up, Nagi? This corner is usually
about advertising for Rental Video Tachibana.
There were a lot of complaints
about the flirting between you two,
so I'm here to check up on you!
Goodness, flirting?! That's an
inappropriate way of putting it, miss!
That's right! Don't be stupid!
So, who do you like more, Isumi or Saki?
Oh, time's up.
There'll be a special edition next time!
Preview
If I become your butler, you'll give up
on the Sanzenin family fortune, right?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
But why would you want that,
after stealing my butler power?
So that you can obtain even
greater butler power...
And be reborn as the perfect butler,
who is totally loyal to me!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
The conclusion to this battle,
"Hurray for the Butler-in-Debt,
Friend to Good Children!"
Hurray for the Butler-in-Debt,
Friend to Good Children!
Hayate... as long as I have you...!
Miss!
Did you know?
In America, they call episodes with endings
designed to keep you in suspense "cliffhangers!"