When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Whew, I'm super stuffed!
No matter how often I taste it,
Maria's cookin's still the best!
Even so, you ate way too much.
I'll have ya know, comedy's about stamina.
Yer body's yer capital.
If ya don't eat well,
you'll never get a laugh!
I don't ever plan to try.
Now, if you're done eating, get out of here!
Ya don't need to tell me. I'm leavin'.
Unlike you, I do the whole
"serious student" thing.
Makita! Kunieda!
All right, I'm off to school!
School, school! What an annoying girl!
Miss, you'll also need to
get ready soon, or you'll be late.
Don't be ridiculous! Isumi's still asleep!
How could I neglect my guest
and go to school?!
Oh, my, so that's
the tack she's taking today.
It must be rough having so many
reasons why you cannot go to school.
Why do you insist on trying
to make me go to school?!
If I head off to school,
I don't get to be with you...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his
mistress in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights
and puts his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
Come to think of it,
we had forgotten for some time
that Nagi has a crush on Hayate.
This is terrible!
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Just let it take you
Karada nami ni makasereba
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
Going to Hell in Cat-Ear Mode
I swear! Why is it that Hayate
can't just... well...
...see how a girl feels about wanting
to be together as much as possible?
I swear, he's so dense!
Cleaning! Cleaning! Oh, what fun!
You must like to clean, Hayate.
What? Oh, yes.
Then, which do you prefer?
Someone older or someone younger?
Huh?
Um, so, in other words, are you
referring to my taste in women?
Yes.
Since Nagi and Hayate's relationship
is based on a misunderstanding,
I should try to get a clear read
on exactly how Hayate feels.
Could this be...
...that in terms of the romantic
plotline of this anime,
the flag has been set for the Maria ending?
I have to say, I like
older women, hands down!
Younger girls are adorable,
but they don't interest me romantically!
Oh, is that so?
She seems to be responding
with some disappointment to that...
What's going on?
Hey, Hayate!
Come here for a second!
Certainly! I will be right there!
Please excuse me.
We can discuss this again later.
Attendance Chart
I guess Nagi's absent again today.
That reminds me, that suspicious
person in black the other day...
I hear he's the Sanzenin
family's new butler.
I only caught a glimpse of him,
but he was a young boy, right?
Yup, yup. I thought he looked pretty manly.
Did he?
I feel like that wasn't quite the case...
Then here, let's go get another look at him!
Yes.
Hey, Hayate, would you mind
trying this outfit on?
Um, I hate to point out the obvious,
but that's a girl's outfit, right?
Don't worry, it's in your size.
No, that's not what I mean.
Why do I have to wear a girl's outfit?
Why...? Because...
I think it'd look good on you.
You're doing this on a whim?!
Well, yes, it's on a whim,
but if I don't come up
with things for you to do,
we can't spend time together!
Darn it!
Quit complaining and put this on!
Please stop! Nooo!
Honestly!
Making me wear a sailor
uniform... You're awful!
No, no, it looks very good on you!
That doesn't make me happy at all!
I know! Let me get my camera!
Please don't!
You mustn't take photos of me like this!
Where's the harm in it?
It's in commemoration.
What's there to commemorate?!
Besides, if the head
butler sees me like this,
I'll be fired!
Huh? What do you mean?
Allow me to explain!
It was actually only a couple days ago
that Hayate received instruction
from Klaus, the head butler,
on how a butler was expected to behave.
Butlers must be manly!!
Butlers must be manly.
Understood?
As a butler of the Sanzenin family,
you must be a gentleman and behave
in a manly manner at all times.
This being an era of equality
between men and women,
manliness is sought after all the more.
If you are incapable of such behavior,
I will expect your immediate resignation!
I see, I had no idea Klaus had said that...
That's why I can't afford
to be seen like this by Mr. Klaus!
And Mr. Klaus isn't the only one!
Maria, too...
If she saw me like this,
I'd die of embarrassment.
Oh, my, what are we to do?
It would be a bit problematic
if you were to die.
M-Maria!
Here I was, wondering
what you two were up to
and to find you doing this...
Th-This isn't what it looks like!
The Miss forced me to do this!
Well, Hayate insisted
that he wanted to try it on, so...
I said no such thing!
You needn't worry.
I don't believe that you have
a taste for cross dressing.
Thank goodness!
I was so worried
that you got the wrong idea.
But really, what a child you are!
But I thought it would look good on Hayate.
Even so, a sailor uniform?
That's right! I'm a man!
Huh?
This frilly one is sure
to look good on Hayate!
Maria!
Hey, Maria, in that case,
how about this skirt?
What? But won't a pink one be cuter?
No, I'd say red.
Oh, my! This blue one
is a tempting choice, too!
This is bad! They're both
totally in high school girl mode!
My purity is in jeopardy!
M-Maria, what do you think of this?!
Carefully...
Oh, my, it's fantastic!
Where are you going?
You can't walk around the residence
dressed in a sailor uniform.
Well, but you know,
I need to work and stuff...
Ah, quite commendable.
Uh...
But we'll just call this work, too.
Why don't you try this on, too?
You're terrible... Doing this to me...
Th-This is...
This is not even funny.
If Mr. Klaus sees me,
I really will end up getting fired!
Oh, don't worry about that.
Or rather, don't look at me like that.
That is right. It is embarrassing.
I'm the one feeling embarrassed here!
But well, you know,
it really looks good on you!
You think so, too, don't you, Tama?
T-Tama, you can't!
You may be an animal, but that's...
...not something you can do in an anime!
Come on, let's do it!
Seriously, let's do it!
Whoa! You stupid idiot!
You weigh over 300 kilos! You'll kill me!
Allow me to explain to you kids
at home watching this for the first time.
To tell the truth, this tiger called Tama
is capable of human speech.
Can't show you!
Please don't ask me why he can do this!
Tell me, Maria,
is Tama assaulting Hayate because
he mistook Hayate for a cute female?
Or is he assaulting Hayate
for being a cute boy? Which is it?
No idea.
Depending on which it is,
I'm thinking of changing the course
of Tama's future education...
But well, it looks like Hayate may end up
dying even as you're saying that.
Tama, stop it!
Can't show you!
Come on, where's the harm?! Just a little!
Honestly! That's enough already!
You damn stupid tiger!
Ooh! He dropped Tama with one blow!
He may look like a girl, but inside,
I guess he's still Herculean.
A-At any rate, I need
to get changed as soon as possible.
If Mr. Klaus sees me like this...
Really, such a beautiful day.
On days like this,
there is no better pastime
than to go around giving new
meanings to the garden flowers.
What is that supposed to mean?
Or rather, never mind that! I have to run!
Who might you be?
A degenerate trespassing
upon the Sanzenin estate...
He could hardly say, "It's Hayate."
When all else fails...!
Fool.
You think you can escape from me
on the grounds of this estate?!
Ooh! That's Klaus for you!
He is keeping up with Hayate's speed.
Th-This is bad. He's going to
catch up to me at this rate.
Since it's come to this, I have no choice
but to hide my face with
the ribbon and intercept him!
Shoot! I can't see anything!
But in a moment of peril,
a person's latent powers awaken!
Rather than rely on my eyes,
I have to have faith in my mind's eye!
Klaus Kick!
That just wasn't going to work.
Die, you miscreant.
What?
WHAT?!
Oh, no!
What's an old guy doing
getting all excited?!
I'm sorry, Mr. Klaus. I'm sorry!
Here, take this chance to change into these.
Thank you very much!
No, I am the one who should apologize
for getting carried away.
No, no, you are kind, Maria!
I am so grateful to you, Maria!
Thank you very much, Maria!
If you weren't here, Maria...
What's with him?
Going on and on about Maria...
Oh, how should I thank you, Maria?
Who knows what might have happened?!
Hayate, hurry up and get changed!
Thank you very much!
Or I'll spread the photos I took earlier!
What?! That is too cruel!
I was kidding! Just kidding!
I guess Nagi not only hired a new butler,
but a new maid, too.
That's the Sanzenin family for you.
But she's an awfully cute looking maid.
They seem busy, though, so shall we leave?
Well, lunch break will be over soon anyway.
I don't think we really need
to attend out afternoon classes.
How the three student council girls...
...were able to slip through
the tight security of the Sanzenin estate
and get onto the grounds is a mystery.
But who in the world was that sweet lady?
If I ever see her again, I would like
to convey my feelings to her.
Hayate's misfortune was far from over.
Chubby perv! (Mucchiri sukebe)
All I did was touch you.
(Betsuni sawatta dake janai)
Hot, hot, hot...
Come to think of it,
I wonder what Ayasaki's doing...
Owowow...
Honestly!
First, I got shoved over by Tama.
Then I got kicked by Mr. Klaus.
I've got injuries everywhere...
My! You seem to have
suffered quite an ordeal.
What?
Isumi! What in the world are you doing here?
The thing is, when I woke up,
I found I had become lost...
I see...
And the experience utterly wore me out.
That must have been quite an ordeal.
Honestly! Your horrible sense
of direction is hardcore.
Do you realize how many times
you've been over here?
No matter how many times, I get lost.
The Sanzenin estate is a horrific labyrinth.
Don't go making it sound all scary.
Now, now. It's late already.
Why don't you stay the night again?
I will be sure to let your family know.
I am sorry to trouble you.
Then please have a good night.
Good night.
Don't tell me Isumi saw me
dressed like a girl...
Don't think about it, don't think about it.
Just get to bed and end the day.
You're not going to sleep yet?
No.
Normally, I have to lie next to Nagi
since she's too frightened
to fall asleep alone,
but with Isumi staying
the night again today...
So you are relieved of your duty.
Yes.
Um, Maria, I had no idea
you played billiards.
Yes, well... If you'd like,
would you care to join me?
And this might be a good time
to have a quiet talk with him.
Considering this morning's question,
could this really mean...
...that the Maria ending has been
flagged in the romantic storyline?
And the reason why I suffered all
that horrendous bad luck today
was to lead up to this
moment of happiness at night?
Hayate was to regret feeling so
giddy in this way shortly later.
Then shall we begin?
Yes.
But Isumi and the Miss
certainly are good friends.
Isumi is special to Nagi.
They met 8 years ago at a party.
What the heck are these scribbles?
They're not scribbles!
They're manga that Nagi worked hard to draw!
Manga, ya say?
So, is this Rikishiman-looking
guy the villain?
That's my mascot character! Hernia!
What the heck's this? Ancient Incan script?
That's the Lethal Old Man Slash!
Well, whatever it is,
quit drawin' this stupid stuff
and come play with us a little outside.
I'll never draw another manga again!
H-Hey, what are you doing,
reading that without my permission?!
Give it back! Haven't you gotten
enough laughs out of it already?!
What happens next?
Huh?
What happens next in that manga?
Because it was really interesting.
That was how they met.
Less than a minute after
they met, the Miss...
Please marry me!
Pardon?
This is how the two became fast friends.
I see.
But Isumi is amazing. To think
she could understand that manga...
I know, right?
Right about now, Nagi
is probably going on and on
about a story that only
those two can understand.
Right then, the ultimate weapon
that came out of Ayers Rock,
the Infinite Ant Production
Device, begins operating!
The infinitely outpouring ants
gather the world's sugar supply
and takes it to the great defeated
warrior general underground!
Thus, the heroes engage
in a three-way battle across the world,
fighting for the sugar!
But well, that is a thought
that makes me worry for the future...
By the way, Hayate, where did
you learn to play billiards?
Oh, I used to work part time
at a billiard bar back in middle school.
Is it all right for a minor
to work at a billiard bar?
But I will set that question aside...
I know! If you'd like, we could make a bet.
That sounds like a good idea.
What? I meant that as a joke...
Now, don't say that.
All right, then what shall we bet?
For example, how about something like
the loser does one thing,
whatever the winner wants?
What? A-Are you sure?
This anime still technically
belongs to a genre
that caters to adolescent boys, you know.
Um, what are you intending
to make me do, Hayate?
Nothing... really that bad...
Besides, Hayate,
don't tell me you actually think
that you even have a 0.1
chance of winning against me?
Then, shall we begin?
I-Incidentally, if I lose,
what are you going to make me do?
What? Well, let me think...
Um...
Don't you think that your 155,823,975
yen debt is an awkward amount?
Huh?
It gets kind of long to say,
"155,823,975 yen."
Don't you think 200 million yen
is a lot easier to say?
Today was a terrible day,
but considering this turn of events,
is Maria the last boss?
This is bad! I can't lose this fight!
However, faced with
an overwhelming difference in skill,
Hayate is helpless!
Uh, um, this is a stupid question,
but if I should end up losing here,
how am I to repay my debt
after it becomes 200 million?
You have a point.
It would be impossible,
no matter how you look at it.
Right?
You're just joking about making my
debt 200 million yen if I lose, right?
Do I look like someone who cracks jokes?
No, you don't.
But there is a possible way
for you to repay it.
What?
No, nothing.
Please, go ahead. It's your turn.
Oh, r-right.
This is bad! I have to
turn the tables somehow!
Incidentally, with regards to the
quick fix way to repay your debt...
How about a bold move,
like you marrying Nagi?
What?!
M-Me?! Marry the Miss?!
Oh, you missed.
N-No way, that shouldn't count...
There are no take-backs in a serious match.
Now, if I make this shot,
your debt will become 200 million yen
and you will have to seduce Nagi in earnest.
Um, I could never marry the Miss.
Are you saying you don't like her?
No, that is not it.
If I were to marry the Miss and my debt
were forgiven because of that,
it would be as if I married
the Miss for her money.
I mean, this is hypothetically
speaking! Purely hypothetical!
There is no way the Miss would
ever fall for someone like me
and even if such an unlikely
thing should happen,
as a human being, I would
never lay a hand on a child!
I mean it!
To me, the Miss is
the person who saved my life
and she is very dear to me,
so I could never do
something like that to her.
Hayate is a truly good kid.
And yet, here I've been trying
to pry into his feelings.
Perhaps this is a matter that should
just be left to the two of them.
Um, is something the matter?
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Then, here I go.
Oh, dear...
All right! I still have a chance to win!
I-I did it!
Congratulations! You win, Hayate!
Th-Then, I can really ask you
to do anything?!
Yes, of course...
All right! Something borderline
to cater to the adolescent boys!
However...
I think you should do something
about the demon at your back first.
Miss...
What's with the perverted
look on your face?!
N-No, this was nothing really...
You listen to me, Hayate!
If you ever lay a hand on Maria,
I'll never forgive you!
Honestly! He's got me!
We're going, Isumi!
Good night.
The last boss that capped
off the unfortunate day...
...turned out to be the Miss.
So, Hayate, what was it
that you actually wanted me to do?
I-I was hoping to be forgiven
for the expensive coat that I ruined.
My! Is that all?
Yes...
As we all know,
the butler-in-debt is a coward.
Next time, he will fight you-know-who
from the science room!
Moshi boku no yume ga kimi no kokoro
If my dreams have taken your heart
Kizutsuke-tetara
And brought it pain
Sono omoi wa itsuka
Someday, that anguish
Boku ga morau yo
I will take from you
Taisetsu na mono ni furue-nagara
While trembling over something precious
Kakezuri-mawatte
And madly dashing about
Seou itami ni hibi wa
The hurt I bore made the days
Muimi ni sugita
Go by emptily
Oikaketa mama de oikosare-tsuzuke
Just chasing and continually being overtaken
Tohou ni kureru kaze
A wind who's lost its bearing
Kimi no doko ni furetara
What part of you should I touch
Ii ka o sagashita
I sought it out
Mamoritai yo kimi dake wa tsuyoku
You alone, I want to protect so much
Yokubou no wadachi kara touzakatte
Getting away from the rut of desire
Itsuka subete te ni ireru sore ga
Someday, it will all be ours and that
Kimi to boku no Proof
Is our proof, yours and mine
Namida mo zenbu azukeru yo
Even all my tears, I entrust to you
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Sign: Butler Report
This episode of "Hayate the Combat Butler"
was yet another masterpiece.
Hm, you think so?
In recording, it wasn't colored
yet, so it's hard to say.
It'll be fine! By the time it's
actually broadcast, it will be!
I hope so.
More importantly, this is
a great song, don't you think?
It conveys my desire to...
You mentioned that in a previous episode.
We got it already, so well,
try this on or something.
What?! What is with this outfit?!
I like you as your manly self,
but I find this hard to give up, too!
I can never be a bridegroom now...
I'll have you, so don't you worry!
Bye-bye!
Preview
Oh? That's strange...
What is the matter, Miss?
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
It seems I forgot my notebook at school.
Wh-What?!
I will go get it for you right away!
Well, it's not that important...
All right, I'm off!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Elohim, Essaim.
Mr. Cow, Mr. Cow! What is it, Mr. Frog?"
What? Hayate from the Sanzenins is
at that old school building?
At the hour of three-eyes,
Elohim Essaim.
Mr. Cow, Mr. Cow! What is it, Mr. Frog?
let's meet again in the world of three-eyes!