When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
What? Shion, is that true?
Yes. Although, it is only a rumor.
I have more money than I want, so it's not as if I wanted more...
...but it's worth a shot as a time killer.
Um, Kuzuha-sama. Those wish tabs are for Tanabata Festival.
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
Today's episode will be based on the Milky Way.
No, it's Christmas!
Sneak peek of the final episode, part 1, here we go!
Milady is late, isn't she?
Could she be playing a game in her room?
No, she did participate last year, too, so I don't think she would be.
Besides...
The invitation says this.
If you do not come, I'll distribute your embarrassing picture.
By Sanzenin Mikado.
Milady?
It might be an embarrassing picture from Milady's perspective.
She had to suffer a penalty game since she fell into his trap.
A trap?
I think this particular incident was related to the investment in a game company.
She got caught with the fake information saying Dream**** 100MB Mk3 would be released.
We managed to stop with losing only 20 trillion yen.
Th-That's considered a trap set by a grandfather against his granddaughter?
Um, who is this butler-like person?
Oh, that would be Himegami-kun.
Nagi's former butler.
Oh, so it's this person?
What is he doing there?
I don't know. Maybe he's searching for a UFO.
Also, he tended to like high places.
I see...
Sorry for making both of you wait.
Milady...
That's the coat I lent you before.
Well, I was wondering what I should wear.
It just happened to catch my eye
when I was going through my closet.
Honestly!
A-hem.
I'm happy to see you all again.
As you see, I'm still up on my two feet.
My condolences to those who are looking forward to inheriting the estate.
Let there be long life to me.
And let there be prosperity to the Sanzenin.
Merry Christmas!
So everybody here is a relative of the Sanzenin family.
Yes. This is an annual gathering done as a way of seeing Grandfather.
It was after I snuck out of this party that I met you.
I see.
What are you doing in a corner of the room, Nagi?
It's a party for crying out loud.
Why aren't you looking like you're suffocating?
Merry-
Choking.
Sakuya-san, that's like a fossilized joke.
Perfect.
You've improved a lot.
Thank you very much, Master.
Keep up the good work.
Hey, Ayasaki Hayate.
This voice is...
Next year, please be defeated by me.
Thank you very much.
Aniki! Where did you sneak in from?
You never learn, do you?
I had completely forgotten about it recently, but...
Pass this on to the other candidates, as well.
Anyone who wants the Sanzenin estate will have to defeat her butler, Ayasaki Hayate, first!
I'm really glad we're facing the end of the year without anything happening.
Hayate.
You have a poor man's face as usual, don't you?
I don't sense any magnanimity from you.
And, this can is made of steel.
When did you...
That wasn't funny in any way, Gramps.
I matched it to your level.
Well, what's your deal? If it's a party,
then why don't you dress like it's one?
Mikado-sama! Please, give me the estate. I beg you.
So, have you found meaning in your life?
Why can't you give it to me?
Ah, well...
Wow, please stop.
Yes. It is my mission in life to protect Milady.
I've done nothing.
What for?
Well, I have multiple debts to Milady.
First of all, I have a debt of ¥150,000,000.
Hey, old fart! Don't criticize Hayate right after you meet.
Milady.
You should go off and train with Sen****maru for a while.
Let's go, Hayate!
Um...
My, my, Grandfather...
Maria. My granddaughter picks on me.
There, there.
Oh, that's right.
Hold on here for a second.
Maria!
Here.
I'm going out for a bit.
Make sure you keep an eye on him.
Thank you, Nagi.
She should say it personally.
That shy granddaughter.
What do you think, Maria?
About Hayate-kun?
He's working out very well.
Nagi likes him, too.
But...
Nagi, Hayate-kun can't accept your feelings yet.
Hayate, don't let what he said bother you.
It's his entertainment in life to harass others.
I see.
On another note, it's not snowing this winter.
It's been a whole year since that day, right?
Yup. Time flies.
Go out with me.
I want you!
It's about time we took the next step, right?
I went all the way and wore this coat.
I'll casually make the motion.
The stars are really beautiful, Hayate!
Yes, they really are.
It's a very romantic Christmas Eve.
I bet right now, all the couples are out there gazing up at the evening sky and talking.
After all, the stars are twinkling so much.
You have interest in astronomy, Milady?
Then let me talk about the constellations you see in the winter sky.
First, take a look at the northern sky.
You can see the North Star, one of the very basics of astronomy.
Hayate must be embarrassed.
Using the big dipper is famous for finding the North Star,
What a shy guy!
but that's actually the standard during spring and summer.
In winter, you use Cassiopeia.
Oh, by the way, I'm used to giving this explanation because I used to work at Nikkou on its 60th-
Wh-What is this noise?
Way to ruin the mood!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Maybe it's construction?
I'm a cyborg butler!
A butler newly born to fight against you!
Hayate. Tell me what I'm seeing right now.
Explain to me so that I understand.
Well...
Don't call me Oji-san.
I'm only twenty years old!
I didn't say anything yet!
These strange battle turnarounds... I didn't think they were still going.
Drill Knee!
Hayate.
What do you think you're doing?
Broken Heavy Knuckle!
Fine. I will play with you.
Hey, Hayate.
It'll be dangerous, so please stay back.
Ready, mysterious person?
Look over here.
Hayate?!
My body...
Merry Christmas, Ayasaki Hayate.
Superintendent.
So you were behind this.
Um, I don't know what you want,
but can you at least leave us alone during Christmas?
Let go of me, midget!
You stay still, too, midget-midget.
White Snake Forbidden Spell 7.
Butler Killing!
Hayate! Hayate!
Are you all right, Hayate?
Yes, Milady.
Get him.
Are you really all right?
Yes. Nothing's wrong with me.
Here I go!
Drill Knee!
A move I've seen once is-
Broken Heavy Knuckle!
H-Hayate...
Milady...
Hell and Heaven!
Hayate!
Hayate...
Shion!
Yes.
Yay.
Yay!
Ayasaki Hayate. If you don't want this picture-
Sweet crepe. Yummy crepe.
It's Crepe Oji-san's, Japan's number one moving house of crepes.
Kuzuha-sama!
Hayate!
Finish him off just in case.
Usage of Final Hammer approved!
Drive!
Hayate! Get a hold of yourself!
Milady. Please don't worry about me and get out of here.
Don't be foolish.
I can't possibly get out of here, leaving you behind.
Gordian Giant Hammer!
Keep your hands off of Hayate!
Milady.
Turn into light!
Who are you?
Are you with them?
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
I'll take the chance to show you my last weapon.
And that is-
Courage!
You're...
Hayate!
Himegami. You...
Himegami? Who would that be?
I'm an unknown hero.
Princess God.
Note: Hime = Princess; Gami = God
That is  your name.
Dai! Baku! Hatsu!
Dai! Baku! Hatsu! = Big Explosion!
Tsumaigoimura
Tsumaigoimura = Tsumagoi Village
What? Where am I?
Hey, Hayate-kun, it's been a while.
Hey.
Dad? Mom?
You two went missing a year ago after leaving all the debts you made to me.
Well, what happened to you? Your outfit?
Me? I'm a butler for Lady Sanzenin Nagi right now.
So, what business do you have?
It's very rude of you two to come back now.
Well, "butler"?
Hayate-kun, you can't possibly manage such a position.
After all, you are our son.
Wh-What?
A-Are you all right, Hayate?
You're finally awake.
S-So it was a dream.
Are you really all right?
Yes.
I'm sorry, after all I'm the one who protects you.
It's all right. Everyone has bad days.
Besides, climbing back up after a loss is a standard plot in any hero manga.
Y-Yes...
Where have you been all this time?
What do you think you're doing, coming back now?
Besides, Himegami! You were fired from the Sanzenin family long ago!
And what is that mask?
So he's Himegami-san.
Is it from that?
And what is the meaning behind the mask?
That strange white crucified thing?
Then hold a spear, too!
Hey, wake up!
My head hurts.
Why?
Because I just hit you.
Do you want another one?
Himegami! What do you think you're doing to Milady?!
An eye for an eye.
That's my beauty.
You...
Besides, I'm not Himegami.
I'm Princess God.
An unknown hero just passing by.
Quit it already, Himegami!
I am not Himegami.
I have said you cannot punch her many times, haven't I, Himegami-kun?
Like I've been saying, I'm Princess-
No, no, you are Himegami Akane.
Um, why was Himegami-san fired from this mansion?
Because he's a moron.
I fired him because he's an absolute moron.
Hmm! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
You think that mask is cool?
Despite what Milady says, he's definitely a butler.
I already have Hayate, so it's too late to come back now.
He has the air of a perfect example.
Nagi and Himegami-kun were always like that.
Oh, I see.
Well, let's have some tea for now.
Milady and Himegami-san,
both of you please drink this and relax.
Yeah, thank you.
It's hot!
Hayate, what's wrong with this tea?
It's so hot that it burns my tongue.
What? It can't be.
Hayate?
Hey, Ayasaki! What do you think you're doing?!
You fail as a butler if you're like that!
I'm sorry. Pardon my rudeness.
Hey, that's odd, something's wrong.
I'm sure I did it properly.
This wasn't the last of Hayate's mistakes.
Eh?
Ayasaki!
He got lost on the way back from shopping.
Eh?
Ayasaki...
Ayasaki! What do you think you're doing?!
I'm sorry!
Would you like a Christmas cake?
What is this? I get the feeling that something bad is happening to Hayate-kun.
To me, too?!
Let's set this aside and pan back to the mansion.
Hayate, what's gotten into you?
It's completely unlike you.
Yes...
How about you take a little time off?
No, I can't.
Yes, it might be a good idea.
I'm fine. I can't possibly take time off at the end of the year when it's busy.
Don't worry. We have Maria, so go ahead and have a good rest.
As you say.
I wonder what happened to Hayate-kun.
He's become incapable of doing any task a butler does.
Hey, Maria. Do you think I'm incapable as a master?
I want to cheer up Hayate, but the right words won't come out.
Even if he makes some mistakes or loses in a fight or two, Hayate is still Hayate.
But I always had this image of Hayate being an invincible hero somewhere in my mind.
Milady...
What is going on with me?
It's because your powers as a butler
have been sucked away by that woman.
Himegami-san.
Banana?
I'm not sharing with you.
I don't understand him.
Forget the banana. What was it that you mentioned?
Right now, you've lost your powers as a butler...
...because of a curse by the superintendent of the Hakuou Academy.
Why do you know that?
This is back from the School Festival.
You were watching over Milady all this time?
Answer me!
Nagi is sad.
Because you, who she trusted so much, lost.
And there is no chance of you being capable of protecting Nagi.
What-
See? Just as I said.
Take my advice.
Leave this place.
No stamp or anything.
Someone brought it here directly?
Hayate-kun?
Would you like to join us for a tea?
This is...
This was for the best.
This is the only thing I can do to protect Milady.
Hayate disappears into the dark alone.
What's the truth behind his words?
Next week, we'll fight against the final episode.
Wataru and,
Saki and,
Nagi's...
Butler Network!
I am back. I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Tachibana Wataru.
I'm Kijima Saki.
Hey Nagi. I thought this section was supposed to be
Rental Video Tachibana's advertisement until this week.
I got feedback saying watching you two flirt with each other is annoying, so I'm here to inspect.
"Flirt"? That's such a filthy word, Lady.
That's right. Don't be foolish.
In the end, do you like Isumi or Saki-san more?
Hey, it's time.
Next week will be a special.
If I become your butler, you will give up on the Sanzenin estate?
But why are you saying that after taking my powers as a butler away?
You will be gaining more butler powers than before.
And you will be reborn as a perfect butler that swears his body and soul to me.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Preview of the final episode, part two.
Friends of the Well-Behaved. Praise the Debt-Ridden Butler!
Hayate! As long as you're with me...
Milady!
Did you know?
In American shows, ending a show at a place that makes you eager to see the next episode is a "cliffhanger".