I am leaving now.
Morning!
Oh, good morning, Futaba—
Youko-san, good morning.
I Am Graduating from Bread Crusts
Youko-san, did you hear?
It's such a nice day, but it's
supposed to rain in the afternoon.
It's a shame.
Oh, what are you doing?
Ow, that hurts!
Wh-What is the matter with you, Futaba-san?
Wh-What do you mean?
What's the matter with you, Youko-san?
What is the matter with me?
Morning...
Man, I'm tired and my body feels heavy.
I'm so proud of myself for going to school.
Ah, good morning, Hayama-san!
"Ha-Hayama-san"?!
Ah.
It's that, right?
"That"?
It is a surprise, or what is it called?
Like a candid camera ruse to surprise me.
Oh, goodness.
I will not be tricked by this.
You can stop your act.
Youko-san is acting strange!
She said, "desu wa yo"!
I don't want to hear it
from you now, Futaba-san!
I finished crocheting lace yesterday!
It took two whole months!
Crocheting lace?
Why don't you just buy it?
Aw, this is my hobby.
Look, isn't it just the cutest?
Oh man, what a girly hobby.
Oh?
What's the matter, Youko-san?
They are even like this
when I am not present.
What is the matter with those two?!
U-Um...
Hm? Huh?
Hmmm?
H-H-Hayama-san... w-well...
What's up, Nishiyama-san?
Y-You're the last one to...
turn in the worksheet.
I have to turn all of them in at once, so...
Ehhh, I haven't done it yet.
Why don't you do it for me, Nishiyama-san?
You're class rep, right?
Huh?
B-But...
Ah, I see.
This is a dream.
You're making it hard for
Nishiyama-san by not turning it in.
Jeez.
Huh?
What a pain...
I'll do it now.
What a terrible dream.
That Hayama.
That Hayama, that Hayama!
Hm?
What a troublemaker!
Curse her!
I'll show her how I am
when I'm not holding back.
Just watch me!
This is...
Hey, Hayama-san!
Look how much trouble
you're giving Nishiyama!
Hurry up and turn it in!
I'm doing it now.
Nishiyama's not class representative
because she wants to be!
She was forced to be class representative, because
nobody else wanted to do all the extra work!
Nishiyama's really timid,
so she couldn't say no.
Maybe they haven't changed all that much.
I feel so lazy!
Maybe I'll ditch afternoon classes.
That won't do!
You should go to class.
So lazy...
I am still not used to these two like this.
But, if this is a dream,
what is everybody else like?
Whoo!
I'm so annoyed!
I hate the world!
Maybe I'll break all the school windows!
If I steal a motorcycle and don't know
how to ride it, it's the world's fault!
Hayama-san's onee-chan is the
top bad girl in this school, right?
Bad girl?
Isn't she studious pupil,
since she properly comes to school?
Oh?
Yamaji!
What, Nishikawa?
Address your teachers properly.
Huh?
What's this?!
Violence at school?!
Youko-san, what are you doing?
You just punched a teacher!
Oh my.
It's a habit...
But he's a teacher!
And I did not punch him.
It was a slap.
Oh, goodness.
That's what you wanted to clarify?!
What's this?!
It's an offense to hit a teacher!
Report to the faculty room, immediately!
If there's a problem, they can come to me.
Why are you so rebellious?!
Youko-san!
Stop!
Now, now.
What's the fuss?
Class is starting soon.
Return to your classrooms.
Or-may-be...
...you want to be punished by Shino-sensei?
And so that kind of dream...
...I saw!
That was Sonobe-san dream?!
Of course it was.
I would do no such thing.
R-Right...
Wasn't it interesting?
It's too bad I woke up right
when it was getting good.
You know...
...wasn't I pretty terrible?
Well, it was a dream.
It wasn't too different from the real me.
You weren't even there, Futaba.
Don't say that!
Central Shopping Arcade
It does seem pretty fun to be a different you.
Especially since you're usually
hiding your real self, right?
Oh, there she is!
Futaba-chan!
Sakura!
Well, how do I look?
I tried changing my image!
Oh, how cute.
I think it's pretty good, too.
You know how I'm going
to be an idol when I grow up.
Ah, you mentioned that.
So, can you listen to me sing?
I need to get used to singing in front
of people, so I don't get nervous.
I'm in full bloom! My charm is never-ending!
I won't let you even glance at other girls!
Today and tomorrow, forever and ever!
U-Ugh... recital...
Unlike one-chan, she's completely off...
Sa-Sakura!
Hm?
Why don't you practice before
performing in front of people?
Yeah, they say to wear a bucket
on your head to cure your tone-deafness.
Do that!
Wha—
What's this.
A bucket...
So I should sing with this on?
Y-Yeah.
That's what I heard.
I'm in full bloom!
I'm in full bloo—
Sakura-san?
F-Futaba-chan?
I might throw up.
Good thing we have a bucket!
Doesn't look good.
I tried doing it like Sakura-san.
Oh, then how about this?
Well?
It does not get in the way...
Want to try on glasses, too?
Hayama-kun.
Glasses.
Glasses aren't an optional feature for braids.
Maybe I should cut it shorter...
Why would you?!
How could you cut your hair?!
I thought it would be a good change.
The ends are damaged, anyway.
Long hair uses a lot of shampoo and water,
which can get expensive, too.
B-But!
It would be a waste to cut your long hair.
You have been growing it out
since you were young.
Right?
It would be a waste.
You can't go back once you have cut it, either.
Your normal hair style
fits you best, Youko-sama.
You think so?
A princess hair cut is a must for a rich girl,
even though you no longer are one!
Not because it looks good on me?
Thank you very much!
I am not just so-so anymore!
Do you not think I am a pro
at working part-time?
You're amazing, Youko-sama!
You're best in the world at anything you do!
You're a professional!
A pro at working part-time?
Well, at first, I couldn't believe
she was working part-time.
She probably grew quickly
because of this environment.
Oh, found it!
It's here, here!
This is the shop from the book!
Welcome!
Which one should I get?
Youko-sama?
Ni...
Nishikawa... san?
Huh? Who's that?
A school friend... from before.
Oh my, Osakabe-san!
Huh? You know her?
Yes, we were in the same grade
at my previous school.
Oh, Mannenro Girls' Academy, right?
The rich girl school.
Hm?
Even rich girls work part-time?
Oh, you're learning how the world works?
No, I no longer have the
standing to be a rich girl.
I am working for the income.
Oh...
These two cakes are our
seasonal recommendations.
Oh. I'll have those, please!
Youko-sama!
Youko-sama is a real part-time pro!
Um...
You can contact me here, just in case.
Let me know if there is
anything I can do for you.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Yo-Youko-sama
Yo-Youko-sama!
You were amazing!
You are pro!
You did your best!
O-Of course.
I have leveled up.
This is nothing!
I am a pro part-timer!
Oh, even though all you have
is pride, you tried so hard!
I-I will take a short break.
I need a drink.
What, that's mayonnaise!
I heard you had it rough yesterday.
It was fine.
It is true that I do not want to be seen like this.
But, I cannot go back to my old self.
Because, the me now is the actual me.
Youko-sama...
Morning!
What a wonderful day it is!
Tee-he-he. Tee-he. He-he.
Tee-he-he, ow ow ow!
Same reaction as in the dream.
Futaba-chan, you don't have
enough feminine power!
What do you mean?
How can you say that when
you're eating like that?!
Even I'm trying my best to
become an idol by doing this!
Futaba-chan, why don't you put
effort into something, too?
That's what happened.
I see...
I was shocked to hear that I didn't
have enough feminine power,
so I wanted to show people that I'm a girl.
Tee-hee!
Youko-sama is trying her best, so I
thought I could try my best, too!
Futaba-san...
Oh, my!
The birdies are having a little chat.
Hayama-san is all polka-dotted!
Are they hives?!
Oh, these are good.
They are.
Oh, do you want some, Odagiri-san?
I'm sorry!
Your feelings are enough for me.
Tee-hee!
Huh?!
What's the matter, Odagiri-san?
Are you feeling sick?
It's almost lunch time, so I
shouldn't eat sweets now.
Are you sure?!
They're burnt milk caramels!
Yup.
I'm okay.
You're drooling!
Oh, so you're not very feminine?
You should have just asked me for pointers.
I do various things to better myself.
You do?
I take rose supplements to smell better.
And also do stretches to maintain my figure,
do sit-ups and use dumbbells on daily basis.
I also do this and that and this.
You do that much?
Amazing!
You're fervently doing so much!
Yeah, I'm trying hard!
What's wrong with that?!
Lucky Number
Your lucky number today is "3".
Your actions will make things go uphill.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
A                                                             A
Lucky Color
My lucky number's three.
My lucky color is yellow.
Lucky Number
Your lucky number today is "3".
Your actions will make things go uphill.
Your smile will make everyone happy!
A                                                             A
Lucky Color
What are you looking at?
At my horoscope.
Girls like checking their horoscopes, right?
That's true.
Oh, Odagiri Futaba!
You're not stopping by Stuffed-san's?
There's a new curry challenge.
If you finish three kilos, it's free!
Three!
Yellow!
No way, no way.
Mm, I-I can't.
What?!
I couldn't finish three kilos of food.
I am a girl.
What are you saying?!
Are you trying to make a fool of me?!
You're just Odagiri Futaba!
Don't say you can't finish it!
It's rude to those who have lost to you!
It's fine.
Go ahead.
Yes.
You are the best when you
are shining brilliantly.
Yeah!
Stuffed Hut
Delicious!
Feminine charm is at absolute zero.
Stuffed Hut
Thanks for the food!
I won't lose next time!
Futaba-chan!
I heard that you wanted to raise
your feminine power.
Ah... er...
I made this for you.
Wait!
It's probably a special soup that will raise
my feminine power or something, right?
Too bad!
It's a juice!
Doesn't make a difference!
Here.
The color! And the smell!
I have some for everyone.
Onee-chan, what happened to you?
You think...
...our feminine power went up?
Anyway, what are you doing
here so early, Yuu-san?
Daddy has a job for your dad!
Oh my, for my father?
That's great, Youko-sama!
Having connections is great, isn't it?
Thank you so much.
How can I thank you?
Huh?!
Then... maybe you'll sign...
a marriage application?
Huh?
Well, you know!
It'll be just for fun, like playing pretend!
Geez, I would be okay with that anytime.
Let's go submit our marriage application.
Let go of me!
I've been learning how to sing.
Aren't you head over heels?!
Well, looks like this is his fate.
I am the daughter of the Nishikawa Family.
My father is a company employee,
and I am his only daughter!
Woah!
Wow, that's so normal!
I am now the same as you.
I will not be easily captivated
by food like before—
U-Um...
Nishikawa-san...
Um...
This is my return gift for Valentine's!
Dietary Supplement Cookies
10 packs of 4 sticks
Huh?
I thought it should be cookies,
but I wanted them to be useful, too.
A-A-Are these for me?
Youko-sama.
She's super happy.
Wait, isn't White Day next week?
What?!
Are you still thinking about it?
I am pitiful.
I have not changed a bit since I met you two.
Huh?
You have changed.
Really?
When we first met, you said,
"Why are you eating here, too?
How bothersome!"
You were more like a rich girl.
Then, I thought, here is a protected species.
What?!
What are you saying, Futaba?
You mean, endangered species.
What?
But wouldn't there be a lot
if you look in the right places?
When did we start talking about animals?
Um...
If it's an endangered species,
maybe they'll go extinct.
That's why we need to protect them.
Um, why have you been
talking about animals?
Oh!
Found another endangered species!
Huh?!
Hm!
Yeah, it'd be annoying if
there were a lot of them.
What would be annoying?!
Aren't they talking about you?
Hey!
Kondou-san is a different kind
of protected species.
Why are you wearing that ...
...Sonobe-san?!
And that's a rare beast.
We shouldn't get too close.
Sonobe!
Let's go, Youko-sama.
Don't feed the animals.
A-And that's...
A-A dangerous, poisonous one.
Run away!
Huh? What?
Hayama-san!
Futaba-san!
Wait for me!
I am graduating from bread crusts!
Oh...
I am trying an instant food today.
Wow!
Sauce   Yakisoba
Sh-She's done it!
She put the sauce in first!
What she said before...
It's all over!
Huh? Huh?!
Oh, look.
She's sulking.
Instant noodles such a hassle,
anyway, it is not like I enjoy them!
Bread crusts are more abundant
and taste delicious.
You brought some?!
Thank you
.          very much!