See? See?!
It goes pretty fast!
Th-This is some pretty... skillful driving.
I know, right?
You may not believe it, but I've been practicing extra hard.
Of all the toys Kiritsugu brought me, this one's my favorite!
Toys, you say?
I could only drive around the courtyard at the castle.
This is incredible!
Shouldn't we have hired a professional driver?
No, that would be boring-
I mean, dangerous!
What if the enemy attacks us?
I suppose so...
Stop!
Irisviel.
Get out of the car and stay close to me.
That presence...
It's a Servant.
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
I've come for you, O Holy Virgin.
You know him?
I've never laid eyes on him.
How could you?!
Are you saying you've forgotten my face?
Forgotten? I've never even met you.
Perhaps you mistake me for someone else.
It's me! Gilles de Rais!
I've been praying solely for your revival and
spent my life waiting for a miracle to reunite us!
I've come all this way to the end of time just for that, Jeanne!
Jeanne?
I don't know your name, nor do I have any idea who this Jeanne might be.
No...
Have you really forgotten who you were in mortal life?
Since you gave me your name, I shall also give you mine in accordance to the knightly code.
My name is Arturia.
Heir to Uther Pendragon and King of Britain.
I am of the Saber class in this battle.
How tragic! How lamentable!
You've lost your memory and gone mad!
Curse you, God...
Curse you!
How could you inflict such cruel torture upon my beautiful maiden?!
That's enough! You embarrass yourself!
Awaken!
Call yourself Saber no longer.
The Holy Grail War has already ended.
The Grail has chosen me, Gilles, with no fighting at all!
For you see, my only wish, the revival of Jeanne d'Arc, has been granted!
If you mock the prayers of us Heroic Spirits any further, the next strike will be for real.
Now, get up!
Has your heart been that tightly sealed, Jeanne?
Very well, then.
Since drastic measures are called for, I will make preparations before coming again.
I swear to you, Jeanne.
I will free your soul from the curse of God.
It's so tiring to deal with someone
who won't listen to what you say.
I will strike before he can speak next time.
People like him infuriate me.
However, this may have been fortunate for me in my current condition.
He felt too dangerous of an enemy to face with my left arm sealed.
Following Saber's Master has resulted in an unexpected reward.
We actually found Caster as well.
Of course, we must follow him, too.
No, no.
Here's what you do with the thumb.
Nice.
Perfect.
Welcome back, Mister.
No way!
Accursed God!
To this day, he keeps an iron grip on Jeanne's soul and refuses to let go!
By Jeanne, you mean the girl in that crystal ball?
We have to prove it to her!
That God's might has long gone and his love is hollow!
That no foul deed or horrible crime results in God's punishment!
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You're so much cooler anyway, Mister!
In that case!
We need greater depravities, greater blasphemies.
We shall create a blasphemous hill of live sacrifices!
Uh, so basically...
It's quantity over quality from now on?
Yes! Exactly that!
Very good, Ryuunosuke.
Let's start by sacrificing the eleven in the cells.
Then, we'll find some more kids to replenish our supplies.
What a waste, though.
We interrupt this program to bring you breaking news.
Unexplained Explosion
An unexplained explosion occurred in the
warehouse district off the Fuyuki City coast.
We go live to the scene...
Why didn't you finish Saber off tonight?
You had not one, but two chances.
It's even worse that you made me waste a Command Spell.
Was your fight with Saber that much fun?
That's not it.
I swear by my honor as a knight that I will bring you Saber's head.
There's no point in swearing it now!
Of course you'll do it.
You made a contract with me to get me the Grail!
And now, you swear to defeat only Saber?
You must be horribly mistaken!
Aren't you the one who's mistaken, Lord El-Melloi?
Sola-Ui...
Lancer did well.
Aren't you the one who's misjudging the situation?
Saber is a particularly powerful Servant.
I couldn't let the chance to defeat her once and for all slip by.
She's been dealt a wound that cannot heal.
You could leave her be and still defeat her whenever you like.
If you find Saber that threatening,
why didn't you go after Saber's Master?
You merely hid and watched.
It doesn't get more pathetic than that.
Kayneth.
I'm sure you understand the advantage you have over the other Masters, right?
You made a special alteration to the usual Master-Servant contract.
You get the Command Spells, while I act
as an additional Master and supply mana.
They don't call you the top prodigy of Necromancy for nothing.
But we must be careful with the beginning.
Oh, is that so?
Yet you press Lancer for results-
That's enough.
Any more will be an insult to my lord.
As a knight, I cannot allow it.
No, I didn't mean it like that...
Sorry. I went too far.
What? What's going on?
I see.
A fire on the lower floors.
It's clearly arson.
Arson?
Tonight, of all nights?
It's a ploy to vacate the place.
Then... it's an attack?
Saber's Master will want to dispel
the spear's curse as soon as possible.
Lancer, head down and receive her.
Don't just drive her off this time.
Understood.
Our guest can enjoy the magical atelier of Kayneth El-Melloi.
A perfect atelier spanning an entire floor.
Twenty-four field layers.
Three mana generators.
Dozens of ghosts and evil spirits roaming as guard dogs.
Countless traps.
Parts of hallways that open out to other worlds.
Both I and my opponent will be able to use
every technique up our sleeves in this fight.
Your statement that I'm pathetic...
I'll have you retract it shortly.
Good. I look forward to it.
Lord Archibald!
Lord Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald!
Are you present?
Yes.
That's me. Don't worry.
Both I, Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald,
and my wife, Sola-Ui, have evacuated.
I see.
Okay, thank you.
Everyone has evacuated.
Very good.
Preparations are complete.
And you?
No problems here.
Ready anytime.
Maiya.
There was no activity from the target up to the end.
He didn't leave the hotel.
A free fall from 150 metres high.
No magic field defense could have saved him from that.
Maiya, withdraw.
Though, it's hard to believe that a Mage would go as far as to blow up an entire building.
I suppose he's skilled at outsmarting Magi.
Kotomine Kirei...
Oh? I don't think we've met before.
Or is there a reason why you already know me?
Then I can guess who you are.
Don't make me do all the talking, woman.
Just answer me this.
Where is the man who was supposed to be here instead of you?
Your agility isn't bad at all.
You seem to be well-trained.
She didn't throw this.
Very well.
Just the knowledge that someone was here to save her will do for tonight.
Kirei-sama.
Didn't I tell you not to expose yourself in the open without cause?
I'm sorry, but there's information that you should hear as soon as possible.
We've located Caster.
After having Assassin perform a detailed investigation,
we learned that Caster and his Master have been kidnapping sleeping children from Miyama and the neighboring district.
They had kidnapped fifteen by dawn.
I believe...
...they are the serial killers everyone is all worked up over.
They use magic without any hesitation and do nothing to hide its traces.
I don't think they're even thinking of the Holy Grail War at this point.
A mad Servant out of control, and a Master who won't restrain him.
Why would they be in the Grail War?
We cannot ignore them, Tokiomi-kun.
Their actions clearly violate the rules beyond what is acceptable.
Of course.
As someone responsible for guarding
the secrets of magic, I cannot allow it.
We'll have to eliminate Caster and his Master.
The problem is that defeating a Servant requires another Servant.
And we can't send my Assassin.
Minor rule changes are within my authority.
We'll mobilize all the other Masters to defeat Caster.
Archer?
Despite being few in number, yours are of
higher quality than those in Tokiomi's room.
What an outrageous apprentice he has.
What do you want?
It appears there's someone besides me with plenty of spare time.
Spare time?
Otherwise, a Master under the Church's protection need not wander about without permission.
What are you talking about?
Are you dissatisfied with your contract this late into the game, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi invited me to this world and maintains my form here.
His greeting was also worthy of my status, so I had to respond.
But I never thought he'd be this boring.
Are you unhappy with Tokiomi as your Master?
Reaching the Swirl of the Root, he says.
What a pointless-sounding ambition.
The desire to access the Root is unique to the Magi.
It's not for outsiders to comment on.
The path to the Root can be said to be an escape to the World Exterior.
Those of us interested only in the World Interior can
only understand it as a "pointless-sounding ambition".
I see.
It's true that I'm satisfied from simply
admiring my garden, the entire universe.
I have no interest in realms outside my dominion.
This Root thing doesn't concern me in the least.
Perhaps, but the Grail isn't a device
specifically designed to seek the Root.
When we say that it is omnipotent, we mean that it has limitless potential to alter even the World Interior.
So you're saying the other Masters have motives other than Tokiomi's for seeking the Grail?
Tokiomi is an archetypal Mage as well as ultra right-wing.
Others generally seek benefits concerned
with the World Interior, the present world.
Prestige, desire, power...
That suits me fine.
I love all of those things.
You are a king that rules over the vulgar, Gilgamesh.
Then what about you, Kirei?
What do you wish from the Grail?
I...
I have no real desire for it.
Impossible.
Doesn't the Grail only call upon those who are worthy of it?
So they say.
But I don't understand it either.
I have no ideals or desires, so why
was I chosen to fight in this battle?
No ideals or desires.
Then why not simply wish for pleasure?
Ridiculous. Pleasure?!
You'd ask me to commit something so sinful and corrupt?
Sinful?
Corrupt?
I don't understand your logic.
Why must pleasure and sin be connected?
Well...
Pleasure through evil means could be a sin.
But people also derive pleasure from good deeds.
What kind of philosophy calls pleasure itself a sin?
Pleasure is another thing that I lack.
I seek for it but cannot find it.
Kotomine Kirei.
I suddenly find you very interesting.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
Sit down.
You see, pleasure is basically a form of the soul.
The question isn't whether it exists, but whether you know it or not.
Kirei, you don't yet see what form your soul has taken.
That's basically what is happening
when you claim that you lack pleasure.
So, some Servant seeks to lecture me?
Don't get cocky, mongrel.
These are the words of a king who has tasted all the pleasures and luxuries of this world.
You should just listen to me.
Kirei, you ought to learn about entertainment.
Start by looking to the outside.
I know.
Why don't you start by joining me in my entertainment?
I have no time to waste on merrymaking.
Don't be like that.
You can pursue it between the jobs Tokiomi assigns you.
Isn't your task to observe the five other Masters anyway?
That's right.
You should investigate not only their plans and strategies, but also their motives.
And then tell me about them.
That's possible if I instruct the Assassins.
But what does it matter to you, Archer?
I told you.
I enjoy watching what humans do.
One or two of them are bound to be interesting.
More interesting than Tokiomi, at the very least.
Very well, Archer.
I accept.
But it will take some time.
That's fine.
I will wait patiently.
I'll help myself to your wine in the meantime.
My reason for seeking the Grail?
I've said too much myself.
It definitely isn't pleasure.
But...
If I can learn about him , will I be able to learn what it is that I seek?
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Episode 6
Night of Stratagems
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
I'll temporarily alter the rules.
Emiya Kiritsugu will end his own life.
If we run now, we can still...!
It will be my spear that takes Saber's life!
I won't think to fight you for the Grail any longer!
Don't get carried away, you bastard!
Next Episode
Forest of Demons