Woah...
Hm? You want a guitar too?
I've never played one, but...
you think I could pull it off?
Just like Momoka-san!
Forget it.
You said you've never played, right?
Just focus on singing.
She's not even listening to you.
Well, performing for the first
time tends to do that to you.
Heh, it's written all over her face.
Being able to pour out all of these repressed feelings...
Being able to scream them out at the top of my lungs...
It's the first time in my life I've ever felt like that.
I've always felt so conscious of people's judging glares,
that I was never able to express myself till now.
Nina!
Let's go practice.
Alright!
4: (SHOCKING) GRATITUDE
Ok, stop.
- What do you think?
- Not bad!
Give it a listen.
I wanna break.
I've got no courage left!
Someone hurry and give me a reason to live.
I'm liking this!
After all, there's many that--
Nina, can you level it
a bit more during the chorus?
Someone hurry and give me a reason to live.
Like that?
Yeah, it comes off as
too conventional otherwise.
Also, let's redo the drums.
Huh? Like, right now?
I've gotta wake up early tomorrow, you know.
Diamond Dust?
Yeah, I saw her looking them up.
You think she's being self-conscious?
But like, aren't they actual pros by now?
I mean, yeah, but...
If she was really being conscious,
Why'd she stick around
with two amateurs like us?
But...
No way...
NO WAY!!
What's wrong?
Sorry, gotta go home!
I'll... see you tomorrow!
Subaru-chan? You okay?
It's nothing serious ...right?
Boyfriend, I'd guess.
H-HUUH?!
I didn't think she had one right now though.
Maybe it's some ex
or something like that?
W-what are you implying?!
Why you acting like it's that outrageous...
I... I mean...
You think that's the case?
Girls in bands tend to be
pretty popular with the boys.
They're easy prey for the vultures.
...Prey?
You should be careful too!
I'm calling her.
As if she'll reply. Again, I'm sure
she'll tell us tomorrow.
But hey, we've all got a right to
date and work as we please, right?
How do you really feel though?
About Diamond Dust, I mean.
Not much, really.
What do you mean by "not much"?
I mean that I'm not holding
a grudge or anything,
All I can do is just wish them good luck, I guess.
But then, why did you leave them?
Let's just drop it.
Don't worry about what doesn't
affect you. Just keep on singing.
Momoka-san. What was your band like?
I said drop it.
Please tell me.
Catch.
It all started as a school club.
But from the beginning, you could
tell we all had talent. And passion.
We all felt like it had to be fate,
that we had to chase this together.
It felt like a miracle. I felt it in the goosebumps.
And I was right.
As early as our first year's school festival,
we had so many attendees they
couldn't even fit in the auditorium.
Those times... they were the best.
We decided to drop out of school
and aim for going pro.
We came here, had our first indie CD, concert,
And then got signed with a major label!
...And then I gave it all up.
Momoka-san...
I've never seen you smiling like this...
S-sorry... I'm not sleeping I swear...
If I'm gonna sleep,
I should just do it on the bed...
Subaru-chan!
Huh? WHAT?!
Quitting the band. Sorry!
HEY?!
I mean, if that's what she wants...
What are you saying?!
Didn't the three of us swear we'd chase
this together?! You'd give her up that easily?!
I don't mean it that way.
If she values the band,
she won't give us up for a man.
If we just force her back,
she'll want to leave us all the more.
You think...?
Let me guess, never had a boyfriend?
What about you, Momoka-san?
Anyone home...?
The hell are you saying?
Being here again,
I can't help but freeze up...
Since you're the band leader,
I'm counting on you.
Leader? Since when?
Also, keep in mind Subaru-chan puts up
an annoying persona at school,
So don't hold it against her.
Oh?
Suba...
...who?
Please, grandmother, if you will.
May I help you?
- Suba--
- Oh, are you lost?
Grandmother, give me a moment
so I can show them the way.
The hell are you doing here?!
Why wouldn't we?!
After that message you sent us...
I'll explain later, but
for now just get out!!
Not if you don't give us a good reason first!
I already said...
Who are they?
Grandmother!
They're... friends. Fellow actresses.
Actresses?
Right?
The glares can be quite overwhelming out there.
It is a busy place. Truly.
Subaru-chan.
- Posture.
- Yes!
Haven't I told you enough times to mind your posture?
One's habits manifest too evidently
when they are performing.
We must always be composed in both heart and mind.
Yes ma'am!
I ask you as well,
That you ensure she does not forget such things.
If you'll excuse me.
Subaru-chan.
I know...
Isn't that... Awa Tendo,
the famous actress?
You're now realizing?
How was I supposed to,
when no one told me?
Yep. She's my grandma alright.
She said she was visiting,
insisting I show her around.
Huh? So you're from a showbiz family?
...Not really.
My parents have normal jobs.
But you don't want to be an actress, right?
Of course not. But like I told you,
I can't just spring that on her now.
Then why did you say
you were quitting the band?
I guess you could say I was panicking.
Didn't Sun Tzu say "To fool your enemies, you must first fool your allies"?
You're making no sense.
Anyway, goes to show how important
it is I keep fooling her.
She seems nice enough though.
Yeah. At first glance. But she's from Kyoto,
So if you take her at face value, you'll come to regret it.
Really?
- Posture!
- Yes!
We should be taking our leave.
But I would like to get a look at
how much your acting has improved first.
...Sure?
Would the two of you care to join us?
W-what is it?
T-t-the truth is... I have feelings? For you!!
Don't you dare.
An... etude?
Indeed. Of a love scene.
You will confess your feelings for your friend,
While her former lover, Subaru-chan,
tries to get her back.
...Sure.
THE HELL IS AN ETUDE??
What a wonderful idea!
Acting. Just improv it!
Then let us hurry back.
Improvise HOW??
So, are you in?
- No way!!
- Just deal with it
- There's literally no way
- Come on!!
- Fuck off.
I must refuse.
Sorry, I think Nina-san
must've misheard you.
NOW LISTEN HERE YOU LITTLE...
- DO IT. OR YOU WANT ME TO QUIT?
- No means NO!!
Please mind your phones, this is improv after all.
Yes!
Then everyone, let us not be late.
Hold it!
Y-you must be...
I've realized I can't hide
my feelings anymore.
I'm also in love with you!
Then why did you leave?
Huh?
I believed in you from
the moment you accepted me.
I really believed we would never fall apart.
So how were you able to tell me
you'd leave like it's nothing?!
Well...
Answer me!
Was everything you told me
back then a lie?
No, I... meant it, but...
Then what gives?!
You're the worst! Using acting
as an excuse to lash out against me...
I don't see where's the problem.
I get it.
It's not like I want to quit the band.
After all, at school...
Everyone only sees me as the granddaughter of Awa Tendo.
- It's just...
- What?
I'm worried I'll get caught.
It's the first time she's showed up all of a sudden.
She's not the type of person
to be spontaneous like that.
It has to be this!
Girls Band Cry.
You're playing in a TV show?!
Watch it! Don't speak into the mic!
What can I even do?
My grandma made the call.
Even so it shouldn't be long,
so I'll be free after a week or so.
But 'till then, no practice.
Got it.
Are you sure?!
Haven't you also skipped practice to study?
That's not the same thing.
- Yes it is!
- No it's not!
Chill out.
But! Aren't you afraid
of losing Subaru-chan?!
It happens with bands.
But...
What's with the tone?
It's because you don't seem to care.
You're the one who doesn't seem to care about us!
I said I'll be back, right?
Why won't you trust me?
But...
Look, everyone has something
they're conscious about.
I mean, you don't like it when
people ask about your past, right?
That's...
We're wasting time.
We only need to record the drums now,
so just go home, Nina.
I'm the one who doesn't care?
Nonsense.
You free tomorrow?
Nope!
I'm lying!! I am!
Where are you taking me?
Oh? This is my place.
Make yourself at home.
THE NEXT DAY
Wow...
You get used to it fast.
- Want some tea?
- Y-yeah!
Just sit wherever, I'll be there.
It's the best for gaming.
Thanks.
Check this out.
She's so pretty...
I felt I should be honest with you
before you snap at me again.
STARRING: TENDO AWA
SUBARU
I was named after this movie's title.
My grandma insisted.
So that actress is...
Yep. Subaru is the film that launched
her career when she was young.
Or so I'm told, since I wasn't born yet.
She said this name would bring me luck
Whenever I'd become an actress.
But... you don't want to, right?
Yeah, you see...
I hate having to live in the shadow
of my grandma. But more than that...
I hate pretending to be who I'm not. It's uncomfortable.
Even so...
When I say I'll follow in her footsteps,
She smiles.
It's the only time she actually smiles.
Without putting a mask on.
What do you think?
If it were you, what would you do?
Hey.
Do you get it now? You dummy!
But you can't keep this up forever.
Wouldn't it be better to be
honest with her sooner than later?
You're probably right.
I am right!
I was hoping that if she saw I
couldn't cut it at acting school,
She'd just give up on it alltogether.
- See you later.
- Mhm.
- Don't worry. I won't leave.
- Really?
When we were playing the other day,
I thought... wow, I never realized
how much I love this!
I told you to trust me, so say something!
Yeah!
What's this?
I ' M  S O R R Y
- N I N A.
If you're sorry, then
don't get mad to begin with.
SOME DAYS LATER...
Starting Detective Grandma on the Case Part 6,
Let's welcome our main actress, Awa Tendo!
A pleasure.
I'm her granddaughter, Subaru.
I'll be playing the cashier.
It's a pleasure.
She's practically drowning in makeup...
She's gotta go the extra mile, you know.
Bands do so too, to look good on stage.
- Huh? You also do makeup?
- Sometimes.
Stop imagining things.
Action!
You think she'll tell her?
Yeah, she said she would.
She'll probably have to quit acting school,
and stop living alone, but she
wants to continue with the band.
If it'll cause her that many problems,
then maybe she should just keep at it for now?
True, but...
I think she's realized she
can't run away from it forever.
Alright, perfect!
Let's check the footage.
Is everything good?
Yes, my part for the day is over.
It's our first time acting together.
You must be thrilled.
I've always dreamt about it.
To share the stage with her.
So you really want her
to become an actress?
Well, obviously.
Subaru shares her name with the
movie that started my career.
You see, my daughter hates this business.
She always resented me for the fact
I tried pushing her into it despite
often not being at home for her.
So you can only imagine how I felt,
when Subaru told me that she liked my acting.
She was the only one who smiled at me.
The only one who
liked me for my work.
So when she said she wanted
to try it, I felt so grateful.
Cut!
Let's check.
Now then, let me see it too.
Grandmother!
Ah, well done!
Ehm, I would like to talk for a moment...
Talk? About what?
It could wait until later, but you might
not make the Shinkansen back.
Good point. I do not have much time.
I see.
Here I go then.
You see...
Truth is...
I...
Grandmother.
I want...
Subaru-chan! Emergency!
I forgot something! We need to hurry!
We gotta hurry! Let's go! Come on!
Huh? Wha- Ouch, wait!
Don't push me!
Hold up, what's wrong?
You say one thing, then you do another?
My bad!
Watch it!
What gives? You weren't lying when
you said I should just tell her, right?
- Well, yeah.
- Then why?!
After I finally got the courage...
It's just... everyone has
something they're conscious about.
Things aren't always that simple,
so you have to be careful about this stuff.
- Right?
- Who do you think you are?
Ouch ouch ouch!
What makes you think you can
preach us after all that's happened?!
And yet you...
But you still need to tell her someday.
When?
When you become sure about
what you want to do in life.
What's with this girl, I swear!
I don't know.
Agh, screw this!
Screw this, screw this, screw this!!
You told me not to quit, so I made up my mind.
Yet I get stuck between a
bipolar self-righteous freak,
And an emotionless know-it-all!
I'll choose my life for myself! Leave me alone!!
Subaru-chan...
So? How's my acting?
Aaah, I needed that!
Ah well, I figured I'd have to come
to terms with it on my own someday,
So until then, I'll be here to kick your asses into shape!
Come on, let's go!
Next Time: Singing Blaze