Komachi!
What?
Would you like some coffee?
Sure.
All right.
Here.
Hey, Komachi...
I need some advice.
'Kay. I'll lend you an ear.
But first,
don't you have something to say to me?
The other day was my bad.
I shouldn't have said that.
Or acted like that.
Or had that personality.
Or those eyes.
Yeah...
I'm sure you did something stupid,
so you're in the wrong anyway.
Right on the money.
And you haven't even apologized.
R-Right.
But you're the older brother,
so you're fine that way.
It's up to little ol' sis here to forgive you.
Also...
I'm sorry, too.
Don't worry about it.
Your big-hearted bro forgives you.
Look at this guy, acting all high and mighty.
So, what happened?
It's a long story.
That's okay.
I'll look for it in the promised land
My Teenage Romcom SNAFU. TOO!
A theory to fill in the blanks
Ought to be the perfect fit
And yet it goes around in circles
The future is an unknown beast
All it takes is a crack
For it to be twisted
And stray from perfection
I'm walking down a path
That will eventually drain me of all warmth
If I want to change
It's now or never
I don't want an ideal replica
All I need is something real
I'll go look for it in the promised land
But you whisper to me
In a fairytale ending
The words I want to hear
Oh. That's so you.
But, you know, I'm probably
the only one who gets it.
I've lived with you my whole life,
and that's why I can understand.
That's why I can go "what an idiot"
and shrug it off with a smile.
I can think "he's a lost cause,"
and that'd be that.
Only I'd still be a little sad.
But it's not that simple for others.
I'm sure they're hurting 'cause they have no idea what you're thinking.
You're nice to me,
but you're only capable of that 'cause I'm your sister, right?
If I weren't, I bet you'd stay as far away from me as possible.
That theory aside,
I'm glad you're my sister, though.
Oh, I'm sure that line scored me some points.
Bro!
That said,
if you weren't my brother, I'd definitely keep my distance and never give you the time of day.
Or so you say, but come on.
I've got some things going for me, right?
As if! You're a total pain!
Still...
Spend fifteen years with someone, and you'll grow fond of them whether you like it or not.
Oh, I'm sure that line scored me some points!
Well, fifteen years is a long time.
And soon, another fifteen years—
no, even more time will pass us by.
Quit running your mouth.
And how long do you think I've had to listen to you run your mouth?
You've got a long road ahead of you.
Got that?
Y-Yeah.
It's not just you.
I've got a future, too.
And I like both Yukino and Yui.
I don't wanna see your club disappear.
So could you help me out?
Could you help my friends out and do something about it?
Well, I can't turn down a request from my sister.
Yeah, do it for me.
I'm so selfish. What are you ever gonna do with me?
Damn straight.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
This is the answer Komachi gave me.
A reason I'd been looking for all along
to preserve that place and the time we spend there.
To keep Yukinoshita Yukino and Yuigahama Yui from becoming student council president,
what is it that Hikigaya Hachiman can do?
Well,
I have no idea, and it's freaking me out!
Oh, how about no uniforms?
That's it!
Also, it'd be nice if there were no more bag checks.
Those really suck.
They end up finding fanzines
I'd borrowed and stuff like that.
That only happens to you.
I-I'll put it down just in case.
Don't bother.
Anyway, I'd like to be able to eat on the rooftop.
Now there's an idea!
You look pathetic, Hikigaya Hachiman!
What're you talking about?
Looking pathetic is my default state.
You need something?
A foolish question.
The library is my haunt of choice during lunch.
And who do I see here today but you,
my partner in crime?
What's the matter, Hachiman?
Nothing important.
You may speak.
Nah, I'll pass.
I shouldn't be talking to others about this.
Don't be stupid.
How many times have you had to listen to my prattle?
I don't mind listening to yours.
I'm so cool for extending a helping hand to the weak.
You actually were, until that last line.
So, who're you ripping off this time?
Nay, I speak from the heart.
Dumbass.
Don't start acting legitimately cool on me.
Zaimokuza, I need a favor from you.
Saizeriya
As for how to go about it...
Oh, there he is!
What're you doing here?
Since you're going through all this effort for me,
I figured I should do my bit, too.
Ta-da! I brought reinforcements!
Why me?
On that note,
let's get right to "Operation Keep Yukino and Yui"!
Yeah!
Not that I care,
but if Yukinoshita and Yuigahama are out,
who's actually gonna be the president?
Dude...
Uh...
Why must we prevent those two from being elected?
Good question.
Going to war with them is a fool's errand, I must say.
Y-You've got a point there, but...
Bro, I want the two of them to stay in the Volunteers Club.
Honestly, I couldn't care less about the student council elections.
R-Right.
But what about Isshiki?
Is this Isshiki person that important to you?
Nope. Not in the least.
Then what's the problem?
But a job's a job...
What's more important to you, me or your job?
You, obviously.
I don't wanna work.
You had to go by elimination, huh?
I'm not really happy about it,
but whatever.
So what're you gonna do?
Let's see...
The number one priority has to be Komachi's request:
keeping Yukinoshita and Yuigahama in the club.
Given the situation, backing another candidate is a tall order.
The only card I can play is...
Negotiate with Isshiki, I guess.
B-But she's a girl, right?
Will she understand our language?
If Isshiki Iroha's playing that character on purpose,
you could say that it actually makes negotiating with her easy.
Long story short, she wants to maintain her brand image.
That's why she wanted to avoid the risk of getting a vote of no confidence.
Which would mean...
My initial approach was all wrong.
Kawasaki.
Gimme a list of names you'd like as student council president.
Yukinoshita
Yuigahama
Hayama
Ebina
Miura
Sagami
Tobe
Oh, and... You, I guess?
As amusing as that sounds,
I can't get thirty nominations.
I know. Just felt like throwing it out there.
Bro,
you have to talk to Yukino and Yui about this.
Promise me.
Sure, but I'll have to sound convincing.
I need to lay the groundwork first.
I'm just worried 'cause you skip a lot of steps despite seeming so methodical.
Relax.
I got my reason, and I've identified the problem and a solution.
My Teenage
Romcom SNAFU.
TOO!
Yukinoshita
Yuigahama
Hayama
Ebina
Miura
Sagami
Tobe
All that's left is to put it into action.
Hayama Hayato for President @ouen_HH
Looking for nominations! Please RT if you
don't mind signing up!
Oh, I'd like the Art Club to get tablets for use!
Yukinoshita Yukino for President @ouen_YYk
Looking for nominations! Please RT if you
don't mind signing up!
Tablets?
Hayama Hayato for President @ouen_HH
Looking for nominations! Please RT if you
don't mind signing up!
Mirai @mirai(・Ө・)
Whoa, there's a Hayama for President account!
I'm gonna back him. You guys should, too!
One-third of the entire student body, huh?
'Tis I.
We've got enough numbers.
Moving on to the next phase.
Hayama Hayato for President
@ouen_HH
Let's help Hayama Hayato win! This is an account
looking for people willing to nominate him for
student council president. Please follow and RT!
This is not a very nice tactic.
There's a lot of risk involved.
Zaimokuza...
Oh, but don't get me wrong!
It is not you that I'm worried about,
Soubu High's Student Council Elections are upon us!
Hayama Hayato for President!!
but rather that I'll be held responsible for carrying it out—or that you'll make me a scapegoat!
Soubu High's Student Council Elections are upon us!
Hayama Hayato for President!!
Let me just tell you in advance that I'm ready to spill the beans if you do!
Soubu High's Student Council Elections are upon us!
Hayama Hayato for President!!
You're such a piece of trash. I love it.
Don't worry.
Try as they might to find out who's behind these accounts, that person doesn't exist.
Edit profile
Hayama for President
Nobody'll get hurt.
Did you know, Zaimokuza?
A problem's not a problem as long as nobody sees it as one.
Could you get Isshiki for me?
Sorry it was just me.
Copying this stuff is a total pain!
Oh, was it Hayama's girlfriend you were hanging out with the other day?
Beats me.
Wouldn't hurt to tell me, right?
Maybe once we're done.
Whatever. They didn't seem like they'd pose much of a problem, anyway.
What, do you li—
What do you think of Hayama?
Huh?
What? Are you hitting on me?
Sorry, not happening. I have someone I like.
That's not it.
I simply wanted to know what you thought of him.
Well, let's see...
He seemed like a nice guy,
so I wanted to sed—
hold his hand or something.
Is it just me, or was she about to say "seduce" there?
Hey, listen to me!
Is there any point in doing this?
I guess it's not like there isn't any.
You don't sound very convincing.
Well, no matter what you do,
you can't beat Yukinoshita or Yuigahama.
In that sense, it is pointless.
I don't particularly want to,
but the possibility of winning scares me.
Nah, you don't stand a chance.
Well, yeah.
Besides, I'm sure the people who nominated you
won't actually vote for you.
I bet they're laughing their asses off right now.
And when you lose, they'll be laughing even harder.
Doesn't that piss you off?
Don't you want to give them a taste of their own medicine?
I'd love to if I could—
You can.
What do you think you've been
writing this whole time?
A list of nominations, right?
That's right.
To be more precise, it's a list of nominations for Isshiki Iroha.
Uh, but I've got enough already.
The rules say you need at least thirty,
but there's no maximum limit.
There's been a campaign backing you for president on the Internet,
and it's got one-third of the entire student body.
With these many supporters, you can win.
Where did that come from?
Also, I don't think I'd be a good president even if I did get elected.
I'm not confident,
and I'm already in a club.
Yeah, juggling the two would be tough.
But you gain a lot in return.
What do you think it is?
Huh?
Experience, I guess?
And a good recommendation, maybe.
You know, you're acting an awful lot like a teacher right now.
Wrong. Listen up.
What you'll gain is the ability to go,
"I'm student council president as a freshman,
and I still try my best to show up at practice!"
Got that?
And as a freshman, your mistakes will also be overlooked.
Also, when you don't feel like working,
you can use practice as an excuse.
Or vice versa.
B-But it'd still be hard work, right?
You can ask Hayama for advice, then.
Hell, have him help you out.
You could even make him walk
you home after practice.
Are you secretly a genius?
Kinda.
Well, I can't say no if I've got this many backers.
It does sound like an attractive proposition, too.
Besides, I don't want my classmates ridiculing me behind my back.
Fine, you got me!
You won't change your minds?
No. This is the best course of action.
I won't, either.
There's no need for you to run.
But I will.
And I don't intend to lose.
Why must you...
Because if you go, the club goes with you.
I don't want that.
That won't happen.
But...
There's actually no need for you to run.
Not just Yuigahama, but you too.
What's that supposed to mean?
I thought I made it clear your plan was rejected.
Yeah, so I'm going with something different.
I'm done with that shit.
Did you do this?
It was some volunteer.
No idea who.
I see.
This is a lot of people.
Yeah. About one-third of the student body.
These numbers are fact.
Of course, there's no way to drum up that much support for Isshiki Iroha.
I really won't be held responsible for this, okay?
Which means there's one big fat lie in this whole thing.
I mean it!
I know.
Later.
Edit profile
This is nothing but a bluff.
Hayama for President
Merely a means to convince them.
So all I need is to get through today,
Isshiki Iroha for President
Miura Yumiko for President
and then I can delete the accounts.
Totsuka Saika for President
It'll all vanish into thin air.
Isshiki Iroha for President
We've cleared all the conditions for Isshiki to become president
and all the shackles that prevented her from doing so.
So there's no need for you two to go for the position anymore.
Campaign account?
That's a relief.
It's all resolved, then.
So there's no longer a problem or a reason for me to act.
I guess.
Yeah.
And here I was sure you'd understand.
I'll let Ms. Hiratsuka know.
W-We'll go with you.
I'll be fine by myself.
Hey... I'm sorry.
Wh-Why are you apologizing?
I mean, you were putting a lot of effort into it.
What with the election pledge and speech and all that.
Oh, that doesn't matter anymore.
You did your bit as well, right?
Like, your hair's all grown out.
It's a mess.
Let me fix it for you.
No, thank you.
There, there.
You did your best, right?
Hardly...
This place is important to me.
And you preserved it for me.
Y'know, I knew all along that I
probably couldn't beat Yukinon.
That even if I did beat her,
I'd be too busy for the club.
So it's all thanks to you.
You've got that wrong.
Are you done yet?
You did your best, Hikki!
Where did that come from?
Stop it. I didn't do anything.
Nothing we could see anyway,
but I bet you did something that'd make an unpleasant sight.
You probably can't change your methods that easily.
And that guilt won't go away.
I couldn't do anything,
but I still ended up wondering if this was the right thing to do.
So I'm sure it'll eat away at you even more.
Things will go back to normal, right?
I don't know.
And here I was sure you'd understand.
This club doesn't have much to do,
and I already know what student council work entails.
There are people who can't act
This is the best option.
unless they're faced with a problem.
I can beat Isshiki, no problem.
Unless they find their reason.
Also, I don't mind doing it.
All I was left with was the sinking suspicion
that I'd gone horribly wrong.
President - Isshiki Iroha
Starting work already?
Unfortunately.
I don't think I'll be able to do anything at the start.
My little sister will enroll here next year.
So make it a good school for her.
What? Are you hitting on me?
Sorry, you're being too obvious!
And it's too creepy! Not happening!
Why'd her reason for rejecting me change?
Well, hang in there.
Oh, Hikigaya.
I'll carry that for you.
Thanks.
I had more stuff here than I expected.
It's like a whole different room.
To tell you the truth, I had high hopes.
Huh?
That Yukinoshita would succeed me as president.
And Yuigahama would be the vice president,
and you'd handle general affairs!
Why don't I get to be on the cabinet?
And then...
Even after graduating, I'd come hang out at the student council every now and then
and talk about how the cultural or athletics festival was so much fun.
I've always wanted something like that.
What if... And this is strictly hypothetical...
What if you could reload your save data to change your previous choice,
like in a game?
Would it change your life?
The Scent of Tea
...No Longer Fills That Room.
The answer is a resounding no.
The Scent of Tea
...No Longer Fills That Room.
Be it our uniforms, or our textbooks
They won't be changed on a whim
These times are fun, if a bit hollow
We'll keep swimming through them
But to preserve this sense of calm
We keep trying to solve the equation
Of the perfect act
Solitude used to be our pillar of strength
But it started crumbling down once we found love
Our everyday life could fall apart in a flash
So we remain cowards
As our overflowing emotions
Continue to hurt us forever
The Conference Dances Around in Circles.
That's all we had to carry in, right, Irohas?
Oh, the fridge needs to go further in.
Also, put the heater next to the desk.
You should've said so earlier.
Look, Irohas,
I need to go now. I got a temp job over Christmas.
But I'm bored, and I'd like to finish remodeling the student council room ASAP.
R-Right...
But I need to get to work.
I wish Hayato'd get here already!
Hayama?
Tobe, I'm good. You may leave.
O-Okay.