When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Unlike Hayate's morning, the day started peacefully.
But he had no clue that this was the start of
the day that would change the rest of his life.
Nagi, how about you visit the main house
where your grandfather is once in a while?
It'd be good to introduce Hayate-kun, too.
And please don't make that spiteful face.
Who's this grandfather?
The head of the Sanzenin family, Grandfather Mikado.
Head?
In other words, he's the current president of the Sanzenin family.
Then any mistake I make might lead to me being fired.
No, to him, it's easy enough to erase your existence from this world.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
The human body contains a mysterious power.
The more you train...
I don't think it's necessary to go say hi to that old man just cause we hired a new butler.
Don't say that.
He's your only blood relative.
Man, it's been a while since I last met Old Mikado.
Wait a minute. Why are you even here?
Come on. I'm a relative, you know.
But, what exactly is your grandfather like?
In terms of Dragon **est, he'd be Zo**.
In terms of comedy show, he'd be the ***.
A-Am I going to survive meeting someone that scary?
I'm sure it won't be safe.
If you displease him, he can easily erase the life of a debt-ridden butler.
After all, he forced Com**** to bankruptcy because he founded Pu** Pu**.
And for your information,
********** going down was done by him, as well.
Seriously?
She's lying, of course.
Anyways, he's like a half-ghost, so don't get possessed by some strange thing he may say.
Yes...
What's that?
Just to let you know, it's not
Toxic-Apple-Eating-Princess Castle at Mouseland.
Sanzenin Mikado-sama.
It's the Grandfather's house.
What country are we in?
What does he do for a living?
Oil baron?
That's not an occupation.
Hayate was coming to an understanding now.
Nagi wasn't an ordinary rich girl on the street.
Welcome home, Lady Nagi.
Yeah, I'm home.
She's a super rich girl.
But they're so uptight.
Sakuya-sama, Maria-dono.
You must both be tired from the long travel.
We're fine, thank you.
Please head on.
By the way, I'm sorry to interrupt you when you've just returned, but...
...what should we do about this unauthorized individual?
He had snuck onto the helicopter.
What a really suspicious-looking guy.
I understand what you mean, but he's fine.
He's my new butler who replaced Himegami.
This guy who looks like he has no luck with money?
Leave me alone.
But... um...
Hayate resisted.
Because it's absolutely true
that he has no money and a poor-man's face.
You don't have to highlight it like that.
But that was hilarious.
Saku, don't laugh too much.
It's fine; I was aware that I'd come to the wrong place.
Don't take it so personally. They only said what they saw and meant no harm.
Exactly. It's only a waste of time to worry over it.
Yes, I do have a 150 million yen debt,
but do I appear to be that detached from money?
A thoughtful mind is more important in this world.
Every individual has to think about the Earth's future.
They're avoiding eye contact.
Oh yeah, Nagi. You can't possibly be in those clothes to meet your grandfather.
You're right.
I'll get changed, so you go get some fresh air outside.
Yes...
I got kicked out.
I don't see the point in saying this now,
but isn't it dangerous to let
a debt-ridden guy like me walk around loose here?
Is this an expensive thing?
What a nice sound.
Maybe I can repay the entire 150 million yen with this.
That vase is only about 5 million yen over Yah** ***tion, so it won't be enough to pay the debt off.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It was only a thought.
Don't worry. I can tell by looking at you
that you're not the kind of person who would do such a thing.
Hey, stop looking at me with those
"hey, what's this old fart saying?" eyes.
I'm sorry.
And, you are?
I live here.
And right now, I'm taking care of the garden.
I see, so you're the landscaper of the house.
You don't believe in my eye, do you?
Just so you know-
Oops, I'm sorry.
All right, I'll show you how accurate my eyes are, so follow me.
His face is sparkling like that of a child.
Look!
Maria, these clothes are a little big.
That's what I thought.
That's called peeping!
You need daily training to improve your eyes.
What kind of criminal do you intend to become after all the training?
But I don't understand how you ended up
with a debt of 150 million yen.
It was originally a debt my parents made from gambling.
My parents are total losers
and gave me as a present to very kind people.
Then Lady Nagi paid the debt off for me.
So right now, I'm in the process of paying her back over the course of forty years.
I see.
I'm really grateful to Lady Nagi,
so you shouldn't be doing things like peeping.
I'll be off now.
So in other words, your life is infinitely worthless, I take it.
You're rather boring for a man Nagi has laid her eyes on.
Mister, who are you?
My eyes are the real thing.
I've foreseen the economy breaking down,
changes in government, and ****-chan balding, too.
I had even foreseen the younger sister boom coming from before the start of World War Two.
And my eyes are telling me.
Your life is even more worthless than those of your trashed parents.
I, Sanzenin Mikado, will give you my words.
My life is worthless?
Yes, it's worthless.
A life spent to repay a debt is infinitely worthless.
But if you still wish to make your life worthwhile...
Wh-What's this?
A levistone?
NO! That's a guide!
If you think your life is not worthless,
then keep that on until
the necessary day comes and do not lose it.
And if you can attain what lies beyond its guidance,
then forget 150 million yen.
You can gain a trillion or ten trillion yen.
After having his life completely rejected,
can Hayate walk to the wards the pendant guides him to?
To be continued in the second half.
Wait.
Hey Maria! Are we sure we don't need a gag?
Oh please, did I ever do any gags before?
No! I can't handle this!
There has to be at least one gag per minute, or else my Kansai blood won't let me be still.
Don't run away! I can't settle down!
That form of gag is already old.
Let me say this clearly.
It's cheap.
Zip it!
Land flat on your face!
Sorry, nothing happened.
Lambada
Dankai no sedai = Baby-Boomer Generation
Dankai no sedai
My granddaughter. Do you seek the Sanzenin estate?
I don't really need it, but I'd be glad to see you leave this world soon.
Maria! Maria! My granddaughter is bullying me.
Oh, what trouble we have.
I'm not bullying him.
Gramps, I don't need the estate, so can you give me some cash?
Besides, even without it,
as long as I have World Business Satellite
and the stock market, I won't have trouble with money.
Damn her. She's gaining unnecessary knowledge every year.
You're the one who taught me to gain this knowledge.
But...
I don't remember teaching you to draw a worthless manga like this!
Where did you get my manga from?!
See, my granddaughter bullies me.
Yes, yes.
Oh, but Grandfather, why are you bringing this up all of a sudden?
Oh, that's because, at this rate,
Nagi will die.
D-Do I have a winning popsicle?
All right, this one's real!
Score!
So ominous.
Because of what my parents were like, I'm always thinking about money.
I never spared a single thought for my life.
But, is that really all right with my life?
A life spent only to pay off debt...
Hayate!
Milady.
I looked all over for you.
Let's go home now.
What? We're returning already?
Yeah. I can't possibly spend any more time with that old man.
Did something happen?
Not yet, but rather will happen, I guess.
What's going to happen?
W-What is this person?
So he really came.
You're pretty good to dodge my sword.
Wh-Who is this fake foreigner?
It'd be a long story to tell,
but he's someone who might inherit the entire Sanzenin estate.
Inherit it all?
So basically...
The story won't go anywhere if we leave Nagi to do the explanation, so-
What?!
So let's just have you watch what happened after we left off.
Oh, but Grandfather, why are you bringing this up all of a sudden?
Oh, that's because, at this rate,
Nagi will die.
Huh? Why will I die?
Have you finally developed dementia, old foggy?
I have not developed dementia, and I'm not a "foggy" either.
Think about it for a second, my granddaughter.
I don't have much time ahead of me.
And when I die, the entire estate will go to you,
but there are many within the family that do not like that.
Yes, there are parents out there that would sell their son for 150 million yen,
so there could be those who may come after Nagi's life.
Exactly.
That's why I've come to a conclusion.
When a certain condition is met,
the estate will be given to this certain person.
Oh. And that condition is?
And that condition is...
I'm sorry.
I lose. I'll give you all the estate,
so please forgive me.
Make Nagi cry and apologize.
I'd rather die than utter such embarrassing words!
It's hard for me to understand what rich people think.
Don't worry, I don't understand, either.
Therefore...
Cry and apologize to me!
Who'd apologize to you, idiot!
Please cry and apologize to me!
Does he not have any pride at all?
It's useless to do that. Go home now.
I see. Then you leave me with no choice.
What are you doing to Hayate!
From what old Mikado tells me,
if I beat down that wimpy looking butler,
there's a chance our Lady will cry and apologize.
So I'll smack him down and make the estate mine!
If Milady can't inherit the Sanzein estate,
she won't be as rich as she is anymore, right?
Then that'll make her alone.
She'll end up on the street like me.
The porridge is ready.
I'm sorry for all the trouble, Maria.
We promised not to say that, right?
If only Hayate-kun would pay the money back...
I shouldn't have lent him 150 million yen.
Such a thing could happen.
Watch out, Hayate!
Prepare yourself!
Money...
Damn it. Take this.
A life spent to repay the debt is infinitely worthless.
Worthless.
Milady, who came to save me wearing such a hilarious mask.
Milady, who took care of me so earnestly.
I can't let Milady have an unpleasant life because of me.
I'll come up with a way to repay the debt soon.
And right now, I need to save her.
I don't know the meaning behind my life yet,
but right now, it's about her!
Why you!
Universe!
Ha... Hayate.
I'll protect you.
I'll protect you from anyone who tries to make you cry.
Is that all right with you?
Ah...
Um...
That's...
Well...
Th-Thank you very much.
What? This is going to become
a battle anime starting next episode?
No, it won't.
The boy lets go of his hesitation
and finds meaning in protecting his master.
Where is butler Hayate's future?
Next time, we'll fight against many issues.
Don't lose that pendant, boy.
Anyway...
Maria's gone...
That hurt.
What, you're still here?
I didn't get any cash off of you, yet.
Rather than that, how do you plan on going back?
Everyone's up there already.
They left me behind?
SFX: Swooooosh....
What a cold, cruel world!
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Unfortunately, today's the last day for Maria's song.
Eh? Really?
Next week, that character's finally showing up!
Would that happen to be the person
who ranked 1st in the popularity ranking, Hina-
No!
Hayate-kun, it'll be Nagi from next week.
But considering this is my last chance,
aren't I being rather badly mistreated?
Look forward to next week!
Bye bye
Um, you're Hayate-kun, right?
Nishizawa-san.
It's been since Christmas we last met. What were you doing until now?
Well, a lot has happened, and I'm working as a butler at a certain mansion.
What? Is that supposed to be a joke?
But I'm glad I got to see your face.
I'm really happy.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
We Were Once Taught by the Space Police That Youth is to Not Look Back.
But Hayate-kun, I... I...
You'll get to see a new type of conflict!