Nothing good comes from believing in people.
You have to look out for yourself.
Wasn't that... what it was all about?
Amid the smoke, the five desperately fought off death as it closed in.
Are we... going to die here?
No.
That can't be.
No way... in hell I'm dying.
Bro...
Sorry, guys!
I'm late.
Bro!
No... way.
Bro?
Bro!
Gimme a minute!
Sakuragi's in cell 2-6, right?
You can't, Bro!
Is he trying to force it open?
It won't work.
We tried to break it down, and we couldn't do it!
Shut up, you fucking kids!
You're gonna give up just like that?
No way...
our lives could be worth so little!
Bro...
I found it!
What do you think you're doing?
Isn't that...
the key to cell six?
Good, now I don't have to find it.
Right, Nomoto?
Sakuragi went inside to save them.
What?
Inside that fire?
I thought I'd failed when I saw Sakuragi in the yard, but...
I see.
He went inside by himself?
Then if we get rid of that key, it's all over.
May I...
May I please... borrow this key?
Hey, Nomoto.
You can't seriously believe I don't know, can you?
I know your cigarette started the fire.
Hey, don't worry.
I won't tell.
You just need to act like nothing happened.
Then it'll all work out.
I believe in you.
So you just need to believe in me.
Now...
give me that key.
I... never used to believe in anyone.
I only cared about myself.
That's how I thought.
But...
They're...
They're my first group of friends!
My first, ever!
You're nothing but a stupid kid!
I'd hoped you were a little smarter!
Bro...
You're so fucking stubborn!
Whatever.
Based on all that noise, I doubt he'll survive.
Go to hell!
Bro! Bro!
Answer me!
Bro!
Shut your trap.
I'm... still alive.
Bro!
Bro, your leg...
It's... over.
I'm sorry, Bro.
We got you... into this.
I'm sorry.
Not yet!
Don't give up yet!
He'll come.
I know it!
He'll come... for sure!
Gripping the key he had stolen from Ishihara,
Uncovered ran desperately to the sixth cell.
"If they're dead, there's no point to staying alive."
For the first time in his life, he felt that way from the bottom of his heart.
Sakuragi!
Don't mind me.
Just...
Just save them!
Guys...
Hey, Turtle!
Don't die on me here!
Joe!
Don't you want to see your sister again?
Soldier! Cabbage!
Mario!
You can't die!
If you die here, what've you been fighting for?
Wake up!
Please, wake up, everyone!
Uncovered...
It's all... my fault!
You're so pathetic.
Looks like he's too heavy for you.
Soldier!
Wouldn't you say, Cabbage?
I won't let you take all the glory.
Thanks, Uncovered.
Bro!
Now go!
Just leave me behind!
What're you saying?
I can't just leave you behind!
I won't go down that easily.
Now go before it's too late!
Stop trying to be tough, you idiot!
Bro, you're not acting like yourself.
Yeah.
You can't just give up!
Guys...
We...
We all care about you.
Geez...
You're all...
fucking idiots.
I heard the guys in cell six didn't keep up.
Yeah, me too.
I don't think they could make it out of this fire.
He's dead!
Sakuragi's dead!
Fuck you, Sakuragi!
Hey, look!
No way!
Sa-Sakuragi.
You...
You're all...
I was worried, you know?
Thank God you're alive.
Right, Nomoto?
Right?
Mr. Ishihara.
The fire... started because of...
Here's a warning, Ishihara.
Next time, it'll hurt even more.
The smoke had seared their lungs.
The experience of nearly being burned alive...
fused their seven hearts together like a stone.
The flames scorched away...
all their bad feelings and doubts.
However, Ishihara continues to hunt Bro...
glaring with his eye, like a serpent.
Sign: Shonan Hospital
Miss Koike, can you take care of the rest?
Yes.
Oh, Sakuragi.
You're awake.
Where's Mario?
Is Uncovered all right?
What about Turtle?
Joe?!
Geez, you need to worry about yourself.
You've got burns and internal bleeding, and your left leg is fractured.
You were unconscious for a whole day.
What about them?
Are they okay?
Don't worry.
They're all fine.
So just lay down in your bed.
You know...
They were as desperate as you were just now.
"Please save Bro!"
"We'll give him every drop of blood we have!"
They even went as far as making the doctor promise that he'd save you.
They must've been truly worried about you.
They're so stupid.
Worrying about a piece of shit like me.
Sakuragi...
My... father died...
at my hands.
Hiya, Mario!
I... killed him.
Well, I'm off.
Rokurouta.
Take care of your mother.
I respected and admired my father, who was a soldier.
But after he left for the front lines, he went missing, and then the war ended.
All five of my older brothers were killed in action.
My mother and I tried to live on our own.
I'm heading out, Mom.
Rokurouta.
Take these with you.
I know you go to boxing practice after work.
You have your father's stubbornness.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you, Mom.
I'll... definitely pay you back.
I'll pay you back a hundredfold!
Father?!
My dad had been held in Siberia for eight years,
and when he returned, he'd changed completely.
He didn't work.
He just drowned himself in sake every day,
shouting at my mother and me.
His old self had disappeared.
I couldn't bear to see him like that, so I stayed at boxing practice every day until nightfall.
Then when the date of my debut match had been set...
Don't you ever come here empty-handed again!
What the hell?
Fuck you!
Boxing?!
That's just an imitation of a fight!
Are you making fun of me?!
Father, I just wanted to become a strong man like you and my brothers-
You think you're stronger than me now, you stupid kid?!
What's wrong?
Why won't you fight back?
I won't lose to you just yet!
Why... did you come back?
Did you come back...
to show me how pathetic you are?
You're fucking hopeless!
Rokurouta...
How old are you now?
Take care of your mother.
The next morning...
they found him in the river, dead.
Now that I think about it,
his guilt at surviving the war,
when his five sons had died...
ultimately changed him.
There was no work, and he couldn't blend into the new society.
While he was suffering, I said the worst possible thing to him...
and pushed him over the edge.
It wasn't your fault.
It was!
It was my fault for not trying to understand his pain.
So... I killed him.
I... don't want to lose anyone important again.
What the hell...
That's what he meant by parricide?
Bro!
Ta-da!
We brought some food!
Guys!
Hey, you!
Where in the world did you get that?
I found it on the floor in the room next door.
You've really got sticky fingers.
What, I'm not lying!
It really was on the floor!
There's no way that could happen in the hospital, you idiot!
Why are you calling me stupid? Well?!
Guys!
Listen.
You see, the fire the other day...
I don't want to hear it.
So don't tell me.
You saved us.
That's all there is to it.
Bro...
Guys...
You're crying again?
I'm not crying.
You were crying when you donated blood, too!
No, I wasn't!
What about you?
Your blood type didn't match, and you-
H-H-Hey!
Th-That's supposed to be a secret!
You promised you wouldn't tell!
Okay, guys.
Your time's up.
Come on!
Five more minutes.
Nope.
You're so mean!
Well...
Bro, see ya!
Yeah.
Okay, let's get you some rest.
They're the best.
Don't you think?
They're all...
They're all my friends.
I can trust her with Bro's life.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Dad...
Once he gets better and comes back,
he'll finally be able to leave.
Yeah.
He will, huh.
That day, the six learned of the deep scar in Bro's heart.
Once he is better, he will leave for the streets without a moment's hesitation.
And after that...
it will be their turn.
The six were overwhelmed by hope.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
He pulled me right away.
Just keep on flying!
So far away, but
I'll never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get all warm inside.
a far-off distance.
Shadows creep up.
Peace lasts just an instant.
The seven carve their future dreams into the tree.
Hi, everyone!
How are you?
I'm Satake Uki!
The manga RAINBOW, was written by this man, Mr. Kakizaki Masasumi.
Today we're interviewing Mr. Kakizaki.
Enjoy.
The most important thing I wanted to do was to depict men who were cool.
And I think the anime also does a good job at expressing that.
At first glance, RAINBOW may just seem to be a cheap story,
but I see it as quite authentic.
I think if viewers genuinely enjoy the show, my meaning will be clear.
I've put a lot of my stony spirit into RAINBOW, so I hope you enjoy it.