It's morning already.
Yeah.
We didn't sleep, after all.
It's all because something like that happened.
What should we do?
Today is the day of the "Scare Minorin, Then Prince Charming Will Arrive" battle.
We were the ones who chickened out.
Can we even scare Kushieda?
Shut up.
In order to alter our futures, we must do it.
That's true...
What should we do about scaring Minorin?
What do you mean by "scaring Minorin?"
Ki-
How early, Kitamura.
What are you scheming this early in the morning?
Scheming...
Don't tell me...
You guys were the ones who scared Kushieda yesterday?
So it's true.
Seriously, why are you two doing this?
Don't you feel sorry for Kushieda?
No, it's because...
It's a present.
Present?
Actually, Minorin likes horror more than anything else.
She's like "I love to be scared," so we're planning on leaving her a nice summer experience...
Hey, Kitamura.
I see.
So that's why Kushieda has those avaricious eyes when she's scared!
All right! Count me in too!
Let's give it our all to scare the living hell out of her!
No, uh...
Right, let's get Ami too!
The stupid Chihuahua?
She should be fairly familiar with the surrounding area.
All right, there shall be no delays!
But Kawashima will say no...
Leave it to me.
I'll surely persuade her.
Don't worry!
What now, Ryuuji?
Now that you ask me...
Regardless of what happens...
Seaweed...
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Preparation!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed there's nothing
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
Fireworks
My, my.
I was planning on making breakfast, but someone else beat me to it.
Good morning, Takasu-kun.
Oh...
Hmm? What are you making?
Oh, boxed lunches.
Everyone's going to the seaside for the whole day today.
So that's why you're up so early?
That's no good.
Master, let me help you!
Please order me!
Oh...
Then help me chop the onions.
Yes, my pleasure!
What's the menu today?
Egg and tuna sandwiches.
I'll also make soup with the leftover curry...
Oh, that sounds great!
You're pretty good at it, Kushieda.
Was that a compliment?
The washing up yesterday, too.
You're amazing.
My parents are always working.
When my little brother was at home, I had to make boxed lunches, too.
You have a little brother?
He's an active high school sportsman, Akechi-kun.
It got in...
Hey, are you all right?
My bad.
Takasu-kun?
Oh, I have to peel the apples...
You're really great at cooking, aren't you?
The curry yesterday was scrumptious.
I'm not really that good...
I think it's cool that you do everything so seriously.
I don't think our classmates know this side of you.
It feels somewhat superior...
Whoever becomes your wife will be really happy.
Kushieda!
What is it, Takasu-kun?
About yesterday...
Please keep that a secret from everyone else.
I've never spoken about it to anyone else.
How should I put it?
I really shouldn't have said it...
But thank goodness it was you.
Thanks for listening to me.
Crap!
The clumsy side of you is pretty cute.
Don't call me cute!
I'm just kidding.
So Master, what should I do next?
Let me see...
Should I mix them?
Should I mix them with all my might?
The sun is beautiful today!
I'm taking off!
Minorin is so spirited...
Then we'll act just as planned later.
Huh? Where's Kawashima?
She'll help, right?
Yeah, Ami will lead us to a cave, and we'll set up a trap there.
So we won't be able to do anything if she isn't here?
What is she doing?
I don't know.
I'll get her.
Taiga, hold this for me.
W-Wait a moment!
Here.
I'll hold it.
It must be heavy for a girl, isn't it?
It's okay, I'm all right.
Kawashima, are you here?
Yeah.
Everyone's already left.
Seriously, what are you-
Oh!
I'm totally charmed.
Do you want to check it out, too?
Seriously...
Hey, isn't this scary?
How is my cleavage?
Not bad.
That's it?
Oh, you've seen me in a bikini at school before.
That's not what I mean.
But look, you can take this off.
See?
Put it back on!
Eh? Help me put it back on...
I refuse!
How cold of you!
I won't help you if you continue to act like that.
D-Don't say that...
Hey, why do you want to make Minori-chan happy?
Why, eh...
I won't help if you don't spill!
You have five seconds.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Have you decided yet?
Two.
One...
Zero, I'm not going to help.
Taiga, bring it on!
Come on! Give it all you've got!
It's cold...
What are they doing?
Hey, why?
Because I'm tired.
If you don't come, I won't know where to go inside the cave.
Didn't I draw a map?
I'm sorry, but you're on your own.
Hey...
You're fine with it, right?
It was your decision, after all.
I'm sorry, Takasu.
She suddenly...
It's okay.
I'll go with you.
It'd be difficult by yourself.
But it might look suspicious if we both disappear together...
Don't worry.
I'll manage alone.
I've brainstormed three traps which could each win a creativity prize.
Kushieda is going to be scared really bad!
R-Really?
Hey, Kushieda! Aisaka!
What is it?
I'm going to use the toilet.
Wow, this is good!
Takasu-kun, you're a genius at cooking!
Not really, you helped, too...
Minorin did?
Yeah!
I was the one who mixed the fillings for the egg sandwich!
Oh, are you guys eating without me?
Kitamura-kun, what were you doing?!
How could you say that you were going to the toilet so loudly in front of girls?!
Oh, sorry.
Preparations completed.
Oh...
What are you guys talking about?
Kushieda, it's like this-
Hey, Minori-chan.
There's a alluring cave around the bay.
A cave?!
It's a secret place.
Secret place?!
Let's take a stroll there later on.
Stroll?!
Yeah! I'm so looking forward to it!
Yes!
Is this it?
The secret strolling spot Ami-chan mentioned...
The air is heavy, isn't it...
Totally.
Now, let's go in.
But it looks haunted...
Oh, so we're going to meet some unidentified creatures?
No, it'd be fine if they were living...
You're right.
We should catch them!
Oh, I'm getting excited!
It was correct to have him come with us.
The way he speaks is so cool.
Let's go, Kitamura's Expedition Team!
Let's find the twin-headed snake!
It's dark. It's narrow. I'm scared!
Where have I heard that phrase before?
It's surprisingly big.
Only around here.
Hey, don't look around.
We're not here to just test how brave we are.
Do you understand?
Oh...
We're going to take a step down, be careful.
The first trap.
What?
Fried bean curd.
I see, Kitamura might be smart...
But he's also an idiot.
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun...
Hey, don't you feel cold?
We're very deep in.
No, that's not what I meant.
What's wrong?
I smell ketchup.
Huh?
Wait, what are you doing?
This is...
A blood message...
It says "Ahhhh".
So this is the second one.
He's really an idiot.
D-Don't speak ill of Kitamura-kun!
Don't sigh!
What?
This is...
Hey, what's wrong?
T-T-Takasu-kun, that's...
Well...
It's a woman's hair!
A curse of the heartbroken woman who died after getting lost in this cave!
No!
Let me leave!
Let me go out!
Minorin, calm down.
Nice assist, Takasu.
You planted traps, too, didn't you?
No, umm...
My final trap is 50 meters ahead of this place.
Look forward to it!
Sure...
Kushieda, get a hold of yourself!
Kitamura-kun is really good.
Minorin is super scared now.
It wasn't Kitamura...
It wasn't me either.
Then...
I'm not joking.
Like last night, it's real.
Minorin!
It's too dangerous to be alone, let's hold hands.
Really?
Let's hold hands! Hold hands until we die!
All right!
Now our bodies are warm, let's go!
Umm...
This is so boring.
I'm taking a shortcut out.
Hey, Kawashima, where are you going?
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun, are we going even deeper?
The exit is here.
Right, Ami?
Where's Ami and Takasu?
Ryuuji?
Kawashima, wait for me!
Do you really know the way out?
Of course.
Do you feel insecure after leaving everyone else?
No, I'm just not good...
...with dark places.
Then what will you do if I leave you alone?
What?
Will you be scared?
Will you feel insecure and lonely if I leave you?
You don't want to leave me, do you?
Hey...
You need me.
No, not really...
Do you want to go back to Minori-chan?
I said!
I don't think you suit her.
Wha- It's not like...
The one who's suitable for you is...
What?
Wait, where are we?
Huh?
No way, we're lost?!
Hey, don't joke around...
Why would I joke around like this?!
What should we do...
Hey...
It'll be all right.
Kitamura will come and find us for sure!
Don't worry, I'm here.
I'm sorry.
No, there's no need to apologize.
I was just joking about getting lost.
It's impossible for me to get lost.
Mr. Stupid.
Ouch!
My gosh, your hands are sticky.
It's not the time to joke around!
But you're just like a kid!
I was really scared!
Takasu-kun, you're really helpless.
Not again...
But that's something I don't hate about you.
Just then, I said you didn't suit Minori-chan, right?
I'm serious about it.
Because you are the moon.
What?
Minori-chan is the sun.
If you be with her, you'll just get burned out.
For example, you'll never hit her, right?
You can't become equal just through admiration.
You can only become equal with someone like me...
Just now...
It was Kushieda's voice!
Hey, Takasu-kun!
I'm sorry, I...
It's okay.
Hurry up!
Oh!
Kushieda!
Ryuuji!
Takasu, Ami, are you guys all right?
Kitamura, where's Kushieda?
What happened?
Well...
Kushieda was taken by something...
What do you mean by something?
I don't know.
But there's something here...
Don't tell me that thing took Kushieda...
It's out of batteries.
Takasu, lend me yours.
What was that sound?
A voice?
Kushieda!
I'm coming now!
Hey, Kitamura...
Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun! Kitamura-kun!
What is this?
Everyone, stay together!
We've got to calm down!
I don't care anymore!
Let's go!
Taiga?!
Tai-
Stop!
Kitamura, an accident happened, go save Taiga!
Got it.
Are you all right, Aisaka?
Kita... Kitamura-kun.
Kitamura?
You're late, Akechi-kun.
K-Kushieda?
Correct, I am Kushieda Minori, also known as Minori.
I am the criminal!
Also, he's the accomplice!
The hair in Takasu's room...
The dress in Taiga's room...
And everything else, it was done by us!
I'm sorry.
The methods you used to scare me were too naïve.
I wanted to show you the true way to scare someone.
So you guys knew from the very beginning?
It became obvious after seeing you guys creeping around.
That's why I got Kitamura-kun to help me pay you guys back.
But it was fun.
Thanks!
You're not mad?
I'm not!
Because I love horror!
This is what they call reverse psychology!
If I keep on saying "I'm scared of ghosts, I'm scared of horror."
Eventually, someone will try to scare me.
Then I'll just take it for granted!
Now, this is the end of that.
It lit!
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Today was an amazing day.
It was just a whole lot of trouble.
I still haven't replied to what you said.
I'll feel lonely without you.
Or should I say, it's not the matter of me being lonely...
It's the matter of you being lonely.
I've never considered that for myself.
Then try to think about it, seriously.
Wouldn't that be painful?
If it hurts, then just let it out.
Because we're... Umm...
Equal?
Hey...
Takasu-kun, sometimes you're just too kind.
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
It's the last night, are you having fun?
Kushieda...
You know...
Thanks.
You totally tricked me and scared the living hell out of me.
Whenever I'm with you, I always feel happy.
That's what I should say.
Actually, I had a lot of fun.
The curry was great.
You didn't laugh after hearing my weird speech.
Takasu-kun, you really understand me.
I'm sorry for scaring you.
I wanted to show you ghosts, so I pulled a prank on you.
Show me?
You said you wanted to see ghosts.
Takasu-kun, why did you want to scare me?
That's because...
Taiga told me you were bad with horror.
So you wanted to pull a prank on me?
That can't be it, you'd never do something like that.
Because you always think of making others happy.
Why would the Takasu-kun I know do something like that?
I want to know.
I really don't get it.
I wanted to show you ghosts.
I want you to believe that ghosts exist.
Even if you can't see it, it's too early for you to give up.
That's what I was thinking.
I see.
Takasu-kun, let's go UFO hunting next time.
Not satellites, but the real ones.
After hunting UFOs...
How about the legendary striker snake?
If we continue to search for things I want to see...
If you continue to change my world...
I will...
Kushieda!
A UFO exploded.
It's like I'm dreaming!
I really saw it!
I saw it!
Did a galaxy war begin?
We'll protect the Earth!
The trip fully ends when we arrive home.
So don't let your guards down.
I'm going home directly.
Bye!
Let's visit the supermarket first.
I'm tired, so don't speak to me as if you're a housewife.
Got it.
Hey, there's a sale today.
Shut up.
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
Oubashi High School Cultural Festival・Part 1
The cultural festival.
There will be a band performance to create atmosphere,
a cosplay café to create excitement,
a campfire to create friendship.
Also, wrestling to make people embarrassed by spreading their legs!
What are you thinking of?