The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
My motorcycle engine roars as if it's singing a song.
Blow up louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Blow up louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
No way... was that a trash can from a convenience store?
Anyway, stay away from a guy named Heiwajima Shizuo.
You can't even see logic or reason
when you get violent. I don't like it.
Didn't I tell you never to show your face in Ikebukuro again?
Shizuo, it's not good to fight.
Shut up!
What? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
It would have to be that guy, don't you think?
Heiwajima Shizuo!
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
I got fired just like that!
They want me out of the dorm, too! No notices, nothing!
Without severance pay!
Where am I going to get the money to eat and survive?
The government won't do anything about it either.
That's right... the government!
Shut up...
It's all the government's fault!
And so you got a loan and now you're paying a whore?
It's love!
Mint and I are madly in love with each other!
What?
You're annoying...
I can only see her at the shop, and I don't know her number either.
But still, there's true love between us!
You piss me off!
You only see her at the shop?
You don't know her number either, huh?!
H-Hey! Shizuo!
I'll tell you this now.
True love...
my...
ass!!
I hate violence.
Strongest Man Alive
Did you hear?
Yeah, the wind felt nice while I was racing through town.
Weather was great today, don't you think?
Apparently, a guy by the name of Heiwajima Shizuo has been causing quite a ruckus recently.
Huh?
Yeah, the wind felt nice while I was racing through town.
Heiwajima Shizuo-san... the person who dresses like a bartender, right?
Yeah.
I've heard that he's always been a scary guy, but he's been especially violent as of late.
Word has it that Ikebukuro is like a battlefield right now!
I've seen him before...
but he must really be scary like people say.
I wonder...
But you probably shouldn't judge people simply based on rumors.
Oh, Setton-san, you know him then?
Don't tell me... you're a gangster as well?
That's so scary! Someone, save me!
I'm not!
Geez... how are we going to collect debts if you beat the hell out of all of them?
Sorry.
Something reeks...
Apparently he hasn't been home in two or three days.
This has been happening a lot lately.
I guess it's another one of those rumored manhunts?
Something reeks...
Whoa, dude... someone's injured!
I heard it's the slasher again.
This just happened recently?!
I saw him!
He ran away in that direction!
Geez...
Ikebukuro's started to get quite rowdy again.
Something reeks...
Something definitely reeks.
This entire city.
What is this smell?
Damn, it's annoying!
Hi, Shizuo and Tom-san.
Yo, Simon.
Shizuo?
Please excuse him.
He's been in a bad mood lately.
Age of puberty, I guess?
"The rebellious age" would be more accurate.
Rebel?
Yo, it's been a while.
So he's starring in another film...
Hanejima Yuhei is quite the star.
No, I guess his real name is Heiwajima Kasuka.
Aren't you proud to have him as your younger brother?
Eh, Heiwajima Shizuo-san?
Pardon my rudeness. This is my card.
Writer
Niekawa Shuji
Not only is he handsome, but he's quite the actor as well.
Oh... what was his debut film again?
Ah, right.
"Carmilla Saizo, Vampire Ninja."
Carmilla Saizo
Vampire Ninja
Ever since I saw that, I knew he was going to make it big.
He performed in all the action
scenes without any stuntmen, right?
I've heard mixed rumors as to whether you coached him or not.
I was wondering if I could take some
time tonight to ask for details on that.
Shizuo!
I hate violence.
That's not a lie.
I wasn't like this from the start.
It first began during a fight I had with my little brother, Kasuka.
I snapped over something silly, picked up the fridge and was ready to chuck it at him.
This is mine,
so don't eat it.
Shizuo
I didn't actually think I'd be able to pick it up.
But I just had to do it.
And ever since then...
Shizuo's a loser!
Idiot! Moron!
I just can't restrain myself.
When I get angry, my body moves by itself.
And every time that happens...
You know about the prodigious strength called forth during dire situations, right?
My guess is that you can use that strength at your will.
The reason why the brain saves the body's strength,
is because going over the limit would result in your bones and muscles being destroyed.
But your brain, Shizuo-kun, lets your strength explode.
A mystery of life!
That's astonishing!
Hey, do you mind if I take a look at your body just once-
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Oww! That hurts, Shizuo-kun!
I don't understand the details.
But anyway, I can't suppress my anger.
That results in me destroying everything around me and destroying my own body as well.
I understand that much.
And then...
I stopped trying to restrain myself.
If I can't actually stop myself, there's no point in trying to do so in the first place.
I'll destroy my own body?
Like I care!
My bones were shattered countless times.
And each time that happened, I got stronger.
Shinra's explanation for this was...
Whatever! It's a drag to think about!
Anyway, I kept on getting stronger!
But then...
Hey...
You're always injured, aren't you?
Are you okay?
Wait here for just a second.
Here.
You need to drink milk to build your bones.
Here's one for you, too.
Thank you.
I've gone and done it again.
When I realized it, I...
Morning!
Why did I become like this?
I was from an ordinary household.
I didn't go through any trauma in my childhood or anything.
Then why...?
Kasuka...
What?
Aren't you... afraid of me?
Not really.
It was around the time when I entered Raira Academy.
Opening commemoration!
You get a discount!
The store is fresh, and so are the fish!
I feel like it's fate that brought us
together in the same school again.
Shut up.
How has your body been feeling?
Oh yeah, can I perform a checkup on your
body as a commemoration of our reunion?
Is that a no?
Can I at least take a sample of your blood?
Selty!
What happened last night?
I was worried since you didn't come home.
Were you looking for your head again?
That's what you say, but are you sure you didn't start dating some guy-
Selty...
Come on, don't stab my solar plexus like-
Let me introduce you to someone, Selty.
I felt a strange aura from her.
This is my friend, Heiwajima Shizuo-kun.
I don't know how to describe it...
Shizuo-kun, this is Selty. She lives with me.
Just felt something odd...
She's my future-
Raira Academy Entrance Ceremony
I just remembered something I've been trying to forget...
Yeah, that's right...
This was around the time when that
damned flea showed himself in front of me.
That guy...
Orihara Izaya!
Ever since I saw him...
His name's Orihara Izaya, and we went to the same middle school.
Well, he's not exactly a great guy, but...
I didn't like him.
Let me take that back; he's an asshole.
That hurt, Shinra.
No, no, I didn't mean it in a bad way.
I don't like you.
Oh?
That's a shame.
I'm pretty sure we'd be able to have lots of fun together.
Shut up.
Don't be like that, Shizuo-kun.
See? Aren't we having fun?
On the day we met, Izaya and I had a deathmatch.
There was no reason for it other
than the fact that I didn't like him.
But...
Are you all right?!
Don't worry, he's fine.
He's pretty built.
I-Is he really all right?
Yes, trust me.
Thank you very much.
Shit...
I messed up.
Oh?
What a coincidence! Izaya's also here.
Wait, why are you unharmed?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
And things really started to get annoying from the next day.
I'll fucking kill you!
Bastards I don't even know started picking fights with me one by one.
I didn't do a thing!
I just wanted to live in peace!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Dammit, they piss me off!
Annoying... Annoying... Annoying...
So annoying...!
I know.
Die!!
It was Izaya.
He was the one who was pulling the strings.
Raira Academy Graduation Ceremony
When I found out about that...
Izaya!
I should have killed him back then!
Dammit!
And after we all graduated from Raira...
What do you think? Does it look good on me?
The idiot was up to something new...
And that damned flea was doing something with the Yakuza.
Either way, things were quiet for a while.
On the other hand, I was...
And like that, for some reason...
Welcome.
Hey, did you see him?!
He can't be real!
It's the actor...!
Hanejima Yuhei!
Yo, Kasuka.
What's up?
Bartender uniform?
You shouldn't change your occupation so often.
I bought you a lot of them so that
you can continue your job forever.
Thanks.
Well, I guess I'll try my best.
But then...
D-Dammit!
Izaya!
I fell into that damned flea's trap.
Then he disappeared from Ikebukuro.
They immediately found me innocent, and I was discharged.
But...
Sorry, I couldn't keep our promise.
Don't drink and drive!
It's a promise between you and I!
Oh, if it isn't Shizuo.
Tom-san was my senior during middle school,
and he wanted me to help him with his job as a debt collector.
Well, in other words, I was a bodyguard.
I wasn't enthusiastic about it at first.
But then...
You don't actually have to force
yourself to get violent with them.
No one from Ikebukuro is going to fight back after hearing the name "Heiwajima Shizuo."
...he motivated me with those words.
But since then, Kasuka's been really busy with work and I haven't seen him since.
I wonder if he's mad at me...
What's all this about?
Yuhei!
Yuhei-san! Please, this way!
I don't know why, but I felt better after that.
And so,
I'm still working with Tom-san to this day.
My debt is overdue?
I don't really get all this complicated stuff.
We're easygoing outcasts, after all.
Yeah.
School, society... it's all their fault!
The unfathomable depths of the human mind!
Hey...
I told you, we don't understand.
Go away, old man.
This old man has a job to do.
Huh? What's with those eyes?
H-Hey!
What's with those clothes?!
You moron, he's a butler.
You guys don't know who Shizuo is?
Who the hell is that?
Some celebrity?
Really, Mr. Butler?
Look what you made me do!
Could you please bring me another glass?
Please, Mr. Butler?
You guys must really be outcasts to not know Shizuo in Ikebukuro.
My clothes...
The clothes I got from my little brother...
Even then, I don't like violence.
I want to become stronger.
Strong enough so that I can suppress my own anger.
I don't know why, but I feel a lot better after talking to you.
Hey, I'm glad.
For some reason, I've been feeling really irritated lately.
I actually heard something about that, so I was worried about you.
Oh.
Sorry I made you worry.
You must really love your little brother.
Shut up.
Later.
I want to distance myself from
others, but I can't stand being alone.
That's why I unconsciously seek attachment to others.
Like Tom-san and Kasuka.
She and I are alike.
I'm sure she also...
Yo.
Shizuo!
Are you done with puberty?
Then it's time for you to eat sushi.
Sushi is good. It's the best!
Maybe next time.
Izaya...
Now I get it.
I knew something reeked...!
It was you!
What is he doing here?
What's he planning to do in this city now?!
Damn you!
I-ZA-YA!!
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My dear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My dear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Life is Transient
I dream.
I have the same dream over and over again.
I wonder if I'm asleep while my head is awake,
and if the eyes on my head are
closed while I'm here, wide awake.
Next time: Life is Transient.