Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Summer time!
Beach time!
So Teacher and Cousin Yui are in
charge of supervising and driving today.
Gotcha!
But you know...
The two of you have a lot of free time.
Summer
Events
Sorry to impose on your day off.
It's nothing.
Don't sweat it.
Narumi-san...
You're an officer in the traffic safety department, right?
That's right.
I know all there is to know about traffic law.
He passed me.
Bastard...
Wa-
Hey!
What happened to safety first?
Cousin Yui goes wild once her hand's on the stick.
Guess we'll have to sacrifice Kagami and Tsukasa.
Really...
Isn't she a cop?
Huh?
That's odd.
I lost sight of them.
Teacher, that's the wrong way!
That's a one-way street!
I messed up big time!
I didn't expect them both to fail!
That car's incredible!
Who is it?!
They both have perfect braking and drifting!
It's practically on top of the FDI!
And it's got better acceleration!
It's practically touching the guard rail!
The point of attack will come...
...in the five consecutive hairpin curves ahead!
It's speeding up!
Did the brakes die?!
Incredible!
What's with the (bleep) D-like driving?!
Nanako-san...
You're really good...
...at driving...
Yeah?
You see...
I get sick whenever I'm in a car.
That's why I brought medicine...
But I didn't feel sick at all with you at the wheel.
Like!
I don't have time to be talking to you!
[Sign: To keep our city clean, fireworks are banned between 10 PM and 7 AM.]
Well...
How about we find a hotel?
The clear sky is perfect weather for a day at the beach.
Seriously...
I was getting worried there yesterday.
I'll put on my swimsuit before we go!
You're such a child...!
Konata-san!
Are you seriously wearing that?
And like...
I've never heard of someone wearing a school swimsuit at this age.
Some people have special needs, Kagamin.
Izumi
H-H-How old is that swimsuit?!
Besides...
Why are you wearing a swim ring when you're good at sports stuff?
The ocean doesn't exist solely for wasting effort on swimming.
You should take it leisurely.
Leisure time.
Plus, to meet those special needs...
...you have to wear a school swimsuit with a swim ring.
People with special needs...
...won't be coming to the beach.
Watermelon cracking is the usual event in manga and anime...
...but it doesn't happen much in reality.
I've seen it before...
...but people probably feel like it's a waste.
That's true...
If you blow up a watermelon with a gun...
...you'll end up covered in watermelon.
You watch too much anime.
Have you ever played it before, Miyuki-san?
Since you're rich.
I haven't.
Well, on second thought...
It doesn't seem like something rich people would do.
You have a point.
It was obvious...
...but I guess your eyes don't end up like in manga.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
But y'know, yeah?
A girls only babysitting trip to the beach at this age...
We're some lonely, single girls, huh?
You're mistak-
But yeah...
If the alternative is resorting to bringing something like that...
...I'm all for a girls only trip.
No, I'm...
They're telling people to marry late these days.
Might as well take our time and choose well.
You're mistaken.
My husband just happens to be busy working far away.
I'm already married!
The beach is a mecca for flirting...
...but it doesn't apply to us, huh?
Well, it's less annoying this way.
Besides, this thing...
...probably makes people think
we're sisters here on a family trip.
And a one-two.
What's up?
Well...
It kind of feels icky to sit down when I'm still wet.
I understand how you feel.
Then you can use an air chair.
You're pretty extreme.
Yakisoba
Yakiudon
Okonomiyaki
Ramen
Curry
Tokoyaki
Ikayaki
Fried Chicken
What is it?
My neck's tired.
Really now.
Just as expected!
What are you so happy about?
Because I got something straight out of a storybook beach house.
Look at how the curry is sauce and nothing else.
This is true beach house fare!
That's true.
Usually, you wouldn't be willing to eat something like this...
...but here, it actually tastes good!
The beer they got at the beach is the best!
Generic beer isn't too bad once in a while.
I find it odd that they're charging
300 yen for a single frankfurter.
Yeah!
Maybe they're only half-cooked.
But we'll eat it anyway.
I actually like how their chicken is...
...dripping in grease and over-spiced.
And this plain fried soba...
...is quite nice.
But still...
You couldn't stand eating this stuff at home!
Konata's touched.
Hey.
Does this food really warrant so much praise?
Not really.
Not enough to make you run towards the ocean in a loincloth.
Is that another anime reference?
Drank too much...
No choice.
Let's stay another night.
What about work, Cousin Yui?
I also took tomorrow off.
It's fine!
I-It's freezing...
You're such a kidder, Teacher.
Why is your hair all squeaky...
...after you've been in the ocean?
Dunno.
Maybe it has to do with salt or something.
Right, Miyuki?
That's right.
The main reason would be salt content and UV rays.
What's so bad about it?
Isn't your hair always getting hit by UV rays?
Well...
It'll take a little while...
...to explain that.
In that case...
The reason your hair is damaged by a trip to the beach...
...would be the adhesion of salt
from seawater and the sea breeze...
...which absorbs the moisture from your hair...
...which now suffers from exposure to strong UV rays.
Also...
Whenever you are exposed to strong UV rays outdoors...
...your melanin levels will fade...
...and your hair will become light brown.
And if residual quantities of salt or chlorine remain in your hair...
...they may result in the discoloration of your hair.
The usual reason for hair damage in summer...
...would be UV rays and residual substances.
The above factors cause damage to the cuticles.
When exposed to strong UV rays...
...the cysteine molecules found in strong hair are broken up...
Look! Look!
Timotei!
What's that?
I wonder how other people would see us.
Not sure...
Nothing to talk about...
Probably sisters or cousins?
Probably.
That's all you have to say?
Cousin Yui!
Timotei!
I remember that!
I used to do it!
Yes!
That's the response I wanted!
How old are you?
Mandom!
Cut out the geezer jokes.
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
I just triggered a flag.
What are you talking about?
This is where the event starts!
In order to see both paths...
...don't forget to save often before a split!
No exceptions!
Picture complete.
Perfect!
Bring it on!
No idea what's going on.
Anyway...
...you being like this is why...
Why...?
Why nobody came to hit on us.
Y-You're the one who brought it up in the first place!
I could really care less about that stuff.
So Kagami wanted someone to hit on her.
N-No...
No!
Damn it!
I missed it!
What is it?
I was wondering what you do about hair.
Mine's pretty smooth, so I don't do anything.
What about you, Sis?
M-Me?!
I guess I'm normal.
Actually, today was kinda dangerous.
What?
Well...
You know...
Almost happened...
Oh, that?
I see.
Good thing then.
You were okay?
No problem at all.
Mine ended a week ago.
The timing was perfect.
It really sucks when that happens.
You're right.
It would be sad if you were the
only one who couldn't go in the water...
But using that would be a little...
Yeah.
Makes you think twice.
I've never used one.
That was a candid conversation.
Wh-What about you?
Don't tell me...
What's with that look?
Nothing.
Apparently, this is a true story...
A photo software wholesaler...
...was on his way home from work...
...and got on the bus as usual late at night...
His house was...
...at the end of the bus line.
So...
As more and more passengers got off...
...eventually, he was the only person left on the bus...
The driver thought that nobody was left on the bus...
...and...
...sang "DANZEN! Futari wa ***Cure" at the top of his lungs!
Just a rumor I heard.
It was nothing...
What a relief...
I was so scared.
I'm also...
I'm Sukekiyo.
Where'd you get that mask from?!
Then good night.
Yes.
Good night.
The Inugami Family!
It's so much fun to scare you.
Go to sleep already.
Hey!
We're going!
Okay!
I don't have anything interesting to say.
I'm Tsukasa.
Sis!
What is it?
I was scared!
A girl just took a step towards becoming an adult, Kagamin.
Comp Festival is a big hit.
'Cause Japanese people are suckers for limited edition stuff.
If the words "limited edition" are enough to boost sales...
...they could just add it to everything.
That would cheapen the value.
So I went and asked.
Yes.
Clean your room before break's over.
Whoa, flashback!
These textbooks are from middle school.
Sis!
Look at this album!
Isn't this picture of Dad a little risqué?
Right?
That's when I started wondering about Dad's thing.
You look like you're having fun...
...but are you getting any cleaning done?
Um...
Hey.
Do you want these clothes?
If you don't need them, I'll take them.
Then I'll leave them here.
Thanks.
Hey.
Do you want this?
Then I guess I'll take it.
What about this?
This?
Wait!
Don't tell me I'm her trash can...
You end up looking through photo albums and stuff instead.
I know what you mean.
If any old magazines are lying around, I start reading them.
That's right.
Oh, yeah. What about Tsukasa?
She doesn't throw anything away, so it takes a while.
She's still at it.
Tsukasa's always slow to act.
On the other hand, Kagami's always trigger happy.
Why is your impression of me...
...so aggressive?
You saved your textbooks from middle school.
You don't have anything like that?
I left them with my memories at my old school.
No, take them home.
You're causing trouble for the school.
I finally finished cleaning.
I don't think that I'll ever use this again...
...but then I remember how I just used it...
...so I can't throw it away.
Yeah.
There really are people who keep everything.
Tsukasa seems the type.
You seem like someone who even throws away useful stuff.
Seeing as how you ditched your textbooks.
Miyuki.
Go have your teeth taken care of...
...before school starts up again.
I understand...
...but I just don't like it.
Well, I would feel bad about forcing you to go.
If you can't go...
...I'll have him come.
A visit from the dentist.
P-Please wait!
Good lucky!
We've already burst into the sixth episode of Lucky Channel!
I hope that you've all become familiar with this corner.
I'm Akira Kogami!
Lame!
You say something?
It appears that newbie Shiraishi-kun
isn't used to the job and is a nervous wreck.
I'm scared...
So scared...
You're all making his heart race.
Whad did I do wrong?
We went to the mountains 'cause Akira-sama said so.
I hope he gets used to the job soon.
Yeah.
Went to the beach, too.
And he better watch how he talks to the
veterans around here or else something may happen.
I'm doing everything I can to make this show funnier!
Yeah...
The gum was hard...
I just hate that!
But it was fifty-four pieces.
Today we'll introduce a key Lucky Star character...
Fifty-four pieces in my mouth!
But I still worked hard!
Konata Izumi-san!
What else will I have to do?
Hey.
Stop blubbering.
Why me?!
Let's see...
Konata Izumi-san.
Seventeen years old.
Her hobbies are gaming, watching anime, and reading.
Uh...
According to the data...
...she always checks out new shows and books.
She games up a storm on weekends.
So she's a geek.
Uh...
Looks like it...
Come up with something quick!
By geek, you mean that, right?
People who watch House Classics, right?
The ones who watch A Dog of Flanders and cry, right?
Which decade of geek are you talking about?
Are you doing your homework?!
Get with the program!
N-No, uh...
Well I guess A Dog of Flanders had the
whole cutesy, appealing character to soothe you.
But people these days prefer a girl like me!
Cute as a button and pure as snow!
You know what I mean?
If I look right, so do you!
If I look left, so do you!
When you line up for my concert the
night before, you can't take a shower!
That may cause hygienic problems...
...but you still want to see me!
That determination burns as hot as the sun in wait of my arrival!
Until the bandana around your head is drenched!
You know...
They're still customers.
When I'm doing handshakes afterward, they won't stop talking.
Yapping away during MC without reading the crowd.
Doesn't that just blow?
I'm only here because of them.
I have to work hard for them.
Y'know?
Is that how it is...
You'll know soon enough.
How hard it is to be an idol...
Once you've been through the
good and bad, you'll see how it really is.
Can't do anything about fans or clients you hate...
Perfect timing!
Hey, everybody!
Do you know who Konata-san is now?
Then we'll see you on next week's Lucky Channel!
Bye-bee!
Uh...
You didn't even introduce Konata...
More like you introduced geeks.
A-Akira-sama?
You okay?
Do it.
Understood!
What the correspondent saw then was...
Not funny.
Kage sure is awesome.
We get the idea.
So did you order a song, Tsukasa?
I did.
Tsukasa-san singing will be quite refreshing.
I wonder if I can sing it well.
What are you going to sing, Miyuki?
I really don't know many songs...
It's quite embarrassing.
So she went with this, huh?
Go for it, Tsukasa-san!
Tomorrow will be a special, SPECIAL DAY!
A once-in-a-year CHANCE!
OH DARLING!
L!
O!
V!
E!
Lovely!
Tsukasa!
OH DARLING!
Hey, now.
L!
O!
I LOVE YOU!
V!
E!
Lovely!
Sayuri!
Who's that?
Everybody's happy about the CARNIVAL!
I'm gonna make his HEART mine!
OH BABY!
Her name isn't Sayuri Kuninama, right?
So who is she already?!
What member number was she?
Oh, when I give to you...
...sweet, sweet chocolate of love.
I still won't stand out.
Shut up already!
So I'm gonna resort to my last card!
VALENTINE DAY KISS!
With a ribbon tied on.
Sha-la-la-la!
Wonderful...
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Kagami.
When you try to get rid of a hanging nail...
...and give it a little tug...
...but then you end up pulling off too much...
...it really hurts, doesn't it?
Also...
...there's the timing for ripping off a scab.
When it starts to itch...
...and you're thinking that it's about time...
...so you pick it off bit by bit.
And just when you're like everything is good...
...it still ends up bleeding!
It leaves some serious damage.
Next time:
Image.
「Image」
Look forward to next time!