[KUREHA giggles]
[SUMIKA] They're so beautiful
when they're blooming,
don't you think?
[KUREHA]
Huh?
I think we can be
together here, okay?
It's pretty private,
so no one should see us.
I don't really care about that.
It's not like we're doing
anything wrong, you know.
Yeah, but--
But what I do care about
is being with you.
That's all I want.
[SUMIKA gasps]
[KUREHA] Sumika, I will
never back down on my love.
[SUMIKA]
Oh, Kureha. I...
I won't either!
[BEAR growling]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Kuma shock!
[STUDENT A screams]
[STUDENT A] A bear!
There's a bear on the loose!
[BOTH gasp]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[sirens wailing]
[KATYUSHA grunts]
No way.
A bear got over the
Wall of Severance?
What do we do?
[KUREHA]
Don't worry, Sumika. I'm here.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
[GINKO] From the
beginning, we hated you,
but also, we loved you
from the beginning, as well.
All we wanted was to become
true friends with you.
So, we had to cross the wall.
[GINKO, LULU]
Yurikuma!
Yurikuma Arashi!
[LULU]
Growl, growl!
Once upon a time, at the
far reaches of space,
the minor planet
Kumaria exploded.
The fragments of
Kumaria that remained
became a meteor swarm that
rained down upon the Earth.
That swarm made the world's
bears rise up together as one!
Then, they all started
attacking humans!
Like, who could've seen
that coming, right?
The humans then decided to
build the Wall of Severance
in an attempt to
drive all the bears,
like us, away from their world.
But guess what!
Silly old man-made rules
don't work on bears!
Do the math, humans! Growl!
We are bears.
We can't help that!
Bears eat people.
That's kind of, like, our thing!
And so...
[YURIIKA]
Everyone, starting today
you'll have some new friends.
This is Ginko Yurishiro
and Lulu Yurigasaki.
Let's give them a warm welcome!
[GINKO]
Growl!
We supposedly transferred here,
but they don't know what we are
because we're
disguised as humans!
[LULU giggles]
[LULU] Looks like nobody
can tell we're bears so far.
[chuckles]
[LULU] So many girls
for Lulu to pick from.
Sniff, sniff.
It's heaven! The whole room
smells delicious, growl!
This is perfect!
Lulu is going to work hard
so she can eat lots of girls!
You too, right, Ginko?
Oh, have you met
Ginko Yurishiro, yet?
She's a bear too, of course!
She's Lulu's darling
and Lulu loves her
and loves her to bits
and bits and bits!
[LULU giggles]
Now then, girls,
I'm sure most of you have
heard the news already,
but, unfortunately, a couple of
bears were sighted this morning
on the roads very
close to this school.
I realize this is a shock.
We considered it
unthinkable for bears
to cross the Wall of Severance
and enter the human world.
The warning has
since been lifted,
but you still need
to be very careful.
Even inside the school,
make sure you're never alone.
You should always have
a friend with you.
[GINKO]
There she is.
I've finally found her.
Yeah, I like how
that girl smells.
I bet she's delicious.
Slurp.
[gasps]
Sumika?
--[footsteps]
--[KUREHA panting]
[SUMIKA]
Hey, Kureha?
What do you like
in your lunch box?
[KUREHA]
My lunch box? Why?
[SUMIKA] Well, I like chikuwa
fried in seaweed tempura.
I was just wondering
what you preferred.
[KUREHA] Let's see, I guess
spaghetti, and shiokara.
[SUMIKA]
Shiokara? Seriously?
[KUREHA]
Is that weird?
[SUMIKA giggles]
[KUREHA]
What?
[SUMIKA] It's just,
you like what old men eat.
[KUREHA]
Old men?
[SUMIKA]
Yeah.
[KUREHA]
That's not very nice.
I mean, yeah, maybe it smells a
little when I open my lunch box,
but so what?
[SUMIKA]
I love it.
[KUREHA]
What?
[SUMIKA] I don't care if you've
got the palette of an old man.
I love you anyway.
I love you so much.
And I always will.
[gasps]
Sumika?
Sumika!
Kureha? Hey.
[gasps]
[SUMIKA]
Is something wrong?
[KUREHA]
No. I just, uh--
[stomach growls]
Oh no, did you not
get to eat lunch?
Uh...
--No.
--[footsteps]
[SUMIKA]
Here.
[gasps]
Let's eat together.
We can each take a half.
[giggles]
[KUREHA] There's chikuwa
in this roll, isn't there?
[SUMIKA] Yeah, but it's
not fried in tempura.
[KUREHA giggles]
[SUMIKA]
What's so funny?
[KUREHA]
Nothing.
You know,
I think we should eat here
every day from now on.
[SUMIKA]
You mean it? Really?
[KUREHA]
Yeah, I wanna eat with you.
[SUMIKA gigles]
[SUMIKA]
I think food tastes better
when we're together anyway.
Do you think that, too?
[KUREHA]
I do.
Grrrrrr.
Growl, growl, growl!
Lulu is practically
starving right now.
Oh, she smells so yummy.
I wanna eat that girl.
Growl, growl.
You are such a glutton, Ginko,
but that's okay because
Lulu will always love you!
You can sink your teeth in Lulu.
Anywhere you'd like. Go on,
you can even do it now.
Oh, Lulu can't believe
she's saying this. Ha!
Lulu feels so vulnerable
when she's around you, Ginko.
[scissors snipping]
[KUREHA]
The storm chased us down.
This is only the beginning.
A warning that it'll start
with what's most precious.
Invisible Storm will destroy
whatever is in its path,
until we're worn
away into nothing.
[SUMIKA] Kureha, I'll never
back down on my love, either.
[KUREHA]
What?
[SUMIKA] You said it earlier,
that you wouldn't give up on me.
Well, I won't give
up on you, either.
I won't give up
on love. Our love.
--[GINKO] Grrrr.
--Growl, growl.
Lulu's so hungry she doesn't
think she can take much more!
Grrrrr.
Grow, growl. I cannot get
over that delicious smell.
Growl, growl.
[BOTH growling]
[KUREHA]
I still feel the same way.
I won't back down. I promise
I'll protect you, Sumika.
I believe you.
[MITSUKO]
I knew it.
[BOTH gasp]
[MITSUKO] I had a feeling
you'd been caught up
in the Invisible Storm, too.
You have, haven't you, Kureha?
[KUREHA]
Mitsuko.
It's cruel to cut down flowers.
Especially when
they're in full bloom.
It's the Invisible Storm.
It destroy beautiful,
kind things first.
Yes, but this time what it's
done has made up my mind.
I can't just sit here and keep
letting these things happen!
Kureha, Sumika,
let's stop the storm.
We can take a stand together!
I know I'm the
class representative,
but I'm ashamed of myself
for not having taken a
stand against it already.
Sumika, I'm so sorry.
Do you think you can
ever forgive me?
For what? There's
nothing to forgive.
Thank you for saying that.
And, you know, I think we
could be the best of friends.
I bet we can stop
the Invisible Storm.
As long as we're working
together, why couldn't we?
But I think we should go
home for the day now.
There's still that bear warning.
I say early tomorrow
morning we come back here.
Then, the flowerbed
can get fixed.
I don't mind helping you at all.
[SUMIKA gasps]
[SUMIKA]
Oh no! Your hand.
No, it's okay. This just
means I'm one of you.
And that we're friends!
[SUMIKA giggles]
[ALL giggling]
[ALL gasp]
Who did that?
[LULU] ♪ Lulu's so happy.
She got to eat a lily. ♪
♪ Lulu wants to eat that girl! ♪
♪ Who do you mean
by "that girl"? ♪
♪ Lulu wants to eat that girl. ♪
♪ Who do you mean
by "that girl"? ♪
♪ Let's go on trial, now!
Yeah, let's go, yeah! ♪
[growling]
[REIA] Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
[KUREHA]
Yep! Guess what, Mom?
We ate snacks together at lunch!
[REIA]
Great! Were they yummy?
[KUREHA]
Mm-hmm!
Everything tastes better when
I get to eat them with her.
[REIA chuckles]
[REIA] Aw, you really love
her, don't you, sweetie?
[KUREHA]
Yeah, I do!
Yes, and that's why this time,
the one I love will be safe.
[KUREHA] I'll protect
her with my own hands!
I'll never forgive the bears!
I'll ruin them. Every one!
[COP A]
This is Unit 103.
We're at the flowerbed
in the Arashigaoka
High School courtyard.
Lots of bear prints here.
And bloodstains.
Looks like there was a vic.
We found her effects
at the scene.
She may be a student.
We're still searching
the area, though.
[MITSUKO] Yes, we were
supposed to meet here.
We were... we were gonna come
early and fix up the flowerbed.
[VOICEMAIL]
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic
voice mail system.
The mobile customer you are
trying to reach is currently...
[KATYUSHA] I heard they
found a shoe on the ground.
[ERIKO] They did? You
know what that means.
[KONOMI]
Apparently she came in early
to try to fix up that flowerbed.
Oh, gosh! It's so
hard to believe!
It's really all her
fault for going alone.
To survive, we need to
make sure we have friends!
[KATYUSHA] Yeah, you're right.
There's no other way.
[ERIKO] Uh-huh. The next
Invisible Storm's coming.
[ERIKO] She's to blame since
she wasn't being Invisible.
To the bears,
we're just weak prey.
We have to stay with
the herd. No matter what.
[KATYUSHA]
Exactly.
The mood of the herd is
what's most important.
[KUREHA]
It's not true. It can't be!
It's not true.
I refuse to believe
Sumika was eaten!
[gasps]
Hello? Uh! Sumika?
[VOICE]
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from
the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true,
go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
[KUREHA] What do you mean?
Is Sumika okay?
[VOICE] Give yourself
over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
The time for judgment
has come. Growl, growl.
[growling]
[KUREHA]
Sumika!
[clattering]
[gasps]
Sumika! Give her back to me!
[growling]
[roaring]
[whimpers]
[BOTH growling]
[whimpering]
[GINKO roars]
[KUREHA yelps]
[screaming]
[GINKO, LULU]
We want to eat that girl!
We want to eat her
right this minute!
[VOICE]
This court is now in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
The door has opened,
so enter what we consider
the land of enlightenment
for all living things.
Yes, even human and bear.
We shall now pass judgment for
the sake of humans and bears!
Life Sexy!
[LIFE COOL]
For humans and bears.
Life Cool!
[LIFE BEAUTY]
For humans and bears.
Life Beauty!
[LIFE SEXY]
Let the Yuri Trial begin.
Defendant bears,
do you admit that you are,
in fact, criminal bears?
Growl.
Yeah, but we can't
be held responsible
because we're so
hungry all the time.
And we won't back
down on our love ever.
Growl, growl.
[LIFE COOL]
Your Honor!
Humans and bears have a
barrier separating them
called the Wall of Severance,
and it is not to be crossed.
The defendants have
crossed it anyway,
infiltrating the
world of the humans.
This is obvious and
blatant overeating.
Therefore, they are guilty!
Sparkle!
Your Honor, the only
thing blatant here
is the prosecutor's hostile
attitude towards bears!
[LIFE SEXY] Counsel, was that
intended to be an objection?
I mean, yeah, even bears
have to eat to live.
That is the way of the universe.
Tell me, do you seriously
expect these poor bears
to starve to death?
But, Your Honor, if we
admit the defendants' appeal,
we can expect more
human lives to be lost!
[LIFE BEAUTY]
Objection!
He's showing undue
favor toward humans!
[LIFE SEXY]
Sustained.
Keep in mind, this court
must act as a scale
that weighs both
worlds impartially.
For that is sexy!
Shaba-da-doo!
[LIFE COOL]
Uh!
Sparkle. Heh.
Growl, thank you.
So, that means we've got
permission to eat her,
right, Your Honor?
Objection!
Your Honor, please.
We ask you to grant the
defendants a Love Judgment.
[LIFE SEXY]
Very well.
Defendant bears, I ask you,
do you want to be invisible?
Or, would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat.
Bring on the humans!
[BOTH]
Growl, growl!
[LIFE SEXY] I am now ready
to declare the verdict.
[LIFE SEXY]
Yuri approved!
[GINKO]
Growl, growl, growl!
Yuri approved!
[LULU]
Growly, growl, growl, growl,
growl, growl, growl!
Kureha, I, Ginko,
am going to eat you.
[KUREHA] I can't find
what I'm searching for.
[KUREHA]
I can't find it.
I've been searching
in the Invisible Storm.
[GINKO]
Searching for what?
[LULU]
Searching for it where?
[KUREHA] Give it to me!
The Promise Kiss!
[gasps]
[MITSUKO] Thank goodness
you're finally awake!
[KUREHA]
Mitsuko, hey. Where are we?
[MITSUKO]
The nurse's office.
[KUREHA]
What? Why?
[MITSUKO]
Something happened.
We found you passed
out on the roof.
[KUREHA gasps]
[KUREHA] What about
Sumika? Where is she?
We don't know.
She hasn't been found yet.
Oh, no. He said the bears on
the roof would give her back!
Sumika! She must have
been up there, too!
Please, calm down.
When we found you, we didn't
see anyone else up there.
Just me? But how?
[MITSUKO]
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go get you
something hot to drink.
Was that just a dream?
No, it had to have been real.
[KUREHA]
Oh, Sumika, be okay, please.
[LULU, GINKO]
Chomp, chomp. Munch, munch.
What's that sound?
Is someone over there
vandalizing the flowerbed again?
[LULU, GINKO]
Chomp, chomp. Munch, munch.
Chomp, chomp. Munch,
munch. Chomp, chomp.
[LULU] Growl! Human girls
really do taste good!
They're delicious!
[GINKO]
I'll eat them.
I don't care if it's
a crime. Growl, growl.
I won't allow it.
No one can wreck my love.
[gasps]
[MITSUKO] Those bears.
They're eating a girl!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Shock.
Kuma shock!
[MITSUKO]
Those are the transfer students!
Oh, I get it.
They've transformed, they're
only pretending to be human!
They're really bears!
[GINKO]
Slurp.