By my third Command Spell, I order you again.
No!
Saber, destroy the Grail.
How could I have understood him if three
commands were all that existed between us?
I couldn't even comprehend the hearts
of those who had served right beside me.
Perhaps this is all a punishment for a king who couldn't understand others...
Th-That's...
Ridiculous...
That's ridiculous!
Kiritsugu...
What's wrong, Ilyasviel?
Um, I had a really scary dream.
I dreamed that I became a cup...
...and seven really big lumps appeared inside me...
It felt like they'd tear me apart.
It was really scary, but I couldn't run away...
Then I heard Justica-sama's voice.
A big black hole opened up over my head.
And then, the world burned.
Kiritsugu saw it happen and cried.
Mommy, is Kiritsugu okay?
Is he alone and really scared?
It's okay.
He's doing his best for you.
He'll make sure our prayers are realized,
so you'll never have to be scared again.
Yeah, you're right.
You must be right.
Kiritsugu always works hard.
I'm sure he'll come home soon after finishing his important work.
Hey, Sakura-chan...
Uncle?
I've come to save you.
Everything's okay now.
Let's go.
Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura!
Kariya-kun.
Aoi-san.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
Thank you.
Daddy Kariya!
He's so stupid.
That's what happens when you disobey Grandpa.
Where am I?
You're a difficult man to look after.
Digging you from the rubble was quite troublesome.
Gilgamesh, what happened?
Who can say?
The mud spat me back out.
It seems to be the will of the gods that I return to this age to rule the world.
So you've achieved true incarnation?
Infuriatingly enough.
I can't believe we fought over that thing and thought it would grant wishes.
This play remained a farce to the very end.
I was shot...
I have no heartbeat...
Did you somehow heal me, Gilgamesh?
Who can say?
You did look like you were dead.
You and I are connected by the contract.
The moment I gained true incarnation within that mud,
perhaps you too were trapped in some sort of absurdity.
You're saying it gave me life?
All the other Servants are gone, which means we have won the Grail.
Kirei, behold the results.
If the Grail really does grant the victor's wish...
Kotomine Kirei, this view is what you most desired.
What?
What am I?
What evil.
What cruelty.
This is my wish?
This destruction and tragedy?
This is my pleasure?
Could Kotomine Risei's seed really have
birthed something so twisted and corrupt?
Impossible.
It's impossible!
What's this?
Could my father really have sired a dog?
Are you satisfied, Kirei?
No, not yet.
This isn't enough.
Yes, it's true that I've finally found
the answer in my life of questioning.
But the problem solving itself was bypassed, and the solution was simply given to me.
Just what can I accept about any of this?
The formula that yielded this strange answer
should exist somewhere as a principle with clarity.
No...
It has to.
I must question.
I must search.
I must use the rest of my life to understand it.
You never cease to amuse me.
Very well.
Your questions would slay the gods themselves.
I, Gilgamesh, shall watch you in your quest for truth.
Angra Mainyu...
I will reach it again and see it to the end next time.
Its birth.
Its proof of existence.
Emiya... Kiritsugu?
I accept your challenge.
What's the matter, Kirei?
Nothing.
I remember that face.
He had tears in his eyes from finding someone still alive.
A man who was happy from the bottom of his heart.
He looked so happy that it seemed like
it was him, not me, who had been saved.
You're alive...
You're alive! You're alive!
And then...
Even though I was on the brink of death,
the man was so grateful that it made me jealous.
"Thank you", he said.
He said he was glad to have found someone,
and that by saving even one person,
he had saved himself.
Episode 25
And now, our next news item.
Fuyuki City
Large Fire in the Fuyuki City New Town
News
At the Fuyuki City New Town...
Did Alexei-san make it back to England safely?
He called me this morning from Heathrow.
I told the fool to think about the time difference.
Oh, he called?
I didn't notice.
But it's just like him to do that.
Hey, Grandpa and Grandma.
There's something I'd like to talk to you about.
What is it?
Well...
I'm thinking of taking a break from school.
Of course, I'll talk to Dad in Toronto about it first.
I want to spend my time on something other than my studies at school.
Oh?
My goodness!
But what brought this on?
You aren't fed up with school, are you?
No, it's not that.
It's just that I haven't been interested in
anything besides studying in my life so far.
I'm regretting that a little.
And so...
I was thinking of doing some traveling.
Oh, my!
Did you hear that, Glen?
Waver-chan just said something that Alexei-san would have.
Anyway, I'll have a lot of preparations to do, and I'll need some money.
So I figured I'd start by finding myself a part-time job.
And so...
This is the real issue.
If you wouldn't mind...
Could I stay here until I get things worked out?
Of course you can!
It will be so wonderful to continue to have you here.
Yes, we'll have to celebrate today!
Geez...
He's just a spirit, so how is he able to leave such a mess behind?
Air Force Technology Research Center
Zero
Fighter
Planes
Really, I wanted him to take me along...
I guess that means I'm not quite there yet.
So he never ended up opening this...
Man.
Air Force Technology Research Center
Zero
Fighter
Planes
A pre-order original bonus T-shirt.
Who would want something like this?
Honestly...
I know that my redeemer lives.
And that, in the end, he will stand upon the Earth.
And after my skin has been destroyed, yet in my flesh,
I will see God.
I, myself, will see him, with my own eyes.
I, and not another.
How my heart yearns within me.
Amen.
Rin.
That was an excellent debut as the new family head.
Your father would've been proud.
Well done.
I'm sure you aren't fully accustomed to your Crest yet.
Does it hurt?
This is nothing. I'm fine.
Tokiomi's preparations truly were flawless.
You will inherit the Tohsaka family magics, Rin, without a problem.
Isn't it about time to take your mother with us?
Yes, I'll do that.
Come on, Mother.
Let's say our last goodbye to Father.
Ah, Rin?
Is it someone's funeral today?
Yes.
Father passed away.
Oh, my...
I need to hurry and take out Tokiomi-san's black suit.
Oh right, Rin.
Help Sakura get changed.
Oh, what should I do?
I have to get ready too.
My dear, your necktie's crooked.
You need to look good.
After all, you're the proud father of Rin and Sakura.
I'll be leaving Japan again for a while.
Do you have any concerns about the future?
No!
There's nothing I'll need your help for.
We will meet again in six months.
I will perform the second Crest transplantation then.
Make sure you monitor your physical condition very closely.
I'd do that even if you didn't tell me!
Rin.
From now on, you are officially the Tohsaka family head.
To commemorate this day, I'd like to give you a present.
An Azoth dagger.
When my master acknowledged
the results of my training, he gave it to me.
You can have it.
This was Father's...
I'm here again...
Everyone...
Lancelot...
I could not stop myself from loving Guinevere, so I was never able to forgive myself.
However, King Arthur...
You never questioned me for my crimes.
You never sought recompense.
You simply continued to stand before us in your righteousness.
But I desired judgment at your hands.
Had your anger judged me, I might not have fallen
onto the path of madness in my search for atonement.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I...
I am not worthy...
But I can say this much with certainty, King Arthur.
Someday, I will win the Holy Grail.
You were the greatest among all kings.
All who served you...
I shouldn't have...
...felt the same way.
...become king.
After that, I visited the Einzberns many times.
But as I had not returned with the Grail,
Jubstacheit never opened up the forest's magic field.
I never saw Ilya again.
However...
Ilya was the last person I would lose.
My life was meant to be full of loss.
But everyone is still here, just like when we first met.
I adopted the boy, Shirou, that I saved that day.
— Five Years Later —
Hey.
Hey, old man.
If you're gonna sleep, do it in your bed.
Right...
Nah, I'm fine.
When I was little, I wanted to be a champion of justice.
What?
You wanted to be one?
Did you give up?
Yeah.
It's unfortunate, but...
Being a hero is a limited-time thing.
When you grow up, it gets hard to call yourself one.
I should have realized that earlier.
I see.
That's just too bad, then.
Indeed.
You're absolutely right.
The moon's really nice tonight.
Yeah.
Since you couldn't do it, I'll do it for you.
You're an adult now, so you can't do it.
But I can.
Leave it to me...
Your dream.
Right.
Yeah.
I can be at peace now.
Hey, Kerry.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
Well...
I want to be a champion of justice.
Will one last miracle come to pass?
あと一度だけ奇跡は起こるだろう
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
優しい声で描く歪んだ未来
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
Kimi wo erande
君を選んで
If I could choose you
Tatta futari no yorokobi wo sagaseta nara
たった二人の 歓びを探せたなら
And search for happiness meant for just the two of us
Donna tsumetai honoo ni mi wo yakaretemo
どんな冷たい焔に身を焼かれても
Even if cold flames should sear my body
Hohoemi no chikaku
微笑みの近く
I will still be close to a smile
Kono sekai wo sunda mizu no naka e kaeshitai
この世界を 澄んだ水の中へ還したい
I want to return this world to the clear water
Kanashimi dake kese wa shinai
哀しみだけ消せはしない
Sadness alone will not disappear
Sonna hito no kokoro no
そんな人の心の
With my very own hands
Kotowari sae kono te de kirisaite
理さえこの手で切り裂いて
I will tear apart even the rules governing the hearts of the suffering
down to zero we go
Kirei na tsuki no hikari wa
綺麗な月の光は
The beautiful moonlight
Tada shizuka ni hajimari e kuchite yuku yo
ただ静かに 始まりへ朽ちて行くよ
Simply and quietly shines towards the beginning and rots away
Tozasareta akogare wa mada tooku e
閉ざされた憧れは まだ遠くへ
The longing that has been sealed is still far away
Yami no naka kimi to ikita hibi no subete
闇の中 君と生きた 日々の全て
Everything about the days where we lived together in the darkness
Yasashii uta
優しい歌
A gentle song