Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
The World She Saw
Defense of Trost (pt 2)
Hey! Hey, what's wrong, Armin?
Hey! Get ahold of yourself!
Armin! Hey! Armin!
Are you with me now?
Are you okay?
Hurt anywhere?
Where's your squad?
My... squad?
Man, get it together already!
Why are you alone?
And why are you so... slimy?
What the hell happened here?
I'm useless! Just leave me to die!
Calm down, Armin.
Where are they?
Just drop it already, Connie.
They're all dead...
Everyone but him.
No way!
Armin didn't say that!
Open your eyes and look the fuck around you.
We don't have time to babysit him.
Why is he unhurt then?
Who knows?
Maybe the Titans mistook him for dead.
It was just bad luck their squad
encountered multiple Titans at once.
But to think this guy was the sole survivor?
Eren and the others didn't deserve this ending.
Hey, you heartless bitch,
you want me to shut your mouth for good?!
Stop it, you two!
Of course everyone's on edge!
Our friends are dying all around us.
It's only natural!
That's my Krista!
After this mission ends, marry me, baby!
That's true...
She's screwing around even more than usual.
Anyways, we can't stay here.
Can you stand, Armin?
Sorry for causing you trouble.
I'll go join the rear guard.
Hey...
Armin!
We gotta go, Connie!
We've been ordered to move ahead!
This is hell...
No, this world hasn't become hell.
I just didn't get it up until right now.
This world's been hell all along.
The strong feed upon the weak.
It's such an obligingly simple rule.
Except in this world,
my friends tried to be strong.
They helped me, though I was weak.
I couldn't bear that...
To the two of them, I was always someone to be protected.
I wanted to become strong like them,
so we could walk together side-by-side
as we lived out our lives in this world.
Just look where that got me!
It's my fault that Eren...
Hannah, what are you doing?
Help me, Armin!
Franz isn't breathing!
I've been performing CPR over and over...
Franz!
Hannah, it's dangerous here! We should hurry—
And just leave Franz behind?!
That's not it, Hannah...
Franz won't...
Please stop...
No more...
I can't take this anymore...
Do you even understand the situation we're in?!
Of course I do!
So if you want to live, you better help!
Fuck off!
We'll all be eaten by the Titans!
What're you doing, soldier?
Get them out of the way!
But...
Just try it, grunt!
I'm the head merchant of this city's shopping district!
Who do you think pays for the food you shat out this morning?
Can you come up with the money to feed the city's soldiers?
You all help push too!
This cargo is worth more than all of your wretched lives combined!
But if you help out, you can earn a share.
Don't worry.
Daddy will defeat the Titans with his cannons.
Mommy...
What's that?
Walls in Heaven! Push if you want to live!
Dammit! Why is it ignoring us?
It's an abnormal! Don't even bother trying to guess!
It's too fast! We're the elite, but we can't even catch up to it!
At this rate...
What... are you doing?
Great!
Make them help out! You'll be greatly rewarded!
My comrades are dying out there.
Because the civilians still haven't finished evacuating,
they're laying down their lives to hold off the Titans.
Of course!
You devoted your hearts to protecting the lives and fortunes of the citizens!
Don't start getting full of yourselves just because you're suddenly useful for the first time in a century!
If you think it's natural for people to
sacrifice their own lives to save others,
surely you understand that, sometimes, a single death can save many lives.
How dare you!
I go way back with your boss!
We'll be laughing together over your dead body.
I wonder, what kind of jokes can corpses tell?
Wait!
Chief?
Pull back the cart.
Thanks, lady!
We're saved, thanks to you. I'm truly grateful.
Nice kill, Ackerman. I'm impressed.
Thank you.
But in my haste, I blunted my blade in just one attack.
I'll be more careful from now on.
What in the world did you endure, to turn out like this?
No, nevermind.
Why am I remembering that now?
Currently Disclosable Information
Super-hardened Steel (pt 1)
A strong and flexible material that can cut through Titan flesh.
It is widely known that single-edged blades forged from this
material are used to slay Titans.
Currently Disclosable Information
Super-hardened Steel (pt 2)
The blast furnaces in industrial towns are indispensable to
the smelting of super-hardened steel, meaning that the steel
can't be produced anywhere else.
I'm done!
Look at this, Mom!
Good job, Mikasa!
It's really pretty.
This embroidering's been passed down for generations in our clan.
You'll teach it to your child too, when the time comes.
How do you make a child?
Well... Ask your father about it.
Hey, Dad...
I'm a bit hazy on the details too.
But Dr. Jaeger will be here soon. We could try asking him.
See? There he is now.
Coming!
Mikasa?
Yeah.
She's a girl your age.
There aren't many kids around here, so try making friends with her.
That depends on what she's like.
Eren, that attitude is why you've only got one friend.
They aren't home?
Mr. Ackerman? It's Jaeger.
Excuse us.
What's wrong?
Dad?
Dammit.
Eren, have you seen any girls around?
Did you see Mikasa?
No.
All right.
I'm going to call the Military Police to request a search for her.
You go home and wait there!
Do you understand, Eren? Eren?
Eren?!
Man, can we really sell her?
We even had to kill her parents to snatch her.
Get a look at her face.
Pretty, but she's still a kid.
I'm not into that stuff.
No one asked about your fancies.
She's an Oriental.
Long ago there were many kinds of people.
She's the last descendant of a clan who escaped to the safety of the walls from a place called "the Orient".
We'll auction her off to those rich
perverts at the capital's black market.
Orientals are already an extinct race. She'll fetch a good price.
Her father didn't look Oriental at all. She's not a pure-blood.
Damn straight! Her mother was the really valuable one!
But you panicked and killed the bitch!
What could I do? She fought back!
Is that all you've got to say?
Dr. Jaeger, we've been wait—
Hello. Pardon the intrusion.
Stay calm, unless you want me to split your skull with this.
Crazy bitch!
Mikasa! Run!
Mom...
Hurry, Mikasa!
But... Dad?
Dammit! Enough already!
What are you doing?!
I told you, only kill the man!
But that bitch—
Screw your excuses!
Take the brat and run!
You'd better behave yourself.
Otherwise you'll get more of this!
It's cold.
Excuse me!
You goddamn brat!
What are you doing here!?
I just... I got lost in the forest...
Then I saw your hut...
That won't do.
Kids shouldn't be walking alone in the forest.
There are scary wolves out there!
But don't worry. We'll take good care of—
Thanks, mister. I get it...
So die already, you worthless shitrag!
You're kidding me...
Stop, you damn brat!
You fucking bastard!
Drop dead!
It's only natural! This is what you deserve!
Never get up again!
It's gonna be okay now. Don't worry.
You're Mikasa, right?
I'm Eren.
I'm the son of Doctor Jaeger.
I'm pretty sure you've met my dad before.
We came to visit you so that the two of us could meet.
But then...
There were three of them.
Did you do this?
Did you kill them?!
Was it you?!
I'll kill you! I'm gonna fucking butcher you!
Fight!
You must fight!
If you win, you live.
If you lose, you die.
What the hell were you thinking, brat?!
If you don't fight, you can't win!
I... can't do it!
That moment I remembered,
I've seen this scene before,
over and over again.
It was always happening right in front of me.
But I pretended not to notice it.
That's right.
This world is... merciless.
That moment my body stopped shaking.
From that moment on, I could perfectly control myself.
I thought I could do anything.
Fight...
Fight!
One stab from behind, right through his heart.
Did those kids really do all this?
Eren, I told you to wait at home.
Do you understand what you did?
I disposed of some dangerous beasts.
Mere animals that just happened to resemble humans!
Eren!
The Military Police only just arrived.
Those bastards would've been long gone!
They would've been too late!
But even still...
You were just lucky, Eren!
I'm scolding you because you risked your life so carelessly!
But I just wanted to save her...
Mikasa, do you remember me?
We've met several times before when you were little.
Dr. Jaeger... Where should I go from here?
It's cold.
I've got nowhere to go home to anymore.
You can have this.
It's warm, right?
It is.
Mikasa, come live with our family.
You've suffered a lot.
You need plenty of rest.
What?
Come on, let's get going...
Back to our home.
Home...
Only the victors are allowed to live.
This world is merciless like that.
We're pulling out, Ackerman.
We're climbing the Wall.
I'll go support the other defensive lines' retreat.
Wait, Ackerman!
But I've got a home in this world.
Eren! As long as you're there for me, I can do anything.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
I've got place to call home.
After finishing her duties in the rear guard, Mikasa rushes to find Eren...
But there she learns what happened to Eren.
A Small Blade
Defense of Trost (pt 3)