Now, the sword hunt that Togame the Strategian and the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika have been on...
has been ongoing for 4 months, and it is now April.
We are now in a certain small village on the outskirts of Suou, in the eastern Yamaguchi prefecture.
On this night where sakura petals dance like falling snow,
Togame is hurrying towards the temporary lodgings which the village mayor had provided them.
That Sabi Hakuhei is just so...
Shichirin!
Note: "shichirin" also means a coal-fueled portable stove
Shichirin, wake up!
I'm not sleeping, and what's with that name?
"What am I, some portable stove or something?" is what you want to say, right?
This is why I used that nickname —
As I'm always saying, you're an idiot, you have no individuality, no flair, you mess your lines up, and your acting is garbage, so...
This is a hassle, and I'm tired...
You look it.
If you had just asked me, I would have helped out.
It's my duty to meet with messengers that the Shogunate sends.
I see.
We're leaving tomorrow morning after we say goodbye to the village mayor.
Tomorrow?
That's pretty fast...
Weren't we going to settle here for a while and wait for reports of that Sabi Hakuhei guy?
I was talking about him with the Shogunate's messenger just now.
I didn't have to look far...
What?
Sign: Letter of Challenge
Sabi noticed the man we had following him, and handed over a letter of challenge, of all things.
My goodness...
How old-fashioned can you get?
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
}己をはらはら花に例えて　散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsumami aguneta guren no tama wo
}摘みあぐねた紅蓮の霊を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarau kare no hi areshi mune yori
}さらう彼の日　荒れし胸より
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
}恐るるまま命は羽搏いて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
}やがて　やがて　天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
}朱く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai kira no yume wo ataeta mou
}すれ違い綺羅の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabite meiyo ni samayoi
}待ち侘びて冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
}共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
}想いがはらはら舞う故に
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
}私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
}無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sora he egaite
}絆を更なる空へ描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
}花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Note: Needle, the Light
Hakutou
Hari
Well, give it a read.
I can't read.
I can't read Japanese Hiragana.
Well, whatever.
To summarize, he said:
"I challenge you to a duel for the Shikizaki Kiki Swords."
Straight to the point.
Yeah.
The more I think it over, the stranger it sounds.
He's such an old-fashioned, straight guy,
and yet he betrayed you and the Shogunate which he was loyal to, simply out of desire for a sword?
It's not such a strange notion when you consider he was touched by the poison of Shikizaki's swords.
The sword's poison...
The more pure a swordsman you are, the more the poison affects you.
Deeply, very deeply...
He's a man who lost most of his humanity after devoting too much of himself to swordsmanship.
His looks and that knotted hairstyle might even trick you into thinking he's a woman,
but he's reputed to be able to cut even the moon clean in half.
Shichirin, hold my hair up for me or it's going to tangle.
It seems that Sabi knows about the swords we have.
At the very least, he knows about Kanna and Namakura.
And it's been a month since we obtained Tsurugi,
so it wouldn't be strange if he knew about that by now too.
The fact that this man doesn't seem to know desire for women probably isn't just because he grew up on a deserted island.
We must be leaking information if Sabi knows about our swords.
That aspect of him is why he was able to kill our third foe, Tsuruga Meisai, so easily.
He has no qualms about killing women.
He doesn't even distinguish between men and women.
That being the case, why has this man, this sword, fallen for me?
Togame?
What?
Like I said, the fact that Sabi knows about the swords we have means that information is leaking from somewhere.
Y-Yeah...
There are talkative people anywhere you go.
Also, when it comes to a swordsman like Sabi,
you'll find that countless people want to help him out of admiration for his skills.
His outstanding strength has the tendency to charm people like that.
Is he that strong?
Truthfully speaking, I wanted to put off the fight between you and Sabi until later on...
But now that it's comes to this, we have no choice.
I'll put my knowledge to full use, so you just focus on putting in your best effort.
On top of that, Hakutou Hari is...
Needle - The Light
thin, frail, and above all, a beautiful sword.
It's going to be tough getting such a frail sword without breaking it.
Don't concern yourself too much with the sword itself this time.
Sabi Hakuhei's level of swordsmanship will require your full attention.
His reputation as Japan's strongest is no bluff, no matter what sword he's using.
Do you really have to call him "strongest"?
Yes, he's—
Togame, don't praise other swords in front of me!
I don't know if Sabi is the strongest or whatever, but Kyotouryuu considers itself the strongest swordsmanship.
I have my own pride as your sword.
It bothers me when you poke at my self respect like that!
M-My collarbone...
Collarbone is bad! I'm weak there!
Take your hands off it!
It tickles, it tickles!
Stop stop stop! Please!
I'm not gripping you that hard.
Please... stop...
I'm just gently stroking—
Yan yan!
Note: Yan Yan is a cute name for pandas
Yan yan?
That's even worse!
Let go!
Ahh this is bad.
I'm sorry! I apologize!
I don't get you at all, Togame.
I don't want to hear that from you!
Anyway, I hope that pride of yours works to our advantage against Sabi Hakuhei.
He's strong, you know.
Come to think of it, if I defeat him, that makes me the strongest in Japan, right?
That doesn't sound bad.
I suppose so...
Do you want that title?
Alright, tie my sash.
Okay.
Of course the title of "Japan's Strongest" is enticing to me.
As a swordsman and as a sword, it means I'm useful to you.
That's a little surprising.
So, did you accept the duel?
Yes.
I'll think up a plan to defeat him on the way to the designated site.
Where is it?
Ganryuu Island.
Ganryuu Island...
That's the place where the legendary duel between Musashi and Kojirou took place over 100 years ago.
As a Kyotouryuu swordsman even you must know of it.
An island, huh...
Speaking of which, I wonder how Nee-chan is doing...
But I still don't understand it at all.
To think that in the span of just a few months, three Maniwa Corps heads have been killed...
There's no mistaking that Koumori-san, Shirasagi-san, and Kuizame-san were killed fighting over the swords.
I heard that the Maniwa Corps are being called the underdogs now.
Especially after Kuizame-dono...
Apparently he was killed instantly by a woman called Meisai...
At this rate, our reputation will only get worse.
It started the moment we got involved with the sword gathering, or rather, with Kyotouryuu.
It feels like fate has abandoned our Maniwa Corps village.
Yeah...
I'm worried about our future.
Are you having second thoughts?
Would you rather have just kept on making a living by doing as the Owari Shogunate says?
No way.
I have no regrets.
It's just...
The way things are going now, with Maniwa taking all the losses, it's a disgrace to our name.
That strategian must be laughing her heart out right now.
The moment we left her, Maniwa went downhill.
It's a pretty pitiful situation.
But we'll wipe the smile off her face soon.
Gentlemen, don't be mistaken here.
The strategian is of no importance to us.
Our problem is Kyotouryuu.
Kyotouryuu...
That hero of the rebellion, huh...
We've done quite a lot of work too, but we don't get called heroes.
There will never be a time when Ninja are hailed as heroes.
Also, the "hero" was the 6th generation Kyotouryuu head.
The man we're dealing with is his son, the 7th generation head.
The young are troublesome.
They don't know fear, much like you.
Oh not at all,
I'm not that bold.
I merely came along to observe the Ninpou you two use for future reference.
Note: Ninpou means Ninja arts
Oh, so you don't mind getting no share of the spoils then?
We were going to divide up the swords between us after defeating Kyotouryuu,
but if you say so, Mitsubachi...
Note: Mitsubachi means Honey Bee
No, that's a different matter...
Look over there.
It's the island.
Just a stride away.
As expected of "Chouchou the Weightless".
Note: Chouchou means butterfly.
Even with us on your shoulders, this distance is just "a stride".
No, even I'm getting tired.
Riding you is a strange feeling no matter how many times I do it.
Let us proceed.
Fly like a butterfly, sting like a bee, and consume like a praying mantis.
Maniwa Corps: Insect Squad!
Proud and coming through!
Bye!
Your idea to pretend to be traveling performers was great!
Nobody suspected us with these outfits.
The children loved it too.
Well, I suppose we can use this act from time to time.
Let's hurry.
I've been thinking, after what you said last night...
If Sabi knows we've collected three swords,
then there's a good chance the Maniwa Corps will also make a move.
They could be going ahead of us to face Sabi.
Wouldn't that be bad?
Geez, what kind of island is this?
It's like this whole thing's a mountain.
This is where Koumori-san...
Yeah.
Um...
Is it possible that Koumori-san accepted the strategian's offer with the intent to betray her from the start?
He may have been thinking about the needs of the village.
That sword would sell for a considerable amount of money.
Koumori-dono's hopes aside, Insect Squad's current objective is to work together to defeat Kyotouryuu and take the swords.
Well, that strategian has no family, but the 7th Kyotouryuu head has an older sister.
Leaving her here alone on this island was far too careless of them.
That's true.
We ninja thrive on unfair play.
Yeah.
So, who's going to be in charge of capturing the lady?
If possible, I'd like to rest for a bit.
It took longer to reach the island than I thought it would.
Shall I go, then?
No, I will.
Why don't you let Mitsubachi do a bit of work?
Make no mistake, that girl is also of Kyotouryuu blood.
It's best for a ninja combat specialist such as myself to go face her.
Well, you are the leader of the Insect Squad,
so we'll let you make the call.
Mitsubachi, you're okay with that?
Yes, we can leave it to him.
You seriously have no ambition, do you?
I'm surprised you keep your position as one of the Maniwa heads.
I'll leave behind my red crystal, just in case.
If anything goes wrong, you two must complete the task.
"If anything goes wrong"?
That's not something I'd expect "Kamakiri the Headhunter" to say.
Note: Kamakiri means praying mantis
That's right.
Please don't say weird things, Kamakiri-san.
I'll be going, then.
That girl, huh...
It seems it's a good thing I came.
Chouchou aside, that young Mitsubachi would probably fall for her.
Should I aim for her feet or her arms?
Ninpou: Tsume Awase.
I wonder how Shichika's doing...
I told Togame-san I'd stay behind to protect the Yasuri household,
but father is dead, and Shichika left...
I really am alone now.
Kamakiri-dono sure is late...
Really?
It hasn't been that long.
I guess...
Hey!
You just cheated!
Right here!
You moved that stone to your advantage!
I did no such thing!
That's not playing fair, Mitsubachi!
I really didn't!
There's no point trying to commit suicide.
I removed your poison molar while you were sleeping.
I apologize once again,
but I'm afraid I'm going to have to torture you now.
Maybe I'll go check on him after all.
Something feels wrong....
No way!
Nothing could happen to Kamakiri-san.
I must be imagining things.
Yeah...
What should we play next?
Let's see...
The reason I bought you here is because your companion is currently buried over there.
My brother buried him.
I believe he said his name was Maniwa Koumori.
So basically, I intend to do you the good will of burying you beside your companion.
You have the choice, so why don't you pick?
Choice? Pick what?
What do you want me to choose?
Whether to keep silent then die, or talk then die.
Though, I don't really mind which one you pick.
That said, I'm not entirely sure how to torture,
so I suppose it might be better for me if you were to stay silent and die.
There isn't all that much I need to ask you, and I already have a good idea of the general situation.
Maniwa Corps...
That's a bit long so I think I'll call you "Maniwani".
That's more cute and charming.
From the fact that you Maniwani came to this island,
I suppose I can assume that Shichika and Togame-san's sword hunt must be well under way.
So, how many swords have they collected so far?
Two, or rather, including the Zettou Kanna they picked up here, three.
That sounds like quite an easygoing journey they're taking...
So that's how it is...
I have yet to meet or even see your brother,
but as the family head, can I presume he is stronger than you?
I wonder about that...
I haven't had a proper contest with Shichika for about a year now.
And on top of that, I never received training in Kyotouryuu from the former head.
So what was that you used earlier on me?
That wasn't a Kyotouryuu skill?
Well I suppose it was...
That was a disarmament counter called "Patrinia".
Wait, why are you asking me questions,
and why am I answering them?
No idea.
Let me ask then.
How many of your people are here?
How many besides you?
You cheated! You cheated again!
Cheated?
You used Ninpou to change the face of the die!
I can't do any magic tricks like that!
Strange question. I came alone, of course.
We don't have the kind of manpower in the village to send more than one soldier after a single girl.
Kidnapping me isn't the end of your plan,
so I wouldn't be surprised if you had brought more people.
For instance, let's see...
The same number as the swords Shichika carries — three.
It would help if you would tell me how many there are and what skills they possess.
Ah, by "would help" I mean would help me, not help your situation.
I wouldn't want you to misunderstand now.
Let me tell you a bit about my brother...
A long time ago he had a habit of biting his fingernails.
It wasn't elegant so I told him to stop, but he wouldn't listen and kept biting them.
His thumb became all ragged after a while.
So one day I tore out all his nails.
Ever since then, he's never bitten his nails.
Though, this is a story about child discipline, so I don't know how applicable it is as torture...
But how about we go in reverse for you?
Bite them.
What's wrong?
I said bite your nails so you can feel like a kid again.
You might cut your tongue a little,
but you're not using it to talk anyway so it doesn't matter right?
W-Wait!
Fine...
"Fine"?
I mean I'll talk...
Our Ninpou...
Ninpou...
Ninpou: Tsume Awase!
Sorry, I've sealed your movements now.
You deliberately used your kimono!
Well, I suppose.
Those eyes...
Please forgive me, Nanami.
The 7th Kyotouryuu head will be Shichika.
With this, I have no choice but to retire from active duty.
While I do have some regrets, as a proud sword I will accept my fate.
I will accomplish my duty in passing Kyotouryuu onto the next generation.
From now on, Shichika,
until my life runs out,
until this body rots away,
until my blade rusts,
I will carve all of Kyotouryuu into your body.
Forgive me, Nanami.
I really wanted to have you succeed me as the head of Kyotouryuu, but that is not possible.
Understand that the impossible is impossible.
Not because you are a woman, or because of your weak body, Nanami.
But because I am unable to raise someone as exceptionally powerful as you.
You have the same eyes as father did when he looked at me then...
I'm tired.
I hadn't thought I'd be able to extract information from a ninja using torture anyway...
Maybe I should say, "as expected"?
I tried to trick you into confessing, but it didn't work at all.
Well, things are pretty much as I imagined though.
Goodness, Shichika...
Only two swords after all this time?
You really are being lazy.
When you come back I'll have to discipline you.
I've only ever fought with Nee-chan once.
Looks like a draw.
Sorry, with my body I can only go for so long.
But you did pretty well.
I wonder whether Sabi or Nee-chan is stronger...
You don't suppose this means something happened to Kamakiri-san?
No, no, no...
There's no way there's any opponent who could oppose Kamakiri-san's Ninpou: Tsume Awase.
Even Kuizame, who was practically a murderer in a Ninja outfit, respected Kamakiri-dono.
Even without his Ninpou, that man has a wealth of experience.
There's no way he could lose!
I suppose...
Those red crystals aren't a certain thing.
Right, right!
And there's been cases where the crystal shattered but the owner came back alive and well.
Well, I've heard that story too...
but I'm pretty sure that was just someone accidentally dropping and breaking it, so...
Um...
In this situation, should we perhaps move with the assumption that Kamakiri-san has lost?
What are you going to do?
If we go in order, I would be next, right?
No, I'll go.
I've rested for quite a bit now.
But regardless of your condition, I think my skills would be more appropriate.
Your Ninpou is a little too... direct.
You don't get it, Mitsubachi.
I really liked Kamakiri-dono!
I feel the same way!
And I'm fond of you too!
If there's to be one survivor in the Insect Squad, it should be you, the youngest of us.
But...
Got it?
Watch my battle with the Kyotouryuu girl from afar.
And then, if I lose...
Use that information to abduct the girl.
But...
But then you would die like a dog!
Idiot.
I don't intend to walk in there as a sacrifice or anything.
For all you know, I could just be saying all this to steal all the credit.
And "die like a dog"? We're the Insect Squad you know!
But...
You know, Mitsubachi...
What?
When this mission is over, I'm getting married.
In our business there's no telling when or where we'll fall, so I'd never thought to take the plunge before...
But now I've decided.
I'm going to get married.
I-Is that so...
To whom?
Someone you know.
With instincts as good as yours, you should be able to figure it out.
No...
She's another one of the 12 heads, Maniwa Oshidori of the Bird Squad.
Oshidori-san?
I get the feeling she'll be the dominant one.
Right?
The Bird Squad is almost like a predator to the Insect Squad.
I guess you could say my heart was eaten by her back then.
That was the start of our romance, but now it seems—
Chouchou-san, that's a nice story, but I think it might be better for you to stop...
Why?
Never mind...
Anyway, we'll do that then.
You're up next so I'll leave it to you.
Though, I am a ninja you know.
If we're going to do this, we'll do it properly.
If anything happens to you, I won't provide any assistance.
For example, even if you're put through torture...
Yeah, that's fine.
If it comes to that, I'll put up a futile resistance and increase the amount of intel for you.
That was close.
I just quit smoking not long ago.
Oshidori really despises smoking.
Even if you smoke outside, the smell gets on you, right?
Wouldn't Oshidori-san forgive you this one smoke just today?
I'll take this for safekeeping.
You can enjoy it at your leisure after the mission is over.
Mitsubachi...
I guess so.
Ah right, keep this for me too.
We'll smoke together later.
I don't...
Okay.
Now then, I guess I'll be off.
Take this.
What for?
The Insect Squad will always be together.
Even in death, our bonds will never fray.
You're an unexpectedly kind person deep down, aren't you?
Oh stop that.
Put it in your left breast pocket.
What do you mean?
Just do it please.
Alright.
Later then.
I hope that crystal...
No, Kamakiri-san's soul...
I hope his soul can protect Chouchou-san.
There's Ganryuu Island.
How did you know?
I thought I'd totally erased my presence....
I think it makes more sense for me to ask why you think you can erase your presence while you're still alive...
The person over there can only be the person over there, right?
It's the same reason you can't search for yourself, because you're right there.
Well, whatever.
I am one of the 12 heads of the Maniwa Corps, Maniwa Chouchou.
I'm here to kidnap you.
That's quite a charming pickup line.
I never thought I'd hear a line like that from a gentleman.
I'm a bit late, and you probably already know, but for the sake of politeness I'll introduce myself.
I am the head of the Yasuri household, Yasuri Nanami.
Yes, I know.
While you're here, could you tell me something?
Not long ago, another person with a similar outfit tried to attack me, but I didn't catch his name.
He didn't introduce himself?
I didn't give him a chance to tell me.
His name was Maniwa Kamakiri.
Kamakiri...
So that's why he used claws as weapons.
Did you kill Kamakiri-dono?
Yes, he attacked me after all.
Oh that's right,
would you mind telling me how many of you there are?
What?
I actually tortured Kamakiri-san a bit, but he wouldn't tell me.
You won't get any information out of me that Kamakiri-san didn't tell you.
I see.
Given your position as the one who defeated Kamakiri-dono, I'm not going to treat you as a woman.
I will unreservedly go all out from the start against you.
Depending on how it goes, I may even kill you.
But then I can't be your hostage.
Of course, my priority is to take you hostage.
However, just displaying your corpse in front of your brother should diminish his fighting spirit considerably.
I see.
That's definitely ninja-like.
Though of course, if you'll surrender, I'll accommodate that.
If you think you're in a pinch, just say so.
As you see fit.
That stance...
This is called Maniwa Kenpou.
Note: Kenpou means Art of defense
It's completely different from the normal Kenpou that you usually see.
Maniwa Kenpou...
The Kyotouryuu founder Yasuri Kazune and our founder once fought together, a long time ago.
Did you know?
No, I had no idea.
Apparently it was a lot of fun.
Why don't we fight like them, too?
What's wrong? Not taking a stance?
As a fellow martial artist, I'd be honored to accept some instruction on it.
I'll wait for you to take a stance.
That's generous of you, but I've never once in my life taken up a stance.
You mean Kyotouryuu has no stances?
Actually, I'm a deviant as far as Kyotouryuu is concerned.
But think of it this way, Chouchou-san.
Stances are useless to begin with.
If you change your stance in reaction to every little thing that happens, won't you become slower?
I can read exactly what you plan to do next from your stance.
You've already revealed to me any mysteries your Kenpou might have had.
Just by taking that stance.
If I had to give mine a name,
it would be Kyotouryuu, zero dance: Fig tree.
Or something like that.
Kyotouryuu: Poppy.
Kyotouryuu:
Poppy
You dodged well.
Maniwa Kenpou and Maniwa Ninpou.
There are few people who've ever fended off this combination on the first try.
Ninpou...
Ninpou: Ashigaru.
Note: Ashigaru = Light Feet
My movements can ignore gravity.
I can hold any object, no matter how heavy,
and even that thin branch would be more than enough to support me.
No matter what kind of attack you throw at me,
I'll just fly off in the direction you're aiming.
You're saying that my attack didn't actually hit,
and just before contact, your body was already set afloat by the air pressure from my hand?
That's right.
You have quite the nerve to call yourself a martial artist while using such a bizarre technique.
Say what you like, but my Ninpou is my Ninpou so there's no helping that.
What now?
If you want to surrender, now's a good opportunity.
Next time I'm going all out.
Didn't you say you were going all out from the start?
Don't you understand how amazing my Ninpou is?
I understand.
It's quite something.
It's a technique which cancels out your weight.
You used that technique to get you and your companions to this island, correct?
But what amazes me most is not the technique itself,
but the amount of time it must have taken you to learn it.
I'm sure it took quite a bit of effort.
I'm guessing it took almost your entire life to learn.
That Kamakiri-san also had his Ninpou: Tsume Awase.
That must also have taken a considerable amount of time, to reshape his body in order to be able to use that.
That technique must have been passed down for centuries from generation to generation, perfecting it until it became complete.
I'm quite...
Quite jealous of that.
I'm sure that you of all people could never understand the feelings of someone who doesn't know what it feels like to make an effort.
Don't blame me if this kills you!
You kindly showed it to me again.
That woman just used Chouchou-san's Ninpou...
Ninpou: Ashigaru.
It worked just like I expected.
Of course, you can't cancel out your weight in reality.
N-No way...
I've seen enough already, so out of mercy I'll kill you right now.
Kyotouryuu: Dandelion.
No way!
It can't be...
That's Tsume Awase!
I wasn't able to use this Ninpou very well because I've only seen it once.
But next time I'm sure I'll do a little better.
N-No way...
Learning the Maniwa Ninpou so easily...
Do you know how much we went through...
Impossible...
Impossible, impossible!
Really...
That's why I'm jealous.
You're able to put effort into everything.
Impossible...
No way!
Two Ninpou in such a short time...
What on earth is that girl?
I've been watching them.
For a long time...
My power is said to be exceptional and deviant.
My father Mutsue tried to contain it as a father and as a swordsman.
That's why he didn't teach me Kyotouryuu at all.
How did I master the skills then?
I was always watching them.
I kept watching my younger brother continuously putting effort into it for 19 years.
I remember most skills by seeing them once.
I master them after the second time.
My method of practice is observation.
Seeing is training for me.
Thank you for showing me.
Stay back, Mitsubachi!
But...
You saw, right?
You need to come up with a proper plan!
This woman...
You can't beat her by ordinary means!
Chouchou-san!
The Insect Squad are...
always together...
I won't forgive you.
Now then...
Someone was watching over this battle.
Isn't it time you came out?
She's ill?
Then this is my chance!
Watch me, Kamakiri-san, Chouchou-san!
Ninpou: Makibishi Shidan!
Note: Caltrops bullet
Ninpou:
Makibishi Shidan
Got her!
I'm one of the 12 heads of the Maniwa Corps, Maniwa Mitsubachi.
I'm Yasuri... Nanami.
You killed two of my friends.
Yes, Kamakiri-san and... Chouchou-san, wasn't it?
You needn't be so wary, as I'm the last one.
Though I think I'm more than enough to take you in your present condition.
Is this poison?
Yes, it's poison.
Don't worry, it's not a lethal one.
What we want isn't you, but rather your brother.
To be precise, we want the completed Shikizaki Kiki Deviant Blades which your brother is collecting.
That said, personally I really want to kill you.
But if I do that, I'll only be able to satisfy my own wish for vengeance.
I'll only truly be able to avenge Kamakiri-san and Chouchou-san by collecting the swords.
You talk a lot.
People really do tend to talk a lot when they have the advantage.
I suppose even Ninja are no exception.
What about you?
I said the poison isn't lethal, but at this point you shouldn't be able to talk.
Perhaps I should hit you with another for good measure.
Is that your Ninpou?
Yes, it's called Ninpou: Makibishi Shidan.
Are you sure you should be showing me that move?
I don't mind what you see in your current state.
You can't do anything, even if you are an unprecedented level of genius.
I'd prefer it if you'd obediently submit, as the gentleman in me would like to avoid scarring that beautiful skin of yours.
Well, thank you.
I look at things objectively.
I understand that you're far stronger than I am.
That being the case, I should at least cut off your arms while I can.
It shouldn't hurt much.
The poison flowing through your veins now should serve well as a painkiller.
Please don't think badly of me.
It's your fault for being too strong.
W-When did you...
Ninpou: Ashigaru...
And yes, Makibishi Shidan.
A caltrop?
There's no way you had any caltrops prepared beforehand!
But you gave them to me.
Two of them.
B-But...
There's no way that a caltrop dug into your flesh could come out so easily!
There are hooks on the prongs!
Yes, so I dug it out with these claws, flesh and all.
W-What about the poison...
Oh, that was an act.
An... act?
A little poison that isn't even lethal means nothing to me.
That's an everyday experience for me.
Everyday?
No matter how excruciating, no matter how painful, no matter how close I am to death,
my body just won't choose death.
Or rather, it won't allow me to die.
Why isn't she dead yet?
It's so pitiful...
She may die at any time...
Or rather, I don't know why she hasn't already died yet.
Why is she still alive?
Even though she's in so much pain...
Unable to even die peacefully...
It hurts, just let me...
If only she'd just die...
If she could just die, she'd be at peace.
That's why I'm jealous of you people, who can feel pain from a little bit of poison.
Not yet! I haven't lost yet!
If you're able to bear this poison, there's no way I can't!
No, I doubt you can.
That caltrop I hit your shoulder with contained another poison, on top of the one you already had on it.
I used the poison from Kamakiri-san's molar.
I did have that prepared beforehand, right?
Since you have the choice, could you tell me what you'd prefer?
Choice?
Will you die by poison or by the sword?
Thanks to you, I've seen how to use a sword for the first time in my life.
Slay me by the sword please...
If I died by suicide poisoning, I wouldn't be able to face my comrades in the next life.
Understood.
Then I will show you Kyotouryuu's 8th and final secret move as a farewell gift.
Before that...
I beg a favor of you.
C-Could you bury...
my corpse along with...
my companions?
That's fine.
And... this too...
What's that?
That really was one tough battle though.
Yeah, it really was.
He was true to his title as Japan's strongest.
Sabi Hakuhei... I won't forget that name for the rest of my life.
You won by the skin of your teeth.
It's no exaggeration to say that we made new history on the holy island of Ganryuu.
It was definitely a close battle.
Without your strategy, I wouldn't be alive now.
What are you talking about?
My strategies don't mean anything without your skills.
I've revised my opinion of you now!
And I've fallen for you all over again.
Oh stop that.
But you really competed with Sabi Hakuhei in swordplay and won.
Now you've truly earned the title of "Japan's strongest" that you wanted.
Japan's strongest, huh...
It hasn't really sunk in yet.
But each of the various techniques Sabi unveiled to us...
they all really caught me by surprise.
The movement technique he used at the start of our duel —
Bakushukuchi — that shocked me.
Note: Bakushukuchi = Explode, Contract, Ground
I never imagined that he could have more flexible footwork than Kyotouryuu's Iris.
Skewered rice dumplings for two, please!
Yes, right away!
Speaking of techniques, that one caught me off guard —
that "Gyakuten Muzan" one where he used the sword and sheath together was really impressive.
I can completely understand why he gained the title of "Holy Swordsman" after learning that technique.
No no, that wizardry which allowed him to freely change the length of the blade — Sokuchiken —
Note: Sokuchiken = Fast Slow Sword
that was a true threat to my Kyotouryuu.
Being a sword of fixed length myself, it was impossible to judge his timing.
I shudder when I think what would have happened if I hadn't lost my footing then...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
And the way he caught your blade when I thought you were about to land a blow on him...
It was quite magnificent.
Even though we won, I'm certain we only faced a fraction of that fallen swordsman's true power.
You're probably right.
Honestly, I don't really feel like I won.
We probably can't even say we were lucky in that battle.
You're absolutely right.
We just managed not to lose.
Sweet red bean soup for two, please!
Certainly!
And it goes without saying that his masterpiece was that "Hakutou Kaigan" technique,
only made possible by Hakutou Hari, the Shikizaki Kiki Completed Deviant Blade that he carried.
I never dreamed that Hakutou might have had such an amazing attribute.
I thought it was just a frail sword, with beauty as its only saving grace.
I feel like I've learned the true horror of that swordsman.
Hot!
That's true.
It was rumored that Sabi's sword could slice even the sun in half.
With that technique, it doesn't sound like such a far fetched idea.
However!
Regardless of the process, we managed to obtain Hakutou.
You should be proud of the fact that you defeated Sabi Hakuhei face to face in a duel!
I probably should.
But what he said on the verge of death bothers me.
That I'm...
No, that Kyotouryuu was left behind by Shikizaki Kiki.
What does that mean?
And what does he mean by "Kiki's bloodline"?
Sabi even called himself an incomplete failed creation...
Didn't you say he betrayed you after being poisoned by the sword?
I don't know.
I'm pretty confident he was affected by the sword's poison,
but Sabi might have had his own unavoidable circumstances.
If we're to believe what he said, it should all become clear as we continue our journey.
Hot!
I suppose.
We managed to obtain Hakutou Hari without snapping it, breaking it, or even scratching it.
With our fourth sword in hand, the end is starting to come into sight.
I understand how you feel, but don't get carried away.
There's still a long way left to our journey.
Let's see, since we came all the way to Kyuushuu, let's collect another sword while we're on a roll.
Alright.
No objections here.
So, where next?
Our next destination is Satsuma.
Our next target is Zokutou Yoroi, which boasts an unparalleled absolute defense.
Your opponent is the captain of a pirate ship.
Red bean soup and dumplings for two please!
Okay!
And so Yasuri Shichika defeated Sabi Hakuhei, obtaining the title of Japan's strongest.
However, the position of strongest swordsman is but a provisional one.
Sabi Hakuhei, huh...
He wasn't as strong as Nee-chan though.
And thus the Insect Squad was wiped out on Fushou island.
Dancing like a butterfly, stinging like a bee, consuming like a praying mantis...
and dying like a bug.
Really Shichika, you call that an ultimate move?
For all that boasting, it has a huge weak point.
You really can't call that a real move.
You can't tell these things till you've tried it out.
I'd better tell him as soon as possible, or he might end up getting in trouble.
What should I do...
Maybe I should join them in the sword hunt.
Now, although this episode probably raised some eyebrows, the story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
soyokaze manimani chiru hana wa
そよ風　随に散る華は
Blossoms flying around in a gentle breeze
utsushiku kanbina yume
美しく　甘美な夢
are beautiful sweet dreams
ukiyoni yurusarezaru
浮世に　許されざる
embracing unforgivable emptiness
kyomu wo daite
虚無を抱いて
in this transient world
dare mo tadoritsuku koto no nai
誰も　辿り着くことのない
Nothing has reflection
kurayami ni wa nani mo utsuranai
暗闇には　何も映らない
in the darkness which no one reaches
jiwari shimiteyuku zetsubou mo
じわり　染みてゆく絶望も
Even despair piercing me little by little
sen no doku ni magure
千の毒に紛れ
is diverted by a thousand poisons
Sabihakuhei was a tough foe.
Although it didn't really feel like we won,
a victory is a victory.
We did win!
The next place I and "Japan's strongest" Shichika head for is Satsuma.
How do we fight a pirate captain with a gang of pirates at his command?
What? He fell for me at first sight?
"Please be my woman"?
What??
Zokutou
Yoroi
N-Next time on Katanagatari: Zokutou Yoroi.
Armor, the Grudge
Cheerio!