I found it lying over there.
Thank you so much!
Your Highness...
"Your Highness"?
Glad to see you're doing well, Choi.
Oh hey, Your Highness.
You're not looking too bad yourself.
I'm fine, as you can see.
I don't believe we've met, but I'm glad to hear that all the same.
What?!
I see this land has talking birds too.
There's one I've known back home ever since I was a child. His name's Dela—
Dela!
You finally recognized me.
You've really grown. Outward, anyway.
A prince from a faraway land.
Is it my fault for having changed so much,
or are we simply drifting apart on the currents of time?
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
Aren't you boys cold?
Don't push yourselves.
You poor boys.
I'll bring you something warm to wear.
Your Highness, this is Father and Grandfather.
I hear you've been of great assistance to several members of my family.
Not at all.
You can take off your coat.
Here you go.
And this is Lady Tamako!
Hello.
Hello...
This is the person Dela showed us, right?
I'm told you've been looking after Choi and Dela for me.
Not at all!
They've helped us out a ton too!
Sorry about all of this.
Please try some of our sweet bean mochi, if you'd like.
They're delicious.
Your Highness!
Have some tea!
That was great!
Mochidel Icious, right?
I wish the rest of our people could eat this too.
Heh.
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Mecha Mochidis Gusting.
Final Episode
Another Year Draws to a Close
The prince ended up coming here...
Yeah...
Tamako!
Oh, I thought you left already.
Like I would.
I thought you'd be taking the day off from school.
So, what's up with him?
He's having breakfast at our place.
That's not what I meant.
That's right, Sis.
Huh?
He came here to pick you up, didn't he?
Huh?!
Well, I think it'd be best if you, uh...
expressed your feelings more honestly.
You're being quite nosy, Mochizou.
Tamako!
Mornin'!
I heard from Grandpa.
He said the prince was here!
Wow. And you only just spoke to him yesterday.
Your household really attracts
the most interesting characters.
A talking bird, Choi, and now a prince.
Hmm...
Tamako?
Well, I'm kinda panicking right now.
So am I!
I'm sure you've got a lot to think about.
Make sure you put in the time and
effort to properly plan your life out!
Do what you think is right.
We've got your back.
Huh?
Okay.
Hey.
What?
His Highness...
He got dragged off to Usa Bath by the people of the market.
They said they wanted to talk to him about some things.
That so?
Don't you have anything you'd like to ask him as well?
Tamako'd have to talk to Mecha Mochidel Icious before me.
It's Mochidis Gusting.
Then tell him to change his name and get back to me!
Try this, if you'd like.
Have some tea too.
Oh, let's all take a picture together.
Uh, um...
Come on, Choi. You get in too.
Say "tofu"!
I'll take the next one.
Um!
Could you sign this with "To Tokiwa Hall" later?
How long does it take to get here from your country?
How old are you?
Looks like he's a bit younger than Tamako.
Yup.
The bird on your shoulder is so cute!
Have any siblings?
What do you do every day?
One question at a time, please!
Oh no!
I wonder if Tamako's okay.
She's off in her own world right now.
Right.
Tamako.
You don't have to make a decision right away.
Yeah.
Take your time.
Come on, I know that!
I could even become Tamako
Kitashirakawa if you wanted me to.
Hey there, my girl.
I see you're back.
And you brought Shiori with you!
Dela!
They're all closed.
Sorry, I need to go.
Tamako?
Hey, my girl!
Come on!
What happened to all of you?
Huh? Tamako!
Welcome home, Tamako.
Oh, welcome home, Sis.
Hey...
Welcome home.
The people of the market are all at Usa Bath, apparently.
The prince and Choi are there as well.
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
It's just like that one time everyone closed their shops in the middle of the afternoon.
Huh?
Sorry, I got kinda scared...
I mean...
You know...
It brought back memories...
Tamako!
When Mom—
My girl!
Rest your feathers against this bosom of mine!
Finally, you're back to normal!
Thanks—
Pat, pat, Tamako.
Sorry...
By the way, my girl.
How do you feel about it?
Huh?
About becoming my prince's bride.
No, wait.
Didn't you fall for me to begin with?
Is that true, Tamako?!
What? No...
A love triangle?
No wait, I'm not seeing the shape here at all!
Anyway, my girl.
How do you feel?
Huh?
You've got a lot on your mind, right?
Would you care to tell me about them?
I...
Tamako Market
I've been here all my life.
My family runs a mochi shop,
so I woke to the smell of red beans every morning.
My dad and granddad were always hard at work making mochi,
except during Obon and New Year's.
The market was my playground when I was little.
I went to Just Meat and the sashimi place with fake currency in hand,
but they'd always play along with me and tell me to "come again."
When I started going to school,
everyone would greet me in the morning
and welcome me home on my way back.
Oh, yeah!
I think I got in a fight with Dad
and ran away to Usa Bath once.
I wanted a magic baton when I was in elementary school.
So I saved my pocket money and went to buy it.
Now that I think back on it, I was 500 yen short.
But then Midori's grandpa gave me a discount!
When Anko was born, Mr. Gohei came to see her every day.
Dad kept yelling at him, "She's not your daughter!"
I used to talk to Mochizou through the window every day until it got late, until Dad snapped at me
and Mrs. Ooji made us the string telephone.
Mochizou's
Mine
She said we could use it to talk in secret.
Oh, right!
There was a small fire once at Just Meat.
That must've been terrible.
Shimizu always gave me a good deal on soy pulp,
Kaoru always gave me the prettiest flowers,
the Uotanis taught me how to cook,
and Shiraki always used our mochi for his power udon noodles.
Every day at this market feels like a festival.
That's why I never felt lonely.
I'm glad to be here.
I'm glad I was born and raised here.
That's why I...
Hold it right there!
We need to talk, Your Highness.
Yes?
I've had my eyes on that Tamako girl,
and I've observed her for nearly a year now.
That girl...
has nothing but her family and mochi on her mind.
She's pointlessly lively and cheerful,
and big-hearted, almost to a fault.
She's the sort of kind-hearted soul who'd let
Choi and me live at her house without a fuss.
She likes to take care of others, and she showed
me that by serving me delicious mochi everyday.
And she kept calling me "Dela" like we were the closest of buddies.
That's why I ended up staying here this long.
Therefore, she is not fit to be a princess!
Dela...
Please give up on her!
Hold it right there!
Um... We need to talk...
I was born and raised here in Usagiyama.
I don't really know much about the outside world.
How should I say this, uh...
I'm sorry, but I can't!
I'm just a girl from a mochi sh—achoo!
Look, Your Highness!
As you can see, this girl's in love with me, so—
I'm sorry!
To tell the truth, I never once
read her fortune regarding this.
I just thought it'd be nice if someone like Lady Tamako could be our princess.
So...
Dela, Choi.
This lady here is not a princess candidate.
Huh?
What?
Look at this bouquet the florist kindly gave me.
I'm sure this is what you smelt on her.
This...
You're right. She always has these flowers near her...
So what, it was a misunderstanding?
It all came crashing down, right from the very foundation.
Midori...
Midori!
Dela!
Yes, ma'am!
You don't have to read her fortune anymore.
Now...
With that, will you two come back with me?
I felt quite lonely without the two of you around.
Yes...
Tamako.
The yellowtails are going cheap!
Here's your delivery.
Would you like some tofu?
Welcome.
It's like a festival.
Indeed.
Hey!
Are you sure this car's okay, Your Highness?
It's wonderful!
Thank you very much.
Are you really gonna go back?
Thank you so much for your help.
I'll definitely repay you for this someday.
Lady Choi, how about I return after helping the mochi shop out on New Year's Eve?
Yeah, that sounds good.
We need Dela around.
Not happening.
Aww.
It's gonna get lonely around here.
Choi, come visit us whenever you want!
You're pretty much part of the family now.
We'll keep a room for you.
I will!
Choi!
Come on, this is way too sudden!
Here, a souvenir.
It's so cute!
Take this too.
It's so shiny!
And this is from me.
Thank you!
Huh?
What?
That was supposed to be a joke...
No thanks.
Huh?
That medal's important to you.
I can't accept it.
In return, I'd like to give you this.
Thanks.
See you, Choi!
Choi? Choi!
What's the matter, Your Highness?
Dela's gone...
What?
Whaaat?!
They left...
I wonder if they'll invite us over someday.
I wanna see the royal palace!
I think that might be a bit much...
You think? Maybe as a favor for their friends?
Want me to invite you over?
Wait.
Why haven't you gone home?
What?
It kinda feels like that ship already sailed.
Whaaat?!
He says he's gonna stay here until after New Year's Eve.
But before that, we have Christmas.
A whole bird, well-roasted,
packed with spices and fried to a crisp.
That sounds good.
I've been holding back all this time.
I wonder if Dela's tasty.
That's kinda scary.
Very scary!
Life isn't only made up of farewells.
Life is only human because of meetings and encounters.
Hey there, Dela!
We've got some New Year's tuna.
Lots and lots of tuna!
Wow, you hit the jackpot!
Nice card, yeah!
All right!
Everything's half-priced from now!
Here you go.
Come again.
This year, I'm gonna give Tamako her present for sure.
Here are your mirror mochi.
Thanks for all your business this year.
Happy New Year!
Stop kicking up dust.
I'm cleaning! Cleaning.
This is a nice place.
with our mochi
Unlike back home, there were days when I felt I'd freeze to death.
But that's not all.
I always felt warm right here.
Always?
Yeah, always.
Come again!
It was fun.
Thanks.
Happy New Year.
Sis, is this all right?
I'm going to leave without saying a word to my girls.
Yeah, it is.
It's against my policy to make girls cry.
Thanks for taking care of me.
Dad!
Could I have some more mirror mochi?
Dela!
I'm so busy!
This smells like the prince...
Dela...
Hello!
Welcome!
You look busy.
Sure am.
I always am at this time of the year.
I have to send this off.
Oh my, it's heavy.
Kaoru!
Could I get some flowers?
Sure.
For Tamako's birthday?
Y-Yeah...
Maybe we should put it in a box and surprise her.
S-Sure.
Dela left earlier than expected.
Yeah.
He didn't even have any soba noodles.
This is kinda heavy.
Tamako!
And hello to you too, Anko.
You're so cute, Midori!
Tamako!
Today was your birthday,
wasn't it?
Huh?
You remembered?
Thanks, Mochizou!
Wow, I wonder what it is.
Looks pretty big.
Open it up!
"Wasn't it?" Yeah, right.
Hey—
He totally knew.
One, two, ta-da!
Dela!
Hm?
Tamako...
Whoa!
Tamako! Tamako?!
What? What?!
What's going on?!
Tamako!
What happened?!
Dela!
When are you coming back?!
Oh hey, it's Choi!
Tamako!
Please tell Dela to hurry up and come back already!
The years pass by,
Okay, I will. But please let him stay here for a while longer.
but there are some things that never change.
Thanks, Mochizou!
They're invisible to the naked eye,
This is the best present!
but visible to the mind's eye.
I know, right?
Mister's tasty, after all.
Congrats, Tamako.
Just wait a bit longer, Choi.
Dela, you're as gross as ever!
Let's go visit the shrine, Dela!
The End
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it