Erika, thanks for coming with me.
I couldn't water them over the
weekend, so I was a little worried.
You really do love your flowers, Tsubomi.
When I look at them, it makes me feel all happy inside.
Hurry up and get better, little flower!
Next!
He's so cool!
They start practice in the mornings, huh?
Outta the way!
No photographs, please!
It'll interfere with our training!
Sheesh!
This is for everyone's benefit! A few snaps won't hurt!
See her? She's the scoop-lover, Tada Kanae!
Well, in any case... I got some photos of the
school's top star, the student council president!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Precure?
Yeah! Apparently, some people saw them at the park!
So... Precure really do exist?!
Tsubomi!
They're talking about us.
You shouldn't be happy about this, Erika...
All right, everyone!
I got some new photos!
There's a horde of scoops in this batch too!
It's nice that people from other classes can look at these photos too.
I guess.
Whoa! Take a look at this!
Daiki got hit right in the face by that ball!
This photo of Kurumi buried in the snow is pretty funny too!
H-Hey, lemme look at that!
Stop it with these photos!
I'm not exactly happy about being
photographed while looking stupid, either!
This is pretty mean, Kanae!
Oh, calm down.
Scoops are the flowers of photography!
A photo that captures a heart-pounding moment...
That is what brings smiles to people's faces!
You see? Everyone's ecstatic!
Well, I'm not happy at all!
Oh, don't be so shy.
He's so manly!
Next time, I'm going to do a scoop on Precure!
Hope you're all looking forward to it!
Yeah!
Whaaat?!
I mean, umm...
Those photographs of the Precure...
I'll be looking forward to them!
All right!
Leave it to me!
Scoop! The Precures'
Identities are Revealed?!
What's with the whole "I'll be looking forward to them"?
Well... I had to say something.
If it gets out that you two are Precure, horrible things will happen!
Horrible things?! What'll happen?!
Now that...
Now that?!
...is a secret!
The heck?
Still, Kanae really does love photos, doesn't she?
But she took a photo of me looking like an idiot. That's just mean.
There were some wonderful photos there, though!
Only because they were of your
beloved student council president.
I-It's not just 'cause of that!
Those photos really showed how the student council president was putting his all into his training!
If you say so...
Oh, it's Kanae!
Miura, you really saw the Precure?
Yeah. In a dream.
Your dream?!
Yeah... Some customers at the shop claimed to have seen them, but I don't know anything.
Well, thanks...
I only saw them in a dream.
Another dream, huh...
Though, now you mention it, I heard a rumor that the Precure were seen near the botanical gardens.
Hmm... The botanical gardens, huh?
Th-This isn't good!
We have to report to Cure Flower!
I can't exactly take photos of the Precure in someone's dreams...
No... Everyone's waiting for this!
I'll definitely get this scoop!
Hey, it's Daiki!
Stop that!
You're just going to end up capturing the moments where I mess up, after all.
Come on! If I just take photos of you looking cool, it won't be interesting, right?
So as long as your photos are
"interesting," nothing else matters?
H-Hey, what's with you?!
Everyone enjoys these, so it's fine, isn't it?!
Kanae...
I'll show him! I'm definitely going to get a scoop on those Precure!
Even Daiki will enjoy it!
So these are the botanical gardens from the rumor, huh?
That girl...
She's followed us here!
Hm?
What was that just now? A bird?!
U-Um...
Thanks...
What was with him? He was really cool, but...
Hey, those weird animals vanished!
Um... Good afternoon.
Good afternoon, Miss Photographer.
What is that?
Lord Coupe, please help us!
What a strange stuffed decoration.
If it's photos you're after, we've got
some really pretty flowers over here.
Shall I show you?
No, that's all right. Flowers aren't my thing.
I'm actually on the hunt for Precure!
"Precure"? I don't recall having heard of such a flower.
No, they're not flowers!
They're legendary warriors that fight monsters and stuff!
Warriors?
How impressive! Who are these people you speak of?
Well... uh...
Sorry for wasting your time!
Chypre, Coffret, it's all right now.
I was so scared!
Lord Coupe, thank you very much!
I wonder if the Flower of her Heart will be all right...
How are the likes of those Precure managing to delay you so?
Both Kumojacky and Kobraja underestimated them.
What a waste of our time.
Just hurry and defeat the Precure.
As you command. This time I, Sasorina, shall crush them underfoot!
We've got trouble! That camera girl was at Cure Flower's place!
Whaaat?!
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
At any rate, we have to go warn Erika!
Kanae?!
Has she already found out that I'm a Precure?!
Maybe she found out about Erika instead...
So kids nowadays start off using a digital camera...
Tsubomi!
Do you have business with Kurumi too, Hanasaki?
No, I don't...
Yo! Welcome.
You must be Tsubomi.
I-I am ! Nice to meet you! I'm Hanasaki Tsubomi!
Nice to meet you. I'm Erika's father.
You perfectly fit my mental image of your name!
I'd kind of built up a mental image of you from what my daughter had told me...
but you really are exactly as I imagined!
Yes, indeed...
This! Is! Tsubomi!
Tsubomi!
A-hem.
Hey, Dad. You're hassling her too much.
Oh, my apologies!
You using my camera for your
photos is an honor, Mr. Kurumi!
An honor?
Her dad is an internationally
renowned top-class photographer!
I wouldn't go that far, but...
Kanae came to get some
photography advice from my dad.
Oh, that's what it is. She's not here about Precure...
Ever since I was young,
I've always admired Mr. Kurumi's photographs,
and thought that someday, I'd try to
become as good a photographer as him!
Well that is truly an honor!
That's why I want to take more scoop-worthy photographs!
Scoops, huh...
Well, merely being eyecatching or surprising doesn't make a photo...
But an interesting scoop makes everyone happy!
I want to take truly amazing
photos and make everyone smile!
A photo that everyone will enjoy is something that makes both the viewer and the subject happy, right?
This photo lacks love!
Love?
Indeed! The most important thing... is love.
Photographs of people should be like a window into their hearts!
This boy's burning soul for soccer
should be captured in its purest form!
That's why a photographer must always have love!
Indeed, the most precious thing when taking any photograph... is love!
Hey, Dad!
Oh, I'm sorry!
When I start talking about photos, I get all fired up...
Kanae's really lost in her thoughts.
The Flower of that girl's Heart seems to be waning a little.
Maybe we should go cheer her up?
Yeah, you're right.
So as long as your photos are
"interesting," nothing else matters?
Do my photos really lack love?
I've found a sad little girl!
Whoa! A weirdo!
What an insolent child.
The Flower of your Heart really is wilting...
It's Sasorina!
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
What's wrong with taking interesting photos?!
Why are you asking us?!
Flaaaaaaaaaaaash!
Kanae's Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen!
Flaaaaaash!
Flashsh!
It seems that getting your photo taken by that thing freezes you in place!
Erika!
Let's do it!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Flash!
Your strange game ends here!
Leave this to us Precure!
So you've finally shown yourselves, Precure!
Desertrian, get them!
All I was trying to do with my photos was make people smile! Why can't you understand?!
Photos nowadays are just digital data, aren't they?
Letting your heart weaken over
something like that is just stupid...
It's not stupid!
Kanae's heart weakened because she
was that serious about taking photos!
Hmph.
We'll take back Kanae's precious heart, no matter what!
Flaaaaaaash!
Marine!
Aww, now you're all alone.
Whatcha gonna do now, Precure?
The Precure...
At this rate, she'll get you as well, Blossom!
Guess we'll have to use a Heart Seed!
We'll use a Red Seed!
Shout "The Blessed Perfume of Red Light!"
Then shout "A spray makes my mood speed up!"
The Blessed Perfume of Red Light!
A spray makes my mood speed up!
Use that power to save Marine!
She's up to something.
Desertrian, get her!
Flaaaaaaaaaaash!
H-Huh? She vanished?!
What happened to me?!
The Red Heart Seed increases your speed!
Now, quickly defeat the Desertrian!
I'm over here!
I feel like a bolt of lightning!
No one can stop me now! Let's go!
Well if nothing else, you've got spirit!
Desertrian!
Amazing!
Blossom...
Butt Punch!
She used her butt, but it's a punch?!
I wanted to take photos that everyone would enjoy!
My love of photos is unsurpassed!
Hmph! Love, you say?
Stop talking about such pointless rubbish!
It's not pointless!
You're just toying with Kanae's photo-loving heart...
And I've had it up to here with this!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Flowers, shine forth!
Precure Pink Forte Wave!
Marine!
Next time I, Sasorina, will knock you all down!
Thank you so much, Blossom!
I was in a real pinch back there!
It's all thanks to the Heart Perfume!
That speed just now didn't even feel like it was my own.
The Heart Seeds still have many other powers!
Now, return the Flower of the Heart to this girl!
Hey, Kanae! If you sleep out here, you're gonna catch a cold!
Huh?
Where's the camera monster?!
No way! You were dreaming too?
I had this dream where a camera monster was causing trouble for everyone.
I wonder if it meant that my photos are causing trouble for everyone...
That's not so!
Everyone really does love your photos!
I guarantee it!
No...
My photos really did lack love.
Thank you, both of you!
Erika, tell your dad this...
I'm going to become a loving photographer, just like him!
The Flower of her Heart is shining white!
In the language of flowers, a
blackberry means "caring for others."
I'm sure that Kanae will be able to take
even more wonderful photos in the future!
I think a Heart Seed is going to be born...
You really do love your flowers, Tsubomi.
Hanasaki! I wanted to say thanks for yesterday.
I-I really didn't do anything!
You woke me up when I was
sleeping on the bank, didn't you?
Well, rather than just saying thanks... I'll give you these!
Whoa! These are...
Looks like you like them!
Next time I'm gonna get some photos of those Precure, so you've got that to look forward to!
I want my photos to convey to everyone the Precures' hearts as they fight for justice!
See ya!
Looks like Kanae's still gonna be on the Precure hunt, then.
These are...
It's not like that!
How do I put this... They're like good luck photos?
Anyway, you've totally got the wrong idea!
Give them back!
Erika, please give them back!
I guess it really does come down to love.
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
What is romance?! Where will I find love?! Please tell me, my fairy!
Hello, we're your fairies!
Romance is but a flower bud!
Love is found beyond the stars!
The student council president is just too amazing!
Unable to stop my maiden's heart, I await our date beyond the stars!
People grow every time their loves are lost!
I shall wipe your tears away!
HeartCatch Precure:
My Beloved Student Council Prez!
A Maiden's Heart Laid Bare!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!