Hey.
Here you go.
Thanks for always helping me out.
You're a genius when it comes to finding rare CDs, Sayaka.
I just have really good luck, I'm sure.
This person has really amazing performances.
Do you want to listen, too, Sayaka?
Y-You sure?
I'd like to let you listen through speakers, but we're in a hospital, so...
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 3     I'm not scared of anything anymore
Tiro Finale!
Mami-san is always cool.
This isn't a show, you know?
I don't want you to forget that what we're doing is dangerous.
Yes!
It didn't drop a Grief Seed.
That's because it was just a familiar that split off from a witch.
They don't have Grief Seeds.
So it wasn't a witch.
We haven't been able to find any lately.
We can't ignore the familiars, though.
They develop into witches just like the original, if they mature.
Anyway, let's go.
Did you two find something to wish for?
What about you, Madoka?
Well, I guess that's normal.
Especially when you actually try to think of something specific.
Mami-san, what type of wish did you make?
No, you don't really have to tell me!
In my case, I...
...didn't even have the time to think about it.
It's not like I regret it.
I think my current way of life is much better than dying back there.
But you know, I think it's better for a girl to carefully consider...
...what they want if they have the opportunity to do so.
Especially since I didn't have that opportunity, you know?
Hey, Mami-san, does your wish have to be for yourself?
Huh?
Like, hypothetically... Hypothetically, you know?
What if there was someone worse off than me,
and I used my wish for that person?
You mean Kamijou-kun?
God, I said I was just speaking hypothetically!
It's not really necessary for the person in the contract to be the target of the wish.
It's not like it hasn't happened before, either.
I can't say I like what you're saying, though.
If you're considering granting a wish for someone else,
then it's even more important that you pause now to consider what you really want.
Miki-san, do you want his wish to come true,
or do you just want to be the person who made his wish come true... a person to which he'd be indebted?
Mami-san...
They might sound the same, but they're completely different.
That was kind of mean.
I'm sorry, but I needed to say that now.
If you don't realise the difference early on, you're going to regret it later.
You're right.
I wasn't thinking hard enough.
Sorry about that.
This is pretty difficult stuff to deal with, isn't it?
You shouldn't just rush and pick something.
The sooner the better for me, though.
That won't do. Girls hate guys who pressure them.
It really isn't that simple, is it?
Considering my position, I can't really push you to make a choice, either.
Giving you any suggestions on the matter is against the rules, too.
I wonder if just wanting to become one is enough.
Madoka, are you just after the power?
No, that's not what I mean...
Or maybe it is...
I'm slow, and there isn't really anything good about me.
So if I could be cool and wonderful like Mami-san, that would make me more than happy.
You can become far stronger than Mami if you become a magical girl.
Huh?
Of course, it also depends on what kind of wish you make when you form the contract,
but even I can't estimate how large of a Soul Gem you might produce.
I've never met a girl with such potential before.
What are you talking about? You must be joking.
No—
Madoka, are you awake?
Yeah, what's wrong?
Again?
Geez...
W-Water...
Damn you, baldy! If you want to drink, then drink by your damn self!
I'll pull that wig off you!
Thank you.
Should I get some hot chocolate started?
Yeah, that'd be good.
I wonder why Mum likes working so much.
Working at that company wasn't really a dream of hers, right?
Hmm... Mum doesn't like working; she likes working hard.
Huh?
I'm sure there are a lot of things that she doesn't like or are pretty trying for her,
but the satisfaction she gets when she overcomes those obstacles is really precious to her.
It wasn't like it was her dream to work somewhere.
But still, she's living the way she wants to live.
Some dreams can come true like that.
So you can make how you live your dream?
I'm sure there are people who'd disagree, but I really like that about your mum.
I can respect that, and I take pride in it.
I can tell people she's a wonderful person.
Yeah.
You know that you're putting innocent civilians in danger, don't you?
They've been chosen by Kyubey.
They're not "innocent civilians" any longer.
You're leading the two of them into becoming magical girls.
And that's what you don't like?
That's right. It's a nuisance.
Especially Kaname Madoka.
I see. So you've noticed her potential, as well.
I can't let her form a contract under any circumstances.
Is it because anyone stronger than you will get in your way?
That sounds like something a person who's been bullied her whole life would think.
I would prefer not fighting you.
In that case, you need to work hard so I don't run into you again.
I'm sure tonight's the last time we'll end this with talking.
Hey. Sorry for the wait.
Huh? You couldn't see Kamijou-kun?
I guess today wasn't a good day to see him.
I came all the way out here, too.
Pretty rude, huh?
What's wrong?
There's something over there...
It's a Grief Seed!
It's about to hatch!
No way. Why is there one here?
This is bad. We have to get away from here fast.
The barrier will go up soon.
That maze thing again?
Madoka, have you asked Mami-san for her cell number?
No.
Darn, we should've.
Madoka, go and get Mami-san.
I'll watch over the seed.
You can't!
It's too dangerous!
We still have time until the witch hatches,
but once the barrier goes up, you won't be able to leave it.
I don't know if Mami will make it here in time...
You won't know where the seed is once the maze goes up, right?
I can't let it hatch in a place like this.
Madoka, go find her.
I'll stay with Sayaka.
If Mami comes here, she'll know where I am because of the telepathy.
If I watch over the Grief Seed with Sayaka,
I'll be able to guide Mami so she takes the shortest route through the barrier.
Thank you, Kyubey.
I'll... hurry and get Mami-san as fast as I can.
Are you scared, Sayaka?
Well, yeah. Of course.
If you can come up with a wish, I can turn you into a magical girl right here.
In Surgery
Yeah.
I might ask you if I have to.
But I'll wait for now.
This is important to me. I'd rather not decide until I'm really ready.
Here, right?
Kyubey, what's going on?
We're good for now.
There's no signs that it's going to hatch right away.
Sayaka-chan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm about to fall asleep from boredom.
It'd be worse to stimulate the egg by using a lot of magic next to it.
You don't need to hurry.
Could you come as calmly as possible?
Got it.
I'm glad we made it in time.
I'd like to get mad at you guys for taking too many risks,
but this was the best choice this time.
Now we don't have to worry about the witch getting—
I thought I said I didn't want to see you again.
I'll take down the prey this time.
You two, withdraw.
I can't do that.
We need to get Miki-san and Kyubey.
I promise they won't get hurt.
You think I'd trust you?
I-Idiot... Now's not the time for this.
I don't plan on letting you get hurt,
but if you struggle too much, I can't promise that won't happen.
This witch is in a different class from the others so far.
If you sit still, I'll let you out on the way back.
Let's go, Kaname-san.
O-Okay.
Wai—
Um... Mami-san.
What is it?
I thought about my wish a lot, and...
Do you think you know what to pick?
Yes, but I think you might get mad at me for not thinking hard enough.
What wish do you plan on having granted?
I've never had a subject I was good at or any skill that I could be proud of.
I kept thinking I'm going to continue on in life not being useful to anyone,
just causing problems for people.
I hated that.
But I met you, and you showed me what it was like to fight to save people.
You told me I might be able to do the same thing.
It made me happier than anything...
So if I become a magical girl, that will be my wish.
If even I can help people and be proud of that, that's the best wish I could have.
It's hard, you know?
You get hurt,
and you don't have time to fall in love or hang out with friends.
But I really want to be like you after seeing you try so hard in spite of all of that.
You shouldn't want to be like me.
I'm... just trying to act cool.
No matter how scary it is, how hard it is, I can't talk to anyone about it.
I always cry alone.
Being a magical girl isn't good at all.
You're not alone anymore, Mami-san.
I... I guess you're right.
Will you really fight with me from now on?
Will you stay by my side?
Yes, if you're really okay with someone like me.
You got me.
I still need to be a teacher for you, too.
I guess I'm really not that great after all.
Mami-san...
But since you have the chance, you should think of something for your wish.
Since I have the chance, you think? I guess you have a point.
It's a contract, so you might as well get something out of it.
Make yourself a billionaire, or get yourself a wonderful boyfriend.
Anything goes!
That's not really...
How about this then?
If you haven't thought of a wish by the time we've taken out this witch,
how about you get Kyubey to treat us to a big dinner and a cake?
A-A cake?
Yeah... The largest, most extravagant party cake you've ever seen!
We'll have a party with everyone.
It'll be to celebrate Kaname Madoka and I joining together as a magical girl team.
I'm going to become a magical girl for cake?
If you don't like it, then come up with something yourself!
Mami.
In Surgery
The Grief Seed has begun to move.
It's started to hatch. Hurry!
Okay. Got it.
We'll take care of this fast today.
Hey!
I feel light.
It's the first time I've been this happy while fighting.
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
I'm not alone anymore!
Sorry for the wait.
You made it...
Watch out.
It's coming out.
Sorry for attacking you right after you hatched, but I'm ending this now.
Here I go!
She did it!
Tiro Finale!
She couldn't have...
You two, hurry up and contract with me!
Madoka! Sayaka!
Decide on your wishes!
Hurry!
There's no need for that.
I'll be the one to take him out.
I guess you two escaped with your lives, then.
Burn this moment into your eyes.
That's what happens when you become a magical girl.
Give that back.
Give it back.
That... That... belongs to Mami-san!
I said give that back to Mami-san!
These are for magical girls.
You two have no right to touch one.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Illustrator Tsuji Santa (Nitro+)
Mami-san was really kind.
As an example of the resolve we'll need to fight, she...
Episode 4     There are such things as miracles and magic
There are such things as miracles and magic.