Irisviel.
Are you all right?
So they waited for Kiritsugu to
leave before attacking head-on...
That lightning, and this brazen method of assault...
The enemy is most likely Rider.
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
And link them on to tomorrow
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Crying and embracing the night
Screaming its grief out loud
The distant ideals gently heal
These legs that've stepped forward
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
No matter where I go
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Whoa!
Hey, Saber!
Rider...
I heard you guys had a castle, so I came over to see it...
But it's kind of gloomy-looking.
And what's with that battle attire?
You aren't wearing your fashionable suit tonight?
Rider, what did you come for?
Can't you tell?
For a drink. What else?
Come on, stop standing there and show me around.
Surely you have a garden fit for a banquet.
I can't stand this castle. It's too dusty!
The Grail is fated to end up in the
hands of the one most worthy of it.
And the battle here in Fuyuki City will determine who that person is.
But if it's just a means to decide,
then there's no need for bloodshed.
If all the Heroic Spirits can
acknowledge each other's ranks...
...then the matter will settle itself.
Oh?
So you wish to start by comparing your rank against mine, Rider?
Indeed.
As we both call ourselves kings,
this is not something we can avoid.
You might consider this a Grail
Dialogue rather than a Grail War.
Which of us is more suited to be the king of the Grail?
The matter will clarify itself as we drink.
That's more than enough nonsense...
...mongrel.
Archer, what is your business here?
Ah, I saw him in town,
so I figured I might as well invite him.
You're late, Goldy.
Well, you did come here by foot, unlike me. Makes sense.
So you chose to hold the Banquet of Kings in this depressing place?
How will you make up for the rudeness of making me walk all the way here?
Aw, don't say that.
Here, start with a drink.
What is this cheap swill?
You really thought we could discern a Heroic Spirit hierarchy with this?
Is that so?
This was among the best I could find at the city marketplace.
That's because you are ignorant of true drink, foolish mongrel.
Behold, and acknowledge your folly.
This is the drink of a king.
Splendid indeed.
This is really good!
My treasury houses only the finest,
whether it be drinks or weapons.
This alone should indicate which
among us is the greatest of kings.
Archer.
Your finest drink is indeed worthy of the best vessel.
Unfortunately, the Grail is not a drinking cup.
First, you'll have to tell us the scale of the wish you have for the Grail.
Quit making distinctions, mongrel.
The premise of having to fight for the Grail already makes no sense to begin with.
The Grail already belongs to me.
Every single one of the world's treasures trace their origin back to my treasury.
So you're saying you once had the Grail?
You would know exactly what it is?
No.
Don't see this with your mongrel standards.
The wealth in my treasury has long
since surpassed my own knowledge.
But the fact that it's treasure is enough to make it mine.
And anyone who would take it for themselves...
...is nothing but a brazen thief.
Your words are no different from Caster's insane rants.
It appears he isn't the only Servant to have gone mad.
Well, I don't know...
I think I have an idea what Goldy's real name is.
Then what, Archer?
Are you saying we just need your consent if we want the Grail?
Exactly.
However, I have absolutely no reason to
bestow such a gift to mongrels like you both.
Selfish, aren't you?
Fool.
Only my subjects and people
are worthy of my compassion.
In other words, Rider, if you submit yourself to me...
I can let you have a drinking cup or two anytime.
That's out of the question.
But, Archer, it's not like you
actually want the Grail, do you?
Of course not.
But I must administer my judgment
to thieves who are after my treasures.
It's a matter of principle.
So then, Archer...
What justice and reasoning do you speak of?
Of the law.
My law that I set down as king.
Perfect, indeed.
You're the king because you see your own law through.
But you know...
I want the Grail so much that I can't stop myself.
It's my style to simply take what I want.
After all, I'm Iskandar...
...King of Conquerors.
It doesn't matter.
You break the law, and I punish you.
There is no room for discussion.
Which means...
...all that's left for us is to cross swords.
Anyway, Archer.
Why don't we finish drinking this wine?
We can fight each other to the death afterwards.
But of course.
Or do you think light of this wine that I let you have?
Absolutely not!
How could I not help myself to such delicious wine?
King of Conquerors.
You acknowledge someone else's rightful
ownership of the Grail, yet you'll take it by force?
Why would you go so far for the Grail?
True incarnation.
Huh?
Huh?!
Hey, wasn't your goal supposed to be world conquest—
Idiot.
What's the point in having some
drinking cup conquer the world for me?
Conquest is a dream I'll entrust to myself.
All I want from the Grail...
...is the first step of that process.
Mongrel.
You'd challenge me for something so small?
Even if mana gives us form in this world, we still ultimately remain Servants.
I want to be firmly rooted to this world as a living human.
And with a body of my very own,
I shall defy both heaven and earth.
That's what the act of conquest is all about.
It's how it begins, proceeds, and is finished.
Such is my path of conquest.
I've decided, Rider.
I shall kill you myself.
There's no need to point that out now.
I also intend to take that treasury of
yours for myself, so be ready for that.
That's not how a king should be.
Let us hear what you wish for, then.
I wish for my homeland's salvation.
With the omnipotent wish-granting device,
I shall avert Britain's fate of destruction.
They're drinking, of all things.
Is it really okay to just leave Archer alone?
I can't do anything.
Since he's the king among kings, he can't
possibly ignore the dialogue being thrust at him.
By the way, Kirei.
What do you think of the difference
in strength between Rider and Archer?
I think the key lies in whether Rider has a
trump card more powerful than Gordius Wheel.
Since Rider is enjoying his drink with his Master undefended,
there is no better time than now for a surprise attack.
It doesn't matter if we have a chance of winning or not.
Even if Assassin is defeated, we'll have achieved
our goal if we can discern the difference in strength.
There's something we can
probably try at this point, Kirei.
I have no objections.
It'll probably take about ten
minutes to gather all the Assassins.
Good. Give the order.
Although this is a big gamble,
we luckily have nothing to lose.
Kirei, use a Command Spell to give this order to Assassin:
Achieve victory, no matter the cost.
Hey, King of Knights.
Did you just say that you would change fate?
Does that mean you wish to change the past?
That's right.
Even if it is a wish that a miracle cannot fulfill,
if the Holy Grail truly is omnipotent, I'm sure...
Uh, Saber...
Just making sure, but that Britain country fell during your time, during your rule, no?
That's right.
That's why I can't accept it.
That's why I lament it.
I want to change how it all ended.
Because it's none other than my responsibility...
Archer, what's so funny?
She calls herself a king and is
praised by everyone as such...
Yet she says that she "laments" it?
How can I possibly keep a straight face?!
Saber.
Surely you aren't saying that you spurn the very marks you left on history?
I am!
Why are you puzzled?
Why do you laugh?
The country that gave me my blade,
the country I offered my life to, was destroyed.
Why is it strange that I'd lament that?
Did you hear that, Rider?
The things this little girl who calls herself King of Knights is saying?!
"The country I offered my life to", she says!
How is that funny at all?!
A king should make any sacrifice
to ensure his country's prosperity.
No.
The king does not sacrifice anything.
It is the country and the people
that sacrifice themselves for the king.
Absolutely not the other way round.
What?
Those are the words of a tyrant!
Exactly.
We are heroes because we are tyrants.
However, Saber.
If a king regrets his rule or its conclusion, that king is nothing but a fool.
Worse than a tyrant.
Iskandar, your reign ended with your heirs slain, and your empire dissolved into three parts.
You have no regrets about how it ended?
None.
If the end was brought about by my decisions and the way
my subjects lived, then I will accept its destruction as inevitable.
I shall grieve. And I shall weep.
But I shall never regret.
You...
Let alone undo it!
Such a foolish act would only mock all
who fought with me to build my empire!
Only brute warriors find glory in destruction!
Of what worth is a king who
fails to protect the powerless?
A just rule, with just laws...
Those are the true duties of a king!
So you, the king, are a slave to what is just?
I don't mind.
A king would willingly die for his ideals.
That's not how a person should live.
If I rule a country as its king,
I cannot hope to live as a person.
King of Conquerors.
You could never understand, as you seek the Grail merely for your own benefit.
You, who became a ruler only to satisfy your endless greed!
A king without greed is even worse than a figurehead!
Saber.
You said you would die for your ideals.
In life, you must have been a pure and honest saint.
A noble and inviolable figure, certainly.
But who on Earth admires the martyr's thorny path?
Who dreams of such a life?
You see...
A king must be greedier, laugh louder,
and be more furious than everyone else.
He must exemplify the extreme of all things, including good and evil.
That is exactly why his subjects envy and adore him.
And why the flame of wanting to be like the king can burn in the hearts of every civilian.
Proud King of Knights.
The righteousness and ideals you bore may have saved your country once.
However...
I'm sure you know what happened to
those who were constantly and only saved.
What?
You saved your subjects, but you never led them.
You never showed them what a king should be.
You abandoned your men when they lost their way.
Alone and untroubled,
you followed your own pretty little ideals.
Thus, you are no true king.
You are but a little girl, bound by the false idol of a king who serves others but not himself.
I...
What are you laughing at, Archer?
Well, it's just that your anguished
face was quite the sight to behold.
It's just like the face of a virgin deflowered in bed.
Exactly what I like.
Bastard...!
Assassin...
Is this your doing, Goldy?
Tokiomi humiliates himself.
This is ridiculous!
Why are there so many Assassins?!
We are one, split into many.
A Servant who is many and also one.
Yet we are one with many shadows.
A Servant with multiple personalities
materializing into separate entities for each?
R-Rider, uh...
Come on, boy. Calm yourself.
Regardless of whether you treat them as guests, they can still judge who is the greatest king.
You'll invite them to the banquet as well, King of Conquerors?
Of course.
The king's words are for all to hear.
If they have come to listen,
it doesn't matter if they are friend or foe.
Now, don't hold back!
Those who'd speak with us, come forth and take a cup.
This drink is as your blood!
Very well.
I did say this drink is as your blood.
If you insist on spilling it...
So be it.
Saber! Archer!
Here is our banquet's final question.
Must the king be alone in his superiority?
The king has no choice but to be alone!
No, you don't understand at all.
Looks like I'll have to show you exactly what a real king is.
This is...
A Reality Marble?!
Ridiculous...
Turning one's imagined terra into reality...
Here, my armies once rode across the land.
A scenery every single one of my heroes who
shared in my joys and sorrows will never forget.
I can make this world real because it
still exists within the hearts of all of us!
Behold my peerless army!
Their bodies have been destroyed, and their souls have been offered to the world as Heroic Spirits.
Yet, these legendary heroes remain loyal to me!
My bond with them is my greatest treasure, my path of kingship!
The ultimate Noble Phantasm that I, Iskandar, possess:
Ionian Hetairoi!
Every single one of them is a Servant!
It's been a long time, partner.
A king must live a life more vivid than
any other and be a figure for all to admire!
Yes!
The king is the one who collects the envy
of all his heroes and stands as their guide!
Therefore, the king is not alone.
For his will equals that of all his followers combined!
Yes!
Now, then...
Shall we begin, Assassin?
As you can see, the battlefield
we've created is an open plain.
I'm afraid we hold the advantage with our superior numbers.
Annihilate them!
That ending was disappointing.
We've said all there is to say.
I suppose that'll do for today.
Wait, Rider.
I'm not done yet...
You can keep your mouth shut.
Kings were to converse in tonight's banquet.
But I no longer recognize you as a king, Saber.
Little girl, wake up from that sad dream of yours.
If you don't, you'll someday lose even that
modicum of pride you have as a Heroic Spirit.
The dream of the kingship you spoke of is a curse.
What?!
You needn't listen to him, Saber.
You are correct.
Follow the path you believe in.
The agony and conflict you wallow in as you bear
the burden of a kingship too heavy for anyone...
It's really quite pleasurable to see.
Keep at it, King of Knights.
You might actually prove worthy of even more of my love.
Saber...
I remember.
There was once a knight who left Camelot, claiming that King Arthur didn't understand how others felt.
Maybe...
...those sentiments were shared
by everyone at the Round Table.
Episode 11
Grail Dialogue
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
If I can find peace in my recollections
While reminiscing about you
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
Amidst the quietly shifting
Distant memories
Proof of the time I spent with you
Is right here with me
You've shown me what it means
To have overflowing feelings
Even if this world were to end
I'll be right by your side
This begins the second stage.
I'm not a normal human.
It can't be that simple!
Do as you desire.
Your path is now clear.
But that is an evil that must be punished!
Next Episode
The Grail's Invitation