Kumi consults Mitsuki about love,
believing that Mitsuki is
an expert on love.
I come up with the idea of
writing him a love letter,
but he ends up thinking
it's from Mitsuki!
What do we do?!
Mitsuki encourages Kumi to
tell the boy how she feels,
and Kumi ends up confessing
her love to him!
Maybe Mitsuki really is
an expert on love!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes...
Have a nice day.
Everybody is out now.
Mitsuki and Takuto are at the event
for the release of the second single.
I'm so bored!
Oh well, I guess I'll watch some TV!
There! Completely white in no time!
- Wow!
Put one cup of rice wine into the pan
and cook for 30 minutes.
How boring!
What? Did it break?
W-What is this?!
What in the world is going on?!
Could it be a ghost?
How rude!
Who do you think I am?
I am Miss Meroko, a Death Spirit
fearsome enough to silence a crying child!
There!
Y-You're so cruel.
No way! Is it really a ghost?!
No, he's a Death Spirit.
That voice... Could it be?
I-Izumi?!
It's been a long time, Mero!
- W-Why did he show up
- Hey, is my nose squashed?
- all of a sudden?
- No, I think it actually got bigger.
I-Izumi, why are you here
in the human world?
Should I not have come?
I'm not going to be a nuisance...am I?
O-Of course not!
It's absurd to think that
you'll be a nuisance!
Of course,
I'm really glad to see you!
Yeah, aren't you?
Oh yes, this is Jonathan,
who became my partner after you, Mero.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, there is this rumor...
A rumor that Green Onion Ramen
is using Death Spirit powers
to become friends
with a human child.
What?!
The Division Chief told us
to go investigate.
If the rumor is true,
it will be a serious problem.
With a very scary punishment.
Punishment?!
Izumi is such a sadist.
That's because you picked on Mero.
Sorry.
I'm the only one who's allowed
to pick on Mero. Right?
So, is the rumor true?
Is it true?
Th-That's nonsense!
Of course we wouldn't do that.
We are Death Spirits!
I thought so.
Yup!
That's fine if that's the case.
By the way, where is Takuto?
And was it Mitsuki Koyama?
Where is the girl you're in charge of?
T-Takuto is out right now.
He's watching over Mitsuki.
See, we're just doing our job.
Mero, why aren't you with him?
Aren't you madly in love with Takuto?
What? W-Well...
Hey, what is this?
There are so many buttons!
The second single is
a very good song.
I'd love it if everybody could make it
to today's concert for the new single!
Everybody, please come to
Full Moon's live concert
to hear her new single
at Nasu Aquatic Stage
- at two o'clock in the afternoon.
- T-Television!
Right now,
I like TV more than Takuto!
Oh yeah?
I feel like I'm dead.
Hey, hey, there's not much to
do by staying here
so let's go out and play until
Takuto comes back.
Okay.
Great! I can trick them and
somehow get them to go back!
Hey, is there anywhere you want to go?
Yeah.
That Full Moon we just saw on TV...
I want to go to her
new single release concert.
Why there, of all places?!
A-Anyhow, I have to get
in touch with Takuto.
Can you wait here a little bit?
It's the first time in a while that I'll be
going out with Izumi, so I want to dress up.
Oh, I'm so excited.
What?! Izumi is here?!
And not only that, he came
to investigate us?!
Yeah! What should I do?
At any rate, all we can do is to
deceive him and buy some time
until the concert for
the new single is over! Got it?!
Okay... I'll try my best.
What do you mean, "I'll try my best"?
U-Umm... My make-up.
Yes, I tried my best with my make-up.
How do I look?
Dang it, Izumi!
Of course he comes
at a bad time!
I want to meet Izumi!
Huh?
Isn't he a friend of
yours and Meroko's?
I have to say hello.
No! There's no need for that!
Izumi is the most sadistic among
the Death Spirits
and basically lives to pick on others.
If he learns that you not only see
the appearance of Death Spirits
but can also talk to us...
Here, here.
No!
No, more than that, if he finds out
that I help you by using my powers,
he'll immediately report it to
the Division Chief,
and both Meroko and I will get punished
and assigned to someone else.
What?
I'm going to hide while Izumi is around.
Okay.
Don't worry. Just be patient until
the new single release concert is over.
Make sure to pretend that
you can't see us.
Okay, I understand.
Wow, there are so many people.
Full Moon is quite popular, huh?
I-I guess so.
I just have to try to get them
as far away as possible.
Hey, Full Moon is over there.
What? Where?
Follow me.
Full Moon!
Machi and Lisa have arrived.
Hello!
How are you doing, Full Moon?
Mero, did you mean to say "here"
when you said "over there"?
That's strange!
Takuto was saying those things,
but I wonder if
he's that scary of a person.
Something wrong, Full Moon?
Oh? Oh, no.
Then, I'll begin your make-up now.
Yes. Thank you.
Yes, I know. Pretend not to see,
pretend not to see.
Isn't she cuter in person
than on TV?
Do you think so?
To me, Mero is so much cuter.
Oh... She has a nose hair sticking out.
Oh, is something wrong?
I-It's just a little itchy.
Full Moon's surprisingly funny.
Really.
Okay! Thank you for coming today to
Full Moon's second single release concert!
Please enjoy
the new world of Full Moon!
All right, it's finally show time.
Go break a leg!
Yes!
Now, it's what everybody
has been waiting for.
Here's Full Moon!
Help me!
Mitsuki!
Hold on!
Takuto!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm so sorry! The horse seems to
have been in a bad mood!
Don't worry!
Full Moon seems to be fine.
Thank goodness you're not hurt.
Yeah.
The knight on a white horse,
Takuto, arrives, eh?
Izumi! What were you thinking?!
Well, I guess I was just
playing around.
Stop messing around!
Why are you so angry?
It shouldn't matter to you
what happens to Full Moon.
Hey, since you're here, does that mean
that girl named Mitsuki is around here too?
Huh? What's wrong?
Where is she?
I want to meet her!
Th-That's...
Takuto is in trouble!
Oh yeah!
Ms. Oshige, Dr. Wakaoji,
I have something to ask.
What?!
Now, let me meet Mitsuki.
I want to meet her!
Come to think of it,
isn't the name "Mitsuki"
written with the Chinese characters
meaning "full moon"?
That's just like "Full Moon" the singer.
What a funny coincidence.
Wait, Full Moon!
Wait!
Oh? Are they playing tag?
Looks like fun.
Darn it, Jonathan.
Takuto! We should go too!
Yeah.
Takuto! Meroko!
Change me back to Mitsuki
while we have this chance!
Mitsuki!
Then that's...
What?
They're gone.
Oh well. Let's go back to Mero.
Was that long enough?
We're back.
How was it?
We lost them.
Oh, yeah?
You came just in time!
I'll introduce her!
This is Mitsuki Koyama that we,
Green Onion Ramen, are in charge of.
Oh, so this is Mitsuki?
She's pretty cute!
Stop it, Izumi!
Yeah, you're going to
scare Mitsuki!
Why? It's not as if
she can see us, right?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Izumi, these two probably
like this girl a lot.
I see.
Oh yeah,
speaking of liking, Mero,
how many times have you
confessed your love to Takuto?
If I recall, it was over 30 times
last time I heard.
It doesn't matter
how many times I do it!
I love that.
Laughing scornfully
while watching your face
bearing humiliation and anger
is one of my tiny joys.
I hate you!
You have such a short temper, Mero.
That's enough, Izumi!
Meroko is my important partner!
Stop making fun of her so much!
Takuto...
Oh? But isn't it bad for you to
be so worried about Meroko?
If you fail this time,
the Division Chief might really get angry!
Fail?
Because you haven't recovered
a single soul up to now.
Right, good-for-nothing Takuto?
Takuto...
Takuto is a late bloomer!
He'll soon become a great Death Spirit!
Well, I'll stop the teasing here for
the sake of my dear Mero's words.
Dummy!
Oh, by the way, Mitsuki is here
but I wonder where Full Moon is.
Sh-She's probably somewhere near here!
Mero-Mero Change!
Now, I have to make this work!
How long are they going to play tag?
Huh?
There she is!
Gosh, how far did Ms. Oshige
and Dr. Wakaoji go?
Is it Meroko?
Oh, so you're Mitsuki?
Huh?
Thank you for the flowers!
I was very happy!
Y-You're welcome.
Izumi, it's Full Moon.
Everybody,
just a little bit longer.
Please wait a little longer.
Okay? Okay?
Thanks for waiting! Mitsuki!
Did it work? Huh?
Huh?
- W-Why are there two Mitsukis—
- Ms. Oshige!
M-Mitsuki, how was it?
Were you able to talk to Full Moon?
Oh? Umm... Yes, just a little bit.
All right, that's great.
Oh, there you guys are.
Both Mr. Oji and Full Moon,
please hurry.
We can't make the crowd
wait any longer.
I understand!
Tell them we'll be going
to the stage now.
Yes, sir!
Now, Full Moon.
What?! B-But I'm...
Now, quick.
B-But...
This is great!
What are they going to do?
Meroko can't sing the new single.
Huh? Only one Mitsuki? Why?
That's enough!
Come back to your senses!
Hi, thanks for
waiting everybody.
It's finally time for
Full Moon to come out!
Mitsuki.
Um, I'm Meroko.
Then the one over there
is the real Mitsuki.
Okay, keep on heading
towards the stage.
After that,
we'll do something about it.
But...
Don't worry. Trust me.
We'll change the stage direction!
Full Moon will appear first and
we'll call her off using the horse.
At this point,
I don't care what happens!
What?! You brought her
up on stage?!
Yeah, we'll switch the two on stage.
What the—?
How are you going to do that?
Not only is Izumi around,
there are the eyes of the crowd!
That's why we'll change
the stage direction a little.
The point is to not have
that moment be visible.
We'll do the final trick for
the song in the beginning.
You're right, if we do that,
the top of the stage will be hidden.
Now Takuto, I have one thing
I have to ask you to do.
Me?
Yes.
Will you do it?
Yeah!
Full Moon, are you feeling well?
Yes, I'm completely fine!
I'm so glad!
Thanks!
Your new single really captures
your essence.
Thank you!
- I did my best!
- She looks distressed. This is great.
Then Full Moon,
please let us hear the song!
Sure.
All right, let the emcee retire stage left.
The song will begin with my signal.
Mitsuki, you got it?
Yes!
All right. Now, let's begin!
Now everybody,
please listen to "Eternal Snow."
- Huh?
-She's so cute!
Mitsuki?
What are they trying to do?
They won't be able to do a thing.
Now!
I can't see!
W-What is this?!
Meroko! Now, while we
have the chance!
Huh?
Takuto!
Meroko! Hurry!
Yeah!
Done!
Darn, I can't see a thing.
How long...has it been...
since I fell in love with you...
My feelings keep
getting stronger...
I'm so tired!
Good work!
Umm... Hey, Izumi?
Sorry, sorry, I might have played
around too much.
What?
Well, Full Moon is a good singer.
I understand why you want
to support her, Takuto.
I was able to meet Mitsuki, and there seems
to be nothing suspicious either, so...
What?! Then...
It's about time we go home.
It was fun, Mero!
See you later!
Aren't you glad they
didn't find out, Takuto?
Yeah...
I hope that's the case.
Izumi, should we report it
to the Division Chief?
No. For now, I'll be silent about it.
Becoming a friend with
a human child like that.
That's why you'll
always be no good.
Before long, I'll make you
understand that Mero is mine.
Meroko, you said she has
a guest from America?
Who is it?
Could it be Eichi?!
No, it's not! It's Ms. Kazumi,
her teacher from the orphanage.
I see.
But Ms. Kazumi's married and
lives in America now!
She might know something about Eichi!
I-I'm just worried about
our assignment as Death Spirits.
It's not like I'm jealous.
Next time on Full Moon:
"Someone Who Might
Know Where Eichi Is"
- Look forward to it!