Kerry!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Kerry!
Wow! Amazing!
Nah, that was nothing!
Shirley.
Shirley!
Kerry!
I'm here.
Hey, Kerry.
Do you know where the name of this island comes from?
Nope.
Oh, isn't Alimango the word for crab?
Yup.
Long ago, this was a place where
people made offerings to the sea gods.
But one day, a girl, with nothing to feed her sick mother,
took some of the food that had been offered.
And so, the girl was cursed and transformed into a crab.
That's where the name comes from?
That's a painful story.
Also, the shrine consecrated to those gods
happens to be up this mountain, around where your mansion is.
That's why none of the villagers want to go up there.
They say it's bad luck.
You'll apparently be cursed if you go there too often.
They're trying to scare me as well.
Man...
But everyone treats me just fine.
You're not exactly an outsider anymore, though.
In the village, they treat you like my little brother.
Little brother, huh?
You've really settled in here.
You think so?
Everyone used to bully you when you first arrived.
You had a weird name.
But—
But you were the first one to use it!
And calling me Kerry...
That's because your actual name's really hard to say!
Kery... Kery...
It's Kiritsugu.
Kerytugu!
Not even close...
Huh?
Seriously?
All right.
Dad, is that new?
Yeah.
This happens to be my hundredth success.
These flowers never wither.
I've altered their flow of time.
They won't grow beyond this,
but they'll never wither either.
Wow...
The question is whether we can get
the same theory to work on humans.
I'm finally done!
Shirley.
That...
Look!
It's my first success!
Shirley's been mimicking me
between her assistant duties.
She seems to have talent as a Mage.
Nah, didn't you do most of it, Sensei?
I only did a little bit at the end.
It's still amazing!
Hey, Dad...
Hmm? What?
Could I try the thing Shirley did?
That'd be great!
If Kerry helps out as well, he can do it!
Right, Sensei?
No.
Kiritsugu, it's still too early for you.
This isn't a game.
It's dangerous.
I only let Shirley try it because I believe she
has the necessary knowledge and experience.
Reverend, why won't you understand?
Shirley...
Everyone has the wrong idea about Sensei!
Listen, Shirley.
Don't go back to that mansion.
Let's talk inside.
My dad should just spend time with the villagers, too.
I dunno...
Reverend Simon and the others really hate him.
He preaches at me all the time.
He says a demon will possess me someday if I keep working there.
Look at this.
He told me to keep it with me at all times.
He says it's a very powerful talisman.
Shirley, does my dad scare you?
Not at all.
Sure, magical research isn't exactly normal.
But Sensei's knowledge and findings are all so incredible that they could make history.
I think he's amazing.
That...
It's sharp and pretty easy to use.
See you tomorrow.
Shirley, is something wrong?
Making a flower bloom forever...
It really is an amazing magic.
You managed to do it, too.
The work with flowers is all I can do.
Sensei has gone much further than that.
His medicines could eradicate human mortality.
I want him to use his power for the good of the world, so everyone'll understand how impressive he is.
He's given up on that.
But, Kerry, I'm sure you can do it.
What?
You're his best student.
If anyone were going to do it, it'd be you.
Not me.
I'm not his student.
The most I can be is his assistant.
Helping him with the little things...
I'm not his student or anything else.
So even when the reverend lectures
me about him, there's nothing I can say.
Kerry.
You're Sensei's heir, without a doubt.
He plans for you to continue all of his current research.
It's just a little too soon right now.
Hey.
Come with me.
Hey, Kerry.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
If you take up your dad's work, what will you use it for?
It's a power that can change the world.
And someday, it'll be yours.
Yeah, change the world.
You can do it.
I guarantee it.
That's...
That's a secret.
Then let me see what you'll do when you grow up.
I'll stay with you until then.
Okay?
Wh...
Whatever!
Stop it!
Take this!
Good morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu, you didn't go inside my atelier last night, did you?
Huh?
No, I didn't.
I see.
Kiritsugu, don't go to the village today.
Just don't leave the house.
What's going on?
Shirley's late...
Hey.
Have you seen Shirley?
Shirley?
What happened to you?
Kerry...
Shirley!
I...
I just wanted to prove Sensei's research!
But...
I guess...
...it didn't work...
Kill me.
Use that.
Please...
You have to kill me.
If you do it now, there's still time...
Please!
I can't...
I can't hold it back anymore!
Hurry!
Was it really Shirley?
Kerry, stay here for now.
I'll go inform the village.
Wh-What is this?
Reverend Simon...?
Looks like I was too late.
W-Wait!
Who are you?
Shouldn't you worry about yourself first?
Well, if you just sit there,
you'll join them soon enough.
What happened?
Who did this?
Why would they burn down the village?
I'm sure you've at least heard of vampires.
We call them Dead Apostles.
Dead Apostles?
They drink blood to reproduce themselves.
Nearly everyone on this island is a Dead Apostle now.
That's why it's being cleaned up.
Two groups down there are
working hard to eliminate them.
One is the Church's Executors.
They believe, without doubt, that it is fine to slaughter anyone who defies the will of God.
Of course, they'll show no mercy to any Dead Apostles.
They'll kill anyone they even suspect of having had their blood sucked.
As for the Mage's Association...
They're harder to explain,
but they basically want to keep the secret of who created
entities as bizarre as the Dead Apostles all to themselves.
Naturally, since their motto is "all to themselves",
they'll kill anyone they suspect of knowing the secret.
They'll destroy any evidence of what happened.
They're the ones who burned the village.
Which side are you on?
I'm like a salesman to the Mage's Association.
Well, kid.
Answer my question.
I'm looking for a Mage who's been marked for sealing.
A Mage...
I suppose that doesn't mean anything to you.
Think of the first person to become a Dead Apostle here.
I'm talking about the medium that
turned that person into a Dead Apostle.
The trigger that caused the transformation.
The evil Mage who made it should
be hiding somewhere on this island.
Do you know anything?
Oh, Kiritsugu.
You're safe.
I'm very relieved.
I told you not to go to the village.
Dad...
Why were you researching Dead Apostles?
Kiritsugu, how did you know...?
Shirley used the magic on herself.
Well, that's very sad, but you can't change the past.
It wasn't my intention, but it just
means Shirley gave me an early answer.
Will you use me one day, like you did with Shirley?
Don't be stupid.
A Dead Apostle that can't control its bloodlust is a failure.
However, the Emiya family
research requires unlimited time.
The Root isn't reachable with a mortal body.
It was a time-consuming experiment, but it seems to have failed.
I'll have to rewrite my theory from scratch.
Kiritsugu, we'll discuss this another time.
We need to run now.
Can we run?
I thought this might happen, so I hid a
motorboat on the south coast a while ago.
I'm sorry, Kiritsugu, but you won't have time to gather your things.
Come on—
I'll do it.
There's a magical field surrounding the forest.
A powerful one.
It'll take time to dispel.
But...
I can get inside.
I have to do it.
Hey, Kerry.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
That field was pretty easy to break through.
Are you mad?
You were just lucky to have arrived in time.
If he had escaped, he would've continued his Dead Apostle research elsewhere.
That's a shitty reason for a kid to kill his father.
You're a good person, aren't you?
I'll get you off the island.
You decide the rest on your own.
Anything you want to take with you?
Nothing at all.
Twinkling quietly, the stars are scattered across the sky
Lost prayers fill the heavens and earth
Episode 18
Distant Memories
Unblossomed futures gleam on the slender branches
Still reluctant, I let the buds fall
Look, the time is ripe
A plump, golden fruit
For simply plucking it with these hands
Will cause the world to end
The whiteness of the falling, unblemished snow
Will disappear once it learns of warmth
A beautiful dream was enough to tear you to pieces
The truth and kindness behind those cold eyes
The furiously twinkling stars turn away from the heavens
Until these injurious prayers bring down the sky
After leaving the island, I spent the next several years
with Natalia Kaminski, the woman who took me from there.
That meant choosing the same path as Natalia.
That is, the path of a hunter.
Next Episode
Where Justice is Found