See you later...
Sleepy again this morning, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
Toru, you don't seem sleepy at all.
I'm a morning person, so I'm fine.
Must be nice... I'm jealous.
I'm not a morning person.
CAW CAW
That's...
What's the matter, Run-chan?
That bird's a little strange! What happened?
Say, Toru, that bird just keeps spinning around.
You think it's okay?
Run-chan, that's a weather vane.
WORRIED...
Fuwa fuwa fuyuu shite
Kirameku tooku no sora to hitotsu ni naru
Kazeyomi kimama na watashi no yukue wa kanata
Issho ni ikou
Shinkokyuu hazundeku, sekai no spring breath
Taiyou ni atsumaru no minna no egao
Ohayou to sayounara no aida wa watashitachi dake
Nandemo dekiru ne
Sukitooru hizashi, umaretate no sora
Machiawaseta yakusoku no morning arch
Te o furu kimi e to totte oki no kyou o watasou
Oshaberi ga hajimaru
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
KILOGRAM
That straight, long hair!
That tight, thin waist.
Those arms, longer than a giraffe's neck!
Huh? I wonder if they're fighting...
There've gotta be other, better things!
Those long, slender legs!
Huh?
Something better!
Those full, E-cup breasts!
Still not there!
Skin as white as tofu!
Still, still, still, still, still, still,
still, still, still not there!
What's gotten into the two of you?
Still, still, still, still, still, still,
still, still, still not there!
We're listing your strong points!
Still, still, still, still, still, still,
still, still, still not there!
Wh-Why they talkin' about that?
Pores that can only be confirmed
with a magnifying glass!
A face as small as a water flea!
All this is just surface stuff.
I wish they'd list some of my
INTERNAL qualities...
More!
Um...
She always dresses super nice!
Plastic
Bottles
Wh-what's the matter, Toru?
Run-chan...
Run-chan only praises YOU, Yuko.
I took it too seriously
and ended up hanging myself...
Come on. Toru, you got some
great qualities, too.
For example.
Huh?! Um, well...
Oh! People go for f-flat chested!
Slender is in now, right?
Toru, you're in the strike zone!
Huh?
Wh-what?
Stop that!
You've got a nice body, so what?!
She's like a model, isn't she? Yuko-chan...
Danger!
I forgot!
This year's goal: To lose three kilograms
by summer and get a model's body!
Wait. There's still time.
Summer doesn't really begin till August.
Our high-school girls' summer hasn't begun!
I still have a month.
With one month, I can make it work!
School-wide
Beautification
POOL
I'm done for.
I forgot again: our high-school girls'
summer starts TODAY.
Havin' to wear our swimsuits
just to clean the pool is such a pain!
But cleaning in our swimsuits sounds like fun.
You think so too, right, Nagi?
What's the matter, Nagi?
N-nothing at all.
So tight!
Don't tell me I gained weight! No, it can't be.
I wonder if our swimsuits shrink...
It's a little tight.
Well, we're still growing. In different ways!
Stop that! Jeez.
Oh! My swimsuit shrank!
Ain't Nagi a little strange today?
Huh? She's the same as always.
* IN CHARGE *
CAMPUS
NO~
Toru-san.
You getting along?
You're Yutaka's friend...
Just call me "Miho".
The truth is, like Yutaka,
I'm a fan of yours, Toru-san.
"Fan"?
So...
I haven't had a chance to ask before now,
but something's been bugging me...
It's so soft! Is it natural? A hairdo?
It's natural.
Toru!
Miporin, how rude! You're being a burden
to Toru as well, aren't you?!
I'm not following her around like Yutaka.
It's not fair if it's just you, Miporin.
Yutaka has to touch, too!
Grab!
Why you...
Torun! Torun!
Say, you two get along well.
You went to the same middle school?
Yes. It wasn't the best of friendships, though.
She's been pretty concerned about the time...
Okay, it's been three minutes.
Please get away from Toru-san now, Yutaka.
Huh, already?
Miporin, you're so cruel!
I'm used to her, so if Yutaka starts
bothering you, feel free to ask me about it.
Speaking of middle school, Miporin's
nickname back then was "remote control".
Pretty uncool, huh?
Do you know WHYIwas called that?
Not a clue!
Yutaka!
Uh, sorry. Yeah. Very sorry.
Well, I'm just glad you get it.
Very sorry.
But, in touching Torun's hair,
I, Yutaka, was also quite-
Toru-san, I'll hold that trash bag.
No! I, Yutaka, will hold it!
Well, thanks very much.
W-wait! This is heavy!
Miporin! S-So heavy!
The remote control...
The sun, shining down upon us...
The poolside!
Like being at a resort?
Nope.
It's too hot!
It sure is hot in the pool, huh?
Yeah, well, the sun's heat
has nowhere else to go.
In any case, let's get this done fast! Hyaa!
Look out!
THP!!
Whatcha think she's doin'?
Beats me.
Yuko-chan! Nagi-chan! It's all slippery here!
She's right.
That's dangerous.
What if you fall and hit your head?
I'll be fine. Whee!
Jeez...
Nagi, you say somethin', too. Huh?
Nagi!
What?!
Yuko-chan, gotcha!
You're all wet!
I see. It's come to this, eh?
Run!
Gotcha!
Hey!
Hyaa!
Mizushibuki kakatta, pichapichapi tte
Caught in a spray of water, going splash splash
Marude tokonatsu poolside, kirakira kagayaku sora
Just like the poolside in an endless summer
Ow...
Marude tokonatsu poolside, kirakira kagayaku sora
Just like the poolside in an endless summer
The sky sparkling
onna no ko minna asebamu hada, mizugi datte ka na?
All the girls' skin is sweaty, and their swimsuits, maybe?
Borderline
Mujaki ni asonde hoshii
I want you to play innocently
Bishonure ga sukisugite, kodomo mitai
You like being soaking wet too much, like a child
Itsuka yume mita rakuen wa resort kibun, kimi to nara
That paradise I saw in a dream once feels like a resort
If I'm with you
Senobi shite mita, himitsu
I tried stretching, it's a secret
Fui ni shirimochi o tsuichatte, tsururi, doji na mainichi sa
And accidentally fell on my butt, SLIP!
Every day was clumsy
Naitari, warattari shinagara ne
While crying and laughing, right?
Itazura shitemo nakayoshi sa
Even if you play pranks, we're still friends
Dokidoki de love na shunkan wa minna no takaramono
That heart-pumping moment of love is everyone's treasure
Subesube ano ko no ohada ni wa jikken shite miru
I'm gonna try an experiment on that girl's soft skin
Splash water on it
Mizu kakete
Take this, and this, and this!
Splash water on it
Mizu kakete
Take this, and this, and this!
Pichipichi ni hajiite kurechau, dakishimetai
Splish, it repelled it, I want to hug her, that still-wet girl
Nureta mama no girl
Um, Torun, what are you looking at?
Gotcha!
Paradise...
This ain't paradise at all!
WORKING
OVERTIME
BECAUSE
IT'S NOT
DONE
I'm home.
So tired...
I should've put on more sunscreen.
It's all right.
I did that much physical activity today.
It's sure to have gone down.
No, I might even have reached my goal
of losing three kilograms. Get a clue, scale!
1 kg UP
Come to think of it, without my clothes on,
it should be minus 1 kg.
Oh, so there was no change.
That was a waste to even worry about it!
Basic Dieting
Knowledge
First, you have to make a one-month plan, huh?
The basics are exercise
and cutting back on food.
And no eating between meals.
Dinner should be early, and light,
using mainly vegetables and with no oil.
"Let's exercise daily; jogging, jump rope,
stretching and so on are effective."
Man, this is sadistic!
That was delicious.
I think I'll keep it a secret from everyone that
I've started a diet. I bet they'd make a fuss.
If Run knew...
Stop, it'll be bad for your health!
Yuko would be...
You're fine the way you are now.
You're plenty good!
Yeah, that sounds like her!
Toru would be...
Aah, delish!
CHOMP CHOMP
CRUNCH Greasy
Potato Chips CRUNCH
Aah, delish!
CHOMP CHOMP
CRUNCH Greasy
Potato Chips CRUNCH
CHOMP CHOMP
CRUNCH Greasy
Potato Chips CRUNCH
Want some? Have as many as you like.
Just imagining that makes me want to eat some!
Nagi.
I was unexpectedly taken aback!
Toru's a sharp one, so I have to be careful.
Hey, what's up?
Diet.
Huh?
Wh-what?
You're on a diet, aren't you?
Wh-what does this mean?
Where are Run and Yuko?
They just went to the bathroom.
How did you know?
Last spring, it was you who said
"Dieting until summer and losing three kilograms
is a piece of cake," right?
You remembered that yesterday, didn't you?
Just forget trivial things like that!
Are you going to tell everyone?
No, I won't.
Huh? Don't tell me, you want money
to keep your mouth shut!
I don't need that.
What are you doing?
They're not here.
Toru, you eat so much junk food
but you're still skinny, huh?
Because I run around the place, maybe?
On the other hand,
THESE don't get any nourishment.
Oh. They say they'll shrink
if they bounce around, huh?
Then I can't go jogging or do jump rope
because my boobs will go away, huh? All right!
If it bothers you that much, why not ask Yuko?
She may be working very hard at it.
There must be something,
some secret to that nice body.
Oh. Yeah, that's true. All right!
They're not here, either?
Maybe we passed each other somewhere.
Toru, you're sweating.
These are tears of sadness
at not seeing Run-chan.
Don't push yourself. You've gotten hot
walking around, haven't you?
I'm not hot.
In any case, why are you still wearing long
sleeves even though it's already summer?
I want my arms to show as little as possible.
You're gonna have a heatstroke, so take this off!
Are you THAT against it?
Okay, open your textbooks to page 52.
Huh? Am I doin' something to keep my figure?
There's no real reason.
I just kinda wanted to ask.
Yeah, well...
Eating whatever I want and getting
a good night's rest, I guess.
Oh, guess I ain't doing anything.
Are you a model or something?!
Don't screw with us! You're no use at all!
Wh-what?
Keeping her figure?
You're talking about a diet?
Oh, you're talkin' about a diet.
Nagi, did you start dieting?
Well, yeah. I guess the cat's out of the bag now.
Run, you ever dieted before?
Not formally, I think.
I don't want to limit what I eat.
You haven't either, right, Yuko-chan?
Yeah. I haven't. Why?
Because, you have a pet, right?
A pet? What do you mean?
What was it, it sounded like something else...
A tapeworm!
CLENCH
Thanks to the power of tapeworm, right?
I don't have that, and it ain't a pet!
The computer.
If you look on the Net,
you'll find a good way to diet.
Oh, really?
Why here, in the library?
The one in the classroom is just fine.
Using the classroom's computer is a little...
Diets speedy weight loss
There's lots of different diets, huh?
I took this and lost 60 kg!!
Slim Magnum EX
New Product!!
I took this and lost 60 kg!!
Slim Magnum EX
New Product!!
"I took this and lost 60 kilograms," it says!
I took this and lost 60 kg!!
Slim Magnum EX
New Product!!
That's too much, right? Sounds fishy.
If you lost that much,
your weight would be minus.
You could fly up in the sky, huh?
Yeah.
I'd be ethereal.
DELICIOUS
MILK
That's it for me.
Nagi-chan, you're done already?
Yeah. Cutting back on food
is the basis of dieting.
You can't push yourself too far, Nagi.
Nah, I'm fine! That was just enough for me.
You're pushing yourself.
Th-that didn't happen! You never heard it!
No, it's no good. We DID hear it!
Just forget it!
Sure enough, I get hungry around this time.
Say, Nagi...
Suddenly chargin' into a diet isn't good
for your body, so you should quit.
You should go slower. You can make
your goal by next year, right?
That's right, Nagi-chan. Let's take it slow!
Yeah. Guess I can't force it, huh?
I'll calm down, take things at my own pace.
Oh, hey, wanna go eat some ice cream?
Yeah, nice!
Hang on a minute! Isn't ice cream a bit strange,
considering what we were just talking about?!
I want chocolate chip and strawberry.
Vanilla and cheese and yogurt...
They're all white, huh?
Now look here!
As for me, I think I'll do mint and raspberry.
And you, Nagi?
Rum raisin.
Dieting's out of the question for a while, huh?
Come on. Let's go, Nagi!
Hey, hold on!
You're fine the way you are.
You're plenty good.
And plenty cute.
Why'd you go and say somethin'
embarrassing like that?!
Wait up, Yuko!
Come on, hurry!
Wait, I said!
Check this out...
New socks!
Ah! They're fluorescent yellow!
They sure stand out.
Nice, huh?
Good morning!
Good morning.
Toru!
Why are you wearing loose socks?!
They're out of date!
Note: Big, leg warmer-looking socks that were all the rage in the late '90s.
Why are you wearing loose socks?!
They're out of date!
Note: Big, leg warmer-looking socks that were all the rage in the late '90s.
No, these are new knee-length socks.
She said they slide easily, though.
Just how the hell skinny are you?
I used Stopper, but they still fall.
Wanna use Soft Touch?
Yes.
I want to gain a little weight.
I just heard something that I can't ignore!
No, it was nothing...
Okay, finished.
Thank you.
I want to gain weight.
Akane ni narabu seitaka kageboushi
Tanoshii ichinichi no owari
Tsukinai oshaberi mada mada aru keredo
Sorosoro o-uchi ni kaeranakucha
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Mail suru kara
Kyou no page ni minna osoroi no egao
Jaa ne, ashita ne
Itsumo arigato
Kyou mo issho ni irete yokatta na
Ru-ru-run, kaze to kokoro humming suru
Tsugi no kado de furimukinagara bye-bye
yup!
Okay, now it's TRULY summer!
And summer means the pool! And the beach!
It's here: the beach!
And the beach means sporty girls in their bikinis!
Ooh, I can't take it!
Are you really a high-school girl?
I think everyone is VERY interested
in seeing I, Yutaka, in a swimsuit.
No, I don't think so.
Next time, on A-Channel: "The Beach"
Next
Episode!
Next time, on A-Channel: "The Beach"
Next
Episode!
The only thing I'm interested in
is Toru in her swimsuit!
Ah, me too!
Huh? No witty insult?