I thought I told you, Sam.
Melanie Square doesn't need hard drugs.
P-Please wait, Tony. I didn't have a choice!
Ben told me to sell them at any cost.
I don't give a crap why you did it!
This is my turf... the Stone Family's turf.
I'll show no mercy to those who can't follow my rules!
I don't care if they're the President or the First Lady!
That's enough.
Old man Gant...
I'll take him. You don't mind, do you?
Suit yourself.
You're old fashioned as always.
You're probably the only mafia family in LA who doesn't allow hard drugs today.
I just want Melanie Square to be a decent place to play.
We don't have to bend our principles since we have enough ways of making money.
Don't talk so big, you novice brat...
you don't even live by the sweat of your brow.
Your words hit home.
Hardheaded Tony, huh?
Moment
Daddy!
Duke! I didn't know you were here.
Sorry to show up suddenly, Tony.
Eva.
We came to the Square to see a movie, so...
Daddy, do you remember?
We're going to the amusement park together the day after tomorrow.
Yeah, of course I remember.
How can I forget if when I always look forward to spending time with you?
Yeah!
Tony, excuse me...
That guy again?
It's about time to settle this.
If he says no, teach him a lesson.
Yes sir.
Ms. McCunnen, this is Richard Harrington.
I'm hoping to get a favorable response from you today.
We're giving you the best deal we can offer.
Yeah, it's not a bad deal.
But my response is the same.
Why?
Don't make me repeat myself. Melanie Square is our family's turf.
Everyone who lives here... Everyone who works here... They're all my family.
I'm not gonna betray them.
You heard him. So go back and tell your boss.
Or do you wanna eat bullets and go back in a body bag?
It seems that you guys still don't realize our true power... the power of Inferno.
What'd you say?!
We'll give you three more days. This is your last chance.
I trust you'll change your mind... Tony Stone.
What a prick! What gives with that cocky attitude?!
Even if it was a bluff, it's creepy.
Lutz, Rob. Do a thorough investigation on who's behind Inferno.
It's hard to think that they're just some new organization.
Yes sir.
Are you ready?
Anytime.
Even when you block your opponent's weapon once, it doesn't end there.
Yeah.
How amazing.
You couldn't do anything at first, but you can hold your own now.
That's because I've got a good coach.
There are two missions that I'd like you to carry out. Will you accept?
Two?
I'll explain at my place. Come with me.
Your place?
So this is your house, Ms. McCunnen?
That's right, though it's a little too big for a single person with no family.
Lizzie's been recruited for a different case today, too, so...
To get to the point, please tell me what those missions are.
First, I want you to be my guard and to keep me company tonight.
What?
I told you... that Lizzie is out.
Although the security here is perfect,
I want someone to be here even if just as a formality.
Why does a senior member like you always have only one guard?
Do I need someone else?
And, the second mission is... to monitor a mother and her child.
Okay, if that's your order.
That's not good.
You're not a doll.
Why you have to monitor them... Why it is important...
You need to ask those things. Okay?
You can't get a clear picture about Inferno?!
Ah, yes. We've asked information brokers and others all over the place,
but they all say something different.
One would say the Verrocchio Family is involved,
and another would say the Cervantes Family is.
And, of course, I heard the Bloodies name as well. What can I say...
What the hell's your problem?!
Lutz, since when did you start letting people sell you a bill of goods?!
I-I'm sorry.
Stop it, Anton.
They did do their job.
What do you mean?
Extending their power in a short time. Doing things in various ways.
Those senior members who don't show. And the information Lutz and Rob got...
If we put them all together, we have the answer.
Inferno is a special organization
that is connected to the mafia families on the West Coast.
What?!
That guy's confidence also comes from that.
The only way for us to survive is to kiss up to them.
He knew that.
Boss, then Melanie Square will be...
Hell no!
No matter who we're facing, I can't betray the people of the Square!
Anton, set up a meeting with Inferno immediately.
But give them a condition.
Tell them to bring their boss.
Tony... don't tell me...
I'll negotiate... at least...
The real boss probably won't show considering their organization system.
But that's okay. It'll be enough to pick a fight with them.
But if we do that, they'll certainly retaliate against us.
He's right. Not just the Square, but your family will also be in danger!
I'll leave them to you. Protect them with your lives.
I'll teach them that we're too troublesome to swallow.
Then, depending on how they react, the mother and her child will have to be...?
That's right. Even if that's the case...
can you do it?
Tell me... Don't just take orders...
Tell me your answer.
Come on! Hurry up!
Okay.
Ah!
Thank you.
No problem.
Looks like you got quite used to it.
In order to blend in with a flock of sheep, you have to wear sheepskin.
What were the characteristics of the fifth person from the last that we passed by?
A Caucasian male in his twenties.
He was wearing a Dodgers cap and a black shirt.
Based on how he was talking on his cell,
he got separated from his friend and is trying to find where they're supposed to meet up.
Correct.
Even when wearing sheepskin, a wolf shouldn't forget his sense of smell.
That's also something you taught me.
Hey, hold on.
Okay, I see. Buy it for him.
Well then, Duke. See you later.
Okay, Daddy.
Tony, be very careful.
Anton said that everything is ready.
Let's go.
What're you hardheaded guys doing all dressed up like that?
Old man Gant... It has nothing to with you, now does it?
Listen. Don't do anything that would hurt the citizens, okay?
If you do...
I know.
Your residence is thoroughly guarded by Abel and Bark.
That place is the safest place in LA tonight.
What about Inferno?
They'll be here soon.
So it's okay to have you handle it, Ms. McCunnen?
Yes. We have to think about the future, too. So I'll be the rep.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness.
My feelings are a bit mixed though, being the one in charge of this district.
We'd like to make Melanie Square ours without turning it into a battlefield.
I'm counting on you, Ms. McCunnen.
Please don't worry. If we have two trump cards,
we can win most of the games.
Rob just contacted me and said that the meeting is about to start.
I see.
Please don't worry. So far, things have been quiet around here.
So long as nothing happens tonight, the game is ours.
Yeah...
I didn't expect such a pretty woman to be a senior member of Inferno.
Many people get surprised.
I sure hope you aren't just a decoration.
I thought we told you to bring your boss.
I won't say that I'm the number one person in Inferno.
However, I've been given full authority with regards to this case.
She's right. Please refrain from speaking rudely to her.
Back off from Melanie Square.
You think we'd just agree to that?
We'll pay the debt later on. That's the code of conduct among mafia, right?
You won't have to. All we want...
is Melanie Square.
Those at the Square were all driven out from other places and live in obscurity.
They are inept and the Square is the only place they can call home.
But they're our family.
I can't betray our family. That's against my principles.
Old-fashioned and hardheaded. You're just like your nickname, Tony Stone.
Can you say the same even if your real family is in danger?
If you do that, you'll lose everything, too. Is that what you want?
I'll ask you one more time.
Will you give Melanie Square over to Inferno?
No.
You're late, Phantom.
Wh-what the hell?!
Duck! It's a sniper!
Shoot back! Shoot him dead!
We can't! It's too far!
Zwei, get to work.
What?! What about Boss?! Is he okay?!
The negotiation was broken off. Boss and Anton are all right,
but Rob and Lutz were...
Oh no...!
In any case, please go stay with Duke.
Okay.
They're crazy.
Inferno...!
Mommy!
Duke, haven't you gone to bed yet?
You see, that guy I saw at the amusement park is...
What?
Eva! Eva!
Wonderful.
You're... wonderful.
Next episode
Conflagration
Be an instrument. Be a tool.
All we need to do... is just function.