This might seem like weird timing,
but I have to do this.
Wh-What is it?
I love you, Kiriyama Yui.
Please go out with me.
What are you doing?
I already turned you down.
My feelings for you haven't changed,
but I was hoping yours might've—
No! Never!
Not yet...
Not yet?
I've been wondering, why me?
Iori's a lot cuter than I am.
Inaba's really pretty too.
There's plenty to like about you.
But this is beyond reason.
From the moment I first saw you, I knew you were special.
I simply love you,
and that hasn't changed.
When the little openings in our hearts connect
and produce new things at the speed of little flashes
then these days that seem to fly by keep us in their embrace
and the strength we thought was gone comes back
If my feelings are clear when I look at you
Yaegashi Taichi
Laugh more
Freshman, class 3
Dumb wrestling nut
Quit beating
around the bush!
How about laughing more?
Gonna go have
fun tomorrow
Loves his little sister
Rice? Bread?
Hurry up and give it back!
Nagase Iori
Won't do anything
dirty at all
Freshman
class 3
Best Smile Ever
Go out with me
)
Cute
Iori, I love you
That comic was pretty cool.
Time for some curry.
Cutest girl in all of Yamaboshi High
Let's go to the
sale tomorrow
then the illusion is dispelled
Scary
Sorry
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
Inabaaaan
Sorry I was even born
Laugh
Freshman, class 3
Curry hot pot
Inaba Himeko
but I still like her
Sorry! I'll bring you
some fruit milk
me yui
We should get married
I love youuuuu
I love you, Yui
Let's go out
Screw that
Freshman, class 1
I want to have
curry hot pot.
What do you say?
The whole world
Let's go
to Disneyland
Kiriyama Yui
Conceited
Aoki Yoshifumi
Freshman, class 1
Sorry, I can't
go out with you.
Seriously.
Done tomorrow's
homework?
I want to eat curry
If I do my best
Don't give up if you're a man!
Suddenly the world that connects us changes
Peeking through a glass marble
the world looks so much more radiant than before
What would I see from there?
When our link shakes, all changes again
Time is multifaceted
Did you hear that?
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
It signals the beginning
Don't let it pass unheard
It signals the future we have chosen
So why are you telling me this now?
How do you feel about Taichi?
Taichi? Well...
I like him.
As a friend.
Wh-What about me?
I hate you as a friend.
No way!
You actually believed that?
Of course I like you.
Oh, but only as a friend, really!
That's the best I can do right now.
Sorry, it's not you.
I'm not ready to go out with anyone.
Well, at least it sounds like I have a chance.
Are you satisfied now?
Can we go back to the classroom and have lunch?
Are you inviting me to join you?
Hell no. My friends are waiting for me!
Hey, wait!
Just so you know, you're way below
Taichi on my male friend list.
How did you know this was gonna happen?
What?! So Taichi is my biggest rival?!
I switched with Yui yesterday and
happened to see the text from Aoki.
It was an accident.
But I figured it might help give you two a push.
A push?
Well, it's up to you from here.
See ya.
We should get going.
I'm okay.
A Confession and Death...
Just you today?
Yeah...
Are you Inaba?
Yeah, that's right.
Iori and I switched places.
So...
What did you think after seeing Aoki and Yui during lunch?
What did I think?
It felt like I was watching people from a different planet.
Why did you want us to watch them?
You can't seriously be so dense,
can you?
Huh?
Forget it.
I'll cut to the chase.
How do you feel about Iori?
Nothing is ever off-limits to you.
And it's even more awkward when you look like Nagase.
Perfect timing, right?
Why would you think that?
Well, I guess...
I really like our current relationship,
and I don't want to ruin that.
But...
Hey, it's just you two?
You're too early, Inaban.
Huh?
Surprise...
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
Iori!
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
Taichi, what did you do?!
Hell if I know!
Nagase was pretending she had switched with you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't get it either...
Because no matter what happens,
no matter how much you change,
I'll always be able to recognize you for who you are.
Looks like you have some idea.
Yeah, I realized that I'm pathetic.
She wanted to trust me.
Want me give you a good punch?
Yeah, go ahe—
Go after her!
I'm not the hero she needs right now.
Fujishima!
Yaegashi...
Did you see Nagase?
Must we live in a world where a couple is defined as a man and a woman?
What are your thoughts?
I don't have time to talk about that right now!
I'm looking for Nagase!
Move, Fujishi—
Nagase ran out the front gate.
I wasn't able to help her.
I'm guessing you're the hero she deserves.
Fujishima...
Are you okay with that?
If you're the hero Nagase needs right now,
I won't stand in your way.
Hurry up now.
Nagase...
Where are you, Nagase?
Nagase!
Taichi...
I'm really sorry I didn't notice it was you!
Especially after my promise...
What defines humans?
Defines us?
Nobody will notice a change on the inside
if you look the same on the outside.
Oh, I'm not blaming you for anything, Taichi.
That was all my fault.
I'm sorry.
But you were trying to move on, right?
Thanks.
And now, it's my turn.
Uh, where to start...
I really admire you, Nagase.
You admire me?
I can't express myself the way you do.
I don't know how to show joy, anger, or sorrow.
That's why I admire the way you enjoy life.
That's because I keep switching personas.
You told me that the other day.
But is that really the case?
What do you mean?
What are you trying to say?
You must be confused.
Whether you joke around or play dumb,
get embarrassed or make dirty jokes,
do things spontaneously or plan everything out,
think too much or don't think at all,
tell a joke before a serious conversation
or act cold...
Um, what are you getting at?
In each case, you're still you.
What's that mean?
You're still Nagase Iori!
There's no such person!
One person can't wear all of those masks!
That's normal.
Everyone wears a mask at some point.
I don't do it often.
You do it a lot.
That's all there is to it.
But I behave differently around different people!
Lots of people change themselves to fit the situation.
But I'm always thinking about which persona to switch to!
Nobody's strong enough to ignore everyone else and be themselves.
But the things I like change with the situation!
I couldn't even choose a club for myself!
That just means you like a lot of things.
And you're no worse than the people who just choose whichever club looks easiest.
That's complete BS.
I had you going, though.
You know,
I admire you, Taichi.
You're always true to yourself.
No matter who I become, you'll always be you.
I admire that stability you project.
Nagase...
I love you, Nagase Iori.
Will you go out with me?
Uh...
Hello.
It's been a while.
You can probably guess who I am.
Heartseed...
Yes...
I'll apologize up front.
Sorry.
But in the end, you're the ones to blame.
You're all just a bit too boring.
Hey, what are you doing?
I already apologized.
Nagase!
Yamaboshi General Hospital
Yes, thank you.
What'd Mr. Go say?
He's almost here.
And they managed to get in touch with Iori's mom.
Hello there.
You bastard...
What do you want?
Nagase Iori's body will die soon.
What are you talking about?!
You think you can play God with our lives?
Of course not.
But the fact remains that I'm capable of many things.
Why should we believe you?
Well, it's up to you to decide if
you want to believe me or not.
So, are you ready?
Listen carefully.
I want you to choose which personality will die with Nagase's body.
Huh? Do you mean...?
For the next 30 minutes,
you'll be able to switch bodies whenever you wish. Just say the word.
There you have it.
Stop treating us like toys!
Taichi!
Understood?
You have 30 minutes.
He's telling us to choose who dies.
But we don't know that Iori's going to die.
The doctors are doing their best.
Yeah, he could've been lying.
Or he could've been telling the truth.
Either way, we have to face reality.
As unsettling as it is...
If...
If someone has to make the sacrifice,
I'll do it.
That's a load of bullshit.
You're volunteering to be the sacrifice?!
Have you ever considered how
it feels to be on the other side?
You act like you're concerned about others,
but you only care about yourself!
Those are the true colors of the white knight!
Is that so wrong?!
That's right!
I don't want to see anyone else suffer!
It hurts me more than I can imagine
when I think about the pain they must feel!
I can't stand it!
I'd rather suffer in their place!
At least then I'd know how much pain they endure.
That way, I could bear my own pain.
That's right.
I'm not doing this for anyone else.
I'm sacrificing myself for my own good!
Really...
Something's wrong with you.
Something's very wrong,
but it's a gentle form of insanity.
Gentle, awkward, and stupid, really.
But you should understand our pain then.
I believe that Iori should be the one
who dies with her body.
How can you say that?!
I didn't want to say it,
but someone had to.
Anyway, we need to tell Iori what's going on.
That's true.
Since I brought it up, I'll switch.
Please switch me, Aoki Yoshifumi, with Nagase Iori.
Huh?
Why is everyone here?
I was talking with Taichi by the river...
Iori, listen carefully.
You're...
In that case,
I have to die.
Nagase, it's not over yet.
I could never bring myself
to kill someone else and take over their body.
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
What about my mom?
She's supposed to be on her way here.
Oh...
Um...
Can I...
talk with each of you individually, one last time?
Taichi,
Iori wants to talk to you.
'Sup, Taichi.
Hey, Nagase.
Oh? You're the only one who doesn't seem too different.
That's because I'm supposed to be the stoic character.
Anyway, Taichi, thanks.
After talking to you,
my problems don't seem so significant.
I think I can learn to love myself.
You said that you love me.
I want to give a response now.
But you're probably expecting a joke first, right?
Not really, but I figured you might drop one on me.
Why are you the same as always?
Everyone else looked so sad.
I am sad.
So sad I could die.
But you must feel even worse.
If I cry, you won't be able to.
I don't want to die.
I want to keep on living.
I have so much to look forward to.
Why?
Why did this have to happen to me?
What did I do wrong?
Right after you told me that you love me...
I love you too, Taichi.
That's why I don't want you to go out with me.
Huh?
I mean, I'm about to die.
That wouldn't be much of a relationship.
How can you...
Instead, I want a memory to remember you by.
So let's kiss.
I'm sure that Inaban will forgive me.
Are you ready?
Who will it be?
Me.
Nagase Iori will die with Nagase Iori's body.
Well, that would be the logical conclusion.
Can I ask you a question?
I need an answer now.
You won't do this to anyone else, right?
Of course.
Oh, it's time.
Where's Iori?!
Wait...
Don't let this end!
Luck was on our side.
She's going to survive.
Huh?
It appears that there won't be any permanent damage.
If you wait a little longer, you'll be able to see her.
Hello again, everyone, and good job.
Take this.
Western Style
Baked Sweets
Consider it my apology.
It also serves as a get well gift for Nagase.
You got us good.
Well, I knew it was a possibility.
So Iori's okay?
She's alive?
That's wonderful.
Hey, how much of this was planned?
Well, I suppose you could say that
everything is part of my plan.
That's one way to look at it,
since you people don't seem to realize what I'm capable of.
So you never intended to do anything to Nagase?
I would never cause any trouble for an innocent person.
I even made sure that her cell phone didn't get wet.
I'm not going to ask for your forgiveness,
but I hope that you won't hold a grudge
since you also benefited from the experience.
Until next time.
Yamaboshi General Hospital
Welcome back!
My daily life, gone with the flow of time
Thanks!
Sorry to make everyone worry.
Don't worry about that.
seemed like a dream beyond what my senses could appreciate
Anyway, did anything strange happen?
I don't understand, I don't understand
Nothing at all.
There hasn't been any more body swapping.
So I mumble, still little more than a child, and dream
Looks like it's all over then.
I hope you're right.
Anyway, let's dig in.
Deadline: Every month on the 25th
Don't be late!!
Aoki, make some tea.
Maybe I'm a coward
Sure. Have a seat, Iori.
It shouldn't matter
Thanks. Sorry about this.
I wish I could be stronger
Come on! Taichi, Inaba, get to work!
Onto that sort of facade,
Right.
I heard from Iori when I went to visit her.
my weak cries,
scattered feelings,
It sounds like you stole my first kiss?
and changing intentions
the sun shone
That's going to cost you dearly.
You were the only one that mattered to me
I knew that
Maybe
A Story That Continued
Before Anyone Realized It
Next Time
If we do our best
me yui
I love my sister
I wanna eat curry.
Tune in next time!
Inaba
Let's go
to Disneyland!