[NARRATOR] Alchemy... the
science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter; however,
it is not an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange--
the basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[NARRATOR] The first branch of
the National Central Library,
where Marcoh had
hidden his notes
regarding the Philosopher's
Stone, was lost to fire...
Aided by former librarian
Sheska, the brothers
were able to obtain a copy
of the doctor's research...
But inside the notes, they
found something truly terrible.
[ED] The main ingredient
for a Philosopher's Stone...
Is... human life!
[NARRATOR] In search of the
truth hidden within the truth,
of which Marcoh
had spoken...
Ed and Al sneaked to
the supposedly abandoned
Fifth Laboratory.
[66]
Ehhhhh!
[thud]
[66] You move pretty
well for your size.
If you didn't, though,
it wouldn't be worth the
effort to cut you down.
[AL]
Who are you?
[66]
I'm Number Sixty-Six...
Well... that's the
name they gave me
when I came to
work here, anyway.
[66] I'm going to cut
you up, nice and neat.
[66] All you have to do
is sit back and scream.
[ED]
What is all this...?
I bet this is what they used
to transmute a
Philosopher's Stone.
[48]
Yes, that's right.
[48] I don't know
who you are, kid,
but you sure figured out a lot
just from looking at a
transmutation circle...
[ED]
I'm just good like that.
Who are you, pal?
[48]
The one in charge
of guarding this place
from curious brats.
[48] For the moment
let's just say
my name is Number Forty-Eight.
[48] And believe me,
I'm not your 'pal'.
[48] My orders are to dispose
of anyone who wanders in here,
poking his nose where
it doesn't belong...
Try not to take
it personally, boy.
[ED]
Alright, I won't.
[ED] And you try not
to take it personally
when this 'boy'
kicks your ass!
[48] Hmm... you're
an alchemist, are you?
[48] All right then...
let's see what you've got.
[48]
A prosthetic arm, huh?
No matter...
My sword can pierce
steel as well as flesh.
[hollow clang]
[ED] My, my,
what's this?
I'm gonna go
out on a limb here
and say you're
hollow inside.
[48] You're a
perceptive one.
[ED] I could tell
from the sound.
I spar against someone
like you all the time.
[48] So are there
people like me
on the outside too, are there?
That's surprising.
[ED] Yeah, it
makes me sick...
To think there's
more than one idiot
in the world who came up
with the brilliant idea
of bonding a disembodied
soul to a suit of armor.
[48] Hmm... Perhaps I should
introduce myself again...
Forty-Eight is the
number I was assigned
when I was on death row...
Back when I still
had a living body,
I was better
known as Slicer.
I was a mass
murderer, you see.
[ED] So you were
slated for execution...
Tell me something then...
This laboratory...
Are they using condemned
prisoners like you
to make Philosopher's
Stones here?
[48] That I
can't tell you.
It isn't my area...
They simply
recognized my skills...
gave me this body,
and made me their
trusty guard dog.
[ED]
Interesting...
I'm sure they gave
you a seal too--
To serve as a medium
between soul and armor?
[48] Yes...
I have a bloodseal.
[48] This is
it right here...
If you destroy this...
the fight's yours.
[ED] That's awfully
considerate of you
to show me your weak spot.
[48] I like to give myself
a little extra challenge
during a fight now and then.
[ED] As long as you're
in such a giving mood,
then how 'bout this...
Why not just let me go?
[48]
Nice try, kid...
but what kind
of mass murderer
lets his prey
get away so easily?
[48]
Now... let's fight.
[HUGHES]
Did you hear what I said...
My dear little Elicia
is about to turn three!
[ROY]
Lt. Colonel Hughes,
do you think this
could wait...?
I'm at work.
[HUGHES] Oh,
what a coincidence,
I'm at work too!
[HUGHES] She's the
cutest little thing!
You should see her.
[ROY] I'm sure
she's adorable,
but stop calling me to
gush over your daughter...
and on a military line, too!
[HUGHES] Not just
my daughter, colonel...
I'll gush over
my wife, too!
[HUGHES] I know, I know,
it's your turn now...!
Go ahead, Colonel...
I know you're dying to
gush over your very own...
[HUGHES]
Scar-faced Ishvalan.
[ROY] We've
found many bodies
on the site
where he vanished...
But all of them
are so decomposed
that it's been difficult
to identify them.
[ROY] He hasn't been
sighted anywhere in the east.
[ROY]
So at the present,
many people here think it's
most likely that he's dead.
[HUGHES] If that's the case,
I should be able to
lift the bodyguard
from the Elric brothers soon.
[ROY] Is Major Armstrong
still in charge
of the boys'
protective detail?
[HUGHES]
He was...
But a couple of his
men have taken over now.
[sobbing]
[ROSS]
We've been played!
[ROSS] I thought it was
suspiciously quiet in here!
[BROSH]
Ah! Major Armstrong's
gonna take his
shirt off again
and yell at us
some more, isn't he?!
[ROSS] Those brats
are going to pay...!
Did they even think about
how this makes us look?
[ROSS]
Let's go, Seargent!
[BROSH]
Where?
[ROSS] Where else
do you think, Brosh?
To the Fifth Laboratory!
[48]
Hrrrggghh!!
[ED]
Hyaaaahh!
[clashes]
[ED]
What happened?
My shoulder
doesn't feel right.
[WINRY] I increased the
percentage of chrome,
so it's less
prone to rusting,
but it's not as strong,
so don't try
anything crazy!
[ED] I have to find a
way to end this quickly...
Or else... I'm... dead!
[clang]
[48] What a cute
little monkey.
[ED] Who are you
calling little?!
[48]
Hahahaha!
It's been too long
since I've had prey
that was worth hunting!
[48] But you're tired
and wounded now...
You won't last much longer.
[48] Right about now,
my companion should
be finishing off
the partner
you left outside.
[ED] Is this companion
of yours strong?
[48]
Yes he is...
He isn't as strong
as I am, though.
[ED]
Hahaha!
[ED] In that case
I don't need to worry...
You see...
We've been sparring
partners a long time...
And I've still
never beaten him!
[66] Damn it...!
Why can't ya sit
still for a second
and let me cut you up,
you big bucket of bolts!
Rrgggh! Augggh!
You're empty!
[66]
Hahaha!
[66] There's a bit of
a story behind that.
[66] Would ya
like to hear...?
It's a pretty good yarn...
You probably already
know it, though.
It all starts with a
man by the name of Barry.
[66] Once upon a time,
right here in Central,
there was a
butcher named Barry
who loved his work...
His favorite part
was cutting up
the meat into little,
tiny pieces...
But one day, Barry
found that cutting up
beef and pork wasn't
enough anymore...
So he took to the
streets and began
cutting up people
instead, night after night.
[66] In time, of course,
Barry was caught...
but not before
twenty-three victims
had fallen prey to
him and his knife.
[66] Naturally, after
terrorizing Central for so long,
Barry was sent to the
gallows for his wicked deeds...
and the world was happily
rid of yet another evil man.
[66] At least, that's what
everyone out there believes...
But our story
isn't over yet.
We haven't even
reached the good part.
Barry isn't actually
dead, you see...
He's very much alive and
charged with guarding
a certain place--
only, without his body...
[66]
Yes, that's right...!
He's standing in front
of your very eyes...!
I am the infamous serial
killer, Barry the Chopper!
[AL] Sorry, I've
never heard of you.
[AL] I'm from a little
town in the east, so--
[66] Fine, but even if
you don't know who I am,
shouldn't you at least
be a little scared...?!
Shouldn't you
be going, "AHHH!"
or "What happened
to your body?!"
Or Something!?
AHHH...!
What happened to
your body, freak?!
[AL] Hey... now
that's impolite.
[66] Oh! I see! You
were on death row too.
You had me
startled there.
[AL] No way!
I'm not a criminal!
[66] Huh? Then what
happened to you?
[AL]
It's kind of a long story.
When I lost my body,
my brother
transmuted my soul
and bonded it to this armor.
[66 laughing]
Your brother?
Of course! Your brother!
[AL] What's so
funny about it?
[66]
Hahaha!
Are you sure you
and your brother
are really related?
[AL] Well,
I guess we don't look
that much
alike anymore...
[66] No, no, no...
That's not what I mean.
[66] Are you sure
that you're not a puppet
created and controlled
by your so-called brother?
[66] Were you ever even a
real person to begin with?
[AL] How can you ask
something like that...?!
I was a real boy,
and my name was
Alphonse Elric!
[66]
Hahahah!
How can you be
so sure of that?
[AL]
I have memories!
I remember who
I was before.
[66]
And who's to say
those memories
aren't made up?
[AL] But Winry and
Granny--they know me!
[66] That's easy...
They're in on it too.
[AL gasps]
[66] Silly boy...
You were never
alive to begin with...
It's as simple as that.
[AL]
Then how do you know
that you were really alive?
[66]
I was, trust me.
[PATROLMAN] This area
is off limits! Don't move!
[66]
There, didja see that?
There's nothing I love more
than chopping up live people.
I can't control myself...
I kill, therefore I am...
As long as I know that,
it's all I need to prove
to myself that
I've always been me.
[48] Your brother
is that good, is he...?
Then I'll have to hurry up
and defeat you
so I can get around
to taking care of him.
[ED]
Go Al! Do it now!
[48]
What?
That was dirty!
[ED] There's no such
thing as 'dirty' in a fight.
[48] What's the matter?
You still haven't
destroyed the bloodseal
I so kindly pointed out...
you going to or not?
[ED] There's something
I need to ask you about.
[48]
The Philosopher's Stone?
[ED] Yes. Tell me
everything you know about it.
[48]
Sorry, can't.
[ED]
Hey now...
Tell me. I did beat
you at your own game.
[48] That's where you're
wrong... I'm not beaten yet.
[ED]
Impossible!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[48]
I forgot to mention something
about this mass
murderer, Slicer.
[48 (YOUNGER)]
His crimes
were really done by
a pair of brothers.
[ED] An independent
head and body...?
That's a dirty trick!
[48] Now, now, weren't
you the one who said
there's no such thing
as "dirty" in a fight?
[48 (YOUNGER)]
Are you ready...?
Round two's about
to begin, short stuff.
[ED]
Don't call me short!
[48 (YOUNGER)]
I don't think so.
I'm not gonna give
you time to transmute!
[ED] Damn! I've
lost too much blood...
I'm starting to feel dizzy.
[ED]
Not good... Not good!
Here he comes...
I'm gonna die...
I'm going to die!
[48 (YOUNGER)]
Die!
[ED] You reminded me
of someone I don't like...
and now I've done
exactly what he did.
[48 (YOUNGER)] How could
you, you little brat?!
[ED] He's wriggling.
That's freaky!
[48 (YOUNGER)]
Brother!
[48] As much as I hate
to admit it, we've lost.
[ED] So you're not
going to tell me
you're really three
brothers, are you?
[48] No, no.
[48 (YOUNGER)] No, no.
[48] Come on,
boy, you won...
Hurry up and destroy us.
[ED]
No. I'm not a murderer.
[48] With bodies
like these,
are we really even people?
[ED]
I consider you people
whether you have
physical bodies or not...
If I didn't, that would
mean I didn't believe
my own brother
is a person either.
[66] Come on, what's
the matter little puppet?
[AL] I told you!
I'm not a puppet!
[66] You keep
telling yourself that.
[66] But how can
you know for sure?
How can you be certain
you were really alive?
[66] There is one
way you can prove
that you're not
just a puppet made
from scraps of armor.
[66] You got a
bloodseal too, right?
Destroy it... Go ahead,
break it yourself...
If you die, you were
a real boy all along,
just like you
want to believe.
[AL]
No...!
There's no way
I could ever do that!
[66]
Oh, no...?
Then I guess I'll have
to do it for you, won't I?
[ED] I know that my
brother is a human being...
That means you
guys are human, too...
I will not take the
life of another person.
[48 (YOUNGER)]
Brother?
[48] My brother and
I have been lying,
stealing, cheating,
and killing together
for as long as
we can remember.
[48] And now that we're
in these pseudo-bodies,
we're being treated like
humans for the first time...
Don't you see the irony?
[48] For that, boy, I'll
give you a parting gift...
I'll tell you everything...
I'll tell you who made
the Philosopher's Stone...
and ordered us
to guard this place.
[LUST] My, that
was a close call.
[LUST]
Number Forty-Eight,
you should know better than
to talk about things
that don't concern you.
[ENVY] Well, well,
would you look at that...
What's the Fullmetal
pipsqueak doing here?
[LUST] Such a
troublesome boy...
How did you find
out about this place?
[48]
Urrrggg!
[48 (YOUNGER)]
Brother! Brother! Brother!!!
[ENVY] Quit your pathetic
blubbering, you idiot!
[ENVY]
You were trying to kill
one of our most
important sacrifices...
Do you understand me?!
[ENVY] You could've
messed up the entire plan!
What would we
have done then?!
Huh?!
[ED] Tell me who
you people are...
What plan are you
talking about...?
What do you mean when you
say 'important sacrifice'?
[ENVY]
Oh, my...
The pipsqueak's
raring to go--
I think I made it angry!
[ED] Don't call
me pipsqueak again!
[ENVY] Then what
would you prefer...?
Eh, pipsqueak?
[ENVY]
Whoa, now...
There's no need
to fight here...
Someone might
get hurt, you know.
[ED] This is a fight
that you started...!
So come on!
[clang]
[LUST]
Technical difficulties?
[ED]
AUUGHH!!
[ENVY]
Lucky me!
[ENVY] You're fortunate
your arm's broken...
If not for that,
you wouldn't be
getting off so easily.
[LUST]
Listen to me well, boy...
Don't ever forget this.
Always remember we
allowed you to live.
[LUST]
We can't have him poking
around this place
again--it's too dangerous...
It'll have to go...
Blow it up.
[ED]
You know, Al...
There's something
I've been wanting
to tell you for awhile...
But I guess I've been
too afraid to say it.
[AL] What was Ed
about to tell me...?
He said he'd been too
afraid to say it before...
What could have
frightened him that much?
[66] Are you sure
you're not a puppet
created by your
so-called brother?
[66] Were you ever even a
real person to begin with?
[66] What's the
matter, little boy?
You got something
on your mind?
[AL] Shut up...!
You're wrong!
[66] Just accept it...
You'll feel better.
[66] You're mine now,
little puppet!
[bang]
[66]
What?
[ROSS]
Stay right there!
Or the next one puts
a hole in your head.
[66] This isn't going
quite as I planned.
[rumbling, cracking]
[ROSS] Sergeant...
get down now!
[crash]
[ROSS]
What are you doing...?!
Get away from there!
[AL] But my brother is
still inside the building!
[ROSS]
Ed's in there?
[66] Hmm... I know
what this means.
Time to get outta here!
[BROSH]
Hey, you!
[66] I'd get going
if I were you!
[BROSH]
Hold it!
[AL]
Brother...! Brother!
[ROSS]
Take cover, Al,
or you're going to
get caught in it too!
[AL]
Ed!
[explosion]
[ENVY]
There you are...!
I brought a little
present for you.
[AL]
Brother!
[ENVY]
His life's not in danger,
but he has lost
a lot of blood,
so you might
want to get him
to a hospital as
soon as you can.
[ENVY] Also, you
really should keep
a better eye on
him--stop him
from taking
these crazy risks...
He's a precious resource.
[ROSS]
But who are you?
[BROSH] Lt. Ross,
we need to go!
[ROSS] Sergeant,
help me with him.
[BROSH]
What happened to him?!
[ROSS]
We'll talk later...
And you should go too--!
What...?! He's gone!
[loud crash]
[rumbling crashes]
[disgruntled racket]
[GUARD 1] All of you!
Quiet...! Calm down now!
[KIMBLEE]
What a lovely sound.
I know it well...
That's the sound of
a building exploding.
Close as it is,
I'd say it's coming
from next door,
the Fifth Laboratory.
Ah... It's such a
comforting sound...
The way it reverberates
through your entire body!
[GUARD] You keep it
down in there, Kimblee!
[KIMBLEE]
Oh, do excuse me...
I was just recalling
the Ishvalan War
of Extermination,
and it put me
in such a good mood!
[66] Are you sure
you're not a puppet
created by your
so-called brother?
[HUGHES] So things here at
Central are pretty hectic...
The senior staff in
charge of State Alchemists
is shorthanded, thanks
to Scar's killing spree.
[ROY]
Oh?
[HUGHES]
Rumor has it;
a promotion to Central
for one Colonel Mustang
isn't far off.
[ROY] Central, huh...?
Not bad at all.
[HUGHES]
Watch yourself, though.
You can't move up
the ladder as
young as you are
without making enemies.
[ROY] I've been prepared
for that from the start.
[HUGHES] Just a
word of warning
from someone who
knows the game.
[HUGHES]
You need as many people
on your side as you can get
your hands on now, Colonel...
which means...
[HUGHES]
Get yourself a wife!
[ROY]
Seriously?!
[HUGHES]
I don't get it...
He hung up on
me just like that.
[RECEPTIONIST]
Lieutenant Colonel...!
Stop making so many
personal phone calls, okay?
[HUGHES]
Oh...! So sorry!
[NARRATOR] Edward Elric
cannot find the right words
to say what he must...
Meanwhile, young
Alphonse is frightened
by his brother's
continued silence...
Where does the truth lie...?
This truth is waiting...
hidden in the
memories of a young girl.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Nine.
"Created Feelings."
The heart begins to waver
because it fears what
the truth may bring.