Amanogawa Kirara!
How dare she return the Perfume and the key?!
Managing both school and work must take too much of her time.
But still...
Amanogawa as Cure Twinkle was just superbly splendid!
She was like a real star princess!
Well, I can't say she wasn't...
And it's amazing that she has such an ambitious dream!
I really want Amanogawa to be a Precure!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Amanogawa, bonjôur!
Bonjour. Your pronunciation's off.
Huh?
I-It was?
Ahem. Bonjoür, bonjôür!
Hold it!
I've got a favor to ask!
You really want me to be a Precure that much?
I do!
Maybe you could be a part-time Precure we call on for emergencies!
Or something! Please?
Nope.
Awww...
You brought me those doughnuts at the show, so I've got nothing against you.
But like I told you, I'm putting 100% into my modeling career, so I don't I have the time.
But—
If you insist,
then how about you try out my schedule?
Huh?
That'll give you an idea...
of just how busy I am.
Go, Trio!
We're the Princess Precures!
Hey, pick up the pace!
Wait up!
The bus'll leave soon! Hurry!
You're... too... fast!
Hurry, Haruharu!
R-Right!
Oh yeah, here's today's schedule.
Let me see...
Lessons, sports gym meet, and a
magazine shoot one after the other?
Followed by an interview... and a fashion show audition tonight?!
Yup! Tonight's audition is being judged by the
world famous designer, Baurollo Bauanne, himself!
Intense!
That's why I'm in a hurry!
Get moving!
W-Wait!
Excellent pose, Amanogawa!
That was so stylish!
Want to try?
Strike a pose at the end!
A-A pose?
That's ballet!
So this is where they do photoshoots!
This one isn't very good.
Is it?
I think you look really cute in it!
It has to make to magazine look good, not me.
My pose was pretty bad here.
Wow, really?
Good work today!
We've gotta get to the next studio, pronto!
We've got no time for the sports gym!
Then we'll cancel on the gym.
Let's run to the studio!
More running?
You okay?
Here.
Marble Doughnuts!
We've got some time until the audition, so let's kick back with a snack!
You're really something to keep up with a schedule like this every day.
Get it now?
Yeah!
I totally get how much you love modeling!
Oh yeah, I didn't get to hear
what your dream was back there.
My dream?
A princess!
A princess?
You already are one. A Princess Precure, right?
I mean, yeah, but I've still got a ways to go.
Well, more like I'm barely qualified...
I still haven't reached my goal, either...
Huh?
Stella, the supermodel?
She's my mom.
Oh. Wait, what?!
Mom is my shining star.
When I learned what her job was, I wanted to be a model, too.
Amanogawa Kirara Style Special
I got accepted when I applied to her agency.
I chose to attend Noble Academy
because it was her alma mater, too.
Oh...
Mom's appeared in Bauanne's shows before, too.
That's why I'm excited for this audition.
I swear...
that I'm gonna pass that audition!
Now let's go.
Sure!
I am le designer, Bauanne.
I expect you all to display your radiance.
Choose your dress and show me how greatly you can shine.
Shine?
Non.
Non!
I'm Amanogawa Kirara. Thank you for having me.
Good reaction!
Non! You still miss le something!
Try again!
I thought you were cute enough...
But if it's not enough for Bauanne, it doesn't matter.
What am I missing?
Amanogawa...
Ah!
Whoah, what is it?
You need stars!
The dress you wore when you became a Precure...
looked like a shining star to me!
When I became a...
It's not this, and not that, either...
Ah!
Amanogawa Kirara.
Bon.
Bonjour.
Star princess...
So they'll announce the results later?
Thanks for your help.
Your advice really saved me.
It was nothing! You would've passed anyway!
It's not that easy.
But I gave it 100%.
I guess it was 120% with your help...
Huh?
I've gotta thank you somehow.
Outside of becoming a Precure.
Yeah.
To be honest, I still really want to team up with you!
But I understand.
You want to give everything you have to your dream.
So, I'm sorry for bothering you so much!
I'll keep working to become a true princess!
Amanogawa, I hope you make your dream come true!
I'm rooting for you!
Oh, it's almost curfew! Let's get back quick!
Well, it's for the best.
Amanogawa!
Bonjour!
Haruharu!
I bought your magazine! Both you and your clothes look super cute in it!
Really?
You know, the clothes I wore at the shoot—
Haruno!
It's time for your lessons!
Oops! I've gotta go!
See ya!
You look silly!
But you're getting better.
I'll keep trying, Kaidou!
Good.
Oh, bonjour.
Bonjour.
Haruno told me about your day. How did the audition go?
Haven't heard back yet.
Is that why you look so glum?
Haruharu's... a weird girl, isn't she?
I told her I wouldn't be a Precure,
but she just accepted it with a smile.
Nobody else in my class would do that.
That girl's been throwing me off for a while now.
Seriously, what's with her?
What?
I'm sorry, but I think I know how you feel.
That girl certainly is an odd one.
Same to you, Minamin.
Huh?
You're Kaidou Minami,
so Minamin for short.
Lady Dyspear's gonna rip me a new one if I go back now.
I gotta do somethin' about those Precures...
So, the crux of the Pythagorean Theorem is...
Hmph.
I solved an equation nobody else could!
I'll toss that dream into the cage of despair!
Close your dream!
Come, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Kaidou!
We've got trouble!
There's a Dyspairvil on the loose!
Dyspairvil!
Haruno.
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
Princess Precures?!
Wait, two?
That dream shall be released at once!
Dyspairvil!
Let's go.
Got it!
Dorm mother, Shirogane.
Whoah, when'd you get there?!
You have a call.
Yes, this is Amanogawa.
Bonjour, Miss Kirara.
Oh, Mr. Bauanne!
Félicitations, my star princess.
You passed.
I can't get close!
We need to defeat the main Dyspairvil.
More incoming!
Over here!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair...
Mermaid!
Vil!
Flora! Mermaid!
I think I've got 'em...
Where's the third one?
She's not coming...
because she has a dream to follow!
Well, ain't it my lucky day!
Dyspairvil, destroy 'em!
Dyspairvil...
Flora!
Mermaid!
Hey!
What did you come here for?
Lend me the Perfume and Dress Up Key!
You already said you weren't gonna be a Precure!
My dream is still to become a top model.
That hasn't changed, but I've found something else just as important!
So...
I'll become a Precure!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Dyspair...
Vil!
Huh?!
Cure Twinkle...
That works, right?
You just said she wasn't coming!
Dyspairvil!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspair!
Take it, girls!
Got it!
Dyspairvil!
Ball's in my court again...
Guess I'll handle it.
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
I ain't done!
Enough, Close.
Lady Dyspear...
Do not embarrass yourself further.
Return.
Right!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Why? Didn't you say you weren't gonna be a Precure?
I passed.
Huh?
I passed the audition.
I just felt like telling you that.
What? I thought you were rooting for me.
Are you happy for me or not?
Congratulations!
You were super cute!
I'm in full bloom happiness!
Thanks.
I can still help out with this Precure thing.
Really?
But your work...
I'll just put in 200% instead of 100%.
I got to 120% with your help
pretty easily, so it'll be a cinch!
So, good luck, Haruharu and Minamin!
Same to you.
Minamin?!
It seems to be my nickname.
I-I'm left out!
Can I call you Minami too?
If I can call you Haruka...
Just call each other whatever. You are friends.
Friends...
In that case...
M-Minami...
Haruka...
Kirara!
I'm glad we're a team now!
Yeah!
The Princess Precures finally...
...have their third member!
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
Princess lessons from Miss Siamour?
I'm too excited!
Go! Princess Precure:
Your First Lesson!
Aim for the Gran Prixncess!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Shizuoka Prefecture - Haruka (Age 6)
Tokyo - Wato (Age 5)