"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
Morning, Kagami.
Hey. You're in a good mood, what's up?
I traded my old cell phone in for a new one!
Oh, finally?
That means you can now set
songs for your ringtones
and customize your screen, right?
I already entered my favorites onto it.
♪ Mi-Mi-Miracle, Mikurun-run ♪
You know, that's some song you got there.
But...
You have to pick up before it enters
the chorus, so it's a shame,
or rather, don't you get stressed over it?
Even if you don't answer, it stops mid-song.
I've never thought about it
myself, but is that how it works?
"Ring"
If you had to pick, Kagami is... an orc!
Why?! Why am I the only monster?!
Yes, hello, Hiiragi here.
Oh, no, it's a habit from answering
calls on the land-line at home.
She was throwing her anger
at me until mere seconds ago.
Today I had a sandwich that you
pour a balsamic vinegar sauce on.
Why can women switch gears so quickly?
But the other day, my mother...
I have returned home!
Oh yes, hello? Huh, Miyuki?
Geez, Miyuki! Here, the phone!
It's from Konata-chan!
Um... Did I do something wrong?
No, Mother really is an open book,
so she's the type that you
can see when she's angry.
Apparently, she hit her foot
against the corner of the desk.
But that's a bit different
from being an open book.
Her personality is exactly as it seems.
Because you know so much,
Miyuki, you really help me out,
getting me answers so quickly!
I was so happy to be
complimented by my mother
that it became a habit to
look up all sorts of things.
Miyuki, you know more than your mom!
Now, it's because it's
fun to learn something...
Does that mean I've brought you up well?
That was the conversation we had.
What's with that spaced-out conversation?
Anyway, Miyuki-san, I can tell
you're definitely her daughter.
You two are just alike.
Are we alike?
Completely, all the way down to the genes.
But Miyuki, you really do
know all sorts of things,
not just what we learn in school.
Nowadays, there are so many
sources of information
that it is fun to learn
about all sorts of things.
That's impossible for me.
I don't feel up to it! I wanna play!
Ask others when you're in a bind!
They do say that only children or
oldest children tend to be selfish.
Come to think of it, you're an
only child too, right, Miyuki?
You're both only children, but I
guess it depends on the person, huh?
No... at home, I have an example,
or someone that seems like an older sister.
Cleaning is a pain! Laundry exhausts me!
Is take-out okay for dinner?
We have two older sisters,
and all meals turn into battles for
food, so you end up very tough.
Yay! Sukiyaki!
Go ahead and eat plenty.
Time to eat!
And so, Kona-chan said that when
your cell phone gets no reception,
it's because the density of some
kind of particles is very high.
I see, I see.
And she said that when the battery is dead,
the situation is "Completely Silent."
Kids nowadays use very strange words.
Hey, let's leave some for Tsukasa too.
I'll give you some of my share, Tsukasa.
Thanks.
You say that, but you were
wolfing it down with us.
I guess there are good and
bad things about siblings.
Only children have their
own problems as well.
That's right, Yuki-chan, sometimes
you really space out, right?
Space out?
You know, the other day...
Considering green (horse dung) sea urchins...
I'm sure they can't stand
the name they've been given.
What's wrong?
I was walking while thinking,
and ran into the door...
Miyuki-san, you really concentrate so hard...
You have lots of situations like that.
Oh, how very embarrassing...
Hey, but if you start thinking
about something else
in the middle of doing something,
do you lack concentration skills?
Wait, which is it?
That really is like you, Miyuki.
That's true.
The other day, I was warming up a drink...
Oh, I had forgotten!
I need to warm it up again...
"Several dozen minutes later"
Oh... I have to do it again...
Oh, again!
Oh!
Geez, Miyuki, you forgot again!
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it...
I guess I have no choice.
I'll bring it over to you.
Thank you so much.
And with a push!
"Several dozen minutes later"
I forgot!
Nothing less from the family
in the Hall of Fame.
It is terribly embarrassing, but...
Miyuki-san, when did you
start wearing glasses?
I think it was in the last few
years in elementary school.
So your eyesight wasn't
that bad to begin with?
When I was a child, I
really loved all the books
that my mother would read
to me before going to sleep.
But my mother would always fall asleep first,
and I wanted to know how the story continued,
and tried so hard to read
on in a dark room...
And eventually my eyesight...
But it's best for kids to be on
good terms with their parents,
like in your family, Miyuki.
I heard that one reason why kids
nowadays are so indifferent and dry
is because they lack affection, or
rather skinship, from their parents.
You know, I wonder, when was the last time
that I got a big hug from Mom?
Tsukasa, you were a spoiled child,
so you were all over Mom
until about 7th grade!
Really?
Maybe that's why you're such a good girl.
In my family, Dad still clings all over me!
That's probably why you
haven't grown up, in a way.
Speaking of children, there
really are a lot of cases
involving abduction or confinement
of young girls lately.
You really have an eye out for
stuff like that for some reason...
But my dad's the one who
worries about that stuff.
Don't say scary things like that so easily.
Well, I'm sure they've been
affected by games, more or less...
But I'd really like them to stop,
because it only troubles other users!
Or rather, at least, stuff like that
never shows up in the games that I play.
Oh, that's right, it's almost
the one-year anniversary.
Of what?
Of me getting a part-time job.
Everyone at work said they
would celebrate it with me.
Come to think of it, I
haven't been there yet.
Maybe I'll go visit you
while you work sometime,
to get back at you for New Year's.
Sure, that's fine!
It's fine?! Isn't this usually
where people get reluctant?
I mean, being seen is like
half of my job already.
They call it a cosplay café, right?
Yeah. Let me know in advance
when you're going to come.
Sometimes we're pretty busy.
I'll do that.
Hey, guys, class has
already started, you know?
Lucky Star!
Oh, hello.
We just came out of the station.
Yeah, yeah, I'll get it for you.
Yeah. Yeah.
Kona-chan said it was all right?
It's all right, but she
wants me to buy this month's
issue of Comp______ and a
Lelou__ comic over there first.
Will we be able to find it easily?
She reminded me to get the
receipt stamped by the cashier,
but it's a bit confusing.
Excuse me, do you mind?
I'd like a picture.
I'm not Kamigishi... I'm Hiiragi...
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
Over here too for a shot, please!
Geez! Stop taking pictures!
Then, excuse me... Can you
say "Hiroyuki-chan" for me?
"Hiroyuki-chan"?
Let's go!
This is the first time I've
been in a store like this,
but it's so spacious that it makes you panic.
On the phone, she told me that it
would be obvious when I got here.
Kona-chan can figure it out...
I think I'd get lost if I was by myself.
Oh, is this it?
Now, I have to find a comic called Lelou__.
It's not here...
I can't find it.
Excuse me, where is the Lelou__ comic?
Oh, that would be this.
Code Ge__ss...
At least tell me the title so that
it's easy for us to understand.
Can I get points on my card
the next time I'm here?
Then, please bring your card with
this receipt on your next visit.
Sure.
Thank you very much!
Now, all we have to do is
go visit Konata's place.
Big sister, I'm hungry!
I'll be getting off of work soon,
so hold on for a few minutes.
How do you want us to get
there, with a map like this?!
As it so happens, I looked the
location up before coming,
so I think it's over here.
Nothing less from Yuki-chan!
In the end, Miyuki is the
one that we can count on.
It's this place, right?
Yes. It's on the third floor of this place.
Welcome back, my master.
Please, over here.
The first hour is 800 yen, and all
soft drinks have free refills.
All the games are free to play,
and the sweets are all-you-can-eat.
Can I have this eel bowl?
We don't have it right now.
Then, the shrimp pilaf.
We can't do it now.
Then, the meat-sauce spaghetti will do.
15 minutes will be required.
Your approval?
All right, let's do it.
With stuff like that, can
this work out as a business?
You guys...
What would you like to drink?
Wait a minute.
Hurry up. If you're late,
you'll pay a fine, a fine!
Is that the attitude you
show towards your customers?
That's the protocol here.
So you've decided already, right?
I'll have melon soda.
I'm not interested in an ordinary menu.
I would like a milk tea.
And what do you want?
I'm still picking one!
That's too slow for a brigade member.
Since when am I a brigade member?!
That's the settings for this outfit.
You're an entire century too early
to disobey your brigade leader.
This is so confusing.
Then, an iced coffee will do.
Orders from the brigade
leader. Sit here and wait!
Oh, brother.
It was the first time it smelled in a while!
We're gonna have a show on
stage now, so please watch.
♪ If we figured out the globe
like we would a riddle ♪
♪ We could all go anywhere together ♪
♪ To the end of time, BOOON! ♪
Encore! Encore!
Amazing!
Everyone performs so well!
Next time, do the Mori version!
She's an exchange student, and
a freshman at our high school.
My name is Patricia Martin. Nice to meet you.
We've released a CD, too. See?
"Mikuru"
"Konata and Patty Cos-tte
(Cos-it)!" "Oh My Honey"
You're allowed to put
something like that on sale?
Excuse me, may I have some tea?
Would you like it hot?
Yes, please make it hot.
I'd like a melon soda.
All right.
Let's see... What kind of drink
is this "up-to-you mix juichu"?
Classified information.
Protocol, protocol!
This café is amazingly tiring...
"Nurse's Office"
My height...
It's all right.
I'm sure you will still grow
more and more in the future.
That's got to be true!
Oh, Sis!
Oh, Yu-chan.
I start with such a hope-destroying
example right next to me!
Sis, how much did you grow height-wise
since you entered high school?
Well... I haven't seen any change,
vertically nor horizontally.
Yu-chan, you should be
prepared for the worst.
"touch, touch"
No depressions, don't be depressed,
there is a need out there.
Hey, you two, have you gone to a reunion yet?
No, not yet.
I haven't either.
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
The often-said "You haven't changed at all!"
Is usually a compliment, right?
But the only people who
are happy to hear that
are the ones that properly changed
in various places, right?
So you cared, at least a little bit.
Now, Golden Week is about to
begin. But understand this, okay?
Aside from the exams you'll
have right after the break,
remember that you guys face
entrance exams this year,
and spend your break in moderation!
And furthermore,
the weekdays in-between the
holidays are not days off!
I won't authorize any plans to
catch a cold and miss school!
Kamchatka!
That aura that emanates
from the entire body...
No doubt about it, it's Legendary Girl A!
Is that new volume today's target?
Or will it be the goods?
Think hard...
Don't forget that we are in the
middle of the spring AV fair!
Not yet!
After drawing her in well,
and letting her guard down...
That's when we recommend something!
That's right. Wait for her to get closer.
That's right!
Now! Call out to her!
I'm going out!
Welcome!
Here's what we've recently got in stock!
Hey, Kagami.
Are you here now?
Yeah, I'll be right over.
She was only passing time
while waiting for someone!
With simmering, you make rolling wedges.
You chop them into random shapes on purpose.
Oh, is that so?
That way, you increase the surface area,
and it's easy for the flavor
to sink in, they say.
After you skim off the scum,
let it simmer on medium
heat for about ten minutes.
It crumbles if you simmer it for too long,
so it's okay to take it off the
heat when a toothpick can sink in.
I see.
It's somewhat surprising that
when it comes to home economics,
Miyuki looks like she's below average.
I now totally understand just how
you usually look at us, Kagami.
Hiiragi-chan, would you
like to study for the exams
together in the library? Think
of it as helping each other out.
Yeah, sure!
Right before exams,
the usual club activities all get cancelled,
so you suddenly have nothing to do.
That's why you study.
That's why there aren't any going on.
Well, I understand that,
but when you're free in the times
that you usually spend in your club,
you see somewhat of a
different world, you know?
When you think about that, you
can't possibly study, right?
It's like you're wasting time,
you get all antsy and excited.
For now, understand that half of the reason
why we're holding this study
group is for your sake.
I'm tired!
So fast!
Let's take a little break!
Maybe you can't concentrate because
you don't have a goal in mind?
Don't you have a dream of what
you want to be in the future?
A dream, huh...
It's not like it's the future or
anything, but during this season,
don't you just wish that you'd
win the lottery or something,
and live an easy life? You get kinda lazy.
Minegishi, do something about that thing.
When I use my brains, sweet
stuff is a must after all!
After we get home, I'll bring you some
of the cookies I baked the other
day, so let's do our best!
Oh, you bake sweets and stuff, Minegishi?
Yeah, though not as much
as that Ajiyoshi boy.
No, no, yours are more
delish than Ajiyoshi's!
Studying is such a chore!
Sis, I tried baking some madeleines!
What's wrong?
Well, um...
I don't think it's like birds
of a feather flocking together,
but I was just wondering whether
or not similar types of friends
naturally come together around you...
Are you taking it lightly,
thinking that it's just
another simple canker sore?
These medical-type shows really
have increased in number lately.
You're right.
It's scary because a lot of it
happens really close to you.
Especially to me!
Or rather, watching this
stuff, you start thinking,
"Maybe I'm going to die soon?"
And can't stop thinking about it.
It just rings too many bells.
That's enough of negative
stories close to home.
I beg you, please stay alive!
Oh, Sis, can you teach me this part?
Let's see...
"Kazu (curses), like chickens,
come home to roast (roost)"?
So, this is...
Kazu likes chicken.
When he comes home, there is roast chicken.
I think.
Sis, can you translate the rest from here?
Let me see...
When you make the contract...
Did I learn stuff like this?
Oh yeah, the other day, when I
was working as a shrine maiden,
guests from overseas were talking
about the origin of the torii arch.
Oh? What were they saying?
Long ago, it was said that
birds (tori) carried the dead,
and it was a tree for the birds to rest on.
That's why they call it a "bird
stay" (torii), apparently.
They know more about Japan than we do!
Maybe it would have been faster
to just ask Kagami-neechan...
Lucky Star!
The Sea of Japan, where the
chill seeps down to the bone.
Where has the one I love gone?
All alone, swimming through the
rough waves of show business.
Let's have her sing!
Miss Akira Kogami, with Cape
Thirties (Misoji Misaki)!
Hold it! What part of this is a live show?!
Considering the show's budget,
this was the absolute limit!
It's practically Ta__ri Club!
It's going to start!
Just who do you think I am--
♪ Can I tell a story as a monologue? ♪
♪ I mumbled softly to the seagulls ♪
♪ A woman, topped with
a one-way caring heart ♪
♪ The sea winds of the
north froze stiff ♪
♪ Separated, love disperses ♪
It's sure taking a long time
for the drinks to get here...
♪ Even words of curses ♪
Yes?
I've brought the drinks that you ordered.
Oh, thanks.
Wait, that brown thing is mine!
♪ Cape Thirties ♪
"Lucky ★ Channel production"
"Akira Kogami's Big Show!!"
Damn tasty!
♪ Falling into tears
in the inn, all alone ♪
Let's see... Where is Kentai Life Returns?
♪ Even if I regretted
the night we made love ♪
Hello?
♪ To the splashing waves ♪
Oh, yes, yes.
An extension?
♪ If I were to toss them ♪
Oh, yes, we're fine.
Yes, my best regards.
We've got five minutes left.
♪ It seems like I can
see you so far away ♪
Let's clean up, let's.
Bye-nee!
Oh, I'd like to release a
song as a solo artist, too.
♪ Cape Thirties ♪
♪ S-S-S-Something forgotten... ♪
♪ Can I tell a story as a monologue? ♪
♪ I mumbled softly to the seagulls ♪
♪ A woman, topped with
a one-way caring heart ♪
♪ The sea winds of the
north froze stiff ♪
♪ Separated, love disperses ♪
♪ Even words of curses ♪
♪ Won't reach you so far away ♪
♪ Just standing here, crying
until you're soaked ♪
♪ Cape Thirties ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
So dull. Nagato, at this
rate, nobody will watch!
I want you to do it more like
someone cheerfully speaking
from the TV out to the living room
around 6:30 PM on a Sunday night.
Now, one more time. Go!
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
It didn't change! Oh, I don't care anymore.
Next episode: Base of the Sun.
Please look forward to it.
No, rock, paper, scissors!