♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
TO BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEOWS]
V.T., YOUR SHIFT OVER?
YEAH, FINALLY.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
JUST ON MY WAY TO YULAPAR.
THAT'LL MAKE YOU SOME BUCKS.
NOTHING LIKE WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN PULLING IN.
I HEARD YOU DID A ROUND TRIP
FROM HERE TO VENUS
IN 4 DAYS OR SO.
IT WAS 3 DAYS.
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
ANYWAY, TAKE IT EASY, NOW.
YOU, TOO.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
HEY, V.T.
HUH?
SO YOU'RE STILL TRYING, HUH?
YEAH, OF COURSE.
AND I'M GONNA KEEP ON TRYING
'TIL I GET MY MONEY BACK.
HEY, KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
OK, YOU'VE ONLY GOT ONE SHOT,
AND YOU GET NO CLUES.
ALL RIGHT, V.T., I SAY
YOUR NAME IS VAL TOMMYANA.
HUH, NICE TRY.
OH, NO!
THIS IS A BAD SIGN.
YOU BE CAREFUL NOW, OTTO.
[MEOWS]
YOU KNOW THAT CROSS-EYED GUY
THEY PUT THAT 8 MILLION
REWARD ON THE OTHER DAY?
GUESS WHO CAUGHT HIM? ME.
ON THE OTHER DAY.
THAT WAS 10 YEARS AGO,
YOU OLD COOT. JEEZ.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW,
YOU YOUNG TURKS?
WHY, I TAUGHT TELPISCOREI
EVERYTHING HE EVER KNEW.
THE TELPISCOREI?
THE BOUNTY HUNTER?
THAT'S RIGHT.
THOSE WITH A PRICE
ON THEIR HEADS QUIVERED IN FEAR
AT THE SOUND OF HIS NAME.
YOU'RE BLOWING SMOKE, OLD MAN.
[ALL GASP]
[MEOWS]
OH, HI, ZEROS.
HEY, V.T. WHAT'S IT
GONNA BE? THE USUAL?
YEAH. WHAT'S WITH
ALL THE MUSCLE BOYS?
THIS PLACE IS USUALLY EMPTY.
THERE'S SOMETHING COMING DOWN.
A BOUNTYHEAD NAMED DECKER'S
SUPPOSED TO SHOW UP HERE
LATER, AND WORD GOT OUT.
THESE GUYS ARE
ALL BOUNTY HUNTERS.
[SCOFFS]
NO WONDER IT'S SUCH A CIRCUS.
LOOKS LIKE PUNKS
ON PARADE IN HERE.
YOU SAID EXCLUSIVE INFORMATION.
NOW THE PLACE IS CRAWLING
WITH BOUNTY HUNTERS.
THEY ALL KNOW ABOUT DECKER,
AND I'VE GOT A HANGOVER
THE SIZE OF NEPTUNE.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THE GUY LOOKS LIKE.
ALL WE KNOW IS HE'S GOT
A TATTOO SHAPED LIKE A DRAGON.
AND FAYE? YEAH, RIGHT.
LIKE SHE'S GONNA FIND
HIM IN THAT PLACE.
WELCOME TO WOODY'S,
THE FAMILY FUN PLACE.
IF YOU'RE CELEBRATING
A BIRTHDAY TODAY, YOU CAN HAVE--
[SIGHS]
HMM.
HI.
WHAT DO YOU WANT, BABE?
YOU LOOKING FOR SOME ACTION?
WELL, YOU MIGHT SAY THAT
A CERTAIN KIND OF ACTION.
I'M ALL YOURS.
PUT YOUR HANDS UP,
DECKER, MY FRIEND.
DON'T BE SO ROUGH!
JUST GET THE HELL OVER HERE.
I'M WORKING RIGHT NOW, PLEASE.
WE JUST WANT TO BE FRIENDS,
SWEETIE... GOOD FRIENDS.
HA HA HA! I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO HAVE SOME FUN.
THAT'S THE WAY!
COME HERE.
STOP, PLEASE!
SOMEONE, HELP!
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
V.T.!
SINCE WHEN IS IT
A BOUNTY HUNTER'S JOB
TO CHASE AFTER A WOMAN'S BUTT
INSTEAD OF CHASING AFTER MONEY?
SORRY. IT'S NOT PERSONAL.
THIS IS MY JOB.
WHAT'D I DO WRONG?
IT'S NO USE PLAYING INNOCENT.
I CAN SEE THE EDGE
OF YOUR DRAGON TATTOO.
YOU GOT THE WRONG GUY.
HEY, YOU WITH THE GLASSES,
PUT A CALL IN TO THE POLICE.
LET 'EM KNOW I CAUGHT DECKER.
MMHMM. MMHMM.
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
NO, WAIT! STOP! DON'T!
WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
I GOT A THING FOR EELS.
NEXT TIME KEEP IT COVERED!
YOU'RE DEAD!
CARVE HIM UP, BOYS.
V.T.!
I'M TIRED OF YOU, BLONDIE!
AAH!
[CRASH]
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
YOU SPILLED MY EGG.
I NEEDED THAT EGG.
AW, DAMN! COME ON, BOYS!
LET'S GET THIS GUY, TOO!
THERE YOU ARE.
AAH!
DAMN! I MAKE YOU PAY FOR THAT!
JUST KIDDING.
JUST FORGET ABOUT US.
MY 12 MILLION, ALL GONE.
TALK ABOUT THE BOTTOM
OF THE FOOD CHAIN.
BOUNTY HUNTERS MUST BE THE
LOWEST FORM OF LIFE THERE IS.
YOU THINK SO?
I KNOW SO. HUMAN BEINGS
ARE JUST A PRICE TAG TO THEM.
THEY LIVE BY GAMBLING
ON OTHER PEOPLE'S LIVES.
YEAH. WELL, THAT MAY BE.
SO HAVE A SEAT.
THE DRINKS ARE ON ME.
[WHINES]
DON'T WHINE.
BEAN SPROUTS ARE VERY HEALTHY.
THEY'RE GOOD FOR YOU.
ANYWAY, THAT'S ALL THERE IS.
GIVE ME A BREAK HERE,
WOULD YOU, PLEASE?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
THAT MUST BE IT.
OH, FAYE, IT'S YOU.
THAT WAS QUICK. WHAT?!
OH, MAN, THAT'S GROSS.
IT'S CALLED A PRAIRIE OYSTER.
GOOD FOR HANGOVERS.
YOU'RE THE SECOND
PERSON I'VE KNOWN
WHO ACTUALLY DRINKS
THOSE AWFUL THINGS.
AND WHO'S THE FIRST?
IT WAS MY HUSBAND.
V.T.
WE'RE BOUND TO
GET IT NOW. ALL CASH.
ONE TRY FOR ALL 3 OF YOU GUYS?
THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. SUIT YOURSELF.
HERE IT IS. LET'S GO.
V.T., I THINK YOUR NAME IS--
ADRIENNE. THAT'S JUST
GOTTA BE IT, RIGHT?
BUT ADRIENNE
DOESN'T START WITH A "V."
OH, YOU SEE? WE SHOULD
HAVE STUCK WITH LETICIA!
YEAH.
SO TELL ME. DO I GET THAT
LITTLE MOUNTAIN OF CASH
IF I CAN GUESS YOUR NAME?
YEAH. I DON'T
REMEMBER WHO STARTED IT,
BUT IT JUST KEPT PILING UP,
AND HERE I AM NOW SITTING
ON A FAT STACK, YOU KNOW?
WELL, I'LL GIVE IT A TRY.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
SPIKE, IT'S ME.
FAYE JUST MISSED DECKER.
GO AFTER HIM. QUICK.
SPIKE!
GET LOST.
HUH?
LYING LOWLIFE BOUNTY HUNTER.
I'M NOT PAYING
FOR YOUR DRINK.
[GASPS]
OH, WAIT, SPIKE!
AAH! MY SHIP!
YEAH. THEY WRECKED IT,
THOSE GUYS YOU BEAT UP.
THEY'RE CALLED
THE SOMETHING BROTHERS.
YOU WERE WATCHING?
UH-HUH.
SO, MURIEL, WHY DIDN'T
YOU TELL ME ABOUT IT?
BUT I DID TELL YOU.
I TOLD YOU JUST NOW.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
[MEOWS]
HUH? YOU'RE HEADED
FOR HOME NOW, V.T.?
THAT'S RIGHT.
ZEROS, COME ON.
[MEOWS]
WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
HITCHHIKING.
THOSE STOOGES
SMASHED UP MY STARSHIP.
YOU'RE JUST A MESSED-UP
LOSER, SPIKE.
AND A LOWLIFE BOUNTY
HUNTER SCUMBAG.
DON'T FORGET THAT.
DON'T PUSH YOUR LUCK.
[MEOWS]
COME ON. LET'S GO.
MIND IF I TAKE ANOTHER
FRIEND OF MINE ALONG?
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING]
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE
TO TELL YOU THE SAME THING?
SHORT, BALD, WITH
GLASSES AND SARASVATI
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I JUST SAID IT! OH!
CAN YOU PLEASE TURN DOWN
THAT REPULSIVE MUSIC?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHEN IN ROME,
DO AS THE ROMANS DO.
HUH?
AND IT'S NOT REPULSIVE.
IT'S VERY SOOTHING.
IT'S CALLED HEAVY METAL,
BY THE WAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY WRECKED
BOTH SHIPS ON THE SAME DAY.
AND WHO DO THEY THINK'S
GONNA REPAIR THESE THINGS?
NOW, WHAT THE HELL
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH THOSE LITTLE SCRAPS
OF INFORMATION, HUH?
HOW MANY BALD GUYS
WITH GLASSES DO
YOU THINK THERE ARE
IN THIS GALAXY?
I SAID BALD, SHORT,
WITH GLASSES,
AND DRIVING A TACKY TRUCK WITH
SARASVATI PAINTED ON THE SIDE.
[BEEPING]
YEAH?
V.T., IS THAT YOU?
HEY, OTTO. WHAT'S UP?
AW, I GOT INTO A HIT-AND-RUN.
HUH?
GUY CUTS INTO LINE
AT THE GATE, RAMS ME,
AND THEN JETS OFF.
DAMN. I GOTTA MAKE HIM
PAY FOR REPAIRS AT LEAST.
SO TELL ME IF
YOU SEE THE WEASEL.
SO HOW DO I SPOT HIM?
WELL, LET ME THINK.
YEAH, THERE WAS THIS GIANT ASIAN
GODDESS PAINTED ON HIS SHIP.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IT WASN'T SARASVATI, WAS IT?
YEAH, YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT IT SAID.
HOW'D YOU KNOW, ANYWAY?
ZEROS.
[MEOWS]
BREAKER 19, BREAKER 19, TO
ALL TRUCKERS ON THE ASTEROIDS,
THIS IS HEAVY METAL QUEEN.
HEY, GUYS, IF YOU SEE A TRUCK
WITH SARASVATI PAINTED ON IT,
GIVE ME A RING. THANKS, GUYS.
HEY, V.T. LOVE MACHINE
OVER HERE IN SECTOR 12.
WHAT'S UP WITH THIS CALL?
DID SOME DUDE SKIP OUT ON YOU?
HUH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I HAVEN'T SEEN THE GUY,
BUT YOU KNOW I'LL BE
OUT LOOKING FOR HIM.
THANKS FOR THE HELP.
YEAH, THIS IS SNEAKY SNAKE.
DID YOU SAY A PAINTING
OF A CLOWN?
NO.
THIS IS SPIDER MIKE,
BLACK PANTHER OF JUPITER, V.T.
I'VE NEVER MET YOU,
BUT I HEAR A LOT OF
WILD STORIES ABOUT
THE HEAVY METAL QUEEN.
I GUESS THAT'S A COMPLIMENT.
SO WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I GOT A POSITIVE I.D.
ON YOUR TARGET
ABOUT 10 MINUTES AGO.
IT WASN'T TOO FAR
FROM THE OLD LINUS MINES.
HOPE THAT HELPS.
THANKS A BUNCH.
I OWE YOU ONE, GUY.
[GRUNTING]
GREAT. ONE MORE
PART TO BE REPLACED.
[PANTING]
HUH?
HE'S MINE.
TRYING TO OUTMANEUVER ME, PAL?
NICE TRY, SCUMBAG!
THIS IS V.T. CALLING.
LET ME TALK TO THAT LOWLIFE
SCUM BOUNTY HUNTER.
THE LINUS MINES?
THAT'S CRAZY! STAY AWAY.
HUH? WHAT'D YOU SAY?
JUST STAY AWAY FROM DECKER.
HE'S HAULING HIGH EXPLOSIVES.
HELLO?
HEY, HOLD ON!
I HAVE FIRST DIBS
ON DECKER! WAIT!
[GRINDING]
IT'S SO UGLY.
AND PARTS OF IT
ARE STILL BROKEN.
TOO BAD IT WASN'T
YOUR MOUTH THAT WAS BROKEN.
I HEARD THAT.
HEY, JET, I'M GOING OUT.
HOLD ON. I DIDN'T EVEN GET
THE ARTILLERY WORKING YET.
THAT WAS A BIG MISTAKE.
HUH?
AAH!
WHAT'S ALL THIS?
ISN'T THIS A LITTLE RISKY?
WATCH YOUR BACK.
THERE GOES MY 12 MILLION.
[MEOWS]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
V.T., YOU THERE?
IF YOU'RE ALIVE,
SAY SOMETHING.
I'M OK. TAKES MORE THAN
THAT TO GET RID OF ME.
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
DECKER WAS SELLING
ENHANCED NITRO,
AND IT'S ALL DESTABILIZED NOW.
HIS SHIP IS PACKED WITH IT.
THE WHOLE THING?
THAT'S ENOUGH NITRO
TO BLOW THIS PLACE TO SHREDS.
IT GETS WORSE.
THIS PLACE IS
AN OLD MINING SATELLITE,
AND THE REACTORS
ARE BREAKING UP.
[GASPS]
WE'VE GOTTA FIND
A WAY OUT OF THIS MESS.
[BEEPING]
HOW MUCH FARTHER
TO THE EXIT CHUTES?
NOT FAR.
ANGLE 20 DEGREES LEFT.
THERE. IT'S UP AHEAD. HUH?
IT'S BLOCKED.
BEHIND YOU, FAYE!
AAH! IN FRONT!
ARE YOU SHOOTING A POP GUN?
YOU'LL NEVER BLAST
THROUGH LIKE THAT.
WELL, EXCUSE ME!
I HAVE NO ARTILLERY.
ALL I HAVE ARE THESE PINCERS.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
THERE MUST BE
A WAY TO GET OUT.
OF COURSE THERE IS,
AND IT'S JUST WAITING FOR US,
PACKED INSIDE THAT FREIGHTER.
I DON'T LIKE THIS.
IT'S A DELICATE OPERATION,
AND I'M NOT REALLY
THE DELICATE TYPE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN,
DON'T BE SO DELICATE.
LET'S JUST GO FOR IT.
[GRUNTING]
NO!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW GRAB ONE.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY,
MR. PERFECT.
UH, THERE'S GAS COMING OUT.
PROBABLY STABILIZERS.
WHICH MEANS?
IT'S TOUCH SENSITIVE.
WHAT?
COME ON, GIRL. WHAT'S
THE WORST THAT CAN HAPPEN?
YOU SCREW UP,
AND WE ALL DIE.
THAT'S VERY COMFORTING.
OK, I'VE GOT ONE.
NOW WHAT DO I DO WITH IT?
I'M PROGRAMMING THIS POD
TO SHOOT TOWARD THE EXIT
AND SELF-EXPLODE IN 40 SECONDS,
SO GET THAT NITRO IN HERE ASAP.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME, FAYE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
MY FLOATING ACT.
- AAH!
ZEROS, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
WE'VE GOTTA LET HIM IN!
BINGO.
IT'S ALL CLEAR! AAH!
I NEED A NEW GIG.
[PANTING]
[MEOWS]
ZEROS.
THANKS FOR THE HELP,
VICTORIA TELPISCOREI.
HUH?
AND GIVE YOUR HUSBAND
MY THANKS, TOO.
I FIGURED OUT WHO
YOU WERE BECAUSE OF THIS.
OF COURSE,
EVERYONE'S HEARD ABOUT HIM
THE LEGENDARY BOUNTY HUNTER
TELPISCOREI AND WIFE.
I WON'T BE ABLE TO GIVE HIM
YOUR THANKS FOR A WHILE.
I'M AFRAID HE'S DOING
ALL HIS BOUNTY HUNTING
UP IN HEAVEN THESE DAYS.
I SEE.
THE REST IS
FOR YOUR HUSBAND.
I'M SURE THAT HE'S GOT
A HANGOVER UP THERE.
TREAT HIM TO
A PRAIRIE OYSTER ON ME.
ONCE IN A WHILE,
I DO THE PREVIEW MYSELF.
I'M JET BLACK,
36 YEARS OLD.
I'M OFTEN TOLD
I DON'T LOOK 36,
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T JUDGE
PEOPLE BASED ON APPEARANCES
OR HOW MUCH HAIR THEY HAVE.
THINGS ARE NEVER
WHAT THEY SEEM TO BE.
THAT'S HOW
THE NEXT EPISODE IS, TOO.
IT'S A STORY THAT SEEMS
VERY UNLIKE BEBOP.
NEXT EPISODE
"WALTZ FOR VENUS."
STUFF LIKE THIS IS GOOD
ONCE IN A WHILE, HUH?