<sign: Medical Offices (Currently Closed) - Nurse's Office>
- Angel Area}
- which sounds wrong in Japanese as well as english :D)}
<sign: Guild Accessway B15 >
< sign: Guild lowest point - Ground Zero >
Mazui presents
mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I open my eyes again, to a sleepy morning
eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie around my neck
kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to
教室のドア潜ると
When I pass through the door of the classroom
honno sukoshi mune wo hatte arukidaseru
ほんの少し胸を張って歩き出せる
I puff my chest out with a little bit of pride
sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind that blows past everyday life
kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought I heard it
kanjita ki ga shitanda
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought I felt it
furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す　今この胸で
It started to shake within my chest
mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would come now
iku oku no hoshi ga kie satteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched countless stars as they vanished
miokutta te wo futta yokatta ne to
見送った　手を振った　良かったねと
I waved goodbye, "I'm glad"
Everyone here is out playing around at night.
Which means...
I have to exact punishment.
What does this mean?
Kanade...
Hey, what's going on?
Wasn't Angel harmless now?
No...
That's not Kanade.
Kanade never drew her blade on us before we showed signs of resistance.
Dammit!
Yurippe, what should we do?
Everyone, form a semi-circle around her!
Why the hell are you giving orders?
Even if she's protected by Distortion, just attack!
Who do you think you are?
Let go of me!
Got it!
Roger!
Move, Yuri!
Fire!
Dammit!
Medical Offices (Currently Closed) - Nurse's Office
Is Kanade going to be okay?
It's quite a deep wound...
She's the same as us.
Even fatal injuries will heal up.
How could there be two of her?
Has this world become even more messed up?
There's a reason.
What is it?
Do you remember the Angel Area Invasion mission?
Yeah...
We found some skill development software on her computer right?
There were a number of powers we'd never seen listed there.
There was one skill called "Harmonics". She activated it.
Harmonics...
What kind of power is that?
Weren't you looking at the screen?
It's a skill that splits her into two.
Basically, a clone.
A clone?
In other words, this skill is something Angel developed herself using that software?
But the other one didn't feel like she was quite the same.
She was way more aggressive than this Angel.
Why?
Kanade wouldn't use a skill for any reason other than to protect herself.
Even when she used her blade, it was just to ricochet our shots.
Seriously, you people are one useless bunch.
With the exception of Otonashi-san, of course!
We're supposed to be a bunch of idiots!
Consider this possibility.
Suppose that when she created that clone, she had a strong offensive intent in mind.
Back then?
I see...
So the clone is continuing to obey the original's command from back then, even now?
But Kanade herself wouldn't go on an all-out assault like that...
Not that it matters, but you seem pretty determined to defend her.
Well...
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Well, whatever.
So, what exactly are we discussing?
A way to fight Angel's clone?
Idiot.
We have to make it disappear.
What did you say?!
But if she voluntarily created the clone, she should be able to erase it voluntarily too.
Can't we just wait for Kanade to wake up?
Wait, if she could voluntarily erase it, would she be lying here like this now?
It was most likely an unconscious command.
That's why she can't erase her.
She had to do something, even if it meant getting stabbed herself.
Hey, wait a second!
If she won't disappear, will this world be stuck with that monster?
She's ignoring us now, but she probably won't let us off the hook tomorrow.
If we don't act like the model students, it'll probably turn into another bloodbath like last night.
Even through she isn't the student council president anymore?
Yes.
The directive to correct our actions has been embedded deep into her.
On top of that, she's aggressive.
This is bad.
Even if we were to try taking her on, there wouldn't be enough time.
I need some time.
How can we buy you time?
Go to class and pretend you're paying attention.
Don't listen to anything the teacher says.
If you take the lesson seriously, you'll disappear.
Concentrate on doing something else, just don't get caught by the clone.
Hold out for one day.
I pray we can all meet up afterwards without losing anyone.
I already know she splits in two!
Girls Dormitories - Angel Area
I need some way to get rid of the other one...
Angel Player?
Looks like a software manual...
Damn!
It's such a thick book, and all in English!
I don't have the time for this!
Let's see...
The number went up...
So this is distance?
Don't care.
What's this?
Yes! This is it!
Originally, the clone was supposed to obey this order and vanish.
So, what do you have to do to activate this?
I don't get it...
How about I just break the computer?
Am I stupid?
That won't make the clone vanish!
Whatever!
I'll just rewrite it into a program I do understand!
Hurry up and disappear!
Delay - 10 seconds!
How's that?
10 seconds feels a long time when you're waiting.
Why wasn't I able to make it less than 10 seconds?
Alright, that should be good.
What's this?
There's more of them?
Howling?
Did the clone make this?
Should I delete it?
No, I've been careful so far.
I should keep alterations to a minimum.
That should be good.
Now Angel just needs to use Harmonics, and the Absorb skill will activate and re-merge the clone.
We screwed up...
Maybe she just went out somewhere?
No way.
Kanade promised she'd stay with us!
She promised that?
Yeah...
Judging by this mess, we can only assume she was kidnapped.
You! What did you do?
What do you mean by that?
I just rewrote a program.
If she uses her power again, the ability I added in will activate,
and the clone will re-merge with her.
You were able to do that?
It was just a quick patch though...
But the enemy moved faster than I expected.
If the clone hides her, there's nothing we can do.
So what now?
We have to look for her.
While avoiding Angel's brutal gaze?
It took all of our effort just to pretend to take lessons.
I guess it'll come down to how long the diversion lasts.
By diversion, you mean me?
Why did you join GirlDeMo in the first place?
Because I admire Iwasawa-san?
GirlDeMo is supposed to be a diversion!
No way, I can't keep such a scary enemy distracted!
Do it!
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'm your senior! I should be the one getting mad!
My senior? Well sorry then!
I might wet myself during the performance, but I'll do it!
I appreciate the determination, but I don't need you to yet.
Let's do what we can for now.
This is a battlefront-wide order:
Collect witness reports of Angel!
Hey, yo, check this out!
It's moonwalk, it's a moonwalk!
Head spin!
Gym interior
From the information we managed to gather, there's a good chance she's being held captive in Guild.
And if that's the case, it'll be in the deepest area.
In the area we detonated?
Right.
The traps are still set.
It's the most dangerous, farthest location from here.
We've got to go down there again?
Last time we pretty much got wiped out.
What, you scared?
You're the first person who died.
I'll keep singing even if I pee myself, for everyone's sake!
I'll be brave!
If that monster strikes, the diversionary squad will be wiped out instantly.
We'll go without a diversion this time.
We're going in openly.
While fighting Angel?
Right.
Listen up.
The plan is to descend into Guild and recapture the original Angel.
Operation...
Start!
Good to see the traps we fell for last time are still inactive.
Guild Accessway B4
Lucky!
Um... If we run into Angel here, I might wet myself...
I don't care.
Care, damn you!
So she's appeared.
Fire!
Damn, she's fast!
We still have handguns!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Get her before she recovers!
It looks like we'll get this done faster than planned.
What...
What the hell?
Is that the original?
No, she's also a clone!
Why is there more than one?
It would appear the enemy is growing in number.
As a side note, that guy got done in first again.
Dammit!
Fire!
What about the one behind us?
No time for that!
Deal with the enemy in front of us!
You seem busy.
Yurippe!
We're low on ammo!
We can't win this.
I'll cover the entrance!
Take up my rear!
Let's go!
Yuri!
Ten seconds!
Anyone who doesn't make it gets left behind!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
We've got two brutal Angels now.
Guild Accessway B5
This is worse than the last Operation Descent.
Why are there two?
The clones can use Hand Sonic and Distortion.
In other words, they can use Harmonics too.
Seriously, you're all imbeciles.
With the exception of Otonashi-san, of course!
Let me tell you our current problems.
Please.
We have two problems:
First, how many clones are there?
If a clone can make a clone, there is no upper bound on the number.
Then besides those two, there might be another ten, twenty, or more?
Wait, but Yuri changed the program.
The clones should go back, shouldn't they?
Can't we just wait for them to disappear?
That's the second problem.
If they cloned themselves before the program was changed...
Then...
Ignorant fools. You've finally realized?
Of course, you're grand nobility, Otonashi-san.
Now, if she knew we'd come after her and started making clones,
then came down here to lure us in...
Then...
Trap.
Right, a trap.
There are already two behind us.
They won't disappear.
You can't win against them.
And there are probably countless below.
So we're sealed in.
And we can't replenish our ammunition.
So we're just waiting to be taken out?
What does she plan to do with us?
When it comes down to it, she wants us to obey the rules.
That's her mission.
She just wants us to disappear?
A perfect plan to get rid of us.
Let's go.
And here's another.
Guild Accessway B10
A third one?
It's a waste of ammo.
What are you going to do?
Matsushita 5th Dan!
Go! Go while I'm still alive!
What's with that line, acting like some cool guy on the brink of death?!
Hurry!
Let's go while we can!
Hold on, Matsushita 5th Dan!
I'll leave the rest to you...
Everyone...
We won't let Matsushita-kun's sacrifice go to waste.
Guild Accessway B11
Thanks to him, we know that that's the best way to move forward.
Angel is small, so that's the best way to stop her from moving.
Even if she's stupidly strong, a Judo pin will hold her down.
It looks like we can finally use what he taught us.
In other words, for each clone, one of us will be sacrificed and the rest will move on.
Sacrifice one and move on?
And if we can save the original, we can save everyone.
Let's hurry.
A fourth clone!
Guild Accessway B12
It's my turn.
Get chance and luck!
TK!
What's with this last-chapter-of-a-shonen-manga scenario?!
Doesn't matter. Let's go!
It appears the time has come to show this body.
Takamatsu!!
Like I'm gonna let myself get scared here!
Fujimaki!!
So shallow...
So shallow!
Shiina!!
Now, you will realize...
You are a clown.
Look, in that dark corner, a lonely girl is calling out to you.
It's true, that won't do!
Let me make you laugh—
Oyama!!
You're horrible...
No that's not what I meant!
He just misunderstood me!
Here, I'll go next!
Hey, someone say something...
I don't know his name...
Let's go.
Guild Accessway B15
How many is this now?
I don't know anymore.
I'm not even counting.
I'll go this time.
Wait, it's my turn.
You need to survive to the end.
Why?
That girl's waiting for you.
At least, that's the feeling I get.
So you need to carry on.
Got it?
And if—
If you're going to go, hurry up and go!!
I'll follow soon, senpai!
I don't get it, do you like him or hate him?
We're here.
This is where Guild was before we blew it up.
Guild lowest point - Ground Zero
We're going to descend straight to the lowest level.
Otonashi-kun and Yui, you look for the original.
When you find her, get her to activate Harmonics.
I should fight as well.
Hinata-kun already told you right?
She's waiting for you.
Then I'll fight.
You're too weak to be of any use.
Let me try!
Let's go then.
No, I'm really strong!
I only hope this is our last operation.
Yeah...
Wait for me!
Huh? Where did Yui go?
I heard a scream for a second...
Angel got her, huh...
Such a pity.
We'll save her soon though.
We're the only two survivors again...
Yeah...
Same as last time.
It's about time for the last one.
I hope so.
Go on, stop standing around and find the original.
Okay.
I thought so.
Damn, she's tough.
Cover your ears!
Guard Skill:
Howling.
What the hell is this?!
My ears...
You didn't pass out...
Eh? What?
What did you say?
I can't hear you through my earplugs.
Just give it up.
My next knife here's going to take care of your throat.
There she is!
Kanade!!
Kanade!
Are you okay?
Everyone in the Battlefront came here and gave their lives to find you!
Really?
Yes!
Kanade, I'm sorry to push you, but I need you to use one of your powers.
If you can use Harmonics again, everyone will be saved.
I see. Alright.
Will your body hold out if you use it again?
Once should be okay.
Guard Skill: Harmonics.
It seems you altered my program.
Yeah, all of you are going to return to her.
That many of us ruthless clones are going to return?
What do you mean?
Even as clones, we have our own consciousness.
Those won't disappear.
They'll be incorporated into her.
The spirits of all the clones you attacked will return to her.
When she takes in all those at once...
she'll pay for it.
It's time.
Wait!!
Dammit!!
Please be okay!
Kanade!!
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつも一人で歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返ると　皆は遠く
When I turn around, everyone's far behind
sore demo atashi wa aruita
それでも あたしは歩いた
Even so, I kept walking
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That was what strength was
mou nani mo kowakunai
もう何も怖くない
"I'm not afraid of anything anymore",
sou tsubuyaitemiseru
そう呟いてみせる
I try to whisper to myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Everyone becomes alone someday
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They live on only in memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru you ni
孤独さえ　愛し笑ってられるように
So I can laugh with my heart, even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakaunda
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenainda
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will show no tears
What's going to happen to us?
It's the first time that's happened to Angel.
There's no choice but to bear through it once.
Are you trying to undress me?
No one's coming to save her!
The hell?
The possibility is about 1%.
Go back!
We'll definitely save her!
Someone hit her!
Am I going to disappear?
Whose side is God on?
Otonashi...
I remember everything.