() Are notes/information for the timer/editor.
(A quick note, Kushieda talks in a real happy/hyper way so I’m having her talk that way in English as well xD)
I'm sleepy…
Sheesh.
Come to think of it, didn't you leave your skirt in the laundry basket without taking the tissues out of the pocket?
It was a real hassle you know.
Also, don't forget to separate colored ones.
The darker ones should be in the orange bask--
Ah, ah, just shut up!
You're too detailed with every little thing!
If you're a man you should just--
Give one shot to 'em!
Yay, yay, yay.
Give one shot.
Yay.
Give one shot to 'em!
Yay, yay, yay.
Don't mind.
Alright!
It looks like I'm up next.
Fight, captain!
Oh well, well.
Thank you for the cheers everyone.
Kushieda…
Alrighty. Bring it on from wherever you want.
That refreshing smile.
Alright!
Kushieda...
That sweat that sparkles brightly.
I got first base. Yay!
I got second base. Yay!
Go around three bases and home run!
Her singing voice that's out of tune.
Home-in!
Oh, Kushieda. This morning you were also...
Your stare is perverted, you creepy dog.
Kushieda, about the male-female team joint practice on the weekend...
Oh, Kitamura-kun. I was just about to--
Hey! You understand, you stupid dog?!
Ugh! Stop it already!
Hey! Wait!
She can run pretty well, considering that she's not in any athletic club.
Taiga!
Being healthy comes first right?
TL Note: DecoDen is short for Decoration Denwa; denwa means phone
DecoDen huh?
Minorin, you have pretty dexterous hands don't you?
Heh, heh, of course.
I may look this way, but my hands are pretty dexterous.
Kushieda, what are you doing?
Alright! Here's one up!
Alrighty, next up is...
Why are you making a noise as if you're being strangled to death?
Oh, it's just--
I know!
Should I make you one too, Takasu-kun?
I’m a DecoDen craftsman at my part-time job.
Cra-Craftsman?
I’ll go ahead and put in “Ryuuji” with a purple swallow.
Kushieda's doing this for me?
No! Uh... I--
Kushieda. Can you do ours too?
Oh my! Looks like I got some orders.
Then go ahead and right your name, the color you want and the image on this sheet.
Um, I want pink with a big heart.
I want it to be totally lovely!
So she has a part-time job as a DecoDen Craftsman huh?
That sparkling Kushieda with sparkling DecoDen.
Isn't it a real intensive combination?
Hey, wasn't it because of Ya-chan's companion job she's not going to be here tonight?
If that's the case, you can leave that part of the meal to--
--and she even said "Ryuuji".
So she remembers my first name too.
It's probably just because I always call you by it.
More importantly, the dishes for Ya-chan--
Oh man. We talked a whole bunch!
Hey Taiga, I was able to talk without acting nervo--us?
Huh?
Listen to people when they’re talking to you!
I'll just tell you while I'm at it but--
You were totally nervous back then!
So, is dinner ready yet?
That freaking hurts!
It's almost ready, sheesh.
Today is a bowl meal so as long there's some rice, I can quickly--
What the heck?!
What's wrong?
The rice cooker... It's broken...
Welcome and good evening.
What should I eat~
We didn't have to come to family restaurant for this.
There wasn't any rice, but we did have bread.
Howl all you want while you still can mutt.
You'll end up bowing down to me with gratitude.
Alrighty! Two up front!
What, we haven't ordered anything ye--
It's a secret but, this is a "Taiga Special" chucked full of ice-cream.
Make sure you hide it from the other customers while you eat.
Thanks as always, Minorin!
As always?
Oh, are you bad with sweets Takasu-kun?
If that's the case, you want some fried potatoes?
I'll give you lots! I'll give you lots!
Um... I-uh--
Minorin also has part-time jobs at a convenience store and a karaoke place.
I certainly do!
I've also been working at a Shabu-shabu restaurant since last week!
That many?!
I'm still saving one more you know.
I can’t take a single day off as the captain of the female baseball team!
Is there something you want that would make you work so hard for?
I have time, I should labor.
TL Note: Kushieda has awkward speech patterns, hence the awkward translation
Labor?
Right, the labor revolution file!
Huh?
It’s the resurrection of labor.
You two certainly get along well don’t you?
Miss, an Ohiya please.
Well, take your time.
You know...
My vision has definitely degraded from today.
A mere mutt, drooling over Minorin's waitress clothes.
I just...
I just thought that her smile was sparkling so brightly.
The eyes! Not the eyes!
If I do it anymore, my fingers will get tainted.
Damn it.
But I wonder why she's working so many part-time jobs?
Didn't she say it was the "Labor Revolution File"?
Maybe she has a reason that she needs money.
Like something at her house.
Maybe she's helping her sick mother.
She said "labor".
But still...
You should get rid of assumptions like that.
"I'm the only one that can understand the real her," that sort of thing.
It just increases your creepiness.
Uh, I can't stand it.
You can walk farther away from me.
You're creeping me out.
Hey! Taiga! Why'd you say it like that? That's so cold!
I told you to stay away from me!
Was I ever NOT cold to you?!
Now that you mention it... you're right.
Here you go Inko-chan, thanks for the wait.
It's your dinner.
I'll give you lots! I'll give you lots!
Poop! Poop!
Wow, you're gonna go Inko-chan?
You’re gonna do it right?
Poop! Poop!
Poop!
The mornings on the weekends are so refreshing.
Right, Taiga?
I knew I shouldn't have told you.
Did you say something?
You abandoned the food preparations and decided to go to the family restaurant to meet Minorin.
Oh come on. It can't be helped since the rice cooker is still broken.
Shouldn't you be going to an electronics store first then?
Plus, you said that you don't like bread.
If it's just breakfast, then bread is fine.
Sheesh, getting all high-spirited.
Those clothes don't suit you either.
Oh, I just remember that I left something.
Ugh, you're such a bother.
For life's sake, let me go!
Whatever you wear, it's not going to change anything anyway.
Hey, Nii-chan.
You're Mirano-chan's son aren't you?
Oh, Inage Ojisan.
Mirano?
Yeah, it's Yasuko's other name--
over at work.
Hi!
It's straight out 200 meters, out from Kitamichi-kaisatsu.
I'm Mirano-chan of Bishamon Heaven.
How old do I look? Twenty-three? You got it!
I guess I have good luck from early in the day.
I'm gonna touch Mirano-chan's DNA
That's pretty nice. It's quite tight. Isn't it great to be young?
Should we go?
This old man kind of pisses me off...
Hey, you two there!
If you haven't had your breakfast yet then I recommend this Gyoni-saka; full of calcium, potassium and hydrochloric acid.
Right.
Huh?
Kushieda--
Minorin?
Here, carry these!
Wha-why--?
There!
One more!
It's better if I carried it.
No, don’t worry about her.
Mirano-chan's son, just go ahead and sip some tea.
Why is it... that I have to do... something like this?!
It's only on days off but I've asked her to work part-time.
Kushieda, you better work hard!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
I've been pretty busy lately.
I just don't have enough people...
Enough people?
I know. Ojou-chan.
Would you like to try working here, since you're friends with Kushieda?
I'll pay you well.
Yes!
I'll do it.
With her.
Like hell I'll do this!
Hey, don't cause any problems. You're going to trouble Kushieda.
Then you should help her by yourself!
Little one, I need you to deliver something.
Just three of those beer cases.
"Right, gladly!"
Alrighty, all set.
Be careful.
What’s wrong, Taiga?
You...
Don't tell me that you can't ride a bicyc--
SHUT UUUUUUP!
So what if I can't ride a bike?!
It should be fine as long as I can carry it!
You've got it wrong! That's wrong!
Woah, Taiga's spouting off!
Dreadful, isn't it?
Well, if she's pushing it, she's safe--I guess.
Oh yeah, I gotta restock the shouchuu.
M-Me too.
I’ll help too.
I would feel bad if I didn't do anything at all.
Then I suppose I'll leave it to you.
R-Right!
Hmm... The potato-Shouchuu is...
It's hard to see since it's so dim.
Yeah. This place isn't used very often.
It's only opened about once a week.
Oh?
We'd be in a lot of trouble if we got trapped in here!
It would simply be like being stranded somewhere.
That little one, she left it wide-open.
Hey! There’re still people in here!
S.O.S! S.O.S!
You have to calm down Takasu-kun!
Kushieda?
It's times like these that are effective.
Huh? Effective?
This is so stupid.
There shouldn't be any reason for me to be working so hard.
Like I can keep it up, sheesh.
Keep what up?
Ki-Kitamura-kun.
Wha-Why are you h-h-h-h-here?
I was just in the middle of self-training.
By the way, is that yours Aisaka?
Huh? Uh... y-yeah.
Well, I suppose so.
Wow. So you learned how to ride a bicycle?
That's quite an eye-opening development.
No, it's not riding, it's more like...
How did you know that I couldn't ride a bicycle?
Oh. I was observing you pretty well last year.
Aren't bicycles great? They open up the world for you.
Well then, Aisaka. See you again tomorrow.
Last year...
He...
Damn it!
Ouch…
A world that Kitamura-kun won't look at...
It’s pointless for it to open up!
Two, Three--
Hey, you're awfully late--
What happened to your clothes--?
It's nothing.
More importantly, what happened to the other two?
Oh yeah, now that you mention it.
Where has that Kushieda run off to?
Ryuuji-kun isn't a problem, but...
While I was out working hard... That MUTT got his sly hands on her!
What are you talking about? Anyway, next I want you to go to the third-block--
Ryuuji! What the hell are you doing?!
Ah, ah! To the future!
The bridge connects!
That is! That is! The bridge!
Ah, my throat's all dried up now.
I can't believe they didn't notice even though we've been so loud.
Oh, he’s usually fixated on the horse races around this time.
Is that so?
It's starting to get a little cold isn't it?
Oh, if you'd like you can use my jacke--
Alrighty... Time to get warmed up!
Huh?
The pitcher's scared. Hey, hey, hey.
Scared...? But aren't you the pitcher, Kushieda?
Scared. Hey! Scared. Hey!
The pitcher's scared. Hey, hey, hey.
Could it be that--
Scared.
You’re actually scared?
Your hands are shaking.
Oh, of course not. I'm just shaking from excitement--excitement.
Alrighty. Here I come!
Right.
Strike!
'kay, switch!
Time to swap players.
Right. Yeah.
I mean... Isn't it pointless to be scared?
So... Just blow away your weak feelings!
Kushieda.
Could it be that--
Huh?
Hey Takasu-kun. Can't we get out from there?
Where?! Where?! Where?! Where?! Where?! Where?!
Where are they?!
See, Takasu-kun!
Over there!
It might be that--
The reason Kushieda always seems to shine isn't only because--
She's high-spirited or full of energy.
W-Watch out!
Kushieda! I'm sorry! Are you okay?
Woah! Y-You got a nosebleed!
It's a disaster that makes no difference.
A disaster?
Nosebleeds are your heart's sweat.
Come on, we're almost there.
Pile 'em! You have to pile them Takasu!
Y-Yeah!
That's it. Just blow away your weak feelings huh?
Alright! We'll definitely come back alive!
Right, of course! Fight!
Huh?
Come on, when I say "fight"...
O-One-shot?
Right-right, here it comes!
Fight!
One-shot!
That's right. Kushieda was sparkling from the very start. Even when we first met.
Fight!
Even now...
One-shot!
She's sparkling.
Huh?
I fou-nd-you!
Taiga! How did you get here?!
How? I used a ladder.
Alright! Takasu-kun! Now we can get out outside!
Oh-but--
Thank you Taiga! This is "that" bridge to the future!
Um, Minori...
Come on! Takasu-kun! Hurry and wake up!
Um, I'm telling you...
I just dropped the ladder earlier...
I’ve closed it deep within my heart.
The memory of just the two of us that I can't tell anyone.
Oh, I already told Takasu.
K-Ki-KI-TA-MU—