Mezamete wa kurikaesu nemui asa wa
目覚めては繰り返す　眠い朝は
I wake once again to a sleepy morning
Eri no tai wo kitsuku shime
襟のタイをきつく締め
And carefully fasten my necktie
Kyoushitsu no doa kuguru to honno sukoshi
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
As I pass the door to the classroom
Mune wo hatte arukidaseru
胸を張って歩き出せる
I walk with my chest held just a little high
Sonna nichijou ni fukinukeru kaze
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
The wind blows through the days spent just like this
Kikoeta ki ga shita
聞こえた気がした
I thought that I heard it
Kanjita ki ga shita n da
感じた気がしたんだ
I thought that I felt it
Furuedasu ima kono mune de
震え出す今この胸で
Now, with these hands that tremble
Mou kuru ki ga shita
もう来る気がした
I felt it would happen soon
Ikuoku no hoshi ga kiesatteku no wo
幾億の星が消え去ってくのを
I watched the millions of stars as they disappeared
Miokutta te wo futta
見送った手を振った
And waved them goodbye
Yokatta ne, to
よかったね、と
So happy for them
It's time.
I'd better get to the meeting place.
Hmm... who should I go for next?
Study Building Courtyard
Maybe I'll ask for Kanade's opinion.
Yo.
Whoa, Hinata!
Otonashi-san.
Naoi?!
Hey, what are you doing here?!
I should ask you the same!  Where'd you come from?!
Um, so, did you two need something?
Oh that's right!  Where were you planning to go, Otonashi?
Oh that's right! Where are you going, Otonashi-san?
He can go where he wants!
It's got nothing to do with you!
I've got business with Otonashi!
I want to help with what he's doing!
Hmph.  That's my job.  You're just a nuisance.
Just disappear!
Yes, look into my eyes.
You're toilet paper.
Toilet paper that's about to be flushed away... realiz-
Hey!  Cut that out!
H-Hey, Hinata!
I'll assist you.
Wait, you two... you know what I'm trying to do?
Yeah, I know.
Of course I understand.
You're trying to erase everybody, one by one, right?
The way you say it makes it sound terrible.
Besides, Naoi...
You shouldn't have any regrets left, right?
I want to be with you!
Besides, I don't wanna disappear before him.
That's a lousy reason to stay.
Then what should I do?
Disappear.
I wasn't asking you.
Come on, Otonashi-san.  You need a partner, right?
Please make use of me, Otonashi-san.
What's wrong?
What's that?
Did you do something again?
What are you talking about?
I haven't done any-
What is that?!
An enemy?  Should I shoot it?
It's coming in.
Something's coming in!
Otonashi-san!
Damn it!
Hinata!
Can this thing even die?!
Did we get it?
What was that?
Hinata-san, Otonashi-san, second one intercepted.
Complete victory.
All unharmed.
The second appearance, huh?
Anti-Angel Operations Headquarters
The most natural conclusion is that Tenshi has made a new skill, but...
It doesn't quite fit, right?
Right.
Relay this to all SSS members.
From now on, solitary action is prohibited.
At the minimum, actions must be taken with two people.
We'll deal with the shadow as if it's a separate power than Tenshi.
Exercise the utmost vigilance.
Roger.
What about you, Yurippe-san?
Yurippe-san will try to investigate any conceivable possibilities.
Student Council President Tachibana Kanade-san.
Incinerator
Please report to the Student Council Room immediately.
Hey, that's Yurippe's voice.
What's going on?
I repeat.
Student Council President Tachibana Kanade-san.
Uh-oh, what we're trying to do might get found out.
Please report to the Student Council Room immediately.
That would be bad.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Student Council
Room
What do you guys want?
Student Council Room
We wanna hear what's going on.
I, the former replacement Student Council President...
And current Vice-President have approved it.
What makes this your jurisdiction?
Because it's the Student Council Room.
Okay, fine.
So, what do you know?
The shadow, the shadow.
I know nothing.
You didn't program it?
No.
Could it be a bug?
When did you last do any programming?
The day before yesterday.
Timing-wise, that's exactly right.
I'm going to enter your room.  Is that alright?
Takeyama-kun, I'm counting on you.
Roger.
Also, call me Chri-
So?  What kind of program was it?
Wings.
Wings?  You made wings?
Don't tell me so you can fly...
No. For decoration.
What?  Decoration?
Yes.  Decoration.
Why?
Because I was told that would be more like an Angel.
Told?
Who told you that?
Oh, crap.
That was me.
I thought it might increase her prestige as Student Council President.
I, the former replacement Student Council President...
And current Vice-President proposed it.
If the Student Council President had wings, it would increase her prestige?
Correct.
For the Student Council President.
Wings.
Would be appropriate, I felt.
What an idiot.
Still, you're more obedient than I'd have expected.
I can't sense even an atom of your former coldheartedness.
It's like you reverted to your previous self.
No, she's cold hearted, alright.
She stabs me, her Vice-President, every day.
Huh?  Why?
When she's annoyed by something, she just stabs whatever is close by.
As Vice-President, I'm usually the closest thing near her.
Just this morning, she stabbed me and my bowels were lying all over the place for a while.
She appears to be in rather a good mood right now though...
What an idiot.
Can you hear me?
Please respond.
Takeyama-kun, right?
How'd it go?
Girl's Dorm - Tenshi-area
I was unable to find any bugs.
This latest program was mostly ornamental, so it was relatively simple.
It would be even stranger to find a bug in such a program.
Also, please call me Chri-
What about the other programs?
In passive, Overdrive.
In active, Hand Sonic.
The same programs as before.
Although the appearance is different...
What should I do now?
Is she going to tell him to erase it all?
Is Kanade going to have to make them all from scratch again?
Huh?  Did you hear a gunshot just now?
Huh?
What are you talking about?  There wasn't a gunshot.
It's outside!
Look!  Over there!
Those monsters!
What's going on?  There're so many.
Kanade, please!
Yurippe!
Amazing.
I'm going, too!
Hey!
Otonashi-san!
TK explode!
Are you okay, Yuri?
Otonashi-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
How ill-mannered.
Hmph.  I don't need reinforcements!
Aww, don't be like that.
How foolish.
Whoa~ Dancing in the shadow.
I kiss you.
Wow... I wouldn't want to eat that.
Hey!  Don't cut your ally!
All part of the plan.
Leave that part out next time!
Stop messing around and cover each other!
What the...
Everyone, are you alright?
What were those guys?  Monsters?
Those ghostly things have never been in this world before.
Is this a nightmare?
A carnival, and we're all invited.
Maybe we've been in this world for too long.
What do you mean?
You see it in games a lot.
Invincible monsters designed to keep you from playing forever.
It's hard to laugh at.
Still...
It's almost like she's our ally now.
Hey!  Hey!
Fujimaki?
This is bad.
Takamatsu was...
Takamatsu was done in!
UTW Presents:
His glasses.
Study Building - Breezeway
I... saw it.
That shadow ate him.
Ate him?
When I came across him...
his whole body was covered in shadow.
I tried to help!
But, I couldn't do anything...
In the end, even his glasses came off.
For him to lose his glasses is unthinkable.
And?
The ground... it swallowed him up.
The ground?
This is way too irregular.
What is this?
A will completely different than we expected has started to work.
What in the world is going on?
Hey~
I found Takamatsu!
Takamatsu-kun!
Takamatsu!
What are you doing?
Study Building A - Classroom
We've all been so worried!
Worried?
About what?
About what?!
You were eaten by a shadow-monster!
I don't understand a word you're saying.
You didn't notice?
You were eaten by a shadow.
And then, swallowed up by the ground.
What happened after that?
Nothing happened.
Just like usual, I woke up in the dorm and came to school.
Came to school?!
You changed into that uniform and came here to take classes?!
Yeah, I suppose.
You'll disappear!
Don't you understand that?
Disappear?
What will disappear?
He's in trouble.
He's acting strange.
I mean, he was always strange, but...
Takamatsu...
You've done enough, Hinata-kun.
What do you mean enough?
Excuse me, but you're interfering with class.
Let's go.
Is it okay to leave him alone?
He'll disappear!
It's fine.
Ooyama-kun!
That conversation just now was more than enough.
Study Building A - Stairs
I understand what's going on.
He's...
... become an NPC.
Wha... wait a minute.  What do you mean?
I don't get it at all.
If he's an NPC, you mean he lost his soul?
Then where did his soul go?!
It was eaten.
What's that supposed to mean?!
What?
Without disappearing, he's gonna just keep going to classes here for eternity?
That's what it looks like is gonna happen.
No way.
That's worse than dying.
For eternity?
Trapped here for eternity?
What's with that?!
Damn it!
It's too cruel.
So things like this are possible in this world, too?
If that's how it works, isn't getting erased by Tenshi the better alternative?
More importantly, the shadows are multiplying.
Hey, what do we do?  Yurippe!
Gymnasium
Irregularities have begun to occur in this world.
The appearance of an enemy other than Tenshi.
It's pretty simplistic, but we're calling it Kage.
TL Note: Kage means "shadow".
It's more elusive than Tenshi...
and has been attacking us indiscriminately.
Those who are eaten by one lose their soul,
and turn into NPCs, going to class every day.
Currently, its numbers are increasing limitlessly.
Its origin is unknown.
We have no countermeasures against it.
As Yusa-san informed you all previously, all we can do right now is watch over each other by moving in groups.
Now, then...
On the verge of this crisis...
a group has appeared within the SSS that has a different ideology.
Planning to revise and lead the Warfront down a different path.
That path is...
... one option to avoid the crisis currently facing us.
Therefore, as the representative of this faction...
Otonashi-kun.
Will you please fairly outline your viewpoint for us?
We've been found out, huh?
Go on.
Don't screw around with us.
Just give it up already!
A convenient solution like that doesn't exist!
That's right.
Like this world would allow it!
It exists!
Yui found it.
Even for someone like me, who died no better than a piece of trash...
In this world, I was able to grant it to her.
Me, too.
I may be God, but...
Even so...
Otonashi-san was the one who...
... returned my human heart to me.
He returned it with his words.
With his words of appreciation.
Whatever path you choose, I'll leave up to you all.
What about you, Yurippe?
What will you do, Yurippe?
Me?
I've always just done whatever I want.
I'm not looking to protect you all.
I'm just gonna do what I want.
We don't have much time.
Everyone think well on this.
That's all.
Dismissed.
Do you have a moment?
What is it, Yuri?
Put her to work on a counter-attack against Kage.
Kanade?  Why?
She's more cut out for battling on instinct, rather than fighting with her head.
At least, as far as I've seen.
You've been watching?
Well... it's impossible to deceive Yurippe, after all.
But, Kanade is our ally.
We should stay together.
The other members are your allies too, right?
We need her power to protect them.
The power she's fought the SSS with until now.
That overwhelming power.
You have a point.
An Angel is suitable for fighting that thing.
She's not actually an Angel, you know.
Huh?!  What did you just say?!
That girl isn't an Angel.
She's a human, just like us.
You didn't notice?
As God, I saw through her all along.
There's something seriously wrong with you.
Really?  You're not an Angel?
I'm not an Angel.
I thought I told you that when we first met.
They were saying you're an Angel or something.
I'm not an Angel.
Gah!  It's true!
A whole lot's happened since then, huh?
It's you people's fault!
So then, why is Kanade here?
She's been the Student Council President so long.
Why hasn't she disappeared?
I'm sure she has her own reasons.
That's right.
Then... you're holding some burden just like us?
We'll have to resolve that, too.
Right?
So, Yuri?
What will you do?
There's something I want to confirm.
Are you going to fight Kage?
That depends.
It's too dangerous alone.
I don't have a choice.
I told everyone else they were free to choose their path.
There's people that will stay with you.
They still need time to think.
It's an important choice.
That's... true, but...
If when I return...
everyone has disappeared, and safely departed this world...
I'll assume it was thanks to you.
No way.
I'll wait for you!
Don't be silly.
If you wait by yourself, Kage will get you.
Before that happens, hurry up and get out of here.
Out of this world.
Don't worry about me.
No, we'll worry.
Hinata-kun?
What are you trying to say all of a sudden?
Didn't we form this Warfront starting with just the two of us?
We've spent a long time together, haven't we?
That's why we'll be together in the end, too.
I can't just leave you.
You're the same fool as always.
Nothing will be solved with sentimental arguments.
Enemy attack!
It's an enemy attack!
Kanade-chan, I'm counting on you.
Hand Sonic: Version 5.
Then, let's meet again if we can.
Yurippe!
What a ridiculous nickname.
But maybe that's why everyone followed me.
Thank you.
itsumo hitori de aruiteta
いつもひとりで歩いてた
I've always walked alone
furikaeru to minna wa tooku
振り返るとみんなは遠く
When I turned around, everyone was far away
soredemo atashi wa aruita
それでもあたしは歩いた
Even so, I walked on
sore ga tsuyosa datta
それが強さだった
That's what it was to be strong
mou nanimo kowaku nai
もう何も恐くない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
sou tsubuyaite miseru
そう呟いてみせる
That's what I try to tell myself
itsuka hito wa hitori ni natte
いつか人は一人になって
Eventually, everyone will be alone
omoide no naka ni ikiteku dake
思い出の中に生きてくだけ
They'll continue to live only through their memories
kodoku sae aishi waratterareru youni
孤独さえ愛し笑ってられるように
So I can love and laugh even in this loneliness
atashi wa tatakau n da
あたしは戦うんだ
I will fight
namida nante misenai n da
涙なんて見せないんだ
I will never show you my tears
Alright, I guess I'll end here.
Christ of the Front Diary
Today was good weather again.
It seems I've stayed in this world a little too long.
I've had a change of heart.
I repeat.
Today was good weather again.
I wonder if I'll be seeing even clearer skies tomorrow.
That transformation.
If it's possible for NPCs to be reprogrammed, just like that girl does to herself...
Using that software to transform the NPCs, and attack us...
Somebody is playing God somewhere in this world.
There has to be a lot of computers wherever they are.
If that's the case, I can only think of one place.
Library
PC  Room 1
PC Room 1
Inside the Library, PC Room 1
Checkmate.
Raise your hands.
What are you talking about, checkmate?
You play chess?
This man is the culprit?
In this age of computers, people still play that kind of game?
You have some excellent hobbies for a young person.
Wait!
Hmm?  Me?
What were you doing?
Here?
Yes.
Just setting up some new computers.
For what purpose?
They're good models, so they often get stolen.
When we're running low, I replace them.
What's the culprit's goal?
Right now I don't know.
Is that enough?
Thank you.
My apologies for stopping you.
There's no question about it.
Whoever is stealing those computers is acting as the God of this world.
He's using the PCs to interfere with the NPCs.
But how do I catch him?
I don't have time to work at this leisurely.
The Kage are multiplying, even now.
They're being stolen, but these aren't exactly easy to just carry off...
Does the culprit sneak in at night, and load them onto a cart, or something?
Or maybe through the window?
Found it.
Wait...
No way.
Not the Guild again!
UTW Staff
Translator:
Ershin
Timer/Editor:
Nikon
TS/Karaoke:
ar
TLC/QC:
Raze
Next Episode Preview
[c 68] Let's break through!
[c 54] Knockin' on heaven's door
[c 59] What with this world?
[c 48] I wonder if even God will be astonished!
[c 94] Is the fighting going to end?
PLACEHOLDER
[c 51] It seems like nobody would notice if I disappeared at this point!
[c 116] Disappear!
PLACEHOLDER
[c 7] Wretchedly disappear like toilet paper!
[c 44] I only move when I can be of use to Yurippe!
[c 81] Think of it as though you're now 100 men stronger.
[c 26] We'll form a band next time around, too.
[c 217] Well done making it this far.
[c 174] Give me your hand!
[c 157] If I disappear from here... I wonder if I can try it all again.