kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
Up you go.
It's already autumn, huh?
A Passing Typhoon
Perceived and Actuality
Huh? Then Kureha-chan's dad was a tank commander?
Right!
After achieving a total victory at Waldenburg,
he freed over a thousand townsfolk and soldiers, and with only six allied Mille-Pattes on his side!
He was the hero of a legendary evacuation!
Amazing...
Isn't it?
And then my father was injured in the line of duty and met an orderly at the hospital he was sent to...
who would eventually become my mother!
And, the one born from that union...
...would be Kureha-chan.
Right!
Wait, am I a potato?!
Oh my! What fine potatoes we have here.
All thanks to Kana-chan, who worked so hard.
With this much, we should be able to share some with the people of this town.
And after that, Klaus-san is supposed to arrive.
Shall we give him a gift?
He's coming?
Kureha-chan, you really like Klaus-san, don't you?
Uh, i-it's not that I like him or anything... I just respect him.
Rio-senpai...
So she can play like this?
That's Rio-senpai for you!
Yeah...
The winds are stirring, aren't they?
It looks like the weather is going to get worse.
Shall we head inside now?
Yeah!
Yeah...
Noël-chan as well.
Huh?
Like I said...
Doesn't it seem like Rio-senpai is acting strange?
How so?
That trumpet, for starters...
Wasn't it wonderful? Cool too.
She seemed to be brooding about something...
Not discussing pointless things is how she normally is.
But... Oh right, dinner!
It was delicious, wasn't it? That tenpura!
Yup! And the potatoes were soft and tasty!
That's not what I mean!
Here, Rio. Have it while it's hot.
Yeah, thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
I see! That's great.
Bell peppers...
She munched on and then ate them!
Our Rio-senpai did?!
Yeah!
No matter how small you tried to cut them up, she'd find them and definitely remove them!
But that Rio-senpai...
This could be serious...
Huh?
Is this... Klaus-san?
Yep! It's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Klaus!
On the left side of his chest is a symbol of his unity with the 481st Platoon: a tattoo of a wolf's head!
Cool, isn't it?
I won't give it to you though.
It's all right not to worry too much.
When the Commander was down, we worried about it too much that time.
But remember, it's Rio-senpai after all.
She's cool, attractive, and good looking.
That's right.
If it's just a bell pepper, I'm sure that if she just gulped it down, she could eat it.
Kureha-chan, you really like Rio-senpai, don't you?
Senpai is who I want to be like.
Well, so do I, but...
Hey, Noël-chan, what do you think?
Tsun...
Watch out!
Noël-chan's already asleep.
I guess there's no helping it. I'll let her share my bed.
Kanata, give me a hand with her.
Okay!
You forgot to put out the bath's heating fire.
Sorry, I was careless.
Leaving things as if you had intended to is one of your charming points,
but lately, it's starting to become an issue.
Sorry.
I know you regret it—hearing from your father on the phone.
But there's no helping it, huh?
When you skip out on your duties, I'll cover for you.
But when you're around them, at least try to remain their cool senpai.
I wonder if it's the wind?
That's not it...
Sorry to disturb you. It's an urgent delivery.
Who is it for?
1121st Platoon's Sergeant Major Kazumiya Rio.
Take it.
Major, in the meantime, why don't you please come in?
With this kind of weather, isn't it best if you don't go anywhere?
Even if they call you "The Desert Wolf."
I told you to stop calling me by that name.
I'm sorry.
As an apology, how about a hot cup of tea and a bath?
Despite there being a typhoon, thank you for completing your mission!
Um, I'm sorry that all we have are leftovers from this evening, but please have some!
When Klaus-san arrived, it would've been nice if you had woken me up!
It's good. It's cold, but still delicious.
The bell peppers don't leave a bad aftertaste, either.
Do you really mean it?!
The one that picked and fried them was me!
Oh? It seems like you'll become a good wife then.
Is that the new newspaper?
Yes. The Major brought it with him.
The Armistice Agreement?
It seems they're still discussing it.
It looks like they can't come to a compromise on it.
If Princess Iliya were still alive, the talks would probably be going differently, don't you think?
Iliya... the Princess?
Seriously?! You really don't know who she was? The hero of Vingt?!
She was Archduke Arkadia's first princess.
She's the Helvetian Army's Goddess of Conquest.
Although, she isn't the god of tanks like the Desert Wolf, Major Klaus, is.
Kureha, that's...
Is everyone here?
There's an emergency.
Rio! Rio!
What's the matter?
One of Yumina's kids has been missing since this morning.
Lend us a hand.
What?
Yumina-san, who's missing?
It's Seiya-san.
The river's risen quite a bit, eh?
And the fields downstream haven't been harvested yet.
If the dam broke, they'd all be done for.
I don't know the way downtown.
I'm counting on you, Kureha.
Okay!
Truly, I'm so very sorry.
I took my eyes off him for one minute...
Disaster relief is one of our duties.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
Right.
Seiya!
Seiya-kun!
Wow, there's so much water.
If he had fallen...
Seiya!
Seiya-kun!
Wh-What the...
You!
You know something, don't you?
You came here because you thought he might be here.
Tell me.
Where's Seiya?
The vegetable plot.
The vegetable plot?
Eggplants. They're Yumina-oneechan's favorite.
So earlier, everyone pooled their allowance and bought some.
I'm sure Seiya...
Where is it?
What are you doing?!
Coming to a place like this in the middle of a typhoon?!
I have to protect the eggplants!
What are you talking about? Don't you get it?!
We're putting our lives on the line for you!
You decided that on your own, right?
I never told you to save me!
What did you say?!
Quit screwing around!
Listen. We orphans have to keep it together more than normal kids.
If we cause people trouble, they'll just say "of course."
It's not just you.
Yumina...
Your oneechan as well.
Kureha...
I'm also an orphan, so I understand.
Now, let's go back.
But...
You still have some lingering recklessness?!
Well, wait.
Something you worked hard for...
Believing that's worth your life is charming, don't you think?
These are plenty big enough to eat.
See here? If you pickle them, they'll taste amazing.
Thanks, Mister.
Major...
Seiya-kun has started climbing.
Major, you can go ahead.
N-No, you go ahead.
I'll watch your back.
Okay!
Somehow, they're both still okay.
However...
With this, they have no way to climb back up.
The situation... has taken a turn for the worst.
Thank you very much.
The situation may have turned bad...
But at least I'm with you, Major.
I'm sure something will happen as long as we have faith!
You're wrong...
Huh? Did you say something?
Nope.
Listen, don't be scared.
Right now you're with Miracle Klaus.
Yeah!
The ground won't hold!
Down to the end, huh?
Damn it! This is why I hate kids!
Kids who don't listen should just be tied and locked up! That'd be best!
Rio!
What good is it to cause unrest?
They're always looking up to you.
Sorry, I said too much...
B-But I'm sure something will happen.
They call Klaus-san "The Miracle Man" after all.
You're wrong.
He isn't "The Desert Wolf" or "Miracle Klaus."
He just has the same name and looks a bit like him.
When they first met, Kureha just assumed that it was him.
Klaus isn't good with words, so he never found a chance to deny it, that's all.
That's...
Anyway, at the moment, we have a soldier who has just been in the service for a long time...
and an eager, but inexperienced soldier...
whom we need to find a way to save from there.
Throw them... a rope?
There's no footing from above.
And it's too far to give them one from here.
If there is a way to get a rope over there...
There is!
When I first met you,
I thought that if my dad was still alive, he would be just like you.
Even though I tell everyone I knew my dad...
You see, I've really only heard that one thing.
I don't actually know him.
He was already gone when I was old enough to understand.
Kureha...
Watch... the upper left?
Takemikazuchi!
Halt!
Noël-chan, how is it?
Anchoring device's linear coil operational. Targeting system sections B7 through F5 activating.
Beginning alignment.
It's possible.
Wire anchor, prepare to fire!
Kanata, do it!
Right!
It's coming.
I'll protect you in place of your late father!
Okay...
...Major.
Ready!
Fire!
Come on!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Hoist the anchor! Hurry!
Hey, Kureha.
Since we somehow made it, I have to tell you...
I'm...
As I thought, you're...
the person whom I admire.
Blue skies after the typhoon passes, huh?
In the end, you kept it a secret.
I'm honestly surprised.
I didn't think you would go that far.
When I saw her trust in me, I was more scared of breaking her dream than dying.
That's how I was able to keep up the act.
In the end, I'm just a coward.
That's not true. Klaus-san was wonderful!
Listen, young lady. What an outsider sees and what the actual person feels is often different.
The glasses of admiration are always out of focus, you see.
Someday, when someone looks at you that way, you'll understand how it feels.
Won't you at least stay till Kureha-chan wakes up and tell her?
Tell Kureha this for me.
This sucker is the greatest battle wound I've ever had in my entire life.
Let’s remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let’s move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You’re just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know you know we’ll be happy!
let’s make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you count my precious hours?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
Setting Off
Time of the First Snow
Next time: Setting Off · Time of the First Snow