A Philosopher's Stone!
But where did he find one?!
Dust in our eyes? Again?
[Al] Hwa!
[Kimblee] Hya!
[Al grunts]
[Al yelps]
[Selim and Al grunt]
[Al grunts]
[Kimblee] Hmph!
[Al gasps]
[Selim startles]
I won't fall for that again!
A Flash bomb!
[Al] A decoy!
That's the stone...
A tricky thing!
[Al exhales]
[Kimblee] Yes, The power of
the Philosopher's Stone...
is truly something to behold...
Having used one myself,
I suppose I know that
better than anyone.
That's why I'm puzzled by you.
What I'd like to know is
why you don't use that power
to get your original body back.
With the stone in hand,
you wouldn't have any
trouble fleeing from us...
And once you had gotten
away, you and your brother
could use the stone to
restore your bodies...
and then your journey
would end, wouldn't it?
[Al] If I did that,
I couldn't save everyone.
It's in accordance
with your ideals...
In order to obtain something...
you give up something
of equal value.
[Al] Tell me...
Why do I have to choose?
It isn't right...
I have to choose between
returning to our original
bodies and saving everyone.
But why can't we have
our real bodies back
and save everyone?
It isn't fair!
But it's the law of
equivalent exchange.
Well, I say searching
for possibilities
that aren't bound
by rules or laws--
that's how humanity advances.
I see... so if you can discover
an exception to the rule,
you can effectively
rewrite the laws of nature
as we understand them.
Is that how it's
supposed to go?
Because there is another
possibility, you know...
You don't get
your bodies back...
And you don't save everyone...
That could certainly happen.
[Al gasps]
[Sloth grunts]
[Armstrong]
I'm not finished yet!
[Armstrong grunts]
[Sloth groans]
[Olivier yells]
Good! He has weak spots!
[Sloth groans]
Ow... I'm dying...
I hate dying.
It's such... a pain.
Ahh... Coming back
is a pain...
But then... fighting all-out...
is the biggest pain of all...
Say what?
All right, General Armstrong!
Throw down your weapon.
[Soldier] What the... What
the hell is that huge thing?!
[Sloth groans]
What was that?
[Sloth] Looks like... I missed.
[Olivier braces, gasps]
He's fast! What
incredible speed!
Sloth the Indolent, indeed!
Olivier!
[Olivier] It's just a
scratch. Just then...
Did you see what he did?
[Armstrong] Only the
blur... For him to have
that kind of speed,
at his size. It's just--
I know... it keeps
getting better.
Yes... I am... the fastest
Homunculus of them all.
[Armstrong yells]
Are you all right?
[Armstrong grunts]
[Olivier] Luckily, he's too
fast to control his movements.
No!
Finally... I hit you.
Mmm... I love that sound...
There's nothing more beautiful
than the sound of
two strong souls
colliding against
each other in battle...
I assure you, Alphonse Elric
is still close by.
Indeed, I think he is.
It will take more
than that to kill him.
[sound of a stone
hitting metal]
There you are!
[Al grunts]
That trick? Again? How
artless... It won't work.
[Al shrieks]
Remember, I can tell
where you are by smell...
I think that's checkmate.
[Al] Are you sure?
I still think you're giving
us humans too little credit.
[Selim scoffs]
[Al grunts]
[Selim] Even with the
stone, there's no way
you'll win this
all by yourself.
[Al] I'm not alone!
Where did the stone go?
[Selim] Can it be...?
The purpose of this dust cloud
was to let him know the
direction of the wind?
It must be. He's set
something downwind
where my sense of
smell won't work.
[Kimblee] It's an
attack from behind!
[Kimblee] Impossible! How could
he move with those injuries?
[Kimblee gasps]
[Kimblee] Doctor Marcoh...!
[Narrator]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[Central Soldier 3] They said it
was an ice cream truck, right?
That's right... So keep
your eyes sharp.
This alchemy stuff--
it really is handy, isn't it?
It wasn't very difficult for me
to change up the
truck's appearance.
[Ross] We can't
get in here either...
North, south, east, west...
the gates are all closed.
[Hawkeye] What do we do now?
Force our way in?
No... We'll leave
that to the others...
The Briggs soldiers
can handle that route...
We're gonna take
a more subtle one.
Sir?
We're splitting up here...
You two take them...
Head for "you-know-where."
Yes, sir.
[Dummies growl]
[Zampano roars]
[Dummies scream]
[Darius grunts]
[Darius] Hm?
[Ed yells]
A good thing I'm so beefy.
[Dummies moan]
I guess that shows you
what a Philosopher's Stone
can do for you, huh?
The legs! Go for the legs!
[Zampano pants]
[Gerso gurgles]
[Dummies moan]
[Ed shudders]
[Dummies yell]
[Ed yells]
[Dummies scream]
[Ed grunts]
[Ed yells]
[Armstrong struggles]
[Olivier gasps]
[Armstrong and Sloth struggle]
[Armstrong yells]
[Soldiers gasp]
[Central Soldier] What?
[Armstrong grunts]
Alex?
Oh... it's just dislocated...
And how about you?
Heh. A few fractures,
that's all.
[Armstrong and Olivier gasp]
[Armstrong coughs]
[Armstrong] Hm? Olivier!
[Sloth groans]
[Armstrong growls]
I'm gonna kill you
quickly and then sleep.
[Heinkel roars]
[Al] He stopped?
[Al] He's reluctant
to endanger Kimblee...
But that's not
like him at all.
I see now.
[Al] Huh?
[Selim] You humans
are indeed tenacious...
However... You have
no hope of winning.
You should know... Our
father is just over there.
But of course...
Before we get to that...
we're going to have
to do something
about your current
situation, aren't we?
[Marcoh yells]
[Al] Who...?
[Al and Selim grunt]
[Yoki cries] I got you!
I really got you!
[Al] Yoki?!
All right! Way to take
him out, fuzzy lip!
[Yoki cries]
You're the last one I expected!
I'm not gonna let you guys
play hero all by yourselves!
I want some glory
of my own, damn it...
Do you hear me?!
How 'bout that?
I landed a shot!
And it was on the strongest
Homunculus of them all!
I got him big time!
Where'd you get the car?
[Marcoh] It's the one
Kimblee rode here in.
The guys who drove it here
are taking a little time out.
Okay! Well done, Dr. Marcoh.
Move it! Let's go!
[Yoki shudders]
Shut up! Quit
whining and drive!
I have no desire to attempt
fighting that monster head-on!
Get us to Central on
the double! We need to
meet up with Ed and get
rid of this "Father" guy
before that thing
can catch up to us.
They may well be
tenacious creatures...
but humans are easy to dupe.
[Kimblee wheezes]
[Selim] Hm?
[Kimblee breathes weakly]
Oh, that's good... So
you're still alive, then.
[Selim] I think that color
suits you very well, don't you?
Lions are called the King
of Beasts for a reason...
He followed the law that
says the fittest survive.
And accordingly,
he was able to bite
right through your windpipe.
[Selim] One can be sure...
in this world...
humans are of
little consequence.
[Kimblee coughs and sputters]
[Selim] What was it
you were always saying?
That you wanted to see which
way the world would choose?
And here you are, dying
like a pathetic wreck...
It must be humiliating.
[Selim] But don't
worry too much.
[Selim] Because you will
continue to live... inside me.
[Olivier moans,
breathes weakly]
[Olivier] What... What happened?
[Olivier] Alex!
I knew he was going
to come charging in,
so all I had to do
was wait for him.
[Sloth moans]
Olivier, are you able to stand?
[sound of guns cocking]
[Soldiers shudder nervously]
By the way... there are orders
to shoot me for being a traitor.
What?! We can't have that!
I'll be the one to inherit
the Armstrong household.
You can't die until all of
the paperwork is in place!
There's nothing to worry
about there. If I die,
the entire estate will be passed
along to Colonel Mustang.
You decided that without
consulting the family?!
[Olivier] He's still
just barely preferable
to a good-for-nothing like you.
[Armstrong] So that's
how you treat someone
who just saved your life?!
Hey... What is this?
We're under attack?
It can't be...
Mustang's soldiers?
[Soldier whimpers]
[Soldier screams]
[Soldiers gasp]
[Soldier screams,
Dummy growls]
[Dummies hiss, moan]
[Dummy growls]
[Soldiers murmur]
[Soldier 8] What
are those things?!
Even when they're shot,
they don't die!
Are they soldiers
from Fort Briggs?
[Olivier] Idiots!
How dare you
compare my brave men
with such disgusting
specimens as those?!
I'm guessing... they're
the same as this guy.
The one who gave you
your orders must have
sent those things out
here for the attack.
Look, we don't know anything
about these creatures,
understand?!
Well then, I guess
they don't care...
It doesn't matter to them
whether you know or not.
[Dummies roar]
All right, soldier...
What's it gonna be?
My brother and I can take
care of these monsters.
Maybe so, but...
[Soldiers shudder]
[Soldier screams]
[Sloth groans]
[Soldier shudders]
Well, what's it gonna be?!
Do you plan on shooting us,
and then fall prey
to the monsters after?
Or are you going
to work with us
and bring them down together?!
Make up your own
damn minds, now!
[May squeals]
[Envy yells]
You brat!
[Dummies moan]
Ah! There's more of you!?
[Dummies growl]
[May yells]
[May squeals]
You're wasting your time...
All of these mannequin
soldiers have been infused
with Philosopher's Stones...
You aren't going to be able
to kill them that easily!
[Dummy struggles]
See now? That's what
you get for running away.
[Dummy growls]
My, these soldiers are tasty!
And with this, I'm
even stronger now!
You don't you get it, do you?
I doubt I'd last very long
against a whole army
of mannequins...
but I know that I can dodge
just one of you all day!
Silence, you brat!
[May] All of these
mannequins have been infused
with Philosopher's Stones...
so they won't die...
That's where their
immortality comes from...
But I'll still find a way...
I must... to save my clan!
[Ed yells]
[Scar grunts]
[Dummies moan]
They're really still coming?
Why won't they die?!
I'm running out of quills!
My spit's starting
to dry up, too.
[Dummies moan]
Damn it!
Stop it!
Look out!
[Ed gasps]
[Roy] Things do always
seem to get messy
whenever you're around.
Maybe I could lend you
a hand... Fullmetal?
[Narrator] When someone
finds the truth,
they must lay
their heart bare...
They are not free to choose...
Not free to avoid that
which they have found...
They have no such luxury...
and they never will again.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 53:
"Flame of Vengeance."
Burn it up... All of it.