Say the password.
Mountain...
The ocean, swimsuits, and hot springs.
Good, enter.
You're late, Ann!
I'm sorry.
Searching for Jellycans to snack on took longer than I thought.
Right.
Now then, we're all gathered.
We'll begin our meeting at once.
There can only be one reason for us to meet in secret at this hour.
It will soon be one year since Hina came to our home.
In other words, Hina's birthday.
When it comes to birthdays,
you've got to have a surprise party, right?
Yes, but a mere surprise party isn't enough!
We need to be extra careful to avoid blunders that could spoil the surprise!
So, what kind of surprise party should we throw?
Anyone got any ideas?
One thing before we start.
What's that, Kurara?
Our surprisee is right over there.
Hina?! Why?
Do not call me by that name.
And we even made a password so we wouldn't be found out!
How did you get in?
You are the ones who intruded upon my weapon maintenance.
Were you whetting a knife?
At this point, why not ask the Shinki in question what she'd like?
If you are to give gifts,
last month's model of grenade launcher or Gatling cannon would suffice.
Again with the deadly weaponry...
Next week, I'll be entering the Shinki Battle Tournament!
And my victory will be my gift to you!
I don't think anyone's dying for that gift.
I wish to enter instead.
But that's wonderful, Kurara.
You're entering again this year.
Didn't you lose to a Strarf model like Hina last year?
This year, my body is fine tuned!
I'll definitely be the champion!
Then we'll all make stuff to cheer you on!
I like the sound of that!
After all my searching, I've finally found you.
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Tonight's the Night! Who's the Strongest Shinki!?
I'm finished!
Look at my banner!
Ooh, what've we got?
Do your best, Kurara!
Nobody will call you a joke character anymore!
You should probably put some more
thought into making it inspirational...
Should I really?
Why not take the chance to give her a cool nickname?
Nickname?
Something like "Ebony Hurricane" or "Crimson Knight".
A name that speaks to her skills and appearance.
Then how about "Ebony Joke Character"?
No, Kurara's not even black to begin with...
And Ann, do you even know what a joke character is?
Ta-dah! I'm done too!
Oh, that's Cheerleader Armor.
It's pretty cute!
This is what Ann and I will wear.
Ines, you'll wear this.
Why me?
It's not just you, but Strarf too!
It's not enough to just have female cheerleaders!
I got a drum too, so feel free to beat it!
May I beat it senseless?
No, we don't want to break the thing.
Just beat it at normal strength.
Hey, don't worry.
We haven't forgotten your birthday, Hina.
It's just not much of a surprise anymore.
Once Kurara's done with the tournament,
we're gonna throw a huge party!
I was not asking for one, per se.
Again? You know you want it.
All I want is to maintain my weapons.
Let's see...
Banner and megaphone, check.
Pom-poms, check.
Cheerleader Armor, check.
Should we bring Lemon flavor cans as refreshment?
Or would a refreshing Mint flavor be better?
Either's fine, but we'll be late if you don't hurry!
Aw Lene, you're such a handful...
It is dated one year ago.
"Thank you for applying for a review model of the latest Strarf-model Shinki.."
Sadly, we have rejected your application.
This is a rejection letter?
What could this mean?
Is something wrong?
N-Nothing at all.
I simply found a year-old postcard under the desk.
Oh, Master's such a scatterbrain!
Like you're one to talk.
I'm gonna be late!
I've got work after school, so good luck with Kurara!
Tell her I'm rooting for her!
We will, Master!
Have a nice day!
Strarf, are you okay?
You've been looking glum.
It is nothing.
Ah, I see it!
The place looks packed!
There are a lot of people.
Well, it only comes once a year!
There she is!
Hey, Kurara!
We're here to root for you!
We stayed up all night making this!
Do your best, Kurara! Your peerless wings carry a snow-white siren.
H-Hey, cut that out!
You're gonna embarrass me!
Aww, come on, we know you love it.
That laugh...
Down, girl!
I can't oil you up if you keep moving!
Pawse, please! I'm ticklish!
Bear with it!
If your body's covered in this slippery lotion,
you'll have the advantage because your opponents won't be able to cat-ch you!
Can't forget this part, huh...
Yep, sounds like another harebrained scheme...
Indeed!
They're giving the finger to fighting fair and square!
There's no elegance in using slippery lotions.
It's Ach and Yda!
If you two are in the tournament,
then does that mean you've found your perfect Master?
No. We registered under a virtual master for the time being.
A virtual master?
Oh, you can do that.
We did, and when we win this tournament,
our true master will fall in love at first sight!
And that is why we simply shall not lose!
And with that, we're off.
What? I can't get in!
It's you!
Hey, it's been a while, you guys!
You came here from the mountain?
Yep, just for today's tournament.
Are you all charged up?
We're full!
Are you entering too?
No, my duty is only to cheer.
Aw, that's a shame.
I want to fight against you some time.
Zelnogrard of the mountain...
I am also in your debt...
You coulda killed me!
My apologies. My hand slipped.
Are you battling too?
Yes, thanks to a certain someone.
So you're saying...
your master came with you?
Of course!
You called?
She's here!
It's that time of year, folks!
The official Battle Tournament!
I'm your host, Mary Takigawa Celes!
And we have the lovely Ia handling commentary!
It's a pleasure to be here.
But everyone's quite excited, it seems.
Do your best, Kurara! Your peerless wings carry a snow-white siren.
Now then, I think it's time to start with Round 1!
Astonishingly, our first bracket contains last year's finalist,
Eukrante-model Shinki Kurara!
Her opponent is Strarf-model Shinki Victoria!
Oh my, a grudge match already?
Hurray, Hurray,
Kurara!
I can't believe I'm fighting you in the first round.
This match's battlefield will be...
a fortress stage prepared specifically for this grudge match!
And that's not all!
This stage is loaded with anti-air cannons, missiles, and more!
Both fighters can use their own weapons in addition to whatever they find!
Oh my, how scary.
And now it's time for the round to begin!
Go mad with bloodshed!
Kurara!
You can do it!
Talk about intense violence!
Even though she's already won,
she's bringing the entire fortress stage down to the ground!
More, more!
Leave nothing but ash in your wake!
Wow...
There were some issues,
but Victoria ended up winning the tournament again.
That's two in a row!
Too bad about Kurara.
But you were awesome out there, Hina!
If you'd entered, you totally would've won!
Of course.
Oh, but...
you got a scratch.
You'll have to have Master fix it.
Excuse me.
Could you be...
my sister Rosa?
Rosa?
Rosa was the name
of a Strarf-model Shinki my master used to own.
She lost in last year's preliminaries,
which damaged her memory card.
We sent her away for repairs,
but she went missing en route.
Sorry, but you've got the wrong Shinki.
That's right. Her name is Hina.
Do not call me by that name.
Look, even that aversion to being called her name...
No, she just hates it when we use her name.
Master's the only one who can call her Hina.
Anyway, it's a different Shinki.
She's a Shinki that belongs to our master.
Hey, don't feel down!
I've got just the thing!
Hard
Hard Nitro!
I got some of this just in case!
Just in case of what?
I knew it, everyone thought I'd lose from the start.
Geez, you're never happy.
Shut up and chug!
Forget your troubles!
Now then, our surroundings should fit the mood...
I can't believe in a place like this!
Get us somewhere less ritzy.
So, something like this?
This is too depressing.
Get us a normal pub or something!
I'd like a bar in a high-rise hotel with a view of the skyline!
Bars like that are for winners!
Who cares, I'm a loser.
A first round loser, too.
I couldn't win anything.
Again with the pouting?
I think we should go with what we had first.
It can heal a beauty's heart!
I told ya, we're not doin' that!
Huh? But...
Hey, are you my sister Rosa?
Sadly, we have rejected your application.
Was I delivered to Master's house...
not as a review model?
It's you.
I'm sorry, but I just kept thinking you were my sister,
so I followed you.
I see. So Hina, you were sent to your
current master as a review model.
Then maybe, back in the factory,
they reformatted Rosa by mistake and sent her out...
Or perhaps the shipping company mistakenly included me among Master's luggage.
And if that were true, then...
would I be right in staying with Master?
Hey, want to stop by my house?
I think it'd be good if you saw where I lived at least once.
And if you meet my master, maybe it could trigger some memories...
It's not working!
No matter how much I wash, the slipperiness won't go away!
I told you not to rub too much on!
Master won't let us back in until I clean you up...
'N the fugg's a Boosow Sheenkey baddull, anywayze?
Izzit 'bout bein' strong?
Shure ain't!
Der're more 'mpor'nt things 'n life, y'know...
I tell ya, Shinkis...
I think you've had enough.
Here, have some water.
Now this calls for...
anoooother round!
Oh no.
I didn't know she was this bad at holding her nitro!
Hm?
What happened to Strarf?
Dun be a killjooy,
y'all oughta chug some too!
Here you gooo...
No, I'm good! I can't drink any more!
I'm bad with nitro...
Lene, speak up and get me outta this!
Hey, don't spray it!
That's my master's house.
So? Isn't it huge?
Hey, Rosa!
Welcome home!
I was so worried.
Surprised?
Master is Victoria's master, too.
Don't be so nervous.
This was your house.
Though I can't do anything about your memories of it being erased.
Victoria,
Iris,
show her around the mansion.
It might bring back some memories.
Our master is a famous Shinki collector.
Isn't it amazing?
Name any Shinki that money can buy,
and Master will have one each for storage, battle, and decoration.
At least three per model!
And Master made all of this for us!
This isn't a Visualizer, either.
It feels like the ugly duckling actually being a swan, doesn't it?
Hey, you should come back and live with us, Rosa!
But I...
We understand.
Hearing a request like this out of the blue leaves you conflicted.
I'm sure your current master treats you well.
You should think carefully over what you'll choose.
But before you do,
we have to confirm whether you really are Rosa.
We'll know immediately if we check the serial number.
Right this way.
Start the password analysis program.
Do it.
With this, you'll belong to Master.
An ultra-rare review model Shinki.
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Just wait.
We'll save you, I promise!
If we don't hurry, we'll be too late!
Is she going to forget all about us?
Don't worry.
I won't let that happen!
Come back, Hina!
We'll all go back to living happily with Master!
Next time, on Busou Shinki.
Next time
"Don't Say Goodbye"
"Don't Say Goodbye".
In any case, I had no role in the last preview.
Don't show up when we're finally having a dramatic moment!