So Tsuyuri, what were
you doing yesterday?
I went to Seibu-Chichibu.
Really? Is there
something at Seibu-Chichibu?
I wonder what was there...
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
I went to Najimi's job yesterday
and had her draw for me.
Really.
She was a little better at it.
Maybe it's because of the training.
Tsuyurin, did you go
somewhere yesterday?
Seibu-Chichibu.
I'm going to play with Justice
at the park today at sundown.
Would you like to join us, Tsuyurin?
I am going to shop at Akihabara.
I don't have time to be
playing with a child after that.
7th Edition
How wonderful the smell of BaLa.
Never thought I would
run into you here...
Nido-san, you're shopping also?
Erotic game...
I...
But, it's not that I really like
erotic games or anything...
More like... I've never experienced it,
so for the purpose of studying...
With the way you just said it,
it's as if you're coming out...
...with a loud voice saying you've
never experienced anything sexually.
No!
It's not like that...
Well, I've never done it before, but...
...of course I know
what kind of things you do.
Nido-san, why don't we do something
that feels a lot better than erotic games?
What?
What! You're going to
become Nido-san's second?
Wait a second, Tsuyuri!
Whose side are you on!
I'm enemies of you both?
What are you saying!
Tsuyuri!
She hung up on me.
This has gotten bad...
Nido-san's second, huh?
Be cautious of the
shape and direction!
What am I to do?
More gentle!
But I will definitely not lose to them!
That's right!
That's a wonderful boobie!
More like what kind of second are you!
What! A perverted manga?
I am?
It's fine.
Basically, an erotic one sells better.
For the meantime,
let's try writing one.
I'm erotic too,
so I can give you advice.
Then I would be able to
sell more than Najimi-san?
Easily.
Let's twist her easily.
Let's do it.
Let's make a really erotic one.
Yes, a really erotic one.
An obscene one...
Immorality...
Hello?
You're Najimi-san's friend...
Why do you have my number?
I got it from Najimi.
Oh, is that so?
So is there something?
I would like to ask you
to help Najimi's rival.
What do you mean?
There is a girl that is competing
on the sales of her dojinshi, but...
...I wanted you to help her so
her ability to draw will get better.
What! N-No, I can't!
That would mean
I'm betraying Najimi-san!
No, it's more for Najimi.
Huh?
People finally grow for the first time
after passing through a trial.
Remember, for their child's own good...
...lions make them come pick them
up at Shibuya station, you know?
I have a feeling you've
mixed it up with the dog story...
I get it!
I purposely give her a trial
and make Najimi-san grow!
Depending on your effort,
you'll be able to receive something big.
S-Something big?
Najimi's heart.
I'll do it!
What do I have to do?
I want you to carefully
select a couple of copies of...
...18+ dojinshi that are for
the female audience and buy them.
18+ dojinshi for the female audience?
With your sense.
Then I will meet you at the
Nerima Station entrance in two hours.
What?
Ah, hold on!
This is Hoshi-kun.
This is Kaneru Nido-san.
Hello...
You're Najimi-san's rival.
Yes...
So, in regards to
creating an erotic manga...
Hoshi-kun, the books please.
Um, here.
What?
I thought if you're going to draw it,
it'd be for the female audience, so...
...I had him go choose some.
That's his choice.
R-Really...
There are those that exist, huh?
What!
I'm going to be drawing like this?
It's reference for that.
What do you think?
Well, if they like that kind of stuff,
I think they are free to draw it.
I understand.
They are free to like whatever they want.
Hoshi-san, when you
say it, it's convincing!
Is that so.
Oh, I'll make some tea.
No, I'll do it!
You have to practice
your drawing, right?
Yes.
Then I'll take you up on the offer.
He definitely has a feminine side,
like he really pays attention to detail.
He has those kinds of traits.
That's true. That's why
Justice doesn't leave him alone.
What!
Justice-san too?
Speaking of...
Excuse me!
Y-Yes?
Hoshi-san, by any chance
do you have someone you like...
...and could that be
someone that I know?
What! W-Why do you know that?
Are you guys dating?
No, but hopefully by some chance...
What about Sora-chan?
Doesn't Sora-chan know about this?
What?
Oh, her?
I don't think she knows.
It's not "I don't think she knows"!
What!
What a hurtful dream!
What?
Um, Nido-san...
Let's go!
Huh?
You are going to
confess your love! Now!
Right now?
If it's right now,
I think they're at the park.
All of a sudden?
For girls, hearing the truth later
than it's supposed to be is worse!
Is that so?
She's been waiting for my words!
I understand!
I'm a man too.
Let's go!
I'm sorry, Sora-chan...
...for hurting your cute dream.
Also, I'm sorry about another thing.
The truth is, just a little...
...really, just a little bit,
I want to see those two as a couple.
Taste of honey...
Sora-chan.
Kaneru-chan?
Is this fine?
Yes...
Oh, make the ribbon...
...yellow, please!
What?
Hoshi-san is going to confess
his love to Justice right now!
Why?
There are men like that in this world!
That's Hoshi-san!
I don't understand.
I'm sorry!
Justice!
What?
Right now, Hoshi-san!
I have to talk to you!
What? Why?
Look at how they're
staring at each other.
What's there to talk about?
Please hurry up.
I have a commitment with Sora.
No, um...
What the heck is that!
Wait a second...
Does that mean I should take care of
the situation with the biggest obstacle...
...which is this man before
I confess my love to Najimi-san?
Here it goes!
Listen well, Justice!
What I have to talk to you about
is nothing out of the ordinary!
It's about Najimi-san and I!
Why don't I listen?
No, um...
I want to become closer
with Najimi-san, so...
Could you please
warmly look over us.
No! I can't let you
get closer to Najimi!
What are you trying to say I did!
I haven't done anything
that Najimi-san wouldn't like!
Even the time we went to
research the hotel together!
I was thinking maybe
if we got into a good situation...
But in the end it didn't become
any good situation anyway!
Good boys and girls...
It's now 5:30PM.
What do you mean by that?
Um, well...
That's...
Justice-san made the move first.
No way...
I would like to listen
to that in more detail.
What!
You're taking his lips forcefully?
No! You can't do such a thing!
Wait!
Justice!
This is another way
love takes shape?
I'm going to make
this my piece's base.
With both of their agreement!
Definitely!
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Has there ever been an
anime this perverted before?
What? There is?
8th Edition, You can see everything!
Please let me borrow that DVD.