See, see? I told you so!
This car takes the turns really fast!
Well, that's because you're a surprisingly good driver.
I know!
You may not believe it, but I practice all the time!
Of all the toys Kiritsugu has brought me
over the years, this is my absolute favorite!
This is a toy?
At the castle, I was only allowed to
drive around the courtyard, so this is great!
Shouldn't we have maybe hired a professional driver?
No, that would be boring.
I mean, it could be really dangerous.
What if the enemy were to
suddenly launch an attack against us?
Well, I suppose you have a point but...
Stop the car!
Irisviel, get out of the car
and stay very close to me.
This presence...
it's a Servant!
I have come for you, my sweet and holy virgin!
Do you know this man?
I've never laid eyes on him.
Oh no!
Are you saying that you've forgotten my face?
Forgotten you?
I've never met you in my life.
You mistake me for another.
Agh!
It's me!
It's Gilles de Rais, my darling!
I have prayed for your resurrection and
have been waiting for a miracle to reunite us!
To that end, I've come all this
way, to the end of time, my Jeanne!
Who is Jeanne?
I know not your name, I assure you.
Nor have I any idea who this Jeanne might be.
No...
No, you can't have forgotten!
Not your former identity!
As you have seen fit to give me your name,
then I must, in keeping with
the chivalric code, give mine.
My name is Arturia,
the heir to Uther Pendragon,
and King of Britain.
I enter this battle in the Saber class.
Oh no!
How tragic!
It's so very sad!
She's lost her memory and gone completely insane!
Curse Him.
Curse Him!
Such cruel tortures God inflicts upon my
beautiful maiden! Such horrible injustices!
Enough!
You embarrass yourself!
Awaken, O fair one.
You have no need to call yourself Saber any longer.
Because the Holy Grail War has already ended.
The Grail has chosen me, Gilles, to be
its champion, with no fighting at all!
For, you see, my one and only eternal wish, the
resurrection of Jeanne d'Arc, has finally been granted!
Ha...
If you mock the true prayers of all the
other heroes again, the next strike will be real!
Now rise!
Has your heart been sealed so tightly, my dearest Jeanne?
Very well.
That's too bad.
If drastic measures are called for to free your heart,
I will take my leave of you to go and prepare.
I swear to you, Jeanne!
I will not rest until I can free your soul
from the terrible prison of God's cruel curse.
It's very difficult to deal with one
who ignores everything that you're saying.
Next time, I shall strike before he speaks!
His type completely infuriates me.
However, this encounter may
have actually been a fortunate one.
I sensed that he was too dangerous to
face without the full use of my left hand.
Following Saber's Master has yielded unexpected fruits.
We found Caster as well.
Of course, we must follow him.
Ah, no, no.
The thumb needs to go like this!
That's nice!
Perfect in fact!
Welcome back, big guy.
Hey!
What the hell?
Accursed God!
He keeps an iron grip on
Jeanne's soul, refusing to let go!
By Jeanne I assume you mean the
girl you saw in the crystal ball?
We must prove the cold hear talked to her!
That God's power is gone and my love wasted!
That no deed no matter how foul,
no crime no matter how horrible
is worthy of God's punishment!
Yeah, I get it.
You're even cooler than I thought!
Therefore, we require greater
depravities, greater blasphemies.
We must erect a veritable Tower
of Babel of human sacrifices!
Mmm, uh, so basically, from
now on it's quantity over quality?
Indeed!
Exactly so!
Impressive, Ryunosuke.
Our first step will be sacrificing
the eleven in their cells right away.
And then, we'll go acquire some
more children for our revelries.
It's kind of a waste, don't you think?
Uh...
We interrupt this regularly scheduled program
to bring you this important breaking news.
An unexplained explosion has occurred
in the Fuyuki Coastal Warehouse District.
We go live to the scene.
Why did you fail to finish off Saber when you faced her?
Not once but twice.
You made me waste the Command Seal, and
yet you couldn't finish the job, idiot!
Was your encounter with Saber
really that much fun for you?
It wasn't like that, Master.
I swear on my honor as a knight, as a Servant
of the Grail War, I will bring you Saber's head.
You don't need to swear to me again!
Of course you will!
You made a pact with me to defeat
all others for the Holy Grail.
And now you sit there like a sniveling
fool swearing to bring me the head of Saber?
What about this do you not understand!?
Aren't you the one who's mistaken here,
Lord El‐Melloi?
Sola‐Ui.
Lancer actually did well.
I'm afraid you're the one who made the mistake.
Saber is a highly skilled and powerful Servant.
I simply couldn't allow a chance to
defeat her pass me by without trying.
He inflicted a wound on her that cannot heal.
By letting her go, you can defeat her at your leisure.
If you're that concerned about her and her lauded
abilities, why didn't you go after her Master instead?
You merely stayed hidden and watched.
Rather pathetic.
Honestly, Kayneth.
It isn't that you don't understand your
distinct advantage over all the other Masters.
You were the one who ensured that.
You made a special alteration
to the usual Master‐Servant pact
that no one other than I knows anything about.
You control Command Seals, and I act as an
additional Master and supply the Servant mana.
Brilliant.
You weren't the Evocation Division's
brightest star for nothing, you know?
But we must take care at the beginning.
Must we now?
So you'll hide while you make Lancer take all the risks?
All right, that's enough of that.
Any more will be an insult to my Master.
As a knight, I cannot allow it.
No, I didn't mean it like that!
I've overstepped my bounds.
I'm sorry.
What?
What's going on?
Yes, I understand.
There's a fire on the lower levels.
It can't be anything but an act of arson, of course.
Arson?
Tonight, of all nights?
They wish to empty the building.
Then it's an attack.
Saber's Master will want to take
down Lancer as soon as possible
to lift his spear's curse and make her whole.
Lancer, go downstairs now and defeat her.
Don't just drive her off this time.
Understood, Master.
Let's see to it that our honored guest enjoys
the amazing magical workshop of Kayneth El‐Melloi.
A perfect workshop requiring an entire floor.
Twenty‐four layered barriers, three mana generators,
dozens of ghosts and spirits roaming as guard dogs.
Thousands of traps and parts of
hallways that open into other worlds.
We shall avail ourselves of all the
magical techniques we have at our disposal.
I shall make you retract your statements
that I am pathetic very shortly.
Oh?
I look forward to it.
Mr. Archibald!
Mr. Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald!
Are you present here?
Yes.
That was me.
Don't worry.
Both Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald
and his wife Sola‐Ui have exited.
Hm.
Oh, I see.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Everyone has evacuated.
Good.
Everything is ready on my end.
And you?
All green.
Just give the word.
Maiya?
The target never even moved from his position.
He didn't leave the hotel before the explosion.
A free fall from 150 meters.
No magical barrier known to man
could've saved him from that.
Maiya, withdraw.
To blow up the entire building...
I can't believe a mage would
actually do something like that.
Then again, I suppose he is
excellent at outsmarting mages.
Kirei Kotomine.
Oh?
I don't believe we've ever met.
Or do you have a good reason why
you would know who I am already?
Well, in that case, I can guess who you are.
Don't make me stand here doing all the talking, woman.
One word from you will suffice.
Tell me, where is the man who should have been here
instead of you?
Not bad, not bad at all.
You seem to have some training.
Hm.
There's no way she threw this gas canister.
No matter.
Just the knowledge that someone was here to save her
from the situation means tonight wasn't a total waste.
Master Kirei.
I thought I gave you explicit orders to
stay hidden and not to expose yourself.
My apologies, Master.
But there is some important news that
I thought you should hear without delay.
We've located the Servant Caster.
After having Assassin perform a detailed investigation,
we learned that Caster and his Master
have kidnapped children from their beds
in the town of Miyama and the next town over.
By dawn, they had taken fifteen.
I would imagine
that they are the serial killer that's been
reported in the news and that everyone is worried about.
They use magic without even the slightest hesitation,
and seem to be doing absolutely
nothing to hide their tracks.
It is quite possible that they are
not even thinking of the Holy Grail War.
A mad Servant out of control
and a Master who doesn't even try to control him.
Why are people like them participating in the Grail War?
This is something we cannot ignore, Tokiomi.
Their actions are in clear violation
of the rules by which we are all bound.
Of course.
As one responsible for guarding the
secrets of magic, this cannot be allowed.
Uh, we shall have to eliminate
Caster as well as his Master.
Yes.
But the problem is that defeating
a Servant requires a Servant,
and we can't send my Assassin
without exposing our deception.
Ah.
Minor rule changes fall completely under my purview.
We'll have all of the Masters
work as a group to defeat Caster.
Archer?
There are far fewer bottles here than
in Tokiomi's room, but of higher quality.
I must say that's some apprentice he has.
What is it you want?
Apparently, there are those in this war other
than myself with an abundance of time on their hands.
What do you mean?
Otherwise, a Master existing under
the kind protection of the Church
would hardly need to wander about.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you dissatisfied with your Master, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi invited me to this
world and maintains my form here.
His greeting was worthy of my elevated station,
and so I felt that I had to respond to that.
But I never expected that he'd
be such a dull and boring person.
So you are unhappy with him as your Master.
He wants to reach the Vortex of the Root.
What a boring and tedious little plan.
The unflinching desire for the "Root" is unique to mages.
It's not for outsiders to comment upon.
In a sense, the path to the "Root" is
the path to an escape from this world.
For us, who are interested only in the world itself,
it may well be a tedious plan.
Is that so?
True.
I am full of love for this universe
that is my personal playground.
I have no interest in realms outside my dominion.
This "Root" of yours does not concern me in the least.
Perhaps.
But the Grail is not a device
specifically designed to seek the Root.
When we say that it is omnipotent,
we mean that it has limitless potential to
alter even the reality of the material world.
So you're saying the other Masters
have motives other than Tokiomi's
for wanting to obtain the Holy Grail.
Tokiomi is an archetypal mage,
and at the same time extremely orthodox.
What the other Masters seek is one form or
another of success here in the material world:
prestige, desires, power.
That suits me fine.
I love every one of those things.
You are a king who rules over the profane and the vulgar,
Gilgamesh.
So what is it that motivates you, Kirei?
What do you want from the Holy Grail?
Me?
Nothing.
I have no real desire for it.
I seriously doubt that.
Doesn't the Holy Grail call only those
Masters whom it considers worthy of possessing it?
So they say.
But why did it choose me?
I have no ideal or other desire.
So why choose me for this battle?
No ideal or other desire?
Then why not simply wish for something like joy?
Ridiculous!
Wish for joy?
You'd ask me to long for something
that blasphemous and sinful?
Blasphemous and sinful you say?
That's going a little far, isn't it?
Why the connection between joy and sin?
Well, I...
True, joy gained by evil means could be considered sin.
But joy may be attained through good deeds as well.
What kind of philosophy calls joy itself a sin?
It's absolutely ludicrous.
Joy is another quality that I lack.
I seek it, but never find it.
Kirei Kotomine,
I find myself interested in you.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said.
Be seated.
True joy, you see,
might be thought of as a form of the soul.
The question isn't whether it exists or not,
but whether you know it.
Kirei, you have yet to see what form your soul has taken.
That's what it actually means when
you claim that you lack joy in your life.
You're just a mere Servant
and you dare sit there and lecture me?
Don't get cocky, mongrel.
I am a king who has tasted all
the pleasures the world has to offer.
Hold your tongue and listen.
Kirei, you ought to learn what pleasure is.
Look first to the outside.
I know.
Why not begin by joining me in my entertainment?
I have no time to waste on pointless trivialities.
Don't be like that.
You can do it between the jobs Tokiomi assigns you.
To begin with, your task is to keep watch
over the five other Masters, isn't that correct?
What of it?
You should investigate not only their plans, but
their motivations for obtaining the Grail as well.
Then give that information to me.
That would be possible if I ask the Assassins.
But, Archer, what does any of that matter to you?
I've already told you.
I enjoy watching humans.
One or two of them are sure to be interesting
enough to keep me entertained for a while.
Compared to that dull Tokiomi at least.
Very well, Archer.
I will accept.
But it will take some time to do it.
That's fine.
I shall wait patiently
as I avail myself of these drinks.
My reason for seeking the Holy Grail?
I said far more than I should have.
I know that it certainly isn't joy.
However, if I can learn about him,
will I also be able to learn
what it is I seek as well?
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I am temporarily altering the rules of the Grail War.
Could eventually kill yourself.
We could escape if we go now.
It will be my lance alone that takes Saber's life.
My fight with you is no longer over the Grail!
Don't get conceited, you savage!