I used to be a normal third-grader,
but a little incident changed everything.
I found courage within my heart,
and I gained magical powers.
Like a storm of emotions,
our encounters are filled with feelings and
words that we can't express to each other.
Because I want to understand
your wishes and sadness...
I'm filled with feelings that
I want to share with you.
Only to you, to your heart.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha will now begin.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
Cradling my knees in the corner of my room,
I trembled with anxiety
Afraid of knowing the truth,
I shut the door to it
I took comfort in a gentle lie,
and found shelter in my dreams
I was sinking in a sea called loneliness
that was dyed a deep blue
But as I earnestly tried to hide it,
I ended up hurting your heart
As your heart is drawn to the secret in my eyes,
and the truth behind my smile,
I will deliver my gentle love to you
If you feel the same, that fragile warmth
will spill forth from the past and overflow into the present
Let us always walk together,
free from the shadows of loneliness
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
And so...
As of 0000 hours today,
the entire crew will assist in the recovery of the Lost Logia,
the Jewel Seeds.
It is our top priority.
Due to the extensive scope and
difficulty of this mission,
we have enlisted the one
who discovered the Lost Logia,
who is also a mage skilled with barriers.
Yes. My name is Yuuno Scrya.
And also the one working with him,
a mage from the world the Seeds fell to.
I-I'm Nanoha Takamachi.
While in the care of the Civil Affairs Bureau,
these two have been assigned to us.
Please take good care of us.
Episode 9
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean.
From now on, we'll be locating
the Jewel Seeds from here.
Once we pinpoint them, we'll send
you two to the scene right away.
Yes, ma'am!
Captain, I've brought you some tea.
Hot.Spring.Tea
Thank you.
Now that I think of it, Nanoha...
will you be okay missing school for a while?
Ah, yes. I came up with an explanation
for my family and friends.
It appears that Ms. Takamachi will be absent
from school due to family circumstances.
But she's not out because of an
illness or anything serious,
so there's no need to worry.
While Ms. Takamachi is absent,
would someone take
notes and homew–
Yes! I will.
Thank you for
volunteering, Arisa.
Okay!
Now then, shall we begin homeroom?
Stand.
Bow.
Nanoha... I wonder how you're doing...
Sit.
I got it, Nanoha!
Okay!
Sealing Mode, Set up.
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical Magical! Jewel Seed Serial VIII.
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt No. VIII.
The situation is under control.
Jewel Seed No. VIII has been safely secured.
Good job down there, Nanoha, Yuuno.
Yep!
I'll create a gate for you two now.
Just wait there for a second.
Hmm... those two sure are impressive.
At this rate, I might want
them to stay with us.
The girl in black... her name is Fate, right?
Fate Testarossa... there was once a
great mage with the same last name.
Huh? Really?
It's an old story now, though...
She was a great mage
from Central Midchilda.
During a magical experiment she ran,
there was an accident,
causing a large dimensional interference,
leading to her exile.
Could this girl be related to her?
Who knows?
It might not even be her real name.
Ah... as I thought,
it's no good. I can't find her.
Fate appears to be using
a complex barrier to block us.
A canine familiar...
It's probably supporting her.
Thanks to that, they've already stolen
two Jewel Seeds we managed to locate.
Do a thorough search,
make sure you find her.
We're really counting on you for this.
Yes, yes...
We haven't seen Fate at all, huh?
Yeah... though it looks like she's been
capturing Jewel Seeds, too...
Yeah...
Fate, it's no good.
There's nothing here.
I see...
Really... hiding from them
while keeping up the search hasn't been easy.
Yeah... but let's try our best a little longer.
It's been ten days since we were
brought on board the Arthra.
We've managed to get Jewel Seeds
VIII, IX, and XII... just those three.
On Fate's side, they've
managed to get two... Serials II and V...
Six more, huh?
The remaining six...
we just can't seem to find them.
We're increasing the scope of
the search beyond landmasses.
There's an ocean nearby,
so they may be underwater.
Amy is searching there right now,
as well as searching for that girl in black.
I see.
We didn't find any today, either.
Yeah...
This could end up taking a lot longer than expected.
Nanoha... I'm sorry.
Aren't you lonely?
Not really. I'm not lonely at all.
I'm here with you, Yuuno.
And I'm pretty used to being alone as it is.
Ever since I was little,
I've been left alone a lot.
You see... when I was still really young,
Dad hurt himself at work,
so he couldn't leave the
hospital for a while.
We had just opened our coffee shop,
and it wasn't as popular as it is now,
so my Mom and brother were
always really busy there.
And my sister was always taking care of Dad.
So... until recently, I've been home
by myself most of the time.
So I'm pretty used to it.
I see...
Now that I think about it, I don't know too
much about your family, Yuuno.
Ah... I've always been alone from the start.
Huh? Really?
I didn't have any parents,
so I was raised by everyone in my clan.
That's why I consider everyone in
the Scrya clan to be my family.
I see...
Yuuno, once we finish things up,
let's talk like this more, okay?
Yeah. Once everything's over.
Once all of this is cleaned up...
once this Jewel Seed incident is over...
Yeah... after that, I'm sure we'll...
Emergency!
A large magical reaction has been
detected within the search parameters.
Wh-What are those kids doing down there?!
Arcus, Cultus, Aegeas...
Heavenly gods who shine over all,
descend upon us now as I guide you.
Baruel, Zaluel, Browzel...
The Jewel Seeds are probably in the ocean.
So she's going to pour
electrical energy into it,
and force activations to locate them all at once.
It'll work, but... Fate...!
Strike with piercing lightning and roar with resonant thunder...
Arcus, Cultus, Aegeas...
I found them... the remaining six!
Using this much mana...
and trying to seal all of them with her remaining strength...
Even with her talent, this is definitely beyond Fate's limits!
Arf, please support me
with spatial barriers.
Yeah! Leave it to me!
So... no matter who comes,
no matter what happens,
I will definitely protect her!
Let's go, Bardiche.
Let's give it everything we have.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
This girl is outrageously reckless!
Reckless, indeed. No doubt she'll end up destroying herself out there.
She can't handle using that much mana at once!
Fate!
Um, I'll head out right away!
There's no need. If we leave her alone
long enough, she'll finish herself off.
Even if she doesn't, we can make our
move once she's used up all her power.
But...!
Start making preparations
to capture the Seeds.
Understood.
Fate! Fate!
We can't afford to lose them now that we've found the last few.
It may seem cruel, but this is the reality of the matter.
But...
Go.
Nanoha, go!
I'll open a gate for you,
so go to that girl.
But Yuuno, the reason
I want to talk to her...
The reason I want to talk to Fate...
doesn't have anything to do with you...
That may be...
but if you're ever in trouble, Nanoha,
I want to be your strength.
Just like you were for me.
What are you–?
I'm sorry, but I, Nanoha Takamachi,
am ignoring orders and acting on my own!
I'm transferring you into
that girl's barrier!
Let's go, Raising Heart.
Wind in the sky...
Stars in the heavens...
The bright, shining light within my arms...
and an unbreakable spirit within my heart!
Raising Heart, Set up!
Stand by, ready.
Don't you dare... get in Fate's way!
No! We didn't come
here to fight you!
Yuuno!
I don't believe this!
What are you two doing?!
I'm sorry. I'll apologize
later for disobeying orders.
But I just can't leave her alone!
She's all alone!
And I know how sad it
is when you're all alone!
First, we have to stop the Jewel Seeds before
this turns into something much worse!
So for now,
let's support their sealing!
Fate!
Let's help each other
and stop the Jewel Seeds!
Power Charge.
Supplying Complete.
We'll each take care of half of them!
Yuuno and Arf are stopping
them for us! Now's our chance!
On the count of three,
we'll seal them all at the same time!
Shooting Mode.
The thing you want most when
you're feeling alone and sad...
isn't to hear, "Everything's all right,"
or the kindness of others, but rather...
Sealing Form, Set up.
Bardiche...
Divine Buster... Full Power.
You can do it, right?
All right, my master.
One, two...!
Thunder...
Divine...
Rage!
Buster!
The remaining six Jewel Seeds
have been confirmed as sealed!
Th-That was ridiculous...
But it was pretty impressive.
Understanding each other
with the same feelings...
The feelings of sadness and loneliness,
taking half of them each...
Ah, that's it... I finally understand.
I want to share them with her.
I want us to be friends.
Dimensional interference?!
A huge magical attack from another
dimension is heading straight for us all!
Ah! Six seconds until impact!
Mother?!
Fate!
Get out of...
our way!
There's only three!?
They'll go out of control!
Hurry up and capture them!
It's no good!
The dimensional attack took
out some of our systems!
25 seconds remaining before functionality returns!
We can't trace the source of the attack!
Until functionality fully returns, transfer all
power into our magic defense systems.
Yes, ma'am!
And also... retrieve Nanoha,
Yuuno, and Chrono.
Make a little wish!
Even though I'll stumble and lose my way,
as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Ah, crossing the sea of cellophane,
weaving through the forests,
and passing through the silver wind,
I was looking for something neither of us had
Ah, within a diorama of the city
I was just crying alone
until the day your warm hand
reached out to me
I felt your strong gaze
during those swaying days,
and then, at long last
I finally found the secret key
Make a little wish!
I'll gather the lemon-colored moon drops,
and shine their light
down upon on your path
Make a little wish, no matter how small!
If you say you can't do anything,
just remember that as long as you're here with me,
I can keep smiling happily
Nanoha
Next Episode Preview
The situation is
reaching its conclusion!
To weather the final storm,
everyone makes a vow within their heart.
And I tell Fate how I feel.
Next time on
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 10
Everyone's Separate Heartfelt Vows
Episode Ten:
Everyone's Separate Heartfelt Vows.
Lyrical Magical,
so I can start anew as my true self!