No!
Caw!
Hey!
Tch!
Huh?
Eren!
Eren.
Fire!
What?
Eren.
Yeah.
Here.
Sure!
I do.
Oh no.
Never!
Carla.
Armin.
Look...
Mikasa.
Mikasa!
Move it!
Oh, God.
Forever.
Shut up!
Come on.
So do I.
Hey guys!
I'm sorry.
It's gone.
That's it.
And then...
Please! No!
Impossible!
Go, go, go!
Eren, wait!
Let go of me!
No, it's not!
I'm with you.
Damn it! Stop!
What the hell?
It isn't easy.
There they are!
Don't leave us!
Retreat or die!
What're you...?
Every last one.
This is the end.
Please be alive!
Give me a break!
What's his deal?
What's the point?
Retreat! Retreat!
No. This is over.
Don't shut it yet!
Are they verified?
No! You're insane!
Glad I caught you.
I told you to stop!
There's still room!
No. The Inner Gate.
Listen to yourself!
Our hands are tied.
I'll kill them all.
Get off! Let me go!
Excuse me, my lords!
Tell me differently.
Of the 250,000 sent,
You don't have to...
That was nice of him.
Bad news travels fast.
Now I'll never get to.
You little piece o'...
What are you aiming at?
Forgive him. I beg you.
but I'm not a parasite!
Hey! What are you doing?
Nightmare. Shake it off.
All of us are parasites.
What are you waiting for?
I don't think so, friend!
Too much is handed to us!
All right. Together then.
You can't do this! Please!
That's it. We're all dead.
You cannot forget the key!
It's the way to the Truth!
One day you'll understand!
so it's an ugly situation.
I need those canons loaded!
Why did I always fight her?
I never said, "I love you."
Dad was... It felt so real.
Poor man's probably hungry.
Armin. You best have a seat.
I'm not getting left behind.
Terror spread like wildfire.
You're not making any sense!
And the following year, 846,
Stop whining and do your job!
That does it, bring 'er down!
Hours after Shiganshina fell,
The Titans are... They're in!
Why was I always such a brat?
And you will grow to hate me.
Am I a fighter, or am I feed?
Spineless cowards! All of you!
I'm not about to let her down.
Wait! Are you out of your mind?
The Titans are closing the gap!
Damn you, this is the only way!
By the way, I'd make that last.
We're parasites. We're cowards.
Punished by the justice of God."
Have you got rocks in your head?
You'll really want to hear this!
What's wrong? You see something?
I'm going to put a stop to this!
the Titans will grow to hate me.
I'm sorry, it's at full capacity!
Wall Maria's been broken through.
Eren! Stay with me, boy! Wake up!
Or am I gonna be the one to bite?
Our house. It's all gone. Forever.
Not exactly a dignified existence.
To do what? Get killed by a Titan?
not even two hundred made it back.
I'm worse. When push came to shove,
It's the same thing all over again.
C'mon! They're headed right for us!
At least let our children on board!
Stop it! Please, you're scaring me!
Whatever you do, you must reach it!
Just ignore it. There's a shortage.
Run away and take what we're given?
Your mom didn't ask us to be brave.
Eat it. She asked us to stay alive.
We have to find a way to stop them.
Straighten those spines, piss-ants!
the Mountain holds no greater pain!"
Hurry up! Keep your eye on the Gate!
I wouldn't try to call out just now.
Because I'm a kid. Because I'm weak.
This isn't real. This is a nightmare.
We've gotta get the hell out of here!
We have to stand on our own two feet!
Have you looked in the mirror lately?
This world will never feel like home.
Right now, you're nothing. Livestock.
'cause here's where you ask yourself:
God help us. God help us. God help us.
Yeah? What're you tying to do, starve?
To become strong enough to fight back.
I was too frightened to hold my ground.
What are the rest of us supposed to do?
Hey. It's okay. You were just dreaming.
Damn it! I'm not trying to drag you in.
Unless you can transmute it into skill.
And driven e'en as a plough by avarice."
Stop dragging your feet! Snap out of it!
Shut the gate, now! We're being charged!
Mom's death pushed you off the deep end!
Now it's where they corral the refugees.
Guess we gotta beef up the herd, though.
You seen one? You seen what they can do?
I'd never seen what they could do to us!
Look at us! What choice do we have here?
Don't take your shortcomings out on him.
Upon the penance of these writhing souls,
every right, so justice here doth chain."
You don't have to! Just give me your arm!
You son of a bitch! We could've saved her!
In terrified haste, The Central Government
But the cold, hard ground yielded nothing.
fraught, fixed, earthen in heart and limb."
Your mother died because I'm a damn coward!
declared the Outlier Districts a lost cause
You don't... You don't know what it's like!
So that's it? This is just the way life is?
The 104th Cadet Corps Boot Camp starts now!
you'll learn to take down your own Goliath.
We're dead and standing at the gate of Hell.
I don't understand what you're trying to do!
Pride be damned; we do what we must to live.
Our lives will never be our own until we do.
They first appeared over a hundred years ago.
"Where covetousness leads, thou sees't bourn.
We almost had her out! Why did you come? Why?
In case you hadn't noticed, we're all hungry.
When are you gonna get sick of their charity?
A few days later, throngs of starved refugees
But over the next three, soul-crushing years,
"As greed has drowned our love for every good,
"Tethered, captive, are; merged with the clay.
Because every last one of us is a damn coward!
I can't do this. I'm going back to Wall Maria.
To hell with all of 'em! Here. I'm going back!
While it did nothing to drive back the Titans,
Next year I'll be applying to join the Cadets.
I will. Just keeping an eye out for my friends.
Look, there's nothing we can do! Push off, now!
You gonna give me attitude or you gonna reload?
"Now, thou behold'st, am I here punished for it.
These things aren't gonna give you a head start!
Oww! Damn it! You picked the wrong man, asshole!
He's sorry! He didn't mean it; he's just hungry.
We couldn't run from certain death without help.
Titans are at the top of the food chain. Period.
and decreed all mankind retreat behind Wall Rose.
every night for the rest of your miserable lives.
The survivors erected Walls Maria, Rose, and Sina;
"'Til then a man apart from God. O wretched was I.
And thus to remain so long as it pleases The Lord:
All I've had for two days is a moldy bit of crust!
nearly twenty percent of the surviving population,
The calculated design flaw in all Outlier Districts
We can't let the Titans get through the Inner Gate.
Tell your buddy a little gratitude goes a long way.
The Titans have to pay for what they've done to us.
For god's sake, we can't even find food on our own.
Look, there's no point in following me to my death!
We've still got people out there! Give 'em a chance!
They're handing out food rations near the warehouse.
Giant, humanoid creatures with a taste for our blood.
Eat up, the Titans like a little meat on their bones!
Bastard. I'm not about to show gratitude to a coward!
Training is gonna be a white-knuckle ride through Hell.
"What else may heav'nly grace do for sins as ours?" Huh?
Yeah. And if I can help it, then it won't be your death.
We're soldiers; we don't get to decide who lives or dies!
I say we make appeals to the Central Government for help.
They were already dealing with famine before we got here,
Remember this moment when you come face to face with him,
Oh, I'm a fighter, alright. And before I'm done with 'em,
There's nothing you could've done for her, you understand?
Hey, now. You're not serious; that's your stomach talking.
Allow me to introduce myself: I'm Commandant Keith Sadies;
We were shoved to the brink
of extinction almost overnight.
That outcropping has held for
a century; it makes no sense.
We all get that way; speak
our minds out of turn sometimes?
Give 'em their space. God only
knows what they've just seen.
Damn it all. Any way it's
sliced the situation is untenable.
I think this used to be where
they stored all the dry goods.
Hard truth: Passion's no
guarantee you'll stick the landing.
There've been at least five-hundred
accounted for in the boats.
The question is how prepared
are we if Shiganshina is in ruins?
Nothin' more gratifyin' than
seein' your rations go to animals.
No personal belongings! We need
to make as much room as possible!
Yeah, well. Keep in mind who's
givin' up their share so you can eat.
Oughta keep you in cages. Shove
you out to the frontlines as a buffer.
"For we lifted not our eye to heights
bequeathed, and like the plou... "
Wake up! The guys standing between
us and them are just a bunch of talk!
were put to plough in the wastelands
as a last-ditch effort to raise food.
Grandpa scrounged a little extra by
telling the powers-that-be he had kids.
Am I gonna be ground up to pulpy human
grist 'tween boulder-sized incisors.
When you're floored by fundamentals
all the heart in the world means nothing.
their sacrifice did at least lessen
the effects of famine within the Interior.
Estimates held that nearly ten-thousand
lives were lost to the Titan offensive.
Drop everything, find the ferry nearest
you and climb aboard for all you're worth!
Sir. With respect, they're old as sin
and not designed for accuracy to begin with!
The brute strength of these aberrations
trumped an average person's many times over.
If I've done my job, you'll be waking up
in a cold sweat from memories of this place
There's nothing you could've done for her,
you understand? You're a kid; you're weak.
If that happens, the handful of lives left
out there'll be the least of our problems!
every man, woman, and child within the
Interior knew the unthinkable had come to pass.
That, and this far in there's a greater
disparity between the haves and the have-nots.
I know I used to think our future was beyond
the walls. But it's like you told that man.
Whether or not they're verified. The refugees
are certainly flooding in like plague rats.
withdrawing behind them in frightened huddles
for what was to be a century of uneasy peace.
What do you think we're meant to make of these
reports of Shiganshina falling to the Titans?
Come now. Surely Wall Maria is enough on its
own to hold the Titans at bay, don't you think?
We can damn-well leave! If you wanna scrape
by on the charity of cowards, that's your thing,
So-called Outlier Districts like Shiganshina jut
out like thorns at vital spots along Wall Maria.
the remaining refugees old enough to serve in
the military were tasked with reclaiming Wall Maria.
There aren't enough resources for the whole human race
to retreat behind the next wall if they break through!
is that they have only a single gate
through which its citizens are able to
retreat deeper inward should the need arise.
Their basic function is to streamline troop dispersal
and keep security costs down by
drawing Titans into specific areas.