ONE PUNCH
THREE, TWO, ONE, KILL SHOT
JOIN THE FIGHT, CERTAIN VICTORY, THE STRONGEST EVER
SANJOU, HISSHOU, SHIJOU SAIKYOU
WHAT WAS THAT? FRUSTRATION
NAN DATTEN DA? FRUSTRATION
THERE'S NO STOPPING ME
ORE WA TOMARANAI
ONE PUNCH, IT'S OVER, VICTORY AFTER VICTORY
ONE PUNCH, KANRYOU, RENSENRENSHOU
I WIN, I ALWAYS WIN, OVERWHELMINGLY
ORE WA KATSU, TSUNE NI KATSU, ASSHOU
POWER, GET POWER
RIGHT TO THE VERY LIMIT
GIRIGIRI GENKAI MADE
HERO
PEOPLE SHOWER ME WITH PRAISE
ORE O TATAERU KOE YA
BUT I DON'T DO THIS FOR THE FAME
KASSAI NANTE HOSHIKU WA NAI SA
HERO
SO I JUST FIGHT EVIL IN SECRET
DAKARA HITOSHIREZU AKU TO TATAKAU
(NOBODY KNOWS WHO HE IS)
COUNTLESS ENEMIES FILL THE SKY
SORA OOI OSHIYOSERU TEKI
BUT I WON'T TURN MY BACK AND FLEE
ORE WA SE WO MUKE WA SHINAI
HERO
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND AND I WON'T GIVE IN
NARABA YURUGINAKI KAKUGO SHITA TAME
A FIGHTING HERO
TATAKAU HERO
A SOLITARY HERO
KODOKU NA HERO
I WANNA BE THE STRONGEST HERO
I WANNA BE A SAIKYOU HERO