Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well.
Do you have a rival?
Someone you don't want to lose to,
whether it's in sports, school,
or some lessons you're taking.
With feelings like that,
we improve very quickly, right?
As for myself, I aspired
to be like Miss Layla,
and so I've kept motivating
myself to perform better until now.
I've been trying not to lose to
myself, and I've kept working hard,
but I've never really thought that
I don't want to lose to someone else.
But, since May joined Kaleido Stage...
This is not the time to say things like this.
It's not! It's not!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts*
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Dracula?
That's right. Dracula.
It just flashed across my mind
when I was looking at Leon.
I thought this had to be our new production!
Is it a horror story?
Horror story?
That means there won't be any gags.
Of course...
Not!
"The Amazing Passionate Rival."
Even though it's a horror story,
it's also a mysterious
and beautiful love story.
Love story?
That's right.
Wandering around night after night
looking for beautiful women's blood:
--Count Dracula!
--What? What?
A beautiful woman who's attracted
to him, even while she's afraid of him:
--Mina Murray!
--What? What? What? What?
--Guided by fate,
the two get together!
--It's so romantic!
--Don't take this the wrong way, Sora!
--This is beyond my control...
--This is good, Mia.
We've never done
anything like this before, right?
Hearing you say that
gives me a little confidence.
After all, this was the first time
I wrote a script imagining somebody.
Yeah, but there are no gags!
Mina Murray...
If Miss Layla played her role,
it would have been wonderful!
Sora,
you're the Kaleido Star now.
I know.
But my time was decreased again yesterday.
I wrote Mina Murray's
character thinking of you.
Of me?
I even have a new spin maneuver,
since those are your specialty.
If Leon sees your Mina Murray,
even he can't say he
wants to decrease your time.
After all, Leon decided to stay here
after saying that he was leaving for France.
So I don't think it's like
he doesn't acknowledge you.
Be confident.
That's right.
Thank you.
You're right.
To answer Miss Layla's
expectations, I should...
For the first time,
I aspired to be like somebody.
I want to appear on stage with Sora!
I have to work hard for Rosetta too.
After all, she came to Kaleido Stage
because she wants to be like you.
What's Rosetta doing?
She's in her room, studying.
In her room?
Since she has work, she said she's
always been tutored by a computer.
I heard she's never been to school.
I see.
It seems like she has to go through a lot.
Mia, thank you.
I'm honored.
Go, Sora.
What do you think, Leon?
I think it's interesting, but...
I'm Dracula?
Yes. What do you think?
This is the first time someone
captured me in this light.
Okay...
So, um... In other words?
I'll ask you to revise it,
but I don't mind doing it.
What? Really?!
Congratulations, Mia!
Thanks!
Good job, Mia!
--I did it! Thank you!
--Getting Mr. Leon's okay,
you're something else.
I feel so good!
Revise it right now.
Yes. Where should I revise?
Get rid of Mina Murray.
Get rid of her? You mean, completely?
Of course.
Excuse me...
Mina Murray's climax, Screw Spin,
is a very difficult maneuver,
but I think Sora can pull it off.
And I think the audience will enjoy
watching the maneuver as a main highlight.
Satisfy me instead of the audience.
If you can't do it, I'll handle
the leading role by myself.
Please see my Screw Spin.
I'm sure I can show you a
performance that will satisfy you.
Double door open!
May...
You can't do it!
Only one person can satisfy Mr. Leon.
The next Layla Hamilton, me!
Wait.
From the beginning,
I wrote this role thinking of Sora...
So what?
It's natural that the person who has
the best abilities should get the role.
So, naturally, this role is mine!
She's so selfish.
I'll give you until tomorrow.
I don't care which one. Satisfy me.
Until tomorrow...
I'm not saying you have to.
Oh, no, please leave it to me!
I'll prepare the swing for practice tonight.
Finally, the time to compete has come.
Even though he said we have one day,
there's only one practice swing.
In short, I can actually
practice only a half day.
With her abilities, May may be
able to master the Screw Spin.
But I cannot allow myself to lose this game!
I will win the game by all means.
Now that Miss Layla's gone, the
one who'll be the Kaleido Star is me.
It can be no one else!
Anna?! What's wrong?!
What are you doing?!
Powerful Pushing!
What the heck?
It's Feng Shui.
What?
If I move into this room
for today and tomorrow,
I'll have a better chance
of winning the duel.
So?
So I will move into this room.
But it's only for today and tomorrow.
Well, I have to bring in my stuff.
Fire Cooking!
In order to win the duel,
I need the heat of fire.
Doing stir-fry is the best for that.
So there you have it.
It's a Chinese dish for this morning's menu.
A Chinese dish in the early morning?
Greasy Chinese?
Isn't it good once in a while?
May was kind enough to cook for us. So...
Hey, so she only cooked for herself?
Uh...
I will cook for everybody now.
So, please wait for a little while.
Good morning.
So that's the swing for the Screw Spin?
Somehow, I made it in time.
Grand Screw Jump!
It was close.
In just one hour, she
managed to get to that point.
It's supposed to be a
pretty difficult maneuver.
So she's not all talk.
Sora could also get that far
easily if she practiced for an hour.
Yeah...
I don't know if I can do
it, but I have to try.
You're supposed to take turns every
hour, so it's your turn next hour, Sora.
Okay.
May, your hour's up!
Switch with Sora.
Sorry. I won't.
What?
Do... Do you understand what I said?
Because I came here one
hour early and started practicing.
That's because breakfast was late...
Yet you shamelessly show
up now, trying to practice.
You're so naïve!
So, you will not let Sora practice?
Is that the only way you can win?!
Yeah, you're a coward!
This is not some swing in a park.
Why do I have to take turns?!
I don't remember agreeing
to anything like that!
But, usually...
Don't they usually say,
"First come, first served"?
This world is controlled
by the law of the jungle.
First of all,
Mr. Leon doesn't acknowledge you at all.
I think I'm the only one
who should take the test.
It's shameful to think he asked
you to take the test out of pity.
You're so awful!
I cannot believe you said that!
Sora, why don't you say something to her?!
May's right.
I'm not acknowledged by Mr. Leon.
But still, I want to do what
I can to make Kaleido Stage better.
So I'm going to take
tomorrow's test by all means.
I intend to attempt it with all my might.
I consider you a friend who's
going to create Kaleido Stage with me.
That's why I want to...
Stop it!
A friend?
That's ridiculous!
Just looking at your face makes me sick.
I hate you!
Every single thing you do is disappointing.
How?
How?!
How can you be the one who performed the
legendary great maneuver with Miss Layla?!
If I were there, without a doubt,
Miss Layla would have chosen me too.
Yet...
May...
I will not be outdone by you!
By taking this upcoming test, I'll prove
to everyone that I'm better than you!
How can you be the one who performed the
legendary great maneuver with Miss Layla?!
If I were there, without a doubt,
Miss Layla would have chosen me too.
Yet...
That time...
That time, Miss Layla and
I were real partners.
I was positive there was nobody
else who could be Miss Layla's partner
and perform the legendary
great maneuver except me.
That time...
Please be my dream, Sora.
I know you can become a true Kaleido Star.
I wonder if I'm able to be
a true Kaleido Star, Fool...
It's up to you, Sora.
What is a true Kaleido Star?
Even I don't know the answer to that.
That's something you must find for yourself.
However, the only thing
certain is that you can see me.
Sora? Please come for a second.
Ken...
This... this is the swing for the Screw Spin.
Sora!
Sorry, since I put this together so quickly,
it doesn't have enough height, but...
Yo-ho!
Go, Sora!
Don't get beaten by somebody like May.
Amazing.
Everyone helped build
this just for you, Sora.
For me?
That's right. After all,
I still want you to play Mina Murray.
It's mortifying if you lose without
even having a chance to practice.
Mia... Anna...
Ready?
Sora is a Kaleido Star!
So, are you motivated now?
Yes!
Thank you, everyone!
--That's Sora for you!
--Always quick to recover.
It's all thanks to you guys.
I'll do my best.
That's right, I don't have
time to doubt myself.
I just have to do it!
What's with this swing?!
Even someone like Sora is having
a hard time grasping the timing.
First, she needs to get
used to this special swing.
Oh, I see.
This swing turns around easily.
But once it starts turning, it can't stop.
It spins too fast.
I don't know the timing
of when I should jump out.
But May was able to master
it this far in only one hour.
So... If I don't work hard now,
I won't be able to face everyone
who's expecting me to do well.
Furthermore,
I'll end up disappointing Miss Layla
who acknowledged me as a partner!
I'm almost there, but...
Sora's Sagittarius.
May's Taurus.
Leon's Scorpio.
It is a beautiful balance.
But if this balance is lost...
Someone will fall to the ground.
--I did it.
--One more time...
--Until I can do it perfectly...
All right, let's go.
Wha--
What?
I feel like I have a fever.
I wonder if it's because of the rain.
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
I just have to do it. I have to! I have to!
All right, we're going to start testing now.
First, Sora.
Yes.
Oh, no.
My body feels heavy. I've got chills.
Anyhow, I have to give this
my best shot. I have to! I have to!
What?
Oh, no... I'm getting dizzy.
I won!
As I thought, that's all you've got!
You were not supposed
to be Miss Layla's partner.
Now I'll show you how a
real Kaleido Star performs.
Beautiful...
Wait, Mr. Leon!
How was my performance?
I passed, right?
It's not even worth discussing.
Why?! I didn't make a mistake!
I practiced so hard!
My performance was better than Sora's!
I don't understand!
Mr. Leon.
He never practiced the Screw Spin...
I wonder if he can do a proper
performance without practice.
Amazing...
Why are you so full of yourself
just because you beat her?
You want to be my partner?
Then shine as brilliantly
as I do. Can you do it?
No...
Our level is too different.
Sora, you have a fever, don't you?
Oh, yes. But, it's not that bad.
Are you kidding?
It's true. Your face is red, Sora.
That's why you failed, isn't it?
Oh... Nothing like that.
Rewrite the script for Dracula.
I will be the only star in the show.
Mr. Leon, Sora has a fever.
--That has nothing to do with this.
--She practiced in the rain yesterday.
--Please give her one more chance.
--It's not because of my temperature.
--Please.
--Everyone, really, you don't need to...
You're all lukewarm.
So lukewarm, you make me sick.
Who knew Kaleido Stage was a
place with such a lukewarm attitude?
I finally understand why Layla
Hamilton chose you for her partner.
Ultimately, it means Layla Hamilton
was also a lukewarm performer like that.
She was a half-baked top star who
couldn't lose her rich girl attitude.
She couldn't be tough on others or herself.
In the end, that she chose
someone like you as a partner
means she was beyond recovery.
I think an easy place like Kaleido
Stage was a perfect place for her.
You know nothing!
You know nothing about her!
I won't let you say that about Miss Layla!
Sora!
--You can say whatever you want about me,
--Sora!
--Calm down!
--but Miss Layla isn't like that!
--Sora!
Apologize!
Apologize! Apologize!
Apologize to Miss Layla.
Apologize!
I'm mortified.
Miss Layla was labeled
like that because of me.
I have no choice but to work harder.
So everyone thinks I'm a
worthy partner for Miss Layla.
I found something I have to do.
For that, I'll make that man...
I'll make Leon...
acknowledge me...
I'll make him acknowledge me as a partner!
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on*
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation,
I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell
phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
"Next Kaleido Star: New Wings"
I'll show him when I'm truly shining!
And so, the audition I did
this time was a disappointment.
Wait a second, Sora.
May still hasn't given up yet.
Now she's saying that she'll
express herself by skating.
I've never skated before.
Well, this is not time to
say this! It's not! It's not!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Amazing Match On Ice."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...