[METAL SCRAPING]
[BRADLEY AND GREED GRUNTING]
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
Darling!
You and Selim, stay back!
Well... Maybe you
can explain this, Wrath.
[GREED]
What the hell is
happening to me?
Why am I seeing these things?
They keep clawing
at the inside of my skull!
And why are you there?
Why do I remember you, Bradley?!
Tell me!
Why did you destroy
my possessions?!
You miss your things?
[BRADLEY]
You're a foolish pack rat
clinging to garbage, Greed.
Quit craving the past!
Bastard!
[CUP SHATTERS]
[SWORD CUTS THROUGH THE AIR]
[PLATE SHATTERS]
[GREED YELLS IN AGONY]
[GREED YELLS]
[GREED SCREAMS]
[SWORD CUTS THROUGH THE AIR]
[SWORD BREAKS]
[WINDOW SHATTERS]
[BUTLER]
Fuhrer Bradley!
Madam Bradley...!
Are you and Selim alright?
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
Ye... yes.
[BUTLER]
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
He overpowered
the security patrol.
[BRADLEY]
Yes. I'm not surprised...
He came close
to overpowering me.
Oh, my.
[OLIVIER]
Father...
I demand you retire.
Oh, Olivier.
[PHILLIP]
It's been years since
we've last seen one another
and that's all
you have to say to me?
[OLIVIER]
I'll head
the family from now on.
You should spend
your final doddering,
frail years in comfort.
Thank you for your concern.
But I had planned to
make Alex my successor.
You mean that
sniveling jellyfish...?
Leave the family
affairs to me.
Why not take a long
vacation in a foreign land?
Alex as the head...?
Would you truly be able
to relax leaving things to him?
[SOMEONE KNOCKS AT THE DOOR]
Olivier.
I didn't know you
had planned to visit.
[PHILLIP]
Ohhhh, Alex...
Perfect timing!
Oh?
Engage your sister in combat.
Huh?
[PHILLIP]
The victor shall earn my
title as head of the family.
Do you find this
acceptable, Olivier?
Yes.
I'd have it no other way.
[PHILLIP]
Olivier insists that I retire
and take a sojourn
in a foreign land.
She what?
How can you treat
Father with such insolence?
For shame.
You've given me no choice!
Understand, sister...
I intend to use every ounce of
my body and soul to fight you.
[ARMSTRONG'S FOOT
SLAMS ON THE FLOOR]
Don't patronize me, Alex...
Your bloated muscles are
worthless without a spine.
[OLIVIER AND ARMSTRONG GRUNTING]
Shall we prepare
for our respite?
- Yes.
[OLIVIER]
Get over here!
So, which exotic
locale might you suggest?
Well, I'm intrigued to
see what Xing is like...
I've heard that they have
tantalizing cuisine there.
Then Xing it is...
Fine with you, Catherine?
Sure...
Sounds exciting.
[DOOR BENDS AND BREAKS OPEN]
[ARMSTRONG YELLS]
[ARMSTRONG]
Nooo...! Enouuuugh!
Please...! Mercy!
[OLIVIER]
No take-backs, Alex!
Are you trying to kill me?
What tipped
you off, moron?
Try to hang
in there, Alex.
[ARMSTRONG GRUNTS]
[CATHERINE]
What sort of souvenirs
should we bring back for them?
[PHILLIP]
Statues seem the most fitting...
Large and solid statues.
Well in that case,
I want a statue too, then.
Oh?
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ARMSTRONG YELLS]
[CAR ACCELERATING]
[ARMSTRONG]
Nooooooo!
[ARMSTRONG SLAMS INTO FIREPLACE]
[ARMSTRONG GRUNTING IN AGONY]
And that settles that.
[SWORD SCRAPES SHEATH]
[ARMSTRONG GRUNTING]
I'm the rightful successor.
The family belongs to me.
[ARMSTRONG]
Olivier...
Why have you become so convivial
with the senior officers?
How can you...?
The senior staff is in league--
I can determine their
complicity with my own eyes.
And what have
your eyes seen...?
Have you exiled Mother
and Father to a foreign land,
so they can't
be taken hostage?
Get out, loser...
You'll stink up my
mansion with your cowardice.
[STEAM RELEASES]
[HALLING]
And where are you
headed, young lady?
You're walking straight
towards the edge of town...
And there's nothing but
desert for hundreds of miles.
Well, I... I'm traveling
back to my own country.
Oh, yeah?
Yes... I'm from Xing.
Across the desert?
Uh-huh.
Wait, you mean
you're gonna
cross the desert
all by yourself?
Yeah.
[CROWD GASPS]
Alright, everyone.
[HALLING]
Let's help her out.
Hand over any extra food.
You don't need to--
[KAYAL]
Hey, don't
worry about it.
Why don't you leave tomorrow?
Stay the night and
get some good rest.
You're more than
welcome to use our bath.
We can make
you some dinner.
[HALLING]
What about you, Steve...?
You've got some empty rooms
now. Why don't you put her up?
[STEVE]
Yeah, sure thing...
She'd be nice and comfy
in Emmy's old room.
[MAN 1]
Did Emmy already leave
for college in Central?
I guess the apple falls pretty
far from the tree after all.
[STEVE]
I guess so.
We'll have to feed your
adorable little kitty, too.
[SHAO MAY YELPS]
Oh! She's certainly hungry.
I get the feeling that
she thinks you're her food.
Oh, hush. Don't be silly...
You don't eat
people, do you, kitty?
[SHAO MAY YELPS]
Y'see...? She said
you look delicious.
[CROWD LAUGHS]
[ENVY]
They sure are nice, huh?
And you don't even
wanna help them?
Well, that's probably
for the best...
I do wonder...
What's your emperor gonna think
when you hand over
a half-dead Homunculus?
I doubt it's gonna do
your clan much good.
But you could
go to Central...
I mean, that's
where you can learn
the true way to
gain immortality...
You could even help save
all of these people's lives.
Oh, well...
Why should you care if
they live or die anyway?
It's not like it's
your country or anything.
[SHAO MAY SQUEALING]
[MAY CHANG]
I'm sorry. Thank you
so much for your kindness!
Wait, where are you going?
[MAY CHANG]
I've gotta get
back to Central!
I've got some
unfinished business!
[ENVY THINKING]
Heh, Idiot...
I'm gonna stuff you in
a jar once we get to Central.
I just need
a Philosopher's Stone...
After that,
I'll be whole again...
Just wait 'til I get a stone.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[DARIUS]
Where are we?
[ED]
We've used this place
as a hideout before.
And you're positive
that your brother's here?
Oh, yeah...
I know Al better
than he knows himself.
This is the only
place he would be.
[DARIUS]
Hey...
There's nobody here!
Yeah, you really
know your brother.
We busted our tails for hundreds
of miles for an empty house?
[HEINKEL SNIFFS]
[HEINKEL COCKS GUN]
[DARIUS GASPS]
[APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS]
[ED STAMMERS]
[BODY THUDS
ONTO THE FLOOR]
Ling...! I mean, Greed!
[LING'S STOMACH GROWLS]
Hungry... Need, food.
Heh... No, it's Ling.
[LING EATING QUICKLY]
[LING LAUGHING]
Well, that
did the trick!
Thanks, Edward...
You're too kind.
[ED]
It's amazing that
you're not a giant fat-ass.
He ate all
of our rations.
Are you gonna
introduce me to your pals?
That's Mr. Gorill--
My name's Darius!
And I'm Heinkel...
We're ex-military...
But we wound up getting stuck
working with this kid somehow.
Now what's
this guy's story?
Well, let's see.
It's really kind of complicated.
I'm a Homunculus.
- Huh?
Can you try to
be more discrete?!
Seriously?!
It'll take too
long to explain...
And what are you doing here,
I thought you'd be in Central.
Well, to put it lightly,
Greed had a falling out
with the other Homunculi...
So I took advantage
of his confusion,
and managed to regain
control of my body.
I had to get
out of Central...
And needed someplace
close by to hide... So I--
[LING WINCING IN PAIN]
What's the matter?
It's Greed...
He's starting to fight back.
[ED]
Hey!
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
Fight him back you idiot!
Don't let him overpower you!
Jeez!
Listen... That guy
beneath Central...
The one that they
call their father...
He's gonna open the portal...
On the "day of reckoning."
I could be
wrong about this...
...but I think you and Al
should jump in when he does.
It's the best chance you have
to get your bodies back.
[ED GASPS]
Wait a minute. That makes
sense and everything but...
...there's a toll that must
be paid to even open the portal.
[ED GASPS]
[ED THINKING]
And why...? Why is
he opening the portal?
[ED]
This "day of reckoning"...
Do you know the exact
day he's gonna open it?
It's happening--
[LING WINCING IN PAIN]
Ling?
C'mon!
Damn it... I can't
hold him much longer.
The message...
You got it to Lan Fan, right?
You gave her the message?
The message...?
Al gave it to her...
And she's doing alright...
I don't know where
she is, but she's safe.
Thank you, Ed.
That's good to hear.
[LING WINCING IN PAIN]
Ling!
[LING]
Sorry...
That's it for me... I'm gone.
[GREED GRUNTS]
Damn...
Pain in the ass prince.
He needs to learn to
keep his big mouth shut.
[ED]
Is that you, Greed?
Yeah, what
tipped you off?
[GUN COCKS]
[GREED]
Don't bother...
You can't even
scratch me with that thing.
[ED STAMMERS]
[GREED]
Well, see ya later.
Hey!
Aren't you gonna
try to capture us?
Huh?
Were you even listening to
anything the prince told you?
I'm working on
my solo career now.
All these memories
came flooding back,
and I kind of went
nuts and attacked Bradley.
Who knows what they'd do
to me if I go crawling back...
And I don't really
work well with others,
so it's probably for the best.
And that's that.
Why don't you
team up with us?
[FLOORBOARD SQUEAKS]
[DARIUS AND HEINKEL]
Huh?!
You've got nowhere to go.
Why not come with us?
[GREED LAUGHS]
[GREED]
Team up with you...?
You want me to follow you?
Thanks for the laugh.
Up yours, kid...
This world is my
possession, not yours.
[GREED]
Now it's a different story
if you wanna follow me...
You're welcome
to join my team.
[GREED LAUGHING]
Later.
[GREED THINKING]
Team up with him?
Do I look that desperate?
It doesn't matter how
many souls I've got in me.
I'm completely alone now.
[LING]
If you're gonna pout about it,
why don't you join up with Ed?
But if you want more, you could
always give me my body back.
I'll take my place
as emperor of Xing...
That should be enough
to fill up your emptiness.
[GREED]
The ruler of
a whole country?
[LING]
Not bad, huh?
[GREED]
Get over it...
You think too small.
That's just not enough.
Now ruler of the world?
I could enjoy that.
The whole world?
[ED]
Hey! Ling...! Wait up!
[GREED]
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'm Greed, not Ling.
It's too difficult
to keep track of...
I'll just call you
Greeling from now on.
No...! You will not--
Listen to me, Greeling...
I'll follow you.
Huh?
I thought about it
and I've decided to
join your team after all...
And since these guys seem
to follow me everywhere,
you've got two chimeras
on your team as well.
[DARIUS GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[DARIUS]
Who do you think you are?!
You don't get to make that call!
[HEINKEL]
Nobody said you were our boss,
pipsqueak! You little runt!
Uhh...
[ED]
I realized something...
I've been a follower ever since
I became a dog of the military.
I lost my pride a while back.
So I'm already used to
rolling over on command...
And besides...
There's too much at stake.
I can't let any
information you've got
slip through the cracks.
[ED LAUGHS]
I really can't let
my ego get in the way.
[GREED]
What a waste...
You lose your temper like this
and you're gonna lose my
information and your brother.
[GREED LAUGHS]
Alright, kid.
But workin' for me means you
haveta' live in the shadows...
I don't wanna
hear any regrets.
Give me a break.
I've already got
a million regrets.
What's one more?
- A million and one.
[GREED]
Good, then it's settled...
So then you guys are
working for me too.
[HEINKEL]
Doesn't seem like
we have much choice.
[DARIUS]
I don't care who I follow
as long as they're feeding me.
So what kind of
Chimeras are you?
[DARIUS]
I'm part gorilla.
[HEINKEL]
I'm part lion.
Heh, well
that's pretty cool.
[ED THINKING]
Oh, yeah... I've still
got Winry's earrings.
I get the feeling
that I won't be seeing
Winry or Al for a while.
The "day of reckoning", huh?
[MASON]
I've told you. You don't
have to keep coming back.
I'll call you when Mrs. Izumi
returns from her trip.
I can't get any work done with
you guys constantly bugging me.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Hello, Curtis Butcher Shop...
Oh, yes, it's almost ready...
Five o'clock is fine.
[SOLDIER 1]
We'll be back.
Well maybe you could
buy something next time!
Sorry 'bout that...
The military's pretty
desperate to find you... Yeah.
I've got a message
for you from Alphonse
and some man
named Hohenheim.
[CAR ACCELERATING]
[SIG]
I see.
That sounds like
it's pretty serious.
Yeah... I'll pass it on.
[PHONE CLICKS]
The "day of reckoning", huh?
[SCATTERED GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIER 2]
Report to headquarters at once!
This is lookout post B!
We're under attack!
[HQ]
What...? Is it Drachma?
We're not sure!
[HQ]
How many of them are there?
Just one!
[HQ]
Just one...? Are you sure?
[SOLDIER 2 SCREAMS]
[HQ]
Hey...! Are you still there?!
Point B...! Who's attacking?!
A housewife!
[MILES]
An attack on the mountain patrol
by a mysterious woman...
It's just the same as those
attacks twenty years ago.
This doesn't look good
for the mountain patrol.
[BUCCANEER]
General Armstrong's gonna
kill us when she gets back.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 1]
Major Miles.
[MILES]
At ease.
[IZUMI]
Well look at this! An Ishvalan
with dark glasses and sideburns,
and a big guy with a Mohawk...
You look just like
they said you would.
I was starting to wonder
how long I'd have
to wait for you guys.
Why don't you
tell us who you are?
I'm no one special. Just
a housewife passing through...
But I do have a message
for you from Alphonse.
[BUCCANEER GRUNTS]
Where can we talk in private?
[FALMAN]
Yes sir.
It's a message
from Alphonse Elric.
It's about that day...
"The Promised Day."
Ah, yes...
The "day of reckoning"...
Your timing
couldn't be better.
This is certainly
getting interesting.
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUMMAN]
Hello there, Rebecca!
Your aim is looking fine,
but not nearly as
fine as your tushie.
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
What do you think you're
doing, General Grumman?!
[GRUMMAN LAUGHS]
You've gotta keep your
guard up on the battlefield.
But seriously...
You're friends with
Lieutenant Hawkeye, correct?
Huh?
Hey Riza! Yoo-hoo! Over here!
Long time no see, Rebecca.
[DOG BARKS]
[REBECCA]
I caught wind of
a rumor that they're gonna
postpone the North versus
East training exercises.
That little border skirmish
between Drachma and Briggs
has thrown everything off.
[HAWKEYE]
They've actually decided to hold
the drills in the east instead.
I heard that from
the Fuhrer himself.
Aww...
It's not fair that you
got Colonel Mustang
and now the Fuhrer.
I think it's time you set me
up with a nice guy from Central.
[DOG BARKS]
[HAWKEYE]
Here. This is the
nicest guy I know.
Oh, Hayate! How can your master
be so cold-blooded and cruel?
[BELLS CHIMING]
Don't doubt me, Riza!
I'm gonna find a nice guy
and quit this lousy job!
If you say so...
Good luck with that.
[REBECCA GASPS]
Make sure to tell
Lieutenant Havoc I said hello.
[HAWKEYE]
You got it.
See ya!
[DOG WHINES]
[HAWKEYE LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Well now... She wants me
to say "Hi." to Havoc? Huh...
[HAVOC]
I'm waiting for
my condition to stabilize.
But I'm thinking about
transferring back east.
Really...? We'll
miss you around here.
I wish I had a better
going away gift,
but I'm sure
you'll like this.
Here you go...
Only one per day, though.
Aw, thanks, Lieutenant!
And I was just about to run out.
I'll drop in again soon.
Thank you.
Oh.
Rebecca wanted me
to say hello for her.
Okay, great.
[HAWKEYE]
Oh, and tell
the Colonel that I said hi.
Okey-doke.
You heard the lady.
She says hi.
Was it really
necessary that you hide?
[ROY]
She and I are both under
constant surveillance...
It'll arouse far too much
suspicion if I have any
private contact with her.
[HAVOC EXHALES]
Oh, yeah... You look like
you could use one too, Colonel.
No thanks...
I better take off.
Oh, trust me,
you can use this one.
Hmm...
[ROY]
Be prepared for
the coming spring.
When the Promised Day arrives...
The north and the east
will make their move.
[NARRATOR]
After the new year has
passed and spring is upon us,
their resolution will evolve and
take the form of a revolution.
And now the young man
will follow his heart
straight into the lion's den.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 46:
"Looming Shadows."
The heart is capable of moving
past the pain of separation...
...as long as one keeps
moving forward as well.