When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
The government will be
addressing the nation shortly
to make an important announcement.
Please leave your TV on and stand
by without changing the channel.
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like
this exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the
wrong idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong, loving
bond between servant and mistress.
Wait! And you just start the opening
like there's nothing going on?
I mean, what's this important announcement?!
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naïve and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
Sure, Amuro May Have Had a
Place to Return to, But...
What? M-Miss...
I have chosen my words carefully, Persian.
What did you just say, Miss?
But you did not.
I told you, you don't have to work anymore.
This is Sparta's answer!
This is blasphemy! Madness!
Hey, now, what are you looking so down for?
Is that to say that you're firing me?
Huh? No, no, that's not it.
You barely managed to pass that
test the other day, right?
What?
If you fail the upcoming finals,
you'll seriously be on thin ice,
so I'm saying you can take a
break from your butler duties
and focus on your studies
until the exams are over.
Wh-What are you saying, Miss?!
I-I can handle that much!
You needn't show such concern.
Then shall we say that you'll get
fired if your grades are bad?
Well?
Why not graciously accept her offer?
Maria...
It is a great kindness that your
mistress is showing you, after all.
Right?
Well, just study hard without
straining yourself.
Right...
But in exchange!
I expect you to play hard with
me once the tests are over,
so brace yourself. Got it?
Y-Yes, I understand.
Yo! What's with the long face?
I don't know why I got smacked...
I do feel a bit apprehensive, though.
Mr. Klaus is currently out
and absent as well...
No, no, what are you saying, Maria?
I'm not a child, you know.
I don't need a butler in
constant attendance...
So you say, but who's the one who
got into a desperate situation,
only to be barely saved when
you had no butler with you?
That was a coincidence! A coincidence!
In preparation for just such an event...
What gives, Klaus? That was a
waste of a perfectly good TV.
P-Please...
In preparation for just such a
situation, I made some arrangements.
Arrangements?
Yes, a new temporary butler.
Um, are you certain you're
fine with keeping me company?
Don't ya sweat it!
Yer workin' hard for Nagi, right?
Then it's my duty as the
partner to help ya out, too.
Yer not makin' any progress here!
What're ya spacin' out for?!
Is it really all right for me to
be taking time off work to study?
As for that, looks like ya
got nothin' to worry 'bout.
I heard somethin' 'bout a new butler comin'.
A new... butler?
Yeah, I overheard the SP guys
sayin' somethin' like that.
I had no idea! I see! I
see! That's news to me!
What the heck? Does that upset ya?
I-I'm not letting it upset me or anything.
Well, she really hates strangers,
so I imagine anyone who isn't me
will have a hard time with her.
But while yer sittin' here,
Nagi and the new butler might
become friendly and...
I see nothing wrong with
them becoming friendly.
Never mind that. It's time to study!
Newest Edition
Basic Problem Collection
Comprehensive English
I have to live up to the faith
the Miss has placed in me!
Um, "atarashii shitsuji"... "New butler".
"A new butler come soon"...
"Coming soon dead"...
C'mon now, don't slip in ominous
soundin' phrases into yer English.
If it bothers ya that much,
why don't ya peek in on 'em on yer
way to the bathroom or somethin'?
What?
But I don't see the need
to get so upset 'bout it.
Even Himegami told ya, right?
That he's countin' on ya
to take care of Nagi?
Have confidence. Yer the only
butler that suits Nagi.
Don't ya think ya could put more
faith in the bond ya have with her?
My bond with the Miss...
You're right.
Pardon me for losing my composure.
Don't sweat it. C'mon, let's
get focused, shall we?
Yes, ma'am!
But first...
I think I'll go to the bathroom
and pull myself together
before I resume my studies.
Bathroom first!
So in the end, he's still upset.
No, no, no! Like hell I need a new butler!
I will never accept another
butler, who is not Hayate!
B-But this butler is extremely capable
and I believe there is no doubt that
he will be of more use than Ayasaki...
None of that matters!
I don't even want to breathe the same
air as a butler that's not Hayate!
Besides, I'm...
Not to worry.
You are certain to come
to like me, Miss Nagi.
Y-You're...!
A pleasure to meet you. I
am Mecha Butler No. 13.
All right, then. Send him
back to Miss Makimura.
Oh?
Uh, um, Miss Nagi?
Oh, so this is basically what
they were referring to.
What the heck? This is borin'.
In that case, I can relax and
devote myself to my studies.
Yup.
Study hard now.
I will!
But this was where Hayate's
guard was not up!
Thank you very much.
Oh, no, you are welcome.
I mean...
Responding in some way is the
polite thing to do, right?
Or actually...
Does its words actually count
as an expression of gratitude?
This is...
Could it be a manga drawn by you, Miss Nagi?
Whoa! Where do you get off looking
at it without my permission?!
Get your butt out of her already, you jerk!
What a lousy manga it is!
Wh-What did you say?!
As if a robot like you could understand
the greatness of my manga!
But the characters do have impact.
Huh?
The layout and dialogue also have
a certain sensibility to them.
The art isn't bad, either.
But the plot developments are abrupt,
which overshadow the good parts.
You have to think about your reader more.
Oh, is that right?
Yes. You are smart, so your level of
comprehension is higher than average.
But your readers will be seeing it for
the first time, so that won't work.
Have you read that manga?
No, I can't reach it, so I haven't read it.
Then please read it, because it
will serve as a good reference.
It is an extremely fine piece of work.
I-Is that so?
Here you are.
Then I'll try reading it a bit.
Huh?
This is rose tea.
It will soothe you and allow
you to read at your leisure.
When did you have time to...?
I'm a Mecha Butler, after all.
I know the path of Heaven
and by overclocking, I can move
more swiftly than human beings.
I see!
H-He's amazing...
Well, then, Miss Maria, I would like
to help with the cleaning and such...
Huh? O-Oh, yes...
Then let us start over here.
Wh-What are you...?!
Pardon me.
But please don't move. It seems
your shoulders are a bit stiff.
What?
Now, relax.
Uh, a-all right.
You may be capable of doing
everything on your own,
but working too hard can be a problem, too.
D-Do you think so?
But he's really good at this.
I think I might kind of like it...
Thank you, No. 13.
Oh, no, it's the least I can do.
If you'll just instruct me, I'll
do the rest of the work for you.
What? B-But...
It's the foolish desire of a guy to
act cool in front of a cute girl,
so please, let me act cool.
Not doing any butler work at all
makes me feel restless somehow.
Come to think of it, I wonder
if that robot butler's left.
Ooh, you're quite good!
All right, I'm going to win the next round!
It will not go so easily.
Wh-What in the world is this?
Somehow...
...he's completely fitting in now.
Long ago, there was an episode of "Doraemon"
where a guy's shadow took the guy's place.
Don't say something so ominous!
S-S-S-Small Light.
(Su-Su-Su-Sumouru raito.)
M-M-M-M-M-My existence has finally become...
(To-To-To-To-To-Toutou boku no sonzai ga...)
What? Hayate's getting jealous?
Yeah, it looks like the way you've
become friendly with that robot
is really gettin' to him.
Oh, my...
But a butler robot, huh?
The technology of the Sanzenin
family sure is impressive.
I am honored to receive
your words of praise.
So, how outstandin' are ya?
Someone, tell her!
I'm askin' ya, ya moron!
I made a jab at him without even meanin' to!
Your reputation precedes you, Miss Sakuya.
You do not overlook even
the smallest of jokes.
Ya...
Ya mean, that was on purpose?!
Outstandin'! This Robot Butler's
so outstandin', it's mind-blowin'!
Hayate's getting jealous over me?
Jealous, huh?
Oh, man, he's so cute!
Um, Miss, why do you look so happy?
Because, to think Hayate
would get jealous...
It's a bit endearing, don't you think?
There ya go with yer warped
sensibilities again.
Endearing?
Is that an emotion that is
enjoyable for human beings?
What? Are there things even
you don't understand, No. 13?
Yes, because my CPU hasn't been
programmed with thought patterns
that encourage negative
emotions in human beings.
I think it's fine that you're
not programmed with them.
This is correct, too.
All right! I got everything right!
Somehow, being a bit depressed
actually makes me more focused.
Human beings are strange creatures.
There's definitely a gloom
about him from behind.
So that's what jealousy
looks like. I see, I see.
Quit grinnin' like a fool and
go on in to comfort him.
Yes, he should be getting
tired from his studies soon,
so maybe I'll make him
some tea or something.
Please wait, Miss.
What is it, No. 13?
If you go to comfort him right away,
you'll be playing right into his hands.
What?
I get it. The adult gambit.
Yes, so this is where...
Yes?
Um, H-Hayate?
I made some tea...
Oh, Maria?
I appreciate you going to the
trouble of making me tea...
Oh, no, please think nothing of it, meow.
A-Are your studies going well, meow?
Right...
Honestly! What about this
is a good idea, No. 13?!
What is Hayate doing?!
Staring all goggly at Maria like that!
Nah, that's not bein' all goggly.
No!
I-I will be taking some time off, meow!
Damn you, Hayate! How dare you look
at Maria with those pervy eyes?!
Now, now, Miss.
I am sorry, but it seems
this plan has failed.
And with that, I've gotten rid of person #1.
Let us take this in a slightly
different direction.
I get it! A late night snack!
It's not night yet, though.
Then I'll pull out all the stops to...
Denied.
What?! Why?!
I'm trying to make a loving dish here!
That's why!
It's obviously leadin' to the totally
cliche explosion punch line!
Don't mock me!
Ya can't even fix up a single
servin' of cup ramen properly!
What did you say?!
If you would not mind, would you
lend a hand as well, Miss Sakuya?
Me?
Wow, this is incredible!
You made all of this for me?
Yup. Eat up and work hard.
I had no idea you were a good cook.
Nah, this stuff is nothin' extraordinary.
What's he doing, being encouraged by Saku?!
So that person named Hayate is
quite close to Miss Sakuya.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Hayate is... Hayate is my...
Goodness, this food is so comforting.
Don't be getting comforted!
I swear! Hayate, I swear!
M-Miss, what are you so angry about?
She seems to be in a foul mood, so
perhaps you should take your leave.
What the heck? She's such a child.
Miss Sakuya, you are more
mature than Miss Nagi.
Ya sure are a smooth talker.
Well, I'll be goin' then.
Now, that makes two.
That just leaves...
So anyway, are you getting
anywhere with your studies?
Yes, well, more or less.
Oh, you've gotten quite a bit done.
Yes, and I owe it to Sakuya for
really drumming it into me.
What about owing to me?
So you owe it more to Saku than to me?
What?
Oh, no, Miss, th-that is not true!
Hayate, you jerk!
Miss...
I swear! I swear, Hayate is just so...!
Good grief.
No. 13...
It seems he is quite a poor butler.
Huh?
N-No, that's not true...
And he seems to be awfully stupid.
At this rate, wouldn't he be considered
a failure as a Sanzenin butler?
No. 13, what are you saying?
That being the case, don't you think
I should just remain your butler?
What?!
H-Hey, you!
Let us forget about someone like him.
I am superior to him, you know.
But...!
How pitiful. Getting so depressed
over something like this.
Hayate...
It's true. When I think of what
would be good for you, Miss...
Hayate, that's not...!
Even with me by your side, your picky
eating habits never get any better,
you keep watching TV late into the night,
you skip school and play
nothing but online games,
and lately, you've gained
an interest in Otome Road
and you've been secretly sending
SP members shopping there...
Also, behind the shelf...
That's enough! That's enough already!
Miss?
You and only you are my butler!
You being a bit less than outstanding
is a better fit for me!
Miss...
Hayate.
Miss, does that count as a compliment?
Uh, w-well, um...
Hayate.
Yes?
Anyway, right now, just study hard!
Yes, you are right!
Could it be that he behaved
like that for my sake?
Being a bit less than
outstanding is better...
Human beings are so complicated.
Eight! Stop, please!
Let go of me, honey!
If I'm going to lose you to him, I'd
rather wreck him and go down with him...
I'll go down with him!
Eight!
Take that!
Oh, Eight, you dummy!
Honey...
Were you hurt at all, No. 13?
Why was he angry?
I had done no harm.
I'm sorry. I kept focusing
all my attention on you,
so it looks like he got jealous.
Jealous? I do not understand.
That emotion has not been
programmed into me yet.
It's fine, it's fine. I don't
really understand it, either.
This one isn't as high-performance
as you, so...
Oof.
I still don't understand, no matter
how high-performance I am.
My being at this residence
ultimately serves as a hindrance
to Miss Nagi's happiness.
I will leave the rest to
Hayate and I will just...
Breaking news!
What is it?! What is it?! What's going on?!
A giant meteor that has suddenly
come flying out of space
is currently approaching Earth!
It appears it will land in Tokyo's
Nerima Ward in just a few minutes!
What?!
Wait, it's already right in front of us!
What a huge turn of events!
Or actually, so the scene before
the opening really had meaning!
At this rate, it's gonna hit us head-on!
Let us hurry and get out of here!
No, at that size, you will
not be able to flee in time.
What?!
Then what are we going to do?!
Hayate, please take care of
the Miss and the others.
D-Don't tell me...
I will destroy the meteor in space,
before it damages the Earth's surface.
If I use the self-destruct
mechanism built into me,
it should be possible.
Yer gonna self-destruct?!
D-Don't do this!
You can't go! No. 13, this is
an order from your mistress!
Miss, it is a butler's duty
to protect his mistress,
even if it costs him his life.
Please forgive me for disobeying your order.
No! No! I'm never letting you go!
If you go, I won't forgive you!
No, No. 13!
Hayate, please get the Miss.
Come, Miss, get away from there!
Let go! Let me go!
If I am ever given the opportunity
to be reborn again,
I will be sure to have the emotion of
jealousy programmed into me next time.
I wish you happiness.
No. 13...
Farewell, everyone.
No. 13!
Farewell, Miss Nagi.
He sure was a good guy.
No. 13...
Miss...
The giant meteor that came
flying out of space yesterday
somehow vanished just before
it collided with Earth.
Thanks to the Mecha Butler
No. 13's courageous deed,
peace on Earth and the happiness of
the Sanzenin Miss were protected.
Thank you, No. 13.
Farewell, Mecha Butler No. 13.
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
Burn, marble soul! I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
Ooh, this is your character song, Hayate.
The deluge of "Hayate the Combat
Butler" character songs
has tapered off, so they decided
they could play my song again.
Are you sure the next song
just didn't get done in time?
That's not true. Though, it's true
that it hasn't been sung yet.
Well, so anyway, we're prepared
a fan service shot of Hayate.
Cross-dressing Hayate is nice, too,
but for all the Hayate
fans across the nation,
this time, we have a pinup of
Hayate in his butler uniform.
When did you get a picture
of me like this, Miss?!
But this is better than the cross-dressing.
Bye-bye!
Preview
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Th-This is...
A letter that's not signed by the sender?
Someone's got quite a lot of
nerve to send me a love letter.
But who in the world could it be?
Could it be...?
Hinagiku.
Hayate?
So is this letter from you, after all?
Next time, "Hina Love".
Episode 48 is a must-see
episode for Hinagiku fans.
Though, I won't be appearing in it much.
Come Izen-cross with "Hayate the
Combat Butler" again next time!
Hina Love