Street No. 03
"The Boy Who Lost His Cat"
And Yet the Town Moves
The eye.
To catch the eye.
Change the color of the eye.
Be the apple of one's eye.
Keep one's eye on something.
The eye is a passive vessel
that collects visual information,
while at times it also shows determination and emotion.
It is an active organ that displays such
thoughts in a kind of symbolic language.
The eyes speak as much as the mouth does.
That is truly a phrase that describes the eye accurately.
And this is its true nature.
That man, I'm sure he came here before...
Yes, he's our homeroom teacher.
I wonder what business he has today.
Did Hotori do something again?
Um... Sensei, can I ask you something?
What is it, Arashiyama?
After school, you came all the way to see me...
You must be in love with me, aren't you?
Huh...?
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
Huh?
"Huh?" he said! Straightforward!
There's no pulse to this romance!
Vitals: heart rate, breathing, blood pressure, all zero!
Oh, Sensei, are you not married?
You're so handsome, it's such a waste.
You make your own lunch...
That's so lonely.
Once it goes into the stomach, it's all the same.
Hey, hey, shoo, shoo!
Don't go putting the moves on him
without any permission!
What's up with you?
The customer belongs to everyone.
Arashiyama, paper, paper.
There's an order!
You said there was no pulse!
So...
What business do you have with me?
I refuse any extracurricular activity that's not dangerous.
While sorting through articles left by my grandfather,
I found something strange.
Are you ignoring my moves?
Actually, here it is.
A drawing? It's a drawing.
It looks like a normal portrait to me.
What don't you understand about it?
Hmm...
...this is a very unique drawing.
Huh?
Everyone says that it's an ordinary drawing,
so why are you the only one saying otherwise?
I know, you're trying to go along with what
your teacher is saying to attract his attention.
You little brat, pretending to be grown up!
That's not true!
Well, it's 20% true...
So you are!
Here, look at it!
This canvas is totally square.
Oh.
Aren't drawings usually longer on the length or width?
That's true...
Now that you mention it...
I see. Indeed, this drawing has an aspect ratio of 1:1.
In other words, a square.
Good, Arashiyama.
I brought this here, anticipating you'd be able
to catch something out of the ordinary!
To me, you are a special existence!
Oh my... But I'm still in high school...
You're interpreting this to your advantage again.
The person who drew this picture is my grandfather.
He was the youngest of three brothers,
and he was a starving artist when he was alive.
My grandfather liked to gamble
and didn't leave much of an inheritance,
IGUSA RACE PARK
DICE
Mahjong
but he did leave many paintings.
PACHINKO
GOOD
FORTUNE
After my grandfather died,
his pieces were split evenly three ways amongst
his brothers and bereaved family; my family.
And... the real problem is...
this other drawing!
What is this?!
Four eyes?
Creepy!
According to the label on the back,
I think these are my grandfather's self-portraits.
And...
EYE
Kozaburo Moriaki
The titles of both drawings are the same.
EYE
"Eye"
"Eye"...?
Why did my grandfather draw such strange pictures?
Ever since I found these drawings,
I can't stop thinking about them.
My heart is cloudy, and I can't fathom why!
As you already know, I am a math teacher.
It's my job to think things through logically.
What were the feelings of the painter
when he drew this picture?
Hah! Nonsense!
How could I let someone who's not the
concerned party know such a thing?
Whoa! He's gone mad!
But, based on accurate guesses,
it is possible to hypothesize an answer.
Arashiyama, you like mystery novels, correct?
Yes! I love them!
So I want to ask you to deduce
why this drawing was made.
Me?!
At all costs, I want you to come up with
a reason that I can agree with.
I will come back tomorrow.
Really, what a troublesome teacher.
If you think the other way around, because of that
troublesome personality he'll never marry.
It's a chance to get him. Right, Hotori?
Enough about the teacher.
Don't bother me while I'm thinking.
Oh, were you still thinking?
I know already.
What?!
I've solved the mystery, too.
You too, Granny?!
My deduction... would you like to hear it?
Do you know the artist of this painting?
Huh?
This is...
Post-impressionist artist, Vincent Van Gogh.
The theory goes that Van Gogh's
unique coloring and touch
is because that's what he was actually seeing.
In the same way, we can explain
that the grandfather saw exactly what he painted.
Huh?!
In conclusion...
The teacher's grandfather had astigmatism!
Wow, that's quite the deduction!
But then why'd he draw only one mouth and nose, huh?
Head Maid! This girl makes me mad!
The other picture's a regular drawing, you see?
It's weird that eyes increase and decrease in numbers.
You're not thinking hard enough, Hotori.
Then you should use backwards reasoning.
The teacher said his grandfather left many drawings.
So, for the teacher to think that that particular
drawing was weird, the rest were not weird.
Landscapes and still life...
Out of many normal drawings,
only that one piece was weird.
Well... that must've been true.
In other words, the grandfather was someone
who always drew normal paintings.
If that's true...
Instead of thinking why only this drawing was special,
it would make more sense to think that this
was just another ordinary piece!
Huh?!
In conclusion!
The teacher's grandfather was a four-eyed alien!
When he drew that picture,
he had his other two eyes closed!
Oh yeah, that's amazing! What big news!
Wha-?! You're so annoying, really!
Head Maid, what should we do with this girl?
Hm? Wait a minute.
Taking something normal and thinking backwards...
Oh!
That's it!
What's with her?
Are you okay? Did you use your head
too much and now it's broken?
When a detective laughs loudly, there's a good chance
that the mystery has been solved!
CLOSED
Well then, let's hear your answer.
Okay, Sensei... There are six cards here.
If you were to split this amongst
three people, how would you do it?
Are you mocking me?
You give two to each person. What else would you do?
Correct!
Then, to divide a castella cake amongst three people?
We'd have to cut it into three.
Correct!
Oh no! There isn't a piece for me!
So what are you trying to say?!
These were just hints.
I...
I hate those slow-paced revelations in mystery novels,
and that blue dolphin on my word processing software!
Stop lining up hints and give me
the quick and simple answer!
That is all of the hints.
If you apply this, then you can solve
the mystery of the drawings.
You try to think about it, too.
Might it be that you don't know?
Hm?
Why can't you figure it out?
Don't do anything in excess;
if you apply a formula then you can solve it!
Why can't you figure it out?!
Oh, so it's like this?!
It feels great!
The teacher always looked down on me with this feeling!
Arashiyama...
Arashiyama, you should let him know soon.
The teacher is at his limit.
Something Arashiyama knows that I don't...
How could this be...?
My thinking is like this...
Yes! Look here!
What is this...?!
This is the true form of this piece.
This was a die!
I added the parts that were missing
by drawing them in myself!
The title "Eye" is a word play
on his eyes and the eyes of the dice,
and so this piece can be considered to be
made up of drawings with one to six eyes!
I say it's a self-portrait worthy of a gambling grandfather.
However, since this piece was a cube that was
split into three, it no longer fulfilled its purpose
and what was left in the teacher's hands
were these two mystery drawings.
This is the truth!
What do you think, Mr. Client?!
Arashiyama seems to look intelligent.
It's a miracle!
No matter how much vinegar I drink,
I don't become flexible, poko.
The eyes speak as much as the mouth does.
The eyes continue to speak the truth,
but whether one can understand their words
depends on if that one has an eye for the truth.
Open
Dear
Arashiyama
When I talked to my relatives, just like Arashiyama said,
I found the remaining four drawings.
I took into consideration my grandfather's intentions
and reconstructed the piece...
"...which I give you as a token of my appreciation."
We don't want it!
What are you going to do by making this
store tighter than it already is?!
If we hang something like this in here,
we'll scare the customers!
Hey, stop it!
If we hang something like this in here,
we'll scare the customers!
The teacher went out of his way to give me this present!
Then put it up in your room!
Uh... um...
That's kind of...
"Poco" means "a little" in Italian, poko.
The onion...
The allyl compound oxidizes the hemoglobin
in the blood causing hemolytic anemia.
So if an animal that's not a human eats it,
there's the risk of death...
If it is a human, it is said there's a
health benefit in that the blood is cleansed.
However, there is no sufficient medical data.
Cutting an onion releases sulfuric allyl
which irritates the eye, producing tears,
but if you chill it beforehand and then cut it,
the release of the sulfuric allyl is suppressed,
making it less likely for tears to come out;
this is the wisdom of housewives.
The reason for my tears...
Aren't you going to ask?
Onion.
Oh!
Seaside
Open
Car-rots, on-ion...
on three!
Aww! I'm not a child! I can go shopping properly!
No you couldn't.
You have a past offense,
so that's why you're being told this.
Mr. Oniot
Here! Mr. Oniot! If you forget on the way, remember this!
See?!
It makes me so mad!
There's a limit to making fun of someone!
Carrots and onions, right?! Who messes that up?!
Oh?
Mr. Oniot
Mr. Oniot, so...
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
I think it's correct that it's a round thing and pointy thing...
Oh? Was the round thing a potato?
Oh? Which one was it...?
Man!
When they go through all that trouble to make sure...
It just makes my doubting heart create
a dark demon all the more!
Koban!
It just makes my doubting heart create
a dark demon all the more!
Hm?
Koban? Koban!
Koban...
Koban! Koban, Koban, Koban!
It's no use...
Whoa... What a beautiful boy.
The eye.
Cross-eyed, teary-eyed, to be the apple of one's eye...
The evil eye that hits you when you're already cursed...
The eye is a mirror that reflects a person's heart,
so if you look into one's eyes you can connect
to their heart and understand each other.
What are you looking at?
Your butt.
Huh...?!
Aha. Seeing that your voice hasn't changed yet,
you must be a boy of about 12 or 13 years of age.
My, my, to bleach your hair blonde at that age...
You are so rebellious!
Oh!
You're the one named Hotori, aren't you?
The other day, I saw you run over
a cop on your kick board.
Is that how you address me?
Shouldn't you say Hotori-san
or Big Sister or something?
Children that don't play right will have
a hard time in this shopping district.
And what are you doing?
You're very suspicious.
What kind of ritual is this?
Take a peek.
A cat...?
A cat's eye.
The phrase is used to describe one's fickle tendencies.
It is a phrase that describes
how its pupil opens wide then closes,
but it can also describe how the cat itself is fickle;
that's how the phrase came about.
Further, those who own cats have at least
some affinity to those fickle tendencies
so the term "cat's eye" applies to people
who have a sort of magical attractiveness.
That's my cat. He's not coming out from there.
Oh, "Koban" is the cat's name.
Yup.
Why did you name your cat Koban...
Oh, "Neko ni Koban"! You're so smart!
Note: "Neko ni Koban" is a commonly used phrase,
much like the English maxim "Pearls before swine"
Thanks!
I know, here's some Oniot.
You mean onion.
Want some?
No.
Not you, I'm saying why don't we
use this as bait to lure him out?
I'm saying cats won't eat onion!
Or rather, you're not supposed to let them eat onion.
Oh, that's right. If a cat eats onion,
he'll get stunned won't he?
Note: "Sore wa Ika" (That's squid) and "Sore wa Ikan!" (That's no good!) are puns;
two sentences phonetically identical except for one letter at the end
That's squid.
That's no good!
Note: the Japanese call a lame joke "cold" when it falls flat
Go home already. Your jokes are lame!
Look, you're making it snow!
I'm sorry... I don't know why I said such a thing...
Koban!
We won't tell any more bad jokes, so come on out!
It's my fault?!
Cats don't like the cold! Koban!
It's okay, he'll come out eventually.
Cats are fickle, right?
My Koban is a good kitty, though.
Cat owners always say that.
If I leave him alone and he catches a cold, I'll feel bad.
Despite your looks, you're very kind.
Wha-
What?
What the heck are you doing?!
Y-you hit me!
Because you strangled me!
Why did you strangle me?!
Well, if the owner was in a pinch,
maybe it would jump out to your rescue?
It's not a dog.
I own a dog at home, and she'll come
when I'm in a pinch, probably.
I. Told. You! See? You get it?!
That's a dog, right?!
Oh my...
This climax really needs some planning.
I won't need your help anymore, so go away already...
He came out!
See, onions were the right answer after all!
Whoa, Hotori! Catch him!
Okay, leave it to Big Sister!
Capture!
I call it "The Maid Cage"!
"Maid Cage" sounds like an adult DVD title.
Fresh little brat!
You had me worried!
Man, thank goodness Koban-chan...
Thank good—!
You're kidding! Did I step on the cat?!
Is there a cat's tail somewhere on the ground?!
Oh no! What should I do?!
By any chance, are you searching for a tail?
Huh?! No, not me!
I mean, it might have been me,
but it was an accident and...
I didn't do it on purpose!
He had no tail to begin with.
He's a breed called "Cymric," and they don't have tails.
A long, long time ago when his ancestor
tried to board Noah's ark,
the tail got caught in the door
and was cut off, or so they say.
Oh... I thought I was going to get yelled at
by the animal rights organization.
Isn't it a romantic story, though?
But isn't that story weird?
Huh?
Koban and his ancestors are separate.
It's like, if the dad got hurt, does
the injury get passed on to the son?
I don't know. Stop splitting hairs.
Well, I'll say thanks for now.
Okay.
"For now," huh.
You were a very fresh brat until the end, weren't you?
Come to think of it, you should
at least tell me your name...
Oh?
Well... I'll just say Cat Boy.
We should've taught her the
"don't make any detours" song, I guess?
Also, we should've drawn her a map...
Oya High School
Ho-to-ri!
Oh!
You're the one I met yesterday! Cat...
...girl?
S-sorry, I thought you were a young boy...
No wonder our conversation didn't quite match up.
So we go to the same school.
I knew.
What class are you in?
Class A.
Huh...?
What?! Wait, I'm in Class A, too, you know?
Was there someone like this in my class? No there isn't!
I should at least remember a classmate's face!
Whoa, oh no!
I knew I was going to encounter one of these some day.
The punch line is that "you are a ghost!"
Come to think of it, she disappeared
yesterday without my noticing...
so if I raised my face would it be,
like, "She's not there, gyah!"
Since she's showing up even in school,
that must mean I'm totally possessed...!
Kon-senpai, hello!
Senpai?
Oh, Haribara...
For today's club meeting, we'll have a tournament.
I just changed the rubber on this racket.
I hope it doesn't become the scythe of the
Grim Reaper ready to chop off your head...
Say things like that only after you win.
Oh my.
Oh my, you were older than me, weren't you, Senpai...
But you look so young...
Well, again and again I apologize
for being so rude, really...
Well, well...
Don't worry about it. Okay?
Big Sister?
Can you forgive me...?
Rap is not the only hip-hop, poko
Maid...
In today's Japan, the word describes
young girls who dress in uniforms
and play the roles of British housekeepers.
Maid Cafe, Maid Bar, Maid Reflexology,
Maid Mahjong House...
On top of that there's a Maid Housekeeping Service,
which is a job that went full circle.
Its force knows no stopping as we approach the now.
And right now, there are two girls
fighting for their honor as Maids.
Why me?!
Do you want to know...?
Fine, I'll tell you before I send
you to the Mei-do Underworld...
Note: 冥土 (Underworld) is pronounced "mei-do," as is the word "Maid"
MEI-DO
ARASHIYAMA, HOTORI
Write down the title for
British housekeepers.                              Answer: MEI-DO
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
There is a curse which people are falling to left and right.
What is that? Scary!
The person cursed will transfer
the curse to one person per minute.
It's kind of a loose curse.
At first, when one was cursed,
the entire student body was cursed in ten minutes.
So, if at first two were cursed, how long would it take
for the whole student body to be cursed?
That's twice as many so half the time is five minutes?
Incorrect!
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Four,
"The Equation of Curses."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 04 "THE EQUATION OF CURSES"
We were turning round and round yesterday, too, poko.
Cafe Seaside