U-Um...
Manabe-kun, is it okay if I open it now?
Sure. I picked it out for you.
Well, aren't you confident.
I am a little interested in seeing what you chose.
Hurry up and open it, Kotoura-san.
Okay.
How cute!
A locket pendant, huh?
That's a pretty good choice, for Manabe-kun.
Actually, I'm shocked to see it's something so normal.
Um...
Thank you, Manabe-kun.
I've already placed the perfect picture inside, too.
A picture?
With that, I'll always be watching over you, Kotoura!
No way!
TLC
Tobikage
Timer   Floris257
Editor
Chippo
K-time
Floris257
Karaoke
Naruto-kun
Logo: KakashiCopyNinja
Typesetter
Floris257
Naruto-kun
QC
Robo731
Floris257
Encoder
October
Okay, starting today, we wear winter uniforms.
It's Not a Date
I always worry about what I'd do
if I wore the wrong uniform today.
Oops, I almost forgot.
There.
Manabe-kun...
Oh, morning, Kotoura.
Mor'ing...
Huh? What's with you?
Goo' mor'ing.
You're talking funny.
And your face is red.
Do you...
You do have a fever!
Huh?
Now tha' you men'hon it, I feel kin'a crappy.
An' maybe a li'l chilly...
Bu' I'm ohay.
You're not "ohay"!
You've totally got a cold!
Huh?
When 'id you all get 'ere?
Just now.
You're the one who opened the door and let us in.
Oh, I did?
You're completely out of it.
Pull yourself together!
Sorry, Moritani-'an.
I'll pu' on some tea.
I-I was kidding!
You don't have to get up. Stay in bed.
Has she seen a doctor?
I was on my way to school.
At least I gave her some medicine.
I cut an apple for you.
It's delicious! This apple is delicious!
Oh, I think you look a little better.
It must be tough living on your own at times like this.
Want me to stay with you today?
That's okay. I've had some medicine.
That's right.
Besides, I'll remain by her side until nightfall.
We're all set!
That's my biggest concern.
What do you mean by that?!
Leaving Kotoura-san with you in this state
is like throwing a lamb out in front of a wolf.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
I'm a gentleman!
You think I'd take advantage of Kotoura's weakness...
and do... something?
Words are shallow.
Idle talk won't bring world peace.
That's why psychic abilities are essential!
Go on, Kotoura-chan, expose the truth in this boy's shallow words!
Just because I'm not saying anything...
But it's true, isn't it?
Well, I mean...
If you observe things from various angles,
and analyze it all a little more scientifically...
Well? How about it, Kotoura-chan?
Huh?
Oh, I wasn't thinking anything inappropriate at all.
Well, just a little.
It's okay. He's not thinking about anything.
Say what?
He's sincere. He honestly plans to take care of me.
A-Are you sure?
Well, if Kotoura-chan says so, it must be true, but...
It's too unexpected.
Are you okay?
Maybe we should get going.
Having so many people here must be a hindrance.
You're right.
Okay, Manabe-kun, we'll leave the rest to you.
Don't you dare turn into a wolf.
I-I know that!
Sorry I couldn't be much of a hostess.
Don't worry about it.
More importantly...
Keep the flirting with Manabe-kun in check, okay?
Kotoura-chan...
She's doing better than I expected, so that's good.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll test it...
Manabe-kun, would you wipe the sweat off me?
Leave it to me. I'll get you nice and clean.
There you go, there you go...
How's that? How's that, Kotoura?!
You like that? You like that?
It tickles...
You like it better here?
Where are you wiping?
Th-That's not my back...
Where do you think I'm wiping? Guess!
Let me hear you!
Manabe-kun, is something wrong?
D-Does this mean...
Kotoura isn't reading my mind?
U-Um, hey...
What?
Just a sec.
Maybe it's because of her cold,
but she can't read minds right now, and she doesn't realize it...
I don't really get it, but this looks like my chance!
Yes, this means...
I can fantasize all I want!
I'm sorry, master. Please punish me.
Want to rip off this bunny's fishnets?
Oh no! I messed up the exorcism,
and now there's a perverted spirit inside me!
Oh no! This poison only dissolves armor, for some reason!
This is no fun at all!
Damn it! There's no point in fantasizing
if it doesn't embarrass Kotoura!
Why did you start crying all of a sudden?
Isn't there anything else I can do?!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance to be a pervert!
I'm soaked with sweat...
I want to wipe it off...
Okay! Just leave that to me!
What?! You can't do that!
Manabe-kun, you pervert!
What are you talking about?
My conscience is squeaky clean.
Above all else, I'm just worried about you.
That's definitely the face of a pervert.
But he's not thinking about anything like that.
Th-Then...
You can do my back only.
What?! For real?!
Y-You must be hungry, Kotoura!
I'll go grab something!
What was I about to do?!
I'm so stupid! Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Useless!
I guess I fell asleep...
Manabe-kun?
Haruka.
The porridge is ready.
Mama...
Feels like your fever has gone down.
Yeah.
Open wide.
Mama, do you think I'll be able to go to kindergarten tomorrow?
Yes. Your fever has gone down.
I'm sure you'll be able to go.
You okay, Kotoura?
M-Manabe-kun...
Feels like your fever has gone down.
Ready for dinner, then?
I just heated up something frozen, but bear with it, okay?
Here, open wide.
Way to chow down!
Here, have some more.
Okay.
Now that I've run around town,
burning off all of my overflowing pervertedness,
I can't fail!
Thanks for feeding me.
Okay, now get some rest,
and that cold will be gone by morning.
Yeah.
Okay, once I clean up, I'll be heading ho—
What is it?
U-Um, Manabe-kun...
If it's okay with you, would you...
hold my hand until I fall asleep?
B-Bad idea?
Is this okay?
Yeah.
Please... hold out just a little longer...
My good sense!
Kotoura Haruka has recovered!
We've been awaiting your return, Kotoura-chan!
Are you okay?
Manabe didn't do anything to you, did he?
M-Manabe-kun didn't have any perverted thoughts at all.
He took very good care of me.
And what's wrong with you?
I worked really hard.
So I can take a break now, right?
I think we need to hear this...
...in a little more detail.
Mori!
Go ahead, Kotoura-san.
I was stupid to trust you!
You pervert!
Hey, that wasn't necessary!
I worked hard to suppress my desires!
But you were thinking perverted things, weren't you?
Of course I was!
All yours, Moritani-san.
Mori!
Um, I'm sorry... Please, no more physical violence...
I thought something seemed off,
but I never thought you'd lose your psychic ability.
Muroto-kun, any idea what this is about?
Well, psychics are human, too.
I'd say health influences psychic abilities as well.
So it was because of her cold?
But she's all better now.
Hey, Kotoura-chan, have you been sick before?
Did the same thing happen then, too?
I've had colds before, but I don't remember.
When I'm laid up with a fever,
I'm in no shape to read minds, anyway.
That's logical.
So, has your ability not returned?
I don't know.
But honestly, I don't mind staying like this.
True...
Well, enough of that.
It was cruel of you
to toy with Kotoura-chan's pure heart, Manabe-kun.
What?! You too, President?!
My turn again?
Not that it matters,
but Moritani-kun has clearly established
her role in the ESP Society.
As atonement, Manabe-kun,
you need to show Kotoura-chan a good time.
Um... How?
It's easy.
Eat some food that she likes with her,
take her to places that she likes,
and engage in activities that she likes to do.
That sounds wonderful!
I see...
Wait, President! Wouldn't that be a date?
What?! A date?!
That's right. Off you go.
Come on, relax!
I wait for Kotoura every morning!
Manabe-kun!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
Nothing, n-not a thing!
What's with me?
I've seen her in regular clothes plenty of times before!
W-Well then, shall we go?
Y-Yeah.
Wh-Where should we go?
Uh... I'll go wherever you want to go.
Really?
Tohru, it's been so long since we were last on a date.
Noriko, I won't let you sleep tonight.
Oh, Tohru...
H-Hey, Kotoura...
Wh-What?
Do you think this is really...
It's not a date! It's your punishment for being mean!
It's definitely not a date!
Uh, I didn't say anything yet—
Look at that. Their first date.
How nice it is to be young.
Mama, what's a date?
Sh-Shall we go, Kotoura?
Yes, Manabe-kun.
What a nice shop!
Can we take a look?
I'd rather look in that one.
Okay, let's go, Mr. Pervert!
I'm sorry!
Mr. Pervert! Mr. Pervert!
Please call me by my real name when we're around people!
Mr. Pervert!
Wow, this is so cute!
Oh, but this one is...
I can't decide...
Then, how about this one?
What does your boyfriend think?
So it really does look like we're on a date!
Oh, man! How embarrassing!
Okay, as her date partner, here's my opinion:
I like this sexy-cute one!
Wh—
But this sexy-racy one is great, too!
Oh, but...
That sexy-casual one is also good!
But then!
So is this sexy-gorgeous one!
Why don't we just buy them all, Kotoura?
Huh?
Your companion left without a sound a moment ago...
Kotoura!
Where are you, Kotoura?!
Don't dump me!
Idiot! He's an idiot!
Well, I knew that, but he's an even bigger idiot!
Jeez... Why did he have to be the one I...
So this is where you ran off to, Kotoura.
Aw, she's mad. Now what...
Manabe-kun?
Jeez...
Where could Manabe-kun have gone?
Surely he didn't go home...
Now I get it.
Moments like this are scary when I can't read minds.
Hey, would ya cheer up already?
Look, I bought you some sweets.
You call taiyaki a sweet?
It is sweet!
But you can't do things like that.
I'm sorry. I just got a little excited.
Actually, there's another place I'd like to go.
This is where you wanted to go?
Yeah.
A trip to the movies is customary on a date, right?
Er, it's not a date... It's not a date, is it?
When I go to see movies...
I always know how they're going to end before they start.
I see!
So I'm really excited to see one now.
Okay, I got it!
Then, let's get pumped to see this movie!
Wh—
Manabe-kun...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing's wrong.
Yeah? Then, let's go in.
Yeah.
I'm so bored... Bored, bored...
Then, why don't you go out, too?
Like Kotoura-kun and Manabe-kun.
Oh, yeah, we could always tail them.
Isn't that a little harsh, after you pushed them into going on a date?
Well, those two drive me nuts.
As the club president, I should support them.
I see.
And how do you really feel?
That's right.
I just wanted to give Kotoura-chan some sort of stimulation.
I can't accomplish my goal
if she doesn't regain her psychic ability.
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
The Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
The Miracle
Clairvoyant
Yuri-chan!
You'll stay for dinner, won't you?
Oh, sure, if it's no trouble.
You're never any trouble.
I wouldn't mind if you ate here every day!
Mom, don't come in without knocking.
Well, you weren't doing
anything that would warrant a knock, were you, Dai-chan?
Why am I the one getting scolded?
Cashier
Thanks!
Kotoura...
Kotoura!
Where should we go next?
Well...
They turned out great, Manabe-kun.
So you like this kind of thing?
Just a sec.
I'll treasure this.
O-Okay...
So... Thank you for today.
And, um... I...
Well...
Let's hang out again sometime.
Yeah!
Manabe-kun, this way! Hurry up!
Hold up, Kotoura!
If you rush, you'll fall again!
I'm not that clumsy!
This is fun. I'm so happy.
I want to feel like this forever.
Kotoura, what's wrong?
Are you all right? What happened?
Hey, she's unconscious!
Call an ambulance!
Ko—
Kotoura!
Starting next week, we enter the vicious battle arc on Kotoura-San!
That's taking a completely different route!
The final boss will appear as well!
There's no need for that at all!
But the perverted stuff will carry on, just like always!
Episode 9
Everyone is Around Me
That's the one thing we need the least.