The problem isn't if the customer is good or not,
but whether if the shop is good or not.
- Martin B. Stone
Welcome home, master
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
七色の黄昏おりてきて
The wind is kinda refreshing
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
風はなんだか涼しげ
Saturday night is lively
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
Everyone can't wait
Minna ukiuki
みんなウキウキ
Can't wait.
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
[Blissful Shop - Before] From Volume 1 Story 1
Even if it is the most run down place,
It's a blissful shop
[Blissful Shop - Before] From Volume 1 Story 1
If the customer can have what they desire.
But no matter how the shop might glitter,
If the customer can't have their request fulfilled
The shop may as well be an empty warehouse.
So what has this customer been doing all this time?
Homework.
Really?
Can I copy? Just the math homework...
Wasn't math the only homework?
Yeah yeah, fine. Lemme in.
Hey, sit on the other side.
No way. I'll make mistakes copying upside down.
No you won't
Will too
The number 9 could turn into a 6
And what are you gonna do if the katakana ヨ turns into an E!
Maybe when the Europeans started using 'E's
Someone miscopied it.
If this theory is true,
It could be an earth shaking discovery!
They don't use katakana in other countries.
Fine then, copy. Make it quick.
Thank you.
A shop where I can be alone with Hotori?
Heaven!
Hmm?
Ah. Nothing.
Everyone wants bliss,
There isn't a person who doesn't want it.
Why? It's because finding bliss
Rarely happens.
It's a slider if they shake their head twice, poko~
Otani High School
Arashiyama.
You copied your homework, didn't you?
Why?
Your answers are mostly right.
What's the problem?
I can do my homework when I need to.
However, you wrote the number 1 in place of the letter I.
Even if that were just a mistake, you wrote 1=0 instead of I=0.
Have any idea about that?
Uhh, I dunno.
Please see me in the office after school.
Auugh
This just had to happen after I managed to
complete my homework for once
Shouldn't that be what the teacher says?
I'll be late for work if I get lectured.
Oh, you have a job?
Yup, at a coffee shop in the neighborhood, wearing a maid outfit.
Could it be a maid café?
Yup, it is.
I just started though...
Huh, pretty classy.
We can have those sort of things here now.
How nice!
I adore maid cafés!
And talking to cute maids while sipping tea...
Hey Arashiyama, would it be ok to drop by your café?
Come, come! We have few customers so your seats are reserved.
^_^
Though it's grandma's store...
so it might be a bit different from what you imagined.
There are two ways imaginations can be cruel.
One way is using imagined worries to scare someone.
Another is to betray the imagination's high expectations.
Maid Café Seaside
Looks like this has to be it...
Not just a bit different... it's quite different from what I imagined.
Ah. Welcome.
Welcome.
Hotori's friends?
Yeah.
Hey you two, take a seat.
It's empty so take any seat you want.
What should we put on the menu?
Oh! I bought some croquettes from Murakami - wanna eat these?
Tatsuno?
This...
This place...
isn't a maid café!
What's up with "Hey welcome"? This isn't a sushi joint!
I... said that?
You did!
Maid cafés have maid café greetings, you know.
Uhh...
Hey! Welcome to our maid café!
Wrong wrong wrong!
This is how you do it, ok?
Your voice doesn't come from your throat and it doesn't come from your belly.
It feels like it comes from here, like...
Welcome home, master~
Ooo
That is a maid,
like what I've seen on TV.
This is basic knowledge. Try it.
Whaa? I have to?
Don't complain! Guys fall in love with that.
Just a maid outfit isn't enough to be a maid.
A maid outfit is enough!
You're pretty good, aren't ya?
Wouldn't you like to take Hotori's place and work here?
Thank you, but I've already decided to join a club
so I don't have time for a job.
We joined the ping pong club.
In place of that, however
I'll train Arashiyama today!
I don't really need it
I can't let this unrefined place call itself a maid café
Hotori, do it for me?
Please listen to her.
But this sort of thing isn't how I am.
Then why are you being a maid?
Hm? Good timing, our prey has arrived.
The dry cleaner guy?
Anyway, it's training.
Quick maid course #1: Maid greeting
Alright! Try what I just showed you before.
Wha? Seriously?
There's no better way to learn than from the real thing!
Now! Good luck, Arashiyama!
Wha
Wel
"Wel"?
Wel...
W-Welcome home, master!
She's nervous...
It's alright. In fact, it's this innocence that's
a hit!
I'm home, Daisy!
Who's Daisy?!
She went for a high angle hit!
Guess the guys around here aren't immune to that.
Grandma's specialty is seven pairs.
Quick maid course #2: Clumsy maid!
Arashiyama is clumsy without any help, no?
Completely true.
Can you not say rude things so casually?
But it's the control of clumsiness that makes a true clumsy maid.
Commit the clumsiness to muscle memory.
Mind if I order?
A Guatemala please.
A hot Guatemala.
Alright, it's your turn, Arashiyama!
How am I suppose to be clumsy?
It's alright. Leave it to me.
Here.
Haribara... now!
Got it.
(Sneeze)
Hooooot!
Wasn't that too cruel?
She continued the combo herself. She's a natural born klutz!
What are you doing!? You...
That was wonderful!
Quick, take this bucket and run!
Sorry! I'll clean it right up!
And now,
trip.
A three hit combo!
She's a goddess! A goddess has come!
Though not a god of maids.
More like a god of laughs.
No. A god of anger. Do you guys have some sort of grudge against me?
Sorry, you were clumsier than expected and we got carried away.
Is the Guatemala ready yet?
What's going on? It's unusually lively inside.
Prey number 2 is here.
C'mon, practice your greeting.
Sanada?
Why are you completely wet?
I'm dripping wet cuz I'm a good girl.
Did you finish getting lectured by the teacher?
Oh... forgot.
Don't say you copied it from me. He'll get mad at me too.
Arashiyama, have a moment?
Huh? What?
If I'm not mistaken,
that was Sanada from seat number 9, wasn't it?
Yeah it was.
Though I don't know his seat number...
Why does he know this shop?
What did he come for?
Does he come often?
Sanada's from the fish market in this neighborhood.
He comes here quite often.
Why?
I see.
This place is a wonderful maid café once you take a good look at it, isn't it?
Head maid,
Huh? I'm the manager.
I'm Tatsuno Toshiko.
Please let me work as a maid.
Eh?
What are you going to do about the club?
Didn't you say we were going to join the ping pong club?
There is a higher calling for me!
With this, we'll be more maid café like.
But, we'll have more staff than customers.
Even if it is the most run down place,
It's a blissful shop
If the customer can have what they desire.
What happen to Arashiyama...
[Blissful shop -  After]  From Volume 1 Story 2
The word "afterschool" is a happy word
that comes with a hint of loneliness.
[Blissful shop -  After]  From Volume 1 Story 2
It's because it's a sign that the day will end soon.
Alright!
Lets see what the day brings!
You start your day now?
Oh yeah, Sanada.
Tatsuno is starting at our shop today.
Wha?
She's actually doing it?
I was just waiting for the maid outfit to be made.
Grandma spent all day sewing it.
Those are hand made?
Well, I'll be leaving first.
Sanada, if you don't mind,
why don't you come later?
Oh... sure.
Hey. You girls.
Are you girls working a part time job without permission from school?
How did he find out?
I dunno.
But today...
We have to escape
Hey! Wait!
Damn it.
Lost sight of them.
I thought they came here for sure...
Isn't this pushing it?
It's ok.
There's Deva king statues in temples
so this isn't out of place.
No one will notice. It's a mind trick.
Where did they go?!
It's about time to go buy toilet paper, poko~
Jeez, the teacher made us late!
I hope Sanada didn't wait
Sorry for being late, head maid!
Welcome.
Welcome? It's just us, don't be so uptight.
I wasn't being uptight.
That was for the customer behind you.
Ow.
Customer? A customer...
is here!
Trying to lose me like that annoys me.
According to the student handbook, page 14, line 8
Non-approved part time jobs are prohibited by school regulations.
Under school regulation number 21, in the event that a part time job is desired
The homeroom teacher must approve in addition to acknowledgment by a school nurse.
My head hurts! Brother...
Please stop! You're exceeding the maximum tolerance level for Arashiyama's brain!
Save me, Mr. Mikuriya!
Who's Mikuriya? My name's Moriaki!
Anyway, I won't accept a job that violates school regulations.
Nobody follows that rule!
Now that I know, I can't let it pass as a homeroom teacher.
You're so strict! Just what I'd expect from a math teacher.
I've been wondering for a while...
How did you know we were going to work?
Now that you mention it,
how did that fact get out?
Could it be that there's a spy somewhere?
Oh yeah, Sanada. Tatsuno is starting at our shop today.
That time...
It got leaked and overheard!
You mean... me?
You're an idiot, aren't you? A real idiot.
Now we have no choice but to get permission for our job.
That's right. I didn't come to stop you.
But can we really get permission to work at a maid café?
We have to make him accept it.
with maid skills.
Maid skills?
We pretend to be submissive while winning the man's heart.
That's what a maid skill is. It's the basic philosophy of a maid café.
Isn't there some ethical problem with that?
Quiet!
This is a battle between the straight laced teacher and the charm of maids,
in other words, light and shadow, good and evil, white and black,
monkey and dog.
Yes. We cannot lose.
To the teacher, this job might look like an hobby,
but to me, this is Sanada's hangout.
I've found my blissful shop.
Head maid!
Is my outfit done?
Yeah, it's on a hanger in the back.
Arashiyama! We're changing into our battle uniforms!
Okay
Salmon is really a white fish, poko~
It's been 22 minutes since they said that.
It takes time for girls to get dressed.
Sorry for making you wait!
Maid number 2, taking care of you starting today, master.
Ditto, maid number 1.
Please, ask for anything, master.
I've lost!
Arashiyama?
I've lost in grades, face, style...
And on top of that, I've been crushed in maid outfit looks.
Get a hold of yourself!
Your battle isn't with me right now!
What am I?
You might not realize this, Arashiyama, but
you have one thing that you definitely can't lose in against Tatsuno.
So if I read between the lines, does this mean
that the teacher has something for me?
Arashiyama, the thing that you're better than Tatsuno at is...
Eyesight.
Oh.
So cruel to hear a third party say so flatly that
other than eyesight,
I lose at everything else.
Arashiyama? Arashiyama!
To destroy a maid's self-respect, critical to maid skills, before she even begins...
is maid murder!
This man is strong.
Tatsuno.
Yes?
Can I have black tea?
Understood.
I've won.
He wanted to test me, but it's backfired.
Black tea is my finest specialty!
I can make a perfect black tea fitting of a maid.
Head maid.
What kind of black tea do you have?
None.
"None"? Is that a kind of tea?
Nope. This shop doesn't have black tea.
W-What? No black tea?
Black tea and cake are the staples of a maid café!
Even without that,
if you say maid, you think English,
and if you say English, you think gentleman,
and if you say gentleman, you think black tea!
I don't like black tea.
And making black tea is annoying.
Do you know what character is used to write "tea" in café「喫茶店」?
It's the character that's in black tea「紅茶」for tea!
But the café in maid café means coffee, right?
Jeez, this back and forth...
I don't really know black tea either.
It's like little grey or something, right?
Those are aliens!
You mean Earl Grey?
I know another one. "No-tarin" or something like that.
(Note: ノータリン/no-tarin means idiot)
You're a no-tarin!
You probably meant to say Darjeeling.
The teacher's leaving no openings...
Rather, this shop is full of openings.
I don't feel like we can win.
I see. If we do that, we could underhandedly take that opening.
Arashiyama, we need an original clumsy maid performance. Anything will be fine.
What?
It's an application of your last lesson.
It's ok. You can do it.
If she manages to strike a weak point with her clumsiness...
There's no black tea. Please bear with coffee, teacher.
If she manages to strike a weak point with her clumsiness,
we can find our opening!
Go ahead.
If so, it would be the perfect maid skill control!
Ack! The coffee erupted!
Oppsie! I make a mistake and brought you cola!
Nice! At the very least, Arashiyama,
I was moved by your clumsiness.
This works!
I'll exchange it right away. Hehe
Hold up, Arashiyama.
Coffee is made in a coffee maker with a coffee siphon and such.
Please explain what could possibly lead to mistakenly bringing cola out.
Huh? Uhh
Why?
Umm... the color is similar...
Did you do it on purpose?
No, uh...
I did it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
She's being lectured normally.
Clumsiness is ineffective against the teacher?
Sit there for a moment, Arashiyama.
Uh, ok.
I don't know why you'd do such an illogical thing
but your actions are truly absurd.
Yes.
Do you even know what maids do for their occupation to begin with?
Is there any waiter in the world who enjoys playing tricks on their customers?
No, there is no such waiter.
Getting permission for a part time job seems uncertain, doesn't it?
Now that the lecture's started, Arashiyama has already won, hasn't she?
Speaking of which, Sanada is late...
Why is the homeroom teacher here?
This isn't a joke.
My blissful shop where I could be alone with Arashiyama...
has changed
You're always like that; writing things like 1 = 0.
Do your realize how these things are illogical?
Absurd. You are really absurd.
Everyone wants bliss,
but bliss doesn't find people.
If you ask why, it's because
bliss never looks for people.
Puppy poko poko three poko poko
Together, poko poko six poko poko~
Even if it is the most run down place,
It's a blissful shop
If the customer can have what they desire.
But no matter how the shop might glitter,
if the customer can't have their request fulfilled
The shop may as well be an empty warehouse.
Black tea
Sorry to keep you waiting
What's going on?
Welcome home, master.
You don't like your maid, do you?
Once you've opened the door, you can't escape.
What did you say?
C'mon, to the back.
Welcome. This is your shop of bliss.
1,
Hi,
ひ、
2,
Fu,
ふ、
1, 2, 3, 4
Hi, fu, mi, yo
ひ、ふ、み、よ
Living alone is boring,
Taikutsu ya
退屈や
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
My pufferfish cheeks
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
Pulls the town into chaos.
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
I didn't confess to him today.
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
I play the drums to train
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
My body for ping pong.
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
But this band isn't a fake!
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
The members aren't playing rock!
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
We're not trying to lead the song!
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
We're not looking for Nirvana!
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
We're maids! Yea!
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
メイド姿で参上！参上！
acho-!
アチョー！
They're maids! Yea!
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
acha~
アチャ～
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
enemaaA!
kanchoooO!
かんちょぉぉお！
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
The adults in society are the worst, complaining about sexual harassment.
I thought of destroying them for the good of society.
Isn't that too much?
I tried to tempt one but he wouldn't yield at all.
I wore sexy underwear and pulled up my skirt, you see.
You're unexpectedly bold.
And then he complained about sexual harassment.
What did you expect?
Street 2  [The Sexual Harassment Trial is Popular]
Next time: Street number 2,
The Sexual Harassment Trial is Popular.
Street 2  [The Sexual Harassment Trial is Popular]
We've been all over the place today, poko~