Street No. 11
"Kon-senpai's Summer of Bitter Tears"
And Yet the Town Moves
It's summer!
It's the beach!
You're very excited, aren't you...
Because I bought a brand new swimsuit
and floating ring just for today!
Yay!
If you run, you'll trip!
Whoa!
There's a hole in the floating ring.
Aw, man. See?
It's all wrinkly now...
A sudden rain!
Demons—!
Hotori!
My new swimsuit!
First, hide yourself as a high school girl!
No, as a woman...
As a human being! Please hide it!
Swimsuit!
I'll buy you some curry, so don't cry.
Lady, one curry please.
I'm sorry, we're sold out of curry...
Oh no, she's crying for real...
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
BINBOU-KUN
By Masakazu Ishiguro
Binbou-kun!
For you who are far from luxury, Binbou,
shall I treat you to foods that are like a dream?
Note: The two characters here are "Binbou" meaning "poor"
and "Kanemochi" meaning "rich"
Kanemochi is always so sarcastic...
Crap...
Crap, but I want to eat, so I'll go...
Wow!
If you put this under your pillow and sleep,
you'll be able to see the feast in your dreams.
Ayumu Arashiyama's Morning
My mornings begin with walking Josephine.
Josephine
Maruko Shopping District
The shopping district is very quiet early in the morning,
as if everything but me is stopped in time.
Hello! Good morning!
It seems there's an unseasonable typhoon approaching!
They say it'll be raining hard starting
this evening. I can't stand it!
Yuji is troubled!
I like the quiet shopping district in the morning.
The shopping district is very quiet early in the morning—
Very quiet, as if everything except me is—
Morning!
PRODUCE   KIKU    PRODUCE          PRODUCE   KIKU    PRODUCE
I heard that a typhoon is here!
I need to make it so that the vegetables out front
won't fly away in the strong winds!
PRODUCE              KIKU                  PRODUCE                                    PRODUCE                  KIKU
Um, if these are that heavy,
I don't think they'll fly away that easily.
Y-yes... well... that's true.
When I'm walking in the silence of the morning,
I forget about the hustle and bustle of the day,
and it's as if my heart is cleansed.
At the usual ditch, I say a quick hello to the
woman who always comes here to jog...
Oh, good morning!
I heard there's an unseasonable typhoon coming!
The typhoons that come during the summer
become a downpour!
I wonder if my house is okay in terms of leaks!
I know, I have to check my emergency kit!
That has an expiration date!
My emergency biscuits are so stale!
And at the usual vending machine,
I buy a can of coffee and go home...
COFFEE
Oh?
COIN
RETURN
CHANGE              REFUND
OUT
OF
ORDER
What an unexpected place
to be affected by the sudden wind...
Are you trying to make me feel better, Josephine?
Yeah. Let's go home.
To our warm home...
Whoa! What is going on from left to right?!
Hotori?!
You went to pick up the paper while brushing your teeth
when it was blown away by a sudden wind, huh?
There seems to be an unseasonable typhoon coming.
Be careful of sudden winds and heavy rain.
Daddy, take us somewhere!
We'll settle for the beach!
Daddy isn't on summer vacation.
Why don't you have Big Sister
take you to the community pool?
Awwwwww!
You kids should stop being so selfish!
Hotori, please take the dog out for a walk in the evening.
Awwwwww!
But I'm busy today!
My kids all turned out to be just like my wife.
In this house, it seems my only ally is Josephine.
BINBOU-KUN
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Binbou-kun.
Today we were invited by Kanemochi to catch insects.
Binbou-kun, put that Japanese beetle
into this gold bug cage.
Oh! There are only two bars, so it got away!
We're cutting costs! It is gold after all!
Hotori Arashiyama's Summer
Sis, you're going out too? What about the pool?!
Sis, why are you going to school
even if you're on summer vacation?!
Why? Hey, hey, why?!
Hey, hey, why, hey?!
Hey, why, hey, hey, why?!
Why, why, hey, hey?!
Shut up!
It's not like I'm going because I want to!
You seem to have no worries; I envy that.
Come on, come on!
Oya High School
Even though I woke up early this morning, I'm late!
MATH
SUMMER
SCHOOL
Oh? I thought I was late, but I'm the first one here!
You are late!
Don't tell me, the only one in summer school is just me?
Gasp, deja vu?!
It is no mistake the second time! Why were you late?
Because my dog seemed so happy...
I give a poetic excuse.
Which is not accepted, of course...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hotori Arashiyama
This is the final exam, and this is the make-up test.
In the make-up, I gave the same questions,
with only the numbers changed.
But why did you get a lower score?!
Even if you say that... All I can say
is that I was just unlucky...
Because I'm writing on intuition.
Intuition?!
Just now, you clearly said you wrote on intuition, right?!
This could overturn the foundations of math.
A unique concept...
I...
So that you would be more eager to understand
on your own, I decided to change it up a little bit.
Change?
Listen carefully, Arashiyama.
Detective work and math are similar!
Yeah, yeah.
If you try something different,
you may reap results in an unexpected way...
Hey! I'm saying this seriously!
You got it? In other words...
Look for the culprit given the limited amount of hints.
Gather information and clues
and combine them in an effective manner.
And when you've taken away
all possible contradictions...
It becomes clear who the culprit is.
There is always only one truth!
Isn't it just like a mystery novel?!
Maybe I went too far... if I do say so myself.
I see!
Huh?!
Detective work is math!
All of a sudden, I feel like I can do this!
Is that so?
Inspector Moriaki!
Oh, Arashiyama.
Did you find out the truth?
Inspector! This ominous incident...
...is now a cold case!
Oh, ouch! That hurts...
Ouch! It hurts!
Josephine
I used my head today, so I'm tired...
Because I was playing with you, I was late.
After I finish walking you, I'm gonna take a nap...
Just like summer vacation...
Hey, not that way!
Don't walk on your own!
Don't pick up everything! You'll hurt your tummy.
Trauma   Trauma
Ramen   Fried
Rice
Ramen
Tiger
480   400
yen   yen
Ahotori!
Note: Wordplay combining "aho" (stupid) with "Hotori" and "baka" (stupid) with "Futaba."
Futabaka!
Hey, what do you mean by Futabaka?!
Who are you calling Ahotori?!
Is that your dog?
Uh-huh.
Hey, Senpai!
It's rude to laugh at someone's pet.
I mean... just look at it!
Ramen
It's a tanuki taking a tanuki for a walk!
Trauma   Trauma
Ramen   Fried
Rice
Ramen
Tiger
480   400
yen   yen
Flash
480   400
Video Mode
Camera
Auto Shutter
Trauma   Trauma
Ramen   Fried
Rice
Ramen
Tiger
yen
Tracking AF
A t-tanuki is... a tanuki...
Get her, Josephine!
Bite her!
Josephine?!
Josephine!
Don't get happy! You're being mocked!
Hotori, Hotori, wake up, poko.
It seems I'm not a dog, but a tanuki.
Eh?
I've decided to go back to the mountains, poko.
Thank you for taking care of me all this time, poko.
Josephine?!
Take care, poko.
Josephine!
Jo...
Josephine
Josephine... went back to the mountains...
Josephine!
Your home is here!
The typhoon's here; what's Hotori doing outside?
Come back!
Maybe she's pretending to be in the Takarazuka troupe?
Note: An all-female musical theater troupe based in Takarazuka, Japan.
Josephine!
Maybe she's pretending to be in the Takarazuka troupe?
She's such a girl.
Josephine!
When I say shake, go like this!
If you can't even manage "shake,"
you're going to be called a tanuki again!
Okay. Now, shake!
It's no use.
It's like I'm trying to lean on a curtain.
There's no sign of you being able to do this...
Living in this house, I have come to realize the ranks...
1st place
It probably goes like this.
2nd place
3rd place
4th place
5th place
Last place
My teacher... when he's teaching math to me,
he must be feeling like this...
I have to change my ways...
It seems the only one who is
lower in rank is the tall male...
BINBOU-KUN
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Binbou-kun!
Well, Binbou, I just bought the DVD of a popular movie.
Would you like to come and watch it
on my home theater?
It's not like—
It's not like I've got anything else to do,
plus I haven't seen it, so I'll go.
MOVIE ROOM
Oh! Wonderful.
Just like a popular DVD, isn't it!
Do you not have a DVD player?
BINBOU-KUN
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Binbou-kun...
Oh, it's cold.
Hello Binbou. You look like you're having
financial difficulties as usual.
How about it?
Let me invite you to our winter home.
Darn it, every time he talks it rubs me the wrong way,
but if I stay home I'll be cold...
I guess I'll go.
Here, it's almost done! You should help us too!
Kawai So
Kon Densuke
That was refreshing...
So hot...
Club activities are almost done, huh?
So cool...
FRESH FISH
SANADA
AC
Airflow
Automatic
The setting
on the AC
is lowered
by 3 degrees
The bottled drink
from the refrigerator
is opened without
permission
Lukewarm...
On top of that,
it's not returned
to the fridge
A floating ring
blown up
for no reason
And that
face
While I wasn't around you were doing as you please...
The cat is
locked out
Angry
Hot!
Meanwhile,
Hotori was...
Your drink, Your Highness, poko.
Your buns, poko.
At ease.
Your Highness, a torch, poko.
A torch, poko.
Hey, you guys, it's hot! I don't need any torches!
Oh, I dropped mine, poko.
Fire, poko!
It's hot, poko! So careless, poko!
Hey! Hey wait a minute!
The hammock is tangled!
It's hot! I can't move! Help!
Ugh... Ponpon Fire Mountain... is on fire...
Uh-huh.
For dinner... is sashimi and miso soup okay?
Oh? Weren't you going to make curry?
That's what I had in mind when I went shopping,
but this bushy bald guy said,
"Take some sashimi," and gave it to me.
Huh?! What was that?!
Take this sashimi!
If you eat that sashimi,
maybe you'll become immortal?!
Oh... I see. Bushy Bald Guy is...
BONITO                  FRESH FISH
BROTH                      SANADA
FRESH FISH SANADA
Sanada's dad.
Say, I discovered this...
If you make a Japanese omelet
and add some sugar, it tastes good.
What kind of Japanese omelet
have you been making all this time?
It's the opposite of what you think!
The sugar is the secret to the yumminess.
Yeah, and stuff like mirin.
How is that opposite to what I think?
Let's put sugar in here too.
Oh no you don't!
It's probably very tasty.
No, thank you!
Pretend you were conned into this!
I don't want it!
Sweet is tasty!
I told you to stop.
Scary...
If you don't have anything to do, write some lyrics.
Lyrics?
Sometimes I want to put a song
to words that someone else wrote.
Okay!
Since I'm going to the beach with you tomorrow,
I'll write a verse with "beach" as the theme...
"Seagulls are great..."
"Crows, I don't like..."
"Bye, Johnny of the port."
Is it bad?
It's really bad.
BINBOU-KUN
by Masakazu Ishiguro
Binbou-kun!
Oh, hello.
Hi Binbou, you look like
you're not eating very good food.
I've completed the ultimate mixed rice.
Would you like to come over and eat some?
Damn it, it rubs me the wrong way...
But there must be some awesome
ingredients. I guess I'll go...
I mixed the koshihikari rice and
the sasanishiki rice at a 6 to 4 ratio.
There's no side dish?
Seaside
Open
What's wrong, Tatsuno?
Are you waiting on someone?
No, it's not like that...
Is it the son of the fishmonger?
Hotori is off today.
While there are no unnecessary spectators today...
I'm going to invite Sanada to the beach!
Oh? Where's Arashiyama today?
She's at the beach. With someone.
The beach?! With someone?!
How can this be?!
All because I was dragging my feet!
Arashiyama and some guy at the beach together...!
If this was the case, I should've taken my
chances and confessed my feelings!
Had she dumped me, I could've gotten over it!
But to think I lost just because I was slow...
Come on, now.
Gather your courage and invite Sanada!
"Would
"Would you
"Would you like to
"Would you like to go
"Would you like to go to
"Would you like to go to the
"Would you like to go to the beach?"
It's only eight words and a question mark!
S-say, Sanada... i-if it's all right with you...
W-would... the beach... beach...
Would you like, see squid swimming at the beach?
When it comes to something important
like this, she's so weak.
Oh, what about the beach?!
What about the beach?!
The beach! I'm going to make it cloudy
with the tears in my heart!
Let it rage like my emotions!
Oh. Looks like it's starting to rain.
Eh?
Seaside
Open
My new swimsuit!
First, hide yourself as a high school girl!
No, as a woman...
As a human being! Please hide it!
Swimsuit!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
Checkmate, Hotori!
What was that move?! Hold on!
Really. If you're not going to eat,
I'm going to put it away.
Hold on! I'm saving it!
Hotori, if you're not wearing this,
I'm going to throw it away.
If I just lose a little more weight,
I'd be able to fit into it, so hold on!
It's pretty late. Arashiyama, I'm going ahead.
Hold on, I'm almost done!
Hotori...
Hotori!
Arashiyama...
Everyone, just hold on!
No, we can't!
Next, Street Number Twelve,
"Soremachi."
Cafe Seaside
Street No. 12 "SOREMACHI"
And yet we turn round and round, poko.
Cafe Seaside