Kei-chan, the fact that you're down to 10 coins…
means if someone bets the fixed maximum of 10 coins,
you will be automatically forced to fold.
Meaning, no matter how tough you act, anyone can force you out.
Keiichi. Today's penalty game is to wear a
wonderful costume while parading across the village.
So that means, Keiichi, you'll probably be wearing a school swimsuit with a garter belt, a corset, even dressed as a maid and…
Bingo! Triple 7s and a Joker!
Meaning I have a Four of a Kind.
…you'll be forced to walk around town with your head down low with your face all blushy blushy.
Rena! I would be grateful if you would lend me the 10 coins you just took from me.
I won't.
It's a cruel world.
Damn it…
Turning the tables here is what a true club member would do!
You got that right, but what do you plan to do?
I... will…
I will bet something else to make up for the 10 coins I lack.
…how's that? Will you accept that?
I knew you would do that.
And, Kei-chan, what will you bet to make up for the 10 coins you lack?
I'll wear that school swimsuit, that garter belt, and also become the mini-skirt maid you desire, and let you take me home...
…then I'll clean your ears! How's that!?
I like it, Kei-chan!
You've got the guts to put your body on the line - I like it!
Why is Mii's face all reddy red?
She must be thinking of being alone with maid Keiichi in her room, lying on his lap while she's blushing going "Kya! Kya!"
How's this? Right here?
Yes, there~
You like that, huh?
This is the life.
I-I-I'm n-n-not thinking of t-t-that.
I-I'm just - as the leader! - enjoying this pure match!
If I can take Keiichi-kun home, then I'm not going to lose this one!
And… do you agree?
Will you accept this additional privilege as compensation for what I lack?
Yeah, it'll do. It'll do. It's more than enough.
You don't need to bet any coins.
Lap-pillow ear cleaning is worth the ten coins!
All right. That means you're all in, right?
Don't freak out when you see my cards!
Take this!
It's a Four of a Kind!
It seems the goddess of victory fell in love with me.
Next draw!
I would like to get in on this draw but…
All right, if I lose this draw then I'll dress up as a maid in an apron as I make you dinner and dessert, okay? Okay?
Oh? I also have a hand I can't afford to pass up.
If that's the case, then on top of betting these 10 coins,
I'll bet the right to dress me up in any way you want while I feed you lunch!
Then I'll bet, on top of these 10 coins, the privilege to put a collar on me and walk me on my hands and knees.
You serious?!
This is getting quite interesting.
I like this spirit of betting risk over coins.
Of course you will bet something too, right Mion?
That's true…
Then I'll dress up the way the winner wants me to, and do their homework for them. How's that?
That isn't bad, getting Mion-san to do my math drills.
You can't! I'll win and take you all home!
Rena, be quiet, be quiet! I'm the one who will win!
And I'll make you all my slaves and make you do this and that.
Keiichi, your drool is dribble drabbling.
Bring it on!!!
What the…?
In the end, because everyone won and lost some,
everyone was forced to cosplay and walk around the village.
What the heck was with today's club activity?
There wasn't a single victor; everyone just lost...
Is that how it worked out?
Nothing good can come from fighting, huh?
Where should we go next?
Where to go? That way will take us to Fukudaya.
Over there was… Takatsudo, I think. Or was it Yagouchi?
I've never been to Yagouchi. What kind of place is it?
Yagouchi doesn't have any homes left standing.
It's a sad place.
Then it's decided! Let's go that way!
I don't want to be seen by any more villagers!
Well, if Kei-chan wants to go that badly, then I guess we'll go for a bit.
We'll make it like a walk.
All right! Let's go!
Let's go. Let's go.
Geez, you can't be helped, can you?
I think it's better that we don't.
There's really nothing here…
Does anyone live here?
Before, yeah. But it's been a ghost town for some time now.
There are barely any lights here, so when night comes it gets really dark; I hear that stray dogs gather there, too.
It would probably be better if we stop here and head back.
You're right.
If we get lost in these ridiculous outfits then it'll be an embarrassment that'll be told for seven generations to come!
No doubt.
Besides, there's nothing else beyond here, right?
Beyond that mountain, there's the remains of a stone quarry.
A quarry?
From an old cement firm.
They went bankrupt long ago and now it's unoccupied.
In this lonesome mountain recess, there are remains of an empty quarry?
Sounds interesting.
No. The quarry isn't a place good kids should go.
That's right. Even on our summer vacation leaflet, it said don't go near the quarry.
When you say it like that, any man would want to sneak in even more.
Maybe there's a treasure heap as big as the one at the Dam Management site!
A new treasure mound! Then I want to go too!
I don't recommend it. They say there's a 'hole' there.
Hole? What do you mean by hole?
I've also heard stories about the 'hole.'
But are they true?
I think it's better that you don't approach the 'hole.'
I wonder what it is… Mii-chan, what is this 'hole?'
Ah, that's right. This isn't a story Kei-chan and Rena would know.
They say two people died.
It's a bit of a ghost story.
A ghost story?
I still remember it quite well.
Especially since it could have been me who slipped inside the 'hole.'
There are times when I get really scared.
You, Mii-chan?
I think that was about six or seven years ago.
It was when the Dam War was still peaceful.
The kids were like the ones now in Hinamizawa, playing in the fields and the mountains.
It was about then that the company owning the quarry collapsed.
The good natured president of the company was tricked into co-signing the debt of the employees, but...
They suddenly all absconded.
If I recall, the president committed a double murder-suicide, right?
Yeah… with his wife and young child.
He killed both of them at the quarry's prefab office tent,
and then poured lamp oil over himself and barbequed himself alive.
Wait. Didn't Rika-chan say two people died?
In that story, three people died.
Ah, my bad, my bad.
Those three don't count towards the 'hole' story.
But because of this suicide, the quarry was closed down and became unoccupied.
And then the rumours that the suffering ghost of the president still wandered around the area of the incident began.
That type of story attracts the curiosity of children, don't you think?
Yeah, it certainly does.
So we started thinking, "let's go there to play!"
Has everyone gone there?
I never have.
We were still very little then.
With that random bit of curiosity,
we decided to play Kick the Can there.
No one seemed to care, but there was this strange odour ever since we stepped foot in the quarry.
It stinks.
Odour?
Yeah, how should I explain it?
It was like the smell of a rotten egg.
Like a rotten egg…? Like sulfur?
Yeah, yeah. Like that.
But sulfur... that's usually emited near volanoes, isn't it?
Is that something you'd smell in a quarry?
Don't know…
But we soon stopped noticing it, and continued to play Kick the Can.
Found you, Takashi!
He found you.
Then all of a sudden, out of nowhere, a person who... looked like a worker there charged at us.
You brats! This isn't a playground!
Get out of here!
In the end we all ran away from there and called it a day…
What? Don't tell me that's the end.
It's not.
What's wrong, Mii-chan?
There was a boy who didn't come home no matter how late it got.
He didn't come home…?
When that man scolded us, we all panicked and ran home separately so we didn't know, but…
He probably… had already disappeared at that time.
Isn't that…
He met with Oyashiro-sama's Curse and was Onikakushi'd,
is what they say.
Onikakushi?
It's another ghost story of Hinamizawa.
A ghost story… huh?
Yeah…
His parents called everyone's houses, but...
None of the children had returned together with him.
And… what happened?
The father thought that he might have possibly gotten into an accident on his way back alone, so he drove to the quarry…
And… was the boy found?
Rather than being found…
the father didn't come back either.
If I recall, the car was found by the river banks in Yagouchi on the path towards Hinamizawa, with both of their bodies inside.
That's a sad story. When the father finally found him and they were on their way back home...
This is where the story gets strange.
It seems the scene of the accident is pretty close to the quarry.
Why is it strange for the scene of the accident to be close to the quarry?
Because, it was quite late when the father went looking for him by car.
To the point where the surrounding area would be pitch black.
That would mean the boy stayed at the quarry until then.
Maybe he was caught by that worker man and was being scolded?
About that… The police looked into it, and they said there wasn't anyone at the quarry that day.
That can't be.
There was no doubt a strange man did chase us out.
No doubt at all.
And now there's the rumour that maybe that worker was a ghost.
That can't be. There's no ghost that makes that much noise as they run heavily!
Putting the identity of that man aside…
What I don't get is why the kid stayed at the quarry until dark.
The rumour is that maybe he fell into the 'hole.'
'Hole?'
We returned back to the 'hole' again, but what is this 'hole?'
It's a 'hole!' A very deep one.
They say it's so deep that it goes to the depths of the earth and connects to the kingdom of Demons.
In the lore of Onigafuchi, it's said that beneath the village is the kingdom of Demons.
Meaning Hell is there.
And it was suggested that maybe there's a hole there that connects the two worlds.
I see. That's why it's called Onikakushi, huh?
But that kid couldn't have vanished, right? He was able to meet with his father and was in an accident afterwards, right?
Didn't I say this at the beginning, that there was a sulfuric odour in the quarry that day?
It seems that when the first person to find the car peered into the vehicle,
he smelled a slight odour of rotten eggs from inside the car.
The sulfuric odour!
The smell of sulfur isn't normal.
Isn't it called hydrogen sulfide, the poisonous gas that reeks with a sulfuric odour?
Every so often, there are stories on the news about workers getting poisoned while cleaning an industrial liquid waste tank, right?
So maybe there was a tank like that at the quarry, and there was a crack which leaked out the bad gas?
Indeed, then the story would make sense.
While he was playing Kick the Can, he walked into a bad area, and breathed in the awful gas from the waste tanks and fell unconscious.
And when the father found him, he must have also breathed in the bad gas.
I see. If you explain it that way, it clears up this old mystery easily.
Well, there's no way to know the truth,
but even so, I think there's something lurking underneath it all that makes this accident not just any accident.
If it wasn't just any accident, then what do you think is lurking underneath?
Hmmm, let's see…
There are several things that stand out.
The worker who shouldn't have been there.
The reason the boy stayed at the quarry until dark.
And then the bizarre death in the car.
Well, if we go to the quarry, we can find out whether or not there really is a dangerous gas leak.
Mion, don't tell me you're actually thinking of going.
If that is true, then the quarry is a dangerous place even now.
I don't agree to going to such a place, I guess…
Well, it's now piqued my interest.
After listening to Kei-chan's theory, I feel like I could see the truth behind this ghost story.
Kei-chan, aren't you interested?
Don't you want to know the real truth?
Mii...
There are places that are taboo.
You said a difficult thing there, Rika-chan.
What do you mean by place of taboo?
Keiichi… In this world, just as wherever there is Light there will always be Darkness;
while there are good places, there will also be bad places.
By stepping into those places for no apparent reason, there are times when sorrow will be brought upon you.
Those terrible places we humans can't describe well with words...
We call those places… taboo.
They say that curiosity killed the cat.
It might be better not to be interested in places with awful rumours.
That's true… I agree with Rena-san.
Is that so?
Let's go home now. If I don't get home by dark, my dad will get worried.
That's true. If his daughter came home dressed like that late at night, he might faint.
The same goes for you, Keiichi-kun.
I suppose there's no choice, then. I guess I'll give in and call it a day.
Yeah, let's go home, go home.
Keiichi?
If I secretly came back and went adventuring at the quarry,
would I also fall in that 'hole' and become Onikakushi'd?
You would.
I see. Then I guess I shouldn't get close to it.
Oooh, Kei-chan. You're not really scared, are you?
Don't be stupid.
Your knees are shaking.
No way they are!
Hey! Wait!
This is for the best.
Even if you don't come looking for it, the Curse will come to you.
Because… it's almost Watanagashi now…
Don't you think there are a lot of cats?
And they seem like they're angry about something…
I wonder what the problem is…?
Well, look at the title.