It's not that I don't like running.
Kurumi, Kurumi, look! Senpai's here!
But my reasons for joining the Track Club
weren't entirely pure.
I wasn't even really fit to be the manager.
I thought those wonderful days would never end.
It's morning, Senpai!
Senpai!
Senpai, please wake up!
Time for breakfast!
Mmm... Bring it to me...
Mii-kun, that's not what a ladle's for.
I know that, but everyone's waiting on us,
so let's pick up the pace.
Sorries...
What's this smell?!
Not again.
Stop lazing around, Mii-kun, let's get moving!
I knew it was curry!
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
So you finally caught wind of the smell.
Morning! We're starting the day off great, huh!
Yeah, we've been eating nothing but
emergency rations lately, huh.
Oh, but make sure you take your vitamin, okay?
But it's a little heavy for breakfast.
You think I'll get fat if I eat this?
Oh, my.
We're all going through our growth spurt right now,
so I think you'll be fine.
That's right, we're still young!
Oh, okay!
Alright, shall we eat?
Yeah!
Let's eat!
Let's eat...
Thanks for the food!
Sure!
Okay, I've gotta go to class.
That's right, you're going to study hard with me!
A one-on-one lesson with Megu-nee!
Why're you all excited?
'Cause I get to be all alone with Megu-nee!
It's gonna be fun!
Doesn't seem like you wanna study.
Gulp!
Of course I do!
Okay, we're off!
See ya!
See you later!
C'mon, Megu-nee, hurry!
Yesterday, Yuki-senpai...
was talking to people in the classroom.
By herself.
Uh-huh...
Shouldn't we do something about her?
I mean, she said she almost went home
by herself not so long ago.
It's dangerous.
I'd disagree.
Right now, Yuki-chan has Megu-nee with her.
And in these circumstances,
don't you think it's great that she can
enjoy herself like this?
But...!
We're not experts on the matter.
Maybe it's best if we watched over her a little longer.
Okay.
Alright, Kurumi Ebisuzawa's
going out for morning rounds!
See you later.
Be careful, okay?
I know, I know!
Okay, let's go.
Okay, Yuki-cha... Takeya-san.
Can you solve this?
Okay!
Alright, then come up to the board, please.
Don't be so frank about it.
Just kidding!
This problem's super easy, Megu-nee!
It's Sakura-sensei!
We've got ten cans of hardtack left.
Thanks.
We're getting low on provisions.
And I'm not sure how much electricity we have left.
We'll have to cut down a bit.
Yeah, it's been really cloudy lately.
Still, it's amazing that the school has both
a vegetable garden and solar panels.
True.
But I'd say you're pretty amazing yourself, Miki-san.
H-huh?
You did really well in that mall all by yourself.
Oh, I wasn't alo...
Looks good.
Wow, Takeya-san.
They're all incorrect.
Huh?!
Oh, thank you very much.
I wonder how widespread this is?
I hope it's just our town.
It might be affecting all of Japan.
I don't think it's spread to the whole world, though.
I'm sure someone will come save us, one day.
It's just one... I can take it.
Just one...
No.
That's not...
the same.
Good night.
I'm tired.
Keep it up just a little more.
Once classes are over...
It'll be summer vacation!
What do you want to do on vacation?
Hmm, let's see...
I wanna go to the beach, and the mountains,
and I wanna do fireworks!
Also, umm...
Where else should I go?
It's my last summer as a high schooler,
so I wanna go and do everything I wanna do!
Hey, Megu-nee?
What do you want to do on your last summer vacation?
Hmm, let's see...
Maybe a test of courage?
Ooh, you gotta do that!
Take one out again?
I told you, you just have to keep watch.
Yeah.
I just happened to be in the right spot.
It's dangerous to go alone.
You don't need to worry.
I'm the club president.
Ahem!
Yeah, yeah.
Look, they're playing soccer again.
Aren't they just reacting to the noise?
Maybe their last memories of life
on Earth are still with them.
What's wrong?
Maybe someone was running on the track.
Yeah.
School Living Club, attention!
We're gonna do a test of courage!
A test of courage?
I can see up your skirt, Mii-kun.
Don't look!
S-sorry!
It's alright.
Okay, let's start the test of courage!
Are you sure this is alright?
Everyone coming over the barrier...
I understand...
But we are running out of provisions.
I wanted to come this way anyway.
And I'd be worried leaving Yuki-chan all by herself.
Alright, why don't we get going?
Kurumi?
Huh?
Yeah, let's go!
Hey, girls!
Don't tell me you're going to leave me alone again!
No, no.
Test of courage!
We're all going to test our courage!
You really don't see much of them at night, huh?
Kurumi-chan!
Mii-kun!
You really don't see much of them at night, huh?
Yeah. Maybe they all went home.
Ri-san!
Taromaru!
Do you think that's part of their past memories?
Test of courage!
Test of cou-
Hey.
Could you be a little more nervous about this?
Oh ho?
Are you afraid of monsters, Kurumi-chan?
Maybe we should've left her behind.
I don't see any monsters.
Looks like we're alright for now.
But a monster might jump out
all of a sudden, so stay quiet, okay?
It's Megu-nee!
No, no, you have to be quiet.
Remember what Ri-san just said?
Okay!
Oh, I didn't know Megu-nee was here.
Good work today, Megu-nee.
Y-yeah, good work.
Okay, I'll explain the rules of-
Alright, I'll explain the rules.
We're going into the school store and the library.
Everyone must bring something back as proof.
If we get separated, stay quiet and come back here.
Okay!
Okay, let's go, then!
C'mon, hurry, Megu-nee!
I'm... your advisor...
Are you sure it's okay to turn the lights on?
I don't think there are any
outside-facing windows in here,
so it shouldn't draw any of them here.
As long as we're careful about the door here, we're fine.
Wow, it's been so long since I came to the school store!
Can we buy anything?
Yup, we'll pay for it with club funds.
Yay!
She went right for the candy.
Yep.
Yes.
Well then, let's gather some other kinds of supplies.
What should I get?
Chocolate or chips?
Oh my gosh...
Unmaibo!
Girls, come quick!
What is it?!
Yuki-chan!
These are awesome! It says they can
grow to twenty times their size!
Aren't they cool? Twenty times, not just two!
They're so cool! A scientific marvel!
Is that why you called us over?
Uh-huh!
Don't scare us during a test of courage!
S-sorry!
What would you use these for, anyway?
Unmaibo?!
Let's see...
Oh, we could make balloon animals!
We could make anything with these!
I don't know how to make those.
Hey, what are you two eating?!
Are you all done shopping?
Uh-huh.
Okay, next up is the library, then.
We're going to the library next.
I want some math textbooks.
I want some books, too.
I want manga!
Guess Unmaibo is all the rage right now.
It sure is dark in here. Wanna turn on the lights?
Hmm, maybe.
But people might see us in here
if we turn on the lights.
That's right, we're doing a test of courage!
What's wrong, Taromaru?
Maybe he's scared to go in.
Then I'll wait here with Taromaru.
Okay, Taromaru?
Ru...?
Uhh, I'll wait with her.
Ru...
I'm kinda worried about her.
Alright, we'll be back.
Wanna lay off the Unmaibo?
I'll tone it down.
Textbooks, workbooks, and...
That's the Ri-san I know, you just love studying!
No, these are for you, Yuki-chan.
You did say you had a hard time with math.
I-I'm gonna go find a book, too!
Hey, wait!
Yuki-chan! Don't go off alone!
Ooh, this one's interesting.
Oh, Megu-nee!
Hey now, you can't run off on your own like that!
You'll scare Ri-san!
Sorry.
Let's go back to everyone, okay?
Okay.
Huh?
A monster?
Be quiet!
Megu-nee...
was that...
It's okay.
Everyone cares about you.
They'll come to save you.
If you're with them, you don't
have to be scared of monsters.
Right?
Stay right here.
Hey, over here!
Oh, there she is!
Are you okay, Yuki-chan?!
Are you hurt?
I'm...
I'm sorry!
There, there.
You were smart to stay right where you were.
Uh-huh, I was really scared of the monster,
but Megu-nee was with me, so I was okay!
Thank you, Megu-nee.
Th-thank you.
H-huh?
Thank you very much!
M-my, even Ebisuzawa-san...
It's alright, I'm your advisor, after all.
Hey, Yuki-chan, did you have fun
with the test of courage?
Yeah!
It was really fun!
Let's do one again next year!
Yeah!
Sure.
You're all third-years, right?
Are you going to retake a year?
Yuki probably will, huh?
Yes.
Kurumi-chan, Ri-san, you're so mean!
Oh, but if I did, I could graduate with you, Mii-kun!
Graduate with you, Senpai?
I want to go to college with you, Senpai!
That's right. You've gotta graduate too, Taromaru!
What's that, you want to go to Tokyo U?
Kurumi?
He can talk?
Sorry. I'm coming.
Kurumi-chan.
Let's stay... together... next year...
Good night.
You're so cool, Kurumi-chan!
Oh yeah! Maybe you should carry a shovel, Megu-nee!
Huh? Me?
Then you'd be Shovel Sensei! You'd be super strong!
I'm not good at carrying heavy things.
Next time on School-Live, episode 3:
"Back Then"