Hey, wake up.
Wake up, Hachiman.
No way.
Could this be a morning kiss?
A real morning kiss?
You're finally awake.
Morning ki—
Everyone already left.
You're gonna miss breakfast if you don't hurry.
Oh, right.
I'm at a training camp.
Summer vacation really throws off your routine.
Guess so.
You haven't exercised at all, right?
Let's play tennis some time.
Sure.
Just call me when you want to play.
Okay.
So... could you tell me your email address?
So far my phone's only purpose was to kill time, tell time, or wake me up on time...
At last, it shall have Totsuka's email address.
Why are you crying, Hachiman?
I'll send you something as a test.
Inbox
Totsuka Saika
It's Saika
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
It's Saika.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
Morning, Hachiman.
This is my first
message to you.
Let's continue being friends.
What's wrong, Hachiman?
Are you okay?
In this room filled with light,
I'll be waiting for you
If you'd realize you're floating and gazing upon a box,
You'd notice it doesn't return your gaze
The reflected heart is pure white
Just like the light from the falling snow
This shivering rain that blankets me
Isn't going to dispel until the spring breeze returns
So let's search for some azalea
Bring me with you to a comforting garden
Is not something I can ask
That fairy tale-like happiness isn't real
I know that much already
But still
I want to go there
All right. Here's the plan for today.
Tonight, we'll do a test of courage and have a campfire.
The afternoon is free time for the kids, so use that time to prepare.
A campfire, huh?
We'll be doing a folk dance.
Dancing like Bentora Bentora Space People, right?
Do you mean Oklahoma Mixer?
They don't really sound alike though.
It doesn't really make a difference.
You'll be like an alien to your partner anyway.
That's mean, Hachiman.
Not really.
I've got my excuses.
We had a campfire in elementary school.
We don't really need to hold hands, right?
All the girls after that did the same thing.
I did an Air Oklahoma Mixer all by myself.
Hikigaya, your eyes are looking rotten again.
Well, I guess they're perfect for a monster.
So we'll be doing the scaring during the test of courage?
I've already got your monster costumes ready.
Divide up the work.
Okay!
Hiya!
Up we go.
And so I'm silently stacking logs by myself.
It's just like Jenga.
Huh? You can play Jenga alone?
What? You can't?
I'm done.
See?
Jenga is fun because you assemble it all by yourself.
Am I wrong?
I'm... wrong?
It's hot...
It's hot. It's hot...
That looks nice.
It's cold!
Oh, it's you, Bro!
Over here!
Hikki.
Hey!
What're you two doing?
Rather, why are you in swimsuits?
Ms. Hiratsuka said we could play in the river.
Forget about that! I got a new bikini!
See?
See!
And my compliments?
Huh? Sure.
You're the cutest in the world.
Yay, now I totally feel complimented!
Well then.
How about Yui?
Wai—
Komachi!
U-Um...
What was it again?
Looks nice.
It suits you.
Really?
Thanks.
Crap.
My eyes are spontaneously gravitating in her direction.
Is this the law of universal gravitation?
Newton really was the breast.
Oh? Are you apologizing on your knees to the river?
Of course no—
So you came too, Hikigaya?
You really can pull it off if you try, Ms. Hiratsuka.
If you say you're around thirty, people will actually belie—
I'm still a fabulous around thirty-year-old.
Huh? So you don't go to Akihabara?
No. No.
It's Ikebukuro. Ikebukuro!
Totally different.
I mean, they're totally different locations.
Akihabara is to the right of Yamanote, so it's the sub. Ikebukuro is above, so it's the dom. Get it now?
Ha, I win.
Well, considering how your older sister looks,
I think you should be more hopeful with those genes.
What does my older sister have to do with this?
It's fine!
A girl's worth isn't decided by that!
Everyone is different.
I'm on your side, Yukino!
Well, thank you.
Sister? Genes?
Worth? Differences?
I'm really not worried about that at all.
If a person's value is decided by their physical appearance,
then the deciding factor should be the overall balance, not an individual part.
Don't give up just yet, Yukinoshita.
Take that!
Jeez, Komachi!
Now I'm all wet!
Getting Totsuka all wet, huh?
Sup.
Why are you alone?
Didn't bring a swimsuit.
You?
They said today is free time.
No one was there when I went back to the room after breakfast.
Why don't you play with us, Rumi?
I see.
Hey, Hachiman...
No respect for elders, huh?
Hachiman, do you have any friends from elementary school?
Nope.
It's probably the same for everyone though.
So you shouldn't worry about it.
You won't hang out with any of them after graduating anyway.
That's just you, Hikki.
I haven't met with any of them either.
That's just because these two are unique, Rumi.
What's wrong with being unique?
It's "special" in English.
It's like we're awesome.
More like "strange" in Japanese in your case.
Yuigahama, how many of your elementary school classmates do you still hang out with?
One or two, I guess.
And how many students in your grade?
Three classes of thirty. Why?
That means the chances of staying friends five years after graduation are about 3-6%.
And that's for Yuigahama who's pretty much friends with everyone.
Pretty?
Yuigahama, he's not really praising you.
Listen up.
Ordinary people aren't friends with everyone.
Most people just get along with 25% of their classmates.
So you can divide that by four, and you're left with 1%.
1% might as well be a calculation error.
Just round it to zero.
I'm sure you know how to round up and down at least.
But when I think about 1% being good enough, I feel a bit at ease.
There are definitely times I get tired of getting along with everyone.
But my mom doesn't get it.
She always tells me to get along with my friends.
She told me to take a lot of pictures with this digital camera at summer camp too.
I see...
Besides, I feel like I'm always the one who gets left out.
I hate it. It's pitiful.
But there's nothing I can do about it...
Why not?
I've been abandoned.
I can't get along anymore.
Even if I could, who knows when this will happen again.
Then things are fine the way they are.
I get it.
This girl has given up already.
People often say, "If I change myself, I'll change the world."
That's a load of crap.
People's judgment of others creates a stereotype, and that's the impression that lasts.
Loners are forced to do things alone.
If you try to stand out by working hard at something,
you just become a target for attack.
It's the rotten rule of the children's kingdom.
Do you hate being pitiable?
Yeah.
Then I hope you enjoy the test of courage.
Hikki?
What's wrong, Hikki?
Question: The world won't change. But you can change yourself. So how should you change?
Answer: I'll become the god of the new world.
She did say monsters for the test of courage, right?
What's with these cheap costumes then?
In the name of the heavens...
This is an exercise in futility.
Exorcists are fine with me too!
Demons begone!
I see.
Are magicians monsters?
Well, they are if you really generalize.
But this isn't scary.
No, it is. Don't worry.
It's seriously scary.
At this rate, I feel like I'll end up taking the Totsuka route before I know it.
Seriously scary.
Hey, Bro.
Tada!
What's that? A cat monster?
Probably.
I don't really know.
It's cute though, so it doesn't matter.
Are you appraising it or something?
It certainly looks good on you.
Thank you!
You look ridiculously good in a kimono. Just like a snow woman.
That looks good on you too. The zombie outfit, I mean.
Those rotten eyes are Hollywood-tier.
I don't have any makeup on. Didn't even have to change.
You seem busy over there.
Oh, Hikki.
U-Um, how is it?
I would've let you know if it didn't look good on you.
I definitely would've made fun of you.
Unfortunately, I can't.
U-Um...
Oh!
Why didn't you just compliment me in the first place?
Dummy!
You sure are a twisty lovey dovey type, Bro.
Don't make up weird terms.
So what do we do about the problem?
I guess Rumi will just have to talk with everyone.
If she did, she'll probably just get ganged up on.
Then what if she talks to people individually?
It'll be the same.
Even if they act nice, it'll just go back to how it was when she looks away.
Girls are much scarier than you think, Hayato.
For real? That's scary.
Hey, I've got an idea.
I doubt it's anything decent.
Well, just listen.
We've got the test of courage tonight.
We can utilize this chance.
How?
If you have any worries about your relationships,
by breaking them, your worries will disappear.
If everyone is turned into loners, there won't be any more conflict or quarrels.
All right!
Next up is this group right here!
Once you start, please bring back the talisman from the shrine deep in the forest.
Rawr! I'm going to eat you!
I look like an idiot...
It's about time.
It's just me.
Huh? Hikigaya?
I thought you were a ghost because of those dead eyes.
Oh, really?
How's the plan going?
Komachi:
Here we go!as
That's the start signal.
And the last ones up are... you guys!
Oh, it's just them.
You're all dressed normally.
So lame!
This test of courage isn't scary at all.
You guys are so stupid for high schoolers!
Huh?
Who do you think you're talking to here?
Hey, aren't you girls being a little too arrogant?
We aren't really your buddies or whatever.
Y'know, one of these bitches made fun of us.
Who was it?
I'm sorry.
I asked who it was.
You think this is a game?
Well?
Get 'em. Get 'em.
Isn't it our job to teach these brats some manners?
Can I properly teach them now, Hayama?
Let's do it this way.
We'll let half of you go.
The other half stays here.
You can decide who stays amongst yourselves.
I'm sorry.
We don't want your apologies.
I said half will stay. Now pick.
Are you deaf?
Or are you just ignoring him?
Hurry it up!
Who's staying?
Will it be you? Huh?
Tsurumi.
You stay.
Yeah. You should.
What happens after this is what you're after, right?
Yeah.
We're going to destroy the relationships around Tsurumi Rumi.
When a person experiences something truly frightening,
they can't think of anyone but themselves.
They'll sacrifice everyone else for their own safety.
After seeing that ugly side of one another, they won't be able to get along anymore.
That way, we'll break them apart.
That won't actually solve the problem though, will it?
No, but we can get rid of it this way.
"It's wrong to run away" is something only the strong think.
It's not always you that's in the wrong.
In society, the world, and your surroundings,
there are plenty of times when someone else is mistaken.
"I can change."
That means conforming like the indifferent trash living in this harsh world.
It's admitting defeat and giving in to subordination.
It's no more than deceiving yourself with pretty words.
So that's how you think?
I understand a little better why she looks out for you.
"She"?
Okay. Let's do that.
However, I think they'll all work together and deal with it.
I think they're all good kids at heart.
That leaves two more.
Hurry up.
If you hadn't said that earlier, Yuka...
It's Yuka's fault.
Yeah!
No, it's not!
Hitomi was first!
I didn't say anything!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Mori had a bad attitude!
She's always like that.
Even with the teachers.
That has nothing to do with this!
Just stop already!
We should all just apologize!
I hate girls who think all they have to do is cry the most.
We'll wait 30 more seconds.
Choose the last two.
You know what's gonna happen if you tattle, right?
We've remembered all your faces!
20 seconds left.
Then it's gotta be Yuka.
You stay, Yuka.
I think so too.
Go on then.
Hey! Don't push me!
Yuka!
Sorry...
But there's no choice.
One more.
10.
9.
8.
All that's left is to just say something like "Just kidding! Did we scare you?" and we should be okay.
Wait.
Why?
Look.
4.
3.
2.
1!
Hey!
This way! Hurry!
Wa—
My eyes...
What was that?
A digital camera's flash?
That girl saved everyone?
So they really were all friends?
There's no way they're genuine friends when they need to bring someone else down to do it.
Really?
I guess not.
But if she extended her hand despite knowing they were fake,
I'm pretty sure that's genuine.
You crossed a dangerous bridge.
Just one little misstep could've turned into a huge problem.
Well, sorry.
I'm not criticizing you.
In fact, I think you did a good job with so little time.
The methods were deplorable though.
Yeah. You're deplorable.
Why are you judging me as a person?
Weren't we talking about the method?
Coming up with that kind of method is deplorable.
But it may be because you're deplorable that you can give support to those who've hit rock bottom.
That habit of yours is really valuable.
What a crappy way of praising me.
There's no reward for you, I guess.
Well, I didn't do anything good anyway.
Things are easier now that the people plotting against her are gone.
Despite the means being deplorable, you made this happen.
So...
Even if no one praises you it, I'm sure it wouldn't be a problem if at least one good thing happens for you.
Sorry for the wait!
Here! Fireworks!
Let's use this one!
Look, Yukinon!
That's dangerous.
Sorry about making you the bad guy.
I don't mind.
It wasn't that bad.
It's just...
It made me remember stuff from the past.
Like not doing anything about a similar situation before.
What do you think would have happened if we went to the same elementary school, Hikitani?
Your school would've just had one more loner.
I think things may have turned out quite differently.
But, still...
I don't think I would've been friends with you, Hikigaya.
I'm just joking.
Good work everyone.
The training camp continues until you return home.
Be careful on your way home.
Dismissed!
Komachi, let's go shopping before heading home.
Aye-aye, sir!
How about you come with us, Yukino?
Hi, Yukino!
Sis?
You weren't coming home at all, Yukino.
I was worried, so I came to pick you up.
Oh, it's Hikigaya!
Was this a date? Huh, was it?
Didn't I say it wasn't like that?
Um, Hikki doesn't like that!
Are you Hikigaya's girlfriend, perhaps?
No!
I'm his classmate, Yuigahama Yui.
His classmate?
Yes.
That's it? Splendid!
I don't know what I would've done if I thought you were getting in Yukino's way.
Keep your hands off Hikigaya, okay?
He's Yukino's.
I'm not hers.
He's not mine.
See? They're in sync.
Leave it at that, Haruno.
Long time no see, Shizuka.
Stop calling me that.
Do you know her, Ms. Hiratsuka?
She's a former student.
That means...
Let's get going then, Yukino.
Mom's waiting.
Sorry to do this after you invited me...
I won't be able to go with you.
Huh? O-Okay...
Goodbye.
Bye bye, Hikigaya!
We're good to go, Tsuzuki.
Say...
That car...
Well, all black luxury cars look the same after all.
I was hurt back them more than anything else.
I don't remember what every single car looks like.
I went and said things I didn't mean.
The truth is that I realized it the instant I saw it.
That summer vacation,
I didn't see Yukinoshita Yukino again.
One day, those guys and girls will learn the truth.
Shining in the bright blue sky I hate so
An airplane soars toward the horizon
Something is stirring from within my heart
I keep all the things I want to say pent up
And turn them into things I can no longer say
I can't even be honest until the end
Just forget that I wanted to be with you,
And that I set you free
If I had told you I wanted to see you
Before the faint trail you left behind vanished,
I would be freed from this
Heartbreak that never ends
I could be here with you again
Hello! Hello! Alone!
Don't expect that kind of thing of me.
Don't expect that
kind of stuff
from me.
But I want to know more...
I want to
know more...
Get to know each other better,
and get along better...
I want us
to be closer.
I want to help each other when there's trouble.
I want to help
each other when there's
trouble.
And...
I'm sure I'd..
I'm sure
I'd...
Yet again, he returns from whence he came.
Next time.