Thank you both very much!
Aisaka-senpai, we've been blessed with good fortune thanks to you!
Yeah, we have!
pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed that and I've won
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade
The Palmtop Tiger of Happiness
Do you know them?
I have absolutely no connection with them.
How dare they act so indecent so early in the morning!
Taiga!
What's with them?
A-Aisaka-san.
What the hell is wrong with you guys?!
Why did you dodge us, Taiga?
I won't ask you to bite me.
You can just step on me with your feet like this, then rub my head against your armpits.
That's disgusting! Don't come near me, you guys.
What is going on?
I think there's something wrong, with all this jinxing happening.
Look, like this.
Stupid Chihuahua, what the hell are you doing?
Oh, my. Ami-chan's beautiful face is...
It's uncensored.
See, I proved that the rumor was false.
I've received bad luck immediately!
Don't smear it on my skirt!
You got some sticky stuff on me. How are you going to pay for it?
You probably did it yourself.
What's this rumor?
You see, things happened to the guests who watched our pro wrestling show during the cultural festival,
especially to the ones who were kicked and hit by Taiga.
Basically, everyone touched by Taiga was blessed with good fortune.
Good fortune?
Correct.
Some have received sudden confessions,
others suddenly inherited huge fortunes from previously unknown grandfathers.
Happiness is being unleashed!
It's like absolutely any wish will be granted.
That's the "Legend of the Happy Palmtop Tiger" which is circulating.
I see.
So that's what's going on.
Why the hell is this?!
Everyone is just messing around!
So Taiga, just a little...
Don't act like you're close to me!
Regardless of how many people try, I won't let anyone touch me.
Good morning, everyone!
Why are all of you gathered around here-
Minorin!
The only one who can touch me is Minorin!
Stop. Stop. Stop.
You're a good girl...
So you'll become happy if you touch Taiga, huh?
On that day, Taiga must've been really far away from happiness.
If Taiga made anyone happy on that day...
That'd be...
What is it? Hurry up and give me my lunch box.
Oh, yeah.
...very ironic.
Takasu-kun is so ironic.
I mean, he's like the closest to Aisaka-san.
Aisaka-san looked like she had a lot fun while dancing with Maruo.
They say you'll receive good fortune if you touch her, but it's so ironic that he's always by her side.
She was even stolen from him by Maruo so easily at the Cultural Festival.
W-What?
These strange rumors-
That's so pitiful.
Yeah, Kitamura-kun stole me away from you.
Hey, shouldn't you stop these rumors?
Well, as a dog's ex-girlfriend, my feelings are a bit mixed.
I'm a human, after all, but it seems like I abandoned you.
Then Kitamura-kun and I...
I should never worry for you.
Oh, thanks.
Now, it's time to get back to my seat.
The unmarried woman with her unmarried face will come to start the unmarried homeroom!
Unmarried face...
Oh, Takasu-kun's lunch box looks as delicious as usual!
Are those fresh spring rolls?
O-Oh, I just wrapped some leftover salad with rice paper.
You're good!
Takasu-kun is amazing, the rice is amazing as well!
You're being targeted, Taiga.
Seriously, I can't eat in peace.
That's not convincing at all.
May I sit with you guys?
Aisaka, don't get overwhelmed by the Cultural Festival rumor.
W-Which one do you mean?
Oh, it's nothing! Never mind!
Speaking of which, the Cultural Festival was amazing!
Yeah, it was!
Our class won everything, the class showdown, the beauty contest and Mr. Lucky Guy!
It was great!
Yeah, it was all thanks to you, Aisaka.
That's not-
Taiga?
H-Hey...
Hey, drink this!
No!
Huh? But...
I won't drink anything but orange juice!
Do you understand what's happening?
Seriously, every single time.
Well, I guess it's good that she's back to normal.
Yeah, I know,
but I have a test soon.
Yeah.
Anyway, just give me a little more time.
All right, I'll call later.
See you.
Yo.
Who were you on the phone with?
Oh, do you want to know my secret?
I don't really care.
Uh... Orange juice...
Juice during lunch?
My gosh, you're such a kid.
Not me, it's for Taiga.
She said she doesn't want coffee or milk.
Wha- Y-You...
Later.
What should I do now?
This is...
Don't run in the hallways! - Student Council
Calcium Chloride Kick!
You're so fricken' slow! I had no other choice but to drink from the tap!
How are you going to make up for it?!
Damn you! You just suddenly...
Hey, are you all right?
I-I'm sorry! It wasn't on purpose.
Aisaka-senpai, I had a favor to ask of you,
so I thought I'd pick up the juice and ask.
You again?
You've been following me around for some time now.
Some time?
Oh, the one who thought he'd be blessed with good fortune if he touched you...
Y-Yes!
Well, I have someone I like very much!
So I want to go and-
Yeah, go...
to heaven.
Seriously.
It's a game of survival in order to receive happiness.
Come on, let's go, lunch break is nearly over.
Huh, where to?
They say pictures from the Cultural Festival were put up.
What about lunch?
I've finished it already, so hurry up!
But I haven't-
Let's go!
You're holding me pretty tightly too.
Huh? Don't make it sound so sick!
That's right, I've touched Taiga so much,
theoretically I should be the happiest person.
God, she looks really happy in that picture.
It's number 133, don't get it wrong.
Sh-Shut up.
But you know, it's a great picture.
Minorin?
Taiga, listen, pay close attention to Amin in number 200.
The codeword is "underboob."
You're such a shockingly perverted dog.
Oh, my bad.
Seriously, sometimes your libido is so strong that I want to kill you.
That's a great way to cross the line.
If you're interested in Stupid Chihuahua's underboob, then I'll tell you about it.
She has six boobs! I saw them!
Sure.
I'm getting dirtier just from being around you.
Minorin, I'm checking out that side.
Taiga, damn you...
Takasu-kun, it's time to begin...
our duel of fate!
I will now sacrifice 90 yen and summon 9 pictures here.
Then, I will reveal my face-down card!
Activate, quick-play magic "Immediate Discovery."
Picture number 93, which includes the lower-classmen from the baseball club, will cost just 10 yen.
End turn.
Uhh...
It's your turn now, Takasu-kun.
Huh? Turn?
Gosh, don't play stupid.
I'm just asking you to show me which pictures you're buying.
Oh, is that so?
You should summon the class group photo in face-up attack mode.
What is she talking about? I don't even...
Show me! Show me!
Oh, 85.
85... 85... 85...
No, don't get the wrong-
I'll buy this one too so I can have the memory.
O-Okay.
Buy it, yeah, for the memory...
What's up with you?
You're only buying pictures of Sugou from Class B.
Shut up! Don't look!
How could you like her pictures? You're so lame.
Huh? What about...
Then let's go to that shop next time.
Everyone's getting so hyped up because of a few pictures.
They're all so childish.
Amin...
You know, photo shoots are part of my job.
The pictures are sold all over Japan.
I don't really care who has my pictures or that they think about them.
In the end they're just pictures.
Yeah, they're just pictures,
you're right.
They're just pictures.
My, my, as expected of Amin-sensei!
You're so mature!
How should we get back?
Can we drop by the station today?
Sure. You have something to do there?
You know, recently...
Unmarried face... Unmarried love... Unmarried palm reading...
Oh, my foretold wealth is decreasing...
Teacher!
What do you want from the back of an unmarried person, Kawashima-san?
I've noticed it this morning...
Your wool sweater was shown in this year's Winter Collection, right?
Eh?
You noticed?
I understand.
Wearing such good brands shows that you're very mature. It's great!
I think everyone will understand your mature charm.
Kawashima-san, you're a really,
really good child.
I'm really mature.
Huh?
No, it's nothing.
Let's go to the supermarket before we head back.
Sounds good. Today, I want to eat...
Meat?
How about some fat meat?
All you know is meat.
You have a problem?
I also pay for the food, you know!
Think about your nutrition balance.
Are you acting all tough because you bought the picture with you and Minorin holding hands?
Y-You saw it?
I knew you'd buy it. See, I was right.
D-Didn't you buy a picture too?
I guess.
It's not like I need it,
since I'm his girlfriend.
Ow...
Oh, the person from a while ago.
S-Sorry, I...
You again?
T-This time, you want to peek up my skirt?
No!
Stay there!
Don't run!
She's back to how she was before the Cultural Festival, eh?
Even though something like that happened...
No, it's because it happened.
President, the total cost of the Cultural Festival has been calculated.
Oh, how is it?
Tomiie-kun has been touched!
What was that about?
It's probably the "Legend of the Happy Palmtop Tiger."
They say that your wishes will come true if Aisaka Taiga touches you.
It's just a rumor, though.
So Tomiie was testing it, huh?
It doesn't matter if it's a rumor or a lie.
It's understandable that people want to put faith in these superstitious ideas.
I'm surprised that you would say something like that.
Really?
Um...
President.
Kitamura.
I have something to tell you.
In the end, I didn't get touched by Taiga.
I really envy the girls she touched.
Taiga herself is also living happily ever after with Maruo now.
They just danced! Nothing more!
It's impossible that Taiga could like Maruo!
Why do you care?
That's why I said...
Whoever believes that jinx is a dumbass.
I wish I were you.
It's like, as long as it has to do with love, you can make anything come true.
Yeah.
You're so mature and you have a great body.
I don't think there's a guy in the world who's out of your reach.
Don't say that...
Ami-chan?
A pack for 1800 yen, huh?
You're really trying hard, aren't you?
Kawashima?
It's all right to look so serious when you're troubled, but...
Takasu-kun, you're being watched by undercover security guards.
Can't you at least smile while you shop?
I-I guess...
But you know, you can buy a four-pack of pork for the same price.
If you're troubled by the price, why don't you go touch Aisaka-san?
You might inherit a fortune from some grandfather you've never heard of.
Probably.
Hey, you'll be blessed with good fortune if you touch Taiga, right?
The credibility is zero.
But what if it's true?
What should I do to make Taiga herself be blessed by good fortune?
She's already very lucky.
I guess you should choose quantity over quality,
since she won't have any complaints as long as she's full.
I guess you're right.
All right, I'll get the pork.
Oh, I don't need a plastic bag.
Takasu-kun, you're like a housewife for collecting these points.
Shut up.
Oh, right.
Here, take it.
I'm giving it to you.
There are only three people in my house, so one or two packs are enough.
Even if I took it, I wouldn't know how to cook it.
Whatever, you should eat some pork.
You don't look well today.
You're probably lacking vitamin B2.
Huh?
You didn't look well this morning.
Remember, at the vending machines?
W-What?
You're like a nosy old lady...
I'm fine with that.
I bet all you're eating is fast food.
You're such a kid.
Grill it with ginger.
Ginger can warm your body.
See you.
Like a kid, huh?
Seriously, that disgusting dog.
How dare he ditch his master and leave first?
K-Kita-Kitamu...
Aisaka?
What are you... doing here?
I'm doing nothing here.
Happy Palmtop Tiger.
I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
Did something happen?
Did you lose your wallet or something?
Were you bullied by that evil Student Council President?
No, nothing like that.
It's nothing.
Um...
I don't understand what's going on, but you can touch me if you want.
Come on, touch me however you want.
Touch me as much as you want!
My gosh! What am I saying?
Aisaka.
I'm sorry, I'm okay.
Thanks.
Tomiie-kun, are you really okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Really?
Are you seriously fine?
Yeah, Sakura-chan, I'm honestly fine.
Oh, welcome back.
Seriously, why did you leave without me?
Hey, Ryuuji, there's a lot of food.
Is it some special day today?
Uh, well...
Uh... I didn't have lunch, so I'm very hungry.
It smells great.
You're good at this type of cooking too?
Yeah, western-style boiled pork.
The special thing about it is that Shinshuu miso was added to the vinegar.
I can't lose to the restaurant that your father took me to.
Uh...
Then you put melted cheese on it...
Are you stupid?
I told you I'm fine already.
Never mind, hurry up and finish cooking.
Yeah, yeah.
The Legend of the Happy Palmtop Tiger, huh?
Seriously, it's the most stupid thing I've ever heard.
Rub, rub, rub, rub...
Ya-chan?
Oh, I can feel the good fortune already!
That's a bit too quick.
The fact that I'm able to rub you like this...
The fact that I'm able to have meals with my family...
This all makes me the happiest person in the world.
Family?
Yeah.
Our family is made up of three people!
Ya-chan, I can't breathe...
If you touch the Palmtop Tiger, any wish can come true.
If that's true...
Yeah, Mom...
I think I want to stay here.
Yeah, I've made new friends.
And also...
I'm fine, I'm also trying my best.
Yeah, people say I'm mature now.
What sort of wish... will I make?
Although I can't really make out the form of my wish...
Or rather, I don't want to see it.
Ryuu-chan, come touch her.
I'll do it too!
Don't use your feet. Don't!
banira saruto de burning love
A salty vanilla... Burning love...
amai dakenara saruto kakemashou
Let's put salt on it if it's too sweet
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo shitte hoshiikara sarakedashitai
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
so I want to disclose myself
demo dekinai no keiken nothing
But that doesn't work since I have no experience
modokashisugiru
This is just too irritating!
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But sweet love is a little different
watashi ga motometeirumono to wa chigau
from what I'm looking for
"shiro" to iwaretara "kuro" datte icchau
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojaku
I just can't be honest, and I'm always contradicting myself
"suki" to iwaretara "daikirai" datte
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni saruto kakeru youni
It's like putting salt on sweet vanilla
Next Episode Preview
The Stars Are Far Away
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Amazing! As expected from Kitamura-kun!
You said it ten times without biting your tongue.
Wait, what do you mean by stop?
Everything!
Stop everything!