When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
~Jyararan
SFX: Splash
~Splash~
My name is Brittney.
As you can see, I'm just a flower girl.
SFX: Splash
Today, I've come all the way to the Sea of Japan, drawn by the fragrance of flowers.
Listening to the waves reminds me of my magical homeland,
Third District of East Nakano.
Shoot me. I just spoke my secret.
You may have noticed now, but my true identity is...
A magical girl!
Today, as the seventeenth episode anniversary,
we'll show you my manga for the entire thirty minutes.
It's an amazing slide show anime that surpasses the level of Kaya**** and Nekome**.
The talent that overwhelms
the Ultra Director of the SO* Brigade.
Please stop! The audience's going think that we're quitting on them.
Besides, what do we celebrate at the seventeenth episode?
Don't make fun of episode number seventeen!
In episode seventeen, A**ro steals a ***dam and leaves the ***** Base!
Even Captain O**** collapses and gets carried into-
A-Anyway, as always, please enjoy Hayate no Gotoku.
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
By the way, there's a Say** fan service shot.
That happens in episode 37!
Episode 17 is Mi***-san.
The girl knows for a fact...
...there are things in this world that cannot be bought even with money.
SFX: BANG
Come to your own conclusion as to what happened.
What's wrong, Milady?!
This is...
Manga magazine?
I apparently don't have enough experience in life.
The reason I can't win anything from the manga I draw is because I don't have enough experience in life.
Wh-What do you think? It's my masterpiece.
It's strange that that doesn't make it into the final selection.
I guess an unreasonable joke like this can happen.
It's not a matter of jokes!
Can't you feel the grand scale of this work?!
I can definitely feel how wicked this is.
It's all because of the lame selection committee that capable new faces die out.
"To create an interesting manga, one must have a rich life."
SFX: Snap
Vague advice like that won't let newcomers improve!
Don't tell me that.
Well, that is like her innate illness, so do not worry about it.
She draws a manga every few months and sends it in.
I see.
What's wrong?
Just thinking that Milady can work hard if it's on something she likes.
Although she is not close to getting accepted.
Yes...
I feel bad for her a little.
You shouldn't.
It is an opportunity for her to learn there are things you cannot do anything about with money, so I think it is good.
True, I think I don't have enough experience in life.
I don't have many friends, don't go to school often,
and don't participate in any sports.
And I'm not active at home;
I can get away every day without doing anything.
Walking down Loser Avenue.
It's because of this blessed life I have!
It's because I lack the experience of being in the depths of poverty like Nero and Maruko.
Nor have I ever been dropped from
the pinnacle of happiness like Se***.
That's why I can't create a story that brings the entire US to tears.
Wait! There's someone who's really acquainted with that kind of life!
What? What I was doing when I was about thirteen years old?
Yes! I want to know how much of a difference there is
between you and I with respect to our life experiences!
Back when I was thirteen, eh?
Let's see, if I'm right, I was working as a Daiuchi at a mah-jong house.
Huh?
Daiuchi...
It's an occupation akin to a bodyguard specialized in dealing with the very kind people that come for mah-jong.
SFX: Rustle...
It's a dangerous occupation that doesn't allow you to lose.
Isn't that really dangerous?
I was fine. I'm really good,
and I was good at playing things under the table, too.
Looks like the difference in life experience is big.
But I think you have plenty of experience in life, too.
You're in high school when you're only thirteen years old.
And living in a big mansion like this.
One can't have this kind of experience very often.
Y-You think so?
By the way, what else did you do?
Let's see...
I was also winning prizes via submitting manga.
Looks like the lack of experience is  the difference in skill.
Milady?
Then I'll do things I usually don't do and gain experience points!
Gain experience points from doing things you don't usually do?
That's the spirit, Milady!
Let's take the opportunity and jump out into the outside world!
Never!
Things outside of the wall are equivalent of experience from Sli***.
I'm looking for experience equivalent to the Lost Me*** series!
Therefore, by picking the thing I would never do...
I'll help out Maria!
What? Help?
Yes! I'll make myself useful.
Tell me to do anything.
Hayate-kun...
Well, since she's motivated for it...
To start out with, I'll start with housekeeping like Maria is always doing.
Wait, Nagi!
Here goes! Zep****th Broom!
That's not a chant for housekeeping.
Y-Yeah, little oopsie.
But I'll do it right next time.
Hayate-kun...
Milady! Wait! Stop!
Hayate. There indeed are things you can never learn without experiencing.
Like what?
Housekeeping makes things messy.
What a very expensive experience.
I've now mastered housekeeping.
Let's move on.
Wait, Milady!
Next, I'll master shopping.
Shopping?
But there are things you can't buy from internet shopping for Ya*** Auctions.
Stop making fun of me.
I'm going outside to do grocery shopping.
Th-There are way too many things.
It's the largest market around here.
If RPG item shops were like this, you could't tell what to buy!
First of all, you check the price and how fresh it is.
And the place it was made,
and if you can, the person who made it, too.
I don't need a complicated command like that.
Hey, staff.
Yes?
I've gained yet another experience.
What is it this time?
If you go grocery shopping, a shop will disappear.
It's news to me, too.
Okay, next up is cleaning out the shed!
You're doing more?
Wow, you might find legendary items here.
Things in here are all practically junk.
No, I'm sure they're all priceless works of art.
Th-This is!
I can't imagine a portrait like this could be worth anything.
You're right.
SFX: KATSU
Katsu!
Who's there?!
That's Rodin's The Thinker.
What? Chief Butler? What are you doing here?
This is my relaxation spot.
When I don't have screen time,
I indulge in art in order to rejuvenate myself.
No wonder I didn't see you around.
We're moving on!
Please wait, Milady!
Milady! Please let me out of here!
It's dark! It's scary!
Neko ga nekoronda
Neko ga nekoronda = The cat took a nap
Daffunda. Daijyobuda.
Gags by Shimura Ken
So Hayate, what should I do next?
Let's see...
I guess serving guests is all that's left.
Serving guests. Gotcha!
Milady!
Please wait. No customers are here right now.
Isumi-san?
Isumi!
Nagi. Hayate-sama.
What are you doing here?
So this was your house.
No wonder the scenery looked familiar.
You see, I was studying in my room until a while ago, but...
My eraser dropped off of my table.
Wait.
And while I was searching the yard...
Before I knew it, I got lost here.
Your way of getting lost is overflowing with originality as always.
Maybe your yard and mine are connected by a wormhole.
But you came here with perfect timing.
I will give you VIP service.
Will Milady be fine?
Did you make the tea for me?
Yes. I mixed every kind of expensive tea leaves
there were in the kitchen,
and made Sanzenin Nagi Original Royal Premium Hyper Giga-Max Blend, so it's really good.
Ah! The cup's dirty!
Let me go get a new one for you.
Hayate?
A blend of Darjeeling, blue mountain, and genmai tea.
And for some reason, I can taste Ba** Star Ramen, too.
I can't possibly serve an Oh My ***bu tea like this.
H-How is it?
It's delicious, Nagi.
Is it?
Look Hayate! Seems like I have a talent for serving others!
I'm happy for you, Milady.
All right, I'll serve more people and gain more experience!
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
¥1,000 for omelet with a word.
If I eat this, will I be considered a rich girl, too?
Whee.
Thanks for coming, everyone!
Nagi?
What's with her getup?
It's the worst choice of cosplay.
It's not a cosplay.
It's gaining experience in life.
Huh?
Hey, what's with this gaining experience in life?
She said she wants to do things she usually doesn't do to gain experience.
I will now show you my talent in serving guests.
I'll make a dish that's so good that it'll melt your cheek and hit the core of Earth.
What? You're going to start making it now?
Here I go!
Hey, is this really going to be fine?
I'm sorry, I'll go see.
Sneaking around~
So gross!
If we serve this to the guests, the reaction will hurt Milady.
I can't let this be.
I-It's good!
This is actually good!
You're right.
What a deep taste composed of a fusion between heavy and light seasoning.
A mellow taste as if spring is here.
A velvety feel on the tongue as if it's an embrace by the great ocean.
The ingredients are going through a nuclear reaction in the mouth,
and a Big Bang flavor explodes!
T-This is...
This is magnificent.
It's wondafo~
It's exquisite!
It's delicious.
Come on, come on, come on!
Bring me seconds!
Katsura-chan, you can't go wild here.
Bring me more booze!
Bring me more food!
And bring me money while you're at it!
Hayate. Everyone likes my cooking.
I'm happy for you, Milady.
Thanks for the food, Hayate-kun.
You're the one that made all of this, right?
Looks like I was right.
It's so easy to read your face.
Please don't tell Milady.
I know.
It's not easy being a butler, heh?
All the work you do to not cause your master shame.
It was delicious, Nagi-chan.
The service was well done, too.
Really?
I'm glad I came.
Hey, Hayate.
Yes?
I think I understand some of what you and Maria feel, even if just a bit.
Doing something for others feels good.
I want many people to enjoy the manga I draw, too,
like they enjoyed today's evening.
Milady.
Milady is a good girl at heart.
I need to keep protecting her kind heart.
Where're my seconds?
If you don't bring more, I'll give you my jumping knee.
Katsura-sensei, you haven't gone home?
This smell!
Yay!
Found my seconds!
And I went through the trouble of hiding it.
Katsura-sensei?
Sensei! Come back!
Hayate...
Milady.
Why is the food I made sitting here untouched?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Everyone cleared your food few minutes ago.
This is a mess I made.
Don't lie to me!
Then explain the signature there!
You don't have to sign it like a manga character.
So the food everyone ate was your cooking, wasn't it?
Um, well...
I see... Perhaps, I wasn't of any help?
I wasn't of any help to you and Maria from the start?
That's absolutely not true!
How should I put it...
Everyone has things they're good and things they're not good at.
So in other words...
You want to say I might not have what it takes to create manga?
I never said that.
It's not like it never crossed my mind.
I thought of it once on a very rare, limited moon.
That the reason why I can't win any prizes is because I don't have any talent.
Milady...
Milady!
I'm...
Are you all right, Milady?
Leave me alone.
I don't have any talent...
I can't help out at all...
It's all right.
Look at that.
Because you helped, they both look so happy.
SFX: Dumbstruck~
Their eyes look dead.
How do we clean this?
There goes my screen time.
You think I don't have talent, either, don't you?
So you do!
Even in your eyes that once received manga prizes,
I appear to not have any talent, huh?!
You do have talent.
You've created many manga and kept submitting, right?
There are many people who can't even finish one story and give up.
But if it's something you like, you can work till the very end without giving up,
you have the talent called passion,
The talent called passion?
Yes.
I give you my word.
You got it, Hayate!
I'll give it a shot with my passion!
That's the spirit, Milady.
Besides, it could be that your manga is too high level.
Too high?
Yes. Like, you in fact have too much experience, therefore the humor is hard to transcend.
I see! Then if I drop the level down a little-
Yes. I'm sure you'll get the next prize.
Okay! Then I'll give it another shot!
Good luck, Milady!
Black Se** **turn?!
That's the trump card for saving the 8-dimensional Earth.
All that's left is winning the music competition.
The tool needed to communicate with the Fourth Space God for the mentioned task is already in hand through Ya*** Auction.
The level's way up there as usual.
The next rookie prize is mine.
Y-Yes.
Therefore, the debt-ridden butler's
life experiences and suffering continue.
Next week, the dragon and hamster go head to head!
But, unfortunately, due to scheduling issues,
it'll be a swimsuit episode.
Can't wait for the next one.
You're amazing, Nagi.
My back pain's gone.
Nagi and...
Hayate's...
Butler Network!
Hello. I'm Katsura Yukiji.
Katsura-sensei. What are you here for?
I thought, since I have a more mature appeal than Hinagiku, everyone would like that more.
I wonder about that.
Besides, boys and girls who like Hinagiku won't be buying the DVD!
We should appeal to single males over twenty years old.
Katsura-sensei, no commercials in the show, please.
You're too naive. I only want people to buy the Hayate no Gotoku DVD.
AHHHH!!!
Don't panic, Ayasaki-kun.
Hey, Onee-chan!
Next week, it's the episode you've all been waiting for,
the summer swimsuit episode!
What did everyone see at the tropical Hakuou Island?
Welcome to Hakuou Island.
I'm the butler and the manager of this island, Schmidt hen Bach.
I will be creating your fun summer memories.
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
The Rare Card is Swimsuit.
I'm talking more than usual.
Now, how do I fight this?