[NARRATOR]
Alchemy... the science
of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter;
however, it is not
an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to
create something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal
value must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange--
the basis of all alchemy.
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[NARRATOR]
Maes Hughes is dead...
The military knows
little of his killers
beyond the fact that they bore
mysterious Uroboros tattoos...
Suspicious about
the circumstances
surrounding his friend's death,
Colonel Mustang began
asking questions of his own.
He learned of a
possible conspiracy
at the senior level
of military command,
which only redoubled his resolve
to be promoted to Central.
Meanwhile, anxious to
see their old teacher,
Ed and Al continued
their journey southward
with Winry in tow,
unaware of the death of
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes.
[WINRY]
Rush Valley!
Automail! Automail! Automail!
[WINRY LAUGHS]
I'm so happy!
[WINRY GASPS]
Look, it's the most
recent Gods model!
I never imagined
I would behold
such a thing with
my very own eyes!
[WINRY SQUEALS IN EXCITEMENT]
[AL] Welcome to
the Holy Land of automail!
This place is bustling.
[ED] Ugh! Remind me again
why we let ourselves get
dragged out into this heat to
look at a bunch of automail?
We should've dropped
Winry off at the station
and headed straight
on to Dublith.
[ENGINEER A]
Hey kid, come back here a sec!
I've never seen an automail
model quite like this before!
It really is unusual.
Everyone take a look!
[CROWD GASPS]
[ED]
Hey, stop that.
Hey, hold on a second!
Have you ever heard
of personal space?!
Quit it! No, no!
Don't undo that! Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Don't be so rude.
They just want a closer look.
Can I get a little
help here, Winry?!
[ED] Jeez!
This is why I steer clear
of automail engineers.
Oh no.
Something wrong, Ed?
It's gone...
[AL AND WINRY]
What didja lose?
Only the thing that proves
I'm a State Alchemist.
My silver watch...
...gone!
[AL AND WINRY YELL]
It sounds like you guys
had a run in with Paninya.
Paninya?
A pickpocket
around here
who likes to
target tourists.
Do you know how I can
track down this Paninya girl?
She took something important!
Let's see,
where is she again?
I know what might
jog my memory...
If only I could have just
one more look at that automail!
The automail shop run by
an engineer named Dominic!
Apparently this guy lives
deep in the mountains
because he can find the highest
quality ore way out here.
Are you absolutely sure we're
going in the right direction?
'Cause those engineers
could've tricked us.
What're you
complaining about?
This is all your fault
for dragging us to
that stupid automail
town in the first place.
[WINRY] My fault?!
You're the one
who was dumb enough
to let his watch get stolen!
[ED]
Oh! Really?!
[AL]
Um, hey, you guys...
What, Al?!
[AL]
Could that be her?
[ED AND WINRY] Huh...?
Ha! Ha! I've got you now!
[PANINYA GASPS]
I'd like my watch back.
That was awesome!
How'd you do that, mister?
I'm an alchemist... Want more?
Wow! So cool!
[ED GRUNTS]
[ED]
Quit movin' around!
[PANINYA]
What's the matter?
Can't catch
a little girl?
[AL]
I've been waiting for you.
Huh...?
[WINRY]
Nicely done, Al.
Now... Why don't you
hand it over? My watch--
[AL AND ED GASP]
Come on, you can't
be too surprised...
You've seen the
town, haven't you?
Oh, and...
[AL AND ED SCREAM]
My other leg's got a one
point five inch cannon.
What do you think of that?
Come back!
No way! Why don't we
see if you can catch me?
Well now,
how do ya like that?
That wasn't so hard.
[ED]
Nice work, Winry!
And now don't let her get away!
[WINRY]
No way I'm letting her go!
Not quite yet, anyway...
Not until I've had a closer
look at that automail!
[AL AND ED YELL]
Oh, hello there, Paninya.
[SATERA]
Friends of yours?
[PANINYA]
Not really...
[WINRY SQUEALS IN EXCITEMENT]
[WINRY] I've never seen
craftsmanship like this before!
It has an advanced suspension,
and would you look
at this balance!
The design of this piece
is truly a work of art!
It's incredible!
Um...
[ED] Do you think we could
have a talk about my watch?
[AL]
It's no use brother.
The work you've done
is simply fantastic.
You're a
wonderful engineer!
Oh, no, don't
look at me miss.
I wasn't the one
who made them.
[DOMINIC] I am.
Huh...?
[METALLIC SOUND]
This arm seems a bit heavy.
Yes, I guess it is.
You want to be more careful
not to strain your outfit-ee.
That could be the reason
why his growth is stunted.
[ED]
Hey, Shut up!
[ED GASPS]
Wait, are you telling me that
if my automail was lighter,
I'd grow taller than this?
It is a possibility.
Wow, Brother,
you're so big!
You've grown
so tall!
Next to me,
you guys sure look small.
Right!
That settles it.
Mister Dominic!
Huh...?
I beg you...
Make me your apprentice!
Not a chance, girl.
Maybe you'd like more
time to consider the idea?
No need.
I don't take on apprentices.
I understand,
but maybe...
you could take time out
of your busy schedule
to teach her how to make
automail to make me taller?
Can it, ya little flea.
[ED GASPS]
Sorry about that...
My old man can
be pretty stubborn.
[RAIN POURS]
A little flea...
He called me a flea!
[AL]
Hmm...?
[AL] Excuse me, but
are you having a baby?
Why, yes I am.
[AL] Do you think...
Would it be all right
if I touched your tummy?
Heh...
Go right ahead.
[HEARTBEAT SOUND]
[ED] It's like there's
a miracle in your stomach.
[AL] Yeah... we were inside
Mom's tummy like this
once upon a time too.
[SATERA WINCES IN PAIN]
[ED]
Are you okay?
[SATERA] Y-Yes.
[RAIN POURS]
[PANINYA GRUNTS]
Whenever it pours
down like this,
my stumps
always get achy.
If you don't mind me
asking, what happened?
[PANINYA]
I was in a train accident
when I was a kid...
It killed my parents.
I wound up losing both
my legs in the wreck.
I couldn't even walk anymore...
...and I had nowhere to go.
It felt like my entire world
had come crashing down.
That's when I met
Mister Dominic,
and everything
changed completely.
You look like
the most miserable,
pathetic girl in
the entire world.
Nothing annoys me more
than mopers like you.
[YOUNG PANINYA]
Let me go, you mean
old man! Put me down!
He said I had eyes
like a dead person.
Probably not far off.
I'm sure I really
did look miserable.
So, without anyone
ever asking my opinion...
I was outfitted
with automail legs.
The surgery and
rehabilitation were painful--
by far the hardest
thing I've ever done.
But then...
Soon enough I was back up
on two legs, and I was so happy!
All thanks to him...
Mister Dominic...
I owe him everything.
I'm gonna pay
him back somehow,
even if it takes
me my whole life!
Of course, he's never willing
to take any money from me,
so that makes it
a bit more difficult.
That's why
you're a thief?
If you're so
grateful to him,
you should clean up your act
and stop picking pockets!
Mr. Dominic gave
you these legs
out of a selfless
act of good will.
So if you really
wanna pay him back,
use that act
as an example!
Instead of stealing trinkets
from hapless tourists,
stand strong on those two legs
that he made for you...
Stand up and get to work!
Mr. Dominic would
respect you more
for doing that
than for stealing.
Probably...
You know what,
you're right!
[PANINYA]
From now on, I'll work honestly
to pay him back myself!
So...
...I should probably
give this thing back.
[WINRY]
Mm-Hmm...
Hey...
What... Uh-oh...
I think I may have
broken it or something...
Can't get it to open.
Let me see.
No, don't worry,
it wasn't you...
It's been sealed
up using alchemy.
Why would he do that?
I think I have
a pretty good idea why.
Something's in here he's too
embarrassed to let anyone see.
Open!
Now... let's have a little
look at what Ed was hiding.
[PANINYA] "Don't forget...
October 3rd... year eleven."
A date?
Here... You should
give this back to Ed.
What is it, Winry?
Nothing...
I'm going to ask Mr. Dominic
to apprentice me again.
[RAIN POURS]
[KNOCKING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[ED BREATHES HEAVILY]
[WINRY]
What's wrong?
The... the ba--
The bay?
[ED MUMBLES]
A bay is a type of horse.
What about it?
The... the...
The baby's coming!
[WINRY SCREAMS]
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[LIGHTNING]
In a storm like this,
we can't get her
to the hospital in town.
I'll fetch the
doctor myself.
[HORSE GALLOPS]
[RIDEL] Pop will be right
back with a doctor...
Just hang on a little
longer for me... okay?
There's no
hanging on here.
It'll come whenever
it's ready to.
[SATERA YELLS]
What's the matter, hon?
[SATERA MUMBLES]
Huh?
Uh... sorry, one
more time...?
I couldn't
hear that.
I said it's coming!
[EVERYONE YELLS]
It's coming?!
What do we do?
The doctor's not here!
[EVERYONE YELLS WORRIEDLY]
We're just going
to have to do it.
Have to do what?
Deliver it.
[EVERYONE YELLS]
So... so you've seen a baby
being delivered before?
No, I... I haven't...
But we don't have any
other options here.
[WINRY]
I need everyone's help.
We are going to do this!
Ed and Al, go and get me
some boiling water!
- Right!
- Sure, Winry!
Paninya, go find some towels.
And hurry!
Roger!
Mr. Ridel, do you have
any rubbing alcohol
we can use
for disinfectant?
I think we have some
in the store room.
[WINRY]
Oh, and some ice chips!
We'll put them by
Mrs. Satera's bedside.
Uh... are we sure your
friend can handle this?
Winry comes from
a family of doctors...
She grew up reading
medical textbooks
instead of picture books
like most kids her age.
That's all
well and good,
but it isn't exactly the
same as a medical degree!
[ED] Well it's clear
that she at least
vaguely remembers some of it.
[RIDEL]
Some of it!
Right now the only
choice we have is to
defer to her knowledge and
the sheer force of her nerve.
[RAIN POURS]
[HORSE GALLOPS]
[WINRY] Boiling water...
disinfectant... towels...
And what else was there...?
Remember it now...
[ED]
Winry...
[EVERYONE]
You can do this!
[WINRY]
Paninya... give me
a hand in here.
Sure...
you got it.
[DOOR CREAKS CLOSED]
[AL] Brother...
Now, when it really counts...
I can't do anything.
[SATERA] Ow!!
Agh! I'm gonna die in here!
It hurts!
I can't take anymore!
[SATERA YELLS IN PAIN]
I know we're not
big believers in God...
But maybe he could
help us... this once.
[HORSE GALLOPS]
[SATERA YELLS IN PAIN]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[AL] Brother!
Wha... what...?
All... that blood.
[PANINYA]
I can't do it anymore.
[WINRY BREATHES HEAVILY]
What's going on...? Hey!
[BABY CRIES]
[RIDEL AND SATERA LAUGH]
It... It's a baby!
Hooray!
[ED] Awesome!
It's a real, live baby!
Awesome! Awesome,
awesome, awesome!
Really...?
Awesome?
That's all you can
think of to describe this?
How else should
I describe it?
This is the birth
of a new life!
[ED] Alchemists have
worked for centuries,
and we're still not
able to do that!
A person creating
another person...
You gotta be
kidding me!
Now you're lumping in alchemy
with the miracle of birth?!
An occupational hazard.
It's just the way I think.
[BABY CRIES]
Besides, Whatever you say,
it really is awesome...
People are awesome.
All right... The baby's born,
and everything's good...
So do you think
there's anything else
you're gonna
need me for now?
Yeah, there is.
Do you think you could...
pick me up please?
Huh?
[WINRY]
It's humiliating
to be carried
by a boy who's
smaller than I am.
I could easily
drop you, you know.
[WINRY] Ed...
Huh, what is it?
[WINRY]
I saw it...
The engraving that's
inside your pocket watch...
[WINRY YELLS]
Ow, ow, ow.
That really hurt!
[ED]
You forced it open?
Yeah. I'm so sorry.
[ED] You idiot.
[WINRY]
Yeah...
I haven't shown that
to anybody. Not even Al.
But why not, Ed?
[ED] It's private.
An admonition to myself.
I hate to admit
how weak I am...
That I had to give what
happened that day substance,
and then carry it around
with me as a reminder.
[RAIN POURS]
Winry, why are
you doing that?
What are you crying for?
Well... there's no turning
back for us now, brother.
[GLASS CRACKS]
[ED] What are you
crying for, Winry?
[WINRY]
You two won't cry...
Someone else should do it
for you, don't you think?
Don't be an idiot.
[ED] You should get
back to Resembool.
You've been gone
a long time.
Granny must be
lonesome without you.
[WINRY]
No... I'm not leaving.
Why?
[WINRY] Seeing your
resolve inspired me.
I wanna do more, Ed.
I can't just commit halfway.
Don't do anything...
There's no need to
get more involved.
Yes there is...
I want to hone my skills
so I'll be able to
make you the finest quality
automail prosthetics.
That way you can continue
your journey knowing
you're as strong
as you can be.
I'm going to try again.
I'll ask Mr. Dominic to
make me his apprentice.
Okay.
Well then, good luck.
[PANINYA]
Winry! Mr. Ridel said he
wanted to talk to you for a...
What's up?
Is there something wrong?
Oh no, don't worry.
It's nothing...
I'll be right
there, okay.
Paninya...
Hmm...?
[LOUD THUD]
Hey! Ow...!
Why'd you go and do that?
Quit whining,
you dirty pickpocket,
and give me my
watch back right now!
[PANINYA]
Didja have to hit me
with your right arm?
[ED]
I can hit you again with
my left if you'd prefer!
Hello, there--
I'm your granddad!
What a cutie!
That's sure
out of character.
Mother and baby both
look perfectly healthy...
It seems like the delivery
was handled expertly.
Well done. Sometimes
even adults can't take
being present at childbirth.
Oh, no...! We did what
we had to, that's all!
[DOMINIC]
We are truly in your debt.
What you did was amazing.
Especially you, young lady.
Thank you.
Please, sir, there's really
no need to thank me...!
Oh my goodness,
now you're going make me blush!
Maybe you could
make an exception
and take on
an apprentice?
One has nothing
to do with the other.
[DOMINIC] I don't take on
apprentices, and that's that.
But...
If that's what
your heart's set on...
I can recommend you to
an accomplished engineer
at the base of the mountain.
Pardon me... would it
be okay if I came by
and watched
you work sometimes?
[DOMINIC]
I won't stop you from
coming once in awhile...
...to see my grandchild.
Same goes for the tomboy.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ED] Move it, Al!
We've gotta hurry.
If we miss this train,
there's not another
one for three days!
Now you two
be careful!
You too, Winry!
[ED] Thank you.
And don't forget to call
Granny and keep her posted!
Oh please, like you're
really one to talk, Ed!
And make sure to steal
that old man's techniques
so you'll have something
even better for me
the next time I see you, okay?
Well, that's it.
They're gone.
They'll be back.
Huh...?
[NARRATOR]
The brothers arrive in Dublith
to visit their old teacher...
While there, they
remember the time
they spent in training
as young boys...
when they took their
first step toward the truth.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 12:
"One is All, All is One."
Afraid of the
possible consequences...
...the Elric brothers
are hesitant to speak.