We're here to return the car we borrowed.
Sign: Fukumoto Gang
Thank you very much.
Well, we'll be going now.
Now, hold on a moment.
I heard the story.
You must be the ones...
who finished off that idiot Tsubouchi before my men got there.
Not bad.
You've got real courage for kids nowadays.
What do you say, guys?
Wanna put your toughness to work under me?
Boss, that wouldn't—
Oh, why not?
Sir...
We want to stay on the right side of the law,
so we'll respectfully decline.
Oh, I see, I see.
Well, come by if you change your mind.
Hey, let's go, Cabbage.
Making money with my toughness...
Joe, what are you going to do now?
Well, we thought about living together,
but since I'm starting from scratch, with hardly any income,
we can't do that yet.
What about you, Meg?
I'm just happy that I've been reunited with my brother.
The place where I work provides lodgings.
Hey, Meg.
Where do you work?
I'll definitely come see you!
Shut up!
You stay out of this, you pervert!
If you dare to lay a finger on her, I'll kill you!
What's it to you, anyway?
Ow!
Ow...
Well, let's have a toast to Joe and Meg.
Cheers!
Mario was so strong when he came to save me.
Oh, really?
What about you, Soldier?
I was busy fulfilling my professional duties.
Hey,
what's up with Cabbage?
Something happened to him.
Well, I have curfew.
Same here. I gotta show my face at the bar.
Meg, I'll walk you back to your place.
Okay.
They're all so serious.
Meg...
I'm jealous.
Mario, Soldier, and Joe...
all have something to do.
Hey, what's wrong, Cabbage?
You too, Uncovered.
You're going to study and become someone important, right?
Turtle and I are the only ones who have nothing.
You know, I actually do have a job.
Then...
it's just me.
Don't say that, Cabbage.
All right! Let's have a second round of drinks.
I'll pay.
I've decided.
I'm going to train with the Fukumoto gang!
The Fukumoto gang?
Don't be stupid!
Do you want to die before you grow up?
Look, that's not a job for a nice guy like you,
so give up on the idea!
See ya, Cabbage!
Stay out of trouble!
Yeah, see ya.
The Fukumoto gang, huh?
We need to do something, or that idiot really will join the yakuza.
Basically, we just need to find something he'll feel comfortable with.
Leave it to me.
I'll restore that shriveled-up cabbage to perfect shape.
Sign: Nonstop Sex, Turtle-blood Powder, 2 for 100 yen
H-Hey, come on over and take a look!
Let's see...
I've got some turtle-blood powder, no doubt about it!
Really, nonstop sex?
2 for 100 yen?
That's cheap.
Just one bag, and you'll be rock hard and standing tall.
I-If your husband's been feeling a little weak lately,
it'll work like a charm and be a blessing!
Really? That's hard to believe.
I smell something fishy.
Y-Yeah!
Why don't you take one yourself and prove that it works?
R-Right! Then...
Um...
Listen, Cabbage.
Turtle will tell you to prove that it's real,
so what you gotta do is drink the fake drug and break this precut rock.
Got it?
This is fake?
Of course it is!
We can't sell the real thing.
I see.
Take the drug, then break the rock.
Hey, what's taking so long?
Right.
And next...
Cabbage...
You did that wrong.
Hey! What's going on here?
Wow!
I'll take some!
Ten, in fact!
Thanks, Uncovered!
Wh-Why are you calling out my name?
This is ridiculous.
He had shills.
So much for that.
Sign: Indestructible Cups, 2 for 100 yen
Come on over and take a look!
I've got cups that will never break.
Mister, are they really indestructible?
Yeah.
No way!
Then prove it!
S-Sure.
Let's see...
Wow, that's amazing!
It doesn't break at all!
Idiot, there's a trick.
Cups have sturdy bottoms.
They don't break that easily.
I see.
Hit the bottom. Hit the bottom.
Hit the bottom...
Hurry up and show us, mister.
Sure, here I go.
Better watch closely!
Hah, it shattered just like that.
That was dumb.
Let's go home.
It's your fault for coming up with those stupid scams in the first place.
What? You were into it too!
Sorry, guys.
I guess I can't do anything at all.
Well, I'm going home now.
Thanks for trying.
Cabbage!
Cabbage...
Please take me under your wing!
I'm Matsuura Mansaku.
Oh, I see, I see.
Thanks for coming.
Train hard.
Thank you very much!
Basically, you guys misled Cabbage into trying some scams.
And then, you couldn't stop Cabbage from joining the yakuza?
What should we do, Mario?
Well...
It was his choice.
What the hell are you saying?!
Do you think Cabbage can possibly live the life of a yaku—
And whose fault is this?
Let's see how things go for a while.
I'm sure he'll come back once he realizes he doesn't fit in.
I'll be in your care.
Hey, Tanaka.
Yes?
I'm putting you in charge of Matsuura.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Got it.
C-Cleaning?
Yeah.
Make this place spotless.
Got it?
Sure.
When do I get food?
I'm hungry.
Ow.
Matsuura.
Once you're done here, come with me.
O-Okay.
Shine these shoes?
Yeah.
Shoes are an important part of being a yakuza.
Make sure they're sparkling clean.
U-Um...
When do I get to eat?
Matsuura, what the hell are you doing?!
Hello.
Yes, this is the Fukumoto gang!
You idiot!
Who gave you permission to pick up the phone?!
Don't you know where you are?
We don't know who's calling!
If you pick up the phone again, I'll kill you!
I see.
Cabbage still hasn't come back?
What's he doing?
It's already been two weeks.
Well, how's Matsuura?
Do you really have to ask?
He's completely useless.
Well, he's a good guy.
I see.
The boss and I have to go to a meeting tonight.
Tanaka, watch the place while we're out.
Yes, sir.
I'll keep watch.
Hey, Matsuura.
Yeah?
Why'd you join the yakuza?
If you're not serious, I suggest you get out while you can.
But...
I'm no good at anything else.
Excuse me!
We have a guest.
Wait.
I'll go take a look.
You stay here.
Excuse me.
Who's there?
I'm sorry for coming so late.
I'm Kato from next door.
Goodness...
What do you want exactly—
Better say your prayers, Fukumoto!
Today's the day you die!
Tanaka?
M-Matsuura, run!
Where's Fukumoto?
Fukumoto!
Come out of hiding!
3 Weeks Later
Mario!
Bad news!
Cabbage...
Cabbage might be dead!
What are you saying?
I heard from a neighbor of the Fukumoto gang that someone broke in.
I've confirmed it too.
There were ambulances, and the police were all over the place.
Some of the youngsters in the Fukumoto gang were slaughtered in the attack.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
I should never have come up with that stupid plan.
What should we do, Mario?!
Are you morons?!
Cabbage wouldn't get killed so easily!
Hey, you said there were ambulances?
Yeah.
I'm sure he got sent to a hospital somewhere.
I can't think of anything else.
Okay, then I'll look into it!
The police should know something.
Sign: Watabe Hospital
This is the hospital.
Is Cabbage here?
We don't know yet.
Let's go.
No one named Matsuura Mansaku was ever admitted to our hospital.
Well, check again!
Matsuura Mansaku!
He has to be here!
I've checked numerous times.
What do you want with Matsuura?
Hey...
You're the guys who came with him to return the car.
Where's Cabbage?
He's hospitalized here, right?
Before we talk, hand over the knife on your hip.
Mario...
You...
Man...
What were you planning to do with this?
Were you planning to go up against us with this?
Are you a fucking moron?!
You wouldn't get away with just an apology if you raised this against professionals!
I wouldn't let you go with an apology either.
What?
If something's happened to Cabbage, I'll get revenge.
No matter who I'm up against, I won't back down.
Cabbage is an irreplaceable friend to us.
This is why I hate ignorant kids like you.
Go to Hibiya Park tonight at seven.
Will Cabbage be there?
He's got some nice friends...
this Cabbage.
Now, hurry up and get lost.
Thank you.
"Who knew that dimwitted Matsuura had friends like that?"
Even Tanaka, who'd been shaped by the rough world he lived in,
knew that friends were more reliable than parents, money, or women.
"I wonder if I used to have friends like them."
He uses the ropes to throw his opponent to the mat!
Then he kicks the guy back down to the floor when he tries to stand!
The crowd is cheering!
Hey, can we really find—
It's Cabbage.
It looks like Mammoth Matsuura won't get his first win today!
No way.
Cabbage?
Old man, more please!
Hey, Cabbage.
I thought you joined the Fukumoto gang.
Yeah, I did.
Then why the hell are you wrestling professionally?!
You see...!
Go to fucking hell!
Then I called the ambulance,
but the police showed up as well,
and they searched the entire office.
You idiot!
Yakuza don't call an ambulance to their office!
I-I'm sorry.
You son of a...
I'll cut you in half and feed you to the dogs.
Boss.
Let me take care of him.
A finger or two just won't be enough this time.
Got that, Arito?!
Yes, sir.
Um...
Is Mr. Tanaka okay?
Yeah.
Really? That's great.
You're worrying about someone else when you were almost killed?
Huh?
You know...
you're not suited at all for the yakuza.
So...
He said he'd show me a macho job that would suit me, and brought me here.
By job, I mean wrestling.
This is unbelievable!
At the dojo, they tell me to eat all the time.
What?
What's so funny?
Back then, even the yakuza believed in dreams and hopes.
Even though Cabbage had blundered,
Arito from the Fukumoto gang didn't do anything to him,
and just sent him to the world of wrestling.
Cabbage, you can eat as much as you want now.
Use your strength to bring excitement to the world.
Thanks for helping Cabbage.
Tanaka was discharged today.
If Matsuura hadn't called an ambulance,
he would've died.
Would you tell him something when you see him?
Tell him never to show his face around the gang again.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
His first woman.
As Uncovered drowns in love,
he loses sight of everything.