The low sky looks like it's about to cry.
I spit a mixture of saliva and agitation on the sidewalk.
I cower at the thought of tomorrow,
Worrying that everything might fall apart.
In my heart, I know that looking ahead
To the day after tomorrow won't give me a single answer.
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
I was wondering if it's really okay for the Dollars to exist.
I have to do something.
No matter what you see, no matter what you learn about her,
don't look away.
A love triangle, indeed.
She was wearing a Raira uniform, glasses, and I think she had big breasts.
No, it's impossible.
She...
Tomorrow is like an empty canvas that extends endlessly;
What should I sketch on it?
Reality begins to stain the canvas black;
What should I draw?
I struggle to shine.
Yellow Scarves are attacking a girl.
Where?
In front of the Veloce.
They've started moving. They're taking her somewhere.
What sort of a girl?
I think that's a Raira uniform...
She's wearing a Raira uniform and glasses.
Huge knockers.
Why is Sonohara...
Everyone in the Dollars! Emergency!
That's right! Let's all save her!
I ain't letting them get away with this!
Yellow Scarves have gone too far!
Now then...
I'll go enjoy the rest in my living room.
Declaration of
Disbandment
Anyone nearby, help her.
Everyone else, get over there!
Hey... Hey, hey, hey! {@@ needs a timing fix)
You with the Dollars? {@@ needs a timing fix)
You were the one who caused trouble at our hideout, with the black bike.
Huh?
You bitch...
These people are with the Yellow Scarves.
Officer!
Over here! Quickly! Quickly!
Wait!
What did I do?
This way.
Go straight.
There's an exit out the back.
I was sure I had to do something.
Where did she go?
I found the girl.
I helped her get out the back of the Orb Ikebukuro Building.
They're still following.
Anyone near the Orb Ikebukuro Building?
But I got confused and all I do is run.
Hurry! There's your exit!
Easier said than bun, no?
Why?
And... button, push!
I got a su-suck-security job at the Orb Ikebukuro Building, and I'm part of the Dollars, so I g-g-awt her away.
Right outside, behind the Orb Ikebukuro Building?
That's my fort, ain't it!
Who are you?
Why?
Why are you helping me?
Damn it...
Sir, are you alright?
I'm a Dollars passing by. I helped out a little.
I was gonna quit, but...
Don't quit!
You can't quit!
I thought you'd come back.
A dream?
Where did the girl go?
Is this a dream?
Move!
The girl has just transformed into a costumed bunny!
Where did she go, damn it?
You...
You'd better get going, or you'll lose her.
Damn it!
Idiots! What are you doing?
Wh-What's going on?
The Dollars are messing with us.
Get some backup.
We'll retaliate with numbers! Numbers!
People I've never met before are helping me.
It's like I'm dreaming.
The bunny's crossed the road safely!
Togusa, get the car moving.
Right!
Fighting is wrong!
You'll be the next sushi dish.
Wow, look at all of them ring!
It's not only our side's phones that are ringing.
Their phones, too.
A bunny?
A bunny with huge boobs?
Kazu-yan
Yeah, a bunny.
Does anyone know where the girl in the bunny costume went?
If anyone's seen her, report right away!
Is that her?
We don't know if her boobs are big or not.
Have to strip her!
But...
My dreams are always lies that I tell myself.
Wait!
There are more and more
guys in yellow!
All I dreamed of was a smiling happy family.
This is bad! Someone find
the bunny girl fast!
So this isn't a dream.
It's reality.
His hand told me so.
And then I realized that I knew it.
I'd never touched it, but...
Um...
When you realize something's important, why's it already gone?
Kida-kun... Why?
Why?
Is there something wrong with me saving you from the Yellow Scarves?
That's my ero-cute Anri!
Even that looks good on you.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What are you doing?
When you were sneaking around, what were you looking for?
Tell me, Anri.
What are you after?
I was... You...
I... What?
It's my fault?
I was an idiot for trying to protect you?
That's right.
That's not... Don't say that.
Does Mikado know nothing?
What were you going to do with him?
I...
He...
You knew how he felt!
Why don't you tell him-
Was it fun?
Tricking me... Sucking up to him...
What am I saying?
I just didn't want you to get hurt, or hurt someone...
I ran from you, too.
I...
There she is!
We found her!
You're with the Dollars.
No.
The hell you aren't.
If you aren't, what are you?
Do you want to know what I am?
What?
What are you?
Well? What are you?
Oh, I know!
You're a hero!
You tried to trick our guys into "protecting the peace."
Wish I could've shown you what happened to them!
We beat the crap out of them.
What I did...
So yeah, if you're the only one who's not hurt...
Damn this beeping...
It just won't stop fucking beeping!
I can't read that many words!
Girls? Bunnies? The hell you want me to do?
Annoying...
I found the girl, she's fine.
Case closed.
Because-
Because...
Because the Fortissimo of Ikebukuro is here!
Um...
Thank you for saving me again.
Who were you again?
Hey, I'm turning my phone off.
See you.
Celty...
Mission complete!
Go Dollars!
We did it! We did it!
That's the Dollars for you!
If we all join together, there's nothing to fear!
Thank you, everyone.
I found it.
The most important thing is...
Mikado?
Oh, my! The match's over?
Shizu showed up at just the right second.
But we're not done yet.
Just a bit more, and I can get the checkmate and the oute.
Thank you, everyone.
Oh, there it is! Celty, get the mushroom!
Oh, come on Celty. That's impossible.
I told you. You need to be more careful.
Hey!
Celty!
E-Excuse me...
You were so sound asleep, I didn't want to wake you.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
It's no trouble.
Stay here for a while.
It's dangerous to be living alone.
Are you sure?
If there's anything you need, I'll go get it.
Thank you.
You're gonna skip school and stay home today, right?
I told Mikado.
You know Ryuugamine?
Yeah, I do.
Um... I...
You don't need to worry about a thing.
I'm on your side. And the weird guy in the white lab coat, you can trust-
...he's on our side, too.
Hey, what was that?
Why did you erase "you can trust"?
Why?
Hey!
Celty!
But I'm surprised.
What?
I didn't think Celty would be living with a guy.
The general ain't been around since then.
Who cares?
We know what we're doing.
Everyone here knows what we gotta do, right?
We beat the shit out of the Dollars!
I'll call the cops!
Where are you?
The yellow guys are beating people up again.
They're getting stronger.
They really messed up some guy. A friend said he saw it.
We can't lose! If we all work together like last time...
What are you thinking right now?
The Dollars are going to disappear.
What do you mean?
This is the founder, right?
Leader, are you running away?
You're not going to disband us, are you?
21:34.
The Ikebukuro Dollars are disbanded?
No!
"Disappear" means that we need to be colorless, invisible!
That's irresponsible, leader!
No! Let's believe!
Say something!
Explain!
The Dollars are going to disappear.
You suck.
I can't access it anymore!
Really?
The top page is still there.
But the BBS is completely closed.
What's going on?
He was serious.
That's enough.
Forget about it.
I was alone for a long time, so I thought and thought and thought.
And then I saw their faces...
Their smiles... And they wouldn't go away.
Uh, can I talk to you?
Of course.
I wanted to talk to you, too.
I thought that since you knew about me, I could tell you everything.
I see.
I understand.
Then those two don't know about you.
The two of them have always been there for me,
Kida and Ryuugamine.
But I...
First, we need to stop this gang war.
Yeah.
We'll have to talk to Mikado.
Um, what does Ryuugamine...?
How much do you know about him?
So you don't know...
He's like you.
It may be that he's hiding what's important from you because you're so close and mean so much to him.
Anyway, he should tell you.
I'll bring him here.
Don't give her any strange ideas while I'm gone.
Or interrogate her, or try to use her for any weird experiments.
Got it.
Trust me.
OK.
I will.
Anri, wait a minute.
Celty.
I don't want to run anymore.
Let's go! Let's go!
Blame Kida Masaomi for ordering this!
Kida Masaomi
"Do dreams exist at a time like this?"
I've gotten tired of speaking like that.
I've been walking this entire time,
but recently, even that seems fruitless and in vain.
"I want to see you."
An irrelevant phrase
often heard sung round and round the city.
Something like that
No, something like that
isn't enough to satisfy me.
I know exactly how I feel.
We're free. We pray that all dreams eventually come true.
Just like that,
everyone searches for their true selves.
What we find after a long journey
is the answer.
We're free. We seek the light.
We float freely like butterflies.
Our hearts reflect the great blue sky.
Even if we happen to lose our freedom amidst a strong wind,
we never want to feel regret.
We're free. We seek the light.
We're free. We long to reach a new height.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Next Time
Dullalala!!
Complicated and Confused
Why couldn't I move then?
What made me hesitate?
What was I afraid of?
Saki... I'm not scared anymore.
I won't run anymore.
Next time:
Complicated and Confused.