When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Got it?
Hayate-sama, are you all right?
Of course I'm fine!
Counting the number of threads
in a tatami mat is child's play to me.
Wow, you're amazing.
One, two, three, four, five...
He's really broken down.
Yeah.
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred...
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred one...
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred two...
Hayate-sama?
Yes?
I'm at one hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred two right now.
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred three...
He's gone.
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred four...
Yeah, he is.
One hundred twenty three thousand, six hundred five...
It's natural for me to be discarded by Milady.
Um...
It was like a dream to be able to work at a mansion like that to begin with.
Um!
I only woke up from a dream.
There's nothing to be sad about.
Um, Hayate-sama?
Push.
I-Isumi-san?
I'm sorry!
You did not look very cheerful, so...
...I tried to cheer you up.
I am sorry for doing something I am not used to doing,
but I did not know what to do.
You mustn't laugh.
No, thanks to you, I feel better!
So I'm fine now!
That's right; all I can do is do my best here.
Therefore I'll do my best and count the number of threads in the tatami in the entire house!
You're amazing!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
His head is broken.
Could be a terminal condition.
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen...
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who dedicates himself.
A butler is a formal guardian who supports the days of their master.
Yes.
This is a super combat battle story of a boy who fights, risking his life for a girl.
Hey! Can you tell who I am?
Yes, it's Gilbert!
Hayate no Gotoku is starting, yo!
Really, what were you thinking,
selling Hayate-kun to the Saginomiyas.
It just turned out like that, so don't blame me.
Do you intend to lose important things one by one like that?
Shut up! Besides, why are you here?
The SPs told me you were here.
Aren't you guys on my side?!
Of course we are!
Oh, you are?
I see.
Nagi's side, huh?
You traitors!
Tyrannical selfishness will not make people follow you.
Maria-san's amazing.
She can handle those big men so easily.
She's different from an aging maid.
Who are you calling an aging maid?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Well, I hope he is not crying.
If you sold him for ¥150,000,000, then what you did is no different from what his parents did to him.
Yes, Hayate-san seems to be a very delicate person.
He smiles on the face but cries in his heart.
Besides, if he always gets yelled at by a tomboy like Nagi,
I can understand why he'd want to cry.
C-Could I possibly have done something terrible to Hayate?
Needless to say, everyone thought, "You just noticed that now?"
I'm... I'm...
Nagi?
W-Why are you crying?
I'm not crying!
Hayate might not like me anymore.
D-Don't worry! Sir will do something about it, Lady!
Me?!
Remember I'm also depressed over Isumi?!
Don't worry! Your power of love will certainly make Isumi-san look in your direction!
You think so?
But Wataru's not that popular.
Lady Nagi!
Are you picking a fight with me?!
Well, whatever. I'll work things out, so wait here!
Sir?
But how are we going to bring him back?
Oh, that's easy.
Hayate-kun must be thinking Nagi hates him now,
so all we have to do is tell him
Nagi is crying and wants him to come back.
But what about Isumi?
From my hunch, I do not think she is that attached to him.
Things'll be fine if you leave it to them.
But Hayate must hate me now.
Then why not test him?
Who are you?
And test what?
I said, test the love.
Excuse me, Lady. Is he someone you know?
Yes, embarrassingly enough, he's a relative.
Not just a relative.
A candidate for heir to the Sanzenin estate!
Gilbert!
Um, is he really your relative?
I'd like him not to be.
So, what's this "test the love"?
What I mean is, if love still exists
between you and him, he shall overcome any obstacles.
For example, say that I kidnapped you; he may or may not come for you!
Fake a kidnapping?!
You can't do that!
Yeah, I don't think so.
Why?
Hayate probably won't come.
Well, he might,
but I feel that it would be out of pity for me.
I see. What a chicken.
For a wuss who won't even take a risk
to be the future president of the Sanzenin...
This world really is corrupt.
You got it, then!
Do whatever you want, a fake kidnapping or whatever!
Lady!
But I'll be the one to win this!
That's the way I want it.
Meanwhile, at the Saginomiya residence...
Are you confortable with the situation, Hayate-kun?
Fine or not, I don't have a choice.
There will be no end if you take every whimsical thing she says seriously.
Well, yes, but...
They're bashing her...
Moreover, don't you want to come back?
Did you not leave things behind
with Nagi and the Sanzenin mansion?
Leave behind? Memories...
Tokyo's underground is amazing as always!
But why come all the way here?
To test the love, the hurdle has to be proportionally large.
Are you planning to fight Hayate again?
Yes.
No matter how strong that butler may be,
it's impossible for him to beat this!
What do you plan to do if Hayate gets hurt?
No worries.
The scientist who made this is a genius.
It's made to be human friendly.
Say, Eight...
Do you remember what this was for?
That'd be the control regulation chip for the giant robot you made yesterday at the request of your friend.
I made a giant robot?
I was half-asleep, so I don't remember well.
That proves how amazing you are, to create that while half-asleep.
You think so?
But it really wasn't that big of a job.
I only used your prototype body and installed your OS 8.1.
Th-That'd be data from when I was most hurt emotionally.
Isn't it very dangerous?
Oh come on, Eight.
That's why I made the control regulation chip.
I-I see...
It's so boring.
I wonder if anything good will happen.
You're joking! This is still fresh off the pan!
It's got to be a present from God!
Sushi, suki ka?
Sushi, suki ka? = Do you like sushi?
Kaikoku shitekudasai
Kaikoku shitekudasai = "Please open the port"
from Matthew Calbraith Perry, who arrived at Japan in 1853
Will Hayate come?
Even if he did, Hayate would now be...
Isumi-san's house is so comfortable.
You're so kind and calm unlike that selfish girl.
It was right to be sold here.
Hey, hey. That's only your imagination.
Y-Yeah, it's all Hayate's fault for cheating on me!
Who cheated on whom?
Sakuya!
Why are you here?
Why? Because I have to watch what my Aniki's doing.
What?
G-Gilbert's is your older brother?
I didn't know until recently myself,
but apparently we have different mothers, and his existence was kept hidden.
But we look alike, don't we?
Is that something to be happy about?
But, how did this happen?
Well... Hayate was cheating on me with Isumi...
Huh?
Not only with Isumi!
Hayate said that he has fun with you, too.
Yeah, we do have lots of fun.
From smacking each other after each gag.
Like I said, over gags.
Ah-ha.
What's this, Nagi-chan?
You're only thirteen, and you took fun as "fun"?
No, absolutely not!
I knew it was over gags. I wasn't misunderstanding him at all!
Don't sweat it. I know. I know.
You're dirty-minded.
But what a horrible story.
That debt-ridden butler had done nothing wrong to be accused of and yet got sold off.
He definitely won't come.
Hayate would never come save me.
Little girl, people's trust becomes stronger as you overcome such misunderstandings.
Therefore you must not fear misunderstandings.
It's the proof of love to come nonetheless!
Wh-What? The machine's moving on its own.
Aniki?
Kill.
Will kill the blond twin-tail and her butler.
My life was ruined thanks to them!
So he says. What should we do?
Well, I don't want to hear a guy bitch about not being popular with girls.
Yeah, why not forget about him and get out of here?
Let's just tell Aniki riding inside, "You are dead."
Don't forsake me, my sister!
Besides, this thing is after Lady Nagi.
I don't think you can get away that easily.
That's right. I will not forgive that blond twin-tail.
Where is she?
Where did she go?
Yup, it's better not to skimp on the CPU.
But I'm glad this didn't turn into a big mess.
Where are you, blond twin-tail?
They could be worried about us, so let's give a call to Sir.
Sounds good.
What's wrong, Saki?
Hey, don't tell me Nagi got kidnapped.
No, not a kidnapping, it's-
Curse you, Sanzenin Nagi. I will kill you.
What?! Don't tell me it's a homicide!
No, absolutely not!
Then is it about to turn into a homicide?
Don't worry, she hasn't been killed yet.
Then is Nagi about to be killed?
Hey Saki! Saki!
Um, Wataru-kun. What was that phone call about?
Not entirely sure, but sounds like Saki screwed something up
and Nagi's kidnapped and about to get killed.
Wh-What? Nagi is?
Hayate-kun!
Huh? Hayate-kun?
Ah, man.
Fine, I'll give them another call.
I think they completely misunderstood what happened.
Oh, if I kill all three of them, then one of them has got to be her.
Hey it's Saku. Just wanted to say...
...we're in real deep trouble, so come save us.
Hey!
Sounds like they really are in big trouble.
It will be all right.
Hayate-sama has already gone to save Nagi.
Ladies!
That! That's attacking us!
What?
To attack our precious Lady Nagi.
I won't forgive you even if you are part of the Sanzenin family!
Shut up! If you don't want to experience any pain,
hand over the twin-tailed girl.
Don't underestimate the Sanzenin's SPs' power.
What?
Look, you piece of metal from Devil **der!
This is the quality of the Sanzenin SP!
I found you, twin-tail!
It's all solved now.
Of course it isn't!
Seriously! This is too horrible!
I've cornered you now, girl.
No, no, no. What do you intend to do after cornering me?
What?
Do what?
*Blush*
Then how about...
What was the blushing about?
And I really don't like how your fingers are moving.
Shut up, girl!
Get out of the way, you idiot!
Sir!
Really, don't make me go through that.
Why are you here?
This place turns out to be right under Isumi's house.
Wh-What?
Sir!
Stop, you fool!
I always thought you were a child,
but you've become a great man without me noticing.
Become... a man...
Will he watch those?
You can't!
Huh?
You're too young for adult videos.
I-I don't watch that stuff!
Hey, you two! You better get out of there!
I won't miss this time.
That's enough, rundown robot!
Did you not hear me, you rundown!
You trashy crab!
W-Why you...
You're inferior to fake ******* in design, and you dare to trouble people?
That's why you're not popular with girls!
I, Sanzenin Nagi, shall be your opponent.
Then eat this!
Watch out, Milady!
Where's Hayate?!
He left for here before I did.
Oh, I get it.
Hayate won't be coming.
Lady Nagi!
He won't come.
He hates me now.
Nagi, run!
Die!
Hayate...
Hayate!!!
Did you call for me, Milady?
Hayate, why are you here?
Why?
Because you called for me.
I have not forgotten the pain you've caused me.
Is there anywhere that hurts, Milady?
I will now return all that back to you.
No, I'm fine.
I see. That's good to hear.
Hey, stop ignoring me!
You don't need to rush; I will have you
take responsibility for endangering Milady.
Could he possibly be angry?
And when those who usually don't get angry get angry...
He's scary.
Hey boy, please don't forget me.
Gilbert is on board this mecha.
I see. So you're the one that was trying to kidnap Milady.
Y-You got that a little wrong.
I was playing along with everyone and...
Playing along?
Then you're saying that Saki-san came up
with the stupid idea of faking a kidnapping?
Well, Saki-san?
No, Gilbert Aniki kidnapped her for the sake of the estate.
Hear that?
My sister...
Looks like money is the only thing you can trust.
Then I will fulfill the requirement and get the Sanzenin estate!
Hell Volcanic Destroy!!!
No you don't.
I won't put Milady in any more danger.
Hayate!
Pass this on to the other candidates, as well.
Anyone who wants the Sanzenin's estate will have to defeat her butler, Ayasaki Hayate, first!
What? Do you understand the danger that comes with that?
I do.
Besides, that Old Mikado wouldn't accept that.
She might hate you because of another misunderstanding and kick you out again.
It doesn't matter if Milady hates me.
My care for her will not change no matter what.
Quit the love-comedy!
No matter how cool you act,
you can't beat this robot, Ayasaki Hayate!
You'll be the one dying!
Watch out, Hayate!
You don't have to worry about a thing.
I've come prepared with various things in case of situations like this.
What?
That's violating the Sword and Firearm Control Law!
Don't worry; I'm aware of how to use this.
From where?
Besides, if it's to protect Milady, I really don't care about the Sword and Firearm Control Law.
Do you want to continue?
Even if you defeat me, the second and third Gilbert will...
What kind of evil lord do you think you are?
I give up! I give up!
The fierce gun battle ended.
Hayate...
Yes, Milady?
And the girl and butler gaze at each other.
Well, um...
"I'm sorry I fired you on an impulse."
"I apologize, so come back to the mansion with me."
...is what Nagi wants to say, but...
I just noticed that I changed the conditions to the inheriting the estate, so staying by you would be more dangerous.
And first of all, I am Isumi-san's butler now, aren't I?
Well, ah...
But, since I ran out, skipping out on work, I could be fired from the position by now.
If so, I'd be lost in the street again
with a debt of ¥150,000,000 on me.
I wonder if there's a cute girl who would find me a new job.
Th-Then...
...would you like to be my butler?
Yes, Milady!
Are you okay with this, Isumi-san?
It's not good to buy and sell people with money.
Plus...
Plus?
Those two go well together.
Nagi and...
Hayate's..
Butler Network!
I've got a great idea.
This is Sanzenin Nagi.
This is Ayasaki Hayate.
And this is Aizawa Sakuya.
Aizawa-san, this is a really refined song.
It's because my cri de coeur  is contained in it.
It's the song most loved by women living in the Osaka area.
It only sounds like an old-fashioned song to me.
I guess a kid like Nagi still can't understand the good parts of the song.
I don't mind not figuring it out for the rest of my life.
Next week will be a special.
Please look forward to it.
Bye bye.
Hey Hayate, what is this about?
Stop this foolish joke.
Um...
I'm not giving Hayate-kun to you.
He's... He's... My important butler!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
It Took 29 Minutes To Deliver, So Please Pay the Amount We Had Originally Asked For... Is an Old Myth Now
Hayate's amnesia? You're joking!
Next week, you'll be excited over Hayate's crossdressing.