Are Haruka and the girls all right?
Could it be?
What's that?!
Our school!
What's goin' on? Are they filming?
And nobody told me?!
Girls!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Encroaching Despair!
The Cornered Princesses!
O foolish masses, deluged in dreams...
your world hereby belongs to me.
Your dreams shall give way to despair,
and every last one...
shall become my strength!
We won't let that happen!
Have you lost your mind?!
Yuuki?
I'll help everyone escape...
Then we'll help too!
As will I!
Just say the word.
We can't leave any students in danger!
You must escape at once!
What's the movie? Get me the director!
What now?
They can't transform here...
The school!
H-Haruno?
Minami?
Girls...
Let's go!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
It's those fighting princesses!
It's them?
Haruno is...
Flora?!
Girls,
let's stop Dyspear!
Escape to safety, everyone!
Akagi's brother?
Girls!
You can do it!
The parrot t—
Perf talked?! And flew?!
Girls...
Nanase...
did you... know about this?
Really?
What's going on?
Please, tell us what's happening!
Those girls...
have been protecting our dreams this whole time.
Close...
Here.
The Precures are coming.
Go forth, as I yet cannot.
Right.
Lastly, take this with you.
Isn't that...
He was an impudent little failure, but he still has some use left.
It's too quiet...
Dyspear, what are you plotting?
You won't be going...
Any further!
No going further means...
No going further!
I'll hold them back!
Vous must get to Dyspear!
Brother!
Madame Siamour!
Hurry!
We owe you one!
Siamour...
At votre service.
Thank you.
What do you think...
You can possibly do?
We can at least...
Keep vous at bay!
Then those girls were...
Yes.
To save Hope Kingdom and
protect our dreams from despair...
they've fought all this time.
Our dreams?
Hey.
Close!
Get 'em, Lock.
Lock?
Is that...
It's him!
No... He's been revived?
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Frozen Ripple!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Scarlet Flame!
I'll protect her, 'kay?
I will protect Lady Dyspear!
Defeat... Precures...
Isn't he acting kinda strange?
Yes...
I am not Dyspear's pawn!
Defeat... for Lady Dyspear!
It's like he's a puppet!
Lock...
Girls!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
Lock, I'll give you even greater despair!
Defeat the Precures!
What the—
I won't give in!
Not when the Precures are fighting so hard!
I won't let despair...
The students!
It's growing by absorbing everyone's despair energy!
No...
What?!
It can't be!
The Princess Rod...
Where...
Who...
We won't give in!
Haruka...
That's right, I'm in the Cage of Despair again!
Girls!
We'll never back down!
This is no time to lie around!
The only ones who can save them from despair... are us!
We shall not lose!
Don't lose!
Never give up!
We're all going...
to grant everyone's dreams!
Right!
Girls...
You're right, this is no time to wallow in some cage!
It's my dream, so I have to fight for it!
Waiting to be rescued won't get me anywhere!
I'll fight too!
I'm with you, Precures!
I did it!
Yui?
Did you just break out of that cage yourself?!
I can't believe it! That's incredible!
Is something...
Aihara! Wake up, Aihara!
Everyone!
Open your eyes!
They ca—
They can!
If I escaped from that cage, then so can everyone else!
Everyone, you can't just lie here and give in to despair!
Remember how the Precures...
how our friends protected our dreams!
Don't be afraid.
There's no sorrow that can't be overcome!
This is Noble Academy,
a place where dreams come true!
Reiko, wake up!
Depression isn't in your character!
Remember your dreams!
We all have them...
Dreams whose flames may fade but can never be put out!
Dreams?
Let's fight together.
The only one who can make your dream come true...
is you!
My... dream...
I won a Grand Slam!
I'm the top idol!
That light!
The power of dreams?
What?
Nanase!
I almost lost my shot at making top idol!
You're okay!
What's wrong, Lock?
Did someone halt the students' despair?
What?!
Curse you...
Girls!
Are you okay?
Yui?!
How are you here?
Yui opened all the cages of despair herself!
Wait, she opened them?!
Inconceivable!
No, it wasn't me alone.
We all knew we had to fight.
If we wanted our dreams, we had to take a stand now!
We had to win against despair!
Thanks to the courage you girls gave us.
If a heart is strong enough, one can overthrow despair!
Thank you, Yui! You gave us some serious courage!
Not enough... despair...
Need... more despair...
For Lady Dyspear...
Poor guy...
Can we help him?
I just... feel sorry for him...
Kuroro...
Already outlived your usefulness?
So be it.
You lot have outlived yours as well!
Shut!
Shut?
What's the big idea?!
Silence!
Lock!
After all the degradation you've put me through,
this is what you become?
Where has all that conceit of yours gone?!
Look!
While we've fallen to disgrace,
the Precures, fairies, and even the humans have been changing!
What are you—
We can change as well!
There's naught but to escape from Dyspear's curse!
'Kay...
Precures, now! On Lock!
Flora!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
They did it!
An exercise in futility.
Curse you, Precures...
But your time has come.
We won't let our dreams be extinguished!
Dyspear!
Now!
Do prepare yourself!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
The thorns are spreading around the world...
Dyspear has grown into a giant! Our attacks can't reach her!
Can we not defeat the despair
without becoming Grand Princesses?
But we still can't give up.
We're the Princess Precures!
We won't hand over our dreams!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Showdown with Dyspear
The Birth of the Grand Princesses!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Shiga Prefecture - Ako (Age 7)
Hyougo Prefecture - Kotoko (Age 5)