What's that?
What in the world...
Take a look, viewers!
A giant creature has appeared out of nowhere!
Just what in the world is going on?
Congratulations on your resurrection, King Selfish.
We have all been long awaiting this day.
Talk about a brown-noser.
Gag me.
We shall conquer the human world and strike down all who oppose!
Very well.
Today shall be the day those meddlesome Precures meet their doom.
Any objections,
Princess Regina?
Of course not. Now go!
Right!
Tryin' to fool yourself?
About what?
I wonder.
I've chosen to live for Daddy's sake.
Well, that's fine.
But...
that glum psyche of yours is an eyesore.
This is a catastrophe!
Everyone in the area, evacuate ASAP!
Huh?
Who are they?
All right, girls.
Let's go!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Cure Heart's Determination!
A Promise to Protect!
Your heart shall go aflutter!
Ace Shot!
Bang!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Let's focus on getting to King Selfish!
Yes. We need to make him stop, quick!
That said, it doesn't look easy...
Complaints won't get us anywhere.
You're right.
Precure Diamond Swirkle!
This is not a movie!
This is real, live coverage!
A giant creature has arisen from the sea and five girls are desperately fighting to stop it!
We don't know who these girls are,
but we can say this:
these girls are risking their lives to protect us and the entire world!
Teacher, we've gotta evacuate now!
I was thinking the same thing.
Hey, look!
It's Cure Heart!
She's always protected us before...
but who is she really?
There's no end to them.
No kidding.
Bel!
Hey there, Precures.
Today marks the end of our miserable acquaint—
Sword!
I'll handle him!
Go on ahead!
You truly think you can stop me alone?
No.
She's not alone!
Rosetta!
Our hearts are all one!
Now hurry!
Thanks!
That was pathetic.
You sure you can beat them?
I don't need to!
Huh?
They'll destroy themselves.
Indeed, because they cling to their foolish delusion of love.
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
I'll be the one to defeat the Precures.
Ira...
You did this last time, too.
Don't remember it.
Oh, what a shame.
You've got no chance now that King Selfish is resurrected.
So, what're you fighting for?
It may be difficult,
but we can't give up.
I see.
Then—
I'll defeat you here, Cure Diamond!
You can try, but you can't defeat me.
What? What do you mean?
Well, in case you didn't know,
diamonds...
are unbreakable!
You brats just don't know when to quit.
What can you possibly do against these odds?
I know not.
But if we all keep trying, we'll certainly find a way!
So I feel!
You "feel"? That's it?
That's all we need!
That's how rigid our bonds are!
What a joke!
That's not all!
I stand here more rigid than ever!
C'mon, Cure Sword.
You won't cut me like that.
I'm not trying to cut you!
What?!
To sever is cowardice, but cutting forth leads to the future!
I am the blade of courage that pierces the heart!
That is why the princess gave me my name:
Cure Sword!
Your blade is dull!
Girls...
Heart!
Regina...
Mana, why do you still persist...
when I can't even stand to see your face anymore?
Because we made a promise.
Huh?
I said we'd meet your dad once you felt better, remember?
My plans got a bit off track,
but now's the time to follow through.
Mr. King Selfiiiiiiiiiiish!
Please listen to meeeeeeee!
Be silent!
Begone from my presence!
You see that?
Your words will never reach Daddy.
I... won't give up!
What?!
Take a moment... and listen... to what others say!
All we want to do... is to protect... everyone's smiles!
Protect?
What can you hope to protect with your feeble power?
Everything!
Both this world and Trump Kingdom...
Both Regina's smile and yours...
We'll protect it all!
Whoah, they pushed him back!
But it's too late for theatrics.
What do you mean?
This world's done for.
I'm sure you already know...
of the day Trump Kingdom fell.
The once peaceful, neighborly citizens...
suddenly twisted in fear.
Move it! I'm goin' first!
Shut it! You're in my way!
The hell was that for?!
Help me!
They thought only of saving themselves, performed despicable acts,
and became Selfishes on their own.
And now,
the people of this world are acting just as those in Trump Kingdom once did.
Just like Trump Kingdom, this entire world shall lose its love!
No, it won't.
What?
I believe that love is undefeatable.
I'm sure that even now...
people are supporting each other with love!
You think people that foolish exist?
They exist.
I can feel it.
Their love is like a racing heart!
Move it! I'm goin' first!
You're in the way!
Excuse me!
Could someone lend a hand?
There are injured people who can't move!
Please, someone help us!
Hey, where are they?
If we don't hurry, we won't make it!
It's you guys! Thank you so much!
Lead the way.
Sure!
I'll help too!
I will, too.
Thank you!
We gotta help each other when we're down!
Yeah!
Oogai University Hospital
You'll be fine.
Someone will come to help.
Thank you so much for your help.
Oh.
Don't worry about it.
Desperate times, and all.
Apologies for the wait!
We'll begin transportation of those needing aid!
I, Itsutsuboshi Reina, shall humbly assist however I can!
Can't you hear the heartbeats of love?
I can feel it...
Caring for others carries such a gentle tone...
A gentle tone that never gives up hope...
It resounds ever further as people help each other...
It creates a harmony!
Foolishness!
I'll just destroy your precious heartbeat of love!
Rosetta!
I can't...
hold it back!
The Clover Tower!
It's not over.
The heartbeat of love isn't gone!
Good point.
It wouldn't do to give up here.
You insolent pests!
You dare resist in the wake of my overwhelming power?
Are you too daft to know fear?
We have nothing to fear!
Yes. The Eternal Golden Crown showed us the truth.
You are Regina's father!
That's why I know you'll be able to see eye to eye!
That's enough.
If you insist on getting in Daddy's way,
I'll fight you!
Heart!
Stay back!
Better watch your backs!
Don't tell me you forgot about us.
Stop this, Regina!
Regina!
What, are you done?
After all you've been through, do you still think you can talk with Daddy or me?
Why won't you fight back?!
I won't fight you, Regina.
Why?!
Because we're friends.
I can't break a promise to a friend.
Get a grip!
That promise lost all meaning long ago!
We're not friends any...
We're friends.
Come on, Regina. Stop hurting yourself.
I-I'm not hurt...
Regina, you were crying.
And those weren't tears of joy.
I saw tears filled with the pain of having nowhere to belong.
Don't you see?
I don't want you to shed those tears.
Why? Why?
What are you after?
You're not my family or anything!
You're a stranger!
I just like you.
I just like you, Regina.
Do I need anything more?
I like you, Regina,
so I'm sure I can like the Daddy you adore.
I want to like him and understand him!
So, can we talk again, Regina?
Just you, me, and your dad.
Be silent!
Do not lend such nonsense your ear!
Regina!
Daddy!
Do not lead Regina astray!
That's...
It's the same beam from before!
Oh no!
If he fires another one...
Nooooooooo!
The spear...
Why, Regina?!
Why do you strike back?!
Could it be that love has sprouted in your heart once more?!
Regina!
Daddy...
No, it hasn't. Not in that way.
Love...
has been in my heart from the beginning, Daddy.
After all, I love you.
But, you know...
I like Mana too!
Just as much as you!
I can't choose between you!
I like Mana!
Regina...
What the heck?
In a way, it's the ultimate selfishness.
Maybe,
but her psyche...
is back to its peachy, perky self.
Is that so wrong?
I don't believe it is.
I love Mana too,
but I also love Rikka, Makoto, Aguri, and you!
Me too.
I used to care only about the princess,
but now I love everyone here.
Silence!
Regina, I am all you need!
I understand how you feel.
I remember having those same emotions.
But...
it's best to let the people you love love others instead of hogging them to yourself.
You get to know more people that way.
What's wrong with that?
Silence, silence, silence!
Please stop this.
The bonds between people are love!
My duty as a warrior of love was not to defeat you,
but to love!
I've finally realized that.
And now...
I can do just that.
Because...
you are my father!
Ann...
Now please, open your eyes!
Father!
Daddy!
Ann...
Regina...
What could this be?
What could it be that boils within my chest?
Have you figured it out, King Selfish?
No, have you remembered?
It's...
Love.
What?!
I refuse...
I need no love!
Love does not exist!
Love shall disappear!
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let us plant smiles like flowers everywhere, and everyone will know love
Love Precure
I want to understand you even better
I want to know ecstasy
I'm so excited (Yeah!) My heart beats so fast (Yeah!)
Let's go find our future
Sometimes we get scared and cry
Who cares? We're girls!
When we look around, we see that we're not alone
It means we're friends now that we're holding hands
Let's smile together and be honest with our feelings
If we stick to how we truly feel,
then miracles will happen, and we will have the strength bring love to everyone
I, Cure Heart, will protect the world's peace and the bonds we share!
Dokidoki Precure:
Hearts Racing at Max Speed!
Precures vs. King Selfish!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!