I'm Plutia.
Nice to meet you.
A toast to Plutia, Planeptune's new CPU!
Hold it right there!
Compa, that makes it sound like she took my place as CPU!
Huh? But she's Planeptune's CPU too.
Yeah, she said Planeptune, but her Planeptune is a different Planeptune to our Planeptune.
Got all that?
Er...
Basically, it seems Plutia came from another dimension.
Though I guess you don't know how to react to being told there's another dimension out there.
Can you transform too?
I can.
But people tell me not to do it too often.
How come?
Hmm...
I wonder why...
Hey, P-ko!
Gonna eat meat!
You can have this, Neptuna!
Get it away from me!
I hate eggplants!
Why don't you give it a try, Neppy?
They came out quite well today, if I do say so myself.
Don't wanna!
The stench alone makes me lose all strength!
But they're so delicious.
You're missing out on about 33% of what life has to offer.
Whatever! I still hate those stupid things!
Eggplants are really good for you, you know.
You're taking the eggplants' side too, Histy?!
Neptune!
What kind of an example does a CPU who's picky about food set for her people?
Lady Histoire!
Are you okay?
I... don't... know....
A curse?!
It's the curse of the eggplants!
It is not!
Yeah, those things just aren't edible!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#07 The Fruit (Deep Purple) of Revenge
Sorry about that.
That was the first time I'd ever received communications from another dimension,
so it took me a while to read the manual and respond accordingly.
I'm sorry about calling you out of the blue, too.
Thank you for taking care of Plutia.
You're kinda tiny.
Don't look down on me just because I'm small!
I was the one who sent Plutia to your dimension, you know.
I see.
That was quite the shock, though.
I had no idea other dimensions existed,
let alone that they were so easy to travel between.
It's not easy!
I'll have you know it's actually quite difficult to do.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Though, well, the manual does contain a how-to guide.
Took me three days to read it all.
That so?
I'll have a look through mine.
Delish Pudding
Nep's
Dessert time!
Delish Pudding
Nep's
Yay!
Hey, P-ko!
Delish Pudding
Nep's
I want this one!
That's mine.
Can't you see it says "Nep's" on the label?
Peashy, the others are the same as that one.
No! I wanna eat Nep's pudding!
Why?
It says it's mine, so it's mine.
Go away.
Say what?
You wanna go?
You're being immature, Neptune.
Don't fight, Neppy.
Anyway,
why did you send Plutia here?
To tell you the truth,
we detected a large flow of energy from our dimension to yours.
I think something—
or someone—moved there.
Oh...
Whatever it is, it holds so much energy that if we let it go,
our world might run out of energy to sustain itself.
Right...
That's why we need Plutia to look for whatever went missing and bring it back.
I see.
So, how would one go about searching for this thing?
P-Punch!
I spent three days investigating that, and I still couldn't figure it out.
Huh? Then...
All we can do is try to stay on top of any changes that happen in your world.
If some kind of major upheaval takes place,
you should be able to find what we seek nearby.
I understand.
I'll let the others know.
And that's the story.
I'd like you all to inform me immediately if you notice anything peculiar.
So you've come, huh?
I'll send you flying clear outta Planeptune!
I'm gonna play with this!
Give that back! Please!
Um, are you listening to me?
Oh, sorry, Histoire.
I'm listening.
W-Wait!
That's if anything peculiar happens, right?
I haven't seen anything yet.
But you haven't moved an inch.
I'll go on patrol, Histoire.
Thanks as always.
I'm counting on you.
Sure. See you later.
Compa, you've got work now, right?
Want a ride on my motorbike?
Yes, thank you!
All done!
Huh? Plutia, is that me?
It's Neptuna!
That's right.
It's so cute.
Totally.
It's got everything that makes me cute!
I like making dolls of my friends.
Me too!
Make me too!
I'll do yours next, then.
And Gear after that.
Yippee!
We did it!
Let me begin right away.
Maybe, just maybe, we'll get to see a real artist at work?
Yeah, maybe she'll make it without any pattern paper.
H-Huh?
She's asleep?
Well, we got to see a piece of work, I guess.
There's a lot of construction work going on today.
Sorry we're running late.
It's okay.
I'm with you, so I'm having fun.
R-Really?
What the?
Hold your breath, Compa!
You certainly fell for that one easily.
Wait, you can't be...
Sis!
Wake up, Sis!
I can't eat any more...
Quit having such clichéd dreams!
Geez, Sis.
What do you want, Nepgear?
What the heck are those?
Oh, no.
They were sent to me from an unknown address.
There was a map attached too.
We need to go save her!
Yeah, but who would do a thing like this?
The time for revenge has come.
You won't achieve anything by doing this, Arfoire.
Neppy and Nepgear will just defeat you again.
This time will be different.
I've got an ace up my sleeve.
That is to say...
all these eggplants!
I've already figured out that eggplants are a goddess's Achilles heel!
I'll put them through hell right here in this eggplant farm.
You don't stand a chance no matter what tricks you pull,
you old hag.
Shut up, pipsqueak.
Choke it all down.
Don't leave a single molecule behind.
Wouldn't want you to miss out on 33% of what life has to offer.
What do you think you're doing, you wrinkly witch?!
Silence!
Eggplant skin is loaded with polyphenols, you know?
Stop it!
There you are, CPU.
Today's the day I send you six feet under.
If it's a fight you want, you've got it.
So unhand Iffy at once—
Are you okay, Sis?
I'm sorry.
The stench of those eggplants—
Took you long enough to notice.
I bought up all this farmland so I could use your Achilles heel against you.
This eggplant field will be your grave!
Don't be stupid.
Sure, I may hate eggplants,
but they're not going to kill me.
We'll see about that.
Come forth, my purple servants!
What are those?
Huh?
Where am I?
A place just for the two of us.
Mister Mouse?
I crawled my way up from the depths of Hell just so I could see you again.
Huh?
From the what of Hell?
Today's the day I give you every last inch of my heart.
Eggplants scary!
Eggplants stop!
Eww. Yikes.
Sis! Plutia!
Outta my way!
Pull yourself together, Neppy!
They're just monsters that this old hag put together with her magic.
Kick their asses!
Haven't had enough yet, eh?
While I'm here, I might as well keep feeding you eggplants!
IF!
Nepgear!
I'm gonna hurl!
Well?
Eggplants taste good raw too, don't they?
How about another?
Eat it.
Eat some more.
Zoinks...
This kinda...
pisses me off.
Why...
would you...
Zoinks!
torment...
Iffy like that?
S-She's my hostage! I can do whatever I want to her!
So that's how it's going to be, is it?
In that case...
Maybe I should do whatever I want, too.
Huh? Plutia?
That's an even more drastic
transformation than my sister's.
Who the hell are you?!
Me?
I'm Iris Heart.
Don't worry about memorizing it.
I'll carve it into your body for you!
Don't tell me you're all flash and no substance, now.
Show me a side of yours that's a little less withered up, would you?!
She seems to be enjoying herself.
A-Anyway, we should let Plutia handle things over there.
Why don't you try opposing me for a change?
While they're at it, let's finish these guys off nice and quick.
Nepgear, go and free Iffy.
I'll chop up these eggplants.
Okay.
I've seen the light.
Nothing seems worth it if you don't have your loved one by your side.
So...
Co... Co... Compa!
M-Mister Mouse?!
Take that!
I thought I'd be able to have a bit more fun,
but I guess a loser's a loser.
I just let my guard down! That's all!
If I'd known about you beforehand...
Man, losers are always so full of excuses.
Blah, blah, blah, blah...
It hurts to listen to.
I'm so not gonna reach the climax like this.
Guess I should just finish you off.
Wait, Plutia.
That's enough—
Did you think I had nothing else up my sleeve?
I'll teach you even more about the true terror of purple.
Behold my newfound powers!
I have become a transcendent being that melds goddess
with eggplant, exceeding the power of both!
My name is Eggfoire!
Hm? You don't seem very impressed.
When you get that huge, you don't look much like an eggplant to me anymore.
You're just a great big lump of purple.
S-Say what?!
Right now, my anger's winning out.
I can't forgive what you did to Iffy
or what you did by bringing eggplants, of all things, into battle.
I'll make you rue the
day you crossed me.
Ready, Nepgear, Plutia?
Yeah, Sis!
I'm always ready.
Wha—
This sure is eggplant on my face!
If you were going to bring veggies into it,
you should've used a more balanced selection.
Compa.
Let's share the kiss of destiny.
Mister Mouse.
Are you no longer a bad guy?
I don't like bad guys.
If I wasn't a bad guy...
Who're you?!
Things were just getting juicy over here! Don't interrupt!
You're just a mouse.
The only thing you're fit to do is scurry through filthy sewer pipes.
I can't believe you'd even think of defiling cute li'l Compa.
Don't tell me. Are you a new CPU?
"CPU"?
You filthy, vulgar vermin.
That's...
"goddess" to you!
Wow. Mister Mouse has such a limber body.
It's stretching like rubber!
Come on! Come on!
What was that? I can't understand you!
Are you okay now, IF?
Yes. I'm not hurt or anything.
That Arfoire sure was a terrifying opponent, wasn't she?
Yeah.
Though there was someone even more terrifying out there.
Huh?
What do you mean, Neppy?
Nothing.
Gotta try and keep her transformations to a minimum from now on.
Dinner's ready!
Dinner! Dinner! Dinner!
Zoinks!
Mauve eggplants?!
Yes.
Wh-Why are we having eggplants again after what just happened?
Peashy requested them.
Looks like she took a liking to them after eating them yesterday.
Eggplants!
I heard you'd overcome your hate for eggplants too, Nep-Nep.
Nah, I wouldn't exactly
call that "overcoming" it.
I was just going with
the flow of battle!
No! Not eggplants!
I hate eggplants.
Eggplants scary!
Don't wanna eat eggplants anymore!
Get a hold of yourself, IF!
Iffy started hating eggplants too?
Well, I can understand how she feels.
Iffy! My bosom buddy!
Eggplants yummy!
Are you seriously going to become an eggplant farmer?
Given up on your quest
for world dominaton?
Yeah, I've grown a little tired of it all.
I used up all my money on that operation,
so I don't even have anywhere else to go.
You'll help me?
I don't have anything better to do.
This is so strange.
For the first time ever,
I feel alive.
I'm not doing it for free, you know.
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
On a faraway island lies a giant, mysterious machine.
Huge, skin-colored,
and sometimes pink.
Like
this!
Is it a trap?
Or perhaps...
Next week, on Hyperdimension Neptunia:
The Forbidden Paradise (Island)
...Where We Do and Have All Kinds of Things Done To Us
and Maybe There'll Not Only Be Some Wardrobe Malfunctions
But Also Some Kinda Licking Too OH MY GOD
I, Neptune, Am Like, So Embarrassed!
The Forbidden Paradise (Island)
...Where We Do and Have All Kinds of Things Done To Us
and Maybe There'll Not Only Be Some Wardrobe Malfunctions
But Also Some Kinda Licking Too OH MY GOD
I, Neptune, Am Like, So Embarrassed!
the prelude to a nightmare.
Tune in or kiss your save data goodbye.