I'm so lost!
Jeez, why are the streets in Meirocho so confusing?
At this rate, I'll never get back to Natsumeya!
Why, hello there, little lost puppy.
I can divine the path for you if you're in trouble.
Paths
Divined
Really?!
I'll give you the special price of one silver coin.
Huh? Money?
I don't have any money!
Then I'll take whatever you can sell me.
A tooth, a nail, an eye...
Huh?!
Your long, long hair...
Stop right there!
Urara Regulation Number 5:
An Urara is not to divine for those who are unwilling.
Compensated divination cannot take place
without the consent of both parties.
Let go of her at once!
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Why're you butting in? It's none of your business!
Urara Regulation Number 9:
An Urara must not hide her face or body
when conducting business.
Regulation Number 11:
Street solicitation is prohibited!
Underhanded divination is strictly prohibited!
And Regulation Number 1:
An Urara must never harm her customers!
Don't come back until you've reevaluated your character!
I-I'll remember this!
Are you alright? Were you hurt?
I-I'm okay!
My, have we met somewhere before?
You have a very familiar face.
Oh, perhaps you just look like my neighbor, Shiro-san.
Three Siblings
No, maybe more like Tamajiro-san
from across the street...
I-I'm a Rank 10 Urara at Natsumeya, Chiya!
My, you're a student at Natsumeya?
My name is Tokie.
Tokie-san?
Natsumeya is quite a ways from here.
I can take you there if you'd like.
Really?!
Yes, but...
Before that, there's a place I'd like to take you.
CLOTHES
Thank you very much!
Urara Regulation Number 25:
An Urara must wear quality clothes befitting of her.
Alright, now, let's head off to Natsumeya.
But I don't like kimonos...
My, how cute!
What a cute Urara.
Huh?
Oh, dear, I want to dress her up!
How wonderfully elegant.
Miss Urara, please, take one.
Good luck in your studies!
Huh? Are you sure?
Take this, too.
And this!
Here!
And this, too!
I might like kimonos now!
Oh, my!
PIGEON
FORTUNES
Hey, Tokie-san, look at this!
It says they can tell pigeon fortunes!
I wonder what that's like!
Meirocho really has a lot of interesting places, huh?
Chiya-san, if you keep stopping to see the sights,
you'll never get back to Natsumeya.
Come on.
Huh?
Hey, Tokie-san, are you an Urara?
Yes, I'm a Rank 2 Urara.
Rank 2?!
My, it's nothing to be surprised by.
Rank 10 and Rank 2 Urara all walk the same path.
We just walk a bit further ahead.
Just like I am right now.
A bit further ahead...
Well, Chiya-san, how are your studies going?
Good! Every day is so much fun!
I'm really good friends with everyone!
We all go eat together, and play
and practice in the field together,
and climb the roofs together, too!
And lately we've been scaring each other with
tests of courage and scary stories before we go to bed!
Eek, a ghost!
And lately we've been scaring each other with
tests of courage and scary stories before we go to bed!
That's part of your studies?
You really are a funny girl, Chiya-san.
Y-you think so?
It's made me want to know more about you.
Conversation is the best way to find out about a person,
but I want to know more about you like an Urara.
Would it be alright if I looked at you?
Crystal ball divining?!
We haven't learned that in class yet!
So we have a deal?
Oh, but I can't give you my hair, or nails, or teeth.
I could let you touch my belly, but that's it.
No need.
What is this...?
Now then, please hold this crystal ball and relax.
I'm going to begin.
Humbly, so humbly, we beseech of thee.
Immerse me into the reflecting pond of the soul.
Let the light pass through all in the deep.
Now, show me your all.
You grew up surrounded by nature,
and were loved by lots of animals.
Wow! How did you know?
My crystal ball shows me what I want to know.
It seems you've found something
precious to you in Meirocho.
I see three big lights shining brightly around you.
Three lights?
They're in the shape of a cat, a tanuki, and a fox.
How cute!
Those must be Koume, Nono, and Kon!
They're my friends at Natsumeya!
The cat is funny, bright, and a little bit of a tease.
Nyan!
Ponpoko!
The tanuki is quiet, but has a heart
that is kinder than anyone's.
Ponpoko!
The tanuki is quiet, but has a heart
that is kinder than anyone's.
The fox is serious and hard-working,
but she's cute and afraid of ghosts.
Kon!
The fox is serious and hard-working,
but she's cute and afraid of ghosts.
Wow, that's right!
I can see gentle lights surrounding you as well.
I got it, they're a sheep and a deer!
Mee!
Shika.
We're here, too!
We're weasels, by the way!
You've made a lot of close friends
since coming to Meirocho.
Yeah!
But something's missing.
Something very important...
You're looking for that very important something.
That's why you came to Meirocho.
Is that right?
That's what you were doing today.
You were wandering Bloque 10, looking for something,
and that's how you ended up so far away.
You were looking for...
Tokie-san, are you okay?!
Y-yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry, I must have made a mistake.
This has never happened to me before.
It was like I was rejected by some enormous power.
Chiya-san, what is it you're looking for?
I'm looking for my mom.
I don't know her name or what she looks like.
All I know is she's in Meirocho.
But I wanna find her so bad.
Sometimes I think that if she's somewhere in Meirocho,
then one day I might just bump into her,
and on some days, like today,
I can't just sit around doing nothing about it.
That's why when you saved me before,
I thought maybe you could be my mom.
Tokie-san, you're not my mom, right?
Sadly, I don't think I am.
Well, maybe you could be!
Maybe you forgot one baby after you gave birth to a lot!
I really don't think that's the case.
Oh...
I'm so stupid, of course it wouldn't go that well.
Chiya-san, your hair's coming undone.
Sit down, I'll fix it for you.
I'm sorry that I couldn't see it with my crystal ball.
It's okay. I just have to work real hard,
become a Rank 1 Urara, and get into Bloque 1!
Then I can find the legendary Rank 1 Urara
and ask her to show me where my mom is!
When I saw you, you were pure and strong.
Huh?
The strong resolve in your eyes will be an arrow
to point you in the right direction.
Chiya-san, you will be a wonderful Urara.
Perhaps this was fate after all.
I'll help you look for your mother as well.
Really?!
Yes. For some reason, I just can't let you be, Chiya-san.
I feel like I've just met an old friend.
Just now, I saw something for just the blink of an eye.
Pitch black, as if corrupted by a curse,
with red eyes that shone in the dark.
Just who is she?
We're finally back!
Tokie-san, thank you so much!
It's quite alright.
I was just about to drop in on Natsumeya myself.
Huh?
Chiya-chan!
Where were you? You've been gone all day!
Tokie-san, this is the cat and the tanuki!
What?
My, Chiya-chan, you're back...
T..Tokie-san?!
What's wrong, Nina-sensei...
M-Mother?!
"Mother"?!
What?! You're Kon's mom, Tokie-san?!
Thank you for helping Kon all this time.
Now that I think of it, she looks like Kon-chan.
But she doesn't have ears!
Note: In Japanese folklore, foxes are notorious shapeshifting tricksters.
Her parents must be good at disguising
themselves as humans, since they're foxes!
Quiet, everyone.
Urara Regulation Number 4: an Urara must maintain
a quiet and calm appearance at all times.
But, why are you here, Mother?
Right, I've got to tell you that.
It's important for all of you to hear,
so please listen carefully.
Today, I came to inform you of a terrifying prophecy.
Prophecy?
Mother, what do you mean "a terrifying prophecy"?
I saw it during my daily divinations.
A great disaster will befall Natsumeya.
It will happen at midnight tonight.
When the midnight bell stops chiming,
one of Natsumeya's stars will fade and die.
One of its stars?
Yes, a tragedy will befall someone in this room.
That person is...
Me?
No way, something's gonna happen to Nono?
However, if the three stars around
the light yellow-haired star sparkle together,
the fourth star will regain her light
if they shine upon one another.
Which means, if the four of you work together,
you can escape this impending disaster.
If we all...
...work together?
My, what a terrifying prophecy!
Nina-sensei?!
B-Big Sister!
I don't know what I'd do if something
happened to my cute little sister!
I-I leave it all in your hands, girls.
Please save Nono from this tragedy...
Faint.
Nina-sensei?!
Nina-sensei, stop fainting and help us!
Anyway, if your prophecy is true, Mother,
then we've got to do something!
Yes, that's correct.
I'll look for a way to avoid it as well.
But Nono-san's fate is in your hands.
Keep that in mind!
Right!
Leave it to us, Mother, we'll protect Nono!
In exchange...
Please take care of Nina-sensei!
I understand.
I know we said we'd help,
but what kind of disaster's gonna happen?
We're always fast asleep at midnight.
So, some dangerous happening
will occur when we're asleep.
Do you have any ideas, Nono?
Huh, uh, er, umm...
N-not too long ago, Koume-chan actually...
B-but seriously, if you think about it,
nothing can happen at Natsumeya if we just sit tight.
Right, right.
Oh, that doesn't mean we're guaranteed to be safe.
There could be a fire, or a robbery.
You're right! There could be an accident,
or a murderer, too.
Or the mushrooms in our miso soup
at dinner could be poisonous!
Right, so she could be poisoned to death!
Huh? I'm going to die?
N-no, jeez, of course not!
We're just coming up with examples!
Anyway, we don't know what kind of disaster's
gonna happen so we'll just leave it at that.
Just leave it to us!
We'll divine just what's going to happen to you, Nono!
Nono's eyes are dead!
I'll try asking a fox spirit!
Kokkuri-sama, Kokkuri-sama, please tell us
if you know what disaster will befall our friend.
FOUR
Death...
Note: The Japanese character for 4 can be read as "yon" or as "shi,"
the latter of which is a homonym for "death."
FOUR! It read "FOUR"!
It means all four of us should work hard! Yeah!
I-I'm gonna go with a plan to use charms
to keep her safe, no matter what happens!
Charms?
It's one way to ward off danger.
Remember, now!
Use all the knowledge you've gained thus far
to help our friend!
Nono! Put these on!
I don't think we need to use them all.
B-but...
Oh yeah, I know one!
A nandina bush charm!
What's that?
It's a story from when I was little.
The boars and the pigs were fighting a huge war.
A war? How?
They were destroying the mountain
and it was affecting all the other animals, too.
That's when Setsu helped.
This nandina bush can help one overcome any hardship.
If you take this branch and pray,
their fight will come to an end.
Then when I was offering the branch, they made up!
And now there are lots of little pig-boars!
Okay, that works way too well!
But if it might work, we've gotta try it.
Uhh...
I haven't found any nandina yet.
How about you guys?
I found some kumquats!
I dug up a ceramic relic!
Note: A snake-like being ranging from 30 - 80 centimeters in length.
I found a tsuchinoko!
How long have we been out here looking?
And the forest is really creepy in the middle of the night.
N-n-no, what is that, a ghost?!
I'm scared!
But...
I have a duty to save my friend!
I can't be afraid!
KON! I'm brave, I'm strong, this ain't scary at all!
All you ghosts and demons go away, away!
What is that creepy song?
Nono, are you okay?!
Y-yeah, I'm okay.
Chiya-chan, you're hurt here!
Oh, something got caught on me just now.
I-I'm sorry...
Nono! What's wrong?
Are you okay?
You guys...
You're getting so dirty, even getting hurt, all for me...
It's fine. Let's just go back to Natsumeya.
You can't give up, Nono!
That's right, Nono!
Keep it up and come sing with me!
Just pluck out your weak, timid heart!
Pluck it right out, yeah!
Seriously, what is with that song?!
But even if we keep looking...
You worry too much, Nono.
Times like these are when you should stick close to us.
Then whatever happens to you
will be split between the four of us.
Th-thanks...
But I don't want that.
Everyone's always protecting me.
I want to protect you, too!
So please, stay away from me!
Wait, Nono!
You can't, Nono!
We're not gonna let you be alone!
Chiya-chan!
The midnight bell.
It's time for the prophecy.
Huh?
Nothing happened.
Good work, everyone.
You certainly worked together to fight impending doom.
Tokie-san?
Congratulations.
You've all passed the preliminary
qualifying examination for Rank 9 Urara.
What?!
So wait, all the stuff about the prophecy
was a lie for this qualifying exam?
And Nina-sensei knew!
Yes.
Sorry to deceive you all.
The test is designed to see
how you will face a prophecy as an Urara.
I've been watching everything from the shadows.
But none of our tries at divining worked.
We couldn't even find a nandina bush.
An Urara's worth does not lie solely
in the success rate of her divining.
What is important is whether or not
she is sympathetic towards her fellow Urara.
The fear you endured and the strange song you
came up with to save your friend was truly wonderful.
Strange?!
Okay, don't you think those are
the wrong things to take out of that?
That's not all.
Your positive ideas,
your use of your knowledge,
your courage to help your friends,
your unwavering determination...
You all did wonderfully.
We-
Well, we passed!
Yay!
Don't celebrate just yet.
It's just the qualifying exam, after all.
You'll have to take the real test, where you'll compete
with the rest of the Rank 10 Urara from the teahouses.
You'll have to win against the other Urara
who passed the qualifying exam...
Make sure you're prepared for that.
Right!
We're not gonna lose!
Go Natsumeya!
Tokie-san, thank you so much for today.
Congratulations on their passing.
I knew the Natsumeya girls could do it.
Of course!
I'm so proud of my students.
It was a relief to see Kon having so much more fun
than when she was studying by herself.
I'm sure it's because she's made such great friends.
I agree!
They're all such good girls!
Still, I was so nervous!
I was afraid I was going to spill the beans
about the preliminary exam!
How was my acting?
A realistic performance, if I do say so myself!
Y-yes...
It's already time for the Rank 9 Urara exams.
It came so fast.
They're going to keep growing,
and one day graduate from Natsumeya.
It's our job to watch over them until then, Nina-san.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what kind of Urara they become.
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Four Girls and the Ranking Exam
are Sometimes a Trial"!
Koume-chan, there's something on your cheek.
I-it's definitely not a piece of red bean from the
Giant Sweet Plum Honey Dango Koume Special!
"Four Girls and the Ranking Exam
are Sometimes a Trial"