Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
Oh, come, come!
No!
You know what baobabs are a metaphor for, don't you?
I hope you do.
The prince needs to lean in and glance upwards, as though leading him on!
Like, "You know what I want, you tease! Come, come!"
One more time, let's go!
Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
Oh, come, come!
Come on, boys, do it right!
We are!
And you're going to finish in time?
Our class is riding on LitMus, you know!
Oh, are the costumes done?
Let me see!
Oh, wow!
The seams are, like, so neat!
Hey, like, would you mind, like...
Incoming Call
Hikky
Hello? What's wrong? Why the call?
You heard? Yukinoshita's out sick today.
Huh?
Looks like she caught a cold.
In this sunlight-filled room
hi no michiru kono heya
Quietly I'll wait for the time
sotto toki wo matsu yo
Before I knew it, I was looking down into the box
kidzukeba fukan de nagameteru hako
No one else saw it like me
onaji mesen wa naku
My heart had turned a cloudy white, completely opaque
itsu shika kokoro wa hakushoku futoumei
Even the light that fell on the snow scattered
yuki ni ochita hikari mo chiru
Cold raindrops keep falling from the clouds
kumo kara koboreru tsumetai ame
Only the distant spring winds can clear them from my eyes
me wo harasu no wa tooi harukaze dake
To a warm garden filled with azaleas you made bloom
azalea wo sakasete atatakai niwa made
Take me there, take me there, just kidding
tsuredashite tsuredashite nante ne
There are no fairy tales that are filled with only happiness
shiawase dake kaita otogibanashi nante nai
I know that, I know that, but still, you know
wakatteru wakatteru sore demo ne
I want to go there
soko he ikitai no
And So, the Curtain Rises on Each's Stage,
And the Festival Grows to a Feast on Us.
Holy crap.
Asleep?
I hope so.
But if she's so sick she can't get up...
Hello?
Yukinon? It's me, Yui!
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine, so...
"So."
"So," what?
"So, go home"? Is that it?
Shut up and open the door.
Why are you here?
We need to talk.
Welcome. Come in.
Have a seat.
What do we need to talk about?
Um... Well...
You were out sick, so I was hoping you were okay.
I was out for one day. You're overreacting.
But you look really tired.
Like, you look kind of pale.
I was somewhat tired, but not enough to be a problem.
But that's the problem.
You don't need to take on all the work yourself.
I know.
That's why I divided the tasks and reduced the load on my—
But not enough.
I'm kinda mad, okay?
I'm mad at you too, Hikky.
You said you'd save her if she was in trouble!
He has performed his duties as assistant historian.
That's sufficient.
But...
I'm fine.
We still have time.
I can work from home, so we're still on schedule.
You needn't be concerned, Yuigahama-san.
But that's just wrong.
Is it?
Relying on others.
Helping each other out.
Supporting one another is the right thing to do. Nothing could be more right.
I see.
But that's idealistic.
Someone always draws the short straw.
So I have no intention of telling you to rely on others.
But the way you're approaching this is wrong.
Then you know the right way to approach it?
Like hell I do.
But it's different from the way you've approached things thus far.
I'm sorry. I'll make some tea.
N-No, it's fine!
I'll make it!
Don't worry about my health.
I feel much better now.
As far as your health goes.
Yukinon, um...
Rely on me and Hikky.
Not on everyone, not on others.
Rely on us!
Hikky's—
Some black tea, perhaps?
Thanks, Yukinon.
Well, I'm going home.
M-Me too!
Yuigahama-san.
Yes?
It's difficult for me now,
but one day, I will rely on you.
So...
Thank you.
Yukinon...
But I need time to think.
Yuigahama, she's all yours.
Huh?
W-Wait!
They say the world changes when you change, but that's not true.
You simply give in to the lies they force on you and compromise.
Let me show you how to really change the world.
Oh, really?
Sagami-san, everyone's here.
Oh, okay!
Vice-Chair
Chair
Yukinoshita-san?
We will now begin the committee meeting.
Today's topic will be, as per
Shiromeguri-senpai's suggestion,
the cultural festival slogan.
Friendship, Effort, Victory
No, that's off.
Fun! Way too fun!
You can hear the sound of the sea breeze
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
That's off too.
Of One Mind
Wow. I think I know who wrote that.
Oh, I like this one!
"One for all."
I like these kinds of ideas.
Yeah, looks like you get it. Simple enough.
Huh?
Force one person to be the scapegoat and eliminate them.
"One for all." You do it often?
Hikigaya...
We thought up this last one.
Friendship
Helping one another:
a cultural festival
Ew.
Friendship
Helping one another:
a cultural festival
Excuse me, but is there a problem?
No, not really.
Sure you don't have a comment to make?
Oh, good. If you do, then come up with one yourself.
Then...
Man
Look closely
and one of them's slacking off:
a cultural festival
Man. ~Look closely and one of them's slacking off: a cultural festival~.
He's an idiot!
He's a total idiot!
That was awesome!
Shoot, it's too much!
My sides!
Haruno, stop laughing.
No, I mean, I think it's a great idea!
Yeah! It's funny! All good!
Hikigaya. Explain.
Well, you know how people say the character for "man" is an ideogram of people
supporting each other?
But one's leaning on top of the other.
I think the concept of "man" includes the assumption that one ends up a sacrifice.
So I'd say it's fitting for this cultural festival and the cultural festival committee.
What do you mean by "sacrifice," specifically?
Look at me, I'm totally a sacrifice here.
I've been forced to work like a slave.
Hell, people are shoving their own work on me.
Or maybe that's what the committee chair means by "helping one another"?
I've never been helped here, so I don't know what you mean.
Hikigaya-kun.
Rejected.
Sagami-san, let's end the meeting here.
We won't have any good suggestions.
Huh? But—
Wasting a day on this would be a foolish decision.
All committee members will think of slogans and present them tomorrow.
If all members work on all remaining days, we can recover the lost time.
Right?
Y-Yeah, right.
Okay, everyone. We'll be meeting again tomorrow.
Thanks for coming today!
What's up with him?
He just wants to slack off himself.
Are you sure?
About what?
You might want to resolve this misunderstanding.
It'll never get resolved.
They're already talking about it.
So the problem ends there.
You make excuses for the most worthless things,
but never make excuses when it's most necessary.
There's no point in making excuses.
Humans make decisions themselves when it's necessary.
Yes. You might be right.
Excuses are meaningless.
Perhaps I need to ask once more.
But more importantly, what was that slogan?
It was absolutely tasteless.
Better than yours, at least.
What are you, a thesaurus?
You're disappointingly unchanging.
Humans can't change that fast.
And you were strange from the start.
If you can't say something nice...
Sometimes, when I see you act,
I have the notion that perhaps attempting to force change would be foolish.
See you.
Yes. Good-bye.
See you tomorrow.
Conference Room
This will be the slogan for this year's cultural festival.
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
Sagami-san, we should advertise using this slogan immediately.
Oh, okay. Advertising, please.
All right, guys! Posters, on the double!
Vice-Chair, home page test update complete!
Understood.
Sagami-san, confirm.
Huh? Y-Yeah, okay.
Upload it to the main server.
Roger!
Hey there, working hard?
As you can see.
Doesn't look like you're working that hard.
Historian
Fuck you, I'm working my ass off!
I mean, you haven't put your own achievements in the record.
Time for a quiz!
What makes a group come together like nothing other?
A coldhearted tyrant?
Oh, come on. You know.
It's an enemy.
Well, the enemy here was kinda wimpy.
Oh, shut up.
But as long as you played the villain, you got a heroic response.
If the enemy slacks off, the group doesn't grow.
Conflict brings about the development of technology.
Wow, could you shut up?
Um...
Did you purposely make—
I don't like boys who can catch on.
Assistant, back to work.
Document that the slogan has been determined.
Also, the record of proceedings.
Inform all participants of the slogan as well.
Oh, and upload all group participation requests to the server as well.
Finish it all today.
Need me to help too?
You just get in the way. Go home.
How mean!
Yukino-chan, you're so mean!
Well, I'm bored, so I'll help out anyway.
We need to review the finances again. Could you do that?
Okay!
Now this is how you get work done!
I'm feeling so fulfilled right now!
Three minutes to curtains. Three minutes to curtains.
Yukinoshita to all hands.
We are proceeding on time.
Report any delays immediately.
Lights, all clear!
PA system, all clear!
Green room, cast preparations behind, but should complete before show time.
All hands, stand by for cue.
Ten seconds.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
Three.
Two.
One.
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
Are you ready to culture?!
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and...
...dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and...
...sing a song!
PA here. Cutting music momentarily.
Roger. Chairwoman Sagami, stand by.
And now, a word from the committee chairwoman!
Hi—
Okay, let's have a do-over!
Committee chairwoman, go ahead!
We're falling behind schedule.
Hang in there!
Hikigaya-kun, signal her to wrap it up.
I've been signalling.
She can't see it.
I see. Perhaps I chose the wrong position for you.
Is that a jab at my inability to stand out?
I never said that.
More importantly, where are you?
In the audience?
Hell, that's a freaking hook!
I am the cultural festival committee chair, Sagami Minami.
You can totally see me!
Um... Vice-Chair, all hands are online.
This year's slogan is Chiba's specialties: festivals and dancing.
We're proceeding according to schedule. All hands, prepare.
We're all fools, so let's dance and sing a song.
Chiba's specialties!
Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools,
so let's dance
Cultural
Festival
Soubu
High School
The Little Prince
I did not know how to understand anything!
I ought not to have listened to him.
He cast his fragrance and radiance over me.
You were too young to know how to love him.
What's up with that role?
She wanted me to play it?
Tonight—you know... do not come.
No, but why not?
I said, I shall not leave you.
Something's wrong here.
The lines from the book sound like slash fiction now.
It was wrong of you to come. You will suffer.
I shall not leave you!
Here it is! Let me go on by myself!
Blugha!
She's done for.
Better do something quick.
So you have chosen him over me.
But it is well.
I shall see you again soon.
Because...
When I drew the muzzle for the sheep,
I did not draw the leather strap.
Heh-heh. Sheep.
On Break
Reception
Nice work.
How was it?
Good, I'm guessing.
The customers enjoyed it.
On Break
Reception
Everyone worked really hard on it.
Yeah, I guess they all did.
I wasn't around, so I don't know.
The committee was crazy busy, so you couldn't really help, huh?
Hey, what the hell?
You're breaking my balls, man!
Let us in already!
What's wrong with you?
How long you gonna keep us waiting?!
That doesn't look good.
It's going to get out of hand at this rate.
All right, everyone. Let's roll.
Please form two lines here.
The back of the line is over here!
Back of Line
Is the 2-E representative here?
Yukinon's so cool.
She's looking a lot better now.
Guess so.
Hey, mind if I ask something?
Huh? What?
Did you talk about anything when you were at Yukinoshita's place?
Not a thing.
After you went home, we were hungry, so we ate dinner together,
we watched some TV,
and I went home.
So she didn't tell me anything you want to know about.
Reception
Hey, there isn't anything I want to know about.
Really?
Reception
I wanted to know.
I've decided to wait for Yukinon.
Reception
I think Yukinon's trying her best to approach us and talk about it.
So I'll wait.
But I won't wait for someone who won't try even if you wait.
Huh?
Well, if they aren't trying, there's no point waiting—
No.
I won't wait and do it myself.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Really.
Oh, right!
You haven't had lunch, right?
Here! Honey toast!
Wow.
It's not that rare, is it?
Hm?
Hold on, this is actually bread.
Shouldn't you try to make it look not like bread?
It's all bread here.
Totally bread.
On Break
Yum!
The bread's hard.
The honey hasn't soaked into it.
And it's all chewy.
What'd I do to deserve this?
Whipped cream's so yummy!
Then did it have to be honey toast?
And you took that cream from my half!
Well, I guess it's good.
I'm so full!
Reception
Oh, right. How much was it?
It's okay, it wasn't much!
Hey, it doesn't work like that.
I said, it's fine.
While I enjoy the idea of being supported,
I have no intention of accepting charity.
What's with that messed up policy?
Fine. You're taking me out for honey toast sometime.
At Pasela.
You're choosing the place?
Does that mean... uh...
Oh.
Hey, can I treat you to something else instead?
Yeah, sure!
When are we doing it?
Uh...
Sorry.
Could you give me time to think?
Reception
Shining in the big blue sky
An airplane, flying to somewhere so far away
air
plane
plane
Something I held in my heart
Started to fall apart
I held in the feelings I wanted to tell you
And turned them into words I couldn't say
I had to be so stubborn
Right until the end
I took the string that tied us together
I tangled it up
And I cut it off
Before the plane trails spread into wind
And they completely disappeared
If I could've said I wanted to see you
Maybe I could've escaped from this
Sadness that will never end
Maybe I'd be alone again with you
Hello Hello, Alone
hel
lo
a
lone
hel
lo
a
lone
mitsumeru tabi doki doki shiteru
Each time I see you, my heart beats faster
kimi ni motto chikadzukitai yo
I want to get closer to you
amai yokan tokechau mae ni
Before the sweet dream melts away
kidzuite ne tokubetsu ni naritai
Notice my feelings, I want to be special to you
Next time:
And So, His and Her and Her Youths
Continue Being Wrong.
And So, His and Her and Her Youths Continue Being Wrong.