At the end of the short cherry blossom season,
the rain that had washed away the flowers was clearing up.
How are you feeling, Lily?
This is Cabbage's room.
He's gone off for his wrestling job,
so take some time off and think about the future.
It's not like I can do anything.
I'm just a poor prostitute.
I can't do anything!
This isn't like you, Lily.
Don't give up like that.
You've been fighting on your own your entire life.
We'll help you,
so... don't just give up.
You, Noboru...
How can you be so concerned about other people?
We take after Bro.
Bro?
Oh, that man the MP's shot...
Bro's teachings are in our hearts.
We owe you anyway.
Odd, Turtle's still not here.
He said he was gonna come around in the morning.
I never knew Turtle lived here.
Noboru never told you guys, huh?
Turtle!
Hey, Turtle, I know you're in there!
I'm coming in.
Hey, Turtle!
Noboru!
Turtle?
What's wrong, Noboru?
Say something!
Lily, I'll take him to the hospital.
A cold?
Yes.
He was having difficulty breathing due to his fever,
but I gave him something for his temperature, so he should be fine now.
Let's play it safe, though, and keep him here for a few days.
You can go now.
Do you still need something?
Is it really... just a cold?
What do you mean?
Isn't there something else?
Goodness, don't worry me like that.
Sorry.
I'll be back on my feet once I eat something tasty.
Very well, then.
I'll cut up an apple for you right now.
I hope you feel honored.
Well, thank you very much.
I see.
We can't do a thorough check up in such a small hospital.
I can't be really sure unless
he's examined at a larger place.
This tastes great!
Of course it does.
Hey, Lily...
Have you thought about what you should do?
Feeling blue isn't going to get me anywhere.
I'm just back to square one, that's all.
It's not too bad if I put it that way.
I've been working my way up with this body...
all by myself.
So I'll be just fine.
What were you going to do with the money you secretly took from the general?
Well, it wasn't for anything grand.
I thought I'd start my own little store.
My very own castle, and a life independent of men.
It was just a small dream.
How much?
How much would it take...
for your little dream?
What are you saying?
You're just a kid!
What's wrong, Mario?
You don't look so good.
Does Turtle... really have just a cold?
Well, isn't that what the doctor said?
Mario, what are you implying?
Is there something about Noboru I don't know?
He...
survived an atomic bomb.
So this could be an after effect of the explosion?
I don't know.
But... he needs to be examined at a bigger hospital.
I don't have the money or the connections to get him admitted.
Hey, tell me, Lily.
What can I do?
Mario...
I can't... do anything for Turtle.
I'm so pathetic.
"No one cares for his friends like Turtle does."
"His kindness comes from the unmatched horrors of his past."
Mario felt frustrated that he was unable to help...
and that an unknown threat...
was making him powerless.
Good morning, Mr. Maeda.
I've come to take your temperature.
Lily.
What brings you here so early in the morning?
You want to take Noboru to a bigger hospital, right?
Come with me.
Lily, why are we at the U.S. base?
I thought we were going to a hospital.
Mario, America built the atomic bombs.
Right...
And they're also the ones with the latest medical technology.
This is the best place to get Noboru checked out.
Sign: Cafe Mironga
That's 100,000 yen.
It's my entire life's saving.
I'll give my body and the money as collateral.
You can do whatever you want with me, including slave labor.
So please, please, lend me some money!
How much?
300,000 yen.
I can only lend up to 3,000 yen.
There are no exceptions.
Then will you give me permission to start a business like yours with my 100,000 yen?
You want to start a One Percent Loan?
If I lend out 100,000 yen, I'll get 1,000 yen in interest every day.
That's 30,000 yen in a month, and in two months, 130,000 yen will become 169,000.
You're free to start any business you wish.
Then...
I have no reason to stop you, so do as you like.
Thank you very much!
However...
I'd like you to tag along with me for a bit.
I want to teach you something.
Man, why are we at a public bath?
Stop complaining and get over here.
It's no sin to wash an old man's back.
Lily, who are they?
They used to serve under my patron.
Don't fuck with me!
Lily!
Let me go!
I'm gonna teach them a lesson!
Just give up.
They won't listen to anything we say.
Let's go, Lily.
Let me go, Mario!
Let me go!
Lily, let's find a different way.
How do you know my name?
You're that boxer...
Oh, from that match!
He says he'll ask them to take a look at Turtle.
Seriously?
That'd be great!
Lily, did he say he wants to box with me?
Yeah, he said that's the condition.
Sure.
But it's now or never.
Mario... but you...
Mario, stop!
This is great.
They'll examine him tomorrow.
Really?
We have to go tell him right away.
Thank you.
We're greatly obliged.
Thanks, Jeffrey.
People smile when they borrow money,
but their smiles become frowns when they return it.
When people borrow money, they thank you endlessly,
but when they have to return it,
they glare at you like you're a demon.
Will you wash my back?
I got that scar right when I started the business.
This scar, and this scar...
All the scars you see...
are from people to whom I've lent money...
in the ten years that I've been running this business.
If you lend money to the wrong person,
you'll lose your life as well as your money.
Do you still want to start a moneylending business?
Yes.
"Mr. Sugi used his own scars to show me the dark side of the business."
"In this world, not everyone returns favors gratefully."
"This isn't a business for an ordinary person."
"It's a business for someone reckless, like me."
Turtle thought to himself,
"How many 'medals' will end up on my body?"
Back at the café, you said you'd give your body as collateral.
Were you serious?
I was.
Then I'm going to ask you for a little favor.
Can you get this man to repay his debt?
His debt?
If all goes well, I'll lend you 300,000 yen.
Really?
However, if you aren't careful,
you'll end up with as many scars as me.
Are you still willing to go?
Sign: Setagaya, Block 4, 3rd District of Mishuku, Corp Nishimura Room 205
Mr. Sugi...
get that 300,000 yen ready for my return.
May I ask you a question?
Why do you need such a large sum of money?
Women? Family?
That's definitely it.
Yeah!
For my family!
He escaped?
When we checked on him this morning, he was gone.
What in the world is he doing in his condition?
That idiot...
Let's look for him, Mario.
Mr. Igarashi!
I know you're in there, Mr. Igarashi!
What the fuck do you want?
I'll kill you if you're trying to rob me!
Who the hell are you?
I'm here from Mr. Sugi.
Sugi?
Oh, that old moneylending guy.
Hey, hurry up!
I know!
Lily, this isn't just for you.
It's my chance to take a step forward.
"If I just sit around, nothing will change."
"I need to use my mind and body to take a first step."
"If I don't find happiness, my life has no meaning."
Bro's teachings gave Turtle a push forward.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Feelings intertwine.
Lily feels kindness for the first time,
and she makes a choice.