[HOHENHEIM BREATHES HEAVILY]
Just calm down.
We need to have a civil
conversation about this.
Please.... Give me
a chance to talk to you.
And then I'll listen to
everything you have to say...
Of course... I promise.
We're all in this... together.
[HOHENHEIM GRUNTS]
[WIND BLOWS HEAVILY]
[MERCHANT 1]
He's got blonde hair.
He must be from the west.
Oh Well.
I guess we should at least
take the time to bury him.
[HOHENHEIM GRUNTS]
Wait, he's still alive!
[MERCHANT 2]
Impossible!
[MERCHANT 1]
Just hang on!
[MERCHANT 2]
Hey! Are you alright?
Water! Get him some water!
Just drink it nice and slow.
Only take little sips.
Can you understand us?
We're traveling
merchants from Xing.
[MERCHANT 1]
What were you doing
out here in the desert?
[HOHENHEIM]
I've got no place to go.
No place to return.
I had to get as far from Xerxes
as I could... Too scared.
I know you are.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't stop him.
I'm so sorry, Sergence.
[EXPLOSION AND GUNFIRE]
[HOHENHEIM]
There was Sergence,
the renowned master carpenter.
He was often called to
the palace for repairs.
Do you remember him?
His son, Dzur, had a deep
admiration for his father.
He worked hard to
follow in his footsteps.
And then there's
the florist, Kaya...
I've rarely met such
a compassionate woman.
Sari, the stable hand, could
never get his fill of liquor.
Trust me, I've had
to drink for him.
Tami's boyhood dream was to
become a respected scholar.
Gidarouche worked as a cook.
He was fired one time for
feeding a starving vagrant
without charging him.
And my fellow slave, Andal...
He bitterly
considered me his rival
because I was
favored by our master.
Suhl was somewhat of
a remorseless reprobate...
He was awaiting execution.
He was probably
the most determined
to get one last shot at you.
And just how would
he go about that?
Every single one of
these tortured souls
has now invaded your being.
[HEARTBEAT]
You're contaminated...
And each soul inside you
is working with me.
Working to see
your destruction.
I'm supposed
to believe that
your Philosopher's Stone
has individual wills?
Those souls were
reduced to mere energy.
[HOHENHEIM]
I'm not surprised
you'd find it impossible.
I was convinced I'd be driven
mad trying to individually
sort out the ocean of
screaming voices within me.
But I had plenty
of time to converse
with each and
every one of them...
That was one of
the few benefits
of this undying body
you gave to me.
You actually
spoke with them?
[HOHENHEIM]
That's right...
Unlike you, I listened
to what they had to say.
It took time...
But I managed to learn
the name of every last soul.
Five hundred thirty six thousand
three hundred twenty nine...
The people you
trapped inside of me.
[FATHER GRUNTS]
[FATHER]
Why you...
[FATHER GRUNTS]
[HOHENHEIM]
Return to the nothing
you were born of.
Your flask is broken, dwarf.
We will destroy you.
And that container of
yours is the first to go.
[FATHER YELLS]
All we have to do is tear
through that leather bag
you designed to look like me...
And you'll be reduced to dust.
You will suffer the pain
of the thousands of
lives you've ruined.
[HOHENHEIM GASPS]
[FATHER GROWLS]
You've picked up the bad
habit of condescension
in your many years.
Haven't you, Hohenheim?
How's it possible you can
live without your skin?
Did you honestly believe
you're the only one
capable of evolving?
[HOHENHEIM GASPS]
I told you that I intend on
becoming the perfect being.
[HOHENHEIM GRUNTS]
[BUCCANEER]
Are you serious?!
He's storming the front?!
Do they really expect me to make
a complete mockery of myself
by entering through the
backdoor of my own palace?
Infantrymen, keep back!
[GUNFIRE]
[BULLETS RICOCHET]
Wha...?!
Impossible!
[TANK FIRES]
[SOLDIERS YELL]
[EXPLOSION]
[TANK OPERATOR 1 YELLS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[SOLDIERS YELL]
[GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
Did we hit him?
[TANK OPERATOR 1 YELLS]
[TANK OPERATOR 2 SCREAMS]
[TANK OPERATOR 3]
Take over the controls!
Uh, yes, sir!
Damn!... Where is he?!
[TANK OPERATOR 3 YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
I don't believe it.
The old bastard
just took out a tank.
[BUCCANEER YELLS]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 5] Captain!
[BUCCANEER SCREAMS]
No, Captain Buccaneer! Ah...!
What's the issue here?
Your country's leader
has returned.
Now open the gate for me.
I said open the gate,
Lieutenant Falman.
[FALMAN CRIES]
[FALMAN]
Please forgive me,
Colonel Mustang...
but it... looks like
I'm dying here.
[BUCCANEER]
That's enough of that...
Ya can't die a heroic death
crying like a coward.
[BUCCANEER GRUNTS]
Don't even think
for a second
you're gonna die a more
manly death than I am.
I've got plenty of
fight left in me.
[BRADLEY]
How ridiculous.
Humans always make a point
of being foolishly stubborn.
[GREED]
Ahh... You got that right.
They always get so frantic
in the heat of the moment...
Heh... Like it's
gonna do them any good.
But, pathetic as it may be...
And they sure are...
I still prefer to
side with the underdog.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[GUNFIRE]
Damn it!
It seems like these guys
got their second wind
as soon as the
Fuhrer showed up.
If they get past us, then
they'll take the main gate!
We can't let them
through, no matter what!
[EXPLOSIONS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[PRODUCER]
Go on... Yes?!
Well that's incredible news!
I just got a phone call that
your husband is alright!
The Fuhrer is alive!
[BRADLEY'S WIFE CRIES JOYFULLY]
[BRADLEY'S WIFE]
Oh, thank you.
[BROADCASTER]
Are you okay?
Yes... I'm just
so overjoyed.
Oh, thank goodness...
I was so scared
that he was dead.
He's not badly
injured, is he?
They haven't informed us yet.
[PRODUCER]
We've only been told
that he's in combat
with the Briggs soldiers
at Central Command.
We'll have to
pin this on Briggs.
We what?
We have to
protect the Colonel.
It's a relief to hear
his Excellency is okay.
Yes... I just pray that
Selim is safe as well.
If the Fuhrer is battling
soldiers from Briggs,
that leads me to believe General
Armstrong is leading the coup.
Wait,
General Armstrong?
Ahhh...
She was recently transferred
to Central, wasn't she?
[BREDA]
The question remains,
how much of the senior staff
is in league with her?
So he's alive...
I guess that's what should
be expected of a Homunculus.
We should've known that
publicly siding with Fuhrer
Bradley could backfire on us.
It just
feels so wrong...
...having to blame
General Armstrong.
It looks like they've got us
completely surrounded, too.
So I've noticed.
What do you think
they'll do to us?
I don't know.
Right now...
The whole city thinks
we're on the Fuhrer's side.
So we've
at least made it
difficult for them to
attack us outright.
But it won't take too long
for Bradley to call our bluff.
When that happens, they'll
probably kill us right away.
Wait, even with
his wife here?
I honestly doubt that he has
any real attachment to her.
Long time no see, Greed...
If you had any sense at all
you would've stayed out
of my sight for good.
Yeah, my avarice tends
to make these decisions for me.
And right now,
I want your life.
Wrath.
[SOLDIERS GASP]
[GREED LAUGHS]
Who's this guy?
Our backup?
[GREED]
Rumor has it that
you died a fiery death
in a train accident.
You look unscathed to me.
Let's just say that
I have sharp eyes.
[EXPLOSION]
[BRADLEY]
It only took a moment
for me to evaluate
a path among
the falling rubble.
The rest of it was just
a matter of foot work.
However, the years
do take their toll.
The whole ordeal left me
with a few aches and pains.
[GREED THINKING]
He's griping about being old
and he's capable of this?
[FALMAN]
You're Ling Yao... Right?
Heyyyy! I haven't
seen you since
we hid out in that
crummy apartment.
It's good to see you,
Warrant Officer.
It's Lieutenant!
Oh, whatever. I owe you one,
so I'll give you a hand...
And I've got a score to settle.
Ha! The truth is...
we both got a grudge to settle
with this self-righteous,
old bastard. Come on!
[GREED YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
Heh...
[BRADLEY]
Trying to hide in
my blind spot, huh?
Ha... I'm surprised that
I didn't think of it,
but the Prince gave me
a few good pointers
on how to fight you.
How helpful.
Unfortunately for you...
[GREED GRUNTS]
He's gaining
the upper hand!
This is starting
to look bad.
[GREED GRUNTS]
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 10]
Fire!... Open fire!
[GUNFIRE]
Dammit! Stay out of this!
[SWORD SLASH]
No! Son of a bitch!
[BUCCANEER YELLS]
[FALMAN] Captain!
Hmm...?
[BUCCANEER SCREAMS]
[BUCCANEER LAUGHS]
You've got some rather
impressive abs, huh.
Heh. Now what are you gonna do
without your fancy sword play?
[GREED]
Are you tryin' to
get killed, dumbass?!
Then again...
I appreciate the help!
[BRADLEY]
Now... let's see.
[GREED GRUNTS]
Not exactly my
weapon of choice,
but I guess that I'll
just have to make do.
You've pissed me
off now, old man.
[GREED YELLS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
I was told
the Fuhrer has returned?
Affirmative.
He's currently
engaged in combat with
an unidentified man, sir.
Send in all
available forces.
We'll wipe out these
worthless Briggs traitors
and then we'll
rescue the Fuhrer.
Call in the reinforcements.
We're retaking the main gate!
[SEARGENT] Yes, sir!
Go, go,
go, go, go!
[FALMAN]
Oh, no!
They're sending another
battalion up the shaft!
[GREED GRUNTS]
[GREED YELLS]
[GREED]
Sorry... but I'm kind of
busy if you haven't noticed.
You're gonna have
to deal with it.
I am?!... But we've hardly
got any men left here,
what the hell am
I supposed to do?!
[GREED GRUNTS]
Just figure it out!
That's easier said than done.
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 10]
Captain! Hang in there!
I guess it
really is up to me.
Hey! You men get
Captain Buccaneer
someplace safe
on the double!
Right! Yes, sir!
Grab that gun,
we're moving it!
Yes, sir!
[GUNFIRE]
[SOLDIERS SCREAM]
Damn it! Those
bastards have only got
two machine guns up there
and we're completely pinned!
They've got us
trapped in here!
[GAMELAN]
Do we have any men
inside we can call?
Have them force open
the gate from their end.
Sir!
This is the third
Sovereign Battalion speaking...
Come in Central Command
Garrison! Do you read me?
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 11]
This is Central
Command Garrison!
Do not enter the base!
What?
I don't understand...
[GAMELAN]
Give it to me.
This is Commander
Gamelan speaking...
Our men are stationed
at the main gate...
Is it possible for
you to open the gate
from within the fortress?
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 11]
Negative, sir...
The base has been overrun
by some kind of monsters.
[GAMELAN]
Did you say monsters?
What are you talking about?
[EXPLOSION]
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
[GAMELAN COUGHS]
[GAMELAN] What is that?!
What the hell's going on?
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 12]
Wait. I think I see something.
[CENTRAL SOLDIER 12 YELLS]
[THUD]
[SOLDIERS SCREAM]
Whatever's going on down there
doesn't sound too good.
Ah...!
[GUNFIRE]
[METAL CLANGS]
Ahh!
[BRIGGS SOLDIER 11 YELLS]
Ahh...!
[GREED]
Heh... Nice moves, old man.
And thanks for the help...
You really saved my ass.
I wasn't trying to
save your ass...
I was saving the body
of the young lord.
Well it's
the same ass...
Your sickening chi is radiating
from the Prince's body.
Although... it did actually
help me to locate you.
So... Why don't you tell me
who this is we're fighting...
Especially since neither of us
could leave a scratch on him.
That's Fuhrer
King Bradley, old man.
[FU GASPS]
Wellll...
This is the first time
I've actually laid eyes on him.
So now I know...
...what the bastard who took my
granddaughter's arm looks like!
[NARRATOR]
A man must come to know his
enemy as clearly as he knows
his own self in order to
see his victory in battle.
And while their two
lives may end as one,
he will not die for nothing.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood,
Episode 57: Eternal Leave.
Farewell, my powerful master.
I promise to eternally watch
over you from the other side.