Summertime. It is summertime
at Fumizuki Academy, too.
It is also a season of splashing
water glistening in the sun.
And of splashing nose blood, as well.
Hottoite sodatsu mono nanda nandarou
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
Deai mashite wa kantan sugiruyo
Saisho ni kimeta kotae wa hitotsu
Tokimeki mashita goukaku shimasuka?
Koi mo shoubu mo awatenai
Kotsu kotsu kotsu to tetsuya ni tameiki
Watashi no naka ni tensai dreamer
Omou koto mina kanaeba iina
Hito no sekai wa kinishinai
Perfect-area complete!
Zettai koko de matterunda
Perfect-area nozomu koe ga kikoeruyo
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? Tomaranai surechigai
Watashi ga soudan aite nara
"Tomodachi kai?" "Tomodachi desu."
Kanashiki rei ten dane
No! Yarinaoshi kakinaoshi
Honki de one more chance please
Ima yori suteki na mirai ga arunoni
Ima yori suteki ni my life, my life, my life!
"Episode 6"
"Me, Pools, and Swimsuit Paradises... and..."
Oh yeah, Yuuji.
Hm?
The gas has been cut off,
so there's no hot water.
You should've told me sooner!
Sorry. Pour water on your arms and
legs, which are far from your heart, first
and then gradually move closer to...
I didn't mean how to take a cold shower!
What are you so worked up about?
Oh yeah, take a cold
shower to cool your head.
That's why I'm worked up, you idiot!
Geez... The gas has been
cut off. There's nothing to eat...
How can you live like this?
Don't be rude. It's not like I have nothing.
I have things I can get calories from.
I'm not interested in drinking
vegetable oil. Your fridge is empty, too.
Don't be rude. It's not empty.
Forget it. Just cool your head with this.
So, Yuuji, what're you gonna have?
Coke, coffee, hot ramen
and chilled ramen noodles.
You jerk! So all you're gonna give me
to eat are the disposable chopsticks?!
You're gonna eat chopsticks?!
It's closer to food than a plastic bag,
which is an inorganic substance.
I'm not gonna give you chopsticks...
...then I'd have to eat ramen with my fingers.
I didn't forget to buy something for you, too.
Diet coke, konjac jelly, and jellied agar.
They've all got zero calories!
I'm being considerate so that
you won't get metabolic syndrome.
And which part of my diet could cause that?!
You've been consuming
mainly sugar and oil, right?
Those are the only things
I've been consuming! I'm so ticked now!
What? Do you wanna fight?
Yeah... I've been thinking
about settling things with you.
Fine. That's just what I want.
My eyes... hurt!
You're not bad...
Neither are you.
But... I'm done fooling around.
I won't hold back!
This battle is too unproductive.
Yeah...
Oh no... It's sticky. I'd better take a shower.
Yuuji, you can go first.
I don't wanna take a shower here!
Then what're you gonna do?
I'm going somewhere where they have hot water.
I see. So you snuck in here
without permission and took a shower.
And while you were at it, you
went swimming in your underwear?
Do you have any excuse?
It was his fault.
It was your fault because
you didn't bring any decent food!
No, it's because you didn't pay your gas bill!
It's better than no water!
You sometimes even get your water stopped?!
Enough... I got it.
Right? It's not my fault, right?
I got that your idiocy knows no bounds!
As punishment, clean the
pool next weekend! Both of you!
Yes sir...
That sounds awful.
To think that we have to clean
such a big pool... How depressing.
Don't be so bummed. In return,
we've got permission to use the pool freely.
Muttsulini, do you wanna come help us?
I'll pass.
By the way, I'm going to
ask Himeji and Shimada as well.
Have a brush and cleanser ready for me.
That sounds fun. I'll help
out too, so may I join you?
Of course!
Hey, what're you guys talking about?
Sounds like something fun.
We can use the pool by ourselves on the weekend.
Do you guys wanna join us?
What?!
Pool... We'll be in swimsuits, right?
Pool... We'll be in swimsuits...
"Akihisa's Vision"
By the way,
--How's this?
--Hideyoshi will come to show his swimsuit to Akihisa.
Th-That's dirty, Kinoshita! Just
because you're confident about yourself...!
She's right! That's not fair, Kinoshita!!
What're you two talking about?
So, what do you wanna do?
--I-I'm coming!
--I'm coming!
I'm gonna prepare things...
Y-Yes, preparation is important, isn't it?
I have to eat less to lose some weight.
Okay. So all I need to do
now is ask Shouko, huh?
Kirishima? I see... You've become mature, Yuuji.
Akihisa... If she finds it out later,
what do you think will happen to my life?
I'm sorry.
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning, Yoshii. Good thing
we have such nice weather today.
I got a new swimsuit for today.
Whoa...!
What?! What kind?!
Trunks type.
That's a men's swimsuit.
I'm disappointed in you.
You're mean, Hideyoshi!
Don't you like me anymore?!
Why am I being blamed?!
Stupid Big Brother! Good morning!
Hazuki?!
She wanted to come and
wouldn't take no for an answer, so...
So everyone's here?
Well then, change into your
swimsuits and we'll meet up poolside.
Okay!
Hey, hey. This way is the guys' changing room.
You and Hideyoshi have to go that way.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not kidding, though.
Now, stop fooling around.
Let's go, Hazuki! Kinoshita!
You, too?! No! I don't wanna be alone
with the girls in the girls' changing room!
If you take off your
clothes in front of Yuuji...
Why should that be a problem?!
Don't worry, Hideyoshi. See?
"Boys' Changing Room"
"Girls' Changing Room"
"Hideyoshi's Changing Room"
So "Hideyoshi" is a gender?
Big Brothers! Thanks for waiting!
Ah, Hazu...ki?!
"Shimada"
I-Isn't that a crime?
I want a lawyer.
Don't lose your head over an
elementary school kid's swimsuit!
Hey, Hazuki! Give that back to me!
If I don't use it, my bikini top is...
Huh?
Oh, it slipped out.
Don't play with this!
It was expensive, you know!
Is that what you call... NuBra?!
Forget it! Forget everything you just saw!
I wanna forget! I wanna forget!
--Almost... Almost...
--I wanna forget everything!
S-Someone, take a picture...
When I went through the
trouble to get them... Stupid Hazuki...
What're you looking at?
Does something look funny?
No. You really look good in it.
Really?
Yeah, your breasts, your bust,
and your boobs are slim and...
my big toe is...!
Didn't you just say my
breasts are small three times?!
Well, don't get so upset.
He talks that way, but he's really
checking you out in your swimsuit.
Gee, Aki...
You should be honest and
say what you think, you know.
Then...
Your breasts are small, aren't they?
I'm gonna poke your eyes!
Ahh! My eyes! My eyes...!
Yuuji. Don't look at other girls.
Big Sister, you're pretty.
That... makes me happy.
Now, Yuuji, there's something
you wanna tell Kirishima too, right?
Shouko...
Hm?
Give me a Kleenex. My tears won't stop.
You should tell her how you
think she looks in a swimsuit.
What am I supposed to say when I can't see?!
Geez... What're we gonna
do with Yuuji huh, Muttsulini?
Oh?
Muttsulini?!
Sorry... I'm gonna leave
this world ahead of you.
Dammit! Who did this?!
Who did this to Muttsulini?!
I'm sorry! It took me a while
to tie the strings on my back!
Ah! This is too good!
Is this... a biological weapon...?
Yoshii! What's the matter?!
Huh?
Worauf für einem Standard
hat Gott jene unterschieden,
--Minami, what's the matter?
--die haben, und jene, die nicht haben?
--When she gets shocked, she sometimes goes back to speaking German.
--Was war für mich ungenügend!
What? What's going on?
You can't look at her.
Is this everyone?
No. I don't think Hideyoshi is here yet.
I wonder what kind of swimsuit it is.
A pair of trunks.
That's right...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
"Dried Up"
Blood no longer comes out from my nose.
It dried up.
Is everyone here?
Kinoshita, just how hard do
you want to make things for us?!
You're playing dirty!
To think you brought our guard
down and betrayed us at the end!
Big Sister, you look very cute.
As you can see, I'm a guy.
But that swimsuit is for girls.
What?! I told the store person
that I wanted regular trunks!
Unless they know you, they'd
naturally recommend girl's clothes.
Yuuji... are your eyes okay?
Yeah, don't worry. They gradually starte--
--There're too many things that I can't let Yuuji see here.
--Kill me already! Just kill me! Now!
Idiot Test
There!
Shouko...? Sh-Shouko?
You're good at swimming, Yoshii.
Aren't you swimming, Himeji?
To tell you the truth, I can't
swim at all. All I can do is float.
Do you want me to teach
you how? I'm good at swimming.
--Really?! Thank you very much!
--A-ranked Himeji usually helps F-ranked Minami study but today...
It's like Minami is A and Himeji is F, right?
"Akihisa"
If I squeeze them together and
lift them, I'm sure it's at least B!
By the way, Yuuji, I'm C ranked.
What're you saying?
Big Brother!
Hm?
Let's play underwater demon!
Underwater demon? Is that underwater tag?
No. In underwater demon,
the demon chases after the others.
When he drags someone in the
water and drowns them, he wins.
That's a demon! That's really a demon!
But Hazuki, that's dangerous,
so you shouldn't play it, okay?
Oh... I shouldn't?
Just watch. Kirishima!
What is it?
I want you to play underwater
demon with Yuuji. The rules are simple.
You drag Yuuji into the water.
When he drowns, you perform CPR on him.
That'll make you a winner.
What the...?! Someone! Hel...
See? It's dangerous, right?
Hmm... Yeah.
Was it you?!
Yuuji, you're stubborn.
Let me go! What do you have against me?!
Oh? Rep?
Aiko?
You're Kudou from Class A...
What're you doing here?
I'm a swimming club member, so...
The other members are here, too.
Honey!
Why did you come to play at
the pool without telling me?!
Why are you here?!
I have a special information network
in order to protect you from pests, so...!
Well then, I'll go change into a swimsuit, too.
Hey, if you're gonna
take a peek, do it unnoticed.
What...?! This means
she's given an official approval.
Then, as a man, I must go.
Yoshii, if you do something you
shouldn't, you'll be in big trouble.
Don't you wanna go home alive, Aki?
What's this vicious mood?
I guess I can't help it. I'll just
place my hopes on Muttsulini's camera.
Dammit!
Ahh... Swimming sure is making me hungry.
Then, I've got something good.
I made a little mistake and
couldn't make enough for everyone,
so I didn't say anything.
To tell you the truth,
I made three waffles this morning.
The First...
Fastest Swimmer Championship Match!
Do-or-die Swimming Contest!
Yaay!
The rules are simple.
The first one to reach the goal
after making a lap is the winner!
Himeji made three murderous
waffles. There are four members.
Which means only the winner can
escape from eating it and survive.
Okay, are you ready? On your mark!
Muttsulini is weak because he bled.
It's hard to think that I'd lose
against Hideyoshi in physical strength.
Set!
Which means...
I've got only one enemy.
Start!
Drop dead!
You're playing dirty!
I'll throw those words right back at you!
Not bad, Akihisa.
You'll have to do more than this to beat me!
You can fight as much as you like,
but the first one is at the turn.
What?
This is bad! As it stands, I'll lose!
Not so fast! I'll stop Muttsulini!
You go stop Hideyoshi!
Okay!
Hideyoshi! I won't let you pass through here!
What?
Oh?
What's this?
Aki!
Yoshii! What're you doing?!
What am I doing?
This..
Could this be, by any chance, Hideyoshi's...
Wh-What?
Yoshii!
Aki!
Kinoshita! Hide your chest quick!
Why? I'm a guy.
I'm a goner, but I have no regrets.
It looks like cleaning will be a lot of work.
That was fun.
Yeah.
But I kinda feel really exhausted, though.
Isn't it anemia rather than exhaustion?
Well... then shall we take
a bath before we go home?
Okay!
"Women's Bath"            "Men's Bath"
Hey, hey. This way is the men's bath.
You and Hideyoshi have to go that way.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not kidding, though.
Now, stop fooling around.
Let's go, Hazuki! Kinoshita!
Again?! Again?!
I don't wanna be alone with
the girls in the women's bath!
Don't worry, Hideyoshi. See?
"Men's Bath"
"Women's Bath"
"Hideyoshi's Bath"
So it's acknowledged by society.
Ahh... this feels good.
It warms you up, doesn't it?
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
The other side is the women's bath.
What?!
--Hey! What're you doing?
--Legal. Legal.
Honey! Let's wash each other! In the
bath, no matter what happens, it's legal.
"No matter what happens"?!
What're you gonna do?!
"Combat Power"
Ah, uhm... There's nothing
good about them being big.
It's tough because they
give you stiff shoulders.
That's what everyone with huge boobs says!
Akihisa, give me the shampoo!
Here.
This is the soap I bought, isn't it?
This creates bubbles, so I thought
we didn't need to buy shampoo.
I was stupid to ask you to get it.
Hey, Shouko! Let me use your shampoo!
Thanks!
Yuuji, let me use your soap.
Here.
You two are kinda like a married couple already.
Wha...?! You talk too much, Himeji!
It'll be a problem if she gets the wrong idea.
She's stupid so she gets
carried away easily and...
Hey! Stop it!
Hey, honey! It's bad manners
to put your towel in the water!
Take that unromantic thing
away and let's be together legally!
Why are you mean to the weak?!
Hey, did you know? The baths at
a public bathing place are connected!
"Butt?"
If you dive, you might be able to see, huh?
Dive Challenge!
Ow, it's hot!
That's a high temperature area
where hot water is flowing out!
I'll first cool myself down
well with water and then...
Second challenge!
It's hot! My eyes...! My eyes...!
Looks like it didn't work, huh?
Dammit. How dare she mock us!
We won't forgive her!
Now that it's come to this,
I'll peek on them at any cost!
This iron bracelet allows him to summon
his Avatar without an attending teacher.
Awaken! I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
Okay! Go!
Ah! That's Stupid Big Brother's Avatar!
Can you see?
Ahh! Even if my Avatar can
see them, it's no fun for me at all!
An alternative plan. Here.
I see! If I have my Avatar
take the digital camera...!
I'm summoning my Avatar!
What?
Summon!
We're not gonna let you play a prank!
Your Avatar probably can't
get through this line of defense.
I'll definitely break through it! Let's go!
Ou... ch!
Those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
Why is Iron Man here?!
--He's got no luck in anything.
--Hey, what were you doing there?!
"Milk"
Oh, I won!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
Jugyou owari shifuku no jikan
Tatoeru no nara “Maji de Angel!”
Fui no kokuchi heiwa kowashita
Tsuishi no shirase “Jigoku da!”
Tomodachi tono warai banashi ni
“Iru wake naiyo sonna baka”
Demo hontou wa mune no oku dewa
Sakendetanda “Jibun ga! Sou deshita!”
Chuusha jou de miru “Tsukigime” no koto
Kaisha no namae dato omotteta...
Zutto...
Baka mo tooseba otoko date
Bokura no joushiki hijoushiki?
Ruuru wa muyou sa kono sekai
Yakiniku teishoku gekokujou
Miroyo!
Nishi kara nobotta ohisama ga shizunde iku
Hashire! Mou gohan da
Ouchi ni kaerou! Ouchi ni kaerou!
Question 7.
What is the marriageable
age in Japanese civil law?
The difference in age doesn't
matter as long as there's love.
Thank you for the dreams and hopes.
Next Episode! "Me, Shouko,
and Kisaragi Grand Park."
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"