Why?
Why did Bro have to die for an addict like you?!
Ishihara!
As Sasaki was working his way smoothly through the election campaign,
the boys from cell 2-6 appeared in front of him.
Doctor!
Dr. Sasaki!
What's gotten into him?
This is a big problem.
We still need to visit a few more places.
I'm overreacting.
Nothing will happen.
Nothing will.
No!
What can those kids do anyway?!
Right, right.
Nothing will happen.
I won't... let anyone get in my way.
O-Oh, it's you.
Great timing. I was starting to lose my nerve.
Yes, wait for me at the usual inn.
I'll be there right away.
Dr. Sasaki.
I'm heading out.
I'll be back by tomorrow morning.
Doctor.
We have a few more places to visit.
I'm sorry, but please tell them that something urgent has come up.
Thank you.
D-Doctor!
Geez.
If only he didn't have that habit...
Good boy.
You were waiting for me in bed?
You know...
I can't bear it anymore.
Come on, show me your face!
Hey, Dr. Sasaki.
You haven't changed.
I guess you were planning to have a lot of fun tonight.
Then...
Why don't you hang out with me, for old times' sake, Dr. Sasaki?
What are you doing here?
What?
Didn't I tell you?
I want to help you with the election.
Help me?
Don't give me that-
Oh, don't be like that, Dr. Sasaki.
Let's play just a little, okay?
Bro...
I did the right thing, right?
Well, we're here, Dr. Sasaki.
Hey, guys, sorry to make you wait!
We brought the star of the party!
We've been waiting for you, Dr. Sasaki.
Uncovered, you're still a genius.
We threatened Sasaki's toy into making the call,
and he showed up with a big smile.
Sorry, Dr. Sasaki.
We didn't mean to raise your hopes.
So...
Is everything ready?
Yeah, we're ready.
Well...
Take a look!
We made a special seat, just for you.
Now, go ahead, Dr. Sasaki.
Cabbage put all his effort into digging that hole.
Is... it money?
Do you want money?
How much?
How much do you want?
I'll pay you as much as you want!
So...
So please spare-
We just...
want to see you have fun.
That's all.
P-Please, wait!
Please, wait!
All right, Cabbage.
Bury him.
Sure.
Stop!
Okay, all done.
A masterpiece of art!
This is what's meant by an octopus's head!
Well, then...
Dr. Sasaki.
Did you know...
that the tides here change rather frequently?
The tide's still pretty low right now,
but in thirty minutes, it'll be at its height.
And...
your head will be right underwater.
It's here!
Would you look at that.
It's not even gonna take thirty minutes.
Hey, I'm begging you.
Save me.
I'll do anything.
Forgive me!
Forget about it.
You deserve to die for what you've done.
Or...
will you confess everything and beg for forgiveness?
If you do...
the waves might not kill you.
You... Go to hell!
Hey, Turtle.
We've had our fun.
Want to get going now?
Yeah, let's do that.
See ya, Dr. Sasaki.
Have fun being food for the crabs.
Hey, wait!
This must be a joke!
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey!
No...
I don't want to die.
Hey! I'll tell you everything!
Don't go!
Save me!
Because he was facing the sea, he couldn't see anyone.
"Are they still there?"
"I don't want to die."
"I'm scared."
Sasaki screamed his lungs out from fear of dying.
Save me!
Excuse me.
Oh, were you still asleep?
Your friend left early this morning.
"Was the tide that splashed my face...
and the pinning of my limbs...
all just a nightmare?"
"No."
Sasaki turned pale and trembled...
from the sensation of being held in a bottomless pit.
Sign: Koike Setsuko
Sorry.
I don't have any clothes that would fit you.
No, I should be apologizing.
I didn't mean to impose on you.
I didn't know... that you were living alone.
Yeah.
I transferred hospitals,
and some other things happened,
so it wasn't exactly easy for me to live at home.
I see.
So...
Did you go... to Numazu?
Yeah.
Ishihara!
Why?
Why won't you kill me, Sakuragi?
You could've killed me a million times!
Why?
You didn't kill me back then either!
You just gave me Hagino's note,
and then you walked away from me!
Where were you going, Sakuragi?
Where were you going without me?
Stop telling me to stay away from your friends,
and fight me one on one!
Come on! Kill me, Sakuragi!
Get lost, Ishihara.
Don't show your face to us again.
You're not even worth killing.
S-Sakuragi...
Ishihara was nothing but a pathetic piece of trash.
"He's not human."
"It's not worth ending his story."
"If I did, I'd hurt Bro just the same."
Mario managed to avoid life imprisonment,
thanks to Sakuragi Rokurouta.
I finally understood.
I know where Bro was heading
after he walked away from Ishihara.
Bro was trying to come see me fight.
Is it weird that I think like that?
No.
He was amazing.
Ishihara stabbed him in the stomach.
Yet that didn't stop him.
He continued to walk towards the gate.
He was amazing.
He was just... really amazing.
Ishihara and Sasaki couldn't defeat him.
Bro...
Bro beat them both.
Of course he did.
Sakuragi... wouldn't lose to anyone.
You're right.
Thank you, Sakuragi.
Thank you for stopping Mario.
Moving along.
Our next speaker is Mr. Sasaki Gisuke.
It's all right.
There's nothing to worry about.
Nothing will happen.
Now, please.
If I get through this speech,
I'll be the mayor by tomorrow.
Then those kids won't be able to lay a finger on me.
I-I-If I... b-become... t-the... mayor...
This is just the beginning...
Dr. Sasaki.
Let the show begin, Dr. Sasaki.
Hey, what's happened to him?
He's fallen silent.
Now, should we begin?
We should indeed.
It was my fault!
Please forgive me!
Spare me! I'll tell you everything!
Isn't this... Sasaki's voice?
Yeah.
That's right, I was raping the boys at the special disciplinary school!
I paid money to the guard, Ishihara, to get him to bring me the cutest ones.
No!
Suzuki Takeyuki, Ozeki Ken, Sodesaki Tomokazu...
This is wrong!
It's all just a lie!
I take full responsibility for Hagino Eiichi's case.
I made him my plaything and drove him to suicide!
I reported his death as an accident so I wouldn't get caught.
I was also behind the killing of Sakuragi Rokurouta!
He knew about what happened to Hagino!
Please forgive me!
I'm sick!
I'm a perverted old man... who raped young boys!
No. No. No!
No!
Of course he'll drop out.
Really.
I almost voted for him.
Did you know?
He mortgaged his hospital to pay for the campaign.
He's finished.
Well, either way...
I'm glad he didn't become our mayor.
Summer's almost over, Sakuragi.
Those boys from cell 2-6 will walk on their own two feet from now on.
And I've also decided.
I'm going to move on.
See you later... Sakuragi.
Yo.
I saw the paper.
That was pretty flashy.
Just what I'd expect from you guys.
Mario.
Did you kill... Ishihara?
These are the bullets from Bro's body.
Setsuko...
said that she wanted each of us to have one.
I didn't need to kill him.
Bro sent him to hell long ago.
The battle was long over.
You guys may not quite like it,
but I think this was for the best.
Well done, Mario.
What will all of you do now?
I'm going to be a SDF officer, no question about it.
I'll probably stay in the black market for a while.
I actually make a lot of money.
And Lily would miss me if I left.
I think I'll go home for a bit.
I'm sure my mom's worried about me.
I'll find an opportunity and become a singer.
I'll do anything if I can eat something good!
Cabbage, that's all you say.
What about you, Mario?
I don't know what I'll do.
You never change.
I don't know where to go yet.
But one day...
One day, I'll be like you.
Sasaki lost his hospital, his fortune, and his honor.
This battle ended with Ishihara left a shadow of a man.
However, the six boys of cell 2-6 felt nothing about destroying Ishihara and Sasaki.
To them, it was just like spitting out a piece of chewed-up gum.
They engraved one thought into their hearts:
"We can fly freely in the sky now."
Love, riches, success, and satisfaction...
Everything was in their own hands.
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Mario's suppressed feelings...
explode into action.
"I won't give her away to anyone."