Growl, growl!
One day, at the far reaches of space,
the minor planet Kumaria exploded!
The fragments of Kumaria became a
meteor swarm that rained down on Earth...
Which made the world's bears rise up as one!
They all started attacking humans!
Like, who could've seen that coming, right?
The humans built the Wall of Severance
to try to drive us bears from their world,
but guess what, man-made rules
don't work on bears! Growl!
We are bears.
Bears eat people. It's what we do!
And so...
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to become true
friends with you. To cross the wall...
Chomp, chomp, chomp.
Bears are... eating someone!
Shock!
Bear shock!
Those are the transfer students...
I get it--they're bears pretending to be human!
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
The bears' cruel attack has ended
Sumika Izumino's earthly life.
On behalf of the student body,
Mitsuko Yurizono will now deliver
a eulogy for our departed friend.
Sumika Izumino was a gentle person.
She showed kindness to the weak,
and was always generous with her love.
She never lost sight of herself, no matter what,
and bore the pure heart her name suggested--
Shock!
What's wrong, Yurizono?
Nothing, I'm sorry.
Izumino was like a white wildflower
in the fields of spring:
brave and sweet, yet graceful--
"Kureha Tsubaki・(Yuri)"
It's not true.
I refuse to believe Sumika was eaten by a bear!
It's not true! It's a lie!
Forgive Kureha for not being able
to come to the memorial today.
Poor thing...
She's lost someone important to her again.
Kureha, did you have fun
with your friend again today?
What's wrong? You seem down.
Don't look so sad.
You really love her, don't you, Kureha?
It's okay. I'm sure you'll see her again.
If you wish really hard...
Mom, I...
No matter how hard I wish,
I'll never see Sumika again!
I couldn't protect my friend!
Bears are really scary.
Does the Wall of Severance even
do anything? A bear got through it!
That reminds me, they say
another girl from that class is missing!
What, really?!
Did the bear get her too, then?
Probably.
I guess it's off the record since
they haven't found a body yet, but...
--Bears are seriously vermin.
--Growl. Those girls look so tasty!
That girl Kureha Tsubaki wasn't here.
Oh, you're right. We can't target her
if she doesn't come to school, huh?
Kureha Tsubaki has a delicious smell, growl.
Tee-hee, you have a gorgeous wild-animal
smell when you're being cool, too!
Oooh, your smell makes me giddy!
I just had a great idea!
I'm so clever!
There's no doubt about it.
Ginko Yurishiro and Lulu Yurigasaki--
those transfer students are bears.
This is horrible. But what I saw
at the flowerbed is hard evidence.
Mitsuko.
Hey, Mitsuko. Mitsuko!
Konomi...
Your head's in the clouds. What's wrong?
You're acting weird today.
It's nothing.
Are you really so concerned about that girl?
Kureha Tsubaki. I know
you're trying to get close to her.
But why? If you make friends with her,
the Invisible Storm will attack you, too.
It'll cause you trouble.
Now that Sumika Izumino is dead,
she's obviously going to be next...
Yes. Kureha Tsubaki didn't back
down on her love of Sumika Izumino.
Girls who don't follow the mood
of the herd get excluded.
That's how the system works, isn't it?
Then you should...
There's just something that concerns me.
What is it? If you're worried
about something, tell me!
All right. The truth is, I saw something awful.
Hello! It's the transfer students,
Lulu Yurigasaki and...
...Ginko Yurishiro.
H-Huh?
Anyway, we want you to let us have a room!
What?
Growl! What a cute house!
Hey, you're not using the attic, right?
Can we live there?
What are you talking ab--
Wah! Ginko and I have been sleeping
outside ever since we moved to town!
I itch all over! Any longer and I'll get fleas!
Can't we at least use your bath?
What's wrong with that?
O-Okay, if it's just the bath...
Yay! Negotiation successful! I'm so clever!
Wait! It's just for today, got it?
Um... ah, Yurigasaki!
You can call me Lulu!
What?
And you can call me Ginko.
What?!
I taste tears, growl.
What?
♪ Bathing, bathing, baths are so fun! ♪
♪ Bubbles, bubbles everywhere,
growl, growl, growl! ♪
You can't have a room here.
Sorry, but after you drink that,
take Yurigasaki and go home.
Were you crying, growl?
Of course I wasn't crying!
Growl. Did you know that sad
and lonely tears taste like a treat?
Growl... This is heaven.
Muahaha, we've safely invaded Kureha's house!
I am so clever!
Anyway, will you two go away
once Yurigasaki is done?
I'll let you take a bath too, if you need one.
I don't, growl.
I see.
What's with this girl? She keeps staring at me.
Not to mention she...
And she talks funny,
with all that "growl" stuff...
Kureha, your love is the real thing.
What?
The taste of tears... Your love is true, growl.
"Flashback"
I love you.
I love you so much.
What would you know?
I know. Because my love is true, too.
You can't know! You don't know
a thing about me and Sumika,
so don't talk like you do!
Growl.
Kureha Tsubaki. I've longed to see you.
We came here to see you.
What do you mean?
You smell, a delicious smell! Growl!
I'll show you my love...
Yurizono?
Yurizono?!
Get away from Kureha right now!
Ginko Yurishiro, Lulu Yurigasaki...
I know what you really are!
I saw. I saw what you were doing that day.
Now get away! I won't let you
lay a finger on Kureha!
Show your true colors!
Ngggh...
Growl.
Damn, that was a quick retreat.
Yurizono, what--
I don't have time to talk.
I'm going after them!
What was that all about?
"Incoming Call: Blocked Number"
Hello?
Is your love the real thing?
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance.
Kureha Tsubaki,
if your love is true, go to the roof.
The bears are waiting for you.
Who are you?
Give yourself over to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
What does that mean? Answer me!
My love...
Mitsuko loves that girl Kureha Tsubaki.
I've never seen her like that.
I won't allow it.
Mitsuko belongs to me!
I won't let anyone else have her!
That Kureha Tsubaki...
Shock!
I, Konomi Yurikawa, will eat her!
Bear shock!
Nasty!
Nasty girl!
Grrrrrrr.
The time for judgment has come, growl.
I'll never forgive those bears.
I'll ruin those bears!
"Flashback"
What flowers will you plant?
Yuri--lilies.
Lilies?
They're my mother's flowers.
"Flashback"
Wow, they're really growing!
I thought lily bulbs were just
something to put in egg custards.
Silly Sumika.
I hope they bloom soon.
"Flashback"
Not long now.
Yeah.
Your love will bloom.
My love?
Yes, love.
My love...
Nasty girl.
I'll prove my love.
I'll never forgive bears. I'll ruin bears!
Nas-ss-ss-ss-sty.
Nasty girl.
I keep missing. Why?
Die, beast! Die, die, die!
It killed Sumika. I... I have to kill it!
Nasty girl!
I want to eat her! I want to eat her right now!
Court is in session!
Welcome to Severance Court.
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
Growl...
Growl, growl.
Your Honor, less than a week has passed
since the defendant-bears
last preyed on a human.
This is blatant overeating. They are guilty!
Objection! I think what constitutes
"mega-hungry" is different for every bear!
Sparkle!
Sustained.
What?!
Bears follow bear instincts--that is the sexy way!
Shaba-da-doo.
Defendant-bears, I ask you:
Will you be invisible? Or will you eat humans?
We'll eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
Growl, growl!
Growl!
Yuri approved!
Ra-Ra-Rawr!
Kureha, I'm going to eat you.
Where is what I hope for?
I'm searching in the Invisible Storm.
Mmm. Searching for what?
Mmm. Searching for it where?
Give me the Promise Kiss!
Nasty?!
Nasty girl!
Yurizono?
That was close.
Are you okay, Kureha? Are you hurt?
I'm fine. But...
There are two bears. There must
be one more lurking somewhere!
Don't worry. Bears are cautious.
They won't attack again today.
But...!
Kureha, you mustn't blame yourself.
Izumino's death isn't your fault.
She was just a little unluckier
than the rest of us.
No... that's not...
I understand. I really do.
Yurizono, I...
It's okay to cry, Kureha.
You were Izumino's true friend.
You have the right to cry.
This is Unit 105.
We found a dead bear on the Arashigaoka
High School access road. I repeat--
Sumika...
Sweet Kureha, your love belongs to me now!
Mmmm.
Delicious smell!
Ah, you're so good I ache!
But not tonight, not yet...
Chomp, chomp, grawr. Chomp, chomp, grawr.
It's no good. Invisible girls
will only ever taste invisible.
After tearing apart so many of them,
I finally understand...
Only excluded individuals are truly delicious.
It's only the meat of girls
who won't back down on love
that tastes like pomegranates
and honey--that satisfies my hunger!
Sumika Izumino, you tasted wonderful.
Soon... the Invisible Storm will come soon!
Oh, I can't wait!
I want to eat you this minute...
...Tsubaki Kureha! Grawr!
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love