Nayu Glasses-Scope!
Underwear-searcher Nayu's sensors react to a mere millisecond of wind.
Sensing slight changes in atmospheric current,
not a single billowing skirt escapes her.
Nice breeze...
suki wo zebune HAGUshitai
“好き”を全部ね ハグしたい
I want to hug everything that I like (I want to hug)
(dakishimetai)
(抱きしめたい)
fukuramu HAATO de GYU tto ne
膨らむハートで ギュッとね
An expanding heart makes it kind of tight (quite a sight)
(meippai ne)
(目一杯ね)
DOKI DOKI hassei tahatsu
ドキドキ発生多発
Excitement breaks out multiple times (here comes trouble)
(jiken boppatsu)
(事件勃発)
kaisatsu de shingou de koumon de
改札で 信号で 校門で
At the ticket barrier, the traffic lights, the school gate (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
hazunda HIPPU no NORI de ne
弾んだヒップのノリでね
Expanded hips makes it easy to put on (it's kind of fun)
(tanoshiku ne)
(楽しくね)
WAKUWAKU kasoku YABAI
ワクワク加速ヤバい
Nervously accelerate, oh great (seriously won't stop)
(maji tomannai)
(まじ止まんない)
haretemo âme demo OUR MORNING'S BRIGHTENING
晴れても雨でも Our Morning's Brightening!!
If it's sun or if it's rain, Our Morning's Brightening!!
A B C D E F G ja hakarenai seifuku no uchigawa
A・B・C・D・E・F・G じゃ測れない 制服の内側
A.B.C.D.E.F.G you can't measure it! Inside of the uniform something is
shikachuu da shi SAIZU kawaru yume yosoku wa fukanou
進化中だし サイズ変わる夢 予測は不可能
Evolving size, changing dream, you can't predict it...!
kyoumi ni riyuu wa nai yo ne
興味に理由はないよね？
There's no interest in reason, right? (Plain and simple)
(tanjunmeikai)
(単純明快)
ki ni naru koto ga ki ni narimasu
気になることが 気になります
You'll get worried over worries
tokenai suushiki to DEREnai
解けない数式とデレない
Don't trouble yourself with an unsolvable formula (tiringly tough tiringly tough)
(nankaikonpai)
(なんかいこんぱい)
ano ko wa tsune ni ne onaji omo sa
あのコは常にね 同じ重要さ
With that girl it's always the same (mainly)
shigyou no chaimu ga RISETTO SAIN
始業のチャイムがリセットサイン
It's a sign the starting bell has reset
kinou no shittai wa shoukyo de iku yo
昨日の失態は消去でいくよ
Yesterday's mistakes are being cleared, here we go!
DERIKEETO de DAINAMIKKU LOW TEENAGERS
デリケートでダイナミック Low Teenagers
Delicate and dynamic Low Teenagers
FURIRU de kakushita honne naze oshieaitai
フリルで隠した本音 なぜ教え合いたい…！？
Frilled, hidden motive- why do you want to join them together... !?
suki ni zenbu ne TACCHI shitai
“好き”に全部ね タッチしたい
I want to touch everything that I like (I want to be sure)
(tashikametai)
(確かめたい)
tokimeku HAATO de sotto ne
ときめくハートで そっとね
My heart's fluttering, treat it softly (gently)
(yasashiku ne)
(優しくね)
KIRAKIRA hasshin funpatsu
キラキラ発信奮発
Sparkling splurge of submissions (experiments one after the other)
(jiken renpatsu)
(実験連発)
kyoushitsu de rouka de bukatsu de
教室で 廊下で 部活で
In the class, the halls, club activities (anywhere)
(ANYWHERE)
tsukisusunjatte in janai
突き進んじゃって いんじゃない
Taking the plunge should be fine, wouldn't it (Not at all it wouldn't)
(zenzen injanai)
(全然いんじゃない)
shirigomi HIPPU mo hoppu NI
尻込みヒップもホップに
Hesitant hip and a hesitant hop (lively now)
(genki ni ne)
(元気にね)
FURUFURU yuuki wo dashi
フルフル勇気を出し
Bring out all your bravery (bring out that spirit)
(sono ki wo dashi)
(その気を出し)
mukae teki nashi mayou hima nashi manande asonde
向かえ敵なし 迷う暇なし 学んで遊んで
Without opposition, without losing time, in study and play,
WE MUST CHOOSE BRIGHT THINGS
Everyone's too quick to cover their skirts.
I was wondering why you were looking around so excitedly this morning.
Good morning, Nayu-chan.
Good morning, Haruka-chan, Yako-chan.
Good morning.
You shouldn't be staring so intently at girls' underwear.
Eh?
It's embarrassing when people see your underwear.
That's not true!
Underwear isn't something to be embarrassed about!
First, there's heat-retention.
For adults, they keep figure and protect the body-
Of course there's lace, frills, embroidery, prints-
They're all cute and pretty, aren't they?
Women should be proud of wearing such wonderful things,
but I'm just telling you what my grandma taught me.
Your grandma?
Hayama Nayu.
Since elementary school,
I've had such bitter experiences because of you, but-
I'll make it clear it won't continue any longer!
Oi! Hayam-
Look! You're also embarrassed.
I'm not! I'm... um...
That's enough for now, let's go to the classroom.
Ah right, I might not be able to go home with you today.
Hmm? What's wrong?
I'm planning on observing some club activities.
Eh? Which club?
A Windy Day
Dammit, I've been so bothered by Hayama;
I couldn't concentrate in class.
I need to hurry and talk with her to set things straight.
Hey, Class Representative.
I'd like you to help me with something tomorrow morning.
Ah! Hayam-
Err, nothing.
I suppose I can do it next time.
Oh, it's my brother.
Yes?
Huh?! Taiyaki?!
The store's pretty close to your school, yeah?
Oi, you listening?!
Like I said, why would I?
I'm keeping my word this time!
Nice shot, Sensei!
It would've been nice if you were the Basketball Club advisor.
Best in School / Giant Breasts Ranking!!
No one even comes close to those.
Definitely the MVP!
Come on, your next class will start soon.
Okay!
Having passed by each other this much,
I feel like some invisible power's messing with me.
Eh? The briefs from the entrance ceremony?
Yeah.
The company's survey also concluded that
most people say they feel quite different.
In the end, that's how they decided to market them.
Really?!
Amazing, Keigo-san!
It's thanks to your report!
Keep up the good work, monitor.
Just leave it to me!
At this rate, you'll be getting your own "Nayu-produced" label underwear.
Ah, whoops, here's the train.
We'll talk later, okay?
Nayu-chan!
Be careful on the way home.
We're almost done cleaning!
Got it! Bye!
Listen, listen!
The briefs I wore at the entrance ceremony-
Idiot! I thought I told you not to yell about panties!
Geez, what an awful breeze.
I get it now. The Handicrafts Club, huh?
Yup! I was wondering if I could make underwear discreetly here.
Haruka-chan, are you fine with coming with me?
Sure I am!
I'm interested, too.
Yako-chan, are you fine with not going to the Kendo club?
Sure, I've decided on the Kendo club,
but I was worried if it would just be the two of you.
All right, I'll open the door!
The Malicious Trio!
Oh, new club entrants?
Or perhaps you're here to observe?
Aren't you the top-ranked student, Hayama-san?
Eh? Um, yes.
Well, I'm pleased that you're interested in my club.
Hey, isn't that-
Yeah.
She's even sucking up to teachers here?
For the time being, feel free to take your time.
Amidst weeding
In preparation for the Culture Festival,
our Handicrafts Club decides on a yearly theme to make items for the display.
Woven toys, bead craft, almost anything can be made,
so long as they are acceptable for the Culture Festival.
Wow, beads!
Do you have any interest in bead accessories and such?
I do think they're cute, but...
If I could, I'd like to learn sewing techniques
and ways to mend clothes.
Yes, yes, hush now...
All right then, how about you?
Huh? I didn't really want to come, um...
I have no interest in tiny things like this...
She loves it.
But, beads could be good!
Embroidering them on briefs or bras would be cute!
As usual, your mind always goes there, huh?
Have you three decided to join?
Um, any handmade crafts are fine, right?
Of course.
Then, how about underwear?
Underwear?
Unbelievable.
That's too embarrassing.
That's not what you should be saying.
Isn't that just the truth?
You make what you make, but...
There's no way you could display that.
No way at all!
That's right.
Members of the opposite sex come to the Culture Festival, too.
Underwear could be a bit embarrassing.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Seriously, what a gang of chickens. Sheesh.
Don't worry about it, Nayu-chan...
Nayu-chan?
Thanks for coming with me today, you two.
Shall we go home now?
Today was pretty windy, wasn't it?
Yeah it was.
Um, Nayu-chan!
Would you join the Cooking Club with me?
You get to make pudding and such, it's fun!
I understand your feelings,
but what Nayu really wants to make isn't "pudding and such".
Oh yeah!
Why don't you just make it?
An Underwear Club!
What are you saying all of a sudden?!
No, really, I'm serious.
Not long ago you suggested that, didn't you?
It'd be nice if there were an Underwear Club, huh?
But how do you form a club?
First you need to gather people who want to join.
Then you need to ask a teacher, and-
Wait! What on Earth are you two talking about?!
I think it'd be great to have one, but-
You're smiling.
It'll be fine.
You could make one!
What happened to the passion you showed when you made me a bra?
But I don't know how to make a club.
You could just look into that!
But I'm only a first-year!
The oldest are only third-years!
But I don't have that much courage!
Then I'll lend you some courage.
We'd enjoy it, too!
But, but, but!
Nobody has more confidence than you when it comes to underwear, right?
But even if we did our best,
could we actually form an Underwear Club?
I've finally found you, Hayama Nayu!
It wouldn't be an overstatement to
say today's effort has all been for this!
This time I'll make it clear!
Hayam-
It really is windy today!
All right, let's have a strategy meeting!
Nayu?
It's morning!
You awake?
Na-yu!
You're gonna be late!
A Leaver lace strapped, silk bra.
Here you are, Nayu.
A present for you in the future.
It's the first of its kind in the world.
It's my own work, and I have great confidence in it.
What is this, Grandma?
Competition-underwear, Junior-type.
C-Competition?! Will I have to fight?!
That's right.
For example, love or studying, there will be a lot to fight for,
but you've got to muster up courage and shape your own destiny.
This is the combat uniform for that day.
So Nayu, to win you mustn't give up until the very end.
All right! I'll make the Underwear Club!
Doing stretches this morning, huh?
Good morning, Yako-chan! Haruka-chan!
Good morning, Nayu-chan!
You've got a fighting spirit this morning.
Mmhmm! I'll do my best!
Today's the day I take the first step
towards establishing the Underwear Club!
That's right!
But our clubs officially start today.
I'm afraid we won't be able to help you...
Oi.
Will you be fine by yourself?
I'll be fine! Thanks!
Oii!
I have to go to the staff room, so-
OI!
Listen, Hayama Nayu.
You got to give the top-ranked student's
greeting at the Entrance Ceremony, right?
From now on, I won't be losing to you, get it?
That's it.
See ya.
You know him?
Eh? Erm... Who is he?
Eh?! You don't know him?!
I'm Komachi! Komachi Hiroki from Class E!
The Komachi you've beaten in elementary school and even cram school!
Oi! Don't be so violent!
Hitting people with your hallway slippers... that's terrible!
See ya.
Weirdo.
Do you remember, Nayu-chan?
Eh? Um... I kind of recognise him, but...
You were classmates, weren't you?
I didn't really like those times...
I might not have remembered because of that.
Ah, I've got to get to the staff room!
I'll see you later.
Right, once you've come up with the idea,
you just need to gather potential members.
Do you have an idea? Class Representative.
Making a new school club...
To think Hayama-san was a girl with such motivation!
So, what kind of club would you like to make?
An Underwear Club.
Hot, hot, hot!
Underwear Club?
Yes!
A club doing things like making and researching underwear.
That's a strange club.
Right. How about you try asking your homeroom assistant, Mizuno-sensei?
I'm already the Judo Club advisor,
Background: The Truth About a Teacher's Activities
and a woman might be more suited to this role, eh?
Well, when you've gathered members, we'll talk.
How absurd.
An Underwear Club. Are you serious, Hayama-san?
Tsukamoto-sensei...
You need to think more about your position as class representative when acting.
You saw everyone's reaction in the Handicrafts Club, correct?
I believe it will be difficult to gather members for such an indecent club.
U-Um...
Pardon me!
That was strict of you.
There are expectations of Hayama-san.
I'm merely protecting her from taking the wrong path.
I think it would be wrong for us to decide that it's the wrong path...
She's bravely decided to take a...
difficult path... um...
Excuse my butting in...
Excuse me! I'm... only a new teacher...
Underwear Club? What the hell is that?
Nayu-chan seems a little down...
She hasn't checked everyone's underwear.
And yet she was so lively this morning...
I believe it will be difficult to gather members for such an indecent club.
Nayu.
When you need a firm resolve,
wear this underwear.
Grandma...
That's right.
Things aren't always easy at first.
Um... You're wearing a cute bra!
Ah, really?
It was mail ordered, but cheap...
She's revived!
I'm interested in underwear.
Would you like to try forming an Underwear Club?
What's that?
A club?
Yeah, it's surprising.
I get it... more people.
Y-Yes! A club for researching underwear...
Sounds kind of... erotic, doesn't it?
Actually, we're already joining the Basketball Club.
Well, don't worry about it.
This is just the beginning.
Should we help you?
I'm fine! I can make it on my own.
Don't overwork yourself.
Thank you, Yako-chan.
Eh? Underwear Club?
Ah, sorry.
I'm not really interested.
Eh-heh? Sounds kinda naughty, doesn't it?
Going Home Club.
Ah... I really can't get anyone...
No, no! I can't give up!
Hey, hey! Are you interested in underwear?
Are you talking about the "Underwear Club?"
Yes, that's right...
Wouldn't it be best to join the Handicrafts Club?
Huh?
I'm worried about how guys would look at me...
It's embarrassing, too...
Also, I heard a rumour that scary teachers like Tsukamoto-sensei...
...will glare at anyone who joins the Underwear Club.
Sorry, Hayama-san.
Haruka-chan and Yako-chan are still doing club activities...
I wonder if I should wait?
Today in Japanese literature, the teacher came without his textbook.
It has been a while since I've been all alone.
It was a real mess!
Since elementary school, perhaps.
Hayama-san, isn't that a bit much?
Eh? Why?
Isn't it cute?
Eh? It's dirty...
Hayama-san's a bit... strange, isn't she?
Grandma...
Is it that embarrassing to like underwear?
Oi.
Does your stomach hurt or something?
Hamachi-kun.
Komachi!
Oh, oh yeah!
Maybe you'd like to join the Underwear Club?!
There's no way I'd join your club!
My aim is to be a manly man.
An Underwear Club would be so...
How do you expect me to join such a weak and girly club?
You can't gather any members?
Everyone says they're too embarrassed to...
Hmm? Do you think it is, Hayama-san?
Frankly, I'd be embarrassed.
Don't say that!
It can't be helped, right?
I'm a man, after all.
It's not true!
There's nothing embarrassing about underwear.
It's embarrassing.
I'm not interested in your underwear,
but if you could share your vision of underwear with everyone,
then you can get members, right?
Vision of underwear...
STEP BY STEP ippozutsu arukidasou
Step By Step 一歩ずつ歩き出そう!
Step by step, a step at a time, let's set out walking!
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
fuku no shita ni mo minna sorezore shuchou ga aru
制服(ふく)の下にも みんなそれぞれ主張がある
Even under the clothes everyone has different opinions
hazukashigarunai de ii otomegokoro ni jishin wo motte
恥ずかしがらないでいい 乙女心に自信を持って
Don't be shy now, have some confidence young lady
aa shitai kou shitai jounetsu wa tomaranai
ああしたい こうしたい 情熱は止まらない
Ah, I want to do something like this- the enthusiasm won't let up
kowagaranaide ima dekiru koto wo hajimemasho
怖がらないで いま できることを始めましょ!
Don't be afraid, let's just do what we can do now!
onna no ko wa nayandeiru kagami wo nozoite
女の子は悩んでいる 鏡を覗いて
The girl worries, peeking into the mirror
minna doko ka yowaki ni naru toshigoro dakara
みんなどこか弱気になる 年頃だから
Everyone's timid about something, they're just that age
HAPPY SMILE egao kara hajimeyou
Happy Smile 笑顔から始めよう!
Happy Smile let's start with a grin!
donna toki datte hitori janai
どんな時だって ひとりじゃない
At any given time, you're not alone
unmei wo kirihiraku kono omoi
運命を切りひらく この想い
Open the way for destiny, using these feelings
hikari kagayaku ashita e
光り輝く あしたへ
To a tomorrow shining with light
tokimeki wo sagashi ni ikou yo SHY GIRLS
ときめきを探しに行こうよ Shy Girls
Let's go look for excitement, Shy Girls
That was a good bath.
C'mon, Nayu.
You're still wearing that?
You'll catch a cold; get some panties on.
Hmm? Hmm.
C'mon, Nayu!
Here it is! This is it!
Preview
I wonder if we could call the Underwear Club something else...?
Lingerie Club?
An-da-wae-ah Club.
Inner Club!
Bra Club, or Panties Club, or Bra-Panties Club!
Maybe just 'Underwear Club' would be fine...
Look forward to the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
To
Each
Their
Own
Figure