"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
3rd year, class B...
Miss Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm? Does that
mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform,
argh, it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop) Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic, something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait, one
of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth
ramen with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away, in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll
be laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
So, I'm raising a dog in-game.
It's just so cute that I
can't help but talk to it!
I see...
You know, for some reason,
when you speak to animals,
you end up using a really coquettish
voice... even though it's a game.
Oh, I know what you mean by that.
When I talk to my goldfish, I end
up with a really sweet voice.
I can understand doing it for dogs and cats,
but talking to fish makes it sound
like you're a really lonely person.
What was that?! That's prejudice, damn you!
What's with that look of pity in your eyes?!
That reminds me of a question
I've had for a while.
Among all the obedience
commands, or rather tricks,
you can teach a dog, what
does "chin-chin" mean?
Well... if I go into the details,
it will get rather long,
so I'll abbreviate and just
say that it's for certain
that the origins of the term
can be traced back to China.
Now, all of you that had naughty
thoughts, raise your hands.
"There's Substance in 2-D"
"Study About Gu__m"
Come to think of it, Gun__m
is still really popular.
Yeah! Your dad here loves it too!
There's various varieties of it, too.
Like V and W and X.
Yeah, I've seen every series in real time.
Call it fan spirit, or a sense of duty.
Then...
If something like G_ndam Serial Murders
or Detective Gunda_ started,
you'd still watch?
If you love Gun_am... You
have a duty to watch it!
Duty?
But if you can't refer to it with a
letter, I'm sure it doesn't count.
While on the subject of
Gu_dam, I just had a thought.
I sure don't look it, but I'm already
two years older than _muro now.
That really was sudden.
And in two more years, I'll be
the same age as Mr. Bri__ht.
I can't even imagine it!
Well, you know, Mr. Br__ht
is rather extreme...
Even for Gun_am.
Ha_an's the same way.
Or rather, since you look more childish
than your actual age, Konata,
I have second thoughts about using
you as the basis to judge from.
At least you could say that I
look younger than my actual age
No, but you're cute!
I got something valuable from our neighbors.
Apparently, it's a vacation souvenir.
What? A vase?
You have grown into a
good girl, just my type!
You're such a cute girl!
Dad, it's hot.
Or rather, that line sounds rather dangerous.
It's morning...
I drank way too much last night,
so I thought I'd totally
pass out until afternoon...
I guess I'm still young?
And now, the morning news
for Monday, July 2...
What? What happened to Sunday?
Where did my holiday go?!
I always think about doing my best
to study for exams until evening.
But I can't help but get sleepy.
I asked Sis about it, and she said...
You're scared of horror flicks, right?
If you watch one, maybe you
won't be able to sleep at night.
The other day, you crawled into
my futon after a show like that.
So I watched something scary, and
since then I haven't fallen asleep.
Nothing like your sister, so to say.
But ever since, at night I get worried
"CLANG"
about what's going on behind me,
and about every faint sound I hear...
It's even harder to concentrate
on studying than it was before!
And because of that, I've been losing sleep,
making me really sleepy during class...
But despite you saying that
you are scared of such shows,
you tend to watch those kinds of
things pretty often, don't you?
It's not that I want to watch them.
My mother is like that as well...
Hey, Miyuki, I rented this.
Would you like to watch with me?
I'm scared to watch it alone.
Those scared of things like that tend
to watch many shows of that type.
They want to see something they're afraid of.
That's not it, Yuki-chan! In my
case, I really hate stuff like that!
Iwasaki-san, do you understand this problem?
I was just thinking that one over myself.
If a little more thought doesn't do it,
I was going to ask Miyuki-san.
I see. We're lucky that we both have
reliable upperclassmen so close to us!
...was what Iwasaki-san and I were
talking about at school today.
What? She's relying on me that much?!
She's going to personally experience
the harshness of reality later on!
Hey, Sis.
Sis, did you ever study for
exams together with Bro Ki?
I didn't...
It's a popular situation in games
and stuff, but when a boy and a girl
who get along well are together, there's no
way they'd be able to concentrate, right?
When you're not concentrating, you
start fantasizing about what you like.
I'm seeing withdrawal symptoms.
Sis, there's something that
I want you to teach me...
I'm kinda cornered with my own
studying now, so can you ask Sis Yui?
Study, gotta study.
What a dirty trick!
I went to a different school...
I didn't learn this at my school!
I see...
Yeah, right!
I'm stuck myself.
Sis, do you understand this?
Of course you wouldn't...
Don't ask if you're not
relying on me for an answer.
Weren't you here for the
conversation I had earlier?
Oh, I wonder if I should just
call Miyuki-san and ask...
Though I'm sure it would bother her.
Yeah, well, I think she'd be bothered.
I mean, it's late.
Why are parents written out of the game
from the start at times like this?
I'd like her to rely on me every so often...
I'll correct that!
Izumi! Don't go falling asleep!
In this day and age where
corporal punishment is banned,
you really punch people on a regular basis.
Not that it bothers me.
True. But it's not just anyone.
I do choose who I hit, in a lot of ways.
It gets to be a pain later on, you know.
Wow, she clearly admitted it... That's
another amazing part about her.
In the first place, the banning
of corporal punishment is absurd!
Well, that's the end of class.
Miyuki-san, I'm sorry, I don't
understand the era titles and stuff.
Yuki-chan, teach me this problem!
All of you with "Takara, Takara!"
Why don't you come ask your teacher
about things you don't understand?!
Miss Kuroi!
Oh, Izumi, what is it?
Well, there was something
that I wanted to ask you.
What is it? You can ask me anything,
go ahead, ask, it's okay!
It's about a rare item in the
game that I'm playing right now.
Hey, wait... Ma'am?
That's not it! That's
not what I want to hear!
It's really hot after a typhoon's passed.
We had a lot of typhoons this
year, so of course they're past.
That was a good one.
Wait, what was good?
I'll ask just to be on the safe side...
You were making a joke earlier, right?
Um, there's something I
want to ask you, Sis...
What is it? You're being so formal.
About this morning... Did
Kona-chan say something strange?
I didn't see anything wrong
about what she said, either...
She watches the news with me, but
why is she at Konata's level?
Why does their timing always make
me think they're aiming for this?!
The pitcher is looking out for
the runner on second base...
What's going on with the
baseball broadcast today?
Oh, at this rate, it looks
like it'll run long.
Again? Geez!
I have to reprogram the timer recording.
Oh, brother...
Why can't they just reserve a longer
slot for the game to begin with?
In the first place,
professional baseball is really
slow with each and every movement.
If the players did all their
movements in a lively manner,
couldn't they shorten the game time?
Well, those who like it like everything
about it, including things like that...
Maybe they're concentrating
mentally or something, too.
How is it? Are you used to school life now?
Yes, but there's lots of homework
and stuff, so it's very hard.
I see.
Seniors concentrate mainly
on entrance exam preparation,
so there's not much homework, right?
Konata... you...
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about.
Whew, it's so hot out.
Konata! What are you thinking,
walking around like that!
What are you going to do
if Yu-chan mimics you?!
But it's been hot out lately.
You know, it's that thing
they do at the Diet, too.
"Cool Biz"?
Yeah, that.
No, that's a bit different.
What have you been doing?
I was wondering when I'd receive a
reply to a text message I sent...
Doesn't it bother you?
I was reading a book,
and missed my station...
As always, Miyuki-san, your
nonchalant clumsiness is so cute!
You think so? I think
it would just be a pain.
You don't get it.
The shameful look in trying to patch
things up is where you find moe.
It's cuter to have a couple of flaws!
What? So, when you're at work, you're like...
I'm sorry, I spilled that. I'm
terribly sorry about it, sir.
...or something?
Kagami... You look a bit stupid,
you know? What are you doing?
It was a conversation topic you brought up!
Though I was the one that did that.
And so? Do you do clumsy things as
well, to gain those kinds of points?
No, I don't do stuff like that.
There might be some prejudice about
it, but the manager would scold me.
Really? Knowing you, I thought
you'd do it and say "That stuff is
so moe," or something like that.
You don't get it, Kagami.
It's true that clumsy girls are
cute, and there is moe there,
but if it does damage in real life,
it's rather irritating, you know?
Even if it's something that you
laugh at and let go in games.
Otaku are really harsh
about things like that.
Once again, if we have a contestant
with a perfect score today,
courtesy of Look JTB,
we'll give away a one month tundra-
tour package to a lucky viewer.
Variety shows and quiz shows like
this often have prizes, and cash too.
Maybe it's because you get
more contestants when you do.
And if a popular celebrity comes for
it, they can get better ratings!
That's true, though I don't know the details.
But, you know...
If they made the viewers
able to join the quiz,
and tilt the prize money
towards the viewer entries,
don't you think the ratings
would go up even more?
I kinda think that way, but you have
a very straightforward appeal there.
Morning!
S'up?
I was thinking while
playing a game yesterday,
but who is the school idol at our school?
What? A school idol? You mean
something like "Miss Ryouou"?
Yeah, something like that. Normally,
you'd see something of that sort.
Normally, in games, you'd have
something like groupies and stuff.
I'm tired again today!
So refreshing!
Oh, I have the early shift tomorrow.
I guess I won't connect to the 'net
tonight, and just go to sleep.
It's bad if I'm late.
Securing hours of sleep first
is a sign that I'm aging...
When I was still in school, I'd shave
off hours of sleep for my hobbies...
Lucky Star!
Tamura-san, what's wrong?
You've been doing all sorts
of things for a while now...
Oh, when you draw, you
know how you end up with
the same facial expression as
the character you're drawing?
I see... So you were drawing?
I didn't know that you
drew manga, Tamura-san.
Though it's mainly doujin.
What kind of manga do you draw?
Well, normal four-panel comic strips...
Or romance manga between my
favorite game characters...
This is so hard to answer!
The lottery ticket that I bought
the other day on a trial basis
was a winner for 3,000 yen.
So I thought that I was in luck
from early in the morning.
Wow, amazing!
But on my way here, my bicycle got a flat
tire and it costs money to repair it,
and I had to buy a lunch at the store
to replace the one I dropped...
Just like it was planned to be, the
3,000 yen cleanly left my hands.
Truth is stranger than fiction, they say.
But, you know,
It's probably good fodder for manga,
so I'm thinking that it's all right.
So tough...
"Thunderous roar"
"Roar"
"Thud"
To an artist, her writing
hand is like her life...
This is one thing that I need
to risk my life to save...
So tough...
Wow, just as I thought, you're
really good, Tamura-san!
No, I've been in a slump
lately... That's a failure.
Oh, but of what I've recently done,
I think this one went pretty well.
"Objection!"
That's right. Often, the
person looking at art doesn't
understand where the artist is being
picky, or the subtleties in the art.
I knew that, I knew that.
Oh, drat!
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
My favorite mechanical pencil!
I was drawing yesterday, and left
it on top of my desk back home!
Shall I lend you one?
No, it has to be that one, or rather,
how it draws is totally different...
You're right, mechanical
pencils are all the same.
Yeah, I know that. I knew
you'd react that way.
And so, I got lost, and couldn't
get out for three hours...
What's wrong, Tamura-san?
So embarrassing!
What are they thinking, to
dress like that on the streets?
Coats?
Wow! Aren't they hot, dressing
like that in the summer?
So this pain is only for those in the know?
Hold on a sec, I'm going to text a friend!
Welcome!
Wow, it's crowded.
I'm going to put our names down on the sheet.
And I ended up playing games
with Sis until really late...
Miss Suzaku? Miss Suzaku, party of three?
They're calling us.
But Tamura-san, that was a different name...
Sometimes, I feel like writing down
the name of my favorite character.
You just want to feel the character
close to you or something...
"Haruhi" "Kyon" "Yuki" "Mikuru"
"Itsuki" "Current turn: Haruhi"
There really are people like
me around everywhere I go...
"Letter from the Nurse's Office"
Thank you.
I wish I could be slender and
tall like you, Iwasaki-san.
"Fantasy"
Minami-chan, I guess you can say that
you're someone I admire... so...
Yutaka...
"Reality"
Kobayakawa-san, I'm sure you'll still grow.
Perhaps you'll end up taller than me.
More than you, Iwasaki-san?
"Fantasy"
Minami-chan... Minami-chan...
Minami-chan.
No! That is the law of the land, so no!
Or rather, the last one
is obviously different!
Calm down, me!
Tamura-san, are you all right?
You seem a bit pale...
Actually, the submission deadline
for the upcoming event was today...
I sent out the manuscript I worked on
all night via courier this morning.
Oh, but when I'm working so
desperately for something,
I feel like I'm shining from within...
So tough!
Tamura-san!
What is yaoi?
Which meaning are you asking about?
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Time passes by quickly, this is already
the 19th episode of Lucky Channel!
It's starting to feel like we're
finally nearing the climax!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
And I'm Minoru Shiraishi, her
assistant. My best regards.
In any case, Akira-sama, you
seem to be in a fine mood.
♪ Helper helper submarine,
something good's gonna happen! ♪
Did something wonderful happen to you?
Do you think something has?
Well...
Never mind.
Oh, being on TV really wears on one's nerves.
Fatigue builds up after 19 episodes.
I feel like I want to
take it slow and unwind,
soaking in a hot spring or something.
I wonder if I can't get something
like that vacation prize,
like the quiz show in the main show.
Then you have to start by becoming
a contestant on that quiz show.
Oh, but vacations are so
nice! I'd like to go myself.
When you travel through lands you
don't know, it clears the soul!
There's nothing better!
You like to travel?
Of course, of course! I love it!
I've actually gone to all
sorts of places, you know.
I climbed up Mt. Takao, and I
had that trip to Jougashima.
I'm an outdoor kind of guy!
So you like to travel.
Lately, I think strolls in
the woods calm your nerves,
with Mother Nature all around you.
Oh, that's wonderful. Mother
Nature, a stroll in the woods.
It calms your nerves down.
Doesn't it just?
Far from the noise of the city,
leaving your body to quiet nature!
It soothes both the body and the mind!
It's good. Isn't Mother Nature wonderful?
Don't you think Mother Nature is wonderful?
You want to go for a stroll in the woods?
Are you serious? Can I?
Oh no, if I can, I'll go!
Yeah, then, it's been decided...
Minoru's Mother Nature Tour.
So huge!
Take it.
And they have what you wish they had.
Um, this...
Where am I going?
Mt. Fuji.
Well, but I've already
been up a mountain once...
Yeah. Not the mountain itself,
but the big forest at its base.
I want you to go into Fuji Forest.
Oh, I see, the forest...
Who? Oh, me?
Yup.
Um, so after getting there, what should I do?
Go scoop up some water.
Water?
I want to drink the famous Fuji
water, so get some from the forest.
You're kidding! You can just buy
it in convenience stores and stuff!
I want it fresh!
I won't be alone, right? Alone? Alone?!
Someone is going to come with me, right?
It's all right, you'll be fine.
The director and producer will
sacrifice themselves to go with you.
Aren't you glad?
Now, don't you just waste time there!
I see...
Don't cross the line between life and death!
Please, let go of me!
Oh, it's already this late?
Everyone, we'll have a lovely guest
for the next episode of Lucky Channel!
Look forward to it! Bye-nee!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You didn't have to have an excuse
to drive him out, did you?
Just hurry up and ch--
♪ A portion of my body is hot! Hot! ♪
Hello there! This is Minoru Shiraishi.
Now, I'd like you to listen: Otokono
Ikizama (The Life of a Man)!
♪ Hah, I want to be just like that guy ♪
♪ Plunging forward looking
only in front of you ♪
♪ Once you make a decision,
as far as you can go ♪
♪ Oh, once you bite
down, you don't let go ♪
♪ Oh, soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle, soft-shelled turtle! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle, soft-shelled turtle-le! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle-le, soft-shelled
turtle-le, soft-shelled turtle-le! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle, soft-shelled turtle-le! ♪
♪ Mentally and physically,
completely naked! ♪
♪ Oh, soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle, soft-shelled turtle! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle-le, soft-shelled turtle! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle-le, soft-shelled
turtle-le, soft-shelled turtle-le! ♪
♪ Soft-shelled turtle, soft-shelled
turtle, soft-shelled turtle-le! ♪
♪ Mentally and physically, comp-- ♪
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the next
episode of Lucky Star?
Nanako here.
Yui-chan here!
I always think that before summer starts,
you have all sorts of expectations and
it gets you really excited and stuff,
but before you know it, it's
over without you doing anything.
Well, it's true that there's not
many special things going on.
In the first place, I can't think
that a relationship with someone
you met in such an irresponsible
time period would last long at all.
I don't know about that.
Well, both of us still have time,
so we should each do our best!
Er, yes?
Oh, that one is hard to reply to...
Next episode: Ways to Spend Summer.
I'm looking!