I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
Vampire
Mikaela
It's a Horseman of the Apocalypse!
Run!
It'll kill us all!
Come, my sword.
We're saved...
We'll get the same protection as Osaka now!
"Protection," he says.
What a joke.
Livestock isn't to be protected. It's to be owned.
Don't you agree?
But really, you sure are strong.
They say you became a vampire by drinking the blood of Third Progenitor Krul Tepes.
Is that true?
Regardless of that, he acted out of line and took all the glory for himself.
Once a human, always a human.
Their greed knows no bounds.
I'm not interested in "glory." Do as you wish.
This district will now be under the protective custody and rule of the vampires.
Your safety will be assured, and in exchange, we will require your blood.
Um...
You saved my life out there.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to offer you my blood by way of gratitude.
If it's for you, I...
This is a memory.
We might as well be livestock!
That's why you should start a revolution with me, Mika.
We can't be treated like this forever.
Jeez, Yuu. You're as shortsighted as always.
What do you mean, "always"?
There's no beating a vampire with brute strength.
It's all about the brains.
I have a plan.
Let's escape from this world.
Just leave it to me!
A memory from before my humanity's end.
And because of my naïve plan...
Hurry up and go!
You idiot!
G-Good...
Even if only Yuu was able to run away, I...
What happened?
Lord Ferid has been shot.
How dare you lay a hand on a noble?
Step away from the boy.
For he is mine.
M-My queen.
What brings you here?
Oh, dear.
He'll be dead soon at this rate.
So, care to explain yourself,
Ferid Bathory?
My, hello to you too.
If it isn't our vampire queen, Krul Tepes.
It's certainly been a while.
You're as beautiful as always.
Why, thank you.
Your smile is as rotten as ever, I see.
Now, that's just rude.
I was shot in the head only a moment ago, you know.
My love for you is the only thing
that's keeping up this smile of mine.
Oh? Love for me, and not my power?
Well, that too.
So you're telling me that you, a Seventh Progenitor,
were shot by a human child?
You can't be serious.
Oh, but it's the truth.
Or rather, you allowed the Seraphs that I owned to escape on purpose.
One managed to run away,
and the other's on the verge of death.
If you'd like to explain yourself, then now's—
I think one of us has significantly more explaining to do than the other.
Toying with the curse of the Seraphs is against the law.
And should the Progenitor Council
just happen to hear about this, you'll—
I'm sorry, what was that? I couldn't hear you.
I said, if this ever gets out to the Progenitor Council...
I might have made her a bit too angry.
I'm not sure I heard you.
Perhaps you'd like to repeat that?
How awful of you, Krul.
I can just stick it back on, but I still feel pain, you know.
Would you like me to do the same for your head?
Now that would be a problem.
Very well, you win this round.
I won't involve myself in this case any longer.
You can take my word for it.
Besides, even I would think twice before crossing you.
As you wish.
But if I catch your nose where it doesn't belong again...
Not to worry.
I value my life, too.
I'll see you soon, Krul.
I love you, after all.
Tell me, human. Would you like to live?
I can give you life—an eternal life.
No...
I see. You don't want to live.
But I'm afraid you have no choice.
Drink my blood, and cast your humanity away.
And so I abandoned the human within me.
Whoa, now. What was that for?
You looking for a fight?
What? The hell are you on about?
That fuckin' hurt.
Bring it on!
Yuu, what happened to your face?
I walked into a telegraph pole.
T-Telegraph pole?
Yeah, a telegraph pole.
A really damn ugly one.
What are you saying?
You sure took your sweet time.
Oh, it's just you.
Wow, your face...
I suppose another suspension is in order?
I wasn't in a fight.
I'll let it go this time.
Today's finally the day, huh?
Yup, it sure is!
Our training for the
Moon Demon Company starts today—
Who needs training?
Just let me at 'em already!
Fine with me.
If you're going to skip training,
feel free to head out without a weapon or uniform.
You might as well send me out stark-naked.
Excuse us.
I've brought these two along, Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
Lieutenant Colonel!
Hm? Oh.
All right!
Listen up, kids.
These two transfer students are the reason for your supervising teacher's rare appearance today.
Not to rain on your parade or anything,
but a supervising teacher
is supposed to attend class every day.
Did I ask for your opinion?
So, uh, yeah. These are the guys.
Hyakuya Yuuichirou and Saotome Yoichi.
The dumbass and the wuss.
Who are you calling a dumbass?
It's time to face the truth.
Now go introduce yourself or something.
Don't need to.
I ain't here to make friends.
And I'll say it once more for you lot, too.
I don't plan on getting all chummy with you guys!
Uh, Yuu...
Listen up, and listen well!
I don't know what you losers
have been studying until now,
but it's all a huge waste of time!
I'll be taking the best weapon for myself.
Class dismissed!
Says who, moron?
Did you even learn anything from the general ed class?
I've had enough. Sit your ass down.
Your seat's over there.
Screw Guren and his brute force.
Uh, 'scuse me.
This is my seat now, so move it.
Hey, you hear me or what?
The hell do you want?
Is it lunchtime already?
You're that freakin' telegraph pole!
What are you doing here?
Screw you. That's my line.
And the hell do you mean, "telegraph pole"?
You bumped into me, damn it!
What's wrong with those two clowns?
If I recall correctly, I also placed
Kimizuki from the general ed class
You were the one spacing out, jackass!
What the fuck was that?!
under your watch.
You wanna go?!
That you did.
And the result?
Need me to paint you a picture?
C'mon, are you taking this seriously?
But I did watch.
This morning, Kimizuki Shihou provoked
Hyakuya Yuuichirou in order to gauge his ability.
And I suppose you just stood there, did you?
I hid somewhere and enjoyed the show.
Seriously, you had one job...
Enough already!
Y-Yuu?
Just leave them.
Right. It's been a while since I last showed up, but let's start class.
Excuse me.
May I have a word, Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose?
Hell no. And don't just come in without permission.
It's about the Infernal Arms Aptitude Test next week.
It goes without saying that I'll be granted a trial for the top-ranked Black Demon Series, right?
Which part of "don't come in" didn't you understand?
I should have the top grades for all subjects.
Why are you in such a rush to acquire power?
Why would you ask?
The army has all the intel, right?
Of course we know.
You need money to cure your sister,
who's infected with the Apocalypse Virus.
The Moon Demon Company is composed of the elite.
If you manage to join and perform well,
you may get unlimited access to treatment
normally unavailable to the public.
But performing well in your current state
is out of the question.
Forget about even touching an Infernal Arm—
it'll just feed on your desires.
And you're saying that ape, Hyakuya, would be any better?
Well, who knows?
But he's broken free
from a demon once, at the very least.
And surprisingly enough,
I think he looks out for his friends too.
That's bullshit!
I'm stronger than him!
Power alone isn't enough!
That's why you need friends.
Don't think you can shoulder it all on your own.
Otherwise,
when the time comes, you'll be possessed
by a demon, and that'll be that.
Demons thrive on desperation and rage.
As you are right now, your desires will only swallow you whole, and you'll turn into a demon yourself.
Okay, pay attention!
In preparation for next week's Infernal Arms Aptitude Test,
I'll be judging each one of your abilities.
If you can't produce results here,
you won't be able to take the test.
So give it your best shot!
I-I wonder if I'll be any good...
In any case, I'll be taking the strongest weapon for sure!
There you go again.
Today, I'll be evaluating how well you operate within a team.
Please pair up.
Wait.
What?
P-Pair up?
Uh, Yoichi...
Yoichi, hey, Yoichi! Let's pair up!
Oh, sure.
Uh, hold up.
C'mon, you guys! Hey!
Um... Anyone?
Seriously?
Is everyone ready?
Then let's begin.
I'll be grading you appropriately,
so get your game faces on!
Seriously?
No way...
Cursed army puppets, huh?
They're clumsy and slow.
Let's deal with them quickly and boost our grades.
Which puppet were you even going for?
Are you trying to mess with me?
You're the one messing—
Ow!
Team Hyakuya-Kimizuki gets minus ten points.
Pardon the interruption.
Kimizuki, please make your way
to the hospital ward immediately.
Your sister Mirai's condition has rapidly deteriorated.
You have a sister?
Shut up. Stay out of this.
Sorry for the trouble.
Please disregard that and continue the training.
Hey, are you serious?
This isn't the time for that.
Your sister's in trouble, right?
I thought I told you to stay out of this.
I have to perform well here!
I've gotten this far.
Even if it means abandoning your sister?
Drop it. Mind your own business.
I will join the Moon Demon Company.
Please continue.
Are you stupid?!
Your family needs you!
If they die...
If your family dies, you'll never see them again!
Kimizuki. We managed to pull through today,
but fighting this virus
with conventional medical equipment isn't...
I understand.
But I'll join the Moon Demon Company soon, and then I'll transfer her to the army's facility.
Please take care of her a little while longer.
I'm glad she's okay.
You may be a real bastard on the outside,
but it's all for your sister, huh?
Why didn't you just say so?
But of course, I'm still not letting you have the strongest Infernal—
It's all your fault.
I got graded poorly because of you.
I won't be able to join the Moon Demon Company.
Which means she can't be saved.
Don't give up on her life that easily.
Graded poorly?
Can't be saved?
Get real.
I'm going to get what I want, no matter what.
Neither the army nor the Moon Demon Company
is gonna get in my way.
But here you are, ready to give up on your family?
What? Who said anything about giving up?!
Damn it!
What the hell is your problem?
It's your fault...
But you're right.
Huh?
I'll thank you just this once, since I was able to be
with my sister during a critical time.
Sorry.
You got stuck with poor grades thanks to my problems, too.
I'll be the judge of that.
You're a serious pain in the ass, man.
We nobles with Progenitor blood are gathered here today for one reason: a new threat!
Running rampant across the whole of Northern Tokyo
is a human organization called
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
They are killing our brothers and sisters,
expanding their territory,
A human organization.
and flirting with forbidden magic as they desire.
According to our intel, they are once again experimenting on the Seraphs of the End.
If we leave them as they are,
a plague like that of eight years ago
will break out once more.
Therefore...
we have decided to crush
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
This is war.
We will wipe out the corrupt humans
so that this world's balance may be preserved!
War, and the Seraphs of the End...
Yuu...
I'll rescue you soon.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Contract
with the Black Demon
"Contract with the Black Demon."