On that day,
mankind was morbidly reminded...
of the fear of living under their rule...
and the humiliation of being trapped like caged birds.
Men, prepare to fight!
There's only one target!
We must eliminate it and secure mankind's first outside base!
Target approaching!
Split into five teams like we practiced!
We'll act as a distraction!
All assault teams, prepare to engage!
Close in from all sides!
Have a taste of mankind's strength!
To You in Two Thousand Years
The Fall of Shiganshina (1)
Huh, Mikasa?
Let's head home.
Why are you here?
Were you so sound asleep that you forgot where you are?
Well, I feel like I had this really long dream.
What was it about again?
I can't remember.
Eren, why are you crying?
Year 845 Shiganshina District
Listen!
The wall was built upon the wisdom of God!
The wall itself is a work of God!
Not one soul shall ever dare to desecrate this wall!
Don't tell anyone that I was crying.
I won't.
But if you were crying for no good reason,
maybe you should have your dad take a look at you.
Don't be stupid!
As if I'd ever tell him about that!
Whatcha been cryin' about, Eren?
Hanneth...
Did Mikasa yell at you or something?
Huh?
Why the hell would I be crying?!
You reek of booze!
That's fine, right?
You're drinking again?
Care to join us?
Uh, but what about your job?
We're manning the gates today.
We work up quite the appetite spending all day here.
Alcohol just happens to be one of the drinks we enjoy from time to time, but it's nothing to worry about.
And if the time comes, will you be able to fight?!
What time are you talking about?
That's obvious!
If they break through the wall and enter the city!
Oh, ouch...
Hey, Eren, there's no need to shout.
The doc's boy sure is lively.
If they manage to break through the wall, we'll take care of 'em.
But you know, that hasn't happened in over a hundred years.
But we're in the most danger once we let our guard down!
That's what my dad told me!
Dr. Jäger, huh?
Well, I guess he's right.
He saved our city from a plague once.
We're all deeply indebted to him.
But this is a bit different.
If you become a soldier, you might have a chance at spotting them while reinforcing the wall.
But I can't think of a single way they would be able to get past this 50-meter-tall wall.
S-So you're not even prepared to fight them at all?
Nope.
What the hell?!
Then stop calling yourselves "border guards."
"Wall builders" would suit you better!
That ain't bad either.
But you know, Eren...
If we have to become active guards,
that means that the worst has come.
As long as we get to live like careless freeloaders, life's more peaceful for everyone.
It's true that even though we can't go beyond the wall,
we can eat, sleep, and live our lives in peace.
But isn't that the same as living like cattle?
This kid's a brave one.
Even though he can't do anything about it, right, Hanneth?
Ah, yeah.
Hey, Eren!
That kid's a weird one.
Don't tell me he wants to join the Recon Corps...
Eren...
You better stop thinking about the Recon Corps.
What, are you gonna start making fun of them too?
It's not that I'm making fun of them.
The Recon Corps is back!
They're opening the front gate!
Let's go, Mikasa!
The heroes are making their triumphant return!
Dammit, I can't see anything.
So few of them are returning.
Looks like they took quite the beating.
That's what happens when you go outside the wall like that.
Moses!
I'm sorry, but I can't find my son, Moses.
Where is my son?
She's Moses's mother...
Bring it out.
That was all...
we were able to bring back.
But my son...
He was useful, right?
It didn't have to be anything great...
But my son contributed...
He contributed to mankind's retaliation, right?!
Of course!
No...
This expedition...
We...
No, once again...
We didn't make any progress at all!
I've been nothing but a failure!
Getting my soldiers killed one after another...
And we haven't been able to uncover a single thing about them!
This is horrible.
Damn right.
At this rate, we're just fattening them up by sending out men as free meals.
What the hell are you doing, you damn brat?!
Hey!
Wait, Mikasa!
Get back here!
Mikasa, let go already!
What are you doing?!
The firewood's scattered all over the place!
Eren...
Have you changed your mind about joining the Recon Corps?
Help me pick these up.
There aren't that many.
Current Disclosable Information
About the Walls (1)
Mankind lives within three layers of walls.
The outermost is Wall Maria,
the middle is Wall Rose,
and the innermost is Wall Sina.
Current Disclosable Information
About the Walls (2)
The distances between each of the walls vary.
There is 100km between Maria and Rose,
130km between Rose and Sina,
and 250km from Sina to the center.
We're back.
Welcome home.
Wow, Eren...
Seems like you really worked hard for a change.
Yeah...
What was that for?!
Your red ears are telling me that you're lying.
Mikasa gave you a hand, didn't she?
Huh, are you leaving, Dad?
Work?
Yeah, I have to see a few patients.
It'll take two or three days.
Eren was saying...
that he wants to join the Recon Corps.
Mikasa, I told you not to say anything!
Eren!
What are you thinking?!
Have you any idea how many have died after going outside the wall?!
I do!
Then why?!
Eren.
Why do you want to go outside?
I want to know what the outside world is like.
I don't want to spend my whole life behind the wall without knowing anything!
And if there's no one to continue what they started,
then all the lives that have been lost were for nothing!
All right.
The ferry will be here soon, so I better get going.
Wait, Honey...
Talk some sense into Eren!
Carla, you can't simply talk someone out of their desire for knowledge and exploration.
Eren, when I come back,
I'll show you the secret room in the basement.
Really?!
Have a nice trip!
It's not happening.
Only a fool would join the Recon Corps.
A fool, you say?!
People who are happy living like cattle are way more foolish!
Eren!
Mikasa.
That boy has a habit of getting into trouble.
Make sure you have each other's backs when that happens, okay?
Okay.
What's wrong, you heretic?
If you've got a problem, then try to hit back!
As if I'd do that!
Then I'd be stooping down to your level!
Say what?!
You're only beating me up because you won't admit that I'm right and aren't able to prove me wrong!
Isn't that the same as admitting that you're wrong?!
Shut up, you smart ass!
Stop!
It's Eren!
That idiot's back for more!
He must really like getting his ass handed to him.
Let's teach him a lesson.
Yeah.
M-Mikasa's there too!
Shit! Run for it!
Look at that, running at the mere sight of me!
No, they ran because they saw Mikasa.
Ouch.
Are you okay, Armin?
I can stand on my own.
Okay...
Then I said that people will have to go outside one day,
but they hit me and called me a heretic.
Dammit...
Why does everyone start looking down on you when you mention wanting to go outside?
That's because there's been a hundred years of peace since we hid behind the wall.
People are afraid that going outside might let one of them in,
so the royal government has made
thinking about going outside a taboo.
If we want to risk our lives, that's our own business, right?
Forget about it.
No way.
That reminds me, thanks for screwing me over!
I can't recall saying that I'd cooperate.
How was it?
Well, they weren't exactly thrilled...
Figures...
Those who believe that the wall will protect us forever are insane.
Mama!
They say it's because the wall hasn't been breached in over a hundred years,
but there's no guarantee that it'll never happen.
What was that?
An explosion?
Over there!
Did something fall?
I have no idea.
Hey, Armin!
What's wrong?
What the hell are you looking at?
No way...
The wall...
It's 50 meters high!
It's one of them!
It's a Titan!
I-It...
broke a hole through the wall...
It's coming!
The Titans are inside!
We have to...
Eren!
My house is over there...
Mom is...
Mikasa!
It's all over...
The city's been invaded by Titans!
There's no way our house has been hit!
I just have to make this turn, and our house will be there, like always...
Mom!
Eren...
Mikasa, grab hold over there.
We need to move this beam!
Hurry, Mikasa!
I know!
The Titans have broken in, haven't they?
Eren, take Mikasa with you and run!
Hurry!
I won't run!
Hurry up and get out!
My legs have been crushed by the debris.
Even if I get out, I won't be able to run.
You understand, don't you?
I'll carry you on my back and run!
Why won't you ever do as I say?!
Can't you at least obey my last wish?!
Mikasa!
No, no!
At this rate, the three of us will...
Hanneth!
Take the kids and get out of here!
Don't think so lightly of me, Carla.
I'll kill that Titan and save the three of you!
Wait!
Don't fight that thing!
She's right that I can definitely save the two of them.
But with this, I can repay my debt!
Hey, Hanneth!
What the hell are you doing?!
Thank you.
Mom's...
She's still...
Eren! Mikasa!
Stay alive!
Don't leave me...
Stop it!
On that day,
mankind was morbidly reminded...
of the fear of living under their rule...
and the humiliation of being trapped like caged birds.
Preview
Shiganshina has fallen.
Now, humanity was only permitted to pray, scream, and then die.
Amidst all this, only Eren swore vengeance in his small heart...
On That Day
The Fall of Shiganshina (2)