Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Do you
have anybody you admire?
Someone you think is cool,
someone wonderful,
or someone you wish you could be like.
To me, that is Miss Layla.
This is a chance to maybe appear
on stage with the person I admire.
I have to get this chance by
all means! I have to! I have to!
Yaritai koto wa nani
Sou kikareru tabi
Aoi sora miageta
Kotae wa only my heart
Honto ni daiji na kotoba
wa kantan ni wa iwanai
Hikari ga yubisasu
basho e to hashiridasu yo
Dakishimetai mono nara
nakitai hodo mune ni aru
Egakitsuzukete yuku kitto take it someday
Shiroi kumo ga nagareru
chiheisen no mukou ni
Naranderu mirai wa itsumo soba ni aru kara
"A Hot, Amazing, New Production."
So, it ended...
my first leading role.
Sora...
Wh-What?
Iyaan...
Iyaan... Iyaan...
What?
Ian! Ian!
Ian?
Yes, Ian, in the flesh!
He's here!
By any chance, are you talking about Ian
who co-starred with Miss Layla in the movie?
Yes!
You're not particularly his fan. Right, Sora?
Well, I'm not particularly his...
Then help us!
Okay, but what kind of help?
I didn't know you meant this kind of help.
There he is. There he is!
Where, where?
He is real!
An amazing million dollar smile!
America's lover.
I can't imagine anyone other than Layla
playing the main role for the next movie.
After all, this is the first
movie that I'm going to produce.
I've already told you
formally that I'm not interested.
I know how you feel, Layla.
There it is again, the million dollar smile!
She is under pressure,
and puzzled over what to do.
So, Kalos, I want you to persuade her, too.
I know you understand that coming
to my place is the best choice for her.
Go ahead, please persuade her.
Layla, I think you should go.
Yes, I think I should.
What! So, okay?!
Bravo!
Hey, it's me.
About Layla, she said okay.
Yep.
Good-bye, then.
Oh, good-bye.
Excuse me.
Sure. Wha--?
What? Uh. Hey!
Yes?
When you said "go,"
what did you mean by that?
We're supposed to go to see the
stage equipment for a new production.
You're kidding! No one told me!
You just invited yourself to follow.
Oh...
Then...
There's a profound
reason why we're doing this.
Please stop embarrassing yourself.
Yes...
It's perfect. You should come with us.
What? Me?
Why... me?
Wait, Layla!
Oh, Mr. Ian also followed them.
Let's go, Sora.
Well... I would like to go, but...
It's still in a trial stage.
Anyway, please take a look.
Hey, what took you so long?
This is...
This is the equipment for ropewalking
in the new production, Arabian Nights.
In the climax, you will perform
action scenes on top of this.
Wow... It sounds amazing.
But, after all, it's just ropewalking.
It's nothing new to you.
On the other hand, my next
movie will be a little different.
It moved!
By the time you perform, more
complicated moves will be possible.
It sounds interesting.
I understand, Layla.
Then, I'll use a ship in my movie, too.
Oh, it's me.
Prepare a ship that I can use for my movie.
Yep. A big one.
This is pretty tricky.
You're going to have a one-on-one
fight with a bandit on top of this.
Also, when you perform before the audience,
the ship will be enveloped in flames.
--What?!
--Fire?!
This is ridiculous, Layla.
I think you should stop--
It sounds interesting.
Fire, fire!
Layla gets excited about
scenes that have fire in them!
Order gunpowder!
Yuri, let's start practicing immediately.
It seems I'm not the one you are
going to have a fight scene with.
What?
Then, I wonder if they're going
to audition for my opponent's role.
Well, our main sponsor Mr. Kenneth
already nominated the person, and...
You're not saying...
That's right.
You and Sora will co-star in
the climax of Arabian Nights.
What?!
I'm going to co-star with... Miss Layla...
Both you and Kenneth
must be out of your minds.
Even the Little Mermaid
could hardly be called a success.
But, Mr. Kenneth says if you
and Sora are going to co-star,
he wouldn't mind doubling the budget.
Why...
Sora.
Yes!
Do you have confidence?
Uh...
If you don't have confidence,
excuse yourself from this role.
Mr. Kenneth will understand.
Kalos, she cannot do this.
I think it's pitiful to pressure her
more than what we're doing now.
Anyhow, it's a bit too much.
Let's ask the scriptwriter to rewrite the
action scenes using Yuri instead of Sora.
Mr. Kenneth will be very disappointed,
but we have no choice.
I...
Miss Layla, I want to try it.
What?
Let me do this, Miss Layla.
Please!
Are you serious?
I am!
You're still a newcomer. How rude!
Right, Layla?
I still don't have confidence, but...
You don't have confidence
and you still want to do it?
Oh, my God!
Please test me.
If you're just going to
give up after the test,
you should resign now.
It's a nuisance if you're going to prepare
yourself with a half-baked attitude.
That's right. That's right.
Let me know when you make up your mind.
Wait, Layla!
Excuse me...
You should make up your own mind.
Ropewalking on a rolling ship...
that sounds tough.
Even Miss Layla fell from the rope.
Sora, have you ever done ropewalking?
Well... a little...
Hey, Naegino!
You're playing circus again!
I'm sorry.
Sora, you're weird.
What?
Usually, people don't volunteer
for that if that is all you did.
What? Really?
If it was me, I'd definitely excuse myself.
But, you're going to do it, right?
Er... I wonder...
if it's impossible after all?
I went over budget because of
the gunpowder I ordered for you.
From the beginning of the
movie, there's fire, fire, fire!
To the end, the whole
movie is fire, fire, fire!
What do you think? Excited, aren't you?
Why...
Why does it have to be Sora?
Why am I so concerned about her?
Why?
One day, it will be her
the audience comes to see.
Oh, it seems like you
finally made up your mind.
Ian...
Layla...
I hope you find a wonderful leading actress.
Thank-- What?!
Excuse me.
It's me!
Cancel the gunpowder.
You can't?! Seriously?!
You need someone to talk to?
I've never felt this way.
I wonder what this is...
It's about Sora, isn't it?
She has something you don't.
What?
She takes chances.
You...
Well, no one here at Kaleido Stage,
including myself, takes chances like she does.
Of course not.
That's true.
But what Kalos wants from her is...
Probably...
Of course, I will support your ideas.
Please take me to Kaleido Stage.
As you wish.
Excuse me...
In the end... do you think
I should excuse myself from this role?
I thought I told you to
make up your own mind.
That's true.
Then... this time, I will...
Wait!
Miss Layla...
Kalos, let's have a test.
I'm going to take a test, too,
about whether I can co-star with her.
Then, I want you to decide.
All right.
The deadline is a week
from now. Is that okay?
Y-Yes.
I look forward to seeing your performance.
My performance?
I'm gonna burn!
Or, it's more like I can't breathe...
Why...
I'm suffocating...
I'm gonna die.
Zzzz... Zzzz...
First thing in the morning,
and you still treat me terrible.
Which is more terrible?!
Thanks to you, I dreamt
I was burning to death!
I will teach you one good thing.
What?
In a story like Arabian Nights,
you should say you're "covered in flames"
instead of saying "burned to death."
I'm sorry.
That's it. Very good.
Look at the front.
Don't look down.
As I thought, Sora has a talent.
Yes, she does.
But she still has a long way to go
before she can co-star with Miss Layla.
Since you're getting
comfortable with ropewalking,
let's try rolling the
ship a little without the bar.
What! Already?!
We don't have much time left.
So, we have to keep going.
O-Okay...
One more time!
If this were a real stage,
you'd be barbecued.
Barbecued?
Okay, then!
Hey, she's doing it!
How's she doing, Ken?
To tell the truth, she has a long way to go,
but her maneuvers are getting bold.
I think she is getting
used to using the rope.
Hm... That's my girl, Sora.
Oh, Mia, Anna.
Did you finish your lessons today?
Yes.
Why don't you have a short break?
Thank you.
But, I want to practice a little more.
Sora!
Miss Sarah.
Sora, we're going.
What? Where are we going?
To overcome your weak points.
My... weak points?
Excuse me...
Katsu!
The resolved mind has no cares!
Thank you.
This is Taurus's star cluster, Pleiades.
--And this star is Aldebaran.
--Excuse me...
And we are in Aldebaran now!!
What?
Even though your body burns on
this earth, you don't feel the heat!
Yes, Master.
What?
We're not afraid of the flame.
We're not afraid of the flame!
Your weak point is your
fear of being barbequed.
What?
You overcame that fear, Sora.
If you're not afraid of
falling into the flame,
you should be able to move more boldly.
Yes... Thank you very much.
I wonder if I'm misunderstanding something.
--Oh, no. Not at all.
- -Really?
Yes!
Good. Then, good luck.
It's almost time to switch with Miss Layla.
Okay.
You're getting better, don't you think?
You're getting quite stable.
Really?
Thank you, Ken.
What's wrong?
You're not doing well?
I started getting ideas
on how to do it right.
That's good, then.
Yes.
But even if I manage to
be able to do ropewalking,
I'm not sure if I can pass the test.
I look forward to seeing your performance.
If you can do this much in this short time...
Don't you think Miss Layla will
acknowledge your performance?
Yes.
But I think something is missing...
Hm?
Come on!
What's wrong?
My locker won't open!
Sora!
Who'd do something like this?
Didn't you do it yourself?
If you get hurt, you can, like,
get out of taking Miss Layla's test.
So, you two did it.
You're so mean!
Diabolo...
Diabolo!
What's wrong with that girl?
She's like, happy.
My performance...
Pushing yourself too hard
will not produce a good result.
Why don't you have a break?
Take a bath...
Oh, sorry.
When you worry, you
should hasten to take a bath...
Oh, sorry.
Take a bath...
Sora! Hey, stop!
What?! Fool, where are you?
Here!
Your jump is too high!
Hey...
Ouch...
Look closely at your diabolo!
Good! Calm down!
It's time to switch.
Oh... yes.
Finally. Tomorrow is the day.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
Tomorrow...
My time for practice is over...
Ken, thank you.
Tomorrow, I will do my best.
Don't you want to practice a little more?
Of course.
But... I...
Come with me.
What?
Yo! I've been waiting for you guys.
Mr. Policeman.
Hm? Excuse me, but aren't you the
doctor who took care of my father?
Yes. I'm Kate.
It's nice to meet you.
Are you dating?
Well...
It's nothing like that.
We're just childhood friends.
What did you mean when
you said you've been waiting?
When I consulted with Mr. Policeman,
he told me that Kate knows
someone who works at Marine Park.
What?
All my family members are
fans of your Little Mermaid.
Oh... Thank you!
Wow, this is a real one!
How is it, Ken?
It's perfect.
Are you okay?
Okay, okay.
Sorry, but it's almost time, I have to....
No, not at all.
Thank you very much.
Well, if you managed to
do this much in one week,
I think you did enough.
It's true.
I still think your last jump is too high.
You have to control yourself a little...
But, of course, that's just like Sora.
Certainly, it makes me nervous.
If you're not afraid of falling into the flame,
you should be able to move more boldly.
Sora?
Not afraid of falling?
It may be okay to fall...
What?
Wonderful.
You're amazing, Layla!
Then, next is Sora.
Yes.
Then, next will be the finish!
Sink or swim.
I have to give it a try.
I have to! I have to! I have to!
It's high!
That is too high.
She will be bounced by the rope.
--What?
--Wow...
You're pretty good, Sora!
You did better than I thought.
So, Layla, what do you think?
Still unimpressed?
Not at all, Mr. Kenneth.
I'm looking forward to finding out
what kind of stage Sora and I can do.
Miss Layla...
It's true.
You have something I don't possess.
What?
But, if you're going to
appear on stage with me,
I expect you to prepare for it accordingly.
Yes!
Then I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you as well.
When you sabishii toki doushitemasuka
Never say sonna no wakannai
Nemuru asobu magazine mekuru
Sabishii toki wa sabishii yo
Mienai denpa ga kyou mo
tulututu machi ni tobikau
Anyway kokoro no bekutoru
so many reason hanashiteru
Jiyuu ni sora o tobitai keredo
Hane o hirogeru basho ga nai
Demo shinjiteru
Katachi no nai mirai ga aru yo
Katachi ni shitai watashi ga iru
Kanashikutemo machigai demo
Omou mama fly to the free
"Next Kaleido Star"
After all, you and she
are like oil and water.
And so, I'm going to appear on
stage with Miss Layla for the first time.
But, because of me, we can't
harmonize our performance at all.
I'm going to stay in your room for a while.
What? Seriously?
Besides, what was waiting for me
was a serious special
training which was unimaginable.
Training! Training!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Competition Calls Up A Storm."
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...