Dear  Oreki Houtarou,
I am currently writing to you from Benares.
Although late, please accept my congratulations for passing your entrance exams.
As I understand, you decided upon Kamiyama High.
Now that you have begun high school,
let me give you one piece of advice as your sister.
Join the Classics Club!
It has a long-running history,
and I too was a member during my high school days.
I have heard that the club currently has no members remaining.
As nobody has joined this year, they plan to to disband it.
As an alumnus of the club, I cannot allow that to happen.
Houtarou,
please protect the stage of your sister's youth, the Classics Club.
All you need to do is sign up for the club.
It's not like you have anything better to do, right?
Yours sincerely,
Oreki Tomoe.
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight!
It's been one month since the revival of the Classics Club.
Activities of the esteemed Classics Club
Earth Sci. Prep. room
It ended up being much easier to visit the clubroom than I expected.
Good afternoon!
Hi.
Whenever I'm bored after classes, I just drop by.
Have some.
I brought them from home.
Take whichever you'd like.
Thanks.
As long as it's not too tiring,
I don't mind being around others. I'm not antisocial.
This is a waste of time.
Doesn't that mean you'll save nine?
That's a stitch in time.
Was that a pun?
Don't ask that.
That's not the point!
Is it a waste of time?
Yes! A waste!
What is?
This whole afternoon!
We can't be productive if we have no purpose!
Thank you for those words of wisdom.
Then, is there something else you expect to get out of the Classics Club?
Yes, there is.
Oh?
It's a personal thing.
I've heard that before.
But right now, I'm talking about the club itself.
A club without club activities is no club at all!
We have no purpose.
Actually, we do.
We're going to release an anthology at the culture fair in October!
An anthology?
Yes!
Give it up.
That'd take way too much effort.
No! Nothing less than an anthology will do!
If you want to take part in the culture fair so badly, can't we do something easier?
Like a food stall?
Traditionally, those kinds of stalls aren't allowed at Kami High's culture fair.
I already submitted the costings for the anthology,
and our club advisor asked me to do it as well.
The Classics Club anthology is a 40-year-old tradition,
so they don't want us to just let it die.
Couldn't you have mentioned all this earlier?
I get it. I'll help.
Thanks!
What's this anthology supposed to consist of, anyway?
I don't know!
Come on.
Sorry. I figured we could work that out later.
If we can find one from a previous year, that might be a good starting point.
Let's take a look around!
Nothing here.
Then let's check the library!
Let's go!
What's the matter? You're coming too.
Come on.
I'd rather not.
It's Friday, so the library assistant will be—
Library
Oh? Oreki, huh?
Long time no see. Pity it couldn't stay that way.
Hey, Ibara. I thought I'd drop by to say "hi".
This is a sanctuary of culture.
Not your kind of place.
But I bet it fits you perfectly, Your Highness.
You're as annoying as ever.
If you just came here to bother me, go away.
Um...
Hey, Houtarou!
What a coincidence!
I see you two are still getting along well.
Living up to your name as Kaburaya Junior High's best couple, huh?
Can it.
He's such a drag.
A slug would be more fun to be around.
A... slug?
Anyway, Fuku, you've sure got guts to tell me that, knowing how I feel and all.
Sorry, sorry. Didn't mean to reopen old wounds.
You're letting your jokes get the better of you again.
You really oughta quit messing around.
Um, what's going on between those two?
She's had a crush on him since junior high.
Oh!
Chitanda, this is Ibara Mayaka.
She went to the same junior high as us.
Nice to meet you.
Mayaka, this is Chitanda Eru.
She's from the Classics Club I just joined.
Nice to meet you too.
By the way, what brings you two here?
Oh, right!
Ibara, there was something I wanted to ask about.
Go on...
Do you keep the previous anthologies published by the club here?
The Classics Club, that is.
The Classics Club...
I don't think we do...
If they're not on the shelves, they might be in the archives...
I see.
What do you need them for?
We're making a new anthology for the culture fair,
so we thought we'd better take a look at the previous ones.
Oh, you're doing something for the Kan'ya Fair?
I'm surprised Houtarou agreed.
It kinda happened after the fact.
What's the "Kan'ya Fair"?
You haven't heard of it?
It's what everyone calls Kamiyama High's culture fair.
This isn't another of your tall tales, is it?
It's true! My seniors in the Handicraft Club all call it that.
And you, Mayaka?
We call it that in the Book Club too.
"Kan'ya"...
How do you write that?
I don't know... though I asked around.
It probably started off as the "Kamiyama High School Culture Fair",
then became the "Kamiyama Culture Fair",
then the "Kan'yama Fair" and finally the "Kan'ya Fair", I guess.
So, Chitanda,
we might be able to find them if we take a look in the archives,
but the librarian is at a staff meeting right now, so we can't go in.
She'll be back in about half an hour, I think.
Want to wait?
What should we do?
I guess we could wait.
You might as well go home.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, Houtarou!
Mayaka, why don't you tell them that story?
I guess.
Oreki,
feel like putting your brain to work for once?
Nope.
What are you talking about?
The popular but unwanted book.
The popular but unwanted book?
It's a pretty weird story.
No matter how hard we thought, it never made any sense.
Mayaka and I were out of ideas.
Please tell us!
Every Friday, I'm here working as the assistant librarian.
And every Friday I see the same book in the returns tray.
For five weeks in a row.
That's weird enough on its own, right?
This is the book.
It's so pretty!
It's huge.
kamiyama high school:
fifty years of history
Can I take a peek inside?
Go on.
You too, Oreki.
It's just your typical school history book.
This doesn't look like an easy read.
It wouldn't be that unusual for someone to borrow this every week, right?
You've never borrowed a book from here, have you?
You can borrow books for up to two weeks.
So you wouldn't need to keep borrowing the same book every week.
And yet, this book gets returned every week.
Do you know who keeps borrowing it?
Of course.
The list of borrowers is at the back. Take a look.
Take a look at this, Oreki!
Class
Name
Borrowed
Suzuki Yoshie
Shima Saori
Yamaguchi
Ryouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Machita
Kyouko
A different person borrows it every week! And they all return it on the same day!
Replay
IV. XX, 15:40
IV. XX, 12:21
Yeah.
They all borrowed and returned it on the same day, for five weeks in a row.
We also know when it was borrowed.
They always borrow it during lunch break and return it after school.
What do you think?
Caught your interest?
Yes...
I can't stop thinking about it!
kamiyama high school:
fifty years of history
Just consider it for a moment, Oreki!
Damn you, Satoshi.
What do you think?
Pretty interesting, right?
You knew this would happen.
You figured out the story behind the locked door and the secret club so easily too!
What are you talking about?
Just an interesting side of Houtarou that you may not have heard about.
Cut it out. It sounds bad when you say it like that.
Anyway, I can't stop thinking about it!
I can.
I can't!
I can!
Oreki!
Quiet.
You too, Chitanda.
Sorry.
I was careless.
Trying to say no at this point would cost me significantly more energy.
Then...
I guess. Let's mull it over for a minute.
Thanks!
Fuku, was Oreki actually smart all along?
Not really.
But with pointless stuff like this,
every now and then he's not entirely useless.
You can shut up now.
And thus, summer has begun.
Summer begins
Hyouka
kamiyama high school:
fifty years of history
For five weeks in a row, different people have borrowed this book,
and returned it on the same day.
It would be easy to say it's a coincidence,
but Chitanda wouldn't accept that.
It doesn't have to be true.
It just has to be something Chitanda can accept.
Let's see.
Library
Assistant
Book
Lunch break
If they borrow it during lunch break and return after classes,
Book
they wouldn't have much time to read it.
Lunch break
break
plus
equals
65 Minutes
Insufficient
School
Home
If they didn't plan to take it home with them,
No
they could have just read it in the library instead.
kamiyama high school:
fifty years of history
Conclusion:
They didn't borrow the book because they wanted to read it.
Which means...
What can you do with a book besides reading it?
You could put a few books together to use as a pillow.
You could tie it to your arm and use it as a shield.
Put some effort into it!
That's right! There has to be some purpose that only this book could be used for.
Then what do you think, Chitanda?
That's right...
You could use it to flatten vegetables for pickling!
Forget I asked.
What kind of honor roll did she manage to end up on?
The local district's "Top Airheads"?
Let's look at this from another angle.
Suzuki  Yoshie
Shima  Saori
Yamaguchi  Ryouko
Sawakiguchi  Misaki
Machita  Kyouko
What can we conclude from the fact that someone different borrows it each week?
Looking at their names, they're all girls.
I can think of two possibilities.
Suzuki Yoshie
Someone
Yamaguchi Ryouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Someone
Machita Kyouko
Shima Saori
Someone
First, that they have nothing in common,
and this book is just popular on Friday afternoons.
Or that they use the book as a group,
Machita
Kyouko
Sawakiguchi Misaki
Tori Saori
Suzuki Yoshie
Yamaguchi
Ryouko
and borrow it in turns.
No group         Group
Popular, huh?
How about for fortune-telling?
Like this?
"Your lucky item this week is... the school history book!
If you borrow it Friday afternoon and return it the same day,
everything will go well with your boyfriend!"
Just kidding.
Don't be stupid. And remember, this happened five weeks in a row!
Don't mind me.
Here's what they have in common: They're all second-year girls.
Different classes, though.
I wonder if there's a reason they're all girls?
Hard to say.
If you randomly selected five students from this school,
there's a decent chance they'll all be girls.
Girls like to stick together too.
Could it be some kind of secret message?
Like returning it one way up to say you passed, and the other way up to say you failed.
I don't think they could use it as a message in that way.
Look.
I see.
You can't really tell which way up they are.
Well, I guess no matter how much Oreki thinks about it, that's as far as he can go.
Fuku spent ages thinking about it as... well...
What?
It smells.
Really?
I don't smell anything.
No, it does.
It's quite pungent.
Like paint thinner...
Now I'm certain!
Like a dog...
Well, if Chitanda is so certain about it,
I don't think she could be mistaken.
Which means...
Houtarou, your face says you figured something out.
Really?
Kind of. I can't be certain, though.
Chitanda, how about a bit of exercise?
There's this place I'd like you to go.
I got it!
No, I'm not going. Just you.
Just me?
Why?
Well...
You're right, Chitanda!
Don't let him just make you run around!
He can only be useful if someone uses him!
You really don't know when to shut up.
No, I just thought that if I needed to go somewhere you'd want come along.
Oh, I see.
So let's go, Oreki.
Welcome!
Thank you for honoring our restaurant.
We have prepared two menus for you.
Dull course
Vegetable Bites of Escapism
Terrine of Idleness and Lethargy
Armchair Meunière with Low Energy Sauce
Penne hardened with Lies, Golden Web style
Slowly stewed Status Quo, Mistake style
Tiramisu of Rejection and Peace
Colorful Course
Vegetable Bites of Danger
Sautè of Trouble and Effort
Tagliatelle of Wasted Effort
Trofie of Interest with Worthwhile Sauce
Provence style Curiosity roast
and Well Done Mille-feuille
Which one would you like?
The chef's suggestion is this one.
Oreki?
I get it, I get it.
PE class had to be called off today due to rain,
so I still have some energy left.
Okay!
Just how limited is your energy to begin with?
Drop it.
Let's go then.
Okay.
Wait!
I'm going too.
I'm a bit interested.
Fuku, can you take the counter for a while?
I can't just leave when I'm supposed to be minding the library.
See you, Satoshi.
Hold the fort while we're gone.
So where are we going, Oreki?
The art room.
That's in the other building.
Yeah. It's pretty far.
That's why I didn't want to go.
Is there any limit to your laziness?
So what's in the art room?
Firstly, let's organize our information.
Consider what they would use the book for.
First of all, I doubt there are any girls who would use that huge book during their break.
Which means they must use it in class.
Considering that they're in the same year but different classes, what subjects could it be?
PE or arts classes, right?
Yeah.
The five girls took turns borrowing the book before class every week.
But we don't know if it's every week.
Since books can be borrowed for up to two weeks...
It's so huge, it'd be easier to just borrow it again each week than to take it home with you.
I guess.
What's wrong?
Something smells like the book!
Really?
Look inside and you'll understand.
That's what they use the book for.
Classes 2-D, 2-E and 2-F take Art together,
and they would have painted those pictures.
The book's cover makes it perfect as a model.
So that smell was paint!
How did you figure it out?
I just...
I just had a moment of inspiration.
It was just luck.
Library
Ah, well done, well done!
I never would have thought they'd use it as a model for painting.
How'd you manage to figure it out?
You're weird, Oreki.
What are you saying?
I'm as average as they come.
I do wonder about that.
But you really did surprise me, Oreki.
I'm really interested in what goes on inside your head.
Interested?
Yes.
So much I'd like to cut it open to see.
There's nothing unusual about my brain.
A top-ranking student like yourself wouldn't get anything out of it.
Huh? She's that good?
Yeah!
The midterms are still a while away,
but I'm sure she'll be among the best in our year!
No,
even if I get good grades,
I'm just putting together things I already know.
What I want to know is beyond those things.
I want to understand the system that gives birth to thoughts.
O-kay...
Actually, her sense of smell is even more of a mystery to me.
Maybe Oreki could...
Nothing.
Never mind.
Well, I guess that was pretty fun.
What about you, Chitanda?
Of course! It was loads of fun!
But it was all over so quickly!
I spent hours on it and never figured it out...
That's so frustrating!
That's why I said he can be useful at times.
But I hate being outdone by Oreki!
It's really, really frustrating!
Now, chill out.
This isn't it.
This just isn't it.
This isn't how I am.
What's different?
What?
That's right, I guess...
That rare flash of sparkling brilliance...
Oreki, you can't leave yet!
Why?
Oh. The anthology.
That's right. We need to wait for the librarian.
Sometimes, Houtarou acts like he's not all there.
Sometimes?
That's an understatement.
Ibara, thanks for your help.
That's all for today.
Ah, you're back, Ms. Itoigawa.
I'm Fukube Satoshi from the Classics Club.
We're looking for an old edition of the anthology to refer to when making the new one.
Can we take a look in the archives?
The Classics Club's...
anthology?
You're in the Classics Club? I see.
I'm sorry, but we don't have any of the previous anthologies in the archive.
Could you have overlooked it?
I don't think so. If we had it, I'd know.
Excuse me.
Sorry for the trouble.
I guess that's it, Chitanda.
This is bad news.
We'll find it, I'm sure.
How was it, Oreki?
Do you feel refreshed from having solved that mystery?
Not really.
Oh.
There's nothing we can do about it. Let's go home.
We still had a good harvest today.
What do you mean?
It's a personal thing.
That again?
Yeah.
Maybe Oreki could...
Hello? Oreki speaking.
Hello? It's Chitanda.
Chitanda?
Sorry, were you resting?
I guess.
I thought it was my sister calling.
So? How come you're calling on a Sunday?
Sorry to bother you,
but I'd like to meet you today.
Pine
apple
Sand
I'd like to ask a very special favor of you.
She's late.
I'm sorry for calling you out like this.
So? What's all this about?
Huh?
I'm asking why you had me come all the way here.
You're the one who chose this café.
I'm going home.
Please wait!
My Sundays are important to me, okay?
I'm not going to waste my time on this comedy act!
I'm sorry...
I'm so nervous.
Nervous, huh?
Were you planning to confess to me or something?
You might consider it a confession.
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: Inheritors of the Classics Club and its circumstances.
Inheritors of the Classics club and its circumstances