Pretty...
So pretty...
I want those crystals even more.
If you want 'em, just take 'em.
Defeating the Precures will get you the crystals.
You'd kill two birds with one stone.
That's how we should act.
You are King Selfish's daughter, after all.
That's true.
But just stealing it wouldn't be any fun.
I'm up against Mana, after all.
I need to make it fun.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Betting The Crystals!
A Selfish Game!
There are five crystals in total that will lead us to Ann.
And we have four of them.
Regina has the final one.
We have to get that crystal from Regina somehow.
What's the matter?
I want to avoid fighting Regina if we can...
Perhaps we could ask her nicely to return the crystal!
We wouldn't be here if asking nicely worked on them.
Is there any way we can get the crystal without fighting?
I know one.
Hi, Mana.
Regina!
Heyo, Ai!
The other crystals are pretty, too.
I want these too...
Anyway, Mana, let's play a game.
A game?
Yes, a game with all five crystals on the line.
And the winner gets every single one.
So?
What game will we play?
You'll just have to wait 'til it starts!
Fine, we'll play!
Mana!
This game thing is too fishy!
It's just a trap to steal the crystals!
Should we lose, we would forfeit all of our crystals!
The risk is too great!
But if we win, we'll get all the crystals without a fight!
That's my Mana.
Good girl!
Maybe it's no normal game, and maybe it's a trap.
But I want to accept this challenge!
Are you with me?
I have a lot of doubts,
but when you put it like that, I can't say no.
We shall be your teammates.
We'll beat her and get that crystal!
Thanks, girls!
But one thing worries me.
Does Regina really plan to give up her crystal if we win?
The winner of the game gets all the crystals.
Is that right, Regina?
Yep.
Then pinky swear.
Pinky what?
It shows that you won't break your promise.
Promise?
Pinky swear and if you lie, stick a needle in your eye.
Do you swear, Regina?
I swear.
Time for a first-class trip to the game world!
Selfish!
Girls!
Sorry, Trump Kingdom Knight,
but Regina did not invite you.
Girls...
Is Ai all right?
She certainly seems so!
Thank goodness...
Where are...
You're on the Game Stage that I created!
And you can't leave until the game is finished.
Let's go, girls!
Yeah!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Oh Regina and her Selfish trio,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your hearts race once more!
Oh, please make my heart race!
There are three games!
Our first game is a match of penalty kicks!
You can do it, Sword!
Get us a goal!
I'll get it through!
She did it!
Leave the defense to me!
Sure, take it.
I can catch that with ease!
Ball Selfish!
Huh? What?
Goal!
Hold on!
Using a Selfish as a ball is cheating!
How could you make a match so unfair?
'Cause I did.
After all, this is my world. I built it.
And I make the rules.
Look! A fish is jumping over a handstanding cat!
Say what?!
He's open!
Hey, stop running!
Stop right there, you!
Selfyselfyselfyselfyselfy!
Come on...
Too bad!
I'm up next!
I'm ready for you!
Here it comes!
She missed!
Selfish.
The goal is a Selfish too?
Selfiiiiiiish!
I shall not allow you!
Love Heart Arrow!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Self?!
Yeah, she blocked it!
Selfiiiish!
Rosetta!
Goal!
Are you okay?
Yes...
You're cheating too much!
Hey, I can cheat.
It's my game.
It all comes down to this shot.
You can do it, Heart!
Selfy selfy, hey hey hey!
Here I go!
Self?!
Sorry!
Wha?!
She got it!
Too bad!
We won the first game.
Our second game is bowling.
They're all strikes!
No way...
They're actually good!
You've finally seen our true strength.
We don't spend all day in a bowling alley for nothing!
Oh, how I've trained in secret for this day!
You girls are up next.
Wh-What?!
You have to knock every pin down to get a strike.
Every pin? How many are there?
We'll do it!
We have to!
I'll go first.
It's straight down the center!
Go!
Selfiiiiish.
Huh?
Ha ha, gutterball!
How is it a gutterball when it rolled down the center?!
'Cause it is!
That's a rule of mine.
Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
We're doomed if we lose here!
We're gonna lose our crystals!
Now the crystals will be all mine...
Now the crystals will be all mine!
Hey, girls! Come here a sec...
So, we do this, then like that...
They tryin' to strategize?
It's hard to watch them struggle in vain.
Okay, got it?
Cure Rosetta shall step in!
What?
It's the twirl she perfected in classic ballet class!
Her high speed spinning can put a lot of force on the ball!
Now!
It won't hit anything, no matter how you throw it!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Selfy selfy self—
Not bad...
But there's still plenty left.
What now?
I'll knock every last pin down myself!
Oh no!
That throw won't hit a single pin!
We've won!
Ai!
Kyupirappa!
Huh?!
We won!
You did great, Ai!
Gweat!
Ai's first word!
She just said "Gweat!"
She totally did!
Wow, that's gweat!
Ai's words are spreading to you too, Sword!
Moving on!
Our third game is dodgeball.
Ai, you'll be our ref.
And just like that, she sealed Ai's power.
If we win this game, we win the bet!
Let's work as a team!
Fight on!
Precure Diamond Shower!
Not bad.
What's with the court?
Your court's a bit slippery, so watch your step!
Heart!
Safe!
Nice catch!
Geez, this is takin' forever.
I'll finish this up quick.
Mammo, you're not a window.
Outta the way.
Nah. How about you move?
Whoops, my bad, hand slipped.
That's fine. It happens. Hands slip.
Oooooopsie, my hand slipped!
Why you little...
Oops.
That hurt.
H-Hey, it wasn't on purpose, honest!
Ira! Mammo!
You two jumped out of the way!
You threw it, so you take the fall.
She speaks the truth.
Why you...
You're all so dead!
Now I'm mad!
I never liked you from the start, brat!
Say what, hag?
I'm still a young lady!
You're a hag compared to my youthful energy!
Um, our game?
It seems they've changed opponents.
Well, that's Selfish Dodgeball...
Active
Match forfeited!
Which means...
The Precures won!
I lost?
Regina, remember our promise!
Give us the crystal!
Give them the crystal?
Regina?
No...
I want the crystals...
I don't want to give it up!
The crystals are Trump Kingdom treasures.
We need them to find someone important to us!
I need them too!
Heart knew that your game could have been a trap!
But she trusted you and accepted the bet!
Trusted... me?
That's right!
No matter what we said, Mana kept trusting you!
You wish to betray such faith?
Regina...
What a pain.
Just break your promise.
Can I do that?
Of course you can!
Take what you want by force!
Just get rid of anyone in your way.
We're all Selfish.
Moreover, you're King Selfish's daughter.
That's right.
I'm King Selfish's daughter!
Regina!
Promises and friendship won't make me give it up!
The crystals belong to me!
Selfish!
Selfish, defeat the Precures and steal the crystals!
Self!
What's yours is mine, so hand 'em over!
Give me the crystals!
If you don't, you'll never leave here!
We'll never let you have them!
We're inside a Selfish,
so we should be able to leave if we purify it!
Steal the crystals, Selfish!
Don't mind if I do!
Regina, promises aren't made to be broken!
They're made to be kept!
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Love love loooove!
Welcome back, Ai, girls.
Hello again...
Where are the crystals?
Right here!
I've got all five of them!
Regina!
This is...
Wh-What?
The crystals...
Flew away...
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
The crystals flew away!
The princess should be right ahead!
Dokidoki Precure:
Guided By The Crystals!
To The Princess's Location!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!