Moms bought me these tickies which is cool and all
But I needs 3 of 'em
Woot! You got 4th place
I think I have one here.
Nice, Anne Donovan!
An' that's how its done
I'll leave it to you.
But...
Don't worry.
We split it 50/50 aight?
Okay!
Charles Barkley, you still in high school?
Nah son, I got pushed back to elementary
We got a field trip next week!
Thas the one with Kobe and the Gang?
Huh?
Can't wait for that, it'll be a ballin time
Got that right, I gotta teach them stuff too
At that age they're just beggin' for it
My nigs are ready to be reared as well
I'm teachin' the 5th graders, I feel you
Oh yeah, where 's Kobe and the Gang going?
They're going down to the South Side.
Damn, the Crips's zone?
Congrats! xD
WINNER WINNER CHICKEN DINNER
Enjoy your trip to the HOOD
Nooooooo
Threads....
Paints 'n' powders for mah face....
Xanax....
Castration tools....
Sewing kit...
Purple drank...
Amphetamines...
TL Note: Why take 20 Advil when you can take 3 Aleve?
20 Advil .
Aw shit, where's the fucking ice?
Damnit, now I'll have to go see Dyrone Tykwalius again
Listen, ya gotta stop seeing that dealer
I know you wanna get drugged up for the trip with Charles, but come on
I'm not n-nervous, that's not w-why I'm on xanax
I just had some extra lying around...
And we'd agreed to split the winnings...
Yo, I honestly congratulate you!
Saywhat?
The two of us have prepared a little gift for you.
Don't tell me
Just take it, you bitch
It's just thanks for taking care of us.
Souno... Shouji... Thank you.
I wonder what this is.
Are these...
P-P-P-PA-PA-PA-PA-PANTIES?!
Hell yes!
Hey, nigs! You prepared for the trip?
But of course. Rather than that, are you ready for the Hood?
Not one bit!
I checked the stash five times! It's perfect!
But I was surprised.
Who'd have thought that Charles Barkley and Anne Donovan go to South Side the same day, too?
Oh~! Black Jesus wills it!
'Black Jesus' you say...
Charles Barkley said he'd meet us when he's not dealing
Where are we going to go?
Oh~! As Black Jesus as my witness, I'll never be alone
I can't wait!
Let's go trip really hard on bad meth!
Yay!
Here.
Thanks.
Look, A homeless man's home!
It's beautiful!
Uh, y-yeah.
What's up?
Your face is red.
Was it the weed?
D-D-D-D-Don't worry, it's not a side affect!
I don't know, that Tupac guy was kinda sketchy
But still, thank god I had enough dough to cover it
Huh?
If it wasn't for you...
I'm sure I'd have lost.
Charles...
You're thinking so much about me...
Of course, there's no one but you in my heart.
Charles...
Charles, I...
If I went on a trip with another girl, her parents definitely wouldn't let us.
But since you're my childhood friend, yours trust me.
I couldn't have gone with anyone else.
Pretty much...
What drug you wanna try next?
Maybe I should ask Kobe and the others...
That's cool and all, but I know a great place to get heroin
Did you say something?
Nothing at all.
Okay.
Charles! Anne!
Yo thanks for the wait!
Well then, where should we go?
Let's go to the House of Huff!
We'll jump off the stage!
Oh~! I haven't injected that yet!
Don't do anything dangerous!
Amazing! I'm so high!
Dirk, you crazy!
Onii-chan, I'm gonna to flyyyy!
No flying allowed.
Charles, let's take a picture!
This is..?
They let you borrow costumes and do crazy shit while tripping out
That sounds great, fantastic! Let's do that!
Char-, Taykwon
Kobe, ugh gurr hurr murr
Verily, ye look beautiful.
N-Nay...
Charles! Nay, I mean, Taykwon-don!
'tis I, Le-a
Hikari no Kimi, endly we meet.
Good evening, Taykwon.
Onii-chan! I am your wifey!
TL note: Pucelle is an archaic expression that refers to young, virgin shorty.
Magnificent! What splendid pucelles!
Pucelles?! What the hell are you saying, Charles!?!
Nigga I don't even
Huh?
By the way, you look pretty hot in those threads
W-What are you saying?
Y-You, too, Charles... You look g—
G-G-G-Great?
Charles, you look kinda gay!
Really?
Yes, completely fruity and homo!
I'm sure the Taykwon was someone as great as you.
You look like a faggot!
Oh~! Onii-chan is a queer!!
Come to think of it, Taykwon was notable for seducing 10 year olds...
Charles, too?
Wow, what's this?
We're there.
We just have to stop here.
Youjiya..?
Children's house?!
Charles, I'm a child!
Child! I'm a child!
Me too!
Me three!
Onii-chan, I'm a child!
Who should I pick?
Charles! No! Stop! Not here! Control your horny level!
TL note: 幼児 (Youji) means "child",
but the homophone 楊枝 means "toothpick". This is a pun, laugh.
You know, Dad's in Chicago's East End
and he wanted me to send him some toothpicks...
Can't I?
Who'd have thought we'd be staying in the same crib...
What a coincidence.
Sure is...
Why are you guys here as well?!
It's nothing more than coincidence.
I kind of doubt that.
Don't start nothing
As if!
The hotel's fully booked, so I guess we'll have to live with one room.
Then again, we're on a couple's trip, so a double room is to be expected.
Anne...
Y-Yes?!
TL Note: Meant to say sec (sort for second) but Freudian slip lol
Go jump in the shower, I'll join  you in a sex
Huh?
I can't wait to wash you all over!
Hey, I heard they have great DMT in here
Yeah.
Sure!
Girls, wait up!
Hey, you dropped this!
Hey, you, what's holding you?
N-Nothing, really.
S-S-S-Shower..?
We've been walking all day and got pretty sweaty, no?
I'll go get some drank
P-P-P-P-P—
What am I supposed to do with these..?
Wear them and win!
Good luck!
No, no! No way! Too embarrassing!
In the House!!
I don't know how to use panties!
I always went commando!
I can't fall asleep here!
Huh? You had trouble sleeping, too?
Yeah... Too many things fantasies through my head...
Wait, 'fantasies'?
Oh, that's just a side affect of the drank
You were worried, too.
I'll get some Lunesta
Oh, sweet thanks.
Return the panties you took last night.
Onii-chan!
Good morning.
Onii-chan, you look scary as heck
No... Good morning, everynigger!
We kept waiting for you to give us more crack!
Meet me in my room tonight, K?
Hey, what was that supposed to mean? Explain yourself.
Exactly what I said.
You picked up Dirk's panties last night. Tonight, you're going to return them.
How exactly do you know that?
Rather, why do you know they're Dirks?!
Charles!!
Oh right, I saw then when I watched her undress
Then why the hell didn't you return them right then and there?!
I can't blow my cover! They'll never let me adopt again if the Feds found out!
I get it.
But why did you make me take those panties up?!
I've been through this already!
You prick!
When you hid them in your shirt, you lost the right to lecture me!
I'll help you out! Tonight, we're returning Dirk's panties!
I'm the one helping you! You picked them up in the first place!
I'm heading out for a bit.
Ah, alright.
Right now, the girls are in the bath getting high
We'll take this opportunity to sneak into their room and put them back.
yo wat
is dat u sensei?
Wat are you guys doing?
Planning to peek into the baths?
No!
We're um. Talking about NBA and ESPN and other stuff
You basketball fanatics sure never change.
Ah well, better than doing dirty things to Anne
Charle's a safe person like me, you know?
What part of you is safe?
I brought lots of things to play with you
Let's have fun together nice and slow.
Hey, Charles, if I ever become a rapper/dealer/thug
I'll leave my sister in your care.
Hang in there, it'll be alright
We just wasted a lot of time!
Hey, do you even have her panties?
Yep, right here.
Do you want them?
Yes please
The panties!
What you doing, busta??!
Shut up and wait there!
Hurry up, man.
What?!
What's up?
Kobe.....
Yooo!
The girls' bath is over there!
W-What did you say?!
The water feels damn fine...
Yeah, we were walking around a lot, after all.
Yay! Got the weed! Got the meth! Got the crack!
Whoo!
LeBron-chon?!
Wat? Don't you dare peek, I swear to Black Jesus if u do
I know.
But just where did my panties go?
Maybe a certain someone took them like he did a while ago?
What nonsense are you on about? Dirk must've dropped them somewhere.
The field trip's over tomorrow, isn't it?
It was fun!
Time flies when you're stoned on bad drugs from the Hood
There's still tonight!
Charles's is getting us some good product from an old friend!
Oh sweet, I hope it's psychedelic
Oh~! I want to mix shrooms with alcohol!
Charles...... I wonder what you're doing right now...
Just a little bit further...
One way or another, I got 'em.
We wasted so much time... They're back already!
It can't be helped. We'll go drug them up and play it off cool
Will this improvised plan even work?
Leave it to me.
Welcome, Charles!
Huh? They're here, too?
I'm not here because I want to!
Hey! What are you doing?! We're not here for a pillow fight!
I know.
I'll create an opening.
Charles...
Give me back my ritalin!
You promised me the product man, come on!
Oh~! Just hand over the drugs!
Charles Barkley!
A floater!
A no-look pass?!
Go!
Charles, nice shot.
Oh~! That was radical!
Yep.
But this is a pillow fight.
You really do love basketball, don't you?
You got me.
I'm back!
Ann...e
Yo, how was that gift?
Naturally, you won, right?
What? You wanna off yourself?
Nah man you got the wrong idea
He must think I trip often...shiiiiit
I prepared myself so much, too...
My B
I just wanted to try them on, nothing more!
I'm really sorry! Please forgive me!
Screw this shit!
You Only Live Once!
Snap out of it Anne! Stay with me!
Anne, here
What's that?
A little gift from a friend to a friend if ya catch my drift
Can I really have this?
Sure. Thanks a lot for everything.
Let's go home