The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Thinking back on it now, it's fairly strange...
But on the other hand, it also makes me think as though it's nothing out of the ordinary.
Either way, it was a life changing event for me.
But it also feels like nothing's changed at all...
It was an odd experience to say the least.
But it's nothing uncommon.
It happened to me here, in Ikebukuro.
First
Words
I-I'm sorry-!
I want to go back.
Don't laugh at me,
but I stayed home for my field trips all
throughout elementary and middle school.
Later!
I've never been out of town.
I'm a fifteen year old who's stranded in Tokyo for the first time, lost about what to do.
My name is Mikado Ryugamine.
The reason why I'm standing in front of the gate of the Tobu Tojo line,
is because I'll be attending Raira
Academy in East Ikebukuro starting in April.
It's a fairly good school, not to mention the
campus is so pretty. Everything is well-maintained.
But my main reason for deciding to attend was because an old friend from elementary school convinced me.
My parents were against the idea, telling me to attend a school close to home,
but I've always wanted to visit Tokyo.
Mikado!
Huh?
Kida?
What, you're doubting me?
Then I'll give you three answers.
Choice one: Masaomi Kida.
Choice two: Masaomi Kida.
Choice three: Masaomi Kida!
Wow, it's really you, Kida?!
What, you're just going to ignore the
awesome joke I spent three years developing?
It's been so long, man!
You've changed so much, I didn't recognize you!
I didn't expect you to dye your hair!
And that was an awful joke.
Well yeah, it's been four years since we last saw each other.
But you, on the other hand, haven't
changed one bit since elementary school!
And don't just crack on my jokes like that.
Yes, this is my best friend, Masaomi Kida.
We haven't seen each other since he moved
away while we were still in elementary school,
but it looks like his appearance
was the only thing that changed.
Well then, let's go.
Let's go outside instead of staying in here.
I'm in the mood for heading West!
I'm a sly tour guide who's going to lead you
towards the Seibu exit instead of the West exit!
His jokes aren't the best, but he's a really nice guy.
I've always chatted with him online,
so I never really realized how far apart we were.
So, what's the difference between the West exit and the Seibu exit?
But after seeing each other for the first time in four years,
In Ikebukuro, the Tobu Department store is at the West Exit, and the Seibu Department Store is at the East exit.
I finally realized that we've been living in different places.
Dammit, why am I explaining a joke
that I failed to make you laugh with?
But really, he hasn't changed on the inside.
Is there anywhere you want to go?
Umm... how about Sunshine 60?
Right now?
If you really want to go there, you should take your girlfriend along.
O-Okay, then how about the Ikebukuro Nishi-guchi koen?
Jesus dude, just call it "West Gate Park".
But I thought all Ikebukuronese called it that...
What do you mean, "Ikebukuronese"?
Wait, so you really want to go?
Well, but...
H-Hang on!
Let's go some other time! It's already dark out!
We're going to get killed by the color gangs!
I don't even know how to respond to you
when you say that with such a serious face.
And besides, it's only six.
Geez... I guess you're still the same old chicken, huh?
Tanaka Taro has joined the chat.
Good evening!
Sup.
Hey, Mr. Setton.
I'm actually going to be staying in Ikebukuro, starting tomorrow.
Oh, really?
Perhaps you'll be living somewhere near me.
Could be.
I'm still at home right now,
but I'm going to be staying at an
apartment near the Sunshine building.
Welcome to Ikebukuro.
This is amazing...
I'm finally seeing the world I'd only
witnessed through comics and websites...
This is even cooler than Kamisakuramachi-ginza...
Then I'll take you to Shibuya next time!
Well, maybe I'll take you out to watch a horse race if you're not used to seeing so many people.
There haven't been many color gang members in the public as of late.
There were a lot of them who stood out in the streets until last year,
but a lot of them got arrested after they fought a gang in Saitama.
And ever since then,
the cops have always been on the lookout...
...for groups dressed in same colored clothes.
So Ikebukuro is pretty safe right now?
Well, I was talking as if I knew everything
about it, but I don't really know the details.
There are plenty of other dangerous guys lurking around, so I'd watch my back if I were you.
Oh...
Oh yeah, the road we're currently on is 60th Street.
There's also a Sunshine Street.
So I guess Sunshine Street was made before it?
I-I'm terribly sorry!
Hey, it's Kida.
Oh, hi, Karisawa, Yumasaki.
How's it going?
Hey, it's been a while.
Yo.
How ya doin', Kida?
Hi!
Who's he? A friend of yours?
Yeah, he's an old friend of mine.
He just moved here today.
Wow, really?
This is Karisawa.
And this is Yumasaki.
And that's Mr. Kadoka and Mr. Togusa.
U-Umm... my name is Mikado Ryugamine.
Did I say something strange?
Is that a pen name?
Why would a high school student be using a pen name?
Oh, maybe he writes for a magazine or talks on a radio show or something?
N-No, it's actually my real name.
Seriously?!
Wow, that's pretty fucking rad, dude!
Sounds like the name of a protagonist from a manga series!
Oh my gosh! You're making me blush!
What should I do... I can't really keep up with them.
Are you on your way home from shopping?
Yup.
A new novel published by Dengeki Bunko came out,
so we bought about thirty of them.
Dengeki Bunko publishes that many each month?!
No way!
One for each of us, and the rest...
Well, we bought a few more for various purposes.
Yeah. Various purposes.
What do they mean by that?
For keepsake? For business purposes? Or perhaps for decorative purposes?
Well, we'd better get going now.
See you soon!
Okay, later.
So, should we carry the head in first?
See you guys!
Hey! Don't hit the car!
Well, they can be a little weird,
but if you're on good terms with them, they're grand people.
Oh... so you also have friends like that, huh?
I've got a hand in a lot of things.
I know how to get things cheaper at shops like that.
I wonder what he went through
over the course of these four years?
Even at stores that sell used clothing and accessories!
While I was there alone, never leaving my town...
Well, if you're familiar with a lot of topics,
you've got something to talk about with most girls out there!
How coarse...
I found her.
Are you sure?
The description fits her accurately.
Roger that.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Make sure you have the right amount.
If she doesn't wake up, we'll get shit for pay.
Who cares?
If she's still a teen, we get an extra fifty percent, don't we?
Twenty percent.
Haven't had a good deal like this in a while. A teenager.
Yeah.
Kudos to the informant.
Good evening.
Mr. Kanra! You were online?
I was actually on the phone.
Oh, I just read the logs. You're coming to Tokyo?
Congrats!
Wanna meet irl sometime?
Ah, that sounds good.
Sure does!
Oh, while we're on the subject, have you heard
about people meeting just to commit mass suicide?
Oh, yeah. That used to be pretty popular.
People meet online, then commit suicide together...
Not very pretty, is it?
But I haven't heard much about it on the news lately.
Maybe they attempted and failed...
Or it could be that a lot of people have done it, but no one's actually realized it yet.
Maybe their bodies haven't been found...
That's not something to joke about.
Now that I think about it, there's
been a lot of disappearances lately.
Really?
Let's see...
It's usually a foreigner who's living here illegally,
or perhaps a child who ran away from home, and went to another district.
I heard it usually happens in the area between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you Miss Magenta?
I am.
Oh, are you Mr. Nakura?
Great! So I wasn't mistaken.
Nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
Well then, shall we get going?
Okay.
It's right around the corner.
There are two others who are going to be joining us.
I see.
It's that van over there.
Hi!
Hi.
Is anyone watching us?
Not a single soul.
Well then...
Sorry we tricked you!
Yeah there is.
Kida kept talking right off the reel.
I was actually a bit tired.
I don't know if I was tired from walking,
or if I was tired from poking fun at his lame jokes.
I know we always chat online,
but now that you're here, I just have so much to talk about!
I'm pretty sure it was both.
Y-You're right.
Personally, I think I've only said about 5/400ths of what I wanted to say.
And 4/400ths of that was about Erika and Walker.
Just when I was about to simplify Kida's
fraction, the man appeared in front of me.
It's been a while, young lady.
A man who was dressed a chef, attracting customers...
No... a giant, black man dressed as a chef...
Or... a person who's supposed to be attracting customers
was dressed as a chef, and for some reason, he was black...
It's been forever, lad!
Yo, Simon! It really has been forever!
Hey, Kida. Want to eat sushi? It's good.
I'll make it cheap for ya!
Sushi is very good!
I'm broke right now, so I'll have to turn down the offer.
I'll drop by once I get paid for my job, so you better give me a discount!
Oh, I can't do that.
If I did, I'd meet a watery grave on Russian land.
How are you going to drown on land?
Well, later.
It's been a while, lad!
You know that guy too?
Yeah. His name's Simon.
He's a Russian of African American descent,
and works as a tout for that sushi shop run by a Russian.
Sorry, but there are just so many
things wrong with what you just said.
No, I'm serious.
His real name is Samia, but everyone just calls him Simon.
It's been a while, young lad!
I'm not too sure on the details,
but apparently, his parents were exiled from the US.
And a friend of his started a sushi bar, so he decided to work there as a tout.
Don't get on his bad side, okay?
I saw him stopping a fight once, and he picked a guy his size with one arm.
Oh, and another guy you shouldn't make an enemy out of is...
What? What's going on?
Speak of the devil...
Anyway, stay away from a guy named Shizuo Heiwajima.
If you live a normal life, he probably won't even talk to you.
I-I wonder what he's like.
Huh? They're still not here.
That's weird.
They're pretty lousy.
They need to get their asses in gear.
Well, who cares?
We don't have anything better to do anyway.
Yeah.
Times like this are really precious, aren't they?
A short, sweet time in the midst of our wild lives...
By the way, I saw that black motorcycle everyone's been talking about today.
Black motorcycle?
You've never heard of it?
The one that's been sighted in Shinjuku and Ikebukuro recently.
I heard it's always been some sort of an urban legend,
but people have been catching him on camera lately.
Oh, I've heard of that.
But, is that really just a member of a motorcycle gang?
It's not like he rides around with a group or anything.
He's an idiot for riding around
without his lights on, that's for sure.
If he's human, that is.
What do you mean by that?
Well, to be blunt...
He's sort of like a monster.
Hey.
Umm... are you here for the trade?
I... really don't think so, dude.
Then who is that?
I think you're looking down on us.
We're kind of in the middle of something right now.
If you're going to get in our way,
we're just going to have to kill you!
A-Are you serious?!
Wait... Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Stop! Get off me!
Stop!!
See what I told you?
Holy...
Holy shit!
W-What the hell is that?!
What the fuck?!
What do you mean, a "monster"?
Dotachin says he's a grim reaper.
Dotachin?
Who's that?
The one who rides the black motorcycle doesn't...
So you're just going to ignore my question...?
Dammit!!
Serves you right!
Son of a bitch!
...have a head.
He doesn't have a head, but he still moves.
S-Seriously... what the fuck are you?
What... the fuck are you?!
Hey, are there other people I should be wary of?
Well, aside from the gangsters...
There's a guy called Izaya Orihara.
Izaya Orihara?
That's a strange name.
That's strange for you to say.
This guy's really dangerous, so don't go near him.
Well, he mainly hangs around Shinjuku,
so you'll probably never have the chance to meet him.
Oh, and don't get associated with people called Dollars either.
Dollars?
Yeah, as in, "one dollars".
"One" dollars?
I don't know much about the details either,
but apparently there's a lot of them.
I heard they're part of the color gangs,
but no one knows what color they represent.
Well, they can't really get together now with all those cops watching,
so maybe they've disbanded already.
Really?
Hey! Are you...
...all right?
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
Hey...
No!
No!!
Hey...
What in the world?
She didn't even thank me for helping her up.
I wonder what happened to her.
Who knows? Anything and everything can happen in this town.
You're pretty lucky.
You met both Mr. Kadota and Simon today.
And you also witnessed Shizuo
throwing vending machines and people,
and you ran into a hottie like her.
Are you sure that makes me lucky?
I'm really happy.
I'll be able to attend school with you here and hang out like we used to.
I am too.
Man, you're really lucky!
You get to see an urban legend with your own eyes too!
Kida!
Wow. Taro Tanaka, you actually saw the black motorcycle?
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black motorcycle today!
Oh, good evening,
Mr. Setton.
The one you mentioned the other day!
I saw that black motorcycle today!
Was it around nine in the evening?
The one you mentioned the other day!
Oh, you heard about it, Mr. Setton?
Yeah, well... I was there, too.
What do you mean, an "urban legend"?!
The black motorcycle!
The headless rider!
And at that moment, I felt my body shaking...
It's not that I was scared.
I think... I was in awe.
I saw something amazing.
Here, in this town,
I experienced something I could
never experience anywhere else.
The reality I thought I'd never reach
was spreading out right before my eyes.
It contradicts what I first said when I came here...
But at that moment,
I felt my body tremble as I sensed that a new world was opening up to me.
Really?!
Then maybe we passed by each other without knowing it!
Could be.
So, back to my earlier question...
Who the heck...
...is Dotachin?
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Highly Unpredictable
A girl with a seemingly mysterious past
catches a glimpse of a reality she's unaware of.
A reality that anyone could encounter, but doesn't.
What was in the eyes of the girl who was fated to die?
Next time: Highly Unpredictable.