The wind feels so nice...
Momoka-san, I...
CENTER OF THE WORLD
Isn't this place a bit too cramped?
Not much we can do about it.
Why did we even pick this place?
Because the other rooms were taken.
That studio we used last time wasn't.
That studio also costs a ton.
Are we really gonna be okay? The festival's right around the corner.
arE wE reAlLY gOnNA be oKaY? THe fEsTivAl's rIGhT ARoUnd tHE cOrNeR.
Can we stop wasting time then?
Are we good on this part or what?
I should start where you told me before, right?
Want me to give you a signal?
Sure, thanks.
- Do we really need that last part?
- I was wondering about that too.
I prefer keeping it as is.
I think both of them work, so let's have Momoka-san make the call.
What do you think?
It might be a bit too loud since we all start playing at the same time.
Let's see how it sounds without my guitar.
From the last chorus.
Got it!
I'm pooped.
Eh, Burton Sister's gonna play right at the end!
No way.
Are you a fan?
N-Not really…
They are pretty hot...
It's not like that!
Look, our name's there too!
Well, duh. We're performing too.
We're up on the first day, right?
Yep, we'll be the first ones on our stage.
Which means we should be able watch the last performers.
And that one, and that one too...
Will you even make it to all of them?
Sure I will.
We get a free pass, might as well make the most of it.
How big is the audience gonna be?
It's a festival, so it depends.
The bigger stages will probably be packed during peak hours,
but I don't know about the smaller ones.
And that's where we're supposed to leave our mark, huh...
- Actually-
- Hey!
I heard they changed your performance time.
I'll be rootin' for you.
We might actually be playing on the second day.
Huh?!
Apparently one of the bands had to cancel.
We'll still be on the same stage, but I asked for their time slot instead.
The second day's supposed to be an all-nighter.
This is a serious upgrade.
Sounds perfect!
So everyone's fine with the change?
Could luck really be on our side this time?
Do you guys have some time after this?
Wait, isn't that…
Yep.
I thought we might as well do some recon ahead of time.
Are we really playing in this huge place?
- Nope. That's the main stage.
- Main?
We'll be on the small stage over there.
Wait, there's more than one stage?
You really haven't done your homework, huh.
The popular bands play on the big one,
and upstarts like us go on the small one.
Naturally, Diamond Dust are on the big one.
I'm really happy.
It's all so...cool.
We'll be challenging Diamond Dust, who are up there on the big stage
from our tiny little stage.
Just like in Giant Killing.
A cornered rat will even bite a cat.
Hold up for a second.
Neither them nor the fans think of it that way.
But we do. Momoka-san and I.
You're all sure you're on board with the schedule change?
We're good, right?
Great.
Must be nice, playing under a sky like this.
Momoka-san!
Please lend me a guitar for the festival!
'Kay, I'm off to work!
Huh? Weren't you working together?
We are, but Nina-san found a second job all on her own.
I don't know if to call her selfish or just whimsical at this point.
She made a decision. To make it on her own.
True. She's come a long way, huh.
Wait, can she actually play the guitar now?
Dunno.
FROM: TENDO AWA
To Subaru-san. I hope you are doing well during the lingering summer heat. I assume your daily life is quite busy, but allow me to ask, how are things with your acting school? There is a new role for which auditions have started recently, and I would love it if you could take part.
Geez.
Look at her, being all sunshine and rainbows now.
Shit.
LIAR
I'm not a liar.
Subaru's still hiding it from her grandma, isn't she.
You know, I like that side of yours.
I-It's not like I actually care...
I hope that one day, you can find it in you to forgive them.
There's no way that'll happen.
You never know what the future holds.
It's impossible.
But at least they're within your reach.
You may not see or talk to them anymore, but they're alive.
The people that were dear to me
have turned to ashes by now.
You still have me.
Thank you.
Why do I make music?
Hmmm...probably because it allows me to connect with others.
Because it gives me somewhere I can be honest with myself, I guess.
Let's see…
Because it lets me forget everything and feel free.
I...
want to feel like I wasn't in the wrong.
That's a lot of people.
Now's when it really starts.
Um, and you are...?
We're TogeToge. Togenashi Togeari.
Oh, alright. You can park over here.
We're up in the evening, right?
Yep. So watch the time.
Looks like we have some time to see other bands.
What? But today's our big day!
Yeah, but seeing other bands could help us get pumped up.
You better not be late though.
Roger that!
Can I come with you?
No Ninas allowed!
Meanie.
Is this our dressing room?
Pretty much.
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Yo!
You came!
Mine-san!
- Is this a good time?
- Of course.
It's good to see you again.
Hello.
It's been a while.
You could have given me a heads-up.
That's no fun, now is it?
Still, it's no small thing playing on the second day at that time!
Thank you very much.
It was mostly luck though.
Nina-chan, how are you doing?
I'm great! Can't say the same for my guitar skills though...
That's good.
You got a much better look on your face now.
Really?
Yep, looking like a real songstress now.
Awesome.
Are you done with the yapping?
Introduce me, come on.
Yo.
We're under attack!
Ah, sorry.
This is Kyoko.
Small world out there, eh?
Hello there.
Hello.
For your information, she's a fan.
Yeah, I love your voice.
We should play together again sometime.
If you’ll have me…
You’re up for it? Awesome!
Let's take a pic for the occasion.
You good at funny faces?
F-funny faces?
C'mon, you guys come too.
Huh? Why?
Ready?
Say cheese.
Nice faces you got there.
Ditching us wasn't very nice of you.
Ooh, we got a bunch of likes.
And comments.
"Can't wait to see TogeToge".
We’re finally getting noticed.
They said it's all-you-can-drink here!
Sounds nice...
Cheers!
Stop.
Just a bit.
We have different definitions of "a bit".
Oh, Miura-san!
You’re Miura-san...right?
You got the wrong person!
Wait, huh? It wasn't her?
- Bottoms up!
- Stop that.
Oh yeah, I just noticed Subaru's not back yet.
She's probably still running between stages.
No fair, I wanted to go with her.
She's already back in the dressing room.
Really?
Put that down.
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Subaru-chan.
Yo.
How was it? Did you get to everyone?
Yeah.
Lucky. I wanted to go too, you know.
Jealous, aren't we?
Look at you, getting all perked up on your own.
Are you okay?
You know, the first time I went to a festival,
a drummer said something that stuck with me.
That as a drummer, he could always see his bandmates' back and support them.
At the time, it really resonated with me.
I saw myself in him.
Subaru-chan…
I sent a message to my grandma yesterday.
What did you say?
That I want to do something other than acting.
Seriously?
So yeah, let's keep this band going.
Even if we mess up today.
Are you sure?
You're the kind of stubborn girl who always does her own thing and runs on ideals.
You're shy, and not exactly friendly on top of that. Of course you'd get bullied.
But you're always honest.
And you always give it your all, so I can trust you.
I want to see where you'll take us.
Thanks.
I'm lying though.
You liar.
Come on.
Momoka-san?
Where to?
You'll see when we get there.
It’s really huge.
Well, it is called the main stage.
There's a lot more people now.
Tomo-chan, can you see anything?
No, and I hate this...
Want me to lift you up?
I see you picked up the habit.
It's starting.
This song…
Yep. That's it.
Momoka-san.
Thank you all for coming here today!
For those who don’t know us yet, we are…
Diamond Dust!
Stay with us until the end please!
Are you ever going to stop playing the tragic heroine?
You were wrong.
There's no point in keeping this up.
You must really be an idiot.
Shut up.
Here we go!
At the edge of the world where everything begins
Only doubt dances
Boredom only accelerates
Living in an unfinished dream
I laugh, completely cornered
Ready to unleash myself to support your sharp gaze
But it will never be enough
Those who lack the courage to shout often reap all the laurels
A prayer for those who have changed
I will continue to scream again and again
Even a prisoner of the chains of a cruel destiny
In a different cycle of desperate sadness
Thank you!
- Welcome, everyone!
- Those in the back, we see you guys too!
They actually got better.
Yep.
When they revealed an idol as their new singer,
they got a lot of flak for becoming industrialized.
"Don't look down on us, we'll show you what we're made of!"
They're putting that frustration into a driving force.
And the fans are feeling it at this point.
So they did think of it that way.
Consider me pissed.
I really love this kind of thing.
Momoka-san. Everyone. Let's steal every single one of these fans!
Yeah.
Togenashi Togeari, sound check please!
Got it!
Wow.
Alright, starting with the drums then.
Alright!
Alright, we're good.
Say something into the microphone please.
Got it!
Great, thank you.
Thank you! We'll be in your care!
Alright, now the bass please.
Alright.
Great. Will you be using pedals?
Yes, for distortion.
Done, anything else?
Nope!
It's almost our turn now.
Then just to get us perked up-
No. Alcohol!
By the way, where's Miura-san?
NEW TANTANMEN RAMEN
She sent me a message a while ago. Said she'll be in the audience.
She won't even visit us?
I like that she keeps her distance. Makes her feel more professional.
I'm not sure that's her reason...
Togenashi Togeari, you're up!
Got it.
Alright, wanna huddle up?
Ew, no.
Want to...raise our pinkies?
Good idea.
Totally.
Lame.
Before us is the most important concert of our lives.
Nina, you have to sing your lungs out so that everyone can hear you. Scream if you have to.
Rip their hearts out with our song.
Got it.
Look, you made her cry!
Get a grip already, we're up!
I can't play the guitar!
Are you kidding me?
You suck.
Now that's rock.
Uh, well… nice to meet you. We're Togenashi Togeari.
We're a band.
And uh, well, it's not easy.
We're all cowards, we don't trust people, we always hesitate.
Sometimes, we even rope each other into something and then don't take it seriously.
Wait, is that supposed to be about me?
Who exactly are you calling indecisive?
I'm not wrong, am I?
Alright, that's enough.
Those were our guitarist Momoka-san and our keyboardist Tomo-chan.
And this is our monstrously self-righteous vocalist, Nina!
And finally our bassist, Rupa-san!
Infighting is the best!
And on drums, we have…
Subaru!
"Give it up. It'll never happen."
"It's impossible. Be realistic."
"Consider yourself lucky."
"It's hard for me too."
That's how reality tried to drown me,
with a disgusting toxic smile on its face.
Through this song, I'll stay true to myself.
And...
Through this song, I'll make everyone who didn't believe in me change their minds.
At all those who denied everything that I am...
I want to shout that I was right all along!
No matter how much I get,
Dore dake te ni iretemo
No matter how much I make mine,
I can't keep up, can't keep up, can't keep up,
Dore dake jibun no mono ni shitemo shitemo shitemo
I'm never good enough
Oitsukenai na
Dreaming too big, they say those rotten words
Takanozomi shishugi nante kusatta youna kotoba
I never wanted to be above everyone else
Dareshimo dare yori mo sugurete hoshiku wa nai nda yo
There's only one reason
Riyuu wa tada hitotsu
To shatter this void, not to be the best.
Uchikudaitete hoshii kara kono kuukyo
When I could look at things with a pure heart
Junsuina kokoro de mireta koro wa
Everything seemed like a rainbow
Subete ga nijiiro ni mieru soutei
But even the things I've always wanted to grasp
Tsukamitai mono sura boyakete nijinde iku no sa
Become a blur and disappear now
I don't want to die, I want to live so much it hurts
Shinitai tte omotte nakute shinu hodo ikite
This soul of mine, this soul of mine
Hoshiinda tte hoshiinda tte kono tamashii ga
Filled with delirious spurts
Fugourina shousou tomerarenain da yo
I can't forgive, I can't forgive, I'm pathetic
Yurusenakute yurusenakute fugainain da
Everything's so detestable, it stings
Nanimo kamo nanimo kamo ototteru nda tte
I hide my tears as best I can
Namida uwatsura dake de
Concealing everything
Kakushitenda
Be obedient, they say those rotten words
Juujuun de inasai nante kusoyogoreteru kotoba
THE ANGER OF BEING ALONE
I admire those who shut them out
Mimi wo fusagu hodo no juuzoku wa mushiro akogare ureite tada hitori
I kicked away the pain of having nowhere else to go
Ikiba no nai itami keriageta
THE JOY THAT I LOST
An empty heart incapable of crying
Karappo na kokoro ja nake nai kurai ni
AND THE SADNESS OF A LIE
I make myself forgettable, my voice now muzzled
Kusubutte oto mo nai koe uzuite
IN THIS SONG
Even what I want to reach has faded, slowly evaporated
Hatashitai koto sura kemutte kasunde yuku no sa
EVERYTHING
PUT EVERYTHING YOU FEEL INTO IT
But even the things I've always wanted to grasp
Tsukamitai mono sura
Become a blur and disappear now
Boyakete nijinde iku no sa
It's not that I want to disappear, I want to destroy it
Kietai tte omotte nakute kowashite hoshiinda
This rusted, distorted chaos
Sabitsuite karamawatta ibitsu na kensou
It's dirty and transparent, but clear once it's shattered
Nigorikitta toumei konagona ni nareba kirei
Everything's so pathetic, it stings.
Nasakenakute nasakenakute iya ni narun da
Meaningless words, dying breath, old fantasies
Igi, taete iki, taeta risou, furui kuusou
I was terrified of even resisting
Aragau koto sura sezu ni obietenda
Terrified of even resisting
Obietenda
VOID AND CATHARSIS
That was amazing!
Momoka-san.
I wasn't wrong, was I?
Next: "And the sky darkens once more."