This isn't... It's still... not over...
Ah!
Take this!
vs.
"Combined Subjects"
Wha...
I-I did it!
Ah... The winner... Class A.
Huh? What? Rep...?
Huh?
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
"Images on screen are flights of fancy; may differ from reality."
The Summoner Test War has ended and a new morning has begun.
Are these possibly...
Drawing boards and rush mats.
I didn't think it could get any
worse than cardboard boxes.
So there was something even below that, huh?
I didn't see this coming.
I'm sorry, Himeji.
No. There's nothing you
should be apologizing for, Akihisa.
The ST War was so much fun.
Himeji...
Geez... Stop weeping! We lost!
There's nothing we can do about it!
We can still take classes
using the drawing boards.
They say home is where you make it, right?
Since this is like sketching in art
class, it seems fun, doesn't it? Ah...
What's the matter, Mizuki?
Well, uhm... I can't see the bottom.
Where are you going, Minami?!
Where else?! I'll go start
an ST War one more time!
Just give up, Shimada!
We can't declare war for at
least the next three months!
But I hate this drawing board!
Your breasts won't be in your way,
and besides, it looks good on you.
And my joints can't be bent in that direction!
I feel like I haven't been
attacked like this for a long time.
--What do you mean by saying
--Almost... Almost... Almost...
--a flat board looks good on me?!
--Hm?!
Almost... Almost... Almost... Almost...
I can almost see... I can almost see...
Almost... Almost... Almost,
almost, almost, almost...
You're on fire! You're burning up, Muttsulini!
Whoa! The fire died down!
What's the matter? You're
already down and out, Muttsulini?
Kudou!
I went to the trouble of putting on
a bra today just for you, Muttsulini.
A very cute one.
Humph. So?
Your body is more honest.
Don't worry. I know, Muttsulini!
Awaken!
Ah...
Sorry, Muttsulini. I forgot
my iron bracelet was broken.
"Note: Muttsulini"
Where are you going, Muttsulini?!
Please give Akihisa
approval to summon his avatar.
What is this for?
To take someone's bra off.
I can't approve.
I wonder if this was our real ability after all.
Well, something like that.
But I can't accept the way we lost.
Well, a defeat is a defeat.
We fought using our fighting skills
as our weapon rather than test scores.
We fought under the same terms.
But they were a cut above us
for being able to attack us
without being affected by the situation.
Which means we lost
because we let our guard down.
But...
That's reality. Well, the end
result is all that matters, so...
Did something happen, Aki?
You said trying hard is
only a means to an end, right?
Yes, I did.
I couldn't get results. I wonder if
I'm just an ordinary idiot after all.
It's true that you're a fool if
you take pride in your own efforts.
However, it's not a bad thing
for others to praise your effort.
Sis...
I think you did your best. You're my
little brother, whom I can be proud of.
Thanks, Sis.
It's okay for you to mope
around over the defeat for now.
What? Wouldn't people normally cheer
you up by saying, "Don't mope around"?
It is important to accept
your defeat as a defeat.
If a person doesn't know the
frustration caused by defeat,
he neither knows how to get up when
he falls, nor can he move further ahead.
So mope around as much as you like.
But when you're done moping,
start walking again towards your future.
Okay!
While you're moping around,
I'll fully comfort you.
Having me sleep by your
side or take a bath with you...
Huh?
Which would you like?
I decline both.
Don't hold back. I'm your sister.
That's exactly why I'm holding back!
When I'm done moping, start
walking again towards my future...
Future...
I wonder if there's still
something I can do by any chance...
Okay, I've decided!
"Clank"
So we're taking a bath together?
That's not what I meant.
So that concludes the ST War result report.
Who is it?
What did you come here for, Yoshii?
I have a request. Please let us
fight an ST War with Class A again!
That's not possible. If you want
to declare war, wait three months.
I can't wait that long!
That's the rule of this
academy. We can't bend it.
Please!
I just can't... accept it
ending like this! Please!
I'd like to request it, too!
I cannot accept how we won, either.
Class A happened to win. However,
I hate to admit it, but they had
us on the ropes during the fight.
Kinoshita? You, too, Kirishima?
You two...
That's not how Class A, the class
that represents the academy, should win.
I don't think the students from the
other classes would accept it, either. So...
I'd like to ask, too.
All of you...
Do you know why this academy
adopted the Summoner Test War system?
We cannot bend the rules. But...
we owe you for the time
the system went out of control.
I'm also responsible for
letting you use the iron bracelet
when it was still experimental.
If you are that insistent, I guess
I'll give you a special treatment.
Special treatment?
Is your wish really the exchange of
equipment between Classes A and F?
--What..?
--If not, there's another option available to you.
What?!
Fight Class A again?
It's okay to fight again?!
I can't believe that old
hag approved such a thing.
This is amazing, Akihisa!
Y-Yeah...
All right then! We'll knock
them down this time for sure!
Shall we make a new plan?!
Well, Yuuji... It's a
little different this time.
Hm?
What?!
You'll duel?!
Yeah. It's been decided that
I'll fight the Class A Rep in a test.
Class A Rep... With Shouko?!
If I win, although we can't exchange equipment,
they said that they'll grant us a small request.
Your opponent is the
Year 2 top student, you know!
Can you win, Aki?
Are you gonna be okay, Akihisa?
Don't worry. I won't cause you guys trouble.
So, Akihisa. What happens if you lose?
They'll grant the other side one request.
If I win, I'll ask to get my
marriage registration form back.
It's not yours to start with!
You bastard! You said you
wouldn't cause us trouble!
But my life is at stake here!
It's nothing important!
Once the war is over, we'll go
on our honeymoon right away.
No way!
Yuuji, how many kids do you want?
Akihisa, you bastard! Win at
any cost! Don't you dare lose!
Shouko! Go easy on him, too!
I remember... You told me not to hold back.
Dammit! My life is... over...
So you decided that I'm gonna lose...
But it's true...
Although I can fight again,
fighting Kirishima all by myself isn't...
--Stupid Big Brother!
--Hm?
Hazuki!
Here! This is a present for you!
Whoa! You can bake cookies?!
I learned in home economics class.
I'm not very good at it, though.
Thanks, Hazuki.
All right! Can you do your best now?
Huh?
I see... Thanks. Your support really helps.
Yeah, these taste good.
You might have a talent for this.
Thank you. I couldn't bake well
and I burned them several times.
But I didn't give up and tried hard,
and finally I was able to do it.
All right!
What's the matter, Big Brother?
I'll try hard and won't give up, too.
I'll be no worse off.
I'll try my best! Thanks, Hazuki!
Yep!
I'm home!
Welcome home, Aki.
I'll cram overnight or do whatever!
I'll become able to answer
as many questions as I can!
Idiot test.
Following the decision on special treatment,
we'll now start a duel between
Class A Rep Shouko Kirishima
and Class F student Akihisa Yoshii.
The duel will follow sudden death rules.
In sudden death rules,
the students are given the
same questions one by one
and answer at the same time.
When either of them makes
a mistake, the game is over.
The one who made the mistake loses.
In other words, whoever
makes a mistake first loses.
At Fumizuki Academy, you're given an
unlimited number of questions in tests,
but the questions get harder each time.
Which means, the outcome will
be decided in the initial stages.
Akihisa...
Well then, let's start!
Good luck, Akihisa!
Yuuji...
I believe that you can win.
You, too, trust your own
ability and do your best! Fight!
So he gives his earnest support
when his future is at stake, huh?
Question 1. Write the
proverb that means the following.
"To fail at something one is good at."
This one is easy.
Unless Akihisa is really stupid, he
shouldn't stumble at the beginning.
He's already stumbled!
What?!
How's that?!
All right!
Both are correct.
Don't scare me, Akihisa!
I'm nervous! What can I do?!
Question 2. Answer how to
calculate the area of a circle.
All right! Kirishima made a mistake!
Huh? What?! How come?! Why?!
I'm surprised you were able
to enter a high school like that.
Well then, question 3.
It's not like it's inedible,
but it's not quite there yet.
Aki must be fighting hard now.
I hope I can make something
that could be called a reward.
I'll try hard, too.
Q-Question 30.
Name the year that the twelve
court rank system was established.
Both are correct.
Whoa...
Good going, Akihisa!
You can still keep on going.
Phew... Somehow my guesses
for study topics were right
so I've been doing okay so far.
But she wouldn't make a
mistake so easily, would she?
If I lose my concentration
on even one question, I'll lose.
Question 31.
Name the person who defeated the last king of
the Achaemenid Empire of Persia and
started his eastern campaign in 334 BC.
Another history question!
This one is tough.
Akihisa...
Both are correct.
Whoa! He got it correct!
Good job, Aki!
Phew. Even I wouldn't make a
mistake on Alexander the Great, would I?
They'll be done with the easy questions soon.
So things will get gradually
tougher for Akihisa, huh?
Akihisa...
Question 32. Japan's very first
imperial era name was "Taika."
Name the year the Taika Reform
took place in Christian Era.
Whoa!
This question is...
A freebie question.
Obviously, they both will get it correct.
We have to wait to see who
wins until the next question.
What's the matter, Akihisa?
T... Taika Reform... Which year was that?
--What?!
--What the hell?! You bastard!
You don't remember that after what happened?!
That's exactly why I got confused
as to which one was correct!
Stop messing around, you idiot!
The key is the word "Reform." I know that much.
Reform... Reform...
645...? Or 625?
"Re-form" or "Re-four-m"?
Reform... Reform... Reform...
Akihisa...
Aki...
Which...?! Which one...?!
If I make a mistake here... it'll all be over!
Aki...
Akihisa!
Dammit!
--Aki!
--Akihisa!
That idiot! He's given up!
No, he hasn't! That's...!
That's Striker Sigma V!
Go!
Stop it, you idiot!
That's the wrong answer!
What?!
It's over... My life is over...
Winner, Akihisa Yoshii, Year 2, Class F!
What?!
I... I got it right?
You did it, Aki!
Good job, Akihisa!
Akihisa!
Shouko... why'd you do that?
Because... I promised...
Hm?
...that I'd never forget.
I'm sorry.
Besides, I got what I wanted, so...
Huh?
I'm going to City Hall now.
How'd you get it?!
A kind person gave it to me.
Don't tell me...
Kindness does not go unrewarded.
I never imagined you'd really win.
Principal...
Well then, as promised,
we'll grant your request.
Thank you very much!
What did you request, Akihisa?
That's...
Well then, Himeji. We'll give
you another placement test.
What? Akihisa... don't tell me...
This was the reason I wanted
to start ST Wars from the start.
I wanted at least you to be able
to study using good equipment, so...
Then...
You can go to the class that suits you.
Isn't that great, Himeji?
Oh no...
Akihisa...
What is it?
Are you... Are you okay with this?
It'll be a bit lonely without you, but if
it's good for you, then that's the best.
I... see...
Thank you very much, Akihisa.
Yep!
"Second Placement Test"
Well then, start!
Class: F; No. 28; Name: Mizuki Himeji"
There're tons of people who're
only good at academics in this world.
But no matter how high one's
individual ability is, there's a limit.
Those who care only about their
own strength never exceed that limit.
When I was in school, it was natural to
work hard together for everyone's sake.
You don't gain much by
working hard only for yourself.
What's important for now
is that you understand that.
That's it!
Looks like you did well. This'll be
good enough for you to join Class A.
Yes sir.
We'll let you know the results.
You can go home now.
Excuse me!
What is it?
I made one big mistake. Please let me fix it.
The test is over. You're not
allowed to make a change.
But...
Don't worry. You answered
a lot. This should be enough.
Please!
Hm?
No matter what...
No matter what, I have to fix it!
Please!
Good morning, Aki!
Good morning, Akihisa.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Yoshii...
Ah, good morning, Kirishima.
I took the form to City Hall,
but they rejected it.
In Japan, men must be 18
and above to get married.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Akihisa!
Aki, have you seen Mizuki yet?
No, I haven't seen her today yet.
I see.
It'll be harder and harder to see
her when she's in a different class.
Yeah.
Did you hear, Akihisa?
Hear what?
Himeji's placement test score. I hear
it's pretty certain that she'll join Class A.
I see...
Was it really okay?
Yeah, Class F isn't where she should be.
She should study comfortably
in the fully furnished Class A.
If that's how you feel,
then we're okay with it, too.
But Akihisa... It doesn't look
like things will go as you planned.
What?
Good morning, Akihisa.
Himeji?! What're you doing here?!
Did you forget something?
No. This is my classroom.
What?! I thought it was certain
that you were going to join Class A!
About that...
To tell you the truth, I forgot to
write my name so I got zero points.
So I've been placed in Class F again.
Himeji...
So, I'm looking forward to studying
together with you again, Akihisa.
What's the matter, Aki?
Are you crying for joy?
I'm happy for you, Akihisa.
This is a happy ending.
That damn old hag!
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
The end of the school day is bliss
If I am to put it into words, "It's really angelic!"
My peace was shattered
by a sudden announcement
Talking about the make up test. "This is Hell!"
While my friends and I were
sharing funny stories, I said,
"There's no way anyone is that stupid"
But the truth is, deep down in my heart
I was shouting, "That was me!"
About that "Monthly Parking"
sign you see in the parking lot
I thought it was the name of a company...
All this time...
Sticking to your idiocy can be cool
Is our common sense nonsense?
We don't need rules in this world
It's dog eat dog food! It's social upheaval!
Look!
The sun that rose from the west is setting
Run home! It's dinner time already.
Let's go home! Let's go home!
You damn old hag!
What'd you barge in here and call
me damn old hag for, you damn brat?
This is wrong, isn't it?!
Why does Himeji get zero points?!
She forgot to put her name.
Of course she gets zero points.
That isn't right! Since she took the test alone,
even if she didn't write her name,
it's completely obvious it was her!
You guys didn't even notice that?! You idiot!
I never thought I'd be called an "idiot" by you.
In any case, please put her points back.
Or let her retake the
placement test from the start!
You really are an idiot, aren't you?
Huh?
What?
Idiot.
A real idiot.
Akihisa, you really are an idiot.
What?! Y-You're saying that too, Himeji?! Why?!
Idiot!
"Idiot"