Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
On a spring night, Virgo is spread out widely.
My favorite star, Spica, is this Alpha star.
If you stretch this line from the Big
Dipper, there's the North Star.
And if you pull the handle of the ladle,
there's the star of the cow
herder, Arcturus, then Spica!
This line is called the Great Arc of Spring.
During the cherry blossom season,
try looking for it in the southern sky!
Marika and Marika
Just as I thought, without a compass, it's hard to figure
out where I am or which direction I'm going in...
This... I feel like I've seen a similar rock before...
Could it be that I've been
going around in circles?
Hey!
Is anyone here?
No one's here...
I wonder how everyone is doing...
Hm?
That's right!
Okay, this will work!
With this, I'll know without a doubt if I'm
going down the same path I took before.
Everything's fine.
I'll get through this somehow.
Oh man! Someone do something about this!
I keep going and going,
but it's just more forest.
I can't take this anymore!
Ow...
Damn it! How is this supposed to be training?
I'll definitely make them
reimburse me for my glasses!
Now that that's done... I wonder how
the little seagull's doing right now?
Is it all over for me?
I wanted to go to space...
You can't go to space alone!
I thought I could go by myself.
I thought the only way to go was alone.
I mean, I was... always alone...
Let's promise!
It's a promise.
Pro...mise...
Yep, Marika-chan, it's a promise
to graduate school together.
And a promise to go to space together!
Together?
I can... go together with people?
I can... go as well?
Of course!
We're friends with the same dream.
So, I'm sure of it.
Surely, we can definitely go together.
It's a promise.
Yes!
I just can't...
Do your best, Marika-chan!
It's a promise!
Do your best, for your dream!
I'm always here.
I'm always with you.
So don't give up, Marika-chan!
What would you know?
Quit meddling in my business.
I... I... have to apologize...
Apologize... then... then...
I have to tell her
that I want to go to space together, too.
That... looked like it was written a long time ago.
Orion 2
Lion-san                       Marika
To Space
Nothing has changed.
It's just as it was back then.
It's just that time has passed...
Hm?
After some time, that girl stopped coming...
Her chronic disease took a turn for the worse,
and she was to leave the country
to get some treatment.
I wanted to meet her again
before that happened.
That's what I thought...
In the end, that was it.
That girl never came back to this mansion.
After a while, the adults were gossiping
that she died overseas or something.
I knew of those rumors... but who knew
if that was even true or not.
They're so alike, it looks
as if she was reborn anew.
And the little one's friend also had
the same name as her... Marika.
Is it just by chance?
Or...
It must be a coincidental resemblance.
First of all, even with the same name, this Marika
and that Marika's ages are too different.
It's not like she's a ghost, like me.
Oops.
Did I break it?
Ukita Marika
Ukita... Marika...
Then... she's...
It can't be... such a thing...
I won't give in...
Not at a place like this...
I don't want to give up.
I...
I walked around all day,
but it definitely seems much larger
than the map showed.
If I could at least find this river,
I'd be able to clearly tell where I am...
I don't think the direction that
the sun rose was wrong, but...
I'll just have to leave this tent behind
and move forward tomorrow.
Even if I have to go a long way, I need to go
to a high place and confirm my location.
Hey, you're really there, right?
Hey, Lion-san!
Lion-san!
The sea!
Thank goodness. Now I can
begin to find out where I am.
The first emergency landing site is around here...
The sea is on this side...
A small hill in front...
That means I'm on this mountain...
If that's the case, it seems like there
isn't much distance to the goal, but...
The time I have to make it there is limited,
and with these mountain paths,
it might take me all five days.
Speaking of which, I wonder if there's some
sign or flag to mark where location A is...
It doesn't say anything here...
I wonder how everyone is doing.
Now that I think about it, since I came to the Space
School, I never really had a meal by myself.
I'm by myself right now.
This is the real me.
You ran too fast in the beginning.
That's why you became exhausted halfway.
But I wanted to reach the goal quickly!
That sort of feeling is also important,
but I always make sure to reach
the goal with half of my strength.
Half of my strength?
To go to space, you need a lot of friends, right?
That's why I leave half of my
strength for the rest of the crew.
So even if you reach the goal first...
If you turn around to see your friend on the floor,
you can go back to lend them a hand.
You can't go to space alone.
Half of my strength for my friends...
For my friends who are somewhere...
The sound of water?
It's cold!
The river is flowing in this direction, so...
Thank goodness. It's just as I thought.
If I go this way...
Someone was here.
Hey! Anyone!
Is anybody there?
That person must be like me...
Moving towards the goal marked
as location A on the map.
I wasn't alone after all. I wasn't alone!
Everyone's doing their best here.
I have to go as well!
Ow!
My feet won't hold out...
It must be because I haven't
eaten anything since yesterday.
Huh?
Would I be able to eat it?
But if I get sick from it...
I won't do it!
Not here anymore?
Is anyone nearby?
Isn't anyone here?
As I thought, they wouldn't be here.
That person would have gone ahead already.
I wonder who was here.
I wonder if that person has
already reached location A...
I'll have to do my best or I'll
be left behind by everyone.
Blood?
Hashimoto General Hospital
W-Where is this?
Me...?
Marika.
I told you. Don't leave this
room without permission.
But, Father...
I will not tolerate back-talk.
It it was the real Marika,
this wouldn't have happened.
Why?
Why does he say that?
I'm myself.
I'm Marika.
You're mistaken.
I didn't want that Marika.
She's completely wrong.
If I was going to have such painful feelings,
I didn't need that Marika.
An unwanted child.
If so, why give birth to me?
If I'm not allowed to be myself...
Where should I go?
Someone... someone save me!
Take me away from here!
Please!
Kamogawa-san...
Are you all right?
Who are you?
I was walking by the corridor
and I heard you call my
friend's name in your delirium.
Me?
Yes.
The name of my old dear friend...
so I couldn't help it.
Sorry.
Um, what did I say?
"Asumi."
Asumi?
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
Kasane-chan treasured the
leaf star from that day.
Her feelings must have connected with me.
What Marika-chan told Kasane-chan
was an unexpected secret.
And even if I reach the goal...
There's still something I have to do, right?
Next time on Twin Spica:
What I Can Do For You Now.
What I Can Do For You Now
End