So, how should we begin?
I've thought about it a lot, and I think we should start with Yui first.
Who?
You know.  She's the one who was singing in the band during the guerrilla-style concert.
You don't remember her?
Oh.
She's always so full of energy,
teasing Hinata while she laughs along.
She's performed in the band, too,
so I think she's done plenty enough to feel fulfilled.
All she needs is a push.
Just a little push to her back, and she'll be able to get out of here.
That's what I think.
Then I suppose that's good.
So you agree with me?
Okay, then let's do this.
So, how are things going on your end?
Well, it took some time to finish.
Hand Sonic: Version 5.
Here is Hand Sonic Version 5.
It's less angelic... and more devilish.
You asked me to make it look diabolic since I'm supposed to be evil, so this is what it became...  Is it not good?
Oh no, it's good.  Looks real badass.
"Badass"?
I mean, it's great!  Just perfect.
Oh, and do you think you can grow wings?
Wings?  What for?
I mean, for awesome visual effect.
You like it "awesome"?
Well, I just thought it'd be more angel-like.
I'll think about it.
Thanks.
So, what should I do?
O-Oh.  Right.
Let's do this.  You'll show up during her band practice.
When you do, say this:
"Other clubs are filing claims over the racket."
Then point at Yui and say, "Your guitar is especially bad."
"The band is dead because of you."
"As such, I will be confiscating that guitar for a while."
Then you'll take Yui's guitar and run off.
Of course, Yui will chase you, but you'll be running.
From there, just make your way over to the courtyard.
When you get there, I'll pretend to bump into you.
You'll drop the guitar at that point, and I'll catch it.  You just keep running away.
It'll create a situation where I can be alone with her.
Okay.
All right.  Let's begin when their practice starts!
Stop!
Come on, Yui!  Don't sing with such poor rhythm.
Yui, maybe you should focus on either singing or playing.
Yeah, that's so true.  They both sound horrendous right now.
What?  But Iwasawa-san sang while she played.
Yeah, since she was good at both.
I'm trying my best, you know.
You're all too harsh!
The concerts are always packed, too.
But this time, we'll be releasing a new song.
Tenshi?!
The band is dead because of your guitar performance.
She pointed out the current band's weakness instantly!
I knew she was special!
She can tell the notes.
Boo!  I thought you wouldn't notice!
As such, I will be confiscating that guitar for a while.
Hey, Yui!
Are you all right?
Here.
Why are you alone?
Because she didn't chase after me.
There.  You're perfect without the guitar.
But there's not enough jam to it.
We need a rhythm guitar in there.
Then how about adding another side guitarist instead?
My point is...
It looks best visually when the vocalist sings and plays the guitar at the same time, damn it!
She just lost it with Hisako-san!
I'm gonna go get my guitar back!
Crap!
Hey!  Dammit, Yui!
Here she comes!
Where did she go?
There she is!
Wait!
Oops, sorry!
You idiot, that's too high!
My guitar!
Don't worry, it's fine.
You rescued it from Tenshi for me?!
Where the fuck did she go?!
Hey, now.  Watch your language.
You're really doing whatever you want, aren't you?
Huh?  Whatever I want?  No, I'm not.
Well, you've got the vocal position in the band, and you're even playing the guitar.
This is nothing.  It's only one of the many things that I've wanted to do.
There are more?
Yeah, a lot.
A lot...  Then-
Actually, wait, let's change tacks.
So, what else is on your list?
Do I need to share them for some reason?
Not if you don't want to.
It's fine.  I'll tell you.
I've got lots of things I want to do, more than others do.
Why do you think that is?
Well, isn't it because you couldn't do them when you were alive?
Yup, that's exactly right.
I got hit by a car from behind when I was little.
That's how I became paralyzed.
I was totally bedridden.
I couldn't live without others taking care of me.
I was completely dependent on Mom.
I felt so bad for her.
But I was able to watch TV, so I watched music channels, saw bands play, and started wishing I could do the same.
I see.  Then I'm happy for you right now.
Yup!
So, what else do you want to do?
Well, I used to watch the baseball broadcasts, too.
If it's baseball, you did that on Ball Day.
But I couldn't get a single one that day!
A hit?
I mean a homerun!
Huh?!  And you have to hit one of those?
Of course I have to.
Once I get better in the band,
I plan on practicing baseball, too.
Balancing those two will be difficult...
Let me ask, just in case: Are there other things?
Soccer.
"Soccer"?
It was so popular.
Yeah, it might have been, but...
You've got too many interests!
Who in the world would try to be in a band, play baseball, and play soccer at the same time?
You wouldn't have more, would you?
Wrestling!
This makes no sense.
Who in the world would...
Well, I guess she just wants to do all the things she saw on TV.
Still, it's going to be a pain to make sure everything she listed comes true.
Okay!  I'll grant those wishes!
First off, um... why don't we start with the easiest one?  Wrestling, that is.
Wrestling?  Really?
Which move?
German Suplex!!
I-I can't do something that elaborate!
Choose something more doable, like a joint lock.
But I love the German Suplex.
And imagine pinning down the game just like that.
Don't say such a scary thing with such a cute voice!
Okay, fine.  Give it a try.
I can?
Yeah.
All right!
Here I go...!
Whoa...
You're stronger than I'd thought!
Go on, finish it!
Ow!!!
I guess a girl like me can't do it.
Yes, you can!  You almost had it there!
Oh, really?
Then can I try it again?
Huh?  S-Sure, but can we do this on the grass?
I'll die otherwise.
Why would you?
No, seriously.
Enough, already.
Please!  I'll do it right next time!
This seriously will be the last time, okay?
I'm heading back.
Senpai!
Let me guess.  You can't do a bridge, can you?
I can, too!
Show me.
Huh?
I knew this was why.
I nearly passed out several times because of this...
You need to work on getting the bridge down first.
Boo!  That's boring.
Just do it!
Ready, set...
Come on.  Higher.
Don't give up!
But I've totally never done a position like that!
If you can't do it, then you can't do a German Suplex, either.
I'll try...
I... have it down... right...?
You're trembling, but I guess that's fine.
All right.  Here I go!
Bring it on!
Her arms are locked good around my waist.  There's no way for me to get out of this!
It's perfect!
It's a perfect... German Suplex!
One.  Two.  Three.
Gong!  Gong!  Gong!
Game set!
I did it!  I did it!
Yay!  Whee!
Yay!  Yay!  Yay!
How many more of these do I have to go through?
Yay!
How about we take care of soccer next?
A one-on-one PK game good enough?
No,  I wanna dribble past five people and score the goal.
That's what Maradona did.
Yes, I know.
Fine!  Leave it to me!
Hey, T.K., do you know where Matsushita Fifth is?
Right now, he can't dance like I can.
Don't let me cry!
I'm sure he couldn't.  So, where is he?
Training.  In the mountains.
Training in the mountains?  Well that's pretty far away from dancing.
So he won't return for a while?
Whatever.  I'll ask you.
Can you get together the people I tell you to right now?
Don't tell Yuri, but I got this letter from Tenshi.
"How ridiculous to call yourselves men when you can't even beat one girl."
You actually read "ridiculous" correctly.
Was your dumbassness cured?
Even a dumbass can read it.
"I shall correct your sissy nature through sport."
"I will be waiting for you out on the soccer field after school ends."
"-Tenshi."  How dare she~?!
That doesn't make sense.  Did she really write that?
The current Tenshi is not the Tenshi we know anymore.
With all of 'em all fused, I guess she could've written some stupid-sounding challenge letter like that.
I'm not taking part in something like that!
I'm bringing this to Yurippe's attention.
I said it's a secret from Yuri, didn't I?
Why is that?
If we tell Yuri about this, it'll turn into another war.
Look here.  It says a sports match.
This time, she's saying we'll be able to fight through sports, fair and square.
Besides, this is a challenge letter to us guys.
Reporting it to Yuri will only sully us further.
I see his point.
Then let's have just us five take care of this.
Kiss you!
That's what I like to hear!
What's this?
Hey, look at that.
Someone's there.
It's Yui.
What's she doing?
So you're finally here.
Kick off!
She's dribbling the ball.
You guys ready?!
I get it!  It was she who wrote the letter!
She must be pissed off at us since we're always so useless!
That's why she's doing this!
Protect the goal!  We can't lose this game!
We men will win!
I don't really get this,
but you got me!
Don't look down on us!
I kiss you!
Hinata, you're the goalie!
You got it!
Move out of my way, jackass!
What a lousy dribble.
You're full of openings!
Prepare yourself!
Ow!
Okay, one down!
What happened?
What're you doin', Noda?!
Two down!
Ref!  That's gotta be a red card, right?!
Safe.
Who are you imitating?
Here I come!
Stop her, T.K.!  Otonashi!
Easy come!  Easy go!
We got it!
Here's number three!
Cut!
Way to go!
Here we go!
Sorry!
Just whose side are you on?!
So you're the last one, eh?!
I'll take the goal even if it means killing you.
Where did your sportsmanship go?!
I don't give a damn!
Take this!  Super Killer Guillotine Shoot!
Is she trying to score the goal or trying to kill me?!
It's a miracle!!
Hinata!
It went in.
Yay!
Yay!  Yay!  I outran five people!
Impossible.
We lost?
To make it worse, it was just to Yui.
Scrambled it.  Trouble down.
This sucks.
Let's keep this a secret.
Yeah.
She actually lost the ball once,
and she didn't dribble past the goalie...
But, oh well.
Okay.
Let's do this!
Before we do, how far does the hit need to go to count as a homerun?
Over the fence, of course.
Seriously?
Well then, hit it the best you can.
Yeah!  I hit it!
Just hitting it isn't what you need.
Keep your eyes on the ball, and hit it with the sweet spot of the bat.
You're only hitting the top of the ball.
You're too low, now.
You'll never hit it with your eyes closed!
She's weak.
Hey, keep it up!
I totally am!
One more!
Huh?
You're too tired.  You're losing your grip.
There's no point in continuing today.
You've got a nice big shout, but your hits aren't big at all!
I'm not done yet!
That was close!
Huh?
It's too dark to see the ball now.
We'll try again tomorrow.
What are you two up to?
Sup.
You wanna play a serious game?
Full swing, eh?
Haven't done one in a while.
Maybe... it wouldn't be such a bad idea.
What's wrong?!  You're not following through on your swings at all!
Are you all right?
Show me your hands.
No.
I said show me.
Naturally, there's no way.
It was impossible to begin with.
Just forget about this dream.
Don't give up...
Thank you for your help.
Why are you doing all this for me, by the way?
Well...
You wanted to do this, right?
Keep working until the end!
Hitting a homerun for me is like a joke.
Even if I couldn't hit a homerun, I was able to move around this much, so that was totally fine.
Every day felt like a club activity.  It was fun!
I told you how I couldn't move, right?
So really, this was a lot of fun!
Then, has everything been granted for you?
"Granted"?  What do you mean?
I mean, did you get to do everything you wanted to do when you were alive?
There's one more thing.
What is it?
To get married.
A girl's ultimate happiness.
But I couldn't do any household chores.
Worse yet, I couldn't do anything alone.
I was such a deadweight.
I wonder who would ever marry me.
God is so mean.
He took... all my happiness away...
That's not true.
In that case, Senpai...  Would you marry me?
That's...
I'd marry you!
Hinata.
I'll marry you.
I mean it... really.
But... you don't know who I really am.
However you might have been when you were alive, I'd marry you!
No matter what kind of handicap you might have had.
I can't walk, you know.  I can't get up, either.
I said no matter what kind of handicap, didn't I?!
Even if you can't walk or get up or have kids...
Even so, I'd still marry you!
I'd always be with you.
The person I came to know in this world isn't a fake Yui.
It's you.
No matter where I might have met you,
I'm sure I'd have come to love you.
If we meet again, with even a one in six billion chance, and even if you couldn't move again,
I'd still marry you.
We'd never meet up with each other.  I'd always be sleeping at home.
Well, I'd be playing baseball.
So I'll end up breaking one of your windows with a ball I've hit.
When I go to fetch that ball, you'd be there.
That's how we'd meet.
We'd start talking, and find that we get along, so I'd start visiting you every day.
I'd start taking care of you, as well.
How does that sound?
I like that.
Hey, when that happens,
my mom will be there, always taking care of me.
Make sure you take the weight off of her.
Count on it.
I'm glad.
Was that all right?
Sure it was.
What are you going to do now?
I'll stick around until the end.
There are still a bunch of people left that worry me.
I see.
What did I just kill?
A shadow?
Give a better explanation.
It can only be described as a shadow.
Noda-san just exterminated it.
Ooyama-san was in danger.
"Was in danger"?
From what?
Something strange is starting to happen in this world.
Did you do something again?!
Who'd have thought he'd drop his glasses...
Is this some sort of nightmare?
I tried to save him, too!
I don't need help!
This is too much of an irregularity...
Something's invading me, Otonashi-san!
Dancing in the shadow!
It'd be better gettin' obliterated by Tenshi.
You'll be obliterated!
What's going on?
Damn it!!
Yurippe!
I'll be waiting!
Well, we'll meet again if we can.