Let's go, one, two, three, four,
fly!
Fly!
"Kenzaki Makoto, the idol."
"Her debut hit sold a million copies in one week."
"Right now, she's on the fast track to stardom."
Could this girl really be Cure Sword?
Yes.
On the day that Cure Sword appeared in Clover Tower,
the number of people that went to and from the viewing platform differed.
Makoto and her manager left no traces of ever leaving.
But that's just...
No, there is more.
We have her fingerprints, shoe size, and DNA retrieved from her hair.
Everything matches.
Did you hire a forensics team?
Makopi is Cure Sword!
An idol and a Precure...
and she's amazing at both to boot!
There's no time to lose!
Hey, where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm gonna see Makopi and talk to her again!
Do you even know where she is?
I mean, we're talking about a celebrity.
It's not going to be that easy to see her.
In that case, please leave the matter to me.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
There's a fourth Precure?
I tell ya, they just keep coming.
There's gonna be a hundred of 'em soon enough.
Do something before it comes to that.
Why're you pushing it on me?
I'll help when they hit a thousand.
Why you...
Even four Precures...
Fiery Singer
can be a headache if they join forces.
I had planned to let them run free until we found a clue about the queen...
but perhaps it's best to destroy them before it's too late?
No Way!
That Girl Is Cure Sword??
It seems that Makoto is being filmed here for a music program.
A TV station?
How do we get inside?
W-Wait, Alice!
Welcome.
Good afternoon.
Oh, we can just walk in.
Good afternoon!
Please stop!
This area is restricted from people without business!
They are fine.
Those girls are my friends, after all.
Right!
My apologies!
What was with that?
This is one of the companies my father manages.
Yotsuba TV...
Yotsuba TV
Guess we should have noticed the name...
This song...
One, two, three, four, fly!
Fly!
Okay!
Good work!
Thank you very much.
Good luck on the show!
I-It's Makopi!
She's quite a splendid lady.
Don't get starstruck now!
We came to find out who she is.
Right.
So, what's the next plan?
There is no plan.
All right, onto the next rehearsal!
Do not worry.
I am certain Mana will find a way.
Ma-Mana!
Mana!
Ma—
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry!
Waiting Room 23
Music Xanadu!
Kenzaki Makoto
What's next on our schedule?
The fashion magazine photo shoot is in an hour.
The radio guest appearance is after that.
You have five interviews to give on the trains there.
Tonight, a meeting about the album.
Make sure to give the fan club an update today.
Oh, that's right.
Sign those while you have time.
I see. I'll start right away.
It's been a bit too busy lately.
I'm fine.
It's all for the people who wait for my songs.
That's right.
I'll bring a drink.
I don't have the time to be tired.
What is it?
Did you forget your wallet?
Be careful not to
forget your belongings.
Excuse me!
It's you again!
Yeah!
I'm Cure Heart!
Please be my ally!
Huh?
I've gotten a lot more experience since we last met!
There are three of us now!
I really admire how you can be so cute,
but still sing so powerfully!
And being a Precure on top of it?
It makes my heart race!
If you join with us,
we'd be a hundred...
no, a thousand times stronger!
Huh?
Um...
you are Cure Sword, right?
What are you talking about?
Huh?!
Do you understand where you are?
A TV station!
We're professionals!
We air dreams right into peoples' living rooms!
This is no place to stomp around as you please!
What's the commotion?
It's you...
There you are!
I figured you'd come to Makoto's waiting room.
I have an important performance soon.
Could you please leave?
Mana, let's go.
What a surprise.
I didn't think they'd let themselves in.
I don't trust that girl.
Perhaps.
But I felt her passion for you.
Really, what were you thinking?
You barged in alone with no plan,
and just did everything on a whim.
You should think more next time...
Rikka, please do not be so harsh.
Mana knows what she did was wrong.
I...
always thought I could befriend anyone with a handshake.
Especially a fellow Precure.
I was positive we'd be great friends.
But I forgot something important.
To be friends...
you have to understand each other's feelings!
Makopi's an idol, so singing is important to her,
but I still stomped on her passion.
Mana...
It seems you understand.
Kenzaki Makoto is always passionate.
That's why her songs echo in the heart.
You're...
the manager!
Filming
Next up is the chart topper, "Song Bird," by Kenzaki Makoto.
Song bird
La la la la
One Two Three Four
Fly!
Flying across the clear blue skies
Humming a tune to keep me strong
I wonder if you can hear the voice?
The melody continues forever
I hope the seeds that my words carry into your hearts
Will bloom into beautiful smiles
The tones that play from my headphones
She isn't very social.
Normally, she's pretty rough.
But her songs hold an important wish.
To make the people who hear her music...
have a smile on their face.
That's why she gives everything her all,
and pushes herself to give the best performance she can.
Can you relate?
I can, yes.
I want to apologize!
I see. I'll make some time, then.
Thank you so much!
The love I want to share
No matter how far away we are
We can come together
La la la la
One Two Three Four Fly
What're the director and cameramen so slack-jawed over?
Don't worry, even if you're sad,
When we sing together, we're happy
I'm not buyin' that she's top idol.
All the attention and spotlight should be on me!
But honestly, she is a better singer and dancer.
I should practice more.
Why not bathe in as much attention as you please?
Wh-Who's there?
I'll turn your desire into a dream come true.
Go berserk!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
It's a Selfish!
What's it doing here?
Now, end them!
Selfish!
I'm...
number one!
Makopi!
I am a star.
A big one, at that!
R-Run!
We have to save Makopi!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Rachel!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
Lance!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
Self!
Oh poor star who has lost his love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race once more!
Now do them in!
You three...
are a new idol group, no?
Huh?
I must pluck you while you're young!
This industry...
is merciless!
You newbies have no respect.
But remember...
This is how a star...
shines!
So bright!
The throne of a star...
is mine!
The only star...
is me!
Rival...
Crush!
Self?
Selfish...
Why did you do that?
I won't let it interfere!
This stage is important to you!
Because you want your songs to put a smile on everyone's face!
Self!
I'm bad with this mushy stuff.
Selfish, finish them off already!
Selfish!
Star...
Shine!
Cure Heart!
Move it!
What's that now? Can't do a thing?
Now end this!
Newbie...
Buster!
Ahself?
Wh-What?
Could that figure be...
Cure Sword!
So you finally show yourself.
Selfish!
Star...
Shine!
Seeelf!
She saw it?!
I didn't need sight to dodge that.
I am...
number one!
Self...
Davi!
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Love love looooove!
Huh?
What was I...
She's strong.
I'll remember this!
Um...
thanks.
I simply didn't want to leave a Selfish to its own devices.
Music Xanadu!
We opened with a lot of energy this week!
Hey, it's Makopi!
Seems that the recording went well.
Thank goodness.
But still...
I didn't get to apologize to Makopi in the end.
Aida Mana
DB?
That's the name of Makoto's manager!
This is...
Please keep singing!
Thank you very much.
Hooray!
Next, please!
It's you.
I came as a fan today.
I'm sorry about the other day.
It's fine now.
I realized something.
Just like the one you sing on,
I have my own stage that demands my attention.
I can't be as splendid as you,
but I want to give everything I can to make things work.
What is it you want to do?
Protect everyone's smiles!
Can you shake my hand?
People are still waiting.
Thank you very much!
Oh!
My dad made these peach buns for you.
They're super delicious, so eat them quick!
Peach... buns?
Line Ends Here
Looks like it went well.
But Makoto still seems to have doubts.
That's true.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Makopi is filming a cooking show with my dad!
Good luck!
Wait, Makopi!
Don't wash your vegetables with detergent!
Eek!
Don't crush those eggs!
How impressive.
She actually cut a cutting board!
That's Makopi for you!
Though that's not what you should praise her for!
Dokidoki Precure:
Hold The Phone!
Makopi's Coming to My House?!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!