It’s been a year and a half since then.
Even now, it's still hard to accept
that you're dead, Anchan.
"World champ"
But I'm glad I met you.
You brought us happiness.
If I hadn't met you that day...
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we can drop
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this wall where rules and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Editing:
Chandy10
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this wall where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find out fast we’re not alone
"Shonan Special Reformatory"
I met Anchan two years ago, in July of 1955.
I was full of desperation then.
So, now what do we do?
Hey. Can't you at least
turn around and say something?
I don't talk to little kids or monkeys.
What'd you say?!
Even after falling this far, you brats
still cling to your pathetic pride.
Or should I call you monkeys after all?
Shut the fuck up...
If you haven't noticed, you're an
asshole who's also "fallen this far."
Which makes us all assholes.
We could fight to the death
and no one would complain...
You're right. No one'll
give a shit if any of you die.
You guys are itchin' to fight, right?
Then bring it on.
I'll kill you!
Have a puff.
You're the last one.
I'll keep six for you. Make it quick.
What, do you think you've
won us over or something?
What exactly would I have to gain
by winning over a bunch of brats like you?
What I do know, though,
is that you guys have had
hard times on the outside.
That's good...
I hope to be on the outside
with you all the summer after next.
Anchan was strong.
Although he beat me up,
his fists were filled with warmth
and his words were filled with kindness.
Hey!
You two! Quit slackin' and play defense!
Sorry! Sorry!
Okay! We're at bat next!
A month later, we'd become close enough
to call each other by our nicknames.
Except for Scam, that is...
Do you know why Sakuragi
was thrown in here?
The truth is...
...he murdered his own parents!
His own parents!
Thanks!
I wouldn't eat it if I were you, Cabbage.
Eat anything a murderer
gives you and you're a goner.
I think it's time you give us an explanation!
And tell us how you ended up here
after murdering your own parents!
Who told you that?!
It was all a lie concocted by Ishihara.
But it soon developed into a serious incident.
What's that?
--What's going on?!
--There's a fire!
A fire?!
It looks like it started in the library!
The library?!
Hey.
Sakuragi is in Block 2,
Cell 6 right now, right?
Huh?
Wh-what are you doing?!
Oh, my. I can't find
the key to Block 2, Cell 6!
Here, Nomoto. Confirm
that the key is missing.
It's not here, right?
There's no way for me to open up
Block 2, Cell 6 now. Right?
We were trapped inside our cell.
It was Anchan who came to save us.
Sorry I took so long!
Anchan!
It's impossible, Anchan!
--Are you trying to open it by force?!
--That's crazy!
It wouldn't even budge
when we tried to ram it!
Shut up, you damn brats!
We can't give up just like that...
Our lives aren't that worthless!
Anchan...
A-Anchan's leg...
We're finished...
We can't give up yet!
He'll come to help us...
I'm sure of it...
I had almost given up all hope.
I hadn't trusted in Scam... I was pathetic...
"Shonan Hospital"
Listen, Everyone!
About the fire... The truth is...
I don't want to hear about it.
You saved us. That's all that matters.
After this incident, our bonds
became unwavering.
And then we all carved
our dreams into a tree on a hill
and promised to gather again
there the summer after next.
"That everyone's dreams come true"
Ishihara!
Rokurota Sakuragi...
Out.
You're moving.
"Block 1, Cell 8"
Even after that, Ishihara and Sasaki
continued their assault on him.
I stepped in to try to help Anchan...
...but wound up having my right hand shattered.
Oof...
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
They antagonized Anchan
because one year earlier...
"Block 2, Cell 6"
...his cellmate, Eiichi Hagino,
supposedly died in an accident.
But it wasn't an accident...
It was suicide.
"Sasaki paid Ishihara
and made me his plaything."
"They also broke their
promise to let me out sooner."
"I'm going to wait for my mom in heaven."
He left Anchan a suicide note.
Now they were going to kill him.
I was certain of it.
Mr. Kumagai, the only
person we could depend on,
was eliminated by Ishihara as well.
Our only option was to
protect Anchan ourselves.
So we set an escape plan into motion.
Hang on, Anchan. We will save you!
Scam's plan was brilliant.
Dr. Sasaki. Sorry to disturb you.
It's Jo Yokosuka from Block 2, Cell 6.
He suddenly has a pain in his stomach...
If it's nothing much, I'll give him
some pills and take him straight back.
I know, Doctor.
I'll make it nice and tight for you now!
Joe Stole the cell key from Sasaki
and Soldier and I rescued Anchan
from solitary confinement.
Anchan!
We came to get you, Anchan...
Okay! Let's go, Anchan!
We're all breaking out!
But things didn't work out
as well as planned.
So Scam...
...Cabbage...
...and Soldier...
--I broke the key.
--They all risked their lives to protect Anchan.
Anchan was finally free...
Setsuko!
Just where are you going, Maeda?
You'll get spotted if you don't stay put!
I brought medicine, food,
and a change of clothes.
I want to help, too.
Setsuko played a big part.
You're so emaciated...
What in the world happened to you?
I refuse... to die...
If it hadn't been for Setsuko,
he probably wouldn't have survived.
Everyone! Sakuragi is awake!
Go back to the reformatory.
Anchan?
Please!
Go and help Soldier, Scam and Cabbage...
Please...
He always cared for his
friends, first and foremost.
Joe gladly returned to the reformatory
after winning at rock-paper-scissors.
Our new life at the hideout
relied entirely on Setsuko,
So we got involved with the black
market to help her out a little.
Oh? You box, kid?
Are you any good?
Are you kidding, lady?!
He's the Shonan Reformatory's best fighter!
What?
He's practically in a league all of his own!
--Shonan Reformatory...
--Hey! Don't say things like that!
--Hey, Honey. It is okay?
--Shut up! You be quiet!
--Sure
Okay! You're in!
I wound up inside a boxing ring
for the first time in my life.
Mario! Mario!
It was a complete defeat.
Get stronger...
Get stronger and then come try again.
Damn it!
I'd felt plenty of frustration before then,
but that was the first time in my life
I'd ever been so mad at myself.
But Anchan understood how I felt.
It's late. Go to bed.
We start training tomorrow.
We can't let you end
on a defeat, can we, Mario?
Anchan held the sandbag for me,
despite not being fully healed.
Hey, Mario! Anchan!
I set up your next fight!
Saturday, January 28!
Anchan!
Yeah! Now let's win this time!
And then, the fated day arrived...
Well, take care!
Yeah. I'll see you later.
Looking back now, Setsuko
seemed strangely sad then.
Maybe that's why I asked him that...
Hey, Anchan...
How do you feel about Setsuko?
What brought that on?
You plan to be with her, don't you?
That's a good question.
There isn't a whole lot I can do for her,
but I do want to make her happy.
She went through a lot
of trouble just for me,
so I really want her to be happy.
Anchan... Watch me. I will win!
But, just before my match, we heard
that the police had caught Turtle.
Go on, Anchan. Something
bad must've happened.
Or else he wouldn't try and call us here...
Make sure you win, Mario.
Of course I will!
Anchan...
What exactly happened after that, Anchan?
You had a fatal stab wound
in your gut before the MPs shot you.
I also heard that Sasaki was there.
It was Ishihara who stabbed you.
I'm sure of it.
I'm gonna go find out now.
I -- we -- can't move forward
until this is finally settled.
You understand, don't you, Anchan?
This sharp gaze
same ta manazashi
What is it focused on?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
Something that needs protecting?
mamoru beki mono
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
Not even if this body matters
to me
even if I rot away
just keep on running
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
will now start to intertwine
with fate
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
and continue into the
endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it's now
a far off distance
There are things a man must do.
The boys take action, to move
forward on their own paths.