It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I believed in the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
Even if your feelings break,
even if your wishes are far away,
don't forget the kindness that
has always been at your side.
There has been a heart
that supported you,
and there is someone that
is waiting for you to smile.
With true feelings, make a wish.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
A dimensional tremor has started,
and its magnitude is
gradually increasing!
If the magnitude continues
to increase at this rate,
we estimate the creation of
a dimensional fault in thirty minutes!
The Garden's reactors are Lost Logia
of the same type as the Jewel Seeds!
She's engaged them,
fully aware that they might
run out of control, to supply her
the output that she lacks!
She meant this to be a one-way trip
from the very beginning!
Chrono, where are you going?
I'm going to head to the scene!
I have to stop the cause of it all!
I'll go with you!
Me too!
All right.
Aruf, you stay by Fate's side.
Right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Chrono, Miss Nanoha, Yuuno!
I'm going to head on-site as well!
I will trust you all with the arrest
of Precia Testarossa!
Roger!
The Time of the Sealing of Our Fates
There's lots of them.
This is only the entrance.
There are many more inside.
Chrono, what are they?
They're nothing but machines
that attack nearby targets.
I see.
Then there's nothing to worry about.
You don't need to waste time
on opponents of this level.
Stinger Snipe.
So quick!
Snipe Shot!
Break Impulse.
Don't just stand there! Let's go!
Okay!
That hole... Be careful of anywhere
that has black spaces!
The imaginary number plane.
It's a space where no magic
can be executed!
Flying magic will also be deleted.
If you fall in, you'll fall to the bottom
of the gravitational pull,
and never be able to
get yourself out of it!
I'll be careful!
We're going to split up here!
You two, seal the reactor
on the top floor!
What about you, Chrono?
I'm going to head over to Precia.
That's my job, after all.
I'lll make you a path right now!
When I do...
Yeah!
Blaze Cannon.
Chrono, be careful!
I will be going as well!
Put up a distortion shield
within the Garden,
and hold back the progress
of the dimensional tremor!
I'm worried about those kids,
so I'm going to go
help them out a little too.
I'll be back soon.
And when everything is all done...
It doesn't matter how slowly,
but I want you to turn back to
the real Fate that I love so much.
From now on, you're free to use
all the time you have for yourself.
Mother didn't smile at me once,
to the very end.
The only reason I wanted to live on
was for Mother to accept me.
No matter how much
she claimed I lacked,
no matter what horrible
things she did to me.
Still, I wanted her to smile.
Even after she threw me
aside so clearly,
I am still clinging to Mother.
Aruf...
Aruf, you've been at my side
for all this time.
I'm sure you were deeply saddened
when I didn't listen to
what you had to say.
That girl in the white outfit that
I clashed with so many times...
The first person who
looked at me straight on,
and treated me as an equal.
I saw her many times,
I fought her many times,
and she called out my name
so many times.
Over and over...
The only reason I wanted to live on
was for Mother to accept me!
I had thought that there was
no other reason for me to live!
I thought that I wouldn't be able
to live on if I couldn't do it!
It's not good to just throw it out.
And it's even worse to just
keep running away from it.
Nothing with me... between us...
has even begun?
Is that so, Bardiche?
Perhaps I haven't even really started?
Get set.
That's right.
You've been at my side for
all this time too, Bardiche!
You don't want it to end
like this either, right?
Yes, sir.
I'm not sure if I can do it well,
but let's try our best together.
You taught me to escape
from the clear skies
The quiet wish that
wells up in my heart
Recovery.
Let's get ourselves
back into our hands
Nothing between us has even begun.
On the other end of the sky
as I look up, your gaze
Gets hit by the rain
of caring and disappears
That is why, in order for me
to begin my true self,
Let me down, it doesn't stop
I have to put an end to
what I have been until now!
Shake up, realizing for the first time,
entrusting, take a shot
Looking around, you were there
The reason why I can fight
without hesitation
Is so that I can bloom
in wondrous colors
To look straight at my weak heart
Dammit! There are too many enemies!
It would be nice if that was all.
You...
Whichever way I turn, which way
to walk headed for where
I have to do something!
I just stood there, unable to decide
on my own path to take
Nanoha!
I just stood there, unable to decide
on my own path to take
Without losing hope
in the distant future
Nanoha!
Without losing hope
in the distant future
Thunder Rage.
Unbreakable courage
hidden in the clouds
I have drive, call it awake
Get set.
Take off, shaken, woken up,
asked, pave the way
Thunder...
Take off, shaken, woken up,
asked, pave the way
Rage!
Take off, shaken, woken up,
asked, pave the way
I will go with you, without worries
Why did you keep hesitating?
Fate?!
So that I can win a clear victory
Let's grab countless
wishes in our hands
It's a big one... The barrier is strong.
Yeah. And that thing on its back!
But if the two of us are together...
Yeah! Yeah, yeah!
Let's go, Bardiche!
Get set.
Us too, Raising Heart!
Stand by ready.
Strongly, gently,
give wind to the wings
Thunder...
Shake up, realizing for the first time,
entrusting, take a shot
There is nothing that I can lose
Smasher!
Shaken, woken up,
asked, pave the way
Divine Buster!
So that I can win a clear victory
Let's grab countless
wishes in our hands
Here we go!
Let's grab countless
wishes in our hands
You're here!
But you didn't make it in time!
Right, Alicia?
Oh, Alicia...
Fate!
Fate! Fate!
Aruf...
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I'll end it with my own hands,
and after that,
I'll begin who I really am.
Just a little bit more...
We can head to the reactor
from that elevator.
Okay, thanks!
Fate, are you going to
head over to your mom?
I, um, I can't really put it
into words well...
Good luck.
Thanks.
Right now, Chrono is
headed there on his own.
If we don't hurry,
we might not make it in time!
Fate!
Amy!
Nanoha and Yuuno have
entered the reactor!
Fate and Aruf are headed
to the bottom floor!
It's all right! I'm sure we can do it!
Yeah!
I'll take care of defense.
Nanoha, concentrate on the sealing!
Yeah. Just like always, right?
Yuuno, you've always been together
with me, and protected me.
Sealing Mode.
That's why I can fight!
Because I have that
warmth at my back!
Let's go!
Divine Shooter, full power!
Shoot!
Precia Testarossa...
This is the end.
I am suppressing the
dimensional tremor.
The reactor will be
sealed away in due time,
and there is an Enforcer
headed towards you.
The forgotten capital, Alhazard,
and all the secret spells that lie there,
their existence is only a vague myth!
That's not true!
The path to Alhazard lies in
the gap between dimensions!
When time and space are shattered,
the glimmers that fall into their gap...
The path surely lies there!
A gamble that has such
a slim chance of winning...
What in the world do you
want to do by going there?
Bring back the lost time and take back
the mistakes you made?
That's right!
I'm going to bring back into my hands
the past and the future
for Alicia and I!
I'm going to bring it back.
This wasn't how it
was supposed to be.
Everything in the world...
This world is always full of things
that weren't supposed to be this way!
From the past, for all time,
for anyone, that's how it is!
Everyone is free to run away
from or stand up against
the reality that wasn't how
it was supposed to be!
But, nowhere, nobody has the right
to rope innocent people into
your selfish depression!
Mother!
What did you come here for?
Begone. I have no more use for you.
I came here because I wanted
to say something to you.
L.
I am not Alicia Testarossa!
I may be just a doll
that you have created.
But, I, Fate Testarossa,
am your daughter, that you
brought to life and raised!
So what?!
Are you telling me to think of you
as a daughter after all this?
If you so wish.
If you so wish,
I will protect you from
anyone in this world,
and from anything that goes on.
Not because I am your daughter.
But because you are my mother!
How stupid.
Not good!
Captain, it's no good!
The Garden is going to fall apart!
Please come back!
Destruction of this caliber won't
cause a dimensional fault!
Chrono, all of you should escape now!
There isn't much time before
that place is destroyed!
Roger that!
Fate Testarossa!
Fate!
I am going to head to Alhazard!
And I will bring everything back!
My past, my future, and my
one and only happiness!
Mother!
Fate!
Let us go together, Alicia.
This time, so that we don't
part from one another...
Fate!
Please, everyone!
Hurry up and escape!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
The incident has finally
come to an end.
Finally, the ending that arrives,
and the time of parting.
But an ending is always
the beginning of something else.
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Thirteen: Call My Name
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode Thirteen: Call My Name
Final episode: Call My Name
Lyrical, magical,
I'll see you again, right?