Reminiscence
It was April 29th,
the first day of Golden Week.
So now, my stepfather's new wife is my mom,
and her new husband is my dad.
So you mean that your current
parents aren't your real parents?
Aren't they supposed to not tell you that kind of thing?
They were frank with me.  I heard
about it before I even started school.
It was like I was just a nuisance.
Even if they wanted to give me up for
adoption, they had to keep up appearances.
That's why I decided to be a good girl.
Being a "good girl" is just being normal, right?
I'd be looked at with prejudice because of my complicated family life, right?
I decided I wasn't going to let that affect me.
Hanekawa...
What are you going to do, Araragi-kun?
It's finally Golden Week.  Aren't you going to study?
It's finally Golden Week, so why do I have to study?
Black
Unnumbered cut
I go for walks on my days off,
since I don't want to be at home.
The thought of spending all day at home... It makes me shiver.
Red
Unnumbered cut
So I go for walks on my days off.
I feel you think too hard about it.
Hey, what's up with your face?
Promise you won't tell anyone?
I promise.
My dad hit me this morning.
He hit you?
That's...!
Come on, think about it, Araragi-kun.
If a kid you didn't know started acting all familiar with you,
don't you think you'd be angry or get rough?
Black
Unnumbered cut
Come on!
Should you really be justifying it!?
You shouldn't forgive that kind of thing!
It's fine.  He only did it once.
Plus, you promised me.
You promised me that you wouldn't tell anyone.
But...
I can't keep that kind of promise.
Please, Araragi-kun!
Don't tell anyone about this!
I'll do anything for you if you keep it secret!
Please!
Fine, I understand.
Black
Unnumbered cut
Huh?
Will you help out?
It's better to back off now while there's still time
Before we misunderstand each other even more
Before I knew it,
The staple you used to bind your words pierced my heart
It's your fault
Don't come to me the way I am now
Don't look at me wherever I go
Don't let go of me with that smile
No matter who you are
I prayed for an endless eternity
In the sky that stretches on forever
Like the sea with its harsh love,
You dove into my heart to take it
I want to deliver these feelings to you
That can't be weighed
GHO      ST   ORY
T S U B A S A   C A T
bakemono
gatari
Hanekawa Tsubasa is,
to me, a very
important person.
She's irreplacable.
I owe her.
N o ,
I owe her
a lot.
Whatever I do, I don't think it's possible to repay her.
Hanekawa
Tsubasa.
A girl with fantastic wings.
A class rep among class
reps, chosen by God.
She's well-received by the school, and popular among the class.
Not only was she honest, but
she had a helpful personality too.
This might not be the right way to put it,
but I couldn't believe what I learned about
her family background during Golden Week.
Golden Week----
The nine days between April 29th and Sunday, May 7th.
She was charmed
by a cat.
She was charmed by a cat like I was attacked by a demon.
The oddities have their reasons
----In this case, it seems like the family discord and twistedness
that Hanekawa felt were that reason.
Even still...
Pressure
Hanekawa reached out her hand to me. She didn't have the time to help me over spring break----but even still, she lifted me up from the deepest depths.
I'll never forget that. No matter what happens.
Yellow
Unnumbered cut
Episode 11
Tsubasa Cat Part 1
Font used in video: HGP Mincho B
Naoetsu High
Black
Unnumbered cut
Sengoku Nadeko
Cut number 62
Koyomi onii-chan, I've been waiting!
Hey, Sengoku!
What are you doing here?
Um, Koyomi onii-chan...
I wanted to thank you again.
You should go thank Kanbaru instead.
Kanbaru came through here already, right?
But before I was able to call out to her, she took off faster than the eye could see.
Perhaps she was on her way to read the rest of all of
those BL novels she bought yesterday ..... the rest omitted
Reprinted from Ghostory vol. 2, published by Kodansha
Cut number 73
I'm sure that she was just in a hurry to get somewhere.
Like a delivery worker.
Why are you referring to the special
attack of Prince Yamato from Bikkuriman!?
It's hard to understand and it takes too long to explain!
I didn't think anyone would find it funny either.
You're always so funny, Koyomi onii-chan.
I haven't really thought about it, but has this been
my role since elementary school? ..... the rest omitted
Reprinted from Ghostory vol. 2, published by Kodansha
Cut number 81
But what should I do?
What's wrong?
I had other things to talk to her about too.
Really?
I'll do that for you.
I've got to thank her, too.
It'd make me feel bad.
Don't say that.  It's nothing.
Leave it to me.
Really?  Can you do it for me?
Here!
Koyomi
Cut number 88
I made her clothes nice and clean, so give them to her if you don't mind, okay?
Sure.
Koyomi
Cut number 93
What kind
of test
is this?
Yeah, sure.
That's right, Sengoku.
Mind if I ask you something?
What would you like to know?
It's not a big deal.  I'm just curious about Shinobu.
Shinobu?
Remember how after dealing with the Snake Constrictor yesterday,
we went and stayed overnight at an abandoned night school since it was so late?
Reminiscence
Answer the question.
Cut number 107
She was the cute little blonde there.
Answer the question.
Cut number 108
Did she tell you anything while I was gone?
Nope.
I see.
She's a vampire, right?
Yeah.
Well, she's more like a pseudo-vampire now.
So she's the one who turned you into a vampire?
It's not her fault.  It's mine.
Besides, it's wrong to blame the oddities.
That's just how they are.
They have their reasons.
That's all there is.
I see.
Oddity
Oh well, don't trouble yourself with it.
You should go back to your everyday life.
Oddity
Well, come see me if anything happens.
If you're really in trouble, you'll get help faster going to Oshino.
Arara
gi-s
enpai
Koyomi
onii-san
Ararag
i-kun
RA RA RA
R-Really?
Well, he did warn me about it.
We can't just keep relying on him.
If we leave everything to Doraemon's secret gadgets, we'll be just like Nobita.
That's right.
Oshino-san's charm was really just like one of Doraemon's secret gadgets.
They're like the genius helmet and the craft glove!
Why are you referring to the minor stuff that only shows up in the movies?
Cut 117
Use the take-copter or the anywhere door as examples!
You're really good at references, Koyomi onii-chan.
What is it?
What do you mean?
You're defending the
wrong place in a lot of ways
When I do it with you, it feels like you're judging me as a man.
Nah, it's nothing.
By the way, Koyomi onii-chan.
What?
I was wondering about Shinobu.
Shinobu?
She kept staring at me.
Her eyes are completely different when she looks at you or Oshino-san
Nadeko's line
Cut number 140
Cut number 141
than when she looks at me or Kanbaru-san.
Nadeko's line
Cut number 140
You mean she looks at men and women differently?
I'm pretty sensitive, so I noticed.
Is that you, Araragi-kun?
Black
Unnumbered cut
What are you doing there?
Umm...
Oh, Hanekawa.  This is the girl I was talking about yesterday.
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-Sorry!
Naoetsu High
School Stop
Hanekawa's line
Cut number 158
That kind of stings, Araragi-kun.
Umm.  She's Sengoku Nadeko, my sister's friend whom I was telling you about yesterday.
Oh, that's right, Araragi-kun.  Umm...
What happened to the snake after that?
It's been dealt with for now.
Oshino ended up helping us out again.
I don't really get what happened, but I guess you it got cleared up quickly.
Yeah, I guess.
Naoetsu High
School Stop
She was pretty cute.
That's your middle school's uniform, right?
You really do know everything.
I don't know everything, I just happen to know this.
By the way, Araragi-kun.
What?
Didn't you say that you were doing something today?
Don't tell me it was to talk with a cute middle scho-
That's not it.
Silence silence silence silence silence silence
Cut number 173
It was about Senjougahara.
I didn't tell you because I was embarrassed.
Senjougahara-san, eh?
Black
Unnumbered cut
I'll tell you some interesting gossip.
What?  It sounds pretty dull, but I'll listen.
Senjougahara has been acting funny ever since she got friendly with you.
You're a bad influence on Senjougahara.
That kind of thing.
Hoshina-sensei asked me about it earlier.
"Hanekawa, do you know anything about this?"
I don't really understand why you two are into each other.
But I'm sure that people will keep on saying that kind of thing.
Yeah, they will.
And it'll be tough.
You have to prove that it's not like that.
Senjougahara-san won't like it if you ruin her reputation by having people say she's no good as she's hooked up with you.
Yeah, you're right.
But I stood up for you.  I told him "no way."
Really?  Thanks.
But do you really think that?
That there's no way?
Yeah, of course!
I don't lie.
You're the only person I've ever heard say that who isn't lying.
Oh?
I'm sure a lot of people do.
It's the other way around.  I think Senjougahara-san is improving.
I don't know whether it's because she's feeling better or it's because of you.
You've got to support this change in her.
You sure don't talk like a high schooler.
Really?  I think it's normal.
Oh.
By the way, I wonder if Hanekawa has anyone like that.
She's kind to everyone, but I wonder if there's someone special.
Hey, Hanekawa.
What?
What is it, Araragi-kun?
Well, umm...
How about Doraemon's secret gadgets?
Ow!
Black
Unnumbered cut
Headache
Cut number 210
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But...!
You worry too much.
Episode 11 Password: Headache
Headache
Cut number 210
Hanekawa, don't tell me...
It's happening again, like it did during Golden Week?
Top curtain   Unnumbered cut
Lower curtain   Unnumbered cut
Remi
niscence
Top curtain   Unnumbered cut
Lower curtain   Unnumbered cut
Golden Week.  The nine days between April 29th and May 7th.
Reminiscences Next
Hey, Hanekawa!
It hurts!
Hanekawa!
She was charmed by a cat.
Meddlesome Cat
Cut number 242
A meddlesome cat.
Meddlesome cat?
Yes.  Perhaps a whitecat.
No, it's usually a meddlesome cat.
A tailless cat.
A cat whose tail you can't pull.
What does that mean, Oshino?
Putting it realistically, a multiple personality disorder.
It's a form given to the Class Rep's hidden personality.
A dark, evil Hanekawa Tsubasa.
Let's call it Black Hanekawa.
White
Unnumbered cut
But she's so white.
It's not about how she looks, it's about what's inside.
What's wrong, Araragi-kun?
You're more impatient than you usually are.
You weren't this irritated when you were attacked by a demon over spring break.
RAGE
So how do I return Hanekawa back to normal?
Don't sweat it.  I'll explain the whole thing.
There's a reason for the Black
Class Rep, the meddlesome cat, appearing.
That reason is stress.
Stress?
Cut number 248
It's gotta be some pretty serious stress.
Pretty major stress that's added up over the years.
Araragi-kun, is there anything the
Class Rep has been stressing about?
Love?  Schoolwork?
Or maybe family.
Cut number 251
Writhing in the darkness
Cut number 253
Meowahaha
Cut number 254
Black Hanekawa attacked the townspeople indiscriminately, night after night.
By doing so, she relieved Hanekawa's stress.
Palm
Drain
Cut number 267
The meddlesome cat's special ability as an oddity is to drain energy.
Like what you see in video games.  It completely sucks away the touched person's strength and vitality.
That energy drain was enough to put people in the hospital.
Man x Woman
Cut number 278
Two patients entered the hospital.
The two who became most ill were the first afflicted.
And these two were the reason for Hanekawa's stress.
Palm
Black
Unnumbered cut
Her parents.
Cut number 281
And on the last day of Golden Week, May 7th.
Dead End
Cut number 292
Hey human, I've caught you.
I don't know what you're trying to do following me around,
but you're wasting your time, meow~
Danger Do Not Enter
As long as the Mistress is still
stressed, I'm not going anywhere.
By the way, meow~  If you
don't deal with it within a year...
Shinobu.
No, back then her name wasn't Shinobu yet.
Her special ability as a vampire is to drain energy, the same as a meddlesome cat.
But meddlesome cats and vampires are
completely different kinds of oddities.
Danger Do Not Enter
The incarnation of Hanekawa's stress was a meddlesome cat.
It was removed thanks to Shinobu's energy drain.
Hanekawa's stress was dealt with for the moment.
Danger Do Not Enter
End of
Reminiscence
That solved the problem.
It's not the same as how she was complaining about strange pains during Golden Week.
But...!
Hey, Hanekawa!
I told you, I'm fine.
The nurse's office...  No, he wouldn't be there now.  How about the hospital?
I told you, I'm fine.  Stop
exaggerating things, Araragi-kun.
But hasn't this been happening to you a lot?
I told you, you worry too much.
You're pretty timid, Araragi-kun.
But you're...!
Well, I guess you're kind.
Black
Unnumbered cut
More importantly, do you understand Senjougahara-san better?
And you've got to put it into practice too.
Sure, got it.
Sorry for making you worry about my problems.
I don't mind.
Anyway, you should show me that you understand what I'm saying.
What?
The bloomers and the school swimsuit that you're clutching like they're your treasure.
Bloomers
Convulsive motion
Cut number 337
School swimsuit
You should probably put them in your bag.
Ghostory
Cat
Tsubasa Cat Part 1
Continued
Next Episode
Deneb, Altair, and Vega
That's the Summer Triangle you pointed at
I remember that when I look up at the sky
I finally found Vega
But where are you, Altair?
You'll be alone like this
I looked up from the pitch dark world
It's like the night sky is filled with raining stars
I wonder when I started to chase after you
Please, no matter what
Don't be surprised
Listen to
These feelings
Of mine
Now streaming an extended preview at our website!
Preview
Dialog
Nisioisin
Cartoon
Haritama Hiroki
I'm Karen!
I'm Tsukihi!
Wake up!
Get up!
Preview puzzle!
Puzzle!?
What's the difference between a puzzle and a quiz?
Damn annoying sisters with a brother complex!
Puzzles are tricky.  Quizzes are hard.
He's drunk
I just don't
know anymore.
Yeah, they're hard.
They're tricky.
Next time, Tsubasa Cat Part 2!
Next Episode
Tsubasa Cat Part 2
It's the last TV episode.
He was late
It's so sudden!