Greater Levitation.
Modifier, Empower!
It is time.
I've had to wait too long, Yurika Nijino.
No, Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika.
You will soon find yourself in
endless fear and suffering.
I will end you.
Invaders of the Rokujyouma!?
Corona Convention
Approved
I told you, I'm not cosplaying!
An Evil Magical Girl Appears?!
I really am a magical girl.
That's Yurika-chan for you.
You really stick to your story, don't you?
Sorry, she's always like this.
Satomi-san, not you, too!
I'm always telling you, there's evil magical
girls after apartment 106 at Corona House!
I'm there to stop them!
I'm really sorry for this.
It's fine.
Please believe me!
Stop by the club room sometimes, okay?
We'll just come and take you by
force when we need you, though.
How can I get them to believe me?
Don't worry, my friend Yurika.
You're one hell of a cosplayer!
I'm trying to tell you...
Good morning.
This class is getting
another transfer student.
Go ahead and introduce yourself.
Maki Aika
My name is Maki Aika.
Nice to meet you all.
M-Maki-chan?!
Maki-chan!
I'm glad you made it here!
Wh-What?
Satomi-san, Satomi-san, look!
Maki Aika
This is one of the bad magical
girls trying to get that room.
She's part of the magical organization "Darkness
Rainbow". Her name is Dark Navy-chan.
What?
I'm surprised you have a friend willing
to cosplay your story with you.
I want the egg next!
Why won't you believe me?
Maki-chan isn't a friend.
She's an enemy!
Dark Navy is good with magic that
controls dark navy hearts.
You're such a pain.
Don't be like that, Sanae.
Yurika, don't worry about what anyone says.
You're fine the way you are.
Satomi-san...
We have aliens, Earth people, ghosts.
It's nice to have a normal person around,
even if your hobbies are kind of strange.
I'm not normal!
Hey, Koutarou.
What did you mean by that?
I'm saying it's important to be different.
I see!
Anyway, let's get back to the classroom.
I'm...
I'm going to stay here for a bit longer.
Got it.
Don't be late to class.
That was someone who lives at the
magical convergence, wasn't it?
Maki-chan...
Do you think you'll
be able to stop us from
getting to him, or that room?
So, we're going to fight...
Of course we are.
Why do you think I came here?
Also, this argument should
have ended centuries ago.
The wound your predecessor, Rainbow Nana,
gave me eight months ago has finally healed.
And now I'm up against a failure like you.
I'm not going to lose.
That's not true!
I'm going to do just fine
in Nana-chan's stead!
It's true you've gotten
a little clever yourself.
You're pretending to be a cosplayer,
and telling everyone you're a magical girl.
That wasn't really—
You don't have to play dumb!
And then you told everyone who
I was when I transferred in.
That was pretty underhanded.
No, Maki-chan.
It's not like I planned any of that...
Then you're saying someone
else planned it for you?
Huh?
No, that's not—
You're not going to fool me.
I already know what's going on.
This is getting interesting.
Please listen to me, Maki-chan!
Huh?
Club Entry Form
Class 1-A
Name: Maki Aika
Cosplay Society
I'm going to join that
Cosplay Society of yours.
Now we'll be the same.
Prepare yourself, Yurika.
Not you, too, Maki-chan...
Oh, Yurika-san.
Sakuraba-senpai?
Good timing.
I wanted to ask you something.
Harukaze Shopping District
I-I want to get closer to Satomi-kun.
You're already pretty friendly.
That's not what I meant...
I, uh...
You know... closer...
Oh...
That's what you meant.
I was hoping Satomi-kun
could treat me less carefully.
Like how he treats you or Theiamillis-san.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I mean, he's kind of mean sometimes,
and has no problem with
hitting you on the head.
But, Satomi-kun's never hit me or
said anything mean to me...
Bop, bop!
Well, he's never been nice to—
I understand how you feel.
I'll do my best to help you.
Glass Masks
I've read this girls' manga for ten years.
I know how to make someone fall in love.
Thank you, Yurika-san.
So, what do I have to do?
Well, you can start by going
on a double date, or something.
Ask Satomi-san to go on a date with you!
A-A date?
I see...
So, Sakuraba-senpai likes Satomi-san...
Well, anyway... I guess now that Maki-chan
is here, I'm going to have to fight.
I'm not sure if I can...
But, I have to.
Nana-san saved my life.
Yurika fight!
So, cheers to Maki Aika for transferring in!
Cheers!
A party for Maki-chan?!
Satomi-chan, why did you
invite Maki-chan here?
Oh, you're finally back, Yurika.
Welcome back, Yurika-san.
We got ourselves a new transfer student.
Why not have a party for her?
I told you already.
Maki-chan is after this room.
She'll be able to take all the data she
wants if you just let her walk right in here.
That's your cosplay story, right?
It's not a story!
Please, Satomi-san, if
we don't kick Maki-chan out,
we'll have a real problem!
H-Hey, Yurika...
You shouldn't talk to a friend like—
What's going on?
Explain it to me, Yurika.
What's going on with Aika-san?
Well...
Hey, look at this, Kou!
They were having a sale on
snacks and stuff at the store,
so I brought some stuff.
Makkenji?!
Rhinoceros Man chocolate,
and Rhinoceros Man gum.
We got potato chips,
dessert pancakes...
Huh?
Rhinoceros beetle,
Rhinoceros beetle...
You chose a rhinoceros beetle over me...
Over me!
Take this!
Ruth-san, calm down!
Let me go!
Let me go, now!
Satomi-san, I need to talk to you!
We're going to lose apartment 106 at this rate!
This is a bad time, Yurika!
Hey, Makkenji!
Get rid of those snacks!
R-Right...
Caucasus
Atlas
Hey!
Ruth-san!
Satomi-san, please listen to me!
We need to kick Maki-chan out, now!
Let it go already, Yurika.
Why not let her stay for today?
You can pretend to be enemies tomorrow.
Yes, I think you're going a little overboard
with the whole "kick her out" thing.
Yeah, this party is for her.
Why doesn't...
Why doesn't anyone believe me?!
Y-Yurika!
I don't care anymore!
I don't care what happens anymore!
Y-Yurika...
A date...
Like a real date, right?
But, I can't...
Yurika-san?
Sakuraba-senpai...
I try to tell everyone the truth,
but no one believes me...
And that's why you're crying here alone?
Even if they don't believe you, you
still care for your friends, correct?
Huh?
That's why you're so sad, right?
I don't know why you're sad,
but if you want them to believe you,
you'll just have to continue to do things
to try and get them to believe you.
Not just with words, with actions.
Try to get them to believe me
with actions, not just words...
Maki-chan is here, so I can...
Thank you, Sakuraba-senpai!
I'll do my best!
You can do it.
Hey, Yurika.
We're going to school.
Do you not feel well?
That's not it.
But, today is...
Just go without me.
Are you sure you're okay?
Does this have to do with what you
were trying to tell me yesterday?
Well...
Koutarou, we're going to be late!
I know.
Anyway, Yurika, come to school if you can.
I don't think we need to worry about Yurika,
but just in case, I'm going
to leave Korama behind.
Thanks, Korama!
No problem, Karama!
Thanks, Kiriha-san.
Anyway, we're going to get going.
Maybe we should let them
know she'll be absent.
We'll see...
I can't depend on words any longer.
I'm a magical girl, and
I will protect this room.
I want Satomi-san... I want
everyone to believe me.
I know Yurika-san said she'd come with me,
but I'm the one who has
to ask Satomi-kun out...
Harumi Sakuraba-san, correct?
Wh-Who are you?
You want to do a continuation
of the Blue Knight play?
Yes.
The theater club has requested
that we have another play at
the beginning of the year...
Well, of course they would.
Anyway, Koutarou, you'll have to
practice being a knight again.
Get ready.
Koutarou, everyone else, come here.
Yurika left in her cosplaying outfit?!
That's correct.
She went somewhere after
dressing up like a magical girl.
Did she skip school so she
could practice cosplaying?
That would be the natural assumption.
Jeez, and everyone was worried, too...
Sis, what should we do?
I'm tracking her on radar.
I can go after her immediately.
Right.
Korama, follow Yurika—
No.
I'll go.
Korama, tell me where she is.
Your friends won't attack that room while
I'm out here with you, right Maki-chan?
Yes, I promise.
Have I lied to you before?
That's true. You...
Also, I can deploy a wide-area spell
to keep people away from here.
That works to both of our benefits.
Sanctuary modifier.
Effective area: colossal!
Here I come, Rainbow Yurika!
I'm going to win.
I'm going to protect that room!
Energy bolt. Target option,
Sidewinder!
Quick Cast,
Multiple Energy Bolt!
Target option, spread!
Korama said she'd be around here.
Yeah, this is the right way.
This soy sauce cup ramen smell...
It's definitely Yurika's spirit energy.
Yurika smells like that?
Inside there!
I'm sure she's in there, Koutarou!
Okay!
S-Sanae?
What's this?
Koutarou, there's an invisible
wall or something here.
What?
Yeah, right.
Let's go.
Huh?
Why?
Yurika...
Yurika's just a regular cosplayer...
Tiny Memory Flash!
Modifier, extend length!
Anti-Magic Shield!
Huh?
Where's Maki-chan?
Right here!
What just happened?
Did you forget?
My magic is the dark navy that
controls people's hearts and minds.
That's right...
You can erase people's
memories for a few seconds.
But, if I give up now, I can't call
myself a resident of apartment 106!
I have to use my actions
to get them to believe me!
It seems you've got more courage than before,
but you won't be—
I found her!
Yurika! Aika-san!
Satomi-san!
Sanae-chan!
Are you saying you got through
both of our barriers?
Let's leave, Yurika.
Let's go back to school.
You can do your cosplay another time.
Satomi-san...
You're just a normal cosplayer.
You don't have to be here.
So, let's go...
You still won't listen to me?
I'm a magical girl!
Maki-chan is my enemy.
I'm fighting her right now.
Yurika...
I've figured this out.
Koutarou Satomi.
You're a mage that has evolved
all on his own in this world,
and then gave Yurika
knowledge and helped her.
What are you saying, Maki?
You even have a ghost...
No!
They don't have anything to do with this.
Your fight's with me!
That's right.
I'm not planning on trying to
fight all of you mages at once.
I'll be taking my leave...
but only after I take
care of you first, Yurika.
Bind Person! Modifier,
double effect!
Quick Cast, Anti-Magic Shield!
I'll be sending you to hell, Yurika!
You dispelled it?
No way. Without a staff
or an incantation...
Also, what was that white light just now?
Maki-san, just stop already.
I'll just have to...
Sakuraba-senpai!
S-Satomi-kun.
Yurika-san.
Why are you here?
I'm not sure why, either...
M-My body is moving on its own...
I can't do anything.
Stop it, Maki-san!
She has a weak constitution!
Don't get her involved in this!
It seems this girl is effective
against you, as well,
and not just Yurika.
What should we do, Koutarou?
Stone Rain! Modifier, effective time double!
Satomi-san, watch out!
Quick Cast, Force Field!
The stones are...
Magical Girl Rainbow Yurika, huh?
Huh?
You were always telling me.
I never believed you.
No, I think I didn't want to believe you.
Satomi-san...
Yurika, let's save Sakuraba-senpai together!
Right!
I'm ending this now, Yurika!
Blast Fireball! Modifier, high concentrate!
What's that?!
Be careful.
Even if you have protective magic,
getting hit by that is dangerous!
We have to get the first hit in, then!
Yurika, back me up!
Sanae, we're splitting up and getting her.
Right!
Not a problem.
I have no intention of aiming at all of you.
Sakuraba-senpai!
Recall, pre-cast teleport.
Yurika!
Yurika-san...
We're playing shiritori today!
I'll start.
Haniwa da ho! (Japanese doll)
Holy crap da ho!
Hoax da ho!
Homunculus da ho!
Homing missile da ho!
Next Episode: The Sun and a Rainbow
Why do they all start with "ho?"
Ho?