I will...
...make your wish come true.
Because I can sense that
your wish and my wish...
...are the same.
But then...
...why are you crying?
Ow, my head...
Tea and pickled plums
work best for hangovers.
Here.
Thank you, Grandma...
What a sad drunk.
Shut up...
Oh my. Ru-chan, look at the time.
Yup, I know.
Time...?
She's going out with her friend.
Sour...!
Nice!
Have fun, you hear?
Okay.
What is it, Bro?
All right. Let your kind,
big brother here send you out.
What? No way!
I'm going!
See you later.
She refused me...
If a pillar goes there...
Taken and granted,
ideals are repetitious games that slip through
My daily life is so shot with holes
that I can barely stand
Empty theories without conclusions
Dance steps along invisible rules
The final bell holding together
the crumbling day rings
In the scene I imagine
you're there
with a smile
No forgiveness? No desires?
And still
We cry "OPEN"
A future to get back and a world to destroy
A wish to open. GOT IT?
Now cross
I wish you don't cry
The future of light and dark,
let's believe in the "future"
so that they overlap to gain color again
There are a lot of couples...
I don't think we really fit here.
What are you saying?
There could be a wonderful encounter, you know?
Someone might pick you up!
P-Pick up?!
Huh?! That's not good!
C'mon, why not?
--Y-Yuzuki, were you asked out before?!
--Wha-?!
Um, ah, yes...
Really?! How was he?
How did he ask you out?
Um... Oh, come on, let's just go!
So, did you go out someplace with him?
It's really not worth talking about...
Aww... No fair.
Tell me! I want to know! I want to know!
Over there!
"Girl meets Girl Festival"
"Lunch bag" "Warmer cover"
"Handkerchief" "Accessory pouch" "Welcome"
Wow, so cute!
I think I can afford this.
"Coaster"
Yup. This is more like us.
Maybe I'll get this for Grandma.
I'm so glad to see Ruko having fun...
Yeah.
I'm going to buy you a
matching pair of scrunchies, too.
Ru!
Ruko!
Look. Isn't it cute?
You're right! Can I get a closer look?
It's quiet over here.
Why don't we take a short break?
Okay.
Ruko!
Hitoe?
I'm sorry. My friends in Aomori
asked me to take a pic.
Your friends?
Yup!
I wrote to them that I made friends in Tokyo,
and they sent me an e-mail asking for more.
Here.
Show me, too!
I kept...
...wishing for friends, but...
...I guess I had friends all along.
Yup.
Maybe I should get a mobile, too.
Huh?
That came out of nowhere.
If I have a mobile, then I can
get in touch with friends quickly.
It helps if something happens,
or if I'm far away...
--Say, can I take a look?
--Yup!
Well, how about we go
shopping for mobiles next time?
Sounds good!
But are you sure you'll
be able to use one, Ruko?
Huh? Is it that hard to use?
Don't worry.
Hm... I guess we'll go to Akihabara then.
--Huh?
--No matter what happens...
Even if I go far away...
Don't you know?
You can only buy mobiles in Akihabara!
Not true! They were being
sold near my place too.
Sure, only the mobile itself.
You can't sign-up except in Akihabara!
Huh?! Seriously?!
I don't want to lose anyone anymore.
Oh, Yuzuki...
She's lying. You can buy them anywhere.
Really? You surprised me there.
You better discuss it with your grandma, too.
Anyone.
I'm getting thirsty. How about
we get something to drink?
Okay!
So...
...why ice cream?
It looks tasty!
Hold on! There's no one around! You know why?!
It's cold!
It's winter!
I'll have caramel flavor.
Ruko?
What's the matter?
Nothing...
Hitoe? Let's get out of here...
Ruko...
"Group A"
WIXOSS...
Open!
What gives, having a competition
at a place like this?
Are there any... Selectors?
No... Let's go.
Ah, hey, wait a second!
Yuzuki?
There's... one here...
Here...?
A Selector?!
She's coming...
Closer... She's coming closer...!
I found you!
Selector...!
Can you battle me, please?!
She's...!
She's... a Selector?
I'm sorry there for my girl's loud voice.
See, look Eldora!
It's exactly like Chiyori said!
I told you we could find Selectors here!
And two of them! Could this be fate?!
Duh, they're having a competition.
Of course you'd find some.
I guess us heroines can't
avoid the fate of battle...
What?! Avoid? You're looking for battle!
Pooh! Eldora, go with the flow!
I'm so sorry! She's like this all the time.
So, anyways...
Yay!
Please battle Chiyori!
Battle...
The back alley!
Mmm...! So battle-ly!
Speaking of, did you folks go
to Urazoe Iona's fan event?
You went, right?
You know, we just couldn't make it there.
E-Eldora!
Open!
Huh...? What...?
My kid here is lousy with directions.
It took a couple hours,
circling around the area over and over again,
just to find the location earlier. The other day...
Wha-?!
Eldora... zip your mouth! Zip it!
G-G-Give! I give! I give!
So, anyways...
The beautiful maidens' battle for
their wishes is about to begin!
Open!
Huh? What? Huh?
We... won't battle.
Huh?
We're not going to battle.
Oh my.
But, you're Selectors.
Your wish won't come true!
I guess you don't know what
happens if you lose your battles.
Huh?
What...! Are...! You saying?!
I knowey.
Death awaits those who lose seven times...
The WIXOSS factors
spread inside your body...
...then from the inside you
go kaboom! Squish! Splat!
No...!
If you lose three times, you lose
your rights and wish, then...
...that very wish is reversed.
If your wish was to be wealthy...
Losing in battle means that you lose all wealth,
and plummeted to poverty.
If your wish was to become
skilled in playing the piano...
You may lose your piano, or you may
become incapable of playing the piano...
In any case, you won't be able
to play the piano, forever...
Hitoe's wish was "to make friends"...
With that wish reversed...
Wish reversed? That's...
...a new setting?!
Ouch...
My wish came true
without relying on WIXOSS.
So you should...
But, but, getting your happiness
through battling is better...
--Winning in battle...
--Hm?
Winning in battle isn't
going to make you happy!
Winning battles aren't enough.
You can't become an Eternal Girl
without your LRIG accepting your wish.
Are you sure about this?
I accept...
I... accept!
...the laws of the Selector.
And...!
...now, a new Eternal Girl will be born!
Yessy, I know!
"How an LRIG is Born"! The second
volume to the WIXOSS novel!
WIXOSS 2! The Flames of Void
Play the Victory Song of Oblivion!
And that's how you get
your wish to come truey!
That's not it.
Hitoe... Show me to her.
What?
--Say, Chiyori?
--Huh?
Do you... remember me?
Huh?
Hmm...
Ah! I knew it!
I thought I sensed something I felt before.
Chiyori, Chiyori! It's her, you know? Her!
What?
She's the one who beat you in
your very first battle you offered!
Whaaaa?!
What?! Why are you a card?!
My wish came true, and I replaced my LRIG.
Oh, really? You too?
Look carefully... This is what happens!
I can't go to school or
eat ice cream any more.
Even the person I love...
Tama can't make Ruko into an LRIG...
I don't want to say bye to Ruko...
Even if you win the battles,
you're going to become just like me!
Eldora, was it?
Eh? Ah, yes, what is it?
If you're an LRIG, then you must know about
that white windowed room, and that girl, Mayu!
Are you letting her battle
knowing what happens?!
Well, my memories have
been fleeting recently and...
...I have no idea
what you're talking about.
It seems she understands now.
Yup.
So, you shouldn't battle...
Yaaaaaah!
It's exactly the same as the novel!
The heroine becomes a card,
and the story is to be continued!
Going into the world of WIXOSS
is like, Chiyori's dream come true!
--So happy!
--Wha...?!
Chiyo-rinda!
Chiyo-ringa...
Chiyo-rumba, Chori-Chori...
Which do you think is better for
my name when I become an LRIG?
I don't think you need one...
What? Eldora, I bet you think Chiyori
can't get her wish to come true!
No-I-believe-in-you-from-the-bottom-of-my-heart.
Why the monotone read?!
What should we do?
Ru...
Say, Ru...?
Stop...
Stop!
Ruko?!
Wait, Ruko!
Huh?
Wait...! Ruko!
Ru... Tama will battle.
This will be the last battle.
White Hope!
No...
Ruko won, so why...?!
Ruko...
Hitoe?
It's going away!
Wait...
No...
Don't... Please don't...
Now, a new Eternal Girl...
...will be born!
Don't...!
What's with the long face, Ru?
My Selector...
Iona-san...
Tama...
Why...?!
Where are you, Tama?!
Tama...!
Iona-san...
What's going on?
Weren't you listening to
what Urith was saying?
Iona-san won more than enough battles.
But, you lacked a condition
to get your wish to come true.
So the condition was met,
and your wish came true?
Iona-san, what is your wish?
To be an LRIG.
To become an LRIG to someone stronger
than me, so as to continue battles.
So the last condition was to lose in battle?!
Your wish came true
because you lost to Ruko?!
But, how...?
That doesn't matter now.
It was great.
I'm so glad... Ru...
Tama...
Where did Tama go...?
Who knows?
Tama...
Tama...!
You should have... battled her.
I'm not going to battle!
You want to meet Tama, right?
That wish may come true... If you battle...
No. I...
I won't...
Then why do you still have me?
If you're not going to battle,
you should throw me away.
I knew it. You want to do it...
Such attachment...
Ruko...
I wasn't going to ask, but...
Why did you bring her with you?
Don't tell me you wanted to battle...
If you battled again, there's
no telling what would happen.
She's right! Tama disappearing...
Iona becoming Ruko's card...
No one could have expected it!
--Something worse may happen next!
--But...!
But, I want to meet Tama...
I still... I want to help Yuzuki,
and everyone else...
Even so...
You shouldn't battle!
I know... I know, but...!
What should I...!
I don't know what to do either,
so let's all think together.
Right. You're not alone, Ruko.
We're with you.
Let's all get through this, together!
Hitoe...
Yuzuki...
There are too many things I don't understand.
Why isn't Ruko battling?
Like me, she seeks battles...
And her wish...
I want to help Yuzuki, and everyone else...
An LRIG only accepts a wish
they believe they can make true.
Despite abandoning the wish,
why did she believe...
...she could make such an
impossible wish come true?
Ruko's LRIG... is me.
I'll change Ruko...
Instead of clinging on to an impossible wish...
...I want her to sense the excitement...
To battle to her heart's desire...
Along with me...
Next is Shinjuku. Shinjuku.
She's my clue... to find Tama.
Did you say something?
No...
Nothing at all...
"This Silent Beginning"
Nothing...
Life...
A city of mazes with no exit
and the sound of bells ringing
I do...
Leave the "now" handed to me
as I begin to walk in the morning
In a world where light and dark intersect
catharsis begins to awake
I swore in my shaking heart
that I won't lose anyone anymore...!
Even if my tears flow tomorrow
I'll run through the wind
Release myself towards the future I selected
to regain it
I won't give up on my wish
It was Akira!
Don't be spouting that crap's name
with that crap voice of yours!
Akira-san?
Shut it, twerp.
If there's a battle...
Mastermind...?
"That Feverish Bond"
That Feverish Bond.