I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you; I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
Your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
Such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
A New
Family
Whatever you do,
do not come out from under the bed!
But...
Sis!
Hey, Lacus.
HQ's calling.
Hm?
Oh, got it.
You've eaten already, René?
Sis...
Saotome Yoichi.
Right now, we're reliving your innermost memory.
Sis, you're alive?
Well, she's not, of course.
Big bro...
Did I wake you up?
My bad, Mirai.
No...
How are you feeling?
I'm doing okay. I feel better today.
That's good.
Are you hungry?
I'll get you something to eat.
Bro...
you know, if I'm just weighing
you down, then you can—
Don't even start.
You're not a bother in any way.
But if this keeps up, you'll also...
No buts!
If we die, we die together!
No, don't say that...
I see you cry every night about how hard it is,
about how you want to leave me.
Why would you say such...
Because you're a greedy human being who only thinks for his own benefit,
Kimizuki Shihou.
You're the demon.
Indeed I am, but this is no mere hallucination.
These are your memories—
the truth within you.
Don't give me that bullshit!
Hm?
Looks like he'll make it through, at least.
Hey, Yuu.
Yuu, who ran away and
abandoned his precious family.
I don't have time for your game of charade.
Oh? I thought I was poking at your softest spot,
but it's almost as if you couldn't care less.
How strange. I wonder why?
I know of these mind games
you demons like so much.
Just give up, and surrender your power to me.
Mika!
Oh, that explains it.
It seems you're not a stranger to my kind.
You have hopes of defeating me just because
you've dealt with that Myou-Ou trash?
I can toy with your flimsy
little heart however I please.
Shut up.
I'll say it again: give me your power!
It belongs to me now!
Why do you wish for power so desperately?
Is it for revenge?
Of course!
Because you lost those precious to you?
That's right.
I lost the family that I never thought I'd have.
That must have been tough.
Very well.
If you desire power for revenge,
then I can give it to you without restraint.
So...
But it's still not enough, Yuu.
I can't help you unless you unconditionally devote yourself to revenge.
The little girl speaks the truth.
So I can't give you my power after all.
Hold on!
Yuu.
Are you going to leave us again?
Are you going to run away on your own again?
Yuu wouldn't do something like that, right?
You'll come live with us again, won't you?
Isn't that right, Yuu?
Relinquish your love, Yuu.
It's the one thing we hate the most.
We love lust,
and loathe love.
Yoichi,
Kimizuki,
Shinoa...
Friends?
You can't be serious.
Are you going to forsake us
and be the only one living happily ever after?
Th-That's...
As the only one who survived,
don't you think you're being unfair?
How could you abandon us, run away,
replace us with new friends,
and completely forget about us?
You're wrong! I haven't forgotten about—
Then cast your friends aside.
We're the only family you need, Yuu.
Stop.
You're going to repay them
for what you've lost, right?
Stop it.
You're going to lead a life of vengeance, right?
Stop it!
All of you, shut the fuck up!
Cut this shit out, and give me your power!
I...
I need the power to protect those precious to me!
Oh, my.
What an incredible contradiction of love and lust entwined.
This is why humans bring ruin upon themselves.
Fine. I like you.
But my loyalty will only be
as strong as your conviction.
If your heart wavers, even for the slightest moment,
your body will be mine.
Sure, that's fine by me!
My name is Asuramaru.
Call upon me when you need my power.
Asuramaru...
Oh, and one more thing.
I'd like to make my new master aware of some information.
Information?
You're something like a mix of odd parts.
As it stands, there's already
ten percent of you that isn't human.
Could the humans be experimenting on you?
What? What does that—
Never trust a human, Yuu.
They're far more terrifying than any vampire or demon.
Ha. Saying that to a human feels a little weird.
What? Seriously, what are you going on about?
With this, the contract has been completed.
I'll lend you my power.
Open your eyes,
strengthen the fierce desire within you,
and pave a new path unto the world...
Hyakuya Yuuichirou!
Oh, did it go well, Yuu?
Guren...
Of course it did.
Don't get too cocky.
It took you long enough.
Did you make it too?
Naturally.
How about Yoichi?
Who are you?
You summoned me, didn't you?
You wished for an Infernal Arm that could avenge your sister.
Oh, that's right...
I was in the middle of contracting with a demon.
So you're the demon?
Sure am.
That's a cruel form to take.
And all you can do is grin like an idiot.
I get that a lot.
So, you want power?
What?
I tampered around with your heart, but there wasn't a single shred of vengeance to be found.
Only stability, compassion, and love for others.
All the things I hate.
Th-That's not true.
I want to avenge my sister's...
That's a lie.
You're glad that it was her instead of you.
N-No, that's not...
You hate conflict.
You don't want your friends,
nor your family to die.
No, you have no desire for any bloodshed.
Vengeance that can't kill?
Give me a break.
You lack lust.
I despise people like you.
That's why I'll avenge her in your stead.
Succumb to me...
pathetic human!
You don't even have enough desire to fight back.
You really are useless after all.
The likes of you aren't suited to be my master.
Oh, man. Bad news.
Yoichi just didn't have what it took, I guess.
But I suppose two passing candidates out of three isn't too bad.
What?
What's going on?
I spy with my little eye... one, two, three, four humans.
All with Infernal Arms, too.
Humans really are troublesome.
Come, my bow.
All right.
Now that you guys have your Infernal Arms,
here's your first job as the vampire extermination unit
known as the Moon Demon Company.
Yuu. Kimizuki.
There's your murderous demon.
Deal with it.
Oh no, whatever shall I do?
Let's slaughter them all.
Yoichi?!
Whew.
I guess the raw strength
of a demon alone is pretty powerful,
even if it hasn't fed on the lust of its victim.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
May I share my opinion?
Hell no.
Pipe down.
But this situation is...
Hey, Guren!
What the hell do you mean, deal with it?!
Yoichi is our comrade!
What?
That thing's a demon no matter how you look at it!
Kill it now, and put him out of his misery!
What the hell?!
There's no way I can kill a comrade!
Don't get smart with me!
This is the Moon Demon Company!
We march on the path to Hell!
Or did you only come here
to play meaningless games of revenge?
If you feel like getting yourselves killed, great.
But Yoichi won't ever come back!
Shit...
If you take any pride in being a soldier,
steel yourselves and get the damn job done!
F-For fuck's sake...
Damn it!
What was...
Yuu!
Give Yoichi back,
you fucking monster!
Got him!
You idiot!
Don't let your guard down!
The demon is inside Yoichi, not the weapon!
Cut it out!
Are you trying to kill Yoichi?!
What's this?
You guys can't even bear to kill him.
Yoichi, snap out of it!
Don't let a shitty demon get the better of you!
Weren't you going to kill the vampires with me?!
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
I believe this has gone a little too far!
They're not ready yet.
Please don't make them kill him!
Oh?
You're usually so distant and cool,
but you actually like these kids, don't you?
Have they grown on you?
Lieutenant Colonel!
Then you do it.
Bear the cross for them.
What?
You'd rather keep your hands clean, huh?
That's the first time I've seen your cute side.
Yoichi, get a grip!
Don't you dare lose to a demon!
Hush, child.
It's time to die.
Do it.
I won't kill a friend.
I promised that I wouldn't abandon them.
And, Yoichi...
you can't kill me either.
If you're the same as me...
If your family died right before your eyes,
then there's no way you can kill a friend!
Are you out of your mind?!
So wake the hell up already!
You freaking moron!
Here we go...
Die.
Yoichi!
Are you going to hide under the bed and watch your family die again?!
Get your damn ass out of there already
and protect your friends!
Yoichi!
Whatever you do,
do not come out from under the bed!
I...
I don't...
I don't want to run away anymore!
That's why...
That's why I need the power
...to protect those dear to me...
The power to annihilate all my enemies...
Give it to me,
demon!
Whoa, there.
No way...
I-Is he back?
There, there.
Welcome back.
Yuu...
You sure took your damn sweet time!
Wh-Why kick me, asshole?
Y-Yuu!
Is this what you anticipated, Lieutenant Colonel?
I thought I told you to pipe down.
I couldn't care less if some kid died.
Or so you say, but your expression near the end suggested otherwise.
Ow!
You have a gift.
You felt guilty for leaving your sister helpless,
and lost your desire to live.
But you found it today, didn't you?
Protecting the friends that saved you
is enough reason to live.
Revenge?
Don't get hung up on something so trivial.
Same goes for you, idiot.
Ow.
Forget about your previous family.
What?
Don't be ridi—
This is your new family.
Put your life on the line for them, dumbass.
There's nothing to be found in the past.
It's the future that has things to offer.
Whatever.
Anyway, since you've all got your Infernal Arms,
and you kinda worked as a team,
I suppose we can head out to the front lines.
The front lines?!
Yeah.
We found out that the vampires from the Kansai region
are planning on reclaiming Shinjuku.
We're going to investigate that area.
So, we can hunt vampires?!
W-We're going out into the field already?
Don't we get a break or something?
Sheesh.
Raising kids sure is a pain in the ass.
We will soon be arriving at Tokyo.
Attacks from the Japanese Imperial Demon Army
are expected around Ikebukuro, Shinjuku, and Shibuya.
Please be careful.
Did you hear that,
Mika?
So Shinjuku is first.
najimeta shiro torikago sumi
I used to like the light, my corner of the cage
kodou eta tsubomi mo
I'm a flower bud made flesh
okizarigoe kurameta kioku no kage
Blinding memories cry after me
i need your blood
I need your blood
you read love tonaeru
You speak of love to me
agaku red light
The red lights dance
kagiwaketa neon to
The neon lamps
kojiaketa reason ga
and the madness of the world
tada heikou ni narabu
share a vanishing point
Come on, break it down for me
come on, break it down for me
a river will flow
A river will flow
My desires remain unfulfilled
key ga nai hoshii demo
rigai naru suzu
A melody of ups and downs
zange sae kawaita yonbyoushi ga
Our song follows the sheet of our will,
kanadeta ito wo tadoru
no longer capable of penance
Crimson beams assault my vision
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time, on Seraph of the End:
Mitsuba's
Squad
"Mitsuba's Squad."