Here at Fumizaki Academy,
the school-wide festival "Seiryousai" will soon be held.
Not only does this academy make use of Summoning Being Exam Wars and other special systems,
each year, the event draws a lively crowd of visitors.
It is also to live up to their expectations
that the students are now working vigorously in preparation.
As this was happening, in Class 2-F...
Come back... come back to us!
Ninja Pervert!!
Resuscitation was underway
The red string of fate we tied
Let's make it love with a butterfly knot
Our future together leaps for joy in my heart
Don't untie it, promise me, kay?
Weight training for my heart,
I'll build up tons of strength, just you see!
Love! This love's not enough
Cry! Its data's all
Trash! Doesn't help me even a bit
Of course it won't
Right! Whenever I'm around you
I'm around first love level, I guess?
How cute!
Talking like you know how I feel
Why? Why? Why?
Just a friend to chat with
But still (but still) everyone (everyone)
wants to know their academic ranking in love!
Go higher!
Average score, then try again, my ever-skillful darling
But what kind of crush are you really harboring?
I'll bring my level up!
The slightly singed red string of fate
Let's make it love with a butterfly knot
I'll pray in my heart for a world with you
Don't look away, come with me!
Idiots, Tests, and
Summoned Beasts
Festival
Idiots, Tests, and
Summoned Beasts
Day 1
"Me and Maids and the Start of a New Journey"
Let's rewind to a few days ago.
The students had begun preparation for Seiryousai.
As this was happening, Class 2-F...
Play ball!
... was playing baseball.
Show me what you've got, Yoshii!
It's on, Sugawa-kun!
The next pitch...
"A curve...
Right at... the batter's face?"
Hey wait, that's totally against the rules!
Don't hold back! Give it all you've got!
Like hell I can!
You punks! Why the hell are you slacking off?
Oh crap! It's Iron Man.
Yoshii! You again?
Why do you always blame it on me?
Can't you tell it was Yuuji, the class rep, who's responsible?
"Stick a fork...
... in Iron Man's...
... crotch!?"
DON'T FUCK WITH ME!
Plus, I'm the one he'd get pissed at!
That's enough! Everyone just return to your classroom!
F-Class is the only class that hasn't decided on a cultural festival event!
Fine...
All right then, let's decide what to do for the cultural festival.
If you've got a suggestion, raise your hand.
Okay, Ninja Pervert.
A photography show.
What kind of photos are we displaying?
Secret.
Secret...?
We'll hang photos around the room
That is,
that provide a valuable peek into the world of mystery.
an irreplaceable
eroticism
A suggestion's a suggestion. Write it on the board.
Sure...
Photography... show...
Se... secr... secret?
P... peek... the room...
Anything else?
Ah, Himeji.
Um, how about a wedding cafe?
Like a maid cafe,
but the waitresses wear wedding dresses!
Ooh, that sounds cute!
The girls would enjoy it, and I bet the boys would like it too!
Marriage is when your life ends.
Akihisa, write it down.
Wedding... life...
Any other suggestions?
How about a Chinese cafe?
Other classes would mostly just serve yamcha tea.
There's nothing with more unexplored possibilities than Chinese cuisine!
Everywhere
Though European culture has been receiving more attention lately.
in the world
flat chests are sad
Akihisa, write it down.
Uhh... Chinese... European?
Oy, Akihisa...
Are you just writing the words you remem-
Have you guys decided on a cultural festival event yet?
We've got three candidates right now!
Photography show
"The Secret Peepshow"
Wedding cafe
"The End of Life"
Chinese cafe
"European"
Perhaps I should lengthen your supplementary lessons.
What's that mean?
Good grief. Why can't you take things seriously for once?
Don't you want to use this opportunity to improve your classroom equipment?
You mean buying new desks with the money we earn?
Oooh! I hadn't thought of doing that.
Are we allowed to, sensei?
As stupid as you all are,
STUPID
I didn't think you could sink lower than orange crates.
A penalty is one thing,
but if it harms your education, our priorities would be backwards.
PRIORITIES
As this is a school event, I'll negotiate with the headmaster
to give you special permission.
Really!?
So we won't have to study using these drawing boards and mats anymore.
Maybe that will change father's mind.
Father?
Uh? Ah... it's nothing.
A-anyway, that sounds interesting!
All right, we're taking a vote!
Raise your hand for the one you want to do!
Aaand done!
Hope we get a lot of customers.
We have to make it work this time no matter what,
so do your best, Aki.
Hm? This time?
Well, she told me to keep it a secret, but...
Mizuki might be transferring.
Himeji-san?
TRANSFER
TRANSFERRING!?
No way.
There's so many fun times we've yet to have!
If the only saving grace of F-Class transfers,
what would happen!?
Everyone would lose hope, the class would fall apart,
we'd devolve into a hell ruled by violence and plundering,
end up with mohawks like in the legend of the Savior of Century's End,
and wearing out the lone heroine Hideyoshi with our endless wars?
Scars: "Idiot"
Akihisa's processor is overloading!
He's not good with unexpected developments.
Akihisa! Wake up!
Hideyoshi... even if I get a mohawk...
will you still love me?
What kind of processing did it take to get that reaction from Mizuki's transferring?
Why is Himeji-san transferring?
Mizuki's parents are...
worried about her studying in F-Class.
Can't blame them.
She's in a run-down classroom
surrounded by the people with the worst grades in the school.
No wonder they're worried about her.
If she transfers, she'll be able to learn in a normal environment.
So that's what she meant by "change father's mind"...
I see.
Meaning if we get ahold of some proper equipment,
it might persuade her father.
If that's how it is, we can't afford to fail, eh, Akihisa?
We're back!
Himeji-san.
Tsuchiya-kun made a menu for the Chinese cafe.
Can we get you to test-taste?
Sesame dumplings.
Hmm. Let's have a try.
Wow! Pretty good!
You're right!
The outside is crunchy, but the inside is soft and chewy.
It's just right, not too sweet.
Makes you want some tea to go with it.
I'll go make some.
Ah, I'll help!
Do they really taste that good?
I guess I'll have one too.
Mmm! The outside is rocky and the inside is glue-like.
The not-too-sweet, far-too-spicy flavor is so very-
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Ninja Pervert!
Did you really make those sesame dumplings?
If I recall...
I only made three.
Why are there more?
Judging by his symptoms, it's got to be something Himeji made.
That was close!
It was a perfect 50/50 odds Russian Roulette!
Grandpa, I'm coming now...
He really has no luck whatsoever.
Fumizuki Academy Seiryousai
And thus, the day of the school festival.
Chinese Cafe
Chi
nese
Chinese Cafe
Ca
fe
Chinese Cafe
Welcome to Chinese cafe "European"!
Somebody! Somebody help revive this guy!
We've already done this part.
Ninja Per...
Akihisa!
We're short on hands.
Could you help out in the kitchen?
Oh well. Guess I'll do it myself.
Thanks for coming!
Welcome!
We're currently taking a popularity poll for our waitresses.
Please submit a vote on your way out!
Well, from the looks of things the cafe's doing fine.
Yeah. We're getting a good amount of customers, too.
Seems like a success.
Geez, how long ya gonna make us wait?
What's wrong with this place?
Ain't even coming to take our orders?
Ah, right, I'll be right there!
Please wait just a...
But we've been waitin' ages!
And we've got other places to be, too.
Don't make us wait forever, ya little octopus!
S-sorry! Please wait a moment!
What's up with those arrogant pricks?
They'll be hard to deal with. Such troublesome customers.
Man I'm fuckin' starving here...
Sesame dumplings
200 yen
Sample
Hey, check it out!
Ah, the outside is rocky and the inside is glue-like...
The not-too-sweet, far-too-spicy flavor is-
Crap! This is bad!
300 joules, charge!
300! Roger that!
3... 2... 1...
That was close...
You've gotten pretty good with that thing.
It's because he's always toying with death.
But what could have...
Th-this is...
Didn't expect someone to eat the display samples...
What's with the food here?
You trying to kill us?
This ain't a joke here!
Oh crap. Gotta cover up somehow...
Congratulations!
You're our first winners of the day!
We won something?
Is there a prize or something?
Eh? Prize?
Uhhh...
Say aah!
Fuck no!
You bastard!
You're not getting away with this!
We'll put this place outta business!
What!
It's your fault for eating it!
Shut up!
Who's the guy in ch-
I'm the class rep, Sakamoto Yuuji.
Might there be anything that is unsatisfactory?
Nagakawa was just punched through the air just now...
That would be my negotiation tactic that begins with a punch.
Don't fuck with me you little shit-
And that would be my negotiation tactic that continues with a kick.
Ouch...
Tsunemura!?
Finally, I've prepared a negotiation tactic that ends in a wrestling move...
Eh, uh, no, that's enough...
Oh really? Well then...
With this, the negotiation is over.
He's holding the position pretty well there.
Karl Gotch style, huh?
Sesame dumplings - 2
Punch, kick - 1 ea.
German suplex
Karl Gotch style
FFF clan now recruiting
Job Description:
A simple job consisting of letting out your emotions
via blunt weapon and beating the crap out of people.
We have various types of equipment available for use.
Of course you're more than welcome to bring your own.
Newbies can rest easy.
Your seniors will kindly and thoroughly guide you.
Come, young ones!!
Ballot box
Thank you very much for coming!
Looks like business is dwindling.
That's strange. Even though it's lunchtime...
We're in trouble if this goes on.
Welcome!
Hello there, stupid onii-chan!
Hazuki-chan! So you came!
Yup!
Since it's your school festival, Hazuki wants to help too!
Thank you, Hazuki-chan!
Don't be shy to ask!
After all, it's Hazuki's future husband's shop.
Since Hazuki had her first kiss with onii-chan...
Huh? Why am I on the floor?
Tsuchiya! Lend me a weapon. Counting spares we should have enough.
There's also mine, so that makes ten.
We will now commence the questioning of the heretic.
For starters, hurry up and lay him out!
Thanks for coming to help,
but as you can see, business is kind of slow.
At this rate we'll be gathering moss soon...
So there's not much to help with.
Aw, really?
Hazuki wanted to wear a china dress too.
100 meat buns, on the double!
Go get them yourself!
Maybe it's because of that rumor.
Forehead: Lolicon
Rumor?
Yeah.
My First Cultural Festival ~Hazuki~ Episode 1
On my way here I got lost,
so I asked lots of people,
"Where's the stupidest onii-chan's shop?"
and they all told me to come here.
He's certainly a landmark by now.
You mean me?
But everyone said,
"I hear that place is filthy so you shouldn't go."
How could they!
We all cleaned up together,
and decorated the place too.
Ballot box
None of the customers we had seemed unhappy.
They should have all been satisfied.
All except two, that is.
I'll bet that Tokonatsu duo is spreading bad rumors about us.
"Tokonatsu"?
Take Tsunemura and Natsukawa,
use the first kanji of each and it's Tokonatsu for short.
I see.
Well, looks like we'll have to find them,
and have some more negotiations.
Hazuki,
where did you hear that rumor?
A place with lots of pretty onee-sans!
Right then!
We'll have to find that place no matter what!
Pretty   Onee-sans
Your objective seems to have changed a bit, though...
Maid Cafe
So this is the place Hazuki-chan was talking about.
I don't see anything unusual.
It's still too early to tell.
Welcome home, master.
Kirishima-san, looking good!
Thank you, Yoshii.
Welcome home.
I won't let you go home tonight, darling~
Can I leave now?
Here's the menu.
Let's see, I'll have...
Shortcake          Mont Blanc
Panna Cotta       Gateau Chocolat
Pumpkin Pudding         Lemon Tart
Marjorlaine         Cheese Tart
Cake set: 450 yen
(a la carte: 300 yen)
Please select a
drink from below
Coffee blend
Cafe Latte
Black Tea (Darjeeling)
... water.
Understood.
What about you, master?
Menu~
(for Yuuji)
Shouko...
What is this menu?
Today's specials.
Honeymoon with the maid.
(Market price)
Lovey-dovey date with the maid.
(Priceless)
Sweet kiss with the maid.
(Secret <3)
It's a limited-time offer, so please order quickly.
Go die!
Maaan it's sure nice and clean here.
Back at class 2-F,
their Chinese cafe was shit!
Quite the difference!
The room was dirty and smelled funny,
the waitresses were fugly, and not to mention,
calling a Chinese cafe "European,"
what are they, dumbasses?
They're spreading lies about us!
Well, one of them was true.
I can't take this anymore!
Hold it.
If we get in a fistfight here it'll just make our reputation worse.
Use your head.
Then what should we do?
Let's see...
Shouko, lend us a maid outfit.
Understood.
Hang on hang on!
What are you doing!?
Because you said you wanted me, Yuuji...
Not you, a maid outfit!
As in, if you have extras lend us one!
I'll go get one.
Don't act so disappointed!
Yuuji. What are we gonna do with a maid outfit?
Isn't it obvious?
We'll get Hideyoshi to help us.
I see. A good plan.
Changing
How's this?
Does it look feminine enough?
Changing
Impressive as usual, Hideyoshi.
It looks pretty darn good.
This sort of make-up is my specialty among specialties.
Wait, even a bra?
If you don't go all the way you can't get into the role.
Usually even down there-
Th-that's a little...
Maid Cafe
Honestly,
that filthy Chinese cafe doesn't know how to treat its customers at all!
Well, this is F-Class we're talking about.
What else do you expect?
Whadya want, missy?
Hey, you're pretty cute!
What? Fallen in love with me or-
GO TO HELL!
Too weak?
Y-you're from F-Class-
Oh shit!
Eek! This man is peeking up my skirt!
Wait, what-
Making lewd moves in public, eh?
You sick bastard!
The hell you talking about!?
We're the victims here!
Silence!
You groped that waitress's breasts, didn't you?
Eek! This man's a pervert!
What's with this?
The hell? It won't come off!
See? He's groping them.
That's completely not what he's doing!
He totally groped her...
This situation's bad...
Run for it, Natsukawa!
Hold it right there!
Hmph. Well, it is nicely done,
but props are still just props.
Isn't there anything scarier?
Damn them! They won't get away with this!
We've got no choice if it's come to this.
We'll put them through hell.
What should we do?
I've got an idea!
Let's go!
What was that just now?
I must have hoped too hard for something scary
and ended up hallucinating it.
Which means, if I instead wish for something beautiful...!
B-beautiful...
Ah, no no!
I already have Yoshii-kun, my heart's sweet honey!
But, her otherworldly beauty...
No, but then I would be false to my feelings for Yoshii-kun!
Oh no! I didn't ask her name and class...
But, I have Yoshii-kun...!
If I go after her now...
What should I do!?
Please just do whatever you want.
Welcome!
Looks like we're getting more customers!
I guess the boys succeeded.
Hazuki's gonna help out a lot!
Tch. They got away.
What do we do, Yuuji?
If they go spread bad rumors again...
What's up, Ninja Pervert?
It's terrible!
A waitress kidnapping has occurred!
Hello?
Yo. You sure went and did it back there.
We were just having a chat with your cute lil' waitress...
With your main selling point gone,
I'll bet business is going down now, eh?
Give us back Himeji-san and Minami-
Whoa there, I suggest you don't lose your temper there.
Don't worry.
We'll play with 'em plenty.
Those scum...
This is unforgivable!
Ninja Pervert.
Do you know where the Tokunatsu duo are hiding?
It'll take some time.
Fine. Go for it.
Boy's Locker Room
Th-this is...
The feed from surveillance cameras around campus?
Though... there's quite a lot of low-angle shots.
My Surveillance Cameras.
Video monitoring from 32 locations on campus.
Don't see the Tokonatsu duo in any of them.
Sound-only monitoring from 57 locations on campus.
Switch to sound-only.
... I know, right?
Right? He was so damn pissed.
Feels good, man.
Bingo!
Where's the signal from?
The gym storage room.
All right!
What the-
What-
Sorry!
Wait for me... Himeji-san... Minami!
What the-
You little- how did you know-
Himeji-san! Minami!
What's wrong, Akihisa?
Those two are still working at the cafe.
Hideyoshi? Why are you...?
They dragged me here,
and forced me to play board games with them.
They played with him plenty all right.
**I swear I'm not trolling it's from 2ch.
orz
And so the curtain fell on the first day of Seiryousai.
How are the proceeds, Shimada?
Amazing!
Even subtracting expenses, we can buy system desks with this!
Really?
What's with this fiendish line item here?
Eh? Let's see...
"Ninja Pervert Presents: High-Quality Photo Album Set."
500 sets, sold out.
Seiryousai limited edition.
Well anyway, that means today was a success!
Wow, stupid onii-chan!
That's great!
Thank you, Hazuki-chan!
This is thanks to your help, too.
We also owe these sales
to the exceptional customer-attracting ability of our waitresses, don't we?
Survey Totals
The survey totals are done.
Today's number 1 popular waitress is...
[Akihisa end]
Aki-chan
Where'd this
cute girl
come from?
I won't say I wanted to take first...
This feeling of dissatisfaction... what should I take it out on?
Isn't that wonderful, Akihisa?
You're first place for once.
That doesn't make me happy at all!
[Hideyoshi end]
Kinoshita
Hideyoshi
Not even
close!!
Just what you'd expect from Hideyoshi!
I'm glad they liked my performance,
I can't really celebrate this result.
Somehow I expected this, but...
Seeing it for real in the results is still a shock...
Hideyoshi!
Let's take this as a sign and someday open a real cafe
and have a happy family together!
Like I keep saying, I'm a guy!
[Minami end]
Shimada
Minami
DFC
forever!
Really?
Congratulations, Minami-chan!
Amazing!
You're number one!
Thanks, you two!
Congrats, Minami!
You slender legs look nice in the China dress,
and your even more slender chest suits the China dress-
You didn't have to call that part slender!
A part of me that shouldn't be slender is starting to feel like it's going to be made very slender!
[Mizuki end]
Himeji
Mizuki
Sexy!
Really?
I hate to say it, but that China dress looked really good on you.
Amazing, pretty onee-chan!
Congrats, Himeji-san!
It really does look good on you.
Thank you very much, Akihisa-kun!
And, I have a request...
Hm? What is it?
As congratulations, I'll do whatever you want!
Well, for the occasion,
I thought I'd make some sesame dumplings with the leftover ingredients.
Would you like to try some?
Th-that's...
That's a great idea!
Gotta celebrate the occasion!
Go right ahead.
What do you mean, you two?
If we're celebrating, we should all have the celebratory food togeth-
Okay! Everyone listen up, I have important news!
I talked it over with the headmaster about your classroom equipment.
Exception
As a special exception, you'll be allowed to buy new ones with your earnings!
However!
There is a condition.
On the second day of Seiryousai there will be a Summoned Being Exam Tournament.
If the winning team comes from this class,
she'll allow you to buy replacements.
Summoned Being Exam Tournament?
Selected teams from the whole student body battle it out
in a random-seed tournament.
The competition's fierce.
No way...
What do you say, Akihisa?
Of course!
We'll do it!
You're required to decide on a team and register!
That is all!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
The day after a day off
should be a day off too!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
The day before a day off
should also be a day off too, yeah!
MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY MONDAY
MONDAY!
I don't want this to end!
I want to stay like this!
I don't want to leave my room!
I don't want to believe it!
I just can't believe it!
I hate Mondays!
If I don't get up it's over.
Amidst this unavoidable drowsiness,
can't I just sleep a little longer?
I'm happy in my dreams.
Maybe I oughta get up, maybe it can't end like this,
but beyond my dreams lies a horrifying reality.
Even if I panic now,
time won't turn back.
So I'll dive back into the world of dreams
And thus,
class 2-F's dreams rested on the second day of the festival.
And here too,
was a man pursuing his dreams.
I wonder who that was...
I've got something good today.
Th-this is-
N-no, I musn't...
Huh? Hey, what're you two up to?
Yoshii-kun!
No...
Th... this is...
not what you think!