Who are you?
You don't need my name.
This'll be the last time we meet.
Farewell, Precures!
This world won't see your light ever again.
It belongs to the Selfish now.
Rikka, Alice!
Great!
Where's Makopi?
The fairies aren't here either.
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
What is that?
My heart's pounding like a fire alarm!
We shouldn't be here!
Run, everyone!
There's no need.
Makopi!
King Selfish is currently in a deep slumber.
He won't fight.
King Selfish?
How do you know that?
Who are you?
My name is Cure Sword.
I am the final warrior guarding Trump Kingdom.
Trump Kingdom's...
final warrior?
An Intense Battle!
Farewell, Precure!!
Mana!
Rikka!
Alice!
Where are you guys?
Hide!
Trump Kingdom's already been taken over by the Selfish!
We're done for if they find us!
We fell into the Selfish's trap,
got sent back to Trump Kingdom,
and now we're separated from Mana and the others!
What should we do?
Even I don't know!
Keep it together!
Crying won't fix anything.
We need to figure out a way home as soon as possible!
Um...
And you are?
I'm Davi!
Cure Sword's partner!
Nice to meet you, I'm Charles!
I'm Rachel!
I'm Lance!
Save the greetings for later!
Meeting up with the Precures is our top priority!
Well, even if it is...
Just think!
Where would the girls be at a time like this?
Oh, the Queen's palace!
Oh yeah, it is the biggest landmark here.
Let's go!
Hey Davi,
how did the Trump Kingdom wear down so quickly?
We were sent to the other world as soon as we were born, so we don't know.
The Trump Kingdom was a peaceful kingdom.
Everyone under Queen Ange's rule lived with a smile.
Have you grown accustomed to the hymn services?
Not quite.
I get nervous in front of such a large audience,
so... my words don't come out well.
I like your singing.
When I listen to your voice,
my heart grows strangely warm.
Thank you for your flattering words, my queen!
There's no need for formality when we're alone.
Right, my queen!
But one day,
we were suddenly attacked...
by King Selfish's underlings!
Selfish!
But the queen didn't give up hope.
She cut through the enemy lines herself!
Sel... fish!
Lady Cure Sword!
Lady Cure Sword...
It's the queen!
The queen...
fought valiantly to seal King Selfish...
and though she turned his body to stone,
the dark energy, Egogy, still smolders within him.
I couldn't protect anything...
Not a thing...
The queen exhausted all of her power,
so she's hiding within the palace.
Please, return to her at once!
You're now the only warrior left!
I cannot allow this kingdom's tragedy  to repeat itself!
Please, search for the legendary warriors, the Precures!
No more hide and seek.
Now, offer your soul to King Selfish, too.
Are you all right?
Cure Sword, you came for me.
What do you think you can do on your own?
This kingdom is already doomed!
A kingdom can always be rebuilt.
So long as we do not lose hope!
Cure Sword...
My queen, let's go!
Shoot!
What's wrong?
The queen jumped into the mirror!
She's not goin' anywhere.
My queen!
Escape, Cure Sword!
Even if you're alone!
You can't give up, my Queen!
Don't let go!
My queen!
I'll catch up to you, I promise.
That's why you must...
My queen!
I lost track of my queen,
and the next thing I knew, I had drifted into your world.
Then, the reason you became an idol...
was to find your queen?
I have nothing left but my songs.
If I kept singing,
then surely, that person would take notice.
But I couldn't find my her.
No matter what I sing, I've heard nothing from my Queen.
Then let's search for your queen together!
If you can't find her alone,
then four people should be enough!
Mana?
What are you saying?
That Mammo woman was searching for the queen.
So if we find her, I'm sure we'll hear her side of the story.
While new Selfishes were being created and running rampant,
they were creating Egogy.
That Egogy is being gathered to revive King Selfish.
But if we can find the queen before he awakens,
we may be able to seal him for good.
Right, see?
Well, if we keep purifying Selfishes,
we'll at least be able to postpone King Selfish's resurrection.
Selfish!
Trump Kingdom is already a Selfish hotbed.
I doubt those little girls can hold out for long...
but it never hurts to make sure.
Get out!
Why are there so many?
All the kingdom's people were turned into Selfishes!
I'm the only one left!
Huh?
Getoutgetoutgetout!
Jump!
Huh?
Nuh-uh, no way, no how!
No can doooo!
Makopi!
Forget about me!
Escape alone if you have to!
I won't run away!
I'll defeat King Selfish,
and bring peace back to Trump Kingdom!
What do you think you can do on your own?
She is certainly not alone!
She's just being a happy prince,
so she forgets that we can help, too!
Stop this!
You three have no reason to get involved!
Do you need a reason to help a friend?
But why?
You don't need a reason to help people!
She's so determined...
This girl's a strong one...
Now, lift!
Getoutgetoutgetout!
Look out!
Oh my.
Um...
you saved me.
Thank you.
Don't mention it!
So, what now?
Returning home seems like a nigh impossible task.
We should at least meet up with the fairies.
There's a magic mirror inside the palace.
A magic mirror?
It's a warp gate that we used in escaping Trump Kingdom.
If we pass through it, we should be able to return to your world once more.
The fairies may already be on their way there.
Let's go.
Makopi, guide us through the palace.
There are a lot of mirrors.
The magic mirror is further in.
Too late.
Were you looking for this?
The magic mirror!
This is the sole link between this world and the other.
I figured you'd make your way here if you were still alive.
You want to fight against me?
You've got a snowball's chance.
You won't know if you don't try!
Sorry, but it's game over.
Now you'll be stuck here for the rest of your lives.
Our last hope is gone.
I'll never see my queen again!
You may as well rot away with this derelict palace.
Hm hm hm hm hmph...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha—
Hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hahahahahaha!
Huh?
Do you think something so trifling would break our hearts?
You're sorely mistaken!
What'd you say?
Your power sent us to the Trump Kingdom.
You proved that you have the power to freely go between worlds!
So, if we don't have a mirror,
we can just have you send us back home!
You're not telling me to be your yes-man, are you?
Absolutely!
Where's that confidence coming from?
It comes from being Mana.
I can't beat that.
Let's return to our world!
Yeah!
Guess you'll need some pain to understand.
Mana!
Charles!
Lance!
Alice!
Rikka!
You're all safe!
I thought I'd never see you again!
Davi, I'll never give up again!
I'll fight the Selfish until peace is restored to Trump Kingdom!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
Transforming won't change a thing.
It's the end for you.
Oh, is that a punch?
I thought you were swatting flies.
Your kicks are light.
Rigid Rosetta Wall!
Rosetta!
Oh, are you done?
Don't lose hope.
Let's combine our strengths and hearts into one!
Our hearts as one...
I'll lure him out.
Strike him when he's open!
Huh?
Just do it!
Got it.
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Where are you aiming?
What?
Now, sparkle!
Twinkle Diamond!
I can't move!
Now!
From me to you,
My Sweet Heart!
We did it!
Curse you...
You stole too much of my Egogy...
He's really stubborn!
Everyone, look!
That's...
The magic mirror is still alive!
Let's go!
I won't let you run!
We're not running!
We'll definitely be back!
And we'll rebuild the Trump Kingdom with the queen!
Curse you, Precures!
Ow...
We're here!
Looks like we got back somehow.
The path to the Trump Kingdom...
Don't worry.
We'll find a way back together.
We've got to find the queen, too.
So we can take back the Trump Kingdom.
Please,
lend me your strength.
Let's do this together!
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Makopi, try holding Ai!
Huh?
I can't do it!
Dokidoki Precure:
Kyupirappa!
A Mysterious Baby is Born!!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!