Without the first issue, there's not much we can do.
That's true.
I'd feel a bit more confident about this investigation if you asked Satoshi and Ibara as well.
Well, I'd prefer...
Even if we can't solve the mystery, it'll be ancient history soon enough.
History?
All right.
I'll ask Fukube and Mayaka for their assistance.
I can't stop thinking about it!
Please help me find out what happened to my uncle 45 years ago!
Your uncle, huh?
I had no idea.
That epic from the past, full of heroism and hidden tragedy...
To think, we might uncover the truth 45 years later.
In fact, I was just researching that period myself.
Were you? Well, this picture makes me curious as well.
If there's some meaning to it, I'd also like to find out what it is.
Pretty exciting, huh?
You know, if we do this right, it could be the topic of this year's anthology.
Let's make this investigation into an official club activity.
And thus, investigating the past has become the utmost priority for all Classics Club members.
Bored, sitting on the windowsill,
I frown at the wind to hide my awkwardness
Hyouka
I nod uncertainly as I shape
the future in my hands feeling mighty
I feel that the wind is bringing change
I guess that's your fault for calling out to my heart
The cloudy sky tells a tale of what's to come
Spread our wings with more courage than ever before
Light and dark are still vague in the distance
but still we want to know the reason behind kindness
No one so far has ever reached
the shining distance far beyond
Let's get there before the past takes it all
Past Days of the Classics Club and Its Glory
Sorry, honey! Wait long?
What's wrong with you, Houtarou?
Shut up! Have you no shame?
So, did you manage to get some documents together?
How about you? Did you come up with a good topic?
Well... Sort of.
I'm looking forward to hearing your theory as to what happened.
Crap. Was I supposed to prepare a theory, too?
Let's get going, then.
The Chitanda family's full of rich farmers, so their Kamiyama mansion is top class!
Aren't you enjoying yourself?
Of course I am! I love cycling!
Going head-on against the wind with nothing but the power of my legs! And—
That's not it. Your high school life in general.
Ah, that "colorful" business, right?
You could say that most people around me live colorful lives as well.
More like, neon bright.
I guess. But you're pretty dull by comparison.
Yeah, I've heard that one before.
Oh, right. I don't look down on you for that, though.
I'm neon bright by nature,
so just being "colorful" doesn't really work for me.
You haven't settled for that already?
Not at all.
What was that, Houtarou?
You're asking because you see how busy I am with the Council and the Handicrafts Club?
Am I wrong?
You are.
Whatever I do, I'll always be me.
I won't tone myself down to fit in.
If I looked down on you, instead of "dull" I'd say you had no personality at all.
I can live without your love.
I'm sure you can.
Anyway, how did your midterms go?
Average marks on every one.
Just what I'd expect from Your Dullness.
Look, over there.
That's the Chitanda mansion.
What do you think? Isn't it amazing?
Let's go. The girls will be waiting.
That's true.
Houtarou,
aren't you expecting servants to show up and greet us?
Welcome! Come in. We've been waiting for you.
Excuse us.
Please, this way.
Just sit down wherever you like.
You sure took your time.
But we're not late.
I've never seen someone look so out of place in a room.
Then, shall we begin the investigation meeting?
Yeah!
Sure!
Okay.
Today, I'd like to focus on what happened in the Classics Club 45 years ago.
If we can find out the truth,
I'd like to include it in this year's anthology.
Firstly, the gathered data and reports.
Then, any questions regarding them.
Following that, your theories.
And finally, I'd like to closely evaluate those theories.
She's a good chairman.
Well then, the first report...
Who should we start from?
...or not.
Whatever. Chitanda, you start.
I guess. Then let's go around from me in clockwise order.
I investigated the second issue of Hyouka itself.
The only part with any mention of what happened 45 years ago is the introduction.
I've summarized the important facts on the second sheet.
1) Sekitani has left us (but who did he leave?)
2.) 45 years ago he was a hero, 44 years ago he was a legend
3.) He was a "quiet fighter" and a "kind hero"
4) He coined the name "Hyouka"
5.) There was a sacrifice in the fight (was it my uncle?)
The first one is about my uncle, Sekitani Jun.
He left Kamiyama High without graduating,
so the highest level of education he completed was middle school.
2.) 45 years ago he was a hero, 44 years ago he was a legend
I think the second one refers to how stories become exaggerated over time.
3.) He was a "quiet fighter" and a "kind hero"
4) He coined the name "Hyouka"
5.) There was a sacrifice in the fight (was it my uncle?)
1) Sekitani has left us (but who did he leave?)
The third and fifth are connected.
He was quiet and kind, and he first became a fighter, then a hero.
And in the end...
A sacrifice.
4) He coined the name "Hyouka"
The fourth is quite interesting, but let's put it aside for now.
That's the end of my report.
Do you have any questions?
Why did you ignore the part that says, "it was nothing even close to an epic"?
epic
Because that's the writer's own interpretation.
Maybe they meant that it wasn't all so glorious, but more of a dirty fight.
I see.
Now for my hypothesis:
My uncle confronted something, and as a result he had to leave the school.
One other thing.
I considered a few other things in addition to those five points.
For instance, this part about how "one year has passed."
My uncle left the school around the time of the Kan'ya fair.
As a side note,
I heard from a friend of mine who studies at another school
that there was an incident at last year's fair.
I've heard of those troublemakers.
There are people who like to threaten the sellers, and make off with their profits.
I think there are always people like that at fairs.
Perhaps that year my uncle was unfortunate enough to be targeted,
and he tried to resist by force.
Could that be how he became a hero?
He took responsibility and left the school,
and the students he left behind wrote this.
It couldn't be that.
Yeah, couldn't be.
It's no good?
Please, tell me why!
Chitanda,
when you first suggested making an anthology, do you remember what I wanted to do instead?
Um... A stall, right?
That's it. But you said that stalls are traditionally disallowed.
There's not much money to be made at the Kan'ya Fair,
so why would troublemakers turn up?
There are probably some who'd turn up even without the promise of money.
Are you even trying, Houtarou?
Oh? I'm sure we'd all love to hear what you think.
First of all, believe it or not, there were no such troublemakers 45 years ago.
Why?
If I mention the 1960s, what comes to mind?
Tokyo... The National Diet Building...
Placards... Demonstrations...
What are you talking about, Satoshi?
The student movement.
The kind of school violence that Chitanda mentioned was hardly present in the 1960s.
They didn't fight the schools or their teachers,
they fought the state and the system.
You talk as if you were there.
Like I said, I did some research into that period.
That's right. I forgot to consider the political climate of that time.
I'm sorry, Chi!
Why are you apologizing?
The data I gathered doesn't fit your theory.
I'm next, so I don't really know how much detail I should go into...
Damn Ibara and her pointless chatter...
Then, let's put my theory aside for now.
How about yours, Mayaka?
Is that okay?
Yeah.
My legs are numb.
This mansion is really huge.
Do you have a pond in your garden?
Yes.
Really? Can I see?
Me too!
Okay, time for a change of scene!
The weather is just perfect on the veranda.
A pond, huh?
The time when awns bear seeds.
Awn Grain
Hyouka
I found this in the library.
It's the first issue of Salute and Solidarity.
I couldn't find any later ones, though.
It's from 44 years ago, the same as Chi's.
Salute
and
Solidarity
Therefore we are the masses, and as such we
are anti-bureaucratic and independent. We would
never yield to the aggression of the reactionaries.
One needs only consider the class war of last
June, when under the heroic leadership of the
Classics Club's president Sekitani Jun, our daring
activism broke the ranks of the spineless
authoritarians, and they fled in unsightly shame.
"Our daring activism"? Sounds like the '60s all right.
Let's start from the beginning. "We" referred to the students,
We
while the "reactionaries" and the "authoritarians" were the teachers.
Reactionaires
Authoritarians
There was a "class war" during June of the previous year,
June
and it was led by none other than the Classics Club's president, Sekitani Jun.
Activism
Furthermore, their activism caused trouble for the teachers.
Oh, so that word means "class war" and not just "fight", huh?
This whole Salute and Solidarity thing is pretty fishy.
Fishy?
I'm not saying that this document is fake,
just that it was written by someone immersed in the student movement.
So what?
Nothing. Just thinking out loud.
Sorry, Chitanda.
Any other questions?
Then, here's my theory.
I refute Chi's hypothesis.
According to Salute and Solidarity, the incident was in June.
If it was bad enough that he had to leave the school, violence must have been involved.
So, the students led by Sekitani Jun went like this,
and gave the teachers a good whacking.
We don't know if they actually beat the teachers,
but 45 years ago something threatened the autonomy of the students, and they resisted.
My uncle...
I see what you're getting at, Mayaka, but still...
What do you mean?
Your point is that the students resisted the teachers' oppression with violence.
Yeah.
Your theory is too abstract.
We can't learn anything more from it.
Sure, it's objective, but is it controversial?
Yes.
Hyouka
Salute and Solidarity
If we believe both Hyouka and Salute and Solidarity,
then the incident happened in June, but he wasn't expelled until October.
Incident
June
Expelled
October
If he was to be punished for a violent incident, he would've been expelled right after, in June.
July August September
June
October
Incident
Expelled
June
October
Incident
Expelled
June
October
Incident
Expelled
June
October
Incident
Expelled
June
October
Incident
Expelled
June
July August September
Incident
October
Expelled
That's true.
Yeah, I'm wondering about that four-month difference as well.
It said a year had passed as of the fair, so he'd probably been expelled in October.
You sure like to nitpick, don't you?
I think we're heading in the right direction, though.
That's right.
I guess that's it for me, then.
Yes, thank you. Then, next up is—
Sorry. I got kinda hungry.
But you've been nibbling sweets all the time!
If you're okay with rice balls, I'll make lunch.
Is that all right with everyone?
Chi, is there anything we can help with?
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Yeah.
A handmade lunch!
I see you're overjoyed.
Fuku, this...
Mayaka, I'm sorry!
My data sort of conflicts with yours.
I forgot to mention it before.
Oh, really?
Is this the Kami High Monthly?
Right, Tougaito did say they were nearing the 500th issue.
That's right!
I went through the older issues of the Kami High Monthly.
This was the only one that mentioned what happened 45 years ago.
The second sheet contains my summary.
- There was no violence involved.
- It influenced the whole school.
- There was a united group ("us") at the center.
- They used non-violent disobedience.
The first and the last point say the same thing.
- There was no violence involved.
- It influenced the whole school.
- There was a united group ("us") at the center.
- They used non-violent disobedience.
- There was no violence involved.
- It influenced the whole school.
- There was a united group ("us") at the center.
- They used non-violent disobedience.
- There was no violence involved.
- It influenced the whole school.
- There was a united group ("us") at the center.
- They used non-violent disobedience.
There was no violence involved,
which derails Mayaka's theory.
Furthermore, if the usage of "us" refers to the whole school,
whole school         "us"
that means that the whole student body was involved in the incident.
Or failing that, it was at least led by someone supported by the whole student body.
Here you go.
Thanks, Chi.
No problem.
I made some with plum, kelp, and leaf mustard filling.
Please, help yourselves.
Thanks!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
This is good!
It's great!
Do you grow this rice yourselves?
Yes.
If you have any questions, go ahead.
Are you sure this "legendary movement" was the same one Sekitani Jun was involved in?
This paper alone doesn't really explain that.
Who knows? I've got no proof.
"Who knows?"
That's not very convincing.
I guess.
There's indirect proof, though.
Sekitani Jun incident
If the Sekitani incident and this "legendary movement" were separate,
Legendary movement
Sekitani Jun incident
they'd refer to this "legendary movement" in more specific terms.
That's it! Just what I wanted to say!
You're good, Mayaka!
Next, let's hear your theory, please.
My theory, huh?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Chitanda, but I can't come up with a theory on my own.
The most I can do is reconcile Ibara's theory with the new facts.
And as you know,
a database can't draw conclusions.
I knew he'd say that.
Now,
Thank you.
It's okay.
what should I do...
Oreki, please begin.
Houtarou, is this what I think it is?
Kamiyama High School: Fifty Years of History?
I suspected some of the details might not have been kept in public records.
But looking at it again, there's nothing really worthy of mention.
And I have no theory. What now?
What's wrong, Houtarou?
Did you forget the procedure?
Start from the summary, please.
Do I really have to do this?
Houtarou!
Oreki!
Oreki?
Damn it...
Just let it go.
What's wrong?
I forgot that we're drying shiitake mushrooms!
I need to take them in right away!
Do you need a hand?
I'll be fine.
Chitanda!
Yes?
Sorry, could I use the bathroom?
Sure. Just go straight down that corridor.
Suffering from page fright?
Straight...
Wait, where am I?
She did this much research, huh?
I guess I could put my head to use for once.
45 years ago...
What happened to Sekitani Jun?
Four sources,
connected by...
Think.
The student movement... A violent incident... The time before he was expelled...
45 years ago... Sekitani Jun...
You sure took your time.
Sorry about that.
It's my turn, isn't it?
Sorry. I didn't prepare a theory,
so let's just skip that and continue to the summary.
Houtarou, you figured something out, didn't you?
I guess. It's one explanation, at least.
You figured something out, Oreki?
Calm down, Chitanda.
Let's hear it.
Don't let us all down, now.
Right, let's go through everything in order.
First, when was it?
45 years ago
45 years ago.
The problem is, what was the time of year?
If we believe both Hyouka and Salute and Solidarity,
then the incident was in June,
Incident
June
but he left in October.
Expulsion
October
Where?
Next, where was it?
At Kamiyama High School.
Kamiyama High School
Next, who did it?
Who?
According to Salute and Solidarity,
Sekitani Jun, president of the Classics Club, was at the center of the incident.
Sekitani Jun
And from the Kami High Monthly,
we know that the whole student body was involved.
Why?
Finally, why?
Who would the students have risen up against? The teachers.
Their reason was, quoting Ibara, that "their autonomy was threatened".
Autonomy Threatened
And the reason for the incident was...
the culture fair.
Did you read that somewhere? That it was the culture fair?
No. To start with the conclusion,
June
the students negotiated with the teachers in June,
October
June
then the fair was held in October.
October
June
By "negotiations",
do you mean this "culture fair discussion meeting"?
Yes. Look at it closely.
Each item has either a circle or a square before it, right?
I get it!
A square means an event that happens every year, and a circle means this year only!
I looked at the other years as well, and that's what I concluded.
Now why was there just one "culture fair discussion meeting", 45 years ago?
Most likely because there was a strong demand for it from the students.
The hint is in Hyouka itself.
Right here.
"The year that he began as a hero and finished as a legend."
"The culture fair was celebrated for five days as always."
The point isn't that it was held, but that it lasted five days.
What do you mean?
It means that those five days were the fruit of Sekitani Jun's heroic fight.
It's just a guess,
but maybe the key is this announcement from the principal about the importance of study.
5 days
The principal had most likely tried to cut the five days of the culture fair short.
That's why all the students rose up angrily.
That's the reason, the "why".
Why?
And as for the way they did it, the "how":
How?
Classics Club president Sekitani Jun
"Under the heroic leadership of the Classics Club's president Sekitani Jun,
Heroic Leadership
Daring Activism
our daring activism broke the ranks of the spineless authoritarians."
This leads to the final "what".
What?
The students used no violence.
Violence
I guess they just organized a boycott.
The school had no choice but to negotiate with the students,
and they gave up on cutting the culture fair short.
But the price they paid was the expulsion of their hero, Sekitani Jun.
Why was there a four-month gap between the incident and his expulsion?
Incident: June
Expulsion: October
If they had expelled him right away, that would have caused even more unrest.
That's why they waited until after the culture fair, when things had calmed down.
And that's the end of my summary.
45 years ago...
That's what happened to my uncle?
I knew I could count on you, Oreki.
That was impressive, Houtarou.
It all makes sense.
Oreki did it again! I can't believe it!
It's just luck.
Do you have any questions?
No issues here.
I hate to admit it, but he's probably right.
Then, we'll put together an anthology for this year centered around Oreki's theory.
Let's talk about the details later.
This meeting is closed.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Really, thank you so much.
I didn't do it alone.
No, it was thanks to you.
Thanks for the umbrella.
See you.
But then...
Why did I cry?
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
This sprouting warmth confuses us
Don't you understand this feeling yet?
Normally such random glances hold no meaning
Isn't it the same when making friends?
The little shooting stars we wish upon, vanishing into the dawn
are a magic that only unfolds in the night
Let us meet in a blissful dream tonight, let it be our love
Find me, I beg you
We promised to meet, drifting in and out of sleep
Next time: The Truth of the Classics Club and Its Past.
The Truth of the Classics Club and Its Past