Stomp!
Hmph!
Oh, it's the Prince!
Fair maiden, would you give me the honor of a dance?
Of course! It'd be my pleasure, my prince!
Home Ec Prep Room
You're up next, Witch!
"This is cruel. My dear Prince. How could you choose her over me?
If this is how it is, then I'll cast a magic spell and..."
That's no good! You have to put more feeling into it!
Your prince was stolen from you! That makes you upset, right?
You have to convey that feeling in your lines!
U-Um...
Got it?
You want something like...
"This is cruel! My dear Prince... how could you choose her over me?!"
Azusa, the Fashion Club's this way!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Just who are you, miss?!
Me?
I'm Takagishi Azusa from the Drama Club!
Nice ta meetcha!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
This is my Fashion Club!
Good afternoon, everyone!
I've come to see the Fashion Club that Erika keeps boasting about!
G-Good afternoon...
Sure is a lively place you've got here!
You're all working hard, I see.
Aww, shucks.
This year's Fashion Club members are really giving it their all!
Well, I'm pretty knowledgeable about clothing design myself.
We have to make our stage costumes over at the Drama Club, after all.
Well, as you can see, we're on a whole other level from your club's costume designs.
We're pretty serious when it comes to fashion, after all.
Now wait just a second!
We put our all into making those costumes too, ya know!
Well, we're pros when it comes to all things fashion.
Your Drama Club might be pros at theatrics, but clothes are out of your league!
What're you talking about?
When it comes to costumes, the Drama Club are the specialists!
Whether it's costumes or not doesn't matter! When it comes to fashion, we're the experts!
N-Now now, you two...
Well, if you're that confident, why
don't you try making our costumes?
Fine! I'll show you just how cool a costume can look!
You mean that, Erika?
Every word.
Wh-What's with these two?
Just what on earth is going on here?
Erika is Her Rival!
A Challenge from the Drama Club!
Beating
Azusa!
Now, what this means for us is we of the Fashion Club are going to make
a seriously awesome costume for the theatrical competition next month!
We've accepted her challenge, so let's rub Azusa's nose right in it!
She's really steaming...
And if we make it right, the entire school will recognize the Fashion Club's talent,
and our popularity will shoot through the roof!
Am I right?!
Y-Yeah...
All right then, everyone! Follow my lead!
O-Okay!
This dress of mine is—
Stop, stop!
A refined lady would have a far more elegant laugh than that!
How many times do I have to tell you this stuff?
Sh-She does seem kinda forceful, doesn't she?
She is rather strict...
Well, Azusa's aiming to become a professional actress,
so she takes even her practices really seriously.
That's really pretty!
Yeah, that does look pretty good!
Doesn't it?!
That's no good at all!
This doesn't befit a noblewoman at all!
Don't you understand that?
U-Um...
All right then!
In that case, the ever-reliable Fashion Club will just have to make you your costume!
You just watch, Azusa!
Sure. I look forward to it.
Must be nice having parents who run a clothes shop.
It really must! There are so many pretty clothes here.
Well, having so many clothes to study helps improve my fashion sense.
So by choosing the upper and lower halves of the design...
You see? We have a basis for our design pattern.
Wow!
But we're making an outfit for a
high-class lady, so how about this?
Oh, that could work!
Though what about this design here?
No, I really think this one is better.
But you have to consider it's Azusa playing that lady. I think this would suit her more.
Well, what do you all think?
I dunno...
I like the coloring on Erika's more.
Tsubomi.
U-Uh, yes?
Which do you prefer, Tsubomi?
M-Me?
Well...
With Azusa's stature, I think the design Toshiko suggested would work best.
I think you might be right!
You've got a good eye, Tokko!
Well, I've got enough confidence that my fashion sense won't lose to yours, Erika!
Well, you'll have to excuse my insolence, then!
All right then!
Let's all make this costume extra special awesome!
Right!
The strider's shaded scarlet, a-i-u-e-o!
You're being too quiet!
Speak from the diaphragm!
The strider's shaded scarlet, a-i-u-e-o!
You're not being loud enough!
We won't win the competition like this!
Huh?!
You mean we're the only ones who came to the ball?!
Indeed.
This is the letter he left behind.
That's so cruel.
Yet again I am cast aside in favor of the allure of the city.
That's no good at all!
You should be shouting that line in a loud voice, right?
But if you're truly saddened by something, you're hardly going to be shouting!
Don't "but" me! Just do as I say!
You should be shouting that line. Understand?
We really don't have time to waste arguing about this.
Don't you all want to win the competition?
We haven't got that long left before the tournament phase starts.
While we're wasting time with this, all the other schools will be making progress—
Just shut up already!
You're always going on about that damn competition!
This club isn't
even fun anymore!
All we're doing is following your grand vision to the letter, Azusa!
You never listen to what we have to say at all!
She's right.
I don't want to follow a leader like you anymore.
Let's go, everyone.
Wait!
I am so beautiful.
Non, non! The light is off-center!
The whole world shall bow before my beauty!
Yay!
Perfect!
Now my next performance can be even more fabulous.
Just wait for me, Precure.
Lights!
Come on, come on, come on!
Erika, about this embroidering...
Oh, this bit?
Something like this, I guess?
That looks difficult...
I know you two can do it!
Erika! You want the lace a little higher up?
Yeah, I'll take a look in a sec!
The strider's shaded scarlet, a-i-u-e-o!
President Erika!
Is this all right?
Oh, that's perfect! Just as I
expected from you, Naminami!
I know, right?
Shrimps swim swiftly through seaweed.
What do you think?
Nice idea!
I thought so!
The plantation produces persimmon...
Wow, it really is!
Isn't it?
The woodpecker whiles...
There she is!
The costume's pretty much done, so gather everyone up and come take a look!
Where's everyone else?
They're... not here yet, it seems.
Oh, really?
Well, I think the costume's turned out pretty well!
We've all worked really hard on it together!
I'm sorry...
I'll come look at it later, all right?
Oh!
Aren't they the Drama Club members?
Tsubomi?!
Excuse me!
You're from the Drama Club, right?
Yeah, and?
Aren't you going to practice?
Azusa's been waiting for you on the rooftop.
We've...
decided to quit the Drama Club.
Huh?
Whaaaat?!
Erika, does this look good?
Erika?
Yeah, that's okay.
Phew, that's a relief.
The thing is, with Azusa...
She loves theater with all her heart, but she loves it so much she loses sight of the people around her.
Yet I can't bring myself to hate her for being so driven.
Because she kinda reminds me of myself.
Hey, Tsubomi...
Yes?
Do you think everyone enjoys being in the Fashion Club?
Erika, just look around you.
See? Everyone's having tons of fun!
Everyone's excited enough to match your frantic pace!
Jeez, Tsubomi!
Thank you!
Erika, we're finished over here!
And here!
And we've just wrapped things up too!
Whoa, this is totally amazing!
This club isn't even fun anymore!
I...
Huh?
Azusa! You came after all!
Come inside! We've finished your costume!
Sorry. I'll come some other time.
Everyone has left this town behind.
And now I...
I stand alone.
Why have you all abandoned me?
Hrm?
The Flower of your Heart has weakened quite considerably, hasn't it?
Je suis si beau.
Who are you?!
Moi?
I am the star of the desert plane, Kobraja!
Flower of the Heart, your moment has come!
Desertrian, that's your cue!
Lights!
That voice just now...
It's a Desertrian!
Azusa?!
Let's go, Erika!
Right!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Liiiiiiiiighhhhhts!
Ah, my extras have finally arrived.
Well, make sure your performance doesn't show me up.
I gave my all to help make the Drama Club what it is!
Marine!
I just wanted them to understand the joy of losing yourself in acting!
But why do you all abandon me like this?!
That's... our leader?
Hmph!
You humans are just so isolated at heart.
Working together to accomplish one single task is just a waste of effort.
It's not a waste!
Being able to make things happen with your friends is what makes them fun.
And there are things you'll never accomplish without them!
And they're a waste of effort too.
I just want everyone...
to act with me!
Leader!
I'm sure the strength of Azusa's determination will reach them!
Marine!
We have to do something about that beam!
Oh my. Are you just going to keep running, Precures?
It seems the star isn't going to need to take center stage.
I won't let you fire it!
Liiiiiiights?
Marine!
Right!
You're just toying with Azusa's theater-loving heart.
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Flowers, glitter bright!
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
Next time, I shall take my leading role! Adieu!
Azusa... Azusa!
Have I been sleeping all this time?
Azusa!
Here! Your costume!
We all worked really hard to make it for you!
You all seemed to be having so much fun in the Fashion Club.
I kept pressing on, no matter what,
but I never stopped to think
about how everyone else felt.
It's all right.
It's not too late to change, you know?
Why not try telling them how you really feel?
Erika...
Everyone has left this town behind.
And now I...
I stand alone.
I really am all alone.
No!
You are not alone!
You guys...
I'm so sorry!
I tried to make this play perfect all by
myself without considering your opinions.
That doesn't change the fact that we love acting too.
That's why we want to return to the Drama Club.
Though we'll be making sure you listen to us in future.
I want us to work together again!
Is that all right?
Yeah...
Yeah!
Hey! Don't cry, Leader!
In the language of flowers, a
bougainvillea means "passion."
Now that she has her friends at her side again,
Azusa's love for acting will bloom once more, won't it?
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree will recover a little more!
I'm so nervous!
Whoa...
Now!
Let us begin the ball!
She looks so pretty...
I can't believe it...
That's the costume we made...
Yeah! It looks really, really beautiful!
Tsubomi?
Designing clothes really is so much fun, isn't it?
It sure is!
I want to keep designing them!
Forever and ever!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Cure Moonlight is so strong and elegant!
But if we want to become stronger, what is it we need?
What you lack is her beautiful spirit!
Don't try to mimic her actions, but rather inherit her pure heart!
Please, Yuri!
Teach us how we can become stronger Precure!
HeartCatch Precure:
Please Recognize
Our Precure Spirits!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!