I love you! I love you! I love you!
You're a parasite.
It's an easy way to live.
I want to be stronger,
strong enough to contain my anger.
Takashi! Takashi! Takashi! Takashi!
Saika wants to love people.
Let's all love each other!
This power... I can use it all.
I depend on Saika, who can love others
in my place. I am her parasite.
It's a lie.
It's the truth.
He's strong...
No. He's terrifying...
No. He's awesome!
Heiwajima Shizuo... Heiwajima Shizuo...
I knew he was strong, but I had
no idea he was this strong.
Think something happened?
Why not go take a look?
You're not doing much right now.
They're special, like my scythe.
They can block a blade.
Thanks.
Now, then...
Everything
Changes
That katana can't be Saika!
Then the one who attacked me...
You even killed your parents?
That child of Saika's never
taught you to fight, did it?
Please tell the other children to stop.
You're the parent.
If you order them, they'll stop.
If Saika had taken them over,
I could issue parental orders, but-
That's impossible!
I held Saika back...
With the power of love!
But you don't know anything about love!
I'll let you listen for a moment.
Listen to Saika's words of love,
which will forever resound within me.
No...
It was a lie.
Stop!
It was the truth.
Her father was an antiquities dealer.
He took his rage at his failing
business out on his family.
Eventually, she began closing her heart.
It was then that the Slasher appeared.
I love you, darling.
The "Slasher" was her mother.
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Shizuo's hurt so bad...
We've carved our love into him.
Once he's been cut,
our minds should flow in,
through pain and fear.
He's not afraid?
Heiwajima Shizuo feels no fear?
Don't get me wrong.
It isn't that no one loves me
'cause they're all scared.
Don't make me laugh.
I'm the one who's scared.
I'm always afraid that I'll
mess up, lose control.
I'm the biggest coward in the world.
But so what?
What's that got to do with kicking your ass?
And you know...
I can't lose in front of someone
who loves me!
How?
How can you endure it?
I lack many things.
So to make up for them,
I live as a parasite off many things.
I don't have a heart capable of love,
so I can listen endlessly,
without being swayed by it.
I did it!
That's right!
I don't care about you!
Why are you scared?
You cut out of love, right?
You let me cut you! Why?
I'm about to do something awful to you.
So now we're even.
I'll have my Saika take over your mind.
I won't apologize.
If I did, it would negate
my very way of life.
I know it isn't fair.
To protect my own peace,
I'm going to do something awful to you.
But it can't be helped.
I'm a parasite.
I love you! I love you! I love you!
Saika is a lonely thing.
From our perspective, it may be wrong.
But she really does love humans.
So, Niekawa-sempai,
you love her, too.
Unlike me, you can love others.
Stop!
Stop, damn it!
Huh?
What's going on?
What are we doing here?
No one died, huh?
At last...
At last, it did what I wanted.
Anri! Is that you?
That girl once came after me with a knife.
I had her transfer, to avoid
making a big fuss.
I guess she hadn't given up-
Anri, let's get out of here!
Sonohara, I've looked out for you.
Right, like with Harima!
Who do you think got you
into Harima's class?
I've already repaid you.
R-Repaid me... With that?
I thought the Slasher was the Black Rider.
So when I thought you were
going to be attacked,
I did everything I could to try to save you.
Not because I liked you.
Because I wanted to repay you.
What are you talking about?
Why was the Black Rider chasing you?
What did you do?
That's the girl from...
What?
Anri, what are you doing with that thing?
Are you one of them, too?
Are you going to...
No. I'm not like Niekawa-sempai.
I detest you.
Smooth-and-hairless ftw!
By the way, what's Dengeki Bunko
got out this month?
I can't do anything bad in this car.
Oh, right. Think there'll be a
new chapter of Kino's Journey?
Maybe Shizu's Journey!
Maybe they'll come out with
Samoyed Mask Can't Possibly Be This Cute!
I knew this would happen
if we asked Yumasaki.
Damn it.
Togusa-san, your face is red.
Got a fever or something?
Shut up!
Are you really OK, Sonohara-san?
Yeah, it's nothing.
I was so shocked when
I heard from Masaomi.
Are you really OK?
So where is Masaomi?
He left a bit ago.
He had something to do.
What could he have to
do, at a time like this?
It's fine, really.
Did you talk to the police?
Supposedly, a lot of other
people were hurt, too...
It's fine.
It's not!
I don't think anything else will happen.
Why?
I'm sorry.
Actually,
several hours before I got hurt,
the Slasher attacked me.
A lot of people saved me.
Some of them were so cool.
Cool?
What is this?
A bartender with sunglasses...
No way. It was Shizuo-san?
And another who was so awesome...
Listen to this!
It was the Headless Rider!
Wait a second!
I talked to them for a minute.
They were so strong,
and they could love others.
You wouldn't believe me, would you?
Um, well, I...
She's a girl!
And when I was attacked later,
the Headless Rider saved me again!
So I think I'm OK.
But they're...
I can't say it. Because if I do...
People like that are far away
from our everyday lives.
So you should stay away.
Ryuugamine-kun, in this world,
what do you think is the real non-everyday?
It's for nothing to happen.
It's to have the same day, over and over,
with nothing happening.
Nothing changing.
That's the real...
I'll show this girl to a doctor I know.
Don't worry.
Celty-san... Um, I-
Don't apologize.
You did what you thought
was right, didn't you?
I think it was the right thing to do, too.
Knocking my head off was a bit much,
but I'll chalk that up to Saika.
I'm not being sympathetic.
I just don't think I could beat you in a fight.
If you can't accept that,
use your power to better this town.
She gained power...
The power to control a group of
over a hundred Saikas at will.
It was a heavy burden for her.
But it was also something she'd wanted.
She felt like she'd been floating along.
And the weight of holding someone's destiny
in her hands would firmly ground her.
Then she heard a voice.
I can't love you, but
I don't mind you.
It may have been her imagination.
She asked who was there,
but no answer came.
But that was fine.
It made her just a little bit happy.
At last, she had returned to her everyday.
But she couldn't tell them the truth.
Not about Saika or about
the one behind this.
When she had taken control
of all the Saikas,
she had learned of them through
Niekawa Haruna's memories.
She didn't know what they were after.
But if that person planned to destroy her peace,
or that of Mikado or Masaomi...
As she struggled with uneasiness and resolve,
she remembered the name.
The name was...
Orihara Izaya's a weird
name, you know that?
It may be a coincidence
that I grew up this way,
but I think that it's perfect for me.
How much do you believe in
coincidence, Namie-san?
What are you talking about?
They think a lot of what happened
this time was coincidence.
I was the one who sent Nasujima
there, at that hour.
But he's an idiot.
To find Sonohara Anri's address, all you need
is to sneak a look at the class roster.
Anyway, you know, once you accept that they
exist, you can find quite a lot of 'em...
Cursed blades, faeries, stuff like that...
Yeah. The real coincidence was when
Nasujima took my money and ran.
He was in serious debt, so
he tried to get money by
blackmailing the father of
Niekawa Haruna, his former stalker.
The Awakusu-Kai, the loan sharks
he owed the money,
introduced him to me as someone
who could investigate her family.
He came here and took
the bait I'd prepared.
Another Random Attack?
12-Year-Old Girl Attacked
I knew Niekawa Haruna was Saika.
The plan was to grab Nasujima and be like,
"You bastard, you stole my money!"
Then I'd be able to threaten
him and use Haruna.
But then the real Saika showed up.
What happened to Nasujima, you ask?
G-Give me your money!
For my part, I'd have been
happy if Shizu-chan had died.
But whatever.
Things worked out just like I wanted.
Just like you wanted?
What do you want?
There are a lot more cops here.
Slasher Night Tolls Over Fifty Victims!
Slasher? Or Terrorism?
The media's making a big deal of it.
Something happened in South
Ikebukuro Park, didn't it?
I heard that was just a brawl.
Wasn't it the Slasher?
What was all that about, anyway?
That guy we saw was weird.
He didn't remember a thing,
like he'd been hypnotized.
The cops think it was a fight
between color gangs.
Not just the cops.
"It was the Dollars' doing!"
Huh?
What?
Is this the leader of the Dollars?
Seeking Information
Seeking information on the Slasher.
Calm down, Mikado.
So, what were you after?
Now the town's split into three forces:
the cursed blade's army, the Dollars,
and the Yellow Scarves.
And the former's infiltrated the latter two.
To be honest, I would've been fine
with Niekawa Haruna,
as long as I got the cursed blade's army.
But Sonohara Anri's interesting, ain't she?
And?
This is just the tinder, and that's fine.
Leave it alone, and it'll keep
piling up and piling up...
I can't wait!
But the Yellow Scarves were started
by a middle school brat.
They that impressive?
That he can gather that many, despite being
a kid, means he's a serious threat.
But... I do know him, though.
Please don't drag me back.
It was the Dollars!
They're getting out of control!
We need you, sempai!
He's the general, damn it!
I'm sorry!
Nah, it's fine, really.
I'm not the general anymore.
I'm just a civvie.
Yeah.
Just a...
Just a high schooler...
That's right. I wanted to
be just a high schooler.
I wanted my peace.
I wanted to live a semi-dangerous life,
surrounded by friends.
And they ruined it!
They'll pay.
They'll pay for going after Anri.
We beat up the Slashers,
no matter how many there are.
And if the Dollars are behind them,
we beat them up, too.
The bastards dragged me back, damn it.
Damn it all!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Out of
Your Control
I came back.
I never wanted to.
But I came back.
To finish what happened in my past. And in Saki's and his.
Next time:
Out of Your Control.