Give it up already!
Yagyu...
Oh, boy! Yagyu's usually cool as a cucumber, but now she's turnin' beet red!
Come on, bring it!
The right side!
Ha! You fell for it!
No way!
Yay!
That was the old maid!
All right! We won!
Aw, Yagyu lost.
Heh heh heh heh. Time for your punishment.
My forehead flicks'll land you in a world of pain!
Wait!
I'm the one who lost! Do it to me!
What're you talkin' about?
This is a team game, right?
So if you lose, the whole team's gotta pay, right?
Yeah, but...
Ain't no buts about it!
Here goes!
Hibari, I'm sorry.
Ee-yow!
Now it's your turn, Yagyu...
That hurt!
That really hurt!
You're so mean, Katsu!
Hibari,
there's no time for pity in the ring.
It's because of you...
...that I ended up with this...
Don't be a sore loser just 'cos you're behind!
I'll enjoy this.
Nobody can stand up to me in a fist fight.
You four, please be quiet.
We're sorry.
The sea breeze sure smells great, though.
Nothin' compared to the scent of a fine young lady like yourself!
Sniff sniff...
H-Hold on, Katsu!
No means no!
Oh, my, that smell is just divine.
I feel like I could down three whole bowls of rice!
Really? Lemme sniff too!
Sniff sniff...
Not you too, Hibari!
Stop it!
Didn't I tell you to be quiet?!
Oh, look what I can see!
Is that...
Yeah. Our seaside training ground, Ninja Island.
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
Seaside Training - Ninja Island
This is our training camp?
Yeah.
This ancient building has deep cultural significance.
You could say it's starting to look a little run down.
Kind of has that old, abandoned feel to it.
Y-Yeah, that's it!
Yes, indeed.
We're here for ninja training, after all.
It looks like a haunted house.
Don't say that, Hibari.
Nobody else went that far.
Really?
This is a ninja house,
where famous ninjas have come to train ever since the Edo period.
How can you possibly not take pride in being able to train here?
Sorry about that, Mr. Kiriya.
It just isn't how I imagined it. It's more like...
...a haunted house.
Don't say that.
Okay, then. Time to start training!
R-Right now?
It's way too soon!
I mean, we came all the way here to the beach! We gotta put on our swimsuits!
That won't be necessary.
After all, your first training exercise will be...
to clean up this place!
He's right. If we don't clean this place up first, it'll be in no shape for us to stay here.
If we have to clean up this whole place, we'll be here until evening.
Aw...
Here we are at the beach, so the beach oughta come first.
What could that be?
I-It's not how it looks, Mr. Kiriya!
I wasn't slacking off!
I'm sorry!
Y-You tryin' to give me a heart attack?!
I thought you were Mr. Kiriya!
Speaking of which, where is Mr. Kiriya?
He went off with Yagyu earlier,
saying something about fishing.
What?!
Leavin' us to do all the cleaning?
And why'd he take Yagyu with him?
I think they're supposed to be securing tonight's dinner.
Got one!
Kiriya
Yagyu
This is bad.
Kiriya
Ya
At the rate I'm going..
Kiriya
Ya
I can hardly call myself a teacher.
You don't suppose our dinner is...
...whatever we can catch ourselves?
I suppose this too is part of our training.
It's all right.
We seem to have plenty of rice, miso, and salt.
You mean that's all we have?!
Hang in there. Super-ninja or bust!
"Super-ninja or bust"?
What's this?
That oughta be enough firewood.
Man, I wanna see everyone's swimsuits...
I thought the bowls were clean,
but they were all covered in dust.
Asuka, what's with those leeks?
They were growing in the field out back.
They're a bit past their prime,
but beggars can't be choosers.
Nope.
Say, Asuka...
"Super-ninja"?
Yep. That's what it said.
Ah, someone from a previous class who came here must have written it.
In that out-of-the-way place?
They might not have been serious,
but I can kind of understand why they'd write their dreams somewhere not everyone could see it.
Oh, so they wrote down their dreams.
I wonder if whoever wrote it went on to become a great ninja.
It'd be nice if they did, huh?
Yeah!
We got us quite a haul!
Kiriya
Wow, we're eating big today!
Leave it to Mr. Kiriya.
Uh, actually...
Let's dig in!
Wow, this looks delicious!
Yagyu, I gotta give you more credit.
Of course.
Mr. Kiriya...
I may have washed out on fishing,
but I'm the one who caught the clams.
What's a "super-ninja"?
Mr. Kiriya?
From the name, it sounds like an ultimate ninja.
One that surpasses all others, you could say.
Really? A ninja like that could easily beat up all the bad guys and bring peace to the world, right?
That they could.
Hey, Katsu! That seaweed's good for you!
Here goes! Ninja Art: Wild Pillow!
Nice try! Ninja Art: Pillow Counter!
I'm in too!
Hibari! Think fast!
Thanks, Yagyu.
That's right! Hibari has her impenetrable barrier: Yagyu!
All right, Asuka. Let's put up a unified front too!
Yeah!
Stop it!
Bull's-eye!
Oh, really?
Should I take that as a challenge?
I accept!
Hey! Do you know what time it—
Make any more noise,
and you'll all go without breakfast.
Right...
It's all your fault that I got dragged into this.
This is just another part of our training.
Sorry? Did you just say something?
Good night!
Yagyu really does like Hibari, doesn't she?
They're both in the same year,
so it's good that they get along.
It's more than just that.
They're almost like sisters.
Asuka, hurry up and get to sleep.
We have an early start tomorrow.
Right.
What's a "super-ninja"?
A super-ninja, huh?
Senran Kagura
Aw, why'd we hafta wear our uniforms to the beach?
What did you expect? We're here to train.
All right, today we'll do some Sudden Death training.
Sudden Death?
Sudden Death
Begin!
Sudden Death is a ninja technique where one's armor is spontaneously shed, placing the user at risk
but greatly increasing speed and attack strength.
However, the increased speed and power
come with a dramatic reduction in defense.
During Sudden Death, any one of your opponent's attacks could prove fatal.
Strike, but do not be struck!
Right!
You girls try it too.
Heave-ho!
Finally, some free time at last! Let's go have some fun!
Hey, Yagyu...
What?
Weren't we just out training in swimsuits?
Why'd we need to change again?
Those and these are two different things.
Yeah. One kind's for fighting, the other's for showing off. There's a big difference.
Katsu! Give me back my swimsuit!
What's wrong with goin' topless? We're all girls here!
No!
Having fun is just another part of training.
Katsu! Give it back!
Not on your life!
Asuka, have you seen Mr. Kiriya anywhere?
No, I haven't.
I wanted to check tomorrow's schedule with him.
I'll be waiting at the cliff.
-Your precious student
Wow!
There are so many fish!
Say, Yagyu, look at all these fish...
Hibari?!
Who's there?!
Up here.
I've got my orders.
Come face me.
Oh?
Looks like you're an expert at running away, if nothing else.
A-Are you... one of the dark ninjas?
I'm a freshman at Serpentine Academy. Mirai's the name.
Take it to the grave with you!
Anyone who attempts to bring harm to Hibari
will answer to me.
Yagyu!
When did she get here?
Come at me with all your might!
Ninja Morph!
You any good?
Any good?
I'd sure like to think so.
Ha.
If I wasn't good enough for this mission I'd just be wastin' all of our time, yeah?
Fine, then.
I've been waitin' for this moment myself.
Ninja Morph!
Damn. I gave as good as I got, and yet...
Is that you?
Rin!
Impossible.
Rin is... gone...
I've been lured away!
Crap!
The students!
Y-Yagyu!
Don't worry. This is nothing.
Don't underestimate me. You might get hurt.
Sterblich!
N-Not bad.
H-Hmph!
I-I think I shall call it a day.
But remember this.
The next time we meet,
you won't get off so lightly!
I won't forget this!
Who was that?
Why did she come here?
I don't know.
But she's more skilled than she looks.
Aren't you a weak one?
Whatever. That oughta do it.
If that's how you wanna play...
Huh?
Where the hell'd you go?!
We're not done here!
The others are so late.
No one has come back yet.
I wonder if something happened.
Ah, here they come!
They got the drop on us, huh?
Serpentine Academy?
You're sure that's what she said?
Y-Yes.
Do you know of it?
I heard about it the other day from Master Hanzo.
The hidden Serpentine Academy for Girls.
Apparently, it's a training facility for dark ninjas,
set up to oppose our own Hanzo Academy.
A training facility...
...for dark ninjas?
I meant to bring them up while we were training here.
Then, that lady who attacked me earlier...
And the puppeteer who attacked us in the shopping district too?
There's no doubt Serpentine Academy was behind both incidents.
The girl I fought didn't seem to want a proper fight in the first place.
She had me wrapped around her finger.
Dammit! I'm so freakin' pissed!
The next time I see her,
she's not gonna get away!
The one who attacked us was much the same.
You too?
Yeah.
She wasn't out for blood.
Then what were they up to?
Either way...
Now that they've come this far,
I doubt their objective is mere provocation.
We don't know what they're after,
but by no means shall we yield to the dark ninjas.
Right!
I don't care who shows up next!
There's no way I'm gonna lose!
Naturally.
Next time, we'll beat them for sure,
and feel 'em all over!
Why are you feeling me?!
Ugh, back to this again?
That's our Katsu!
Come on, Hibari!
Ah, it's almost time for supper.
And these two only think of their stomachs.
It wouldn't kill us to show a little more urgency.
Tonight, we're having squid sashimi,
broiled squid, and fried squid legs.
What, nothing but squid?!
If you've got a problem with it, you can just go hungry.
That form...
How does the enemy know about Rin?
When the love you devoted to others vanishes, girl,
your heart will turn to ice
When the wishes you believed in have rotted away, girl,
you will come to know only strife
Once I was deemed innocent,
but now those days are gone forever,
and I wander aimlessly and all alone
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
The fragrant flower                           in your heart
blooms undaunted                               under this sky
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
There is a red flower in your heart
Let it bloom and scatter its petals before it is picked
Next Episode Preview
Yagyu, you really like dried squid, don't you?
There are other things I like too, you know.
Oh? Like what?
Hibari.
So Hibari's on the same level as dried squid to you...
Next time, "Sneak Attack! Hanzo Academy."
Sneak Attack! Hanzo Academy
Come get it like your life depended on it.