Sasa
Sasami Report,
Sasami Re
eport
Number 3,
Number 3
Second draft.
Second draft
Everything in this country houses a god.
houses a god.
They're known as the gods of the Yaoyorozu.
From roadside pebbles to buildings and gadgets,
from animals to weeds,
and even from forces of nature to laws of physics.
Everything that exists houses a god
that controls it.
that controls
it.
These gods are ranked by divinity.
Gods with high divinity reign over the lower ones,
and can transform them at will.
This is called a Transformation.
call
called
called a Transformation.
The god with the greatest divinity that rules over all
is the Supreme God, Amaterasu.
Every god will change their form to suit Amaterasu's wishes,
Transformation       Transformation
and Transform.
What would you like to search?
Options                      Search
The world takes the form of whatever the supreme god wishes.
How to get you
Options                      Search
deleted!
I once inherited that great power,
Moron
maintained it,
and managed it.
However,
Amaterasu's power is currently...
inside my brother, of all places.
My brother can now be considered equal to the supreme god.
"Supreme God"
That's why whenever my brother wishes for something,
The gods of the Yaoyorozu will try to curry favor,
and cause a Transformation.
Yesterday's Valentine Tragedy was one of them.
To please my brother,
all the gods morphed into chocolate,
and begged to be eaten.
Fortunately,
Tsurugi,
Kagami,
and Tama, a.k.a. the three Yagami sisters,
subdued the Transformation.
I can't be certain as to who they are,
but their strong spiritual powers and high divinity can't be debated.
It seems that not only my brother,
but those sisters require observation as well.
Over.
Tsukuyomi Sasami.
Tsukuyomi Sasami
God's hand paints the seasons
They are the song that rocks me in my sleep
as my dreams journey past the eternal stars
while I rock in my sleep
Sasami
Ganbaranai
When I cup my ears and walk through the crowds
my sense of self disappears
I'm not yet old enough to accept that sometimes
your heart desires discord
I saw a scared, gentle flower in the wilderness
When I touched it, the diorama turned into reality
The whims of God draw the map that depicts my future
Countless sounds echo from it
so I do not care
what my inevitable tomorrow may bring
The bonds that let us sit together under a starry sky
show me human warmth
The bonds we forge as we hurt others
are the bonds I want to protect
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Episode 2
Home Security Guard
Hooray, I won!
Shaddup, jerky jerkface!
And come on, grown-ups don't get all worked up over winnin' a game, you poophead!
You're loud, so quiet down.
We're in class, after all.
With your childish attitude,
I'm unable to show myself in public
as either your student or your sister.
As your teacher and your sister,
I don't care what someone who sleeps through class has to whine about.
The drill ended long ago.
However, my homework checking partner is not here.
Say,
we've got a lot of empty chairs.
It's been that way for some time.
Oh, is that so?
Please pay more attention.
You're a teacher, after all.
Teachers care far less about students
than you all seem to think.
I did not need to know the cruel truth.
Augh, I'm pissed!
Just spill it already!
Something's gotta be up!
Why's it a ghost town in here?
Secret Freshman Class
H... Hello.
Chat Log
Evening!!!
Yesterday was fun.
Let's play again.
Lots of decorations
in stock!
Finally saved some SP
Yesterday was fun.
Let's play again.
You're high level.
I'm jealous.
Roger that.
You're high level.
I'm jealous.
Roger that.
You're high level.
I'm jealous.
Roger that.
You're high level.
I'm jealous.
FROGGIIIIES
Roger that.
Look at this.
The heck's that?
It's the raddest hit game that the kids can't get enough of, Eight-Forked Serpent SNS.
Eight-Forked Serpent SNS?
Simply put, it's a swords-and-sorcery school fantasy social network system.
And so,
him, her, and her
oh, sleeping
Teacher's coming!
No, lol
are all students staying home from school
to play in this online world all day.
Is it that fun?
I can't say.
The game was poorly balanced,
and it was a grindfest on the verge of shutdown due to bankruptcy,
but it surged in popularity three years ago for some reason, and now it's everywhere.
I should give it a try.
Oh?
If you're interested, does that mean it's a Transformation?
Tsukuyomi, your sister's got a computer, right?
Yes.
Around ten, I believe.
So yeah,
lend us a PC.
Hi, Mr. Fluffy!
This is not bad.
Hey, I'm not chewin' you out for playin' hooky,
so work with me here.
Eight-Forked Serpent
Password
User ID
How many computers does one girl need?
Ya can't even use 'em all.
Sure I can.
One for internet, one for games, one for videos, one for music, one for games, one for games...
How many do ya need for games?!
Each one has a purpose.
Anyway, I'm new with these things.
You know how these games work, right?
I've never played one with Sasami.
I-I restrain myself.
I don't even know why people like this crap, anyway.
Wow, you're a shut-in from the internet, too?
I can't speak it.
I'm a hardcore online gamer,
so I've sunk thousands of hours into Eight-Forked Serpent SNS!
I can't tell them I've built the strongest character and decked her out in the rarest gear!
S-So uh, what's with this Eight-Sporked thingy?
No clue.
But if it's suspicious, we gotta squash it out.
If we're too late, we're gonna have problems.
Like the recent Valentine Tragedy.
This is bad.
If they deem Eight-Forked Serpent SNS an Oddity and destroy it,
my experience, gold, Serpent Rank, items, and the thousands of hours I've invested will all...
I have to stop them at all costs!
Sweet, done!
I'm startin'.
Welcome to Heaven's Gate Academy!
Before your entrance ceremony, could you tell me about yourself?
What should I do?
You have to create a character first.
I wanna get through this quick, so I'll pick a warrior class.
Job Selection
Back
Oh,
is this your real job?
Huh?
You're quite lucky, sister.
That message seldom appears.
You've unlocked a rare class.
Serious?!
Tsurugi's true job is... this!
Name
Sex
Age
Race
Job
tsurugi
Female
Human
Delinquent
I
HP
Armor
Weapon
Default Items
Ability
Trench coat
Wooden Sword
Cigarettes x3
Extortion
I
A Delinquent!
What the crap?!
Wait, being a delinquent's a job?
Say hello to a fun school lifestyle!
Whoooooopsie,
my hand sliiiiiipped.
Nooooooo,
the router's broke.
A cable has been disconnected.
Please check your network connection.
Hey, what the heck're you doing?
Sorry, guess we can't use the net anymore.
There is no need to worry.
I have my own high speed connection.
I have completed mine as well.
I believe we need a designated healer.
Start heating
Cancel
Minutes
Seconds
Open
Clear
Clean
Deodorize
Minutes
Start heating
Deodorize
Cancel
Start heating
Minutes
Choose Rice
Timer Adjustment (Long Press)
Schedule
Choose Temperature
Timer Adjustment (Long Press)
Schedule
Choose Rice
Timer Adjustment (Long Press)
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Single
Weatherproof Model
Basic Electrical Energy Standards
Official Number
AC Single Phase
Wire
Model
Voltage
Year of Manufacture
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Oh, a nurse?
No, a veterinarian.
I've no interest in regular humans.
Name
Sex
Age
Race
Job
kagami
Female
Elf
Vet
I
HP
Armor
Weapon
Default Items
Ability
Nurse Outfit -3
Nurse Cap -3
Syringe
Anesthetic x3
Anesthesia
I
Shikaku Electronics Inc.
Year of Manufacture
Can vets heal humans?
Sleepin' when things get tough, huh?
Oh, whoopsie!
The breaker got tripped.
You didn't save anything, either.
May as well give up for today.
I'm doney too!
Name
Sex
Age
Race
Job
tama
Female
Demon
Pastry Chef
I
HP
Armor
Weapon
Default Items
Ability
Maid Outfit
Kitchen Knife
None
Julienne
I
I'm a pastry cheffy!
I'm gonna make all the pastries I can eat!
Shoot!
I gave them all laptops, so their batteries—
I didn't save my report!
Hey Tsukuyomi, turn the breaker on.
Yes, right away.
Hurry up, we're waiting on you.
Yes, in a moment.
Oh, your time ran out.
Can't even pick one option, huh?
I bet you're some piece of shit who can't choose for himself in real life, either.
You may want to drown out your pathetic social life in games,
but the internet's a bitch too, faggot.
Was I really just insulted that much?
This suits you both inside and out!
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Eight-Forked
Serpent
Online
Name
Sex
Age
Race
Job
kamiomi
Male
Human
Loser
I
HP
Armor
Weapon
Default Items
Ability
None
Manservant
I
Your job is... loser?
I'm not even wearing clothes...
My brother's pathetic even in a game...
Say hello to a fun school lifestyle!
Chat Log
Okay, so now we start for real.
Don't miss any signs of a Transformation, guys.
I couldn't stop them.
I tried the blackout trick,
the birdlime trick,
and my clumsy damsel trick,
and they all ended in failure!
So anyway, what do we do next?
There is no set path, per se.
One may behave however they wish in this world.
And what's so fun about that?
Screw the net, you can just do whatever you want in real life.
Maybe you can.
Anyway, you got any tea in this place?
Who said you could make yourself at home?
I'll get some!
Some candy or chips would be cool too!
Have some consideration!
I want a chocolate parfait!
Make it yourself, chef!
Potato Chips
Your orders, ladies.
My bad, you didn't have to.
You sure made it sound like he did!
What's up?
Don't touch things with those chip hands!
You're getting the keyboard dirty!
C'mon, who cares?
I care!
Use chopsticks!
Nah, sounds like a pain.
You have to, Sister.
Shut-ins have their own form of etiquette.
But if you simply crunch the chips like this,
your hands won't be dirtied if you eat directly from the bag.
You're a genius!
Now then...
What have you done?!
Don't worry.
If you eat it in thirty seconds, it's totally safe.
Forget the chips!
Hey, I can use the chopsticks!
I need the vacuum!
Hey.
You've been way too quiet.
I didn't do anything.
Did you do something?
I-I didn't do anything!
Let me see.
No, don't look!
I told you not to look...
Just shut it down already!
Oh, you've got this comic?
I've been dying to read it!
Get your chip hands away from those!
We'll just read it together.
It's a first edition, so you're killing the value!
C'mon, I won't rip it up.
Don't throw out the insert!
Oh, I've yet to see this movie.
Don't open that!
I haven't even opened it myself!
Hey hey, what do I do here?
It's asking me to "delete" or something.
NOW DELETING DATA
PLEASE WAIT
DATA     DELETED
My party!
I'm done.
One person can't fight against being terrorized on all fronts!
I miscalculated!
I lost the moment I let them into my room!
Chat Log
Hey, you!
Don't cause a ruckus in class!
He hit me?
But I was paying attention in class!
Chat Log
kamiomi received 2 damage.
kamiomi has died.
And I died?
Hey kamiomi, you dead?
Someone take him to the infirmary.
He's takin' it lightly!
Chat Log
Now then, let us resurrect Mr. Tsukuyomi.
So, how do we do that?
Minigame
Minigame: "Naughty Infirmary" has begun.
Naughty
Infirmary
Chat Log
Huh?
Do anything you can to restore his health within the time limit.
Sooo, how about this?
Chat Log
tama cooled kamiomi's head.
You tryin' to cure his cold?
kamiomi returned to life.
Chat Log
Why?!
You've saved my life, Tama!
Chat Log
kamiomi's Heart Points rose 20 points.
Heart Points? What're those?
If you raise your Heart Points,
two characters can get married,
and they can create baby characters.
What?
This game's got baby-makin'?!
If that's true, I'm up next!
Infirmary beds are easy spots to start porn scenes in!
Chat Log
Now, Tsukuyomi, you strip too!
What? Me too?
Chat Log
I'm no innocent maiden,
so lie back and enjoy it!
I'm aware that you're not quite innocent,
but this isn't that kind of game—
I'm really, really scared!
Tsurugi and Paparin are naked and doing weird things!
Please don't traumatize elementary schoolers.
Aw yeah gurl, take it!
This is outrageous, Ms. Tsurugi!
It may be a game, but if you continue...
Your resistance only makes me harder!
How's this?
Chat Log
What are you doing to my brother?!
W-What?
Would... this be you?
Wow! She looks duper strong!
You're still my brother, Brother!
Don't lie there just because it's a game, stupid!
Pervert! Shitstain!
Go ahead and bone a 2D sprite and marry it or whatever and see if I care!
You retarded perma-bonered dumbfuck piece of human scum!
Sasami is in this game?
Chat Log
And she's berating me in her cute, sadistic way...
Human scum!
Chat Log
Stay away!
kamiomi received 9999 damage.
kamiomi has died.
So, you've been ditching school and playing Eight-Forked Serpent SNS this whole time?
Well, I've also shopped online, watched videos, read net idol blogs, and stuff...
Same thing!
But I'm not the only one addicted to that game...
I've hacked the administration,
and it seems that approximately ten thousand people are shut-ins due to this game.
I wonder what their purpose is.
Beats me.
I don't get anything this guy's doing.
Tsurugi...
A crisis situation has come about!
What's wrong?
I...
I have to pee!
You shoulda gone earlier.
Tsurugi, come with me!
You're in grade school now, so can't you go potty on your own?
It may be a cruel truth,
but mankind has yet to reach such a state!
You lost me!
We'll be right back, so play without us.
So, what will you do now?
For now, we shall advance through the game.
First, return to the classroom.
What could this mean?
Chat Log
Did... something happen?
Look closely.
Chat Log
Are those lights... the players' spirit energy?
That thing's sucking up the spirit energy...
Chat Log
The Demon Army?
I sense a great power.
An exceptional divi... ni... ty...
Kagami!
Aah!
Owie, my posterior.
Could this be...
What could have happened?
Chat Log
Oh no.
Brother,
ru—
This is quite the Oddity.
It seems our consciousnesses have been sucked into Eight-Forked Serpent SNS.
So, this really is a Transformation?
The Eight-Forked Serpent...
Its divinity is too high.
It reached this state by consuming the spirit energy of the players.
No...
But one thing eludes me.
Why did nothing else happen while it was growing so large?
Were it an evil god,
it would possess the players' corporeal bodies
and use them to invade the real world.
Yet this one only devours its sacrifices and does nothing more.
How puzzling.
With such power,
it could invade the real world and construct its own kingdom.
It doesn't care about the real world.
It only cares about maintaining this one.
Its sole desire is to live forever in this alternate world.
Because that's where it belongs.
What do you mean?
It's got the same stench as us.
With a divinity that high, it has to be a pal of the Supreme God.
In other words,
it's a monster that Sasami unconsciously brought to life.
You'll know if you check its profile.
You started playing here three years ago, right?
So you could run from the pain of reality.
So you could escape your rigorous ascetic training.
You played here, right?
And you made a wish.
This game was on the verge of collapse,
but it came back to life overnight three years ago.
Nice coincidence, huh?
He kept your playground alive all this time.
He protected it.
So it's...
something I wished for?
Back when I still had the Supreme God's power...
my desire...
created this?
Really?
I see.
You've protected this world for me this whole time.
You get it now, right?
He's played out his role.
So go tell him that.
I command you by the name of Tsukuyomi Sasami.
Rampaging god,
be still.
Scatter,
melt into the world and rest.
I'm fine now.
My life's pretty happy.
So that's why you don't have to...
try so hard anymore.
When you wake
up, make sure you
sleep in your bed.
Important notice to all users
Due to a technical issue, Eight-Forked Serpent SNS
is experiencing momentary downtime.
Sasami
Ganbaranai
Hooray, it's finally here! Sasami's live performance!
I'm certain she'll sing for us this time!
Yeah, yeah! Take your mic!
Are you ready?
Hey, come on!
Oh? You're not responding?
You're unmotivated to the bone!
Oh, the song's already started!
We'll be broadcasting dead air at this rate!
This is all for Sasami,
so while I may be unfit,
I shall rise to the occasion as best I can!
Yay!
C'mon!
Chachacha!
Yo!
Whoo!
Whoo, Fever!
Phew, I worked hard back there.
I put my heart into those shouts!
But even so, it seems Sasami still has no motivation.
I need to take more drastic measures.
This plan failed pretty badly.
Oh, that's right!
Next time, I should get the Yagami sisters to assist me!
Weather Forecast
It's time for Whatever Weather.
Today's weather for people who stay inside from morning till night doesn't matter one bit.
Today's Weather
Nagasaki
Osaka
Nagoya
Tokyo
Sapporo
You're home at night, you're home at midnight,
and you're home the next morning, so it doesn't make a difference.
But the sun wakes me up when the sky's clear, and I wish it'd cut that out.
I'm jealous of people with thick curtains.
Next time, on Episode 3:
Next Time, on Episode 3
Work is for suckers.
Work is for suckers