Minami, do you want to stay here in Germany?
If you really want to, I'll make arrangements for you.
Sis...
Won't you come with me...?
Sure I will!
I'll come with you, Hazuki.
I'll come with you
to Japan.
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
though a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Question 8
Me, Japan, and words I don't know
This was one year ago during the school's entrance ceremony.
I had just arrived in Japan and didn't speak Japanese very well.
I hope we get along!
Whether I would make it or not in Japan depended on the impression I made then,
so I sat there, nervously waiting for my turn to introduce myself,
hoping I didn't say anything stupid.
Next is... Shimada Minami.
My name is Shimada Minami.
I hope we get along!
What's going on? Did I say something weird?
Ahem. Shimada has been living in Germany until now.
She hasn't been in Japan for very long, so there'll be many things she doesn't know.
I hope we'll all help her get used to her new life here.
It'll be all right, Shimada.
You can take your time to learn the Chinese characters.
Chinese characters?
Shimada
Minahi
h
i
I hope we get along!
He could've just told me if it was the wrong character!
It's so much crueler to not point it out and laugh on the inside!
Dad said the Japanese are really nice people,
but I can't help but feel anxious about this class.
Came from Kannazuki Junior High School.
The name's Sakamoto Yuuji.
It's the "Man-Eater" of Kannazuki Junior High!
And he's in our class.
Sakamoto
Yuuji
Is this kind of behavior the norm in Japan?
No, Dad said Japan's one of the rare countries that maintains perfect public order.
He must be trying to look cool.
Kinoshita Hideyoshi is my name.
Well met.
I wonder why she's wearing the boys' uniform.
Kinoshita
Hideyoshi
She probably doesn't like wearing skirts. Yeah.
I shouldn't worry.
Dad said that there's nothing weird or scary in Japan.
Tsuchiya
Kouta
Tsuchiya Kouta.
My hobbies are peeping on gir— nothing really.
I'm good at eavesdrop— nothing in particular.
Tsuchiya
Kouta
Hey! You dropped...
Forget what you just saw!
This isn't weird, is it?
He's gonna record the lectures with that, isn't he?
I should believe you, right, Dad?
I'm from Nagatsuki Junior High! My name's Yoshii Akihisa!
Let's all get along!
Yoshii
Akihisa
He tricked me.
My own father tricked me!
Did you live in Japan before, Shimada?
When did you come back to Japan?
Were you born abroad too?
A foreigner returning to Japan must've been very unusual.
Everyone was bombarding me with questions.
You must be very good at English, right?
Are you gonna join a club?
Do you have a boyfriend in Germany?
Oh dear.
I don't understand Japanese very well,
so if they all talk to me at once...
How do I tell them to slow down in Japanese?
What are your hobbies?
What do you like to eat?
What's your bust size?
I know!
That girl I saw this morning said something to get rid of the boys talking to her.
I should try the same thing.
Cork...
"Cork"?
Cork it, you filthy pigs!
Huh?
I messed up on my very first day.
Dad told me later that I said something really horrible.
Because of that, no one wanted to talk to me anymore...
except one boy.
Umm... You're Shimada, right?
Yes!
Huh? What?
Why are you wearing...
Oh, this? It's because...
I overslept this morning, so I was in a hurry.
Do Japanese boys wear girls' uniforms if they're in a hurry?
They never teach you these things in school.
Hey, moron!
Don't block the exit while talking about your crap.
Don't be like that, Sakamoto.
Shimada is new to Japan. You shouldn't call her a moron!
I'm calling you a moron, Yoshii!
What have I done to be called a moron?!
Your uniform and your speech, for starters!
What did you say? Don't judge me just because of my outfit!
Nah, it's already clear that you're a moron!
In that case, aren't you a moron too?!
You were ignoring that super-cute girl who was talking to you in the morning!
That's none of your fucking business, now is it?!
Your retardation has been getting on my nerves since I first saw your stupid face!
That's my line! How rude of you to call someone you just met a moron!
You expect me to be courteous to an idiot who showed up at the entrance ceremony in a frickin' girl's uniform?!
Well, good-bye!
I didn't know what they were talking about,
but I did understand one thing.
If I got any more involved with those two, my normal school life would be history.
I wonder if I can make it though this school.
I was really worried if I made the right decision to come to Japan with Hazuki because of Dad's transfer.
So, in Japan, the girls' restroom is blue, and the boys' restroom is pink!
It would've been so embarrassing if I hadn't noticed!
Why are these two girls in here?
Halt! I am not a girl—
Come with me, Kinoshita!
Thou art mistaken!
Why did thee drag me out here?
What were you doing in the men's restroom?
What is it? What art thee enraged about?
I am just a man, going about his business—
Hark! Shimada!
I still didn't understand Japan very well.
Still, it's only my first day.
I'll surely learn in the coming days.
Meanwhile, I'll be patient and try to get along—
I... can see!
Nope. I don't get Japan at all.
So how was school?
Is something wrong?
No, everything's fine.
There are a lot of unique and unusual people in my class.
They really are unique.
Really? I'm glad you're enjoying it!
I hope you make lots of friends, Sis!
M-Me too!
Friends, huh?
Question 8
Translate the following English
sentence into Japanese.
Shimada
Minami's
answer:
"Music brings
joy to men
and enriches
their heart."
I think this
sentence is i
German, not
in English.
Sakamoto Yuuji's answer:
The sentence is in German,
not English, so I don't know the
answer.
Teacher's comment:
I'm really sorry. I accidentally put the wrong
question in the test. Shimada did give the
right answer, but since it was my fault, I'll
award full marks for this question to every—
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
(Invisible ink)
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
(Invisible to fools)
Teacher's comment:
... but I'll make an exception for
you two. Zero points.
A week has passed since then.
Classes have started for real now.
I still haven't really gotten used to Japanese,
so wrapping my head around Modern Japanese was rather difficult,
and the language in the classics read like pure gibberish.
Okay, Yoshii.
In this case, what's the conjugated form of haberi ?
I know.
It's hannari.
My lecture is on classic conjugation, but your answer is in the Kyoto dialect.
I like how you gave me the answer to the next lesson in two days.
Huh? W-What?
Go over this
part carefully
Well then, review what we covered today for the next class.
Thank God it's over.
I almost died of boredom.
Hey, Shimada, where are you going?
Why do you ask?
Ich gehe nach home.
Huh? What a sea?
I'm going home!
Oh, I get it. "I'm going home."
Sorry, I couldn't really understand that.
You just came back from abroad, so I thought you were speaking in a foreign language.
I only knew a little Japanese, so I couldn't understand his fast speech.
I really tried to make sense of it, but my mind just couldn't keep up and went pop like a flat tire.
I want to go home too, but we still have homeroom.
Huh?
What's so funny?
Is it so funny that I can't speak Japanese?
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie?
I think he said, "What clubs were you in when you is in junior high, Minami?"
but why is he asking that all of a sudden?
His own grammar is wrong in the first place!
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie?
Umm... Tunevoudrais...
I don't understand!
What should I do?
Why can't they understand me?
I'm trying so hard.
I'm home.
Ah!
Welcome home, Sis!
Maybe they hate me?
How was school?
It was a lot of fun.
Maybe I shouldn't be here.
Did you make any friends?
Yes. I made a ton of wonderful friends!
Really?
Maybe I...
Yes. Japan really is a great country.
That's great!
That day, I fit into the class as badly as ever.
I couldn't make friends because I couldn't understand Japanese,
so no one would even talk to me.
It was a vicious cycle.
It's because I messed up my first impression on the first day of school...
when I wrote down the wrong characters for my name.
Shimada Minami
Huh?
I'm sure I never corrected this,
so why?
Hey, Akihisa!
Some guys from Agebono Junior High want to play basketball with the stakes being candy at the student shop.
Wanna play?
Totally!
I'm out of money for food for this month.
I'll help.
I'd like to participate too. It sounds fun.
When did they become such good pals?
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie?
What's with this guy?
I have no idea what he's saying again.
Doesn't he know I don't understand Japanese!
What's with the "Monamie" anyway?
My name's Minami, not Monamie!
You don't even remember my name!
Don't act so familiar!
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie?
Tune—
Don't talk to me, you idiot!
Huh? Dontok tumi?
"I'm a man. What about you?"
I'm a guy, of course.
What? You're a man, Shimada?
Won't even English get through to him?
She said you're annoying as hell.
Really?
You've got some nerve calling an angry girl a man.
That's not it, Shimada!
I didn't think you were a man just because your chest is so flat—
She's breaking my elbow!!
I don't understand Japanese, but I somehow heard him call my chest flat crystal clearly.
This sucks.
This sucks so much.
I wish I had never come to Japan.
Hey, Shimada.
We've only just met, so I don't really know for sure...
but I think that idiot is a pretty interesting guy.
I...diot?
Go look up what he was saying.
Oh, it means "idiot."
I already know he's an idiot.
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie.
What the hell does that mean?
I bet he was making fun of me.
I'll look up what he said and completely embarrass him.
Tunevoudraispas... Tunevoudraispas... Tunevoudraispas...
I can't find any words that fit.
What did he say?
Was it even correct Japanese?
He sure didn't get my name right.
I'm Minami, not Monamie!
Mon amie?
Mon amie
Why are they calling my name?
That's not it, sweetie.
They're saying "mon amie", not "Minami".
There it is.
Minami, 3 years old, in France
France.
Tunevoudraispasdevenir monamie.
It's not Japanese.
It's not German either.
He mixed it up and translated it into French.
He's really a complete idiot.
The library doesn't have a German-to-French dictionary.
I'll have to translate it to English first, and from there to German.
I don't know the French spellings, so I have no clue whether I'm transcribing the sounds correctly.
But...
Tu ne voudrais pas means "Wouldn't you" in English.
Devenir means "become".
Monamie is mon amie, "my friend".
If you put it together,
Won't you be my friend?
I'm sure he looked it up just like I did.
Even though it was an unknown language of a foreign country...
Even though he has trouble with the literature of his own country...
Yoshii
Akihisa
He's an idiot, and yet...
A damn idiot...
Even though he's such an idiot...
Won't you be my friend?
Won't you?
Good morning, Yoshii!
Yeah. Good morning, Shimada.
Huh? What's up, Shimada?
Hey, Yoshii.
I...
"What a shit"?
I'm sorry. Have I done something to offend you again?
No, no. I...
Hey, Yoshii.
I...
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem.
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby.
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you.
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N.
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go.
I've fallen in love.
I don't want any doubts in my heart.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Sparkling, glittering.
The right answer is pop!
Question 9
Answer the
following question:
What is it called
when a group
attempts to
influence the
government's
decisions by
influencing
politicians?
Himeji Mizuki's answer
Lobbying.
Teacher's comment:
That's correct.
Well done, Himeji.
It's called lobbying because
of the lobbies
where members of
congress meet with
the public.
Shimada Minami's answer
A "mixer"?
Teacher's comment:
What's being mixed?
Next time
Question 9.
What is it called when an organization attempts to influence the government's decisions by bribing politicians?
A "mixer"?
What's being mixed?
Next time: Me, romance, and the art of negotiation!
Me, romance, and the art of negotiation
This will be on the test.