We're finally back...
Hey, Waver.
Where are you looking? Over here, over here.
G-Grandpa!
What are you doing?
Does it matter?
You come up here too.
Let's talk for a while.
Talk?
Why do we have to talk on the roof?
Grandpa, can it wait?
Oh, don't be like that.
He really likes you, boy.
Listen, he's just under my spell-
Well, go up anyway.
It looks like the old man has something important to tell you.
I'll wander about and patrol, so don't worry.
No need to hold back.
It's not that I'm holding back...
Utw
Presents
Will one last miracle come to pass?
あと一度だけ奇跡は起こるだろう
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
優しい声で描く歪んだ未来
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
もう誰も泣かない世界の為に
Mou dare mo nakanai sekai no tame ni
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
紅く汚された空の何処にも
Akaku kegasareta sora no doko ni mo
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
届かず消える叫びと祈り
Todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
慰めは捨てて行ける
Nagusame wa sutete yukeru
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
綺麗な月の光が始まりへと沈み行く
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga hajimari e to shizumiyuku
Into the distance
その彼方へ
Sono kanata e
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
閉ざされてく瞳でまだ遠くへ手を伸ばす
Tozasareteku hitomi de mada tooku e te wo nobasu
I believe in your sorrow
君の嘆きを 信じて
Kimi no nageki wo shinjite
This is the best place to get some sunlight early in the morning.
Sit down.
Here, I've prepared some coffee.
It'll warm you up.
Grandpa, how long have you been up here?
When I woke up this morning, you weren't back yet.
So I thought I'd watch the sky while
waiting for my grandson to come home.
When you were little, we used to
come up here and stargaze all the time.
Do you remember?
Yeah, I do.
When Martha and I settled in Japan,
we decided to build our house on higher ground in Miyama with a skylight we could use to access the roof.
It's always been our dream to sit out here on our
beloved roof with our grandchildren to watch the stars.
We never thought we'd have the chance, though.
Our real grandchildren never once came out here.
Whenever I watched the stars, I was always alone.
Hey, Waver.
You're not our grandson, are you?
It's strange how Martha and I believed you were.
You were a little too nice to be our grandson.
You're not mad?
Well, maybe I should be angry.
But Martha's been really happy lately.
I wouldn't have imagined it before.
Really, I'm grateful to you two.
At any rate, it doesn't look like you're
staying here because you want to do us harm.
In fact, what do you think?
If possible, I'd like this to continue for a while longer.
I'm sorry...
But I can't promise that.
I can't even guarantee I'll make it back here safely.
So you two are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I don't know how important what you're doing is to you.
But when you look back after a long life,
you'll realize there's nothing really worth risking your life for.
It's been about forty hours since I last slept.
To win the war and summon the Grail, one must
perform the ritual at one of the four Fuyuki ley line areas.
At two of them, the church and the Tohsaka residence,
Kotomine Kirei was nowhere to be found.
Which leaves the other two.
Here, at Mt. Enzou, or the Fuyuki City Hall.
This is the more likely place,
considering their respective spiritualities.
Even if he chooses the City Hall, I can launch a frontal assault there.
If Maiya were still alive, I would've sent her to secure it.
Once again, I'm alone.
Come to think of it, I didn't count her in.
Since last night, I've been searching the entire city for Irisviel.
But I have found nothing.
I am deeply sorry.
Well then. If you need me, use a Command Spell to summon me like you did before.
Woman.
Can you hear me, woman?
Kotomine... Kirei.
This is where Caster's Master once hid.
Emiya Kiritsugu never managed to find it.
Soon, the Grail War will come to its conclusion.
It's likely that I'll be the one to realize the wish of the Einzberns.
Are you so unhappy that it would be me?
I would entrust the Grail to only one man.
And that person isn't you, Executor.
Emiya Kiritsugu has already seen right through you.
He recognizes you as his greatest enemy.
Prepare yourself.
That's good news to me.
Emiya Kiritsugu is exactly as I had imagined, after all.
How laughable.
You couldn't be more different from him.
What?
While Kiritsugu can see through you, the reverse is impossible.
You have none of the things he carries in his heart.
Why are you appraising me?
I admit it.
I am an empty man.
However...
How do he and I differ?
All these years, he's thrown himself into battles with no conceivable gain.
He simply slaughtered over and over again.
His utter recklessness, the wasted effort!
If he isn't lost, then what is he?!
Answer me.
What does Emiya Kiritsugu want from the Holy Grail?
What prayer would he ask of the wish-granting device?
Very well.
I'll tell you.
Emiya Kiritsugu's wish...
He wishes for humanity's salvation,
the elimination of war and bloodshed.
For eternal peace on Earth.
What was that?
You can't possibly understand.
That's the difference between him and you.
He has faith, and you don't.
Conflict is humanity's primal instinct.
Eliminating it would mean eliminating humanity itself.
It doesn't even work as an ideal.
It's practically a childish joke!
That's why he has no choice but to hope for a miracle.
Many times, he's been forced to
sacrifice his loved ones for his beliefs.
Yes...
He is too kind to chase ideals.
He can't help but love others, despite knowing he'll eventually lose them...
I understand.
I understand very well.
So that's Emiya Kiritsugu.
I can finally see...
...my reason to fight.
Emiya Kiritsugu.
I shall smash your ideals, and the Holy Grail, into smithereens right in front of you.
Oh, you're awake, boy?
I told you to wake me up when night had fallen.
Why didn't you do that?
Sorry, sorry.
But I thought it might be a good idea to take
more time than usual with preparations tonight.
Why?
Well, it's just a feeling,
but I think everything will reach its conclusion tonight.
Right.
The night air seems too still.
Does that mean only a few participants remain?
It means there will only be the strong from now on.
Wh-What was that?
That's a strange mana surge.
I've experienced something similar before.
That pattern...
What?
Is it some sort of code?
Four and seven, in different colors.
"Victory" and "success".
Does the sending up of that signal mean the Grail War is over?
No.
It's in a different direction from the church.
So it wasn't the Church that sent the message?
In essence, someone is getting ahead of himself and declaring victory.
He's inviting anyone who objects to come get him.
It's a challenge.
Tonight will likely be the final battle!
I see.
This is it, then.
That's right!
And now that our battlefield is known, I must go forth in a way that will not shame the Rider class!
Come forth, my beloved steed!
Now, boy.
The ride won't be as smooth as going by chariot... hmm?
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
From this point, only the strong can continue, right?
My Servant.
By my Command Spell, I, Waver Velvet, order you.
Rider, fight until you gain victory.
And by another Command Spell, I order you.
Rider, win the Holy Grail.
And by yet another Command Spell, I order you.
Rider, conquer the world.
I won't accept failure.
Well, I'm no longer your Master or anything now.
Go.
Go wherever.
You're no longer...
Sure, I'll be on my way.
After giving me those annoying orders, surely you must be prepared to see them to the end.
You idiot, you idiot!
Listen!
I have no Command Spells!
I quit being your Master!
Why would you still take me with you?
I...
Master or not, you are my friend.
A-Are you...
Are you sure I'm worthy enough?
I can stay by your side?
What are you talking about? You've been through so many battles with me.
Idiot.
Up until now, have you not faced the same enemies as I have?
That makes you my friend!
So hold your chest high, and consider yourself...
...my equal.
All right.
I shall begin by answering your first command.
Boy, open your eyes and watch to the end!
Yeah, do it!
Right before my eyes!
In order to gain the initiative in battle,
he chose the place least suited to the ritual.
In other words, his plan is not to secure the Grail,
but to use it as bait to kill me and the other Masters.
That simplifies things.
If that's the best he could come up with, I'll just quickly eliminate him.
Kotomine Kirei...
You're looking particularly ferocious tonight, Kirei.
Now, what will you do?
Do you want me to wait here?
If your powers were released at close range, they could endanger the ceremony.
If you want to fight at full strength, go out and meet them.
Very well.
But what if this place comes under attack while I'm away?
I'll use a Command Spell to save myself. Is that permissible?
I shall allow it.
However, I can't guarantee the Grail's safety.
I won't be holding back tonight.
That would be the worst outcome,
but if that ensues, it would be fate.
Kirei.
You seem to have found your reason to fight,
but do you still have no prayer to ask of the Grail?
I can't think of anything I'd want.
If I had to answer, it'd be that nothing will interfere with this coming fight.
Well, well.
As I suspected, the only recourse is to let the Grail reveal what you hide within your heart.
Oh.
If Saber appears here before I return,
have Berserker entertain her for a while.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber, what happened to
the doll she was trying so hard to protect?
Doesn't the Grail vessel reside within her?
I killed her.
I couldn't find a reason to keep her alive.
Are you crying, Mommy?
Mommy, I had a really scary dream.
I dreamed that I became a cup...
...and seven really big lumps appeared inside me...
It's okay... it's okay.
I won't let that happen.
That will never happen to you, Ilya.
I'm sure the chains of fate will release you.
Is this place...
...inside the Grail?
That can't be!
Then...
If I'm in here...
...who am I?
I see.
This is inside the Holy Grail.
The omnipotent wishing device that will dispel all the world's sorrows and erase all suffering.
I'll have the power to make that happen.
The end is almost at hand.
Episode 22
All the World's Evil
Doushite sora wa konnani aokute
どうして空はこんなに青くて
Why is the sky so blue?
Nanimo kanashimi wo shiranu you ni
何も悲しみを知らぬように
As if oblivious to sadness
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita e to kuzureochiru
いつも躊躇わず明日へと崩れ落ちる
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuru no ne
命は足りないまま生まれてくるのね
I suppose we are born with our lives short
Kakeochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
かけおちた心にあなたが触れて
You have touched my torn heart
Futari de yuku mirai wa kegare no nai tsuyosa de
二人で行く未来は穢れのない強さで
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
空は高く 風は歌う
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Yume wo miteta yorokobi e to
夢を見てた喜びへと
Men will one day come to realize
Hito wa itsuka tadoritsukeru
人はいつか辿り着ける
The joy of chasing after a dream
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
子供の瞳であなたは信じた
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
Soba ni iru yo
そばにいるよ
I'll be right beside you
Kooritsuita mori wo nukete
凍りついた森を抜けて
As we pass through the frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni mayowanu you ni
その瞳が世界の嘆きに迷わぬように
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
Our enemy is the mighty King of Heroes.
A worthy opponent!
Let us show him our path of conquest!
King of Conquerors, you will learn of
the conclusion to your endless dream.
I'll personally show you how things are.
Next Episode
The Sea at the World's Edge