Toru.
Run-chan! Jeez...
What is it?
Thank you, Toru.
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
BIRTHDAYS
Push
Button
to Cross
at Night
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Another cold day today, huh?
Can't it be spring already?
Speaking of, isn't Toru's birthday coming up?
Yeah, that's right.
So, will you have a party?
No, that's fine.
Come on, don't be shy.
Look forward to your present this year, okay?
"Look forward" to it?
Don't tell me it'll be one of THOSE!
What was that thing anyway?
Those school uniforms...
Yeah, they're probably in elementary school.
There's a graduation ceremony today.
Oh, really?
Come the new year, those kids will be
taking entrance exams, right?
And we'll be a year older, huh?
Entrance exams...
Entrance exams?
Brings back memories, doesn't it, Toru?
Yeah.
NIKOU
Ah, I have to hurry and come up
with a second choice.
So you already have a first choice?
Yeah. With my grades, they think this is
the closest to being at my level.
What will you do for high school, Toru?
I guess you haven't decided yet,
being a second-year.
I want to try for the same place.
For Nikou? You can go to a better school, right?
You have good grades.
No.
I'll go wherever YOU go.
Here.
Thank you.
Well? Have you decided on your high school?
Yeah, kind of.
What about Nikou?
Well, why not? It's well regarded.
And they use a grade curve there, don't they?
Yeah.
Oh. And Toru said she'd go to
the high school that I go to.
Go to a better school.
B-but...
A better one will make things easier for you later.
You just said Nikou would be good-
I've changed my mind!
But even if I tried, I know how it'll turn out.
The grage curfe won' be enoush.
That's right.
NOW, that is.
W-wait! Who are you calling?
A cram school.
No!
Fine. I get it.
Forcing you to do it wouldn't change anything.
So!
What about all-you-can-eat Kobe beef?
Okay! I'll try!
Run-chan, you went for a high-tier school?
Yeah, I guess.
I decided to after talking with my mom.
So you're doing cram school and got a tutor?
You're so determined!
My tutor is someone you know, Hira-chan.
There.
Introducing!
Miss Toru!
Pleased to meet you.
But Toru-chan doesn't...
Yes, that's true, but glasses are a must.
After all, she's a teacher.
I'm not talking about her glasses...
Very well. Let's begin studying.
We'll start with something simple.
For now, remember this. All of it.
It's basic. Simple memorization.
I-It's so much...
Jenga!
The answer there is "A"!
Multiple-choice questions are tricky. Be careful!
What's this?
What's this voice in my head
that's talking to me?!
My hand! It's like it's not mine,
writing the answer!
What's going on?!
Huh?
A dream?
Ah! The letters!
Wait!
I won't be able to solve the problem!
Huh?
Run-chan. Wake up.
A dream?
Yup.
Push
Button
to Cross
at Night
ESENAPAJ
Math
Please do the following for the
double-underlined sections below:
complete
Mastery
You've brought your grades up.
High School-Entrance Series
MATH
I read study guides every minute I'm awake!
Oh.
All the study guides have gotten dog-eared...
Ah, sorry. I dropped them in the bathtub.
You dropped them ALL in?!
I'll buy you new ones.
Okay, here I go!
Run-chan, do your best!
Aoigaoka
High School
Entrance
Exam Site
Okay, well...
When the bell rings, open your
test booklets and begin.
Here goes!
Begin!
Gotta use another pencil...
She's sabotagin' me?
Tokyo is scary!
Okay, I'll collect your answer sheets.
Um...
I'm sorry. Did my pencil lead fly at you?
Nah, it's fine.
I'm glad!
So it wasn't a sabotage.
Oh, you came from Kansai today
just for the test?
Yeah. I'll be movin' here this spring. So I-
Ah! Speaking of Kansai...
It's my good-luck charm for today!
Like, the god of cows or something?
I did it! There it is! It's there!
Look, that's my number!
I passed thanks to YOU, Toru!
No. It's because of your hard work.
Congratulations.
So, that's how it went.
Somehow, I passed the test.
Run, you worked hard!
I'd write vocab on my hands
so I wouldn't forget them.
Ah. I've written stuff on my hands
so I won't forget them, too.
But if you did that for the test,
you'd be cheating, huh?
Of course I washed them for the test!
Revolution
Renaissance
But it had become a habit and
I'd written all over my body,
MOUNTAIN RANGE
Nagasaki
But it had become a habit and
I'd written all over my body,
so getting it all off was hard work!
Good morning.
They announce the results today, right?
Aren't they already posting on the signboards?
Yeah...
I'll go later.
You don't seem very concerned.
Those Who
Passed
rabble
You don't seem very concerned.
Those Who
Passed
rabble
Those Who
Passed
rabble
I won't be able to see anyway...
Those Who
Passed
rabble
Coming!
I have a present for you today, Toru!
Here. It's almost your birthday, right?
Cake?
Cake!
They call that the three-second rule, right?
Um, that was completely upside-down.
Fooled ya!
Ta-daa! THIS is the real one.
Did I get you?
I heard that giving something
after you've depressed someone
will make them even happier!
And I wanted you to be happy!
Who did you hear that from?
I'll hold the cake.
No, I won't drop it again!
It's fine.
But I can't make you carry something.
IT'S FINE.
Toru, are you angry?
You're gonna be 16 already, aren't you?
You've gotten big.
You used to be so small, though!
You'd be on all fours, chasing after me...
And you'd cry if you weren't always
holding some candy. That was so cute.
Run-chan...
What are you talking about?
About a dream I had the other day.
THEY MET WHILE IN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
A dream?
Look, you've gotten THIS tall.
You're still small, though.
I'll always
be small
Look, you've gotten THIS tall.
You're still small, though.
Don't treat me like a child.
I found a gray hair!
You brought cake to school?
That's brave of you.
There's enough for everyone,
so let's eat at lunch.
Where will you put it till lunch?
Oh, that's right! They have to be kept cold, huh?
We don't have one, do we?
What if we put it in the
coldest part of the school?
The bathroom, huh?
Ulp...
YOU'RE gonna be eating some, too.
So it's almost Toru's birthday, huh?
Congratulations.
Thanks
a lot
What will you do on your actual birthday?
Not to worry! I've got a present for her
on her real birthday!
Huh. I'll give you that book
you wanted the other day.
Thank you.
I...
A cup.
A cup?
What's
with that
ruler?
A cup?
What's
with that
ruler?
What kind?
An E cup.
Come on, let's eat that cake. Before it goes bad.
Yeah, you're right.
Nice!
They look delicious.
Heart-Pounding Game!
Actually, one of these cakes has wasabi in it!
Can't you just celebrate normally?
One of them is clearly green.
That's totally obvious!
I'll let Yuko play the starring role.
Here.
After all, you're from Kansai.
Sure am jealous.
SPICY...
Well, shall we eat?
Do not be shocked!
The cake with wasabi in it...
Was one of two-!
Run-chan!
It sure is cute. This cake.
Oh. A celebratory pic, huh?
N-nice.
We should all take one together.
Okay.
Yuko. You're blurry.
Huh?!
I didn't move!
Maybe you were twitching.
Because
of the
wasabi?
Maybe you were twitching.
Let's take another!
Okay, everyone do like Yuko.
Just take it normally!
Ah, I moved! One more time!
Okay, everyone do like Yuko again. One, two...
Ah, I moved again!
Jeez!
Okay, continuing from yesterday...
Yesterday, we used covered area principle
to determine the volume
and surface area of a sphere.
Volume V was 4/3 pi R3, and
surface area S was 4 pi R2, yes?
Torun?
Volume V was 4/3 pi R3, and
surface area S was 4 pi R2, yes?
Cake! Th-this is... Um, um, um!
Following problem No. 51 in your textbooks,
let's try using a sphere like the one shown,
where diameter equals height, comparing the
ratio of volume and surface area of a cylinder,
circular cone and sphere
in relation to basal diameter.
Torun! TORUN!
circular cone and sphere
in relation to basal diameter.
Congratulations.
Here->
Okay, Yutaka-san. Solve the problem.
HUH?!
Here! Look!
What's that?
A picture from when I was studying for exams!
Two years ago, huh?
You're eating cake.
Yeah. That was Toru's birthday.
Why are you making her feed you?
Such is the life of a test-taker!
Don't interrupt me, Toru!
Just kidding!
Here! Happy birthday, Toru!
But you didn't forget her present, huh?
Yeah. That's the main thing. Also...
Look.
What's this?
This is Toru's birthday last year.
This time, Toru was the test-taker, huh?
That's right.
Toru, Good Luck
Toru said I didn't have to,
since she was studying for exams,
Toru, Good Luck
but I wanted to get her cake and a present.
Say "Aah."
Weren't you a distraction?
Not at all! Right, Toru?
Toru worked hard too, huh?
And...
Ta-daa! Here's THIS year's
commemorative photo!
Hey, what's with that photo?!
I just got it from Toru.
Jeez, erase that thing!
Hey! I swear.
No way.
Give me that phone! I'll erase it myself.
Hey! I swear.
Let's go, Toru.
No!
Please!
Hey!
Kyoushitsu kara koboreru kaiwa no aida o surinukete
I slip past while conversation spills out from the classroom
Hitorikiri de aruku rouka wa sukoshi samishii
The hallway I walk down all alone is a little lonely
Tanoshii jikan wa itsudemo
Because the fun times always
Hayaku sugite iku kara
Go by so quickly
Omoide no album no page wa mugen nan da ne
The pages in the album of memories are endless, aren't they?
Kitto kitto kitto
For sure, for sure, for sure
Zutto zutto zutto
Forever, forever, forever
Kienai egao no kioku
These memories of smiling faces won't fade
Say, Toru, let's all eat cake next year too, okay?
Kienai egao no kioku
These memories of smiling faces won't fade
Say, Toru, let's all eat cake next year too, okay?
Motto motto motto
More, more, more
But don't do the wasabi cake!
Motto motto motto
More, more, more
But don't do the wasabi cake!
Kyou mo ashita mo asatte mo
Today and tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
Hey now!
Kyou mo ashita mo asatte mo
Today and tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
Hey now!
Ippai fuyashite ikou ne
Let's make lots of them
Next year, we'll be taking entrance exams.
Ippai fuyashite ikou ne
Let's make lots of them
C'mon, Nagi! Don't say scary stuff like that!
Ippai fuyashite ikou ne
Let's make lots of them
What are you talking about? It's the truth.
Oh. Next year, we'll be taking exams.
100M
To Station
Taking exams...
Well, I'm going this way today.
Bye-bye!
It's gone by so fast, huh?
I was thinking about how you'd
just entered our school,
but you'll already be a second-year soon.
Yeah.
Then Run will be a third-year...
Toru, Good Luck
Toru.
What's the matter?
Nothing at all.
Really?
Yeah.
By the way, Run-chan...
Hm?
I'm late in asking, but why did you
change to THIS high school?
Mm, why do you think?
Tell me.
It's. A. Secret.
Whaat?
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!
Someone from outer space?
Someone from outer space!
Come to correct the wrongs of
present-day Earth?!
That would be someone from the FUTURE.
Pithecanthropus Erectus!
Currently, it's Homo Erectus.
Wait, that's primitive man!
The only one who can call out
my air-headedness is YOU, Miporin!
Sort
of
The only one who can call out
my air-headedness is YOU, Miporin!
Grind Grind
The only one who can call out
my air-headedness is YOU, Miporin!
That doesn't make me happy at all.
Next
Episode!
THE ALIEN
Next time, on A-Channel: "The Alien"
Next
Episode!
THE ALIEN
They were wiped out by a
legendary three-headed dragon.
Note: Reference to King Ghidorah from the Godzilla films,
who destroyed Venus.
They were wiped out by a
legendary three-headed dragon.
Note: Reference to King Ghidorah from the Godzilla films,
who destroyed Venus.
That's someone from Venus!