Professor is written as ?? in Japanese, pronounced kyoujyu. Jyusan sounds like Jyu-san - Jyu plus the honorific -san.
Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Rika-chama
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Ready to advance...
Forward!
Advancing.
Enemy sighted.
Prepare to fire main cannon!
Distance 800.
Loader, prepare high explosive projectiles!
R-Right!
Loading complete!
Ready...
Fire!
Boom!
Target hit!
Good.  Notify those behind us.
One enemy unit destroyed.  Fall in!
Roger!
"One enemy unit destroyed," huh?
Bravo.
We still have a ways to go!
Phylicia, it's Krause.
Oh my... then shall we have some tea?
Good work, everyone!
Shuko's really healthy now, isn't she?
Even though her wounds are all healed, she still hangs around here.
Well, this place is just wonderful, isn't it?
Hey!
It's so hot and yet she's so energetic...
Yeah...
It's so...
This is from Headquarters.
Here's the receipt.
Here you are.
And here are the personal correspondences.
Kana-chan!
Yes?
Yes, yes, yes?
This one's addressed to you.
Thank you!
Press...!
It's from Momma!
There's one for you too, Noel-chan.
From the usual professor.
"Professor"?
Yeah.
His family name is Kyou, his given name, Jyusan.
A very common full name in the Sept Province.
Wow!  So it's Jyusan-san?
That's amazing for you to have friends from so far away!
Sorry.
Huh?
A joke.
Oh, you... Noel-chan!  I believed you!
Take Krause a present.
Okay!
Rio?
The u-s-u-a-l!
Pitch it.
Aww...
So?  What did Headquarters have to say?
Excuse me!
What's the matter, Kureha?
M-Major Krause, sir... here!
This year's, huh?
Yes!
U-Um, t-thank you so much for all you do!
Not worth mentioning.  It's my job.
Major?
Here you are.
Oh?
Roger.  I'll take care of everything while you're away.
"Away"?
Good luck to you, Private Second Class.
T-Thank you.
Everyone, we're going on an outing tomorrow.
Yay!
An outing!
Noel-chan, isn't this great?  Aren't you excited?
"An outing"?  Phylicia...
Although I'm calling it an outing, simply walking around wouldn't be fun, so we'll be playing a little game!
"A game"?
You recall that on the southern border of Seize, that is, where it borders No-Man's Land,
there stands some observation equipment from the old age, right?
Among those, three units are due for their regular maintenance check.
I would like you all to take the outing as an opportunity to stop by and take a look at them.
That's...
This is totally a mission, isn't it?!
Oh no, an outing!  Just an outing!
I mean, even if they were broken, there'd be nothing we could do about it!
Noctour-type observation equipment has completely become a black box now.
Impossible to disassemble.
And so it's an outing!
So this is what he meant by "good luck to you," huh?
However, it'd be a waste to just walk around normally.
As such, I'll have each of you...
carry one of those!
You're so weak.
Listen, the only way to deal with these is to put your weight forward squarely and...
Wow, wow!
I... I can't move.
Fail.
Like you can talk!
You really are all such good children to follow everything we've told you up til now, aren't you?
Listen up!
When you need to carry heavy supplies like this, first, you fall back.
Then... once you've gotten the entire weight of the pack on your back...
How uncool...
Shut your mouths...
and do it!
Y-Yes!
Good!
Now Phylicia and I will go on ahead to the goal point marked on your maps and wait for you guys.
If you somehow reach a point where you just can't go on, sound your trumpet.
So that we'll come and search—
for you!
And also, wild beasts have been known to appear on this mountain.
If you encounter one, rely on yourselves.
I permit the usage of explosives.
Got it?
All right then, have fun, okay?
All troops... right face!
Right face!
Forward... march!
March!
Next up...
Right, so I'll leave the rest to you, all right?
Roger that.
Heavy...
Heavy, heavy, it's so heavy!
Kureha-chan, stop saying that.
The more you say it, the heavier it gets.
Noel, how much further?
Noel!
Hey!  Kanata!
Found one!
Woohoo!
Amazing...
Operational.  Nothing out of order.
What's with that?  We found that one easily enough.
Let's keep this up!
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Nothing, really.  It's just that...
when I think about how it's been here for so long all by itself, protecting the city for us...
All right then. Where's the next one, Noel?
Umm...
Seeing how we're here right now...
On that mountain.
"T-T-That mountain"?
Someone, please, do something about these packs!
Heavy.
The captain and Rio-sempai must hate me after all!
That must be it.  That's why they've made me—
Heavy.
Hey, say something, Kanata!
It's not like you to be so quiet!
Hey, come on!
Loud.
What the hell?!
I can hear.
What?
I can hear it.
I can hear it!
Hey, wait, Kanata!
What's the matter with her?
She broke?
Wow, how wonderful!
It's so refreshing, isn't it?  And pretty!
Break time!  No matter what anyone says, we're taking a break!
I've decided!
I'm first!
Not fair...
Tastes good!
Now you've done it!
Take that!
Once in a lifetime chance.
Noel, you!
Take that!
It's a fish!
Come look, Kureha-chan!
It's amazing, isn't it?  Isn't this so much fun?!
Yeah!  Wait— no!
You really lack any sense of urgency.
But it's an outing after all!  We can't not have fun!
Have you forgotten those ridiculously heavy packs?
This is training!
But Phylicia-san said...
Oh, cut it out and quit being thick!
That woman's black.
Pitch black!
Huh?
But she has blonde hair and white skin, and she's wonderful.
That's not what I'm talking about...
Kureha doesn't get it.
Get what?
Phylicia's good here.
Right?
No, incorrect!
You guys are completely looking at the wrong things!
Someone do something about this goody-goody combo!
Time for food, time for food!
We've gotten completely soaked, haven't we?
We'll dry off quickly though, with this weather.
What happened here?!
Provisions... gone.
Could it have been a wild boar?
Back home in the countryside, they often tore apart the fields.
But since food is plentiful in the summer time, they normally don't come out now...
The problem is bigger.
What?
Compass is missing.
What?!
I wonder if it was okay... to leave our packs behind like that.
Seeing how things have turned out like this, reaching our goal is now our first priority!
Are we going in the right direction?
The first apparatus was here.
The river is here.
We've come upon the mountain with the second apparatus at its peak.
So for now, if we just climb upwards, it should be fine.
Okay!  No matter what happens, we'll—
You're hungry, aren't you?
Is there anything edible or...
Found something!
Mountain peaches!
Are those... edible?
Yup!  They're sweet, a little sour, and delicious!
That was like a chord, wasn't it?
But climbing up there is impossible, isn't it?  It's dangerous!
Is it?
We should hurry forward.
They say that Major Krause crossed a desert in a tank, without food or water for three days,
in order to take out an enemy fortress!
We should be just fine!
Really?
Have you never heard about it?
He's called the Desert Wolf.  He's an amazing person!
Wow... so Krause-san is...?
Like I said, we have to keep moving!
Ah, the mountain peaches!
No complaints!
Second one, sighted!
A wild boar?!
Where is that last one?
It's gotten pretty dark, hasn't it?
Because we've had to check the directions one by one, every time, you know?
Is this really the right way?
Probably.
What do you mean, "probably"?!
Without a compass, there's no 100% certainty.
Then what?  Do you mean to say that despite everything we've come all this way for nothing?
I didn't say that.
And anyway, if that compass is so important, you should keep it on your person!
Come on now, don't fight in a place like this.
At any rate, you shouldn't have been playing all carefree like that at the river.
Huh?
That's right!
You have no sense of urgency!
With your "outing, outing" nonsense!
You're always going around like a ditz, spacing out all the time!
We're in this mess 'cause of stuff like that!
Don't you get it?
Found it!
Yay!
Hey, wait up!  Kanata!
Man... I guess things will turn out fine somehow.
Goal!
We did it!  We did it, Kureha-chan!
I got it.  I got it already, so let go of me!
Painful...
Look.
No-Man's Land.
This is the edge of the world inhabited by people.
Good work.
We apologize, Captain!  We couldn't carry out our mission.
What mission?
Huh?  I mean...
I said this was an outing, didn't I?
But!
I just wanted to have all of you see these.
These are the signatures of our elders.
All of the bastion maidens have come here at least once.
And each saw this scene...
the edge of this world.
That's history... right?
That's right.
Could you all possibly walk a little more?
There's one more thing that our predecessors have left for us.
You're late!
Rio... -sempai?
What happened?
Here!
Mountain peaches!
Refreshing.
So, did you win?
Don't ask.
Still... it was worth the effort.
Next time, Kanata's Day Off: Hairdressing!