"11 Years Ago・(History)"
It smells nice. You smell it, too!
Sniff, sniff.
Okay, all set.
Everybody smile pretty!
Say cheese!
We hated you from the beginning--
and loved you from the beginning, too.
And so we wanted to
become true friends with you.
I want to cross the wall...
...and have you all to myself.
Yurikumaaaaaaaaa!
Yurikuma Arashi!
"I WANT TO HAVE YOU ALL TO MYSELF"
Viens avec moi
Church chimes echo in the distance
Offer up a prayer and betray today
Wander in a dark forest, then become
the morning moon at the Wall of Severance
I won't join the Invisible Storm
Once I've made you stickier
with sweet, thin honey
Please, approve me, I'll be a good girl
Picture-book pages dancing on
the breeze shake up shadowy memories
Always
I'll be waiting you-know-where,
in an empty world
Even if everything falls apart
Even if you have to gracefully writhe,
even if you have to bend space-time
Find me
Flower petals will slowly
enfold us on a starry night
Come on...
J'ai besoin de toi
Delicious smell.
Slurp.
Kureha, good morning, growl.
Hmm?
Ginko! Good morning.
Growl.
Lick!
Kureha, you're close to me...
What are you doing?
Hmm?
Why are you in my house?!
I moved in, growl.
What?!
Growl! All finished moving!
What?
What?!
We're your...
...new neighbors!
New-neighbor new-dles!
We're your...
...new neighbors!
New-neighbor new-dles!
Get... Get...
Get out!
It's not acceptable to move in
without asking! I want you out today.
Growl. But Kure-chin, you ate your noodles!
Th-That isn't the issue here!
Look, it's that girl.
The one who's bad luck to all her friends?
It's worse than bad luck! Girls are
going missing--and only from her class!
There you have it.
Getting close to me is bad luck.
It's true. You'll get caught
up in the Invisible Storm.
The Invisible Storm...
Yes. If you make friends with me,
you'll be excluded. It's the law of this herd.
Now that you get it, just leave me alone.
Growl! You're the one who doesn't get it!
I told you, Ginko and I came
here to make friends with you!
We'll protect Kureha from the Invisible Storm.
We won't back down on love, growl.
I'm not lying! There was a bear
masquerading as human!
That's impossible.
Please believe me.
Yurizono really did turn into a bear!
Yurizono ate Sumika--I mean, Izumino.
She told me so herself!
So I...
I looked right at her and...
Kureha.
That's enough of that.
But Teacher!
You poor thing. The shock was too
much for you, and you hallucinated.
No! It was--
I won't tell you to do it right away,
but eventually you'll need to accept reality.
Oh, that's right--next Sunday
is your birthday, isn't it?
Yes.
Reia's little girl, about to
be seventeen! Time certainly flies.
What would you like this year?
Dinner out? Or is there a present you want?
No, not this year...
Come to think of it, your mother's pendant...
I gave that pendant to her
for her seventeenth birthday.
You did?
Yes. It was a symbol of our
promise between friends...
We pledged to never forget love.
Never forget love?
That's right. As long as you don't
forget love, you'll never be alone.
If you don't give up on love,
even if you lose something,
you'll never be invisible.
But love does cause us pain sometimes.
Whenever we remember that lost time...
That lost time...
"Flashback"
Sumika.
When that happens, we try to focus on
something else and not be too hard on ourselves.
Kureha, what you need
right now is a new friend.
A... new friend?
Yes, someone who's not Izumino.
No.
What?
I don't want a new friend.
Sumika is my only friend.
I'll never give up on love!
Growl, growl, growl, growl.
Growl. Kure-chin's eating a chikuwa roll again?
Does it really smell that delicious?
That's the taste of love for Kureha.
The taste of love?
Yes, something no storm
or bear or human can destroy.
Are you sure anything like that exists?
Of course. It's...
"Flashback"
It's okay, you're not alone. I'm your friend!
I love you.
Lady Kumaria...?
I remember getting love from someone.
That's why I came here, across the wall.
Kureha, I want you...
...all to myself!
Tsubaki.
Do you have a minute?
We all talked it over this morning.
We were wrong.
We think we've been really cruel.
So we want to make amends!
To you... and to Izumino.
What?
Give me a break.
You people excluded Sumika!
You don't have the right!
Why the change of heart now?
If you're playing a game, play it to the end!
I won't lose to people like you.
You won't make me invisible!
W-We're sorry! We've been so awful...
We're sorry!
Only we get to make friends with Kureha.
Girls in our way big time...
...get eaten by bears, growl.
"Yuri Store"
Growl...
Let's see. "Article 1: The way to
a girl's heart is through her stomach."
Okay then!
You and I gotta make Kure-chin a
flavor she loves as much as chikuwa rolls!
And then... Muahaha, I'm so clever!
Delicious smell, growl.
Ginko! You can't transform here,
no matter how hungry you are.
We're only allowed to eat
the flesh of invisible girls.
Grooowl!
So, what foods does Kure-chin like?
Shiokara and spaghetti.
Isn't that sort of old-man-ish?
She's liked them since she was little.
Hmm, then tonight's dinner will be...
"All for Kureha"
Growl! Welcome home, Kure-chin!
What are you doing?
Dinner, growl.
Heehee, we're making your love flavor!
My... "love flavor"?
Yep, your two favorites!
Y-You can't mean...
Yes! We call it "Shiokara Spaghetti"!
Delicious smell, growl!
O-Oh, wow! A flavor pairing made in heaven!
Here, Ginko, a cherry tomato. Say "ah"!
Ah!
Here, Ginko, creamy honey flan. Say "ah"!
Here, Ginko, creamy lightly
salted salmon. Say "ah"!
Ah!
Now it's your turn, growl! Say "ah"!
I won't eat it.
Huh?
--But... but... you like shiokara and spaghetti!
--Mm-hmm!
How did you know that?
Huh? Um...
I only ever told Sumika that.
You transfer students wouldn't know!
Hmm, I'm not sure how!
I told you to stay away from me!
Growl! But we want to be your friends--
Stop it!
Enough about "friends"!
Why is everyone trying to
make me give up on my love?!
I don't want any new friends.
Sumika is my only friend!
Sumika is my only love!
I don't want anything else!
What's with you two?!
Why do you want to get close to me?!
Growl. I was super scared back there!
I thought you were about
to tell Kure-chin the truth.
But if you tell her,
we can't be human girls anymore.
Those are the rules.
Sheesh, I hope she remembers you soon!
Here I am, Ginko!
I'm sorry about before.
I was happy, but I just couldn't admit it...
It's okay, growl.
So I was thinking,
if we washed each other all over,
we could really get to know each other!
Gorgeous smell!
Does that feel good, Ginko?
Yeah, it does.
Does this spot feel good too, Ginko?
Yeah, that's... good too...
Does this spot feel really good, Ginko?
Yeah, that's... really... good!
There, all clean!
"Happy Birthday Kureha"
"From Sumika"
Here, Kureha.
"Flashback"
I know it's a little early...
"One Month Ago・(History)"
My birthday isn't for a while, you know.
I know. But I have to give you this today.
Oh? You're so weird, Sumika.
Wait! Don't open it now.
Huh?
I want you to read it here on your birthday.
Why?
It's my present to you.
Present?
Please? You'll understand when you read it.
Okay.
Listen, Kureha...
I want you to always smile like that, like a flower.
That's my love.
So I'd be happy even just
watching you from a distance.
What are you talking about?
I'm always by your side, Sumika.
That's true... You didn't back down on love.
I'll never, never forget that.
Sumika?
They'll bloom soon, huh?
Yeah.
Sumika, you're my only friend.
The flowerbed...
We asked the school to make it
so you could grow flowers here again.
Sorry about yesterday. But...
The Invisible Storm wrecked
this place, and we want to fix it.
We want to fill it with flowers,
and make Izumino's last wish come true...
Sumika's last wish?
Yes. Next Sunday is your birthday, right?
Yes...
See, I heard that a little while
before that happened to Izumino...
What?
...she said she wanted to celebrate
your birthday in a garden full of flowers.
It's my present to you.
Sumika...
We want you to let us celebrate your birthday.
Because that's what Izumino wanted.
Please--for Izumino's sake.
Growl! What's with that?!
You and I are her friends, not them!
Right, Ginko?
We don't have much time before Tsubaki's birthday.
Let's start today.
Yes!
Everyone, thank you for
working hard these past few days.
"Exclusion Ceremony・(Exclusion)"
Thanks to your efforts,
Kureha Tsubaki has started to
believe that we are her friends.
We just need to endure a little longer.
Now, let's confirm our feelings one more time.
Who is the evil we must exclude?
Let's search evil!
"5. Hinako Serina"
"6. Uchiko Ai"
"4. Saori Shimabukuro"
"3. Aoi Uezu"
"2. Karen Tanaka"
"1. Evil = Kureha Tsubaki"
Select!
We have chosen Kureha Tsubaki as the evil.
Grrrrrrr...
Growl. This is great, Ginko.
She is an invisible girl.
This means we can eat her!
The time for judgment has come, growl.
"Convening Yuri Trial・(Trial)"
We now begin the Yuri Trial.
I want to eat her. I'll save
Kureha from the Invisible Storm, growl!
This again?
Doesn't everyone want to protect
the girl they love? Sparkle!
I wouldn't be too sure.
Defendant-bears, you've eaten several
humans affiliated with the Invisible Storm
in the name of "saving
Kureha Tsubaki," haven't you?
Yes.
You're guilty!
Ginko Yurishiro, answer honestly:
what is it that you want?
"Saving Kureha Tsubaki" is an excuse.
Isn't it true that all you really want
is to make yourself
Kureha Tsubaki's only friend?
Objection! The prosecutor is
speculating based on his personal sadism!
Yeah! Ginko only wants to give
back the love she got from Kure-chin.
She only wants a Promise Kiss!
Order! Objection overruled.
Ginko Yurishiro, please answer
the prosecutor's question.
That's right. I want to
have Kureha all to myself.
Ginko?!
I want to be friends with
Kureha again. I want her love.
That's why I crossed the wall,
and dragged Lulu into it too.
No, I wanted to--
But I still won't back down on love!
I'll do whatever I have to for love.
I'll do anything. There's no going
back now--I've committed a serious crime.
Ginko? What "serious crime"?
I--
Whoa! No need to finish that sentence, okay?
Your Honor, the defendant-bear
just confessed to a crime.
Please find her guilty at once!
Ginko Yurishiro, is your love the real thing?
Yes.
And if it's an egotistical love?
If that pride destroys you?
That's fine. I'm a criminal-bear.
I see. Defendant-bears, will you
be invisible? Or will you eat humans?
We'll eat...
...humans!
Growl!
I now declare the verdict.
Yuri approved!
What did you want? It's late.
Growl. Ginko and I are going to
be friends with Kure-chin, got it?
What are you talking about?
We won't let you have your way.
In other words, disappear!
Shock!
Bear shock!
What are you two? A-Are you--
Growl! We're bears!
We'll eat you up, growl.
N-No! S-Someone help me!
Ginko!
One bear successfully eliminated by our trap!
We know what you two really are!
Kureha...
On the boundary that severed
ripe moon from sleeping forest
Break the law God shackles us with and smile
I turned away from the bleating flock
of shadows and howled my bloodthirsty ego
Here amidst the Invisible Storm
Overflowing honey and soul
I want to rend silk with my fangs
I'm afraid you'll vanish
like the world's last ray of hope
The savage beast inside me
tore out the throat of innocence
Come on, shoot me through the heart
with your sweet-scented Barrett of love