In the year 1732, during the Kyoho famine,
many of the Hitogashima islanders died of starvation.
And on a day where the island was on the brink of death,
a huge whale drifted ashore onto Omoto Beach.
The islanders rejoiced, gathering around to eat the whale,
believing it to be a blessing bestowed from God.
A fisherman's daughter approached the whale,
and the whale's body glowed with a dazzling bright light.
The whale took the appearance of the girl in a flash.
It then proceeded to devour her.
The islanders, fearing divine punishment,
came to worship the girl as the living goddess Hiruko.
That is the Hiruko legend that's passed down in Hitogashima.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Face-to-Face
Sense any Shadows?
No.
Miss Nagumo was right.
Karikiri isn't a Shadow.
I see.
Still, don't let yer guard down.
Right.
My!
This heat never lets up, does it?
No.
How about Tokyo?
Is it hotter than Wakayama?
Well, it's not much different.
Please, have some cold barely tea.
Oh, thanks.
But, Karikiri,
weren't ya in Tokyo last year?
Yesterday, ya told me ya went to a game event in Tokyo.
Oh, right! By the ocean in Makuhari!
Makuhari's in Chiba, though.
My, you're right! Tokyo sure was hot!
And my word, the crowds!
So ya like video games?
What do ya play?
I was all about RPGs in my younger days.
Now, I play FPS games on PC.
I also like simulation games.
Are ya going back this year?
No, I don't think I can this year.
But I really wanted to play Final Fantasy VII Remake.
When's it coming out?
Is Final Fantasy VII fun?
I hear that name a lot.
Huh?
Shinpei, don't tell me ya ain't played it!
I wasn't born yet when it was out.
I really love the game's world.
Maybe because it came out at the end of the century,
but the art and music have this very post-apocalyptic feel to them.
It makes ya think about how yer life will end.
Life, huh?
So, for ya, games are like how novels are for me?
Have ya heard of the novel
Swamp Man by Nagumo Ryuunosuke?
I really like it.
Lately, I've been thinking that it's a story written about me.
That it's my story.
Swamp Man?
I don't know it, but I do know the Swampman thought experiment.
Are they similar?
Swamp Man
Nagumo
Ryuunosuke
Yes.
One day, a copy of the protagonist appears and takes over their life.
No one realizes the switch,
not even their friends or family.
The copy is a perfect reproduction of the protagonist's memories, personality, and DNA.
If that's the case, y'could say the copy is the real thing.
What do ya think?
Well, I'd say they're the same.
Human cells are continuously being replaced due to metabolism.
Cell division creates countless copies.
The only difference is whether the replacement happens instantly or slowly over time.
In other words, the copy is the same as the original.
That's what I think, yes.
Is yer head filled with thoughts like these?
Ya asked about the shadow sickness yesterday too.
I learned about the Hiruko legend too.
At first, I was going to ask ya,
but Hizuru told me all about it.
About 300 years ago, during the Edo period, a god washed ashore on this island.
That was Hiruko.
Ya could think of it as an ancient being from outside our world.
Let's say, for example, it came from space.
A living being that was adrift in space.
Perhaps this creature copied and transformed into other things nearby, and sustained itself off the copied data.
But there are only so many things one can transform into in outer space.
So it most likely arrived on Earth in the form of a meteorite.
I'm guessing it fell into the ocean.
There are all sorts of things it could've copied there.
What follows is mostly from Hizuru's imagination.
But it matches up with the records we have of the Hiruko legend.
It transformed into a whale 300 years ago.
And, somehow, it washed ashore on this island.
The villagers all gathered to look.
One of them, a fisherman's daughter.
It copied her.
That's where the shadow sickness began.
That is certainly how the Hiruko legend goes.
But ya can't be trying to say it's real, are ya?
I am.
Shadows exist.
They killed Ushio.
They killed my parents.
And they're going to kill everyone who gathers for the festival here tomorrow.
Oh, my apologies.
But, Shinpei, ya must've read too many books.
I understand that losing Ushio has upset ya.
Perhaps some rest is in order.
I already know everything.
Karikiri, ya know that this is the truth.
Because ya witnessed it all first-hand.
Whazzat? A whale?
I didn't notice it at first,
but Dr. Hishigata showed it to me and said that it was ya.
And apparently the man on the left is his grandfather.
What are ya doing in a photograph taken over 70 years ago, Karikiri Masahito?
Or should I say Hishigata Shidehiko?
You're Shide!
Haine!
Get back here, Haine!
Ha—
Haine, hurry back now...
Shide!
Summer Time Rendering
Shinpei—
Don't move.
Move and I kill ya.
What did Dr. Hishigata say?
I ain't answering your questions.
Ya answer mine!
Look at the other photo.
Time passed, until 40 years ago.
That's when Dr. Hishigata's father took that photo.
Ya ain't a Shadow.
But you're no mere human, either.
The Swamp Man, huh?
Fourth loop, July 23rd
While investigating the old Hishigata Clinic
Hiruko? What would somethin' like that be doin' here?
No idea. It's just a guess.
But if this is Hiruko,
then is there a connection between the Hishigata Clinic and the Hito Shrine?
Fifth loop, July 22nd
Fourth battery ruins, after Nagumo's and Nezu's pseudo loop
The four-armed one might actually be Karikiri Masahito.
What?! That whippersnapper Karikiri?!
You two suspect this as well, don't you?
Yes.
Haine...
If Hiruko is the mother of Shadows,
then doesn't the Hito Shrine dedicated to her become really suspicious?
And Karikiri is the head priest of the shrine.
Yeah, but Karikiri is human, ain't he?
Why does the four-armed one hide its face?
If it's a Shadow, it could just transform into someone else.
But what if it's actually human and has no copy ability?
I've never seen it scan something.
But it did print.
What if the four-armed one is a human wearing the black mud that creates Shadows like armor?
If it's hiding its face, that means it doesn't want to be seen.
In other words, it's someone we all know really well.
Sixth loop, July 22nd
After canceling entry to Koba Mart
How dare they do that to Ryuunosuke.
The four-armed one must be Karikiri Masahito.
After viewing our clash via your memories, I'm sure of it.
H-How can ya know?!
That priest has always rubbed me the wrong way.
And the four-armed one bothers me on a biological level, as well.
Say what?!
His armor may hide his face, but it can't hide his humanity.
Plus, the fact that Nezu couldn't pin his shadow means the chances he's human are extremely high.
But Karikiri should've been at the funeral then.
Maybe he left a Shadow in his place.
If there's really someone in there, an assassination could be effective.
Assuming he's human, killing him will be no problem.
I could go to the shrine, pretending to be there for a chat, and then smash.
That's straight up murder!
We need more definitive proof.
If he's human, then he might be willing to negotiate if we can corner him.
Seventh loop, July 22nd
After the battle at the gym
Shide received a burn on its left arm.
This will help us spot its true self.
Seventh loop, July 22nd
Hishigata Clinic basement
Take a look at this.
Shide is Haine's guardian and the first child she ever gave birth to.
His original name was Hishigata Shidehiko.
The founder of the Hishigata Clinic,
as well as its first director.
Wh-What is this photo?
The Hishigatas have been in charge of religious services on this island since ancient times.
In the middle of the Edo period, Shidehiko's father began pretending to be a doctor.
Wait a sec.
Hishigata is Karikiri from the shrine, right?
The Hishigatas and Karikiris were originally from the same household.
The Karikiris eventually split off from us and became independent.
Do you all know the legend of Hiruko?
The day Hiruko washed ashore, it became Haine,
and the islanders worshiped her as their god.
Indeed.
And eventually, Shidehiko produced a child with said god.
But not a Shadow created by scanning,
birthed from outside the body.
This came from within. Haine's flesh and blood body was impregnated and she gave birth.
So he called himself the husband of a god and began calling himself by Haine's surname, Karikiri.
Shidehiko also had an older brother.
After Haine gave birth, the Hishigata house split apart.
The Karikiris became servants of God,
while the older brother became a family of doctors.
In other words, Shide is a distant relative of ours?
That can't be...
And what of the child?
The child grew up and apparently was the spitting image of Shidehiko.
This must be the nature of Shadows.
The child Haine gave natural birth to was a clone of its father.
But that's not the end.
Seeing this, a certain ambition awoke within Shidehiko.
Don't tell me...
He made Haine copy his personality and memories,
transferring them into the child.
Thus restoring his youth.
Disgusting.
No wonder I never liked him.
My father delivered the baby.
He also took that photo.
His current body is how he was born.
Shide has continued this secret rite and been reborn by Haine over and over.
It's allowed him to live for 300 years.
You're a human-shadow hybrid!
Good grief.
It's not fair that ya can loop, Shinpei.
After only one day back, ya got this far.
But why don't ya sit down and have a drink?
I haven't poisoned it.
So ya admit it?
Back then,
yes, when I was a mere 40 years old...
It was the summer of 1732.
The year of the Kyoho famine.
Have ya heard of it?
It's in the Japanese history textbooks.
The harvests were terrible.
The adults who went fishing died too,
and we were left without the means to fish.
But then Haine appeared.
The people of this island have always believed that God resides in the things that wash ashore here,
so Haine truly was a god.
And apparently in exchange for feeding her humans,
she blessed us with bounties of fish.
That part of the legend is incorrect.
All that happened was hundreds of islanders were turned into Shadows.
The Shadows didn't need to be fishers,
so they were able to save the starving islanders.
Hitogashima survived thanks to me.
Quit screwin' around, ya bastard!
Y'think yer doin' the right thing?!
Then why did ya kill Shinpei's parents?!
Because they interfered,
much like ya did, Ushio.
They stumbled upon Hiruko cave and were about to announce it to the world.
A couple of idiots, to be sure,
but the mother was quite delicious.
Unforgivable piece of crap!
Oh, would ya have been happier if I'd turned them into Shadows instead?
I-I'm not like ya!
I don't wanna murder people,
and ya don't wanna die either, do ya?!
Why do ya protect Haine?
Ya can't accompany Haine on her way "home."
Give us Haine.
Then it can all be over, okay?
That is not my ending.
It's my duty to see my mother's wish fulfilled.
Damn it.
Damn it!
Besides, ya never know.
My Shadow might exist.
Something's off!
Pull the trigger!
I don't sense any Shadows nearby!
Why? Why is he...
Shoot him, Shinpei!
This is our only chance to take out Shide!
I understand exactly what you're thinking right now.
"Why doesn't he have a burn on his left hand?"
Correct?
By the way, Shinpei, may I move now?
That's it! I can't take this anymore!
Ushio, wai—
He's dead.
Is it over now?
I said I'd do it.
I didn't want ya to have to do something like this.
I just couldn't let ya become a murderer.
Why?
I was gonna get my revenge.
Yer too nice, Shinpei.
It would've eaten ya up inside.
Ya saw him as human, didn't ya?
Like how ya see me.
Just leave all the dirty work to me!
Ushio...
Gimme.
Y'all heard that?
I killed Shide.
Shin...
One down.
Shide?
H-How?!
No, it can't be!
I'm sorry, Shinpei!
Notice...
What a shame, Shinpei.
Ya needed to be just a little more objective.
You're going alone?
Ya want to convert him?!
I'm against this.
If Shide exposes his body, ya have to be able to pull the trigger without hesitation!
I'll kill him.
Please wait!
Let me do this just once!
I just want to know what he's thinking.
Or else, I can't kill him.
I want to hear why he killed my parents from his own mouth.
I just can't accept it otherwise.
But—
It's important to me!
I wouldn't mind dying once more to find out.
I'll come with ya.
If the shrine is crawling with Shadows,
you'll never even get to talk!
Ushio is right.
If you go alone, it's possible they'll make a move to capture you.
We'll accompany ya to the grounds.
Okay.
Can we monitor the conversation too?
What if we put his phone in his breast pocket and have a group call going?
No, can't hear a thing like that.
In that case, let's make gun shots our signal.
I'll shoot his Shadow first with two shots in order to confirm whether he's human or not.
If ya hear a third shot, that's yer signal to bust in!
How are ya feeling right now, Shinpei?
Like a child who's had his save data erased right before the final boss?
Ushio is dead.
You little brats.
Did you really think you could change my ending?
It'll be okay.
I'll be with ya, no matter what happens.
The only things you'll take back with you on your loop are despair and regret.
Have a pleasant journey!
Shinpei's whipped!
Yeah, it's like they're married!
Huh?
H-Huh?
Where's Ushio?
She was there just a second ago.
Shinpei?
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
But even now I still see visions of you
In reality I only have vivid memories
To play in my head over and over again
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
But it's too late for that
Next time
Made in Black