I'm burnin'!
The temperature's hit 39 degrees today...
Japanese summers are so hot!
I give...
Let's turn on the AC.
We can't do that until Master gets home.
But he just left!
Oh yeah,
Master didn't clean up his snacks again...
We'll have to clean that up...
But I don't want to move right now...
Hmph.
Slovenly, the lot of you.
Don't fake it.
Such heat is nothing!
Please, don't push yourself!
If this heat doesn't let up, my private parts will overheat!
Don't we have any cooler spots?
I know a cooler spot!
This feels great!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
The Visitor that Comes with the Rain...
Fr-Freezing!
It felt nice at first, but then...
My lips are purple!
Such cold is...
I told ya, don't fake it.
How about something like this?
It's... really eerie.
This atmosphere is too much!
Indeed, it is rather tense.
I-I don't care! Only kids would fall for this.
That's cold!
Wha... what's this?
Konjac jelly?
It's a very realistic creation.
I feel that I've cooled off somewhat.
Using a Naked Shinki as the ghost is cheap!
Let's change the setting next.
How's this?
It's a ghost story house!
R-Really?
I hear that a real ghost might appear while we tell stories!
Interesting.
I accept the challenge.
It all started in a countryside village.
It's a story still spoken of today.
A lone elderly woman was doing her laundry by the river.
She heard a rumbling from upstream.
It rumbled...
It was a bizarre sound.
Ever so timidly, the woman turned to face the source.
"Hi!"
she gasped.
A fruit the size of a human being flowed down the stream.
And when she listened closely...
she heard ever so faintly...
a baby's cries from inside.
The woman grasped a knife,
and sliced the fruit open.
And just what did she find?
The boy born from a peach, Momotaro.
I was so nervous!
Ann...
Guess we should've explained the basics first.
No, it gave me shivers, in a sense.
It was very well done.
You're making me blush.
May I tell a story next?
Heheh, go ahead!
Let's keep the ball rolling!
This is a story of a time when I lost my way in the mountains.
While I wandered about,
the sun had fully set.
The black trees made eerie, chattering sounds.
My heart swelled with terror,
and then...
I saw a small light from deep within the mountain.
I bounded towards what I thought would be my savior.
However...
I found only filthy piles of Shinkis,
each body heaped cruelly atop the next!
And with emptiness in their eyes,
they all turned to stare at me.
I immediately tried to run,
but my body would not do as I commanded.
I collapsed on the spot.
There was a crash from behind.
I heard the noise loud and clear.
I no longer had control over my body...
I could only move my eyes.
And when I did...
what I saw was...
It's the real thing!
Are you a ghost?
No. I am the Shinki living next door.
Really? Don't scare my screws off.
You carried no presence.
You seemed to be having fun, so I...
It started raining out of nowhere.
As I thought, that flash was real lightning.
Master didn't take his umbrella today.
Oh no!
We all need to find him!
But there's that...
We will choose one to watch the house.
One Shinki can handle that mess.
Well Ines, take care of the house!
We should be back soon.
R-Right! Time for some cleaning!
Gotta do th—
But isn't it strange?
The weather forecast said today would be sunny.
I wonder if it's an omen...
We're going downhill!
Allow me to help.
O-Oh, it's you again.
When did you...
I was always right next to you.
Huh?
Well, whatever.
An extra hand always helps.
How about we work here next?
Fine.
You know, for someone who lives right next door,
we haven't seen you before at all.
That is true.
We all moved here in spring.
When we tried to greet our neighbors back then,
everyone was out of their homes.
Is that so...
And you know the housewarming soba?
We bought the raw noodles for it,
but Master wound up eating it all himself.
I see.
Well, I welcome new acquaintances all the same.
Having friends in the area lets you share advice when you're in trouble.
Is that true?
Wh-What's with the close-up?
You must never go back on those words.
Go... back?
It's hard to go against the wind!
At this rate, we won't meet Master when he reaches the station!
Wind bearing, north-northwest.
Wind speed, 18 meters per second.
Calculating direction and distance to station from current location...
Now! Hold on!
You know our master?
He's a scatterbrain and kind of unreliable...
but he's always thinking about us Shinkis,
so he's a nice master.
Is that so...
So what's your master like?
Hm? What's wrong?
You ask... of my master?
My apologies.
My hand slipped.
Th-That was dangerous!
That slipped out from my pocket.
Th-That coulda killed me!
Be careful!
I was careless...
You gotta be kiddin' me!
That was great, Strarf!
You read the wind with just a 3-meter margin of error!
Such calculations are nothing.
Thanks to you, we reached the station ahead of schedule!
We'll see Master arrive if we wait up here.
Shall we compete to see who can spot Master first?
A battle? Interesting.
Just how I like it.
And the winner gets a head pat from Master as a reward!
Can we decide that without his permission?
A... head pat, you say?
Act now, and you'll get a special maintenance coupon too!
Master will inspect every nook and cranny of your body.
How splendid!
But we still need Master's permission...
E-Every nook and cranny...
We're finally done!
Heh, thanks!
I couldn't have finished so quickly without you.
I should give you a reward.
I apologize...
for this to happen to you...
I was only here by chance...
O-Oh yeah!
I'll make some tea, so let's have a drink!
I'm gonna heat up some Jellycans!
Master...
I shall finish this soon.
I see him! It's Master!
I saw him sooner!
He is passing us by.
What? Oh no!
Master, hold on!
We brought your umbrella!
Oh, girls!
You're lifesavers!
I was just about to call home.
Hm? Where's Ines?
Cleaning while watching the house.
Did I leave food out again?
Sorry about that.
We should call Ines to tell her we met you safely.
Well, here you go.
Oh, I'm all done here.
That Shinki from earlier helped me out,
but I'm getting a different vibe from her now.
I can't put my finger on it...
Wh-What?
I was hoping to help you with your tea...
You... heard that?
Would you help me with my task?
Ines, are you there?
What's wrong?
It seems she was just with that Shinki from next door...
The Fubuki model we met earlier?
Fubuki model?
Hm?
That Fubuki Shinki next door should be long gone...
What do you mean?
I heard it from a neighbor a while ago...
Master's shoe strap!
Another bad omen!
I have a bad feeling about this!
Girls, we need to hurry home!
Umm...
What've you been up to?
It's sharpened.
So you've touched it.
Master.
Continue your story.
Right.
The next door neighbor's Shinki went missing in the mountains a year ago.
She should have lost power there a long time ago...
So there's no way for her...
Master!
Now, at last...
Wh-What's that?
This?
Are you curious?
It's used like this...
Ines!
and then you're done!
Huh? Done?
Welcome home, Master.
Geez, don't scare my screws off.
This is something my master treasured very deeply.
When I fell in the middle of the mountain that day...
Things seem to fall a lot around you, huh?
Yes, it shames me to say.
That earned my master's ire,
and while I scoured the mountain alone in search,
my charge ran out.
Hey now, wait your turn!
When you're done charging, start moving on your own!
Oh, are you awake?
Good grief.
You've gotta be crazy to enter the mountains in such light gear.
I've had a lot on my plate lately, you know.
Put yourself in the shoes of the Shinki on patrol.
Could that mountain Zelnogrard have been...
Being in good health is important.
It was slightly damaged,
but I found this hairpin that I carry now.
So you came because you wanted to borrow some tools to repair it, then?
Yes.
But, um...
Could you take this to Master
and give it to her in my stead?
That day, Master told me...
that she no longer wished to see my face.
Don't worry, Fubuki.
Your master is waiting for you!
I-I just...
cannot do this.
Even if I were to return after all this time...
That won't happen, don't worry!
Master told us one thing.
That our neighbor's still waiting for a precious Shinki to return home.
I just can't meet her!
How could I possibly greet her?
You stall now of all places?
Yet you still call yourself a Shinki?
Master, we're good here,
so go ring that doorbell.
Yes, who is it?
Hm?
Master.
Fuki!
Master
I brought your hairpin.
I'm so sorry,
Fuki...
Welcome home.
Excuse me,
these may not be much...
Oh!
We'll graciously accept!
How 'bout using the door?
Hm? That's weird.
What's weird, Master?
I was chatting with the landlord earlier,
And that address we went to yesterday...
I'm in your debt for your help yesterday.
Oh, good timing.
Listen, I heard that nobody's renting out that apartment right now.
Oh, my master's not renting that apartment out.
She's clinging to it!
Whenever a new tenant enters that apartment,
once they see Master,
they all run right back out!
Um, wouldn't that mean...
Fubuki, your master isn't a...
Gh-Ghost?
What might that be?
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Fuki, we're so glad you were able to meet your master again!
Yeah, that's all well and good,
but her master's a ghost!
We've got a ghost living right next door!
Are you okay with that?
If you are a ghost,
Even then I will love you.
A Busou Shinki.
Why are you summarizing in haiku?
More importantly,
next episode, Ann will be in trouble!
Next time on Busou Shinki:
Next time
"One Day, Somewhere"
"One Day, Somewhere".
Ann turns into a human and goes on a date with Master?
Whaaaaat?!