Run!
Good morning.
Ah, Nagi-chan! Yuko-chan! Good morning.
What's with you? Standing there motionless...
Hey, look! This was stuck on my forehead!
You just now noticed?
Yeah!
You're the same as always, Run.
Oh. Really?
Run-chan.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Run-chan!
Hey, did you watch the show yesterday?
Yeah, I did! It was fun!
Run sure has a lot of male friends, huh?
Yeah...
T-Toru!
It's early but she's full of spunk, huh?
What's the matter, Toru?
Run-chan...
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
LOVE
Good morning, Toru.
You're still short, huh?
Don't pet me!
Hey!
Why's your uniform so dirty?! Did you fall?
Well, Run-chan...
The thing is...
What?! Don't tell me Run was being bullied!
She was chasing a butterfly and
looked like she'd get hit by a car.
You sure look after her.
Well, see ya, Toru.
See you.
Well, see you at lunch, Toru.
Good morning!
Successful Applicants - Aoigaoka High School
Yes?
Hello, Run-chan?
Toru! It's been ages!
Yeah. Say, can I come by right now?
Sure, come over.
Thanks. Well, see you in a bit.
"Been ages," huh?
I guess it has been a while,
what with tests and all.
Coming!
Oh, Toru-chan! It's been a while.
I hope you've been well.
Run's inside.
Thank you.
Pardon the intrusion.
Run-chan... I wonder if she'll be happy.
Run-chan!
I got into your high school, Run-chan! I passed!
Ah, Toru!
Wha...
Ow!
Run, what's with this chick?!
Run-chan, who is this? What was that just now?
You passed? Congratulations!
Never mind that I passed!
Is this Toru?
She really is short, isn't she?
So this is who you wanted to introduce us to?
"Introduce"?
Yeah, that's right!
Today's when they announce who passed,
so I thought you might come by.
That's why I asked them here.
These are my friends from school,
Yuko-chan and Nagi-chan.
Hey there.
Friends...
We'll be seeing you this spring, Toru.
Whoa, she's totally hatin' on me!
Your first impression was terrible, Yuko.
Tell her what was going on just now.
Um... You misunderstood.
Run was tryin' to tickle me.
I wasn't doin' nothin' weird.
Note: Yuko has let loose with her rough-and-ready Kansai dialect.
We were just playin' around.
The heck was that for?!
Eeeek!
I'm glad they've opened up
to each other already.
Eeeek!
SQUEEEZE
I'm glad they've opened up
to each other already.
Eeeek!
I'm glad they've opened up
to each other already.
Eeeek!
Slap
I'm glad they've opened up
to each other already.
Eeeek!
Slap
So we shouldn't stop them?
Eeeek!
Slap
Stop it!
So we shouldn't stop them?
Eeeek!
Stop it!
So we shouldn't stop them?
Eeeek!
Stop it! Bwomp
So we shouldn't stop them?
Eeeek!
Stop it! Bwomp
Stop it!
Eeeek!
So, I'm passin' out handouts
for your elective classes, okay?
You all did this last year,
so you know the drill, right?
Here.
Our homeroom teacher
this year is pretty flippant...
And so, that is how to fill out your
elective course printouts.
ABOUT ELECTIVE CLASSES
Types of Courses,
and How to Choose Them
They affect your future!
Choose with care!!
*College you'd like to go to,
classes you'd like to take
*Skills you'd like to improve
ABOUT ELECTIVE CLASSES
Types of Courses,
and How to Choose Them
They affect your future!
Choose with care!!
*College you'd like to go to,
classes you'd like to take
*Skills you'd like to improve
Does anyone have any questions?
As freshmen, you have few electives, but
there will be more of them as you go forward.
Application - Elective Courses
As freshmen, you have few electives, but
there will be more of them as you go forward.
Application - Elective Courses
These will affect your future,
so let's choose and decide carefully.
If anyone needs advice,
please ask me at any time.
I wonder if Run's okay...
What is she doing?
Lunch time, lunch time!
Toru, let's eat.
You sure are eager.
Toru isn't here yet.
Oh, you're right. I just...
She's here, Nagi-chan! That's Toru, all right!
Run
chan!
She's here, Nagi-chan! That's Toru, all right!
Run
chan!
Don't tell me...
She heard just now?
Ah! That squirrel pick is so cute!
Yeah, right? I love that stuff.
I like animals!
Huh. What kinda animal you like, Run?
Birds, I guess.
Like, parakeets?
They're cute, aren't they?
Come to think of it...
Run, your head looks like a parakeet's.
And they're delicious!
THAT'S how you like them?!
Eatin' parakeets is just cruel!
That ain't true, right?!
Run-chan likes chicken.
Oh, so that's it?
Meaning, chicken is
one of your fave foods, right?
That's right! But I like all kinds of meat.
Wanna get Korean barbecue sometime?
I wanna eat short ribs and salted tongue!
Now I really want to eat Korean barbecue!
It's like I can even HEAR the sound of
grilling meat coming from somewhere!
New
message
Sorry, that's me.
It's your ringtone?!
Run, your rolled egg looks delicious!
Gimme a bite?
Sure! Here.
Thanks.
Ah, that's delicious! Did you make that, Run?
Geh...
A-Again?!
Those two really get along, huh?
That's getting along?
Our lunches were delicious, right, Toru?
Yeah.
Run, where do you think you're going?
Our classroom is THIS way.
Oh, that's right. We were freshmen
up till recently, so...
Move it, Run. Toru, you'll be late
if you don't hurry, too.
Well, see you later, okay?
Toru!
Run, you didn't fall asleep
in our afternoon classes, did you?
Nope! Afternoon was no problem.
Almost fallin' woke you up a bit, huh?
You gotta be more careful.
'Kay.
I'M sleepier in the afternoon...
Oh!
Want some candy to clear the sleep away? Here.
Thank you.
Here. You get one, too, Run.
Thank you!
That's the last one.
Oh. Then I'll save this for Toru.
But that'd leave none for you.
No, I'll split it with her.
You're so thoughtful, Run!
How are you going to "split" that candy?
Oh, that's it!
Box cutter!
I wonder if this can cut it in half...
Don't push it. You'll look like a moron
if you hurt yourself over a piece of candy.
I'll be fine.
Think it'll work?
It fell on the floor!
What did I tell you?
I thought it would be fine!
Aoigaoka
High School
Toru.
Sorry for the wait.
Well, let's go home.
What's the matter, Toru?
I smell candy.
I smell the smell of candy.
Huh? You had more?
Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy! Candy!
No...
I forgot to throw the bag away.
That's incredible, Toru.
You could smell the empty bag?
Because Toru loves sweets!
Sorry. We all ate the last ones earlier.
I'll bring more next time.
I'd like sugar candy!
Um, maybe something not so sweet...
Or, something with fewer calories.
Huh? But sweeter is tastier!
Okay, I get it. I'll have more tomorrow.
What'd you two choose for your electives?
What was that again?
Miss Kamate told us about it, right?
Run, that's when you were sleeping.
Ah.
Oh, is that right?
So, Yuko, why did you slip?
Run looked like she'd fall over,
so I tried to catch her.
Then Run suddenly stopped
and I lost my balance.
So, Toru, what did you choose
for your freshman electives?
Toru?
I want to take... the same class as you.
As YOU.
It's all right.
Nothing's changed between us.
Yeah.
You sure are cute, Toru.
S-S-Stop!
Say, Toru, wanna come hang out with us?
Let go of me.
That's cruel, Yuko.
Let me have a squeeze of her, too.
So soft!
Wh-what gives? Jeez!
Let's go, Toru.
Yume to harukaze no kagaku
Dreams and the chemistry of spring breeze
Tomaranai yokan
A premonition that won't stop
Lucky, happy, kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky, happy, Stop at this finger!
Itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
Always running boisterously, and the destination
Wakaranai kedo sore ga ii ne
Is unknown, but that's fine
Hajimaru yo
It's going to start
Honpou, my pace, jugyouchuu wa gahaku
Uninhibited, leisurely paced, drawing during class
Kirehashi ni wa keikaku
A plan on the scraps
Doko ni yukou? Kitto ima ga paradise
Where shall we go? Surely, right now is paradise
Nejimakisugi no munasawagi
Apprehension, wound up too tight
Yakusoku wa chikoku dakedo douchaku
Later than promised, but we showed up at the same time
Skirt no stage wa donna hibi ni naru no?
What sorts of days will the skirted stage bring?
Yume to harukaze no kagaku
Dreams and the chemistry of spring breeze
Tomaranai yokan
A premonition that won't stop
Lucky, happy, kono yubi ni tomare
Lucky, happy, Stop at this finger!
Itsumo kashimashiku hashiru sono saki wa
Always running boisterously, and the destination
Wakaranai kedo sore ga ii ne
Is unknown, but that's fine
Hajimaru yo
It's going to start
Aoigasaki
High
School
Hey, hey...
Run really has a lotta guy friends, huh?
What'cha think they're talkin' about?
"Hey, tell us Yuko-chan's
measurements, Run-chan!"
"Keep it a secret, okay? From top to bottom,
it's 88 cm, 56 cm, 87 cm."
"Whoa! That's awesome!"
Something like that, no?
Wh-Wh-Why do you know my
measurements, Nagi?!
Uh, well, see you later, Run-chan.
See you!
Later.
Huh? They all took off.
I get it.
Ah! Toru!
Run-chan.
You're full of spunk every morning, huh, Toru?
Toru.
I brought some candy, as promised.
Let's all have some later, okay?
Wh-Why?!
No! Stoooop!
Those two really do get along, huh?
Yeah.
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!
!
.
There are different types of rain, aren't there?
Sprinkles, showers, teardrops o' rain...
That's right. You sure know a lot, don't you?
Note: Miporin is a nickname; Miho is her real name.
Now here's a quiz, Miporin!
What is it?
Well, WHO are we?
Wait, you just revealed my name, didn't you?
Ruh-roh! I, Yutaka, made a serious error...
Next time on A-Channel:
"Rainy Days Call for Baths"!
Next
Episode!
Next time on A-Channel:
"Rainy Days Call for Baths"!
Next
Episode!
Wait, if we have this many lines,
does it mean we'll be appearing next-
Next
Episode!
That's a secret.