Haruka's Room
Number 5
It's Haruka's Room, you know?
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for today...
Mori! Mori! Mori!
Please welcome my classmate, Moritani Hiyori!
Hold on.
Yes?
That introduction was weird!
You did a better job introducing the others!
I'm sorry. I didn't put enough energy into the "Mori," right?
Please forgive me, I'm still a newbie.
That's not what I was—
Oh, forget it.
Let's continue.
Right!
Hm... You didn't seem to like me much, Moritani-san.
Why is that? Did I do something wrong?
Umm... I felt like you were stealing Manabe away from me.
That made me irritated, and so...
So you're saying you love Manabe-kun, right?
You already know that!
It appears that we're not only classmates, but rivals in love as well!
"Rivals in love"? So, I still have a chance?
Nope. No chance at all.
Damn you!
Please, control yourself!
Please standby
The End