Sigh, I'm in math now!
It's over!
That test was hard.
How's life at your school, Suzu?
Yeah, I just finished my test, too!
I don't think it went well...
What're you doing after this?
About to head to practice!
It's hot today,
so it's gonna be really bad!
Chi-chan, hang in there!
Suzuko, we're ready.
Let's go home!
Okay.
The thing in third period today...
I know!
Wasn't it hilarious?
Who is it? Your boyfriend?
No, it's my dad.
He says he wants Japanese cooking for dinner.
Wow, he tells you what he wants, huh?
You two are so close.
Homura Suzuko-san.
Yes?
Um...
Okay, Suzuko, see you later.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
Um...
Homura Suzuko-san.
Want to do it with me?
U-Um... How did you know who I was?
Mizushima Kiyoi.
I was a Selector, like you.
I want to see your power.
Power...
Summon Valkyrie Argos.
Ener Charge Argos's ability.
Activate spell "Innocent Jeweled Blade."
Attack, and turn end.
Grow.
Summon Aztec and place Voyni on the field.
ARTS: Death Colossao.
Banish all your SIGNI.
You're good.
You think so?
I do.
But I couldn't beat that man.
Satomi Kou.
You defeated him and took back your memories,
then you left the battle.
Right?
Tell me about your battle with Satomi.
I was so desperate...
I told myself I had to protect Chi-chan.
Now, it's time for the finale.
End it, Carnival.
You're sure you want me
to crush your toy, Kou?
Suzu!
Chi-chan?
Use this!
You can do it.
Right.
Coin bet!
Requiem.
Wh-What?
Just...
die already!
Riru won't lose.
We won't lose.
If the two of us are together!
The darkness doesn't end.
Yes. It wasn't going to end.
Each time you lose a battle,
each time the time limit comes,
you lose one of your precious memories.
You suffer, you tremble at
the fear of ceasing to exist...
The despair increases.
It takes physical form,
and a new LRIG is born.
The battles will begin again. I know it.
No...
Grow.
The effect sends one card to the trash.
Attack with SIGNI.
Turn end.
You didn't really think
it was all over, did you?
I... I don't know.
But...
But?
I don't want to think about
that happening again...
Is that what you really think?
You could've refused when
I invited you to play WIXOSS.
When I told you I was a Selector.
If you really never wanted
to do this again...
I...
Are you still thinking about it?
Telling yourself it can't be over yet?
No.
Do you want to fight more battles? Or...
No!
Grow!
Summon two SIGNI.
ARTS: Stole Story.
I steal your Death Collosao
and active its effect.
Then summon SIGNI.
And... attack.
Just what I should've expected.
Homura Suzuko-san, I want your help.
I want to end the cycle of darkness.
I need powerful Selectors.
But I...
"I'm done with it."
If that's what you think,
then I won't force you.
But if that's not true...
Contact me.
Yeah, this is great.
You're getting better at cooking.
Suzuko? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is basketball practice tough?
Yeah, I joined partway through year two,
so I'm below even the first-year students.
I have to do all the grunt work.
That sounds rough.
But when we're playing a game,
I get really fired up.
I yell at the players,
"What are you doing? Run faster!"
Scary!
You were like that during dodgeball
in elementary school, too.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Oh, right.
Look, this movie's coming out next month.
That looks interesting.
But will it be crowded on the first day?
If there's anything I can do...
Mizushima-san!
Sorry! Did I keep you waiting?
No. Let's go.
Wait.
Another friend of mine is coming.
Friend?
A girl from my school.
She's really good at WIXOSS and can help
with a lot of things, so I asked her.
Homura-san, do you know
what we're doing today?
Yes.
Satomi-san... or rather,
it's an LRIG that's inside him now.
But we're going to find him, right?
We don't know where he is or what he's doing.
There's a chance that he's up to
no good and waiting to ambush us.
This isn't a game.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
I don't know who you asked to come, but...
Acceptance.
So it was you?
It's been a long time.
It has.
Huh? You know her?
Connection.
We met as Selectors and fought.
I was thoroughly defeated.
You lost, Hanna-chan?
She really is strong.
Lucky.
I was hoping to see you again.
I wanted a chance to play you again.
I'm always willing.
U-Um...
I made cookies!
Want some?
Exhaustion.
You're acting like we're going on a field trip.
Am I?
Stable.
Chocolate chip and banana.
The same as your usual.
Try some.
It's better than you'll find at most stores.
It's good.
Unfair!
Are you going to eat them all yourself?
It was your suggestion.
There's plenty more!
If Satomi-san... er, what used to be Satomi-san?
Complex.
Let's just call him Carnival.
It's Carnival that's inside him now.
Yeah...
If Carnival is trying to get
involved in the battles again...
We need to be chosen as Selectors again.
Inevitable.
He should be going in and
out of card shops a lot.
And listening to people on the street and
reading the Internet to gather information.
Satomi once used this bar as his base
when he was the bookmaker.
But he hasn't come here once
since the battles ended.
He used two people who'd been
inhabited by LRIGs as his servants.
Sumida Sou and Narumi Shou.
We don't know where they are, either.
Narumi-san...
Are there a lot of people who've
changed places with LRIGs?
Question.
Why are you so intent
on unraveling the mysteries of the Selector battles, Mizushima-san?
Two reasons.
One is that I lost some of my memories
in the last round of battles.
Very, very important ones...
Green Tea
I'm going to get them
back in the next battle.
Warning.
Getting all your memories back
doesn't always lead to happiness.
Hanna-chan...
True.
But no matter what kind of memories
they are, they're a part of me.
That means I'm not the real me right now.
The real...
The other reason is that I have a
responsibility to stop the Selector battles.
Responsibility?
In the first Selector battles, I was an LRIG.
An LRIG?
The first battles... The ones
created by the girl called Mayu?
Yes.
I've met that girl, Mayu,
many times in that white room...
This is her game.
I was her toy. She was merely playing with me.
But that didn't bother me.
I intended to use her, too.
I annihilated the girls I faced in
battle as a way to get my revenge.
Sometimes even the Selectors who owned me...
The "first LRIGs" were born from
the sorrows of young girls...
And I'm sure some of those
sorrows were created by me.
So...
I don't think it's your fault.
Anyone who gets caught up in these awful
battles can only care about themselves...
So it's not your fault, Kiyoi-chan!
Kiyoi-chan?
Oh... S-Sorry! I wasn't thinking...
But you can call me Suzuko.
Thank you, Suzuko.
Sure, Kiyoi-cha—
Can I call you Ki-chan?
Hasty.
Suzuko-san, don't you think
you're moving a little too fast?
Sorry.
I'll just call you Kiyoi-chan.
If you really don't like it,
then never mind, I guess...
Doubt.
Is there any point in
following the former LRIGs?
Once they have a human body,
isn't the only thing left for
them to accept their new lives?
I can feel it...
It feels like the LRIGs are slowly
evolving into something dangerous.
Oh, no... What do I do?
Six months ago, I battled
with a girl I met by chance.
Piruluk, attack.
She had one coin left.
I'm going to lose.
What do I do?
Turn end.
My goal was to find Satomi.
I was going to just let her win soon, when...
Oh, no!
Listen, you're seriously about to disappear.
Forever.
Stop hiding how you really feel.
You wanna just die while
others treat you like scum?
It's the people around you
who are to blame, right?
You're always saying it on the inside...
"I wish they'd just all disappear."
Let all the black, painful stuff
deep inside you spill out.
Let it spill out all over
the trash in the world!
Why?
Why is it always me?
...sappear.
All of you, disappear!
That's right! That's right,
let it all spill out!
Leyra, grow.
Coin bet.
Doping!
Do it!
Her damage output increased,
but she's taking damage, too?
More! More!
Piruluk...
Just disappear... All of you, just disappear!
You're a good girl!
Huh?
Why?
That's right...
Leyra... Why? No... I'm going to dis—
It feels great.
She was a disgusting woman,
perfect for the battles.
Bye-bye!
That LRIG was clearly in
control of the girl's heart.
If their goal isn't just
luring them into battles,
but awakening the evil that's
deep within their hearts
and making it into their own power...
Doubt!
I can see no point in LRIGs doing that.
I'm just afraid of the worst possibility.
If evil LRIGs like Satomi start to
increase their numbers and come together,
they'll devour this world.
Doubt.
I think that's taking it a bit far.
You won't know what an LRIG really thinks
after it's taken over a human
until you see for yourself.
Suggestion.
Someone comes to mind.
That's right. We know Shirai-san... Donor-san.
Excitement.
I was right to ask how to contact him.
I don't know anything about the other LRIGs.
Honestly, lately I find myself
forgetting that I was an LRIG.
All the memories of Shirai
Shouhei are still inside me.
Everyone around me treats me like him.
And it kind of feels like I've
spent my whole life in this body.
But at times, I desperately
want to fight a battle.
A LRIG instinct, perhaps?
When it happens, I get scared of myself.
Can you sense what Carnival
or the other LRIGs are doing?
Nope.
But I can't see her just doing nothing.
It feels like I'm really talking to Shirai-san.
You sound like a boy.
When I was an LRIG, I was pretty tomboyish.
Shou-chan used to pick on me for it.
Hey, that girl... Morikawa Chinatsu.
Does she remember Shou-chan?
I see... Yeah, of course.
Will you stay out of them from now on?
The Selector battles.
Shou-chan lost his life protecting her.
Morikawa Chinatsu, and you, too...
I never want you to get close
to that darkness again!
Kiyoi-chan, listen... I...
Carnival!
Kiyoi-chan!
Excuse me!
Let's split up.
Roger!
Okay!
I-I'm sorry!
Now, let's begin again...
Was I mistaken?
I guess that's it for today.
Confirmation.
Are you going to continue chasing after
the darkness of the Selector battles?
Yes.
Suzuko-san?
I...
Warning. Shouldn't you give it more thought?
Remember all the things those horrible
days took from you and Chinatsu-san,
and how dangerous it is to return to them.
Don't you owe it to Shirai-san?
Kiyoi-chan, I'm sorry.
I can't help after all.
I decided I'd follow a
new path with Chi-chan.
All right.
But, Suzuko...
You're still uncertain.
See you later.
Sorry, Suzu.
Did you wait long?
No.
What's wrong, Suzu?
It's nothing. Let's go, Chi-chan.
I'm not...
going back.
Hello,
Kominato Ruuko-san.
Omen / Daybreak and Dawn