The blue ocean...
The white sands...
The billowing clouds!
It's a perfect Okinawan beach!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
Seaside Swimsuit Armor
It's so cold!
My head is stinging!
I hear ya!
So this is what they call brain freeze, huh?
What happened?
Look at this!
I picked a winner!
So pretty...
It's so fantastic!
It feels like we turned into fish!
Sea slug!
Stop it!
It's so gross!
Armor equipped!
Does this look like armor to you?
It suits you!
What's so funny, huh?
Tepid. Far too tepid.
What is?
I shall enjoy myself in my own way.
What kinda game needs you to blindfold yourself in Swimsuit Armor?
If one is to play a game upon a summer beach, there is but one option!
No! Not here! Not the face!
The melon's to the right! The right!
Yummy!
What should we play next?
Hmm... isn't that Swimsuit Armor a bit lame for an Okinawan beach?
You don't have anything cuter?
I've no need for cuteness.
This provides the greatest amount of mobility.
Mobility, huh?
Wanna test that theory?
Interesting. I accept.
Okay, here it comes!
A crab?
Aah! Not in my screw hole!
Such is the weakness of Bikini-type Armor.
Its defense is frail.
M-Master?
What are you all doing in your Swimsuit Armor?
Oh, just doing a rehearsal for tomorrow's Okinawa trip.
Practicing is fine, but I need to pack you girls up soon.
We've got an early day tomorrow.
Yes, Master!
But I can't decide on what to wear...
Master, which Swimsuit Armor do you like better?
Hmm... I think this one suits you better.
Oh yeah, I need to give you a coat of this before it gets late.
Waterproofing oil.
It also blocks UV rays.
Please do, Master.
Here, lie down.
Your Swimsuit Armor leaves a lot exposed,
so I'll need to use a lot of oil.
Master, do me! Do me!
Now now, wait your turn.
Then I'll go next!
Lene, you meanie! I'm next!
Okay Master,
we're going to bed.
We'll be inside the bag, so take care.
I've got to finish my summer homework first, and then I'll go to sleep.
Don't stay up too late.
Good night, Master!
Yeah, good night.
I'm so excited that I can't enter sleep mode.
Did we forget anything?
What's up, Ann?
Now, for day two,
I think Shuri Castle would be better than the aquarium...
You should really ask Master about that.
Can't we worry about that when we get there?
Just go to sleep.
What the heck is that?!
Oh, I borrowed that from Ms. Ia.
It's Mermaid-type Armor!
It's too friggin' huge!
And didn't we agree on a luggage limit of 500 grams?
But Ines, didn't you…
Oh no, it's leaking!
Why did you bring so many Jellycans?
They make great snacks—
I mean, they're not that heavy, right?
Well that's news to me!
In that case, I want to bring...
What do you wanna take?
No, we're not taking you.
I really think Bikini-type Armor suits you best.
I-I'm retiring!
Let's go to sleep too.
When we wake up tomorrow,
we'll already be in Okinawa...
Ah!
What now, Lene?
We should get those fried sweet buns as a souvenir!
Or maybe Okinawan sweets?
I just said to worry about that when we get there!
Crap, I slept in!
Wallet, handkerchief, tissues...
and my passport!
... dom'f need it.
We're here, girls.
Come on out.
Aw crap, it's the wrong case!
Hello, Okinawa!
Huh?
Did we get...
left behind?
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
You don't need to apologize so much.
Master, we know you were up late with homework last night.
It wasn't your fault. Yes. Yes.
What?
I see...
So, we can't see you for three days?
We'll be away from Master for three whole days?
And Master was just about to enjoy himself in Okinawa...
What do we do?
Nothing can be done. We are unable to board airplanes.
We can't give up!
Huh? But...
It's not like it's on the other side of the globe!
We can do it somehow!
We'll go by ourselves,
to Okinawa!
Yeah, I'm with ya, Ann!
As do I!
My blade would grow dull were we to remain here.
Let's give Master a huge surprise!
Where are we now?
Well, we can still see Mt. Fuji, so...
Our journey is still long.
Wait, we're not planning on flying the whole way there, are we?
Don't worry.
Let me check the transfer guides to make a route.
We can ride that bus!
What a nice breeze!
Where is this bus headed?
Guess it'd be too much to hope for a straight shot to Okinawa.
We'll transfer to a train next!
It is here.
A freight train?
Let's go!
Traveling by train is nice, too!
The bumpy ride feels nice.
Though it makes me kinda sleepy.
Good thing I packed a lunch!
Ta-dah!
Mountain kettle rice flavor.
Wouldn't it make us even sleepier to fill up on one of those?
So you don't want any, Ines?
Whoah, I'll have some!
We'll take turns with one sip each.
I forgot to bring tea.
Aw c'mon, hurry up!
I brought squid flavor!
Our luggage!
What now?
Aw, don't get depressed on us.
It was our fault for dozing off.
But without that...
What were its contents?
The spare battery packs... everyone's.
Huh?!
Which means...
If we can't charge on the way there,
we won't have the energy to make it to Okinawa?
For now, let us return to the rails.
We can find a Shinki Shop should we find a large town.
I'm so thirsty...
Here.
Why'd you have to pick kettle rice flavor for this?
If you can complain, do not drink.
But it's strange that we've been walking so far without seeing another train.
Oh yeah, there are a bunch of transfer points on railroads.
Don't tell me we crossed onto an unused railroad...
It seems I must tell you.
It's abandoned? We must have taken a wrong turn.
Where the heck are we? Pull up a map!
It's no use, we're out of range.
I can't connect to the net.
Then we're down to our last resort. Time to fly—
No. The energy consumption of flight mode is great.
Entering that mode in an unknown area would...
What's wrong?
Something is here.
A human?
No.
Is it a wild animal?
We may be armed, but it is best to avoid combat.
You're right.
Fighting exhausts much more energy than just flying.
Regardless, it is dark, so movement will bring danger.
We shall camp the night here.
We will take turns standing guard, two at a time.
If we run out of power in this mountain and stop functioning,
nobody will come to save us.
We'll never see Master again.
I wonder what Master is doing right now...
Certainly asleep.
This is all my fault...
You are not the one at fault.
But I was the one who said we should all go...
Should you not have said it, someone else certainly would have.
In addition...
I have yet to see the ocean, so I wished to go as well, if but once.
Strarf...
Such thoughts may have been born from my own weakness,
but I am quite skilled in survival.
This situation is nothing.
Thank you, Strarf.
So, we are not alone!
Strarf,
I'll fight with you!
You guys have gotta be crazy to enter the mountains in such light gear!
I've got a generator, so it'll take some time,
but you should all be done by morning.
Thank you very much.
You've saved us!
But what are you doing in the mountains living in a tent all alone?
Is your master not home?
My master's in the SDF.
Look.
Over in that base.
My mission is to protect this mountain.
That's why I camp out here when he's on duty.
South is that way.
Well, I'm out.
Thank you.
We must surely cross swords when next we meet.
Yeah, I'll look forward to that.
I've always wanted to fight a Strarf model.
We're truly in your debt.
You even gave us spare battery packs.
No problem.
We're all the same when we're in trouble.
Can we reach Okinawa by today?
I'm sure we can make it happen!
I hope you see your master safe and sound!
We will!
Let us go to the sea
Let us travel there
I can't reach it with my feet, though
When I am with you, I want to go on an adventure
as the southern cross shines in the sky above
I won't ever forget this moment when my heart leapt with joy
Let us walk into a bright and vast dawn
holding boundless possibilities
When I am with you
Okinawa
I feel like I can walk so far into the future
I don't know which way is which, but I won't run away again,
so let's stay together until the end of time
Let us run together
into our future
I don't care what awaits us
Master!
You are there for me, and you taught me so much
I'll look up at the sky as I walk the path
that leads into our future
Master, we're here!
You wouldn't believe the day we had!
But it was a lot of fun!
Sorry, girls.
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Okinawa was so much fun!
I wished to see a battle between viper and mongoose.
We bought souvenirs and took tons of pictures!
And we took an airplane home!
Next time on Busou Shinki:
"Attention Please! This Plane Is Experiencing a Descent into Hell."
Wait, Hell?!
It seems a terrorist planted a bomb in our plane!
Why's this show getting serious all of a sudden?
We've been fighting tentacle monsters and having wacky races 'til now!
Next time
"Attention Please! This Plane Is
Experiencing a Descent into Hell."
Either way, we have no choice but to fight for Master!