The treacherous sunset wipes
away those annoying sweat drops.
The city roars as if it's singing a song.
Roar out louder!
Selty Sturluson
The quiet fairy is within your sight.
Roar out louder!
Seiji
Yagiri
To compensate, you must gather the shards of a broken love.
Namie
Yagiri
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Shizuo Heiwajima
You can see it in the gap between the buildings!
Izaya
Orihara
As long as you believe in it now,
tomorrow won't turn out to be completely worthless.
Erika
Karisawa
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Walker
Yumasaki
Kyohei
Kadota
Piercing through the darkness!
As long as you take the moment to sense it,
Saburo
Togusa
you'll see that meaningful dream come true.
There's surely something we can see that's invisible to everyone else.
Mikado
Ryugamine
Something worthwhile no one can take from us.
Masaomi
Kida
Anri
Sonohara
Dollars?
They're pipiru piru piru angels who fly in the sky while showing their underwear to everyone below them!
Make sure you have the right amount.
If she doesn't wake up, we'll get shit for pay.
Well, we don't know much about the Dollars ourselves.
But we'll tell you everything we know.
I heard they're part of the color gangs,
but no one knows what color they represent.
A new novel published by Dengeki Bunko came out.
We bought a few more for various purposes.
Yeah. Various purposes.
The sun rises above the horizon, yeah!
Simon Brezhnev
It's the line that separates earth from the sky!
As long as you believe in it now,
Shinra
Kishitani
things will shine as bright as that ray of light.
Dullalala!!
Don't even think you're getting away!
Turning right!
Men need to have strong abdominal muscles.
This is the first time we've done this since we joined the Dollars, Mr. Kadota!
Keep your asses on your seats!
The Dollars aren't pipiru piru piru angels who fly in the sky while showing their underwear to everyone below them, right?
Dotachin?
I keep telling you not to call me that!
Okay, we've lost them.
Are they out of their minds?!
Dammit!
Okay, I've got some things I want to ask you.
To be precise, the human
experimentations you guys are taking part in.
My name is Kyohei Kadota.
I really don't like being called 'Dotachin'.
This all started around eight hours ago.
Always On The Move
What I'm about to tell you are the details about the famous Kaztano incident.
The one who went missing was a classmate of mine.
Specifically, a friend of a friend.
I've never met her before.
What?! Is that one of those disappearances that has been happening lately?! Spirited away?
So someone you know has gone missing...
Oh yeah,
there's been a lot of these disappearances lately.
I hear a lot of rumors about these incidents.
You really love rumors, don't you.
Hahaha!
From what I've heard,
it's usually a foreigner who's living here illegally,
or perhaps a child who ran away from home, and came to this district.
So basically, people who won't be noticed if they go missing.
A lot of those people disappear in the area between Ikebukuro and Shibuya.
And when they disappear, they're never heard of again.
Is this true?
There's a scarier rumor out there too.
The reason why the people are never found is because the Dollars dispose of their bodies somewhere and eat them.
Huh?
Nice! A rusty sign!
This has to be the place.
The supplier the informant told us about.
Yeah, it does seem like a lot of illegal aliens would be living here.
Okay, let's hurry and stock up on those goods and deliver them. That's how we make our living.
Kaztano! Kaztano!
Yo! Yo! Yo!
This is fun!
Whoa! Teenage girls!
We get an extra twenty percent!
Nah, let's do this steadily today.
If we try that again, the monster
may come to get us like last time.
The headless monster, huh...
This is enough for today.
What happened?
You sure there's nothing wrong with him?
Well, he's still a human.
Guess we'll have to deal with being paid less for bringing a middle-aged man with problems.
Hey.
Yo, you're the reason we get to eat.
I'm Japanese! Just like you!
But a lot of people say I look like a foreigner.
I'm sad, un poco.
I get bullied sometimes.
I don't think we'll make enough to eat with this guy.
The hell does "un poco" mean, anyway?
So without a little brother type like Yuta who serves as a helpful fairy character,
she's just a really masochistic wolf with a hair fetish.
I'd say he's a trap, not a little brother type.
I want a little sister type who serves as a helpful fairy character.
Well, not that I'd mind the big sister type.
I'll kill you guys if you talk about that during dinner.
Dotachin! Let's go out to eat!
Let's eat! Let's eat!
Sure.
Wow, your craftsmanship is amazing as usual.
This bathroom is bigger than my room.
The concept they asked for was a "high-class cabaret that allows you to relax peacefully".
You'd better hurry.
Today's the one important day of the month.
Yeah.
Who is it?
Kaztano.
"Bin kid broke."
Just buy a new bin then.
Tell him to hit up the dollar store!
I'm Japanese!!
He didn't screw up typing "I've been kidnapped", right?
You're overthinking it.
He's so annoying! Put him to sleep already!
Fine.
It's real cheap!
Very fresh!
So you've heard that rumor too, Sonohana.
Yes...
Just chill.
That's definitely bullshit.
Yeah!
Harima just disappeared. It's not like she was kidnapped or anything.
There's no way she was kidnapped and disposed of!
Why do you need to go into detail?
Did I just dig my own grave?
Three servings of sushi!
Don't worry, our sushi is made of fish.
Even on 50% off days, we don't serve humans in our dishes.
However...
Is he going to keep this discussion up?!
Simon!
The banner up front was broken off!
The banner?!
Yeah, the banner!
Let's go fix it, yeah?
Okay?
Let's go fix it!
I'm serious.
The sushi shop around the corner
doesn't serve fish on 50% off days.
They serve humans.
Isn't that scary?
Mr. Togusa, why don't you get an italian car?
Italian cars are awesome.
I'm gonna kill you.
Italian cars are expensive since they're foreign.
Can I get a squilla from the Seto Inland Sea?
I want a yellowtail and a yellow jack!
That was dangerous!
Yeah it was.
Why did you splatter the entire bottle? You got it on us too..
I can't do this... I'm too sleepy...
Don't fall asleep until we deliver the goods.
This isn't good...
My eyelids are shutting by themselves!
Watch where you're going!
Excuse me.
What is it?
He's the source of all our drowsiness.
If you just dump him back there, we'll feel more awake.
What?
Kaztano! We brought you sushi!
Hey! We brought you an old bin from "Russia Sushi"!
What the hell is this?!
So he didn't actually mean "a kid broke my bin" in that text.
Yeah...
It was a china bowl!
Dotachin!
"Kana to kanji for dummies".
Kaztano...
Kaztano must have been kidnapped by those guys who hunt down humans.
We'll never see him again...
How am I supposed to live without Kaztano?
Who's going to be here to support me?!
We all knew how important Kaztano was to Togusa.
No one can replace Kaztano.
Not even the three of us.
Although that makes me feel a little sad...
If he was kidnapped when we got the text, it wasn't that long ago.
We need to get him back before they deliver him.
But how...?!
I know how!
I saw what their car looks like!
Hashim!
Here he is!
The best little brother and helpful fairy character ever!
Okay, sure.
Gotcha.
So if we find them, we need to release the foreigner, right?
Yeah.
We don't know when and where those thugs will hand over their goods to the higher-ups.
But we want to save him as soon as possible.
Okay, a black van, right?
Any idea about their license plate number?
Yeah, you ready?
Hang on a sec.
Ready.
Thanks, Hashim.
Sure.
Can you eat sushi?
Yeah!
Later!
Do these have wasabi in them?
Yeah.
Don't worry. Russian wasabi isn't spicy at all.
Don't lie to him!
Let's go.
Let's!
It's a black van, and here's its license plate number.
Be careful!
The ones who did it are subcontractors of some unethical business.
Anyway, they're underlings.
Apparently, they kidnap people that won't be noticed even if they go missing, and they hand them over to the higher-ups.
I'm guessing that the humans are
used as materials for a lot of things.
It's almost like cannibalism.
We've been receiving a low amount of
supplies from our subcontractors this month.
Yes, recently, we've been careful about how we obtain the 'materials'...
I didn't ask for excuses.
Cut the subcontractors who can't raise our numbers.
But...
Or would you rather become a 'material' yourself?
You may leave.
Seiji...
Tissues
60w light bulb
Coffee
Shinra, you idiot...!
Sparkling naked!
Let's dance, b-
We desperately searched for the
black van that kidnapped Kaztano.
We were determined to find him for sure.
We tried everything, but we just couldn't find out where he was.
A hint of anxiety rushed through my mind.
Will we never hear that phrase from Kaztano again?
That old phrase I always heard when I was a kid.
That phrase I thought I'll never hear again now that I'm an adult.
Do you have tickets?
Ticket / Sold / Bought
I've got tickets!
Yes, Kaztano is a working man; a rare being in today's society.
And Togusa relied on Kaztano for the greatest joy in his life.
Ruri Hijiribe, Togusa's eternal goddess.
A goddess whom Togusa one-sidedly offers his love to.
Kaztano was a magician to Togusa, since he always acquired the seat closest to his goddess, which was quite hard to obtain.
We must rescue Kaztano by all means, for Togusa's sake.
What are you talking about, Dotachin?
And who are you talking to?
Well...
I was thinking, why don't we try calling Kaztano's cell?
We may be able to make a deal with those guys.
Sushi love.
I like fatty tuna.
Who the hell is this?
Whoa, that voice! Is this Dotachin!?
So, check this out!
I was walking along the street and
found someone sleeping on the ground.
His cell phone was ringing, so I got it for him-
Huh? Where am I?
I'm by Taishoken of south Ikebukuro.
Huh?
Well, because...
Isn't today 50% off day at "Russia Sushi"?
Izaya! Get your ass out of Ikebukuro!!
Oops, Shizzy found me.
Later!
Izaaaayaaaaaaa!!!
Wake up!
Hey! Wake up!
Wake the hell up!
Wake up, dammit!
Not that.
I said wake the fuck up!
You'll put him to sleep forever.
But if we don't hurry, Kaztano's gonna...!
Yeah! Once he's delivered, they're going to dispose of him!
What are we gonna do?
I'm going to make his buddies tell me where they're taking Kaztano.
It's almost time to make the exchange.
The higher-ups are coming, so you better keep an eye.
Okay.
I'm Japanese!!
It's about time you guys realized you made a mistake!
You're still saying that?
So that means you're listed as a Japanese in your family register too, right?
You gotta pay attention to this part!
My family register burned up in the air raids!
Just how old do you claim to be?!
Hello?
Yo yo, it's me.
Oh, Kanazawa?
You awake now?
Sorry, I'm gonna head over to you guys now.
Wait, where was the exchange point again?
Jesus, dude...
We're fucking amazing!
Aww yeah!
We did it!
Who the hell are you guys?
We're...!
The Dollars!
Dollar...?
's'!
Remember it well!
I'm sleepy...
So sleepy...
Let's go.
The reason why we joined the Dollars is very simple.
To begin with, these three were already hanging out with me when I realized it.
I wonder what they saw in someone like me.
Geez... they're a laudable bunch.
One day, I got a text.
"Want to join the Dollars?"
"There are no restrictions or rules."
"You just have to say you're part of the Dollars."
A strange invitation.
A little while before this, rumors began circulating about that group being a little weird.
At first, I thought it was some prank,
but when I agreed to the text to see what would happen,
a URL and a password was sent to me the next day.
When I logged in, my nick was displayed on the Dollars site.
None of the members, including myself, have ever seen our leader.
There are many small groups within the group, and each of them form a vertically-structured society,
but the actual top is nowhere to be seen.
Since the leader can't be found, I don't feel like I'm working under anybody.
But I'm extremely curious as to who created this strange group system.
Don't tell anyone, but there's someone who I speculate to be the leader.
That rude man who started calling me 'Dotachin'...
All right, fatty tuna!
The thing you're looking for isn't in that direction, you know.
Nerima Ward
I'm so sorry, Selty...
How much do you think we can get for that guy?
A real bargain, I'm sure.
I guess you're right...
Is that them?
I think so.
What the hell?!
Kaztano!
Kaztano! I'm coming to save you!
Think it'll be that easy?
Prepare for trouble!
You hear that? That's so old school!
"Prepare for trouble"?
T-The headless monster!
We picked an old guy despite the shitty pay on purpose!
We won't do it again! We won't do it again!
What the hell?
Kaztano!
Dotachino!
They're getting away!
Don't even think you're getting away!
Turning right!
I wonder if I can go home now...
You should hurry up and tell us
where you're delivering the goods.
No no no, it'll be boring if they spill it without us torturing them.
Well, please pick a book.
We're going to torture you with a method relating to the plot of the one you pick.
Hey! I don't care what you do, but don't be using gasoline inside the car like last time!
Gaso-!
Togusano!
Let's perform the morning ritual!
I'll tell you! I will!
Please, let me tell you!!
Yagiri Pharmacy, eh?
Place is pretty grand.
Is this really the place where they
hold the human experimentations?
We were doubtful.
At least, from the exterior...
But most things have both a light side and a dark side.
Especially here, in Ikebukuro,
there are so many things hidden in the darkness.
Well, want to go grab something to eat?
Good idea!
Let's grab breakfast at Russia Sushi!
Sounds good! Let's go!
Sounds like that's that.
Use however much of the money you want, and whenever you want.
Thanks, sis.
Bye, Seiji.
Let's go.
Those are the details of the "Kaztano incident", as people may call it.
Well, for now...
...we're glad we got our friend back safe and sound.
Trust me...
I really wanna be with you.
Trust me... Yeah!
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
I can hear the voice of your heart.
This love will always stay true.
Don't hesitate to cry and rely on me.
I decided long ago to carry all your burdens.
(I'm here) Wherever you are,
(Call me) we'll be together.
(Trust me) These feelings for you will never change.
(My tear) Just put down
(Trust me) those bags you're carrying.
I exist for your sake.
(I'm here) I'm right here.
(Call me) I'm right beside you.
(Trust me) You don't need to be afraid.
(My tear) We're connected by
(Trust me) an invisible thread,
so feel my warmth by your side.
This is a work of fiction. Any similarity or likeness to any events or persons living or dead is purely coincidental.
Dullalala!!
Next Time
Strongest Man Alive
Shut up.
You're annoying.
You piss me off.
If I can't hold back my anger, my body moves by itself.
I don't care what happens to me.
Next time: Strongest Man Alive.
But I hate violence!