I have an announcement to make!
Once I, Aisaka Taiga, am elected
student council president,
I'll take over the school
and stick your high school
experience and damn memories...
in a m-moggu...morgue!
The Palm-top Tiger's gonna be
student council president!?
Oh snap! For the love of all that is holy!
I'm in charge of her campaign!
Any complaints, direct them to me!
Hey, it's Kitamura.
He announced that he's skipping the
election and quitting the student council.
Is that why the Palm-top Tiger's running?
I'll show no mercy to anyone
who gets in my way!
Doggone it!
If the Palm-top Tiger becomes president,
our high school experience will be ruined!
Is there no one willing to run against her!?
Yeah! If only Kitamura would run!
Why isn't he, anyway?
We're begging you, run!
They'll ruin our high school experience!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
A plan to bait Kitamura?
One Step Forward
Yes, we thought that if we created
a situation that's bad for everyone,
he'd have no choice but
to run in the election.
So, you think convincing Kitamura-kun
to become president will fix him?
We're not the only ones who feel this way.
We called everyone in the
class last night to explain.
They're all on board.
That would explain your little performance.
But what'll happen if
Kitamura-kun doesn't run?
If nobody else announces their candidacy
before the Friday deadline,
you'll become student council
president, Aisaka-san.
Kitamura-kun isn't the kind of person
to stand back and ignore everything.
All right.
Stop by the faculty office later.
I'll teach you how to use the printer.
You'll need to make posters
and campaign flyers, right?
Messenger from Hell
Taiga the Terrible
Demonic Pact
Aisaka Taiga's Ideal School Order
Man...
Kitamura's so stubborn...
I figured this would be enough
to get him to act...
Campaign Speech
Tomorrow's the last day...
Is there nothing else we can do?
I don't know.
I have no idea anymore...
Hello?
Uh, is this Takasu-kun's phone?
Uh, yeah...
Sorry.
This is the first time we've spoken.
I'm Murase from the student council.
From the student council?
I see...
Thank you for telling me.
Ryuji?
What was that about?
Ryuji...?
Where are you going?
To slug the crap out of Kitamura!
Hey, wait...
President Kano will be leaving this
school next week to study abroad.
I think Kitamura might be...
Frickin' idiot!
Takasu?
Sorry that I never told you.
That's cold, Kitamura.
I was too ashamed to admit...
that all this is because I'm
in love with the president.
I heard she's going to America next week.
Yeah, she wants to become an astronaut.
A professor from an astronautics
department invited her to enroll.
Crazy stuff.
She never said a word to me...
Truth be told, I was going to wait till I'd
been elected and earned her approval...
before telling her how I feel.
But she'll be gone by the time that happens.
So there's really no point...
Once that hit me, I just wanted
to give up on everything.
Destroy everything...
So you bleached your hair?
My dad finally snapped today.
Gave me a good "talking to,"
as you can probably tell.
I'm such an idiot.
It's not like I could convince her to stay.
Nothing goes the way you want it to...
Where'd that come from?
Well...
I had a similar conversation
with Taiga a while back.
The two of us were talking about how
nothing ever goes as planned.
Taiga ended up losing her cool
and kicked down a lamppost.
How like her.
She's really something...
Maybe...
I might feel better if
I let Aisaka kick me...
Ryuji!
Hey, stupid dog!
Taiga.
I know what you guys are doing.
Because of me, Aisaka's
running for class president...
And everyone's worried about me...
I can't let things go on like this.
I'm going home.
Thanks for listening.
Kitamura!
I'm okay.
I'll make this decision on my own.
I'll see you at school tomorrow.
Jeez, there you are!
What were you doing here?
Don't tell me you actually
beat Kitamura-kun up...
No...
Then what was that phone call about?
Not saying.
Now!
Tomorrow's election day!
If any of you refuse to vote for me,
I'll chase you into the depths of hell!
Got it?
- This school belongs to—
- Ta-Taiga!
Kitamura...
Kitamura-kun...
Sorry about all the fuss, you guys.
I'm okay now.
No!
I cannot allow this outrage to continue!
I, Kitamura Yusaku, will lead this
school down a good and noble path!
Kitamura-kun...
So you've made up your mind...
Kitamura...
Are you sure there isn't
some kind of mistake?
I'm positive.
Kitamura-kun hasn't turned in the
application to run for office.
If he intends to run, the rules require
him to submit it by four o'clock.
Excuse me.
- I need to go!
- Wait, Takasu-kun!
What's up, Takasu?
Aisaka and the gang went home already.
They mentioned something about
a new cafe by the station.
You have until four to
turn in the application.
What are you going to do?
Will you really just—
Let's go home, Takasu.
You sure?
There's still time for you
to change your mind—
I spent the whole day thinking,
and I've decided to give up.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Kitamura...
We haven't walked home together in ages.
The last time was when we were freshmen.
The student council's kept you busy.
Come to think of it, I
never did tell you why...
I joined the student council.
Oh, true.
I was so psyched when
I first came to this school.
Set to make a splash here and all that.
And finding a girlfriend would be the first
step to an enjoyable high school experience.
That's when I heard about this incredibly
beautiful girl in another class.
So I ran off to profess my love...
But I guess I already told you this part.
Yeah...
I was feeling pretty down
after Aisaka rejected me.
That's when...she appeared.
I saw everything, newcomer!
Worry not!
Your high school experience
has only just begun!
Join the student council!
She dragged me down to
the student council office,
saying she'd get me back on my feet
by burying me in menial tasks.
Since then, every day's been a blast.
I've managed to become
good friends with Aisaka,
and successfully made my high
school experience fun.
The shaky first step I took after receiving
the president's encouragement...
wasn't for nothing.
But after all that...
Now...
I'm too scared to take the next step.
So you're going to run away?
What about the kids who believe
you'll be the next president?
You're just going to ditch them?
Is that the kind of man you are!?
Haven't you already lifted your foot,
preparing to step forward?
Then you only have one option!
Finish taking that next step!
Don't you slack.
I'll be watching to see what kind
of president you'll become.
What was that about?
Takasu, what time is it?
3:58 p.m.
Showing up at the very last second...
Student Council President
Candidacy Application
like a superstar.
Sorry, something's come up.
Yeah.
We will now hear the presidential
candidates deliver their speeches.
Since the other candidate
pulled out of the race,
Student Council President Election Speeches
Kitamura Yusaku-san from 2-C is
the only remaining candidate.
Please take the stage.
As you all just heard, I'm Kitamura Yusaku.
Well...
I am...
No...
I'm...
President...
I am...
in love with you!
I'm standing here right now because...
I fell in love with you!
Before you leave, I have
to know how you feel!
Do I have any chance at all!?
Do we share a special bond!?
Please, tell me!
Did he just confess his love?
Kano, answer him!
Yeah! Answer him!
Say something, Kano-san!
Well? How about it?
And there you have it.
Kitamura Yusaku, our very
own vice president.
Fun guy, yeah?
This school will be a lot more fun with
a fun guy like him as president.
So please vote for Mr. Fun, here!
Kano-senpai!
Why...?
Why didn't you answer his question?
Yesterday...
You told Kitamura to take
the next step, didn't you?
So, why?
I told him to run in the election.
Not to confess his love.
You're going to run away!?
A person who's honest to a
fault will struggle in life...
Kitamura needs to learn to live wisely.
You're a good friend.
Please continue to support him.
Wait!
I'm not finished!
Taiga?
Kitamura-kun was crying.
Please, Ryuji.
You should be by his side right now.
I can't do it.
I can't be by his side.
What...
What about you?
I'm fine...
I mean it.
Go to Kitamura-kun.
But...
Go!
I can never have what I want.
As I realized that and stood frozen in place,
Kitamura-kun took my hand and smiled.
He's such a kind person.
A thousand thanks wouldn't be
enough to show how grateful I am.
I realize I'm not the one in his heart...
But...
I want to do what I can...
Just like Kitamura-kun did for me...
Kano!
- Sumire!
- What the—!? The Palm-top Tiger!?
Why is she here?
Am I...
doing the wrong thing?
The fight is on!
I see there's still one fool
left for me to deal with.
Very well.
I'll take you on.
I happen to be in an irritable mood.
- Kendo-clubber. Your wooden sword.
- I don't know if I'm doing the wrong thing...
All I do know...
is that I can't stop myself anymore.
Is that Takasu guy here!?
We need you!
The Palm-top Tiger is...!
You fool!
Stop calling us fools!
You're just a coward!
You're scared of getting hurt!
And of hurting others!
Your cowardice! Your spinelessness!
Those hurt Kitamura-kun!
I won't accept that!
I'll never let you get away with this!
Stop it, Taiga!
Let me go!
Oh, man...
- What's going on!?
- Taiga!?
Spineless!
Coward!
Weakling who can't face her own feelings!
I can live with that!
You're a simple-minded, violent psychopath!
Still better than you!
Say it!
If you refuse to accept Kitamura-kun's
feelings, say that you hate him!
Say it!
How could you possibly
understand how I feel!?
I'd die to be as simple-minded as you!
I'd die to be a fool who only
knows how to barge ahead!
If I told him I feel the same way,
that imbecile would chase after me!
If he knew that's what I want, he'd do it!
Even if it means sacrificing
his own hopes and dreams!
That's how he is...
And that's why...
That's why I can never become a fool!
You've always been too kind.
I loved you from the bottom of my heart.
I'm truly glad that I had the
chance to fall in love with you.
Thank you for everything!
Until the teachers raced over
to take control of the situation,
we weren't able to do a single thing.
We're sorry for all the trouble we caused.
What's wrong?
I found a student handbook
while we were cleaning.
I think it's the tiger's.
Then leave it with Takasu-kun...
Oh, I guess he went
off with the teachers.
She really does love him...
Hmm? Underneath...
Give me that.
I'll return it.
Let's go back to class.
Guilt all gone?
Kano-senpai spent her last day
at our school with a bruised face.
Two days later, she left for America.
Kitamura was dubbed the most
unfortunate guy on campus,
and elected student council president.
Also...
Taiga got suspended for two weeks.
Write an apology letter.
- Yuri
banira sorutode
Add vanilla salt.
BURNING LOVE
Burning Love
amai dakenara
If it's too sweet,
soruto kakemashou
we can add some salt.
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I tell you all these things because
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
modokashi sugiru
This is so frustrating.
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
But a love that's purely sweet
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
shiroto iwaretara
If you say white,
kurodatte icchau
I say black.
sunaoni narenai
A little imp
amanojaku
who can't be honest to herself.
sukito iwaretara
If you say love,
daikirai datte
I say hate.
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
soruto kakeru youni
to sweet vanilla...
Sumire, there's a postcard for you.
Fool.
Mercury is Retrograde
at Christmas
Christmas!
The lovely angel Taiga will
help you win romance!
I'm even willing to shed a layer
or two, if that's what it takes!
It'll mean more work for me if you
catch a cold, so keep your clothes on.