On that day, mankind received a grim reminder.
We lived in fear of the Titans,
disgraced to cower within the cages we called Walls.
Everyone, get ready to fight!
There's only one target!
We will exterminate it and make this mankind's first outside base!
Target approaching!
Split into fives! Remember your training!
We'll distract the target!
All attack teams, prepare to move up!
We'll close in on it from the sides!
Have a taste of mankind's strength!
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
To You, 2000 Years From Now
Fall of Shiganshina (pt 1)
Huh? Mikasa?
We should start heading back.
What am I doing here?
Were you sleeping that soundly?
No, it just feels like I was having a really long dream.
What was it about?
I can't remember.
Eren, why are you crying?
Huh?
Year 845
Shiganshina District
Hear ye! These Walls were built in accordance with God's wisdom!
The Walls are the work of God himself!
No soul shall dare desecrate the Walls!
Don't tell anyone that I was crying.
I won't.
But if you were crying and you don't know why,
maybe you should bring it up with your dad.
Are you kidding?
I can't tell my dad about this!
What were you crying about, Eren?
Hannes...
Did you piss off Mikasa?
What?
Why would I be crying?
You reek of booze!
Nothin' wrong with that.
You're drinking again?
Wanna join us?
Uh... Aren't you on duty?
Yeah, we're guarding the gates today.
We've been here all day, so we were bound to get hungry and thirsty eventually.
And so what if we happen to drink a little alcohol? No sweat off my back.
But if you're drunk, how will you be able to fight?
Huh? When would we have to fight?
When else?!
When they breach the Wall and invade the city!
Ouch...
Eren, don't just start yelling like that.
You've sure got spirit, doctor's kid.
If they ever breached the Wall, we'd get our jobs done.
But you know what?
Not once in the past hundred years has that happened.
Still!
My dad said that as soon as you lower your guard, you put yourself in danger!
Dr. Jaeger said that?
Well, he's right.
He once saved our whole town from an epidemic.
We are truly in his debt.
But these Titans are another matter.
I see Titans walking around all the time when I go up to maintain the Wall.
But I don't think they can do anything to overcome this 50-meter Wall.
S-So... You don't even have the will to fight them?
Nope.
What the hell?!
You should just start calling yourselves the Wall Repair Corps, rather than the Garrison!
That's got a nice ring to it.
But Eren, when people see soldiers fighting, that means something bad is going on.
Everyone's much better off when they can call us useless freeloaders and good-for-nothings.
I know. We might get to never leave these Walls,
but as long as we can eat and sleep, we'll survive.
But... We're living our lives...
just like livestock!
This kid's sure got a mouth on him!
Not that he can do shit to back it up, eh, Hannes?
Uh, right.
Hey, Eren!
You're one strange kid!
Don't tell me... He wants to join the Recon Corps?
Eren, you should forget about entering the Recon Corps.
What? Now you think they're stupid too?
It's not that I'm calling them stupid or anything...
The Recon Corps is back!
The front gate's opening!
Let's go, Mikasa! The heroes have returned!
Shit! I can't see.
Only this many of them made it back?
The rest must've been eaten.
That's what happens when you venture outside the Wall.
Moses? Moses!
My son, Moses... I don't see him anywhere.
Where can I find him?
This is Moses' mother.
Bring it here.
That was the only part of him we could salvage.
But... my son... did his part, right?
Even if he wasn't a hero,
at least he died helping mankind fight back, right?!
Of course!
No...
During this mission, we...
No, even after all of our missions,
we still haven't made any progress!
I'm a failure.
I've been getting soldiers killed left and right!
And we still haven't learned anything useful about the Titans!
Damn, that was brutal.
Seriously.
It's like all our tax dollars go to feeding the Titans now.
What was that for, kid?
Hey! What are you doing, Mikasa?
Hey, get back here!
Mikasa, that's enough already!
What was that for?
All the firewood got spilled!
Eren...
Have you changed your mind about joining the Recon Corps?
Help me pick these up.
There's hardly enough to bother.
Currently Disclosable Information
Regarding Walls (1)
Mankind lives encircled by three layers of Walls.
The outermost ring is Wall Maria.
The middle ring is Wall Rose.
Finally, the innermost ring,
protecting the center, is Wall Sina.
Currently Disclosable Information
Regarding Walls (2)
The spacing of the Walls is nearly equidistant.
There's 100km between Maria and Rose,
130km between Rose and Sina,
and 250km between Sina and the center.
We're back.
Welcome home.
Wow, Eren.
I'm surprised you gathered so much firewood today.
Y-Yeah.
What was that for?
Your ears turned red.
You were lying.
Mikasa helped you out, didn't she?
Huh? Dad, are you going somewhere?
Work?
Yeah. I'm going inside the Wall to see patients.
I'll be gone for two or three days.
Eren wants to join the Recon Corps.
Mikasa, you traitor!
Eren!
What are you thinking?!
Do you know how many people have died outside the Walls?
Of course I do!
You clearly don't!
Eren.
Why do you want to venture outside?
I want to know what the world out there is like.
I don't want to live my entire life confined within these Walls!
On top of that, if no one follows in their footsteps,
everyone who lost their lives so far will have died in vain!
I see.
It's time for my ferry.
I must be going.
Wait, dear!
Help me dissuade Eren!
Carla, the spirit of human curiosity isn't something that you can restrain with words.
Eren.
When I get back, I'll show you what I've been hiding in the basement all this time.
For real?
Have a safe trip!
I won't let you.
Joining the Recon Corps? Don't be stupid!
Huh? Stupid?!
If you ask me who's stupid, it's the people who're content with living like livestock!
Eren!
Mikasa, that boy never thinks before he acts.
When you get into trouble, please look out for each other.
Okay.
What's wrong, heretic?
If you don't like it, punch me back!
Like I'd ever do that.
I won't stoop to your level.
Say that again!
You're beating me up because you know I'm right, and you can't say a thing to refute me.
Doesn't that mean you've admitted that you're wrong?
I'll shut your smart mouth for good!
Stop it!
It's Eren.
That moron! He's back for more?
Does he want another ass-kicking?
Let's give it to him!
Mi-Mikasa's with him!
Shit! Run!
Hey, they ran away when they saw me!
No, they took off once they saw Mikasa.
Ow.
Hey, you okay, Armin?
I can stand up on my own.
Oh, sorry.
So, after I said that mankind would need to go outside eventually,
they called me a heretic and beat me up.
Damn it.
We just want to go outside. Why is that such a big deal?
Well, the sanctuary of the Walls has let us live peacefully for the past century.
Allowing people to freely travel outside the Wall creates more chances for them to get inside,
so the King's government declared all interest in the outside world taboo.
We're only risking our own lives!
It's our decision!
I won't let you.
No way.
Oh, and you! Why'd you rat me out to my parents?
I don't remember ever saying I'd help you.
H-How did that go?
Well, they weren't exactly thrilled.
No kidding.
In truth, my concern is that people believe these Walls will protect us forever.
Mama!
Even though the Wall hasn't been breached for a hundred years,
there's no guarantee that today won't be the day it all comes crashing down.
Wh-What was that?
An explosion?
Over there!
Did something fall?
I'm not sure.
Hey, Armin!
What happened?
What the hell are you staring at?
You're kidding... That Wall is 50 meters high!
It's them ...
The Titans!
I-It... It broke right through the Wall.
They're coming!
Titans are getting inside!
We need to get—
Eren!
My house is over there.
Mom is...
Mikasa!
It's all over.
This town will be overrun by the Titans!
No way my house got hit!
Once I turn this corner, my house will be there... Like always!
Mom!
Eren...
Mikasa, grab that side.
We need to move this pillar.
Hurry, Mikasa!
I know!
The Titans are getting inside.
Eren, take Mikasa and run.
Hurry!
I want to run too!
So hurry up and get out!
My legs were crushed under the debris.
I couldn't run even if I got free.
You understand, don't you?
Then I'll carry you while I run!
Why won't you just heed your mother for once?!
Please listen to me! Just one last time!
Mikasa!
No... No!
At this rate, all three of us will...
Hannes!
Take the kids and run!
Don't take me lightly, Carla.
I'll kill the Titan and save all three of you.
Wait! Don't fight it!
It's true. I could just save those two kids.
But this is my opportunity to repay my debt to them!
Hey, Hannes!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Thank you.
Mom's still trapped in there!
Eren! Mikasa!
You must live on!
Don't go...
Stop!
On that day, mankind received a grim reminder.
We lived in fear of the Titans,
disgraced to cower within the cages we called Walls.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
Shiganshina has fallen.
All that remains for mankind is to pray, scream, and die.
In the midst of this, Eren swears vengeance within his young heart.
That Day
Fall of Shiganshina (pt 2)