saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
People I'm thankful to...
My presence is required!
This is a present from me!
I-I lost...
You bind him with a scarf
embedded with wires...
She's asleep!
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
Valentine's Fest
It's finally the season, huh?
It certainly is.
The season of wanting winter to end
so I can save on my heating bill...
That's not what I meant...
Didn't we just
have this conversation?
It's almost Valentine's!
Valentine's is an important day!
It's the day to chow down
on chocolate...
That's not what
Valentine's Day is about.
I've also heard
this conversation before...
Miss Youko, are you going
to give chocolate to anyone?
I wasn't planning on it.
It's not a big deal.
You just give it
to people you're thankful to.
I see.
People I'm thankful to...
A Day to Chow Down
on Chocolate
I just remembered.
Something happened
the other day...
Oh, my.
It's stuck up in the tree.
Wh-What should I do?
It's really high up.
The tree looks thin, so it might not
be able to support my weight.
But I must rescue it!
My presence is required!
No more time to waste
on these trifling matters!
Trifling matters?
So in the end,
Yamaji helped me rescue the cat.
What? Shouldn't I have been
the one to get that event?
Event?
So what happened to the cat?
Well, after we got it down,
it ran away.
I can't believe it.
So that's how it all ends?!
I apologize I couldn't
meet your expectations.
You triggered the flag
for it to repay you someday.
Repay me?
You know, like stories of animals
who repay people for saving them.
My, it would be so cute
if the kitten came to repay me.
That would be lovely.
Like...
I got this fish for you.
Here!
Salted salmon?
I got this cash for you. Here!
Cash?
I guess I'll let you
touch my paw pads... just this once!
That's it?
And she gave it a personality too!
Where's Yamaji?
Huh? Y-Yamaj—
At your service.
Yamaji!
Y-Yes?
Um, this might be
a weird request.
If...
If the kitten comes to repay you,
please capture the moment!
I'm not sure I understand.
Please!
Teru.
Teru!
What? Bel?!
Teru, thanks for always
taking care of me!
I'm so happy that you took me in
and were so kind to me.
So... here.
This is a present from me!
Those sounded like
Bel's last words!
I guess it was because of
Miss Youko's story.
Well, it wasn't a bad dream.
Thank you...
That's what happened
this morning.
My!
Good for you, Hayama.
She was repaying you.
You're right.
Of course, cats show their love
differently than humans.
It takes a good owner to be able
to understand and accept that.
Once an animal lover,
always an animal lover.
You're a model pet owner.
I can't just let that one slide.
Hayama, a model pet owner?
That takes some nerve.
Oh, has El ever
brought you a repayment gift?
Of course she has!
But just having her
by my side is plenty.
Isn't that how
a pet owner should think?
Is it?
Nishiyama!
Then why don't you two have a competition
to see who cats like more?
What?
Bel Hayama (1 year old)
Didn't you take
pictures of your cats before?
Whoever takes
a cuter cat picture wins!
Hold still, Bel.
H-Hey, stay put!
The tendinitis in my wrists from holding
the camera since morning is quickly healing!
Master Beelzebub!
They're all so cute,
I can't decide!
They're all best shots!
I brought my pictures.
Me too.
Here are my best shots.
We'll judge the results.
Oh, they're cute.
So cute!
They are very cute.
But this is like comparing
two peas from the same pod.
What do you mean?!
That's not true!
Well, she is cute.
Yes, so cute!
I guess it might be a tie.
Can I have this?
Yeah, let's trade!
You won't get a real competition
between two cat fans, I guess.
What was the competition even for?
Well, we got something out of it,
so we're both winners.
Oh. Well, if we're looking
for a competition...
Futaba Odagiri!
We have a competitor.
The older Tsuji.
You're probably going
to challenge me, huh?
Well, this time, I'll challenge you!
What?!
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo
Hamburg
Steaks
Jumbo hamburg!
You're on!
Steaks
They wouldn't let me in!
Is this one of the places
you're banned from?
Oh, that's right!
You had forgotten?
They let me in,
which means
that I win by default!
Total victory for me! Oh yeah!
Woohoo! Oh yeah!
I-I lost...
Hang on.
Think about it for a second.
I didn't lose! They wouldn't let me in
because I'm a bigger threat!
Hey, hold it!
You didn't win!
Think about it!
Well, congratulations on your win.
Oh, uh, what was your name?
Ni... Ni... Nishi-something?
How do you know my name?
He only said the "Nishi" part, though.
It's "Nishikawa"! Ni-shi-ka-wa!
And that's Miss Youko Nishikawa.
Don't leave out the "Miss,"
you glutton!
Yamaji! Pipe down!
That's pretty cool.
It's just like Sasame told me.
Oh, you heard from your sister.
Yup. You're, uh,
one of her friends, right?
What?!
Well, thanks for
taking care of my sister.
Oh. Well, er...
It's my... pleasure!
Miss Youko is being considerate!
Sasame!
Guess what!
I won against Odagiri!
You didn't win.
Based on what you said,
that doesn't count as winning.
What?!
B-But she congratulated me.
You know, uh, Nishi... hara...
kawa... tani?
It's Nishikawa.
Yeah, Nishikawa.
And I was even polite and told her
thanks for always taking care of my sister!
What?!
That's what a big bro would do.
I was super adult-like.
You idiot!
Huh?
Why'd you say that to her?
You probably
made her feel awkward!
Wasn't that
the polite thing to say?
Yeah, if we were friends already.
Nishikawa and I
aren't that close yet.
Really?
You idiot!
We're still
building our friendship!
I didn't even say any—
Hey, Sasame!
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Do you have any good ideas?
When I give Yuu the chocolates,
I want it to be memorable.
Memorable, huh?
I wonder how many kinds of chocolates
I can eat with my allowance this year—
I'm not talking about you!
Don't you think a hand-knitted scarf
and homemade chocolate would be best?
What? Isn't that too normal?
Is it?
You bind him with a scarf embedded with wires and force-feed him drugged chocolate.
Whoa.
Hayama!
So that's the plan?
Well, off I go!
I need to get ready.
Be careful on your way home.
Thank you!
Ahh, that's what
Miss Usuda is planning?
Young Master Takezono
will have a fine Valentine's Day.
I-I also want to...
I also want to make chocolate.
Apologies, but my hearing
has declined recently.
Chocolate!
I want to make chocolate!
Ah, I see.
You want to store it
as emergency rations.
No, for Valentine's!
And to whom
will you be giving them?
My friends.
And I'll send a mountain
of chocolates to Father too.
You're going mountain climbing?
No, I'm talking about Valentine's!
Oh, Sonobe.
I want to make chocolate.
Good.
This time of year
is as busy as Christmas,
so even you could be a big help.
Not for the shop!
I want to give homemade chocolate
to people I'm thankful for.
Of course, I won't slack off
on my duties here.
Miss Youko wants to make
chocolate from scratch?
She'll probably
start off energetically,
but end up worn out because
she's not used to making sweets.
And then she'll be sick in bed,
and I'll be even busier on Valentine's
than on Christmas!
That's my situation.
Please, you'll be such a big help!
No way! Why do I have to?
You can just ask someone else.
You're the right person
for the job.
What?!
You don't have anything to do
on Valentine's anyway, right?
How rude!
What are you doing?
I was asking Nishiyama
to give me a hand at the shop.
I can help!
You don't have to pay me either.
What?
I'll take my compensation in cakes.
No, thank you. I will pay you.
Aww, too bad.
I'd love to have
your help too, Hayama.
As long as I don't
have to wear that maid outfit.
All... right... mm... hmm...
I can't hear you!
All right, let's work hard today!
Yes!
Miss Youko didn't faint
from exhaustion.
What?
Hey!
Why am I stuck wearing this?!
Oh, good; it fits perfectly.
This isn't what we agreed on!
You didn't want to wear this maid outfit,
so I prepared a different one for you.
It's fine. It looks good!
I agree.
I wanted to make some for you two as well,
but I didn't have enough time.
Is prepping
for Valentine's that tough?
I pulled two all-nighters
making Hayama's new maid outfit.
Don't blame me!
Thank you for waiting.
We'll allow people to enter in order,
so please be patient.
Welcome!
I can ring you up here once you've decided
what items you'd like.
Wait, how did I get roped into this too?
Look around you.
This place is seriously busy.
What about that other guy?
The former butler?
My apologies!
I have my hands full with making
a special chocolate cake for Miss Youko.
Why are you making that now?!
Excuse me, Sonobe?
She's asleep!
She said she hasn't slept
in two nights.
How can she be sleeping
when it's this busy?
It's fine.
You always come through
in the clutch!
Y-You bet!
Welcome!
So easily manipulated...
I apologize for the long wait.
Don't worry.
It's Valentine's, after all.
Keep it up!
Thank you very much!
I-It's so busy!
Sonobe.
Wake up, Sonobe!
Sonobe!
Oh, you're already tired, Hayama?
How undisciplined.
You're amazing, Nishiyama.
Of course.
I'm just getting started.
I'm going to take
a short break, then.
Wha—?!
Excuse me.
Y-Yes, how can I help you?
She always comes through
in the clutch!
She makes life hard for herself.
Thank you very much.
One limited edition
gâteau chocolat.
Okay, one gâteau chocolat.
Huh? It's the Tsuji siblings.
What are you doing here?
I-It's not a big deal for a guy
to buy Valentine's cakes.
Yeah, who cares?
There's a bunch of stuff you can only get
around Valentine's and Christmas.
He saves up for this!
Doesn't it take courage for a guy to buy
chocolate-flavored things around Valentine's?
I don't really care.
I get tons of chocolate at school,
so it doesn't bother me.
Wow, that's unexpected.
Yeah. He's popular at school.
Even in my club,
I'm an important mascot character!
Ahh...
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Sorry.
I just wanted to see
Nishiyama hard at work.
Nothing interesting to see here.
Then would you like
to start working here too?
She's awake?!
No thanks, that's not my thing.
Reconsider and I'll throw in a dessert.
Not her thing?
Oh, no thank you.
Sold out.
Thank you very much!
Everyone,
thank you for working so hard.
I got to catch up on sleep
thanks to you!
Sonobe!
On your knees!
February 14th
Yesterday was pretty tiring.
I want to try on
a maid outfit sometime too.
Maybe I'll ask Sonobe next time.
Won't work.
Huh?
Miss Youko said that she just enjoys
forcing it on unwilling people.
Ah, I see.
So that's why Nishiyama
always ends up a maid!
Nishiyama... a maid? No way.
Sh-She asked me to wear it,
and that was the only thing she had.
I-I wasn't wearing it
because I wanted to.
Ah, now I get it.
What are you talking about?!
I never want to wear
those clothes again.
I didn't enjoy it one bit.
Y-Yeah, right?
It fit you size-wise,
but it didn't look very good.
It looked like
the clothes were wearing you.
You look better
in more straight-cut clothes.
Y-Yeah, that's right.
I thought it looked
pretty good on you.
D-Don't make fun of me!
Nishiyama!
I actually think that, though.
She's not used to you
complimenting her.
Thank you
for all your help yesterday.
This is to show my gratitude
for everything you've done for me.
Here!
Oh, is this that charcoal stuff
to get rid of odors?
They're truffles!
I made them from scratch.
What?!
I poured all my gratitude into them.
Miss Youko made these
from scratch?
They don't melt,
but they're edible.
Right? I can do it if I try.
You're amazing, Miss Youko!
It's not melting?
Not really.
Oh, Tsuji!
Here you go.
What?!
Chocolates? F-For me?
Yes. I hope you like them.
Nishikawa gave me chocolates!
Wh-Wh-What should I
give her in return?
How much should my return gift cost?
Triple? More?
Maybe a house or something?!
Here, Yamaji. These are for you.
What?!
I get some too?!
Thank you very much!
I'll offer them on the family altar!
You can just eat them.
Father should be getting
his chocolates today too.
And that's all of them!
Hmm?
What?
That's all?
What about me?
Where are my gratitude chocolates?
Miss Youko?!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if it's turned black inside
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if I can't be extravagant
ryou ga ookutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
sannin dakara tabechaou
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm not wasting electricity at night
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
egao ni nareru mono
Things that make me smile?
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
Food! Money! And things I can't say
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
Let's have fun and make silly memories
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
Will continue forever in just the same way
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
If you want to know the answer to one times three
nee koko ni oide
Then come on over here
Next week is the last episode
of Sansha Sanyou!
Let's have Miss Youko
say the title.
Okay, I will.
Next time, "I Am Graduating
From Bread Crusts."
I hope you enjoy it.
Well, that'll never happen.
Next
Time:
I Am Graduating
From Bread Crusts
Next
Time:
I Am Graduating
From Bread Crusts
Nope.
It will!