And so, with their promised kisses fulfilled,
they were guided by the star of love to set forth beyond severance.
Hey, Mom. What kind of story are you writing?
A story of you and that girl who taught us of Kumaria-sama.
This is the final page.
Who's that girl?
The girl you care so much for.
You were just telling me about how you sang the song of love together.
I don't know any girl like that.
What?
Kureha, it couldn't be...
Have you forgotten about her?
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Storm!
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shite
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so give me your approval
kaze ni notte ehon no page ga
As pages from a picture book flutter in the wind
kagirinaku kioku wo yurasu no
so sway my countless memories along with them
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
kurai kono sekai no naka
in this dark world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
If only I could've shown you the face
Tsubaki Kureha made at that moment.
I love this pleasure you taught me.
You found me from amongst countless others.
I'm no longer one of the weak girls who can only be blown about by the Invisible Storm.
They couldn't possibly exclude someone so precious to you. Isn't that right?
Bear Shock!
Beware
Porridge, start to boil up.
Bubble, bubble, boil up.
Growl, growl, growl!
Since that day, we've officially been accepted as Kurechin's freeloaders.
Yes, we have finally come this far!
Just one more push until
Ginko gets her promised kiss!
Flashback
I won't... back down on love!
Yurishiro-san.
Why did you protect Sumika's letter?
What made you risk your life?
Yuri Amour!
Yurishiro-san?
Thank goodness, you've come to!
Um...
I will tell you of my love.
So long as you don't forget love, you will never be alone.
So long as you don't back down on love, even if you were to lose something, you won't become invisible.
Where did you hear that?
You are my Kumaria-sama.
Kumaria-sama?
You mean... from the picture book?
Deliciousmell.
You reek, Kureha. Growl.
Search for that which you desire.
That which I desire?
Yes.
What am I searching for? Where am I searching?
You know the answer.
Remember with your fingers, with your lips,
and with... this place.
Now, bestow upon me the promised kiss.
The promised kiss...
From me to you?
And from me to you.
With this, everything shall awaken, and everything shall change.
What was I just...
No, such an awful dream...
Growl! I finished making the honey porridge.
Kurechin, what's wrong? You're red up to your ears.
I-It's just the lighting.
In any case, keep watch over Yurishiro-san; she's sweating quite badly. Goodbye.
Kumaria-sama...
Why did I see such a dream?
Kureha, did you play nicely with your friend today?
I did, Mom! Today, I taught her how to sing the song of love!
My, that song?
Yep!
That girl is my precious friend. She's special to me!
I see. You must really care for that girl, Kureha.
Yeah, I love her!
That girl!
Who is... that girl?
Why have I forgotten until now?
Without doubt, I used to have a friend.
Please tell me, Mom.
Who is... that girl?
There was another bear attack!
No way. Wasn't it exterminated?
By that girl, um... the student with the gun.
Oh, the girl who brings misfortune to her friends?
Listen, it was another girl from her class that got killed!
Seriously?
Seriously.
Spill the beans. Who was it?
What? Harishima-san?
Yes. She was found before the garden this morning.
Her wounds indicate a bear attack.
But how... didn't I kill it?
The only conclusion is that there are other bears hiding within this academy.
How fearsome.
The bears took not only Reia's life, but also the proof of our love,
her star pendant.
Yuriika-sensei...
The bear who holds Reia's pendant is our foe.
When you finally find it one day...
I will kill it.
Come to think of it, didn't you have something to ask?
Yes, about my past... a friend I used to have.
A past friend?
That's right. I recalled her while
listening to my mother's music box.
A precious friend I had as a child.
I can only remember her as "that girl".
For some reason, her name and face escape me.
I thought you might have an inkling.
Thinking back, I do seem to recall Reia saying something strange just before her passing.
I believe she said that you had suddenly forgotten about your friend.
And also... yes, it was about her picture book, The Moon Girl and The Forest Girl.
She told me that she wrote it based upon you and that friend of yours.
A story of me and that girl?
Ginko, stay strong.
Growlsob. Her fever isn't breaking.
I know!
These'll chill you right down and make you feel better!
I'm such a genius!
Flashback
Kumaria-sama is love itself.
She is the Mother of the world, approving all living beings and providing them with her love.
The little cub found during a blizzard was named Ginko after the silver snow that brought it.
Several Years Later
HISTORY
Hey, Ginko.
You're an unwanted bear.
Nobody will ever find you!
You're the queen of being sad and lonely!
Yeah, what is this?
You tryin' to be queen of the loners or something?
Loner Queen.
Loner Queen!
Bear Shock!
Shut up!
That is how Ginko became truly alone.
In time, she came to be known as Loner Queen Ginko.
Loner Queen Ginko
BEAR
I understand. This world is ruled by power.
The weak will not receive kindness from anyone.
Survival of the fittest. Salmon eat salmon!
Kumami! It's dinner time!
Coming!
Kumako! Come on home!
Kumari!
Coming!
Kumargaret!
Kumacaron!
Coming!
Tonight we're having your favorite, salmon pizza!
I love salmon pizza!
You're a real cutie.
The world soon faced the Day of Severance.
All the bears with similar circumstances
gathered around the elder, Lady Kumaster.
Rejoice. You have all been found.
I shall give unto you unwanted cubs the opportunity to be approved.
Lady Kumaster
BEAR
There is but one in this entire world who needs you and will approve of you.
She is Kumaria-sama!
Kumaria-sama?
From this day on, you will be cubs of Kumaria-sama.
Live as the watchbears of the
boundary between bear and man.
Exclude those humans who should try and cross the boundary,
and protect our world.
That is Mother Kumaria-sama's mission for you.
Human excluded! Growl!
Headquarters, come in!
We request immediate reinforcements.
Bear excluded!
Ginko believed.
She believed that Kumaria-sama would give her approval if she fulfilled her mission,
and one day provide her with her love.
I'm no unwanted Loner Queen!
I'll eat more and more people
and be approved!
And one day, Kumaria-sama will provide me...
...with her love.
Beware
And so, the Moon Girl and the Forest Girl
looked up to the sky day after day.
Is the Forest Girl referring to that girl?
I can't remember.
Huh?
Kurechin, you're back.
Yeah.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
What are you reading?
A picture book my mother wrote.
Wow. Can I read it?
I don't mind, but this book has no end.
What do you mean?
The
Moon
Girl.
The
Moon
Girl.
and
The
Forest
Girl
The
Forest
Girl
My mother died before she could finish it.
She was killed by a bear.
I'm going to check up on Yurishiro-san.
Yurishiro-san.
Flashback
Because Ginko loves you, Kurechin!
Why?
Didn't we meet for the first time only recently?
I haven't done anything for you.
Your wounds and pain should have been mine.
Flashback
She's done for.
You're right. Let's exclude those who would be a burden.
Exclude them.
The world of animals is cruel.
Those without strength and those who don't adapt to those around them are excluded without mercy.
I see... I failed.
You are an unwanted bear. The Loner Queen.
Loner Queen.
Oh... I wasn't found.
I'm a bear who wasn't approved.
Will I die here without ever receiving love?
This is the song of love my mom taught me.
Don't worry.
You're not alone.
I'm your friend.
I love you.
Kumaria-sama...
Kumaria... sama?
Why do you know about the picture book?
Kureha...
Th-Thank goodness, you're finally awake.
Kureha, the song you were singing...
Um, well...
I'll go call Yurigasaki-san.
It's all finished!
Growl! The ginger milk is ready!
Once I mix in a heaping spoonful of honey, my honey ginger milk will be complete!
Look, it's ready.
Why don't you share a cup with your friend?
Yay!
Growl!
You two certainly do love honey ginger milk.
Yep! It's got the flavor we love!
What's wrong? You're spacing out.
I remembered something from my childhood.
An old friend...
We used to drink the honey ginger milk my mother made together here.
I'd long since forgotten how I felt back then.
But now I can remember that happiness.
Ginko too.
Honey ginger milk has the flavor Ginko loves too.
She said it's a flavor that reminds her she's not alone in this world.
A flavor that shines and glimmers like a star.
The flavor Yurishiro-san loves?
Growl! But it's not ready until I plop in the honey.
I'll go get some!
Why did I forget a friend who was that precious to me?
The
Moon
Girl
and
The
Forest
Girl
That's right... I loved her so much.
My honey ginger milk is gonna push
Ginko and Kurechin together all at once!
I'm such a genius!
The picture book Kurechin's mother wrote?
The Moon Girl and The Forest Girl.
Flashback
Kureha.
Is the Moon Girl Kureha?
Then does that make Ginko the Forest Girl?
Long ago, the world was split into two by the sky.
The Moon World and the Forest World.
You mustn't. The two worlds are severed.
It is prideful to attempt to cross them—
a grave sin.
This song...
It's Mom's song of love.
"There is but a single way to grant your wish.
If your love is true,
then your friend will be awaiting you beyond that door."
Kumaria-sama then asked the girls:
"Is your love true?"
I found you.
You were my friend.
You were that girl.
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger
Alright! Lulu's special honey ginger milk is ready!
What's this?
To
Cri
bear
mi
Crimibear?
"Yurishiro Ginko.
I know about the grave sin you committed. You..."
Ginko... you couldn't have!