Tsukuyomi Shrine work log.
Log keeper: Micchan.
Log keeper:
Micchan
(alias)
The head of the family keeps saying,
"I don't think I should put forth any effort,"
"Do I really have to try so hard? I'm human after all,"
and "It's always good to have some variety."
That alone wouldn't be a problem; but every time he'd looked at me
with that proud expression, as if he'd said something that was awe-inspiring.
I got carried away and raised my hand, then my mind went blank...
Hours had passed by in an instant, then
suddenly the next thing I could recollect,
was the head of the family kneeling down before me, stark naked.
Instead of Micchan, he now refers to me as Master.
Master
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 9
It's not that I can't do it
I'm an assassin of the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki.
I'm the spirit in this Sesshou golem! I'm the fair and golden nine-tailed fox!
The nine-tailed fox?
In this land you call me Tamamo-no-Mae, the one who plays with the scales.
Tamamo-no-Mae?
Hey, have you ever wanted to change the past?
The past?
I can't recall this event ever happening before.
So then...
Mom would never get caught like this!
I've been waiting for this moment!
I clung onto you when you were young,
and I've waited for an entire decade.
I had to wait until you decided that you wanted to change the past.
What do you mean?
I programmed myself so that your desire to change the past would wake me.
I'll use and live off the power of Amaterasu,
and transform the past to my liking.
Transform the past?
Yes, transform history! That's my power!
But I need tremendous power to do that.
It'd be impossible without leeching off of you and using your power of Amaterasu.
Transforming the past... Changing history is forbidden!
You mustn't do that!
But this is what you desired.
Tsukuyomi Sasami, you felt regret.
To regret is to abhor the mistakes of the past.
Amaterasu's regret warps spacetime.
You could even alter the past!
But...
Sure, I did regret...
I betrayed Mom.
I broke my promise and couldn't even allow my dead mother to rest in peace.
Originally at this time and place, this Sesshou golem didn't appear.
Do you understand the meaning of this?
The transformation of history has already begun.
The moment you felt regret, it was all over.
But...
I'll kill Tsukuyomi Juju now.
Then the power of Amaterasu within her will move to her daughter.
And her daughter, Tsukuyomi Sasami, just so happens to be in my hands!
That's the whole goal of transforming history!
We need to weaken our ancient
adversaries, the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
The power of Amaterasu is ours.
The Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki will grow further and further.
We may even help milady a little.
Milady?
And we of Arahabaki will rule the world, this planet and everything that encompasses it!
Are you nuts?
Just to oversee a single country, my mother worked herself to death.
I'm already at my limit, just having to live in my body!
And you want the world?
Don't make me laugh!
You! You can't do anything without changing the past!
There's not a single thing you can do!
You could never rule the world!
Is that all you had to say?
It is time for you to die now, Tsukuyomi Juju.
This is the end of the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Glory to Arahabaki!
I remember this day, this is when Mom died.
Good work there.
Tsurugi?
What's going on here?
Why am I in the past? Why am I in other people's bodies?
The past is getting transformed!
We don't have time for this.
Mom?
Yes. I am your mother.
I could not endure the foolishness of my daughter,
and have thus returned from the underworld.
Finally, you caught up?
What's going on?
Don't you remember? She gave you drugs by sticking her hand into your stomach.
Then, she inserted her totem into your body.
It's her lifeline, her gateway from the underworld.
There's something like that in me?
Is that what caused me to bloat up like a whale?
I'd hoped it would only give a pimple or two,
but I wasn't able to adjust it properly.
I was so scared when I couldn't get thin, even with Amaterasu's power!
For now we will have to put our differences aside.
We must work together and and stop Tamamo-no-Mae.
Indubitably. We cannot allow her to take over the world.
Changing the past in itself is a despisable act.
This is the perfect opportunity for a parent-
teacher-student meeting, don't you think?
Regret triggered Tamamo-no-Mae's awakening.
To defeat her, just erase those negative feelings.
But how?
Travel in time and find the indications, of course!
Can we do that?
We're already in a different time, aren't we?
Apparently she didn't expect your mother's spirit to return to you,
and her powers didn't seem to work very well.
So I took advantage of that.
Let's move on!
Yay, I'm out!
Oh, I lose again?
Take it off, Tsukuyomi!
But I'm already down to my skivvies..
Well then, how about your briefcase ?
I mustn't let go of this.
But I can't take off my last piece of clothing either...
I got it, Paparin!
Give up on your briefcase, and hide your face using your underwear instead! That'll solve everything!
Ah, how could I not notice that yet?
You're smart, Tama!
Yay, I've been praised!
That doesn't solve anything...
What is going on here?
Whoops, wrong time.
You seem to lead a happy life, do you not?
Yeah, it's lots of fun every day!
Sasami, I think she was criticizing you there.
Huh? Did she?
Let's move on!
What... is this?
This was right after Brother and I escaped the Tsukuyomi Shrine.
I felt so guilty for escaping that it almost broke me.
What're you doing here?!
Your brother is always by your side, Sasami!
When you see one of me, consider that an army of 30!
Shut up, you pest! Get lost!
He was such a freak that I had no time to feel down.
That saved me.
Here, Mom!
Mommy
What is this?
A present for Mothers' Day!
I heard there's an event like that!
Draw not, Sasami.
Artful creations are wicked.
When humans create, they place their wishes within their creation.
The wishes of the one who holds Amaterasu's power shakes the very foundation of the world.
If you have time to play, go and train! You failure!
I was really sad back then.
It had to be done.
You are in training to become a Tsukuyomi prie—
You were happy after all!
I have trained to suppress my emotions.
It is a fact that creation is dangerous.
It was my motherly duty to chasten it.
Mom...
Mom, you look so happy.
It is natural that a human is happy when she gives birth.
I was born because you wanted me...
Of course.
Look! They're doing something fun over there!
Wait!
What does the next Tsukuyomi priestess want from a failure like me?
Train hard! Don't go to town!
I had enough of your preaching, Sister!
Ruza, I...
I love you!
What?
Drop dead!
Mom was so surprisingly passionate!
Do not look! Stop!
Do not look at my youthful missteps!
Creation follows destruction.
Those cornered on the verge of death,
and see the abyss of ruin yield power.
I was so insolent.
Whoa, that's some intense training!
Humans have it rough...
This is also the duty of a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Mom...
I shall ask you again, Sasami.
No matter how many times you ask me, I won't become a Tsukuyomi priestess.
You are a Tsukuyomi priestess.
Whether you shoulder or abandon the duty you inherited from your ancestors,
you must be sincere.
In this age full of changes, when the borders of the world are becoming unclear,
we cannot trust the wanton gods of Japan to take care of this land.
Therefore it is necessary that humans guard and oversee it ourselves.
Yeah, the gods of this land are really random.
They're all so weak, so uncertain, and fail so miserably...
But they can only grow if they overcome that.
Then they could get stronger, couldn't they?
My bed in my closed room is no paradise.
If I go to school, if I go outside, I might get hurt,
but that must mean I'll eventually get stronger and grow up.
We should believe in the gods of this land more. We should let them out!
We're just entrusted with the power of Amaterasu temporarily.
That power isn't ours.
It's so arrogant to say we could protect it...
We don't have to make efforts for the world and for the people.
The age of protection is over.
I want to believe in the gods more!
So I'm no longer putting forth my effort.
We don't have to put forth effort anymore.
I'm not that great, so I get dragged around a lot.
So I'll give the power of Amaterasu to you for a while.
During that time I'll grow stronger.
Strong enough so that the power won't crush me.
So that is what you think?
Because I died early you were made a Tsukuyomi priestess without the proper preparations.
That is why I thought you were spoiled.
I thought you felt disdain; that you did not want to put forth the effort due to a lack of determination.
However,
you thought-out, pondered and reached that conclusion.
You figured out our true duty, the one we
thought was lost with the passage of time.
Your mother is proud of you.
You stood up against me with conviction.
I will no longer consider you a traitor.
I was the one mistaken and foolish.
You weren't mistaken. You just worked too hard.
You worked for so long shouldering such a troublesome duty.
Thanks for your hard work.
We're done now!
Is this when the grandson of Amaterasu descended to Earth?
What do we do now?
It all started because I was tired of my power and threw it away.
We could redo it from this point onward, you know.
I've had enough rest.
I depended on you guys, and remained in my slumber for much longer than I should have.
I ruined humans in exchange.
This should have never happened.
The Sun just gave up saying "darn I've had enough of this."
It's not allowed.
I don't know if your history built on that was right or not.
You've suffered a lot, and many of you have died along the way.
This land was a real mess.
It's because I refused to put forth the effort.
That's what I regret.
Answer me honestly!
Was I wrong? Did I fail?
I've wondered for such a long time
but I couldn't figure it out myself.
Should I have worked a bit harder?
You worked hard for a really long time.
Then after you rested, you came back to us.
If you're tired, just pass the torch.
That's the most effective way.
You weren't wrong.
Don't regret our history, goddess.
We're gonna work hard until the sun rises,
but we can only provide the faintest of moonlight.
Okay!
Die now, Tsukuyomi Juju!
This is the end of the Tsukuyomi Shrine!
Glory to Arahabaki!
Too bad for you, I made a promise to work hard for a while now.
I cannot allow you to kill me now.
What?!
You awakened your powers, triggered by our desire to change the past.
However, we have no more regrets!
What the...
Why is there such a great soul in Sasami?
I could have easily dealt with an untrained Sasami!
Why is there such a great soul!?
My bad! I used you to allow the mother and daughter to make up with each other.
Tsurugi?
You've got the unusual power to sail against the stream of time, so I used you!
Prepare!
You used me?!
Me, the fair and golden nine-tailed fox who's overthrown so many countries before?!
Amaterasu entrusted us with a great duty a long time ago,
and finally, we can carry that out in its true meaning.
I'll butcher you! Ground you into minced meat!
You'll be my appetizer before a grand feast!
We will hold until sunrise.
That is our pride, given form in the three sacred treasures!
Well then, just a bit longer!
I'm back!
Welcome home, Sasami!
Should I help too?
It's okay! Go and warm yourself up inside.
Come on, let me do a little!
Fine, I'll bring another shovel and we can clear the snow together!
And the neighbor lady will say "Ah, you siblings get along so well,"
and we could answer "Siblings? We are a married couple!"
Stop spouting nonsense!
Hello,
Tsukuyomi Sasami!
H-Hello...
Do we know each other?
Tsukuyomi
Kamiomi
Sasami
You're famous!
You skipped school for so long then suddenly showed up,
not to mention you're the younger sister of a teacher...
It's really fascinating!
Everyone's really interested in you!
Uh...
I'm the president of the Ko-no-Hana Saku Ya Academy's student council.
If you need help with anything, just say a word!
Let's be friends!
Uh, Sure...
Oh my, isn't that lovely, Sasami?
You've got another friend!
Nothing would make me happier than if you got along well.
However, if you try to use Sasami in wicked schemes
or maybe even try to hurt Sasami,
I will make you pay dearly, if you are her friend.
Oh? Are you an Emishi? Or a Tsuchigumo?
Or maybe a Kumaso?
I believe I am something different than you think.
You're making all the more curious.
You guys are very interesting.
What's your name?
Jou, Edogawa Jou.
Weird name, isn't it?
Nice to meet you, Sasami.
You scared me there.
It's unusual for you to take direct action.
Weren't you listening?
I'm really interested in that girl.
You shouldn't let your curiosity out like that.
She doesn't have the power of Amaterasu anymore.
No way! Even from here I could feel her gigantic divinity!
You should know from Amaterasu's case that some divinity remains even in an empty shell.
I wanted to drain the power of Amaterasu from her, but I had mistaken the target.
But I think times will get more gaiety from now on.
Second year... Spring is behind the corner.
You are our master.
If you desire destruction, we shall abide by your will.
Yeah, I've got high expectations for you.
It's all for my happiness,
for my desires and interests.
Let's use the complete power of the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki,
to spit in the eyes of those damn gods who think so highly of themselves,
in this land and this world!
As you wish, milady.
Sasami@Unmotivated
What, is this the ending song?
So there's a whole different world here.
It's a tiny sandbox that's beyond even Amaterasu's powers.
We should take over this place to make it the base of the Wicked Occult Society Arahabaki,
as our first step towards world domination!
Milady, being so passionate head-on may scare people away...
Why? The first steps are the most important!
Though certainly it might be unsightly to invade without a declaration of war.
We should valiantly abide by the rules of this world then!
What should I do? I, Edogawa Jou will do anything in a laugh!
It seems you should take this microphone and sing.
What do you mean?!
Oh well, whatever.
Arahabaki created the contradiction of a monotheistic god in a polytheistic myth!
I inherited that power, so impossible is a meaningless word to me!
I can hear your voice.
Your voice echoes on and on like a symphony.
Keep it up, milady!
Light shines down like love.
Great!
Let's hold hands forever.
Yay!
I can feel our osmotic pressure,
Wonderful!
and I don't want it to stop.
That's it!
Great work, milady!
But apparently it's time, so let's go home for now and warm ourselves!
I get the feeling that I was just used.
Preview
It's time for Unmotivated@Pro-Wrestling. I will be the commentator, Tsukuyomi Sasami.
Unmotivated@Pro Wrestling
Unmotivated@
Pro Wrestling
In the red corner: the Great Unmotivated.
In the blue corner: Unmotivated the Kid.
In the black corner: Unmotivated Animal.
In the yellow: Unmotivated Isamu.
Unmotivated@
Pro Wrestling
In the pink: Unmotivated Rusher.
Unmotivated@
Pro Wrestling
With their powers combined...
Unmotivated@
Pro Wrestling
Next time, episode ten:
Next Time
Episode Ten
Try fighting an invisible enemy.
Try fighting an     invisible enemy