This is an extremely important
matter to me.
I feel like I'm going to
forget my own face!
Um...
No! No!
Hey!
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals, huh?
Is this really where they're doing
the human experiments?
It's not Harima Mika...
Use as much money, any way you like.
You and I, right now, are eternity.
I love you, Celty.
They're all fake.
The world's filled with them.
They say they love you, they cherish you,
but they just try to hold you down.
"Look at me."
"Stay by me."
They take.
They make themselves dependent on you.
My love is different.
It's a greater, more perfect thing...
I know, Sis.
Thanks for the deposit.
See you.
Want me to get you something to drink?
There's a vending machine
right over there.
Wait a second.
You're so pretty.
Love and
Cherish
You still haven't found them?
No. I'm sorry.
What the hell was their watcher doing?
According to the person on duty,
they'd been staying at the same
hotel for several nights,
but late last night,
Seiji-san changed locations.
He was still answering his
phone around seven!
If something happens to him...
He promised not to leave Ikebukuro,
so I think we'll find him soon.
Listen!
What do you think will happen
if the police find that thing?!
Well...
Enough.
I can't wait for you people.
Chief!
I'll be back soon.
To me, it was just a doll.
An expensive, beautiful foreign doll,
like my uncle used to buy me.
Even as a child, I never liked dolls.
I think he was just sending
me ones he liked,
without caring whether they
would make me happy.
Seiji, look!
Pretty, huh?
Now, what is this?
What is it?
Silence filled the inside of the house,
and Seiji and I were always alone.
Even before my brother was born,
I was sent to my uncle's house a lot,
and I went in and out of his study often.
And there it was...
I'd heard that it was smuggled in
from outside the country.
My uncle seemed possessed by it.
Sometimes he even spoke to it.
It was beautiful indeed,
more so than any doll my
uncle had given me.
Strangely enough, there was
no hint of brutality to it,
as though the head were,
itself, complete.
But to me, that's all it was.
So that day, when I secretly invited
my brother into the study,
it was just for play.
Perhaps I'd simply wanted someone
to share the secret with.
Pretty, isn't it?
That was the beginning of everything.
My one regret, which
continues to this day...
This is our first time meeting, isn't it?
Was that list of illegal aliens
useful, Yagiri Namie-san?
I'm honored to have the sixth chief of
Yagiri Pharmaceuticals come out here.
Take a seat.
It's an emergency.
Find my brother!
I'll pay as much as you'd like.
I haven't been able to contact
him since last night.
He should still be somewhere
in Ikebukuro.
It hasn't been that long.
Why so worried?
He's with a woman,
a woman with a scar around her neck.
A woman.
He's about the right age.
Get started now!
Wait a second!
Aren't there other important things
you should be investigating?
There's a rumor that the foreign company
Nebra might buy you out.
That would mean that your position-
Orihara Izaya-san, I don't
have time to talk!
Surprising.
I didn't think a talented woman like you
would fall for her brother.
What do you know about me?
The Yagiri Namie I know
is a great woman.
But your dad screwed up and
lost his own family company,
and the current president
is quite reserved...
But you entered the company
on your own and
worked your way up to
your present position.
And you're so cute.
I guess you do know me well.
Since you're that talented, you'll have
no problem finding my brother.
Your brother, right...
You shouldn't meddle
too much, you know.
I'm not meddling!
I'm the only one who can protect him.
Stalkers are always the only ones who
don't know what they're doing.
They always think they're
protecting the person-
Don't compare me to a stalker!
Scary!
I was kidding.
OK, I'll help.
But in my own way.
I'm not the cops or an information broker.
What kind of rules does that have?
Question: are you jealous of the girl
with the scar on her neck?
Why?
I can't be jealous of her!
The rust-red jealousy in my heart is...
Sister... There's a girl I like.
I knew Seiji was getting
stranger and stranger.
He kept wanting to go
into my uncle's study,
and when he snuck in,
he'd stare at it for hours.
It wasn't a person he loved.
There was no heart, not even a body.
I wanted to get it away from him,
so as soon as I joined the company, I brought
it into work for research purposes.
And then it happened.
Nebra began contacting us,
and I was working my hardest
to prevent research leaks.
Then a security
card was stolen.
A card I alone owned.
Sister, I might have killed someone...
What should I do?
What I felt then was not fear or anger,
but endless pleasure.
I was the one Seiji relied on.
You don't need to worry about a thing.
Leave it all to me, OK?
I've got a question about
her. Not this girl...
So you were the one who took it.
It's all right.
Leave her to me, too.
It'll be fine.
At the time, I didn't know that
Seiji was being followed by a foolish
stalker named Harima Mika.
She'd snuck into his
room and seen it.
To protect you, I'll use whatever
methods I must.
Right, right.
It doesn't seem like that big a problem.
The cops have him.
They'll probably call you in a second.
It's probably no big deal, though.
Probably...
Shut up!
Yes?
Yes, that's right.
Be careful. You're still
being chased.
Where are you?
What?
What's wrong?
We're leaving?
But we haven't...
Wait!
I'm happy you love me so much.
I love you.
I always will.
I'm scared.
Of what?
Please! Let's go somewhere far away!
I want to be with you.
But where?
What the heck?
A lover's quarrel?
St-Stop!
Calm down.
We're not going to hurt you.
Listen to us.
Let go-
Let go of her!
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt.
Go.
I don't know what's going on,
but you have to chase her, right?
I've always wanted to say this.
"Leave this to me! You go on ahead!"
Wait!
E-Excuse me.
Are you all right?
You're-
Wait!
No! You wait!
Let me go!
Let me go, I said.
Is she your girlfriend?
That's right!
Fate brought us together!
Why is she like that?
Hell if I know!
What the hell does that mean?!
You love her, but you don't know
anything about her?
Isn't that a little irresponsible?
That has nothing to do with loving her!
Then what?
Why'd fate bring you together?
Because I love her!
There's no other reason!
You can't express love in words!
So I...
I'll show it with my actions!
I'll protect her!
That's all!
I like you a lot more than Izaya,
so I'll let you off with this!
This'll bleed if I take it out.
Better buy a band-aid first.
No, maybe some super glue would be better.
So basically, your head was
walking along, attached to a body,
and you grabbed her but were
interrupted by a high school kid.
You chased her, but then another
high school kid appeared,
and they took your head away.
You expect me to believe that?
I won't force you to believe it.
I believe it.
But what was Shizuo-kun doing there?
I'd forgotten, but Izaya had asked me to
be in the park, on standby, for a job.
And he stopped by, and we had a chat.
I later heard that the job
itself was canceled.
Orihara-kun, huh?
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you...
You're still confused.
I'll talk to you as much as you want.
Why does some other
body have my head?!
There's no answer I could give
that would be entirely clear,
but if you'd like a guess...
Like maybe...
It found some other body around
the right size and changed bodies!
How terrifying...
Maybe there was a fresh corpse
or something it found?
Stop it!
Yeah. But...
Is that... Is that even possible?
What I did wasn't wrong.
After that experiment,
when I made her for him...
I have to go.
It's fine.
It's all right now.
She... She's...
You must have been scared.
But see? Nothing happened.
Even when she ran away and joined Seiji,
my love didn't change.
Seiji's love exists because it
takes advantage of mine.
And Seiji knows this,
and I know he knows.
It's all twisted, but even so...
Damn! A Raira Academy
uniform... Who was he?
I know who it was.
Leave it to me.
Anyway, I need to find the kid from Raira.
Then I need to talk to my head.
The head that screamed when it saw you?
It's living on its own.
What will you do with it?
Are you going to rip it off its body?
Celty...
I don't want to admit it...
That my head and memories are gone.
That everything I've done over the
past twenty years has been useless.
It wasn't useless at all.
I'll get her back,
so you wait here. All right?
Oh, right.
Where's your phone?
Did you drop it?
I don't know.
It was gone, even though
I put it in my bag.
She needs me!
We need to be together!
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
It's fine.
Leave it all to me.
How annoying.
A doll should behave like
a doll and stay put,
not interfere with my love.
I've decided...
I don't want to regret anything anymore.
Listen up. Round up everyone
under you for this.
I don't care if they're alive or dead.
If necessary, eliminate them right away!
Are you safe?
Where are you?
Ryuugamine Mikado
No one is in the chat room right now.
I see. You're all busy.
This'll be fun! This'll be fun! This'll be fun!
There's just so much in this town
that even I don't know about!
It just comes and goes!
This is why I love the places
where humans gather.
I love people!
Love them!
I love them all!
And that's why...
The humans should love me, too.
Thank you.
Calmed down?
Can you answer my questions?
You said you don't remember
anything, right?
So you...
uh, have amnesia?
I ought to say it again... Shouldn't you
go to the police or a hospital?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's OK. Don't apologize.
I have to go. Before that
person stops me...
Forever, forever...
I have to go.
Seiji...
Seiji-san...
I love you.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Never Before
Seen
Um, the Headless Rider and Orihara Izaya,
and that girl with the scarred neck, all showed up again.
And then, the guy in the next class over is one of the Dollar's...
Next time:
Never Before Seen.
I dreamed of a life that wasn't normal, but...