There was once a girl who,
owing to her superhuman intelligence,
was sent to an orphanage
before she was one year old.
It was not long after
she'd learned to speak.
There, she learned about games.
She was made to play many games
they called "intelligence tests",
but they were too boring for her to enjoy,
no matter who she played with.
After two years had passed,
she was reunited with a woman
who seemed to be her mother,
and a boy who was
seven years older than her.
He told the adults
whatever they wanted to hear
and greeted all those he met
with a blank, empty smile.
The girl's words to him were the
first she'd spoken in a long, long time.
You really are empty.
Let's play a game.
Who is that?
...Blank...
...Blank doesn't...
You must've had a bad dream.
I'll bring you some warm milk.
No! No!
He was with me.
He was always with me.
...That's why...
Shiro.
Shiro!
...It's cold...
There you are, Master.
Dola was in a panic, saying you'd run off,
so I wondered what had happened.
Jibril?
Yes, what is it?
Who are your masters?
...Why are you asking me—
Answer me!
You are my master, Shiro.
So who fought you?
It was you, Shiro.
Who told Stephanie to
fall in love with them?
I'm told it was you, Shiro.
Who found out about the
Eastern Federation's games?
You, Shiro, aided by the information
Dola's grandfather left behind.
I was charmed by your unparalleled
brilliance and strategic mind,
and I decided to obey you.
Obey... me?
Yes.
You, Shiro—queen of Elkia and
designated representative of Imanity.
In other words, there was
somebody besides her?
There seems to be no
material evidence, though.
We've questioned people throughout the castle,
...and then across the whole city, but...
Shiro's House
Yes, nobody in the protest demonstrations
knows anything about him, either.
Shiro's House
...Which means...
...It's likely...
that our master challenged
someone unbeknown to us,
lost, and had her memories altered.
That's impossible.
...Who could have...
The Eastern Federation?
Yes. They're capable of that.
Master.
Let's play a game.
A game?
Yes. The wager will be the false memories
that have been implanted in you.
False?
And I know this is
most impolite to ask,
but would you please lose?
That's check.
...False memories...
Are they really false?
Is that why they're disappearing?
Hey, Shiro.
They say people can change,
but is that really true?
...They're all...
They're all disappearing.
If they decide they want to fly,
will they grow wings?
I don't think so.
You don't change yourself,
just how you do things.
...Bro...
You have to make your own way.
You have to create a way to fly,
even while you stay the same.
Let's think of a way to make
wings that will let you fly.
We can take our time.
They're all false.
All of them are lies.
If they disappear,
I'll feel better.
Blank?
Master?
...Blank...
...Blank never...
Blank never loses!
Why did you win?
He's real. Sora is real!
I know he's real!
Sora?
...Master, please consid—
He's real! He is real!
Calm down, Master.
Think logically.
You're right.
It might be more natural
to think he doesn't exist,
but I'm sure he does.
What are you saying, Dola?
Because I know you two
would never lose!
...Steph...
...But...
Yeah, they'd never lose.
There must be some reason.
Some reason this happened.
You're letting sentimentality
cloud your judgment.
...You need to—
What did you two do yesterday?
Yesterday?
I spent some time dealing
with the demonstrations,
and then you played a
game in the throne room.
That was two days ago. The 19th.
st
I'll change my question.
Where were you two nights ago?
That same night, then?
...Um... Um...
Huh?
...I can't...
You can't remember. That's right.
Now I just need to confirm.
...U-Um, what are you...
Fondling your breasts.
How am I supposed to respond to that?
It doesn't make you excited?
Even though I told you
to fall in love with me?
...Well...
So you're saying someone other than
you told her to fall in love with them.
Yes. It was Bro who told her that.
But I thought she
already believed he existed.
So why did you fondle my breasts?
To thank you. Without you,
I wouldn't have noticed.
...Shiro...
Let's think, then.
If this Sora existed,
how could he have disappeared?
How could our memories of the
last day and a half have been erased?
A large-scale magic spell could do it,
but not without leaving
some kind of trace.
What if it was a game?
A game?
What if a game was held in
accordance with the commandments,
and that was part of the rules?
If the game involved
Imanity's representatives,
it could affect the entire race.
...But Jibril...
No, since they are my masters,
in a way, I'm subordinate to them.
We can assume I would
also be under its effects.
I see.
But what kind of game could that be?
I don't know.
But... I know what Bro said.
I believe in you.
Shiro, the two of us are always one.
Bro would never leave me alone.
...So...
Shiro, are you there?
You're still there, right, Shiro?
Brother!
Would you hold me
somewhere—anywhere I can still feel?
To keep me sane.
Bro!
Shiro?
Think hard, even if it burns you out.
Think about what's going on.
Bro trusted you with this!
Use all the memories you still have!
Bro said that we were always one.
So he must still be here.
Bro said that we always
win our games before they start.
And that we're bound by a promise?
Bro said we're not the heroes
from some boys' comic.
No!
Think harder!
...Harder...
Bro said he was going to
get the last piece we need.
Get the piece we need?
So this game is to get us something
we need to face the Eastern Federation.
...Tool...
...Wisdom...
...Observer...
Elf?
He's going to get an elf?
How?
Challenge Elven Garde?
Clammy?
No. Clammy doesn't believe in Bro.
...She'd never agree to...
What if the game was to
steal each other's existence?
Shiro! Shiro!
A game to steal each other's existence?
That's right.
The thirty-two stones collectively
constitute your existence
Sky Walk
and are ranked by importance according to the
priority assigned to them by your subconscious.
In other words, you won't know
which stone constitutes which part of you
until your opponent takes it.
For example, the existence
of that elf next to you.
Or your arms, legs,
nerves, or memories.
In the end,
your very existence is taken,
and no one will even
realize you're there.
In other words, you'll disappear.
Are you serious?
Yep.
Commandment five: The challenged party
has the right to decide how the game is played.
If you don't like it, the game is off.
What will you do?
...Clammy...
Fi, this man is going to
wager Imanity's Race Piece.
We can't just ignore that.
For shame. And here I was hoping
we could reconcile after what happened.
We still can.
You just have to trust me
and lend me that elf of yours.
Absolutely not!
Thought as much.
What is the wager?
We'll say the winner gets the right
to make two demands of the loser.
You could, for example,
make the results of the game eternal,
erasing your opponent's
existence permanently,
and then alter the memories of
their partners to make them join you.
In other words, we're each
betting our existence
and complete rights
over our partners, right?
That's right.
You're insane.
Well, just as long as I'm insane,
I'd like to propose one more important rule.
Bro?
Master?
Shiro! Are you okay?
Bro!
...Jibril...
What is it?
Would it be possible to make a game
where the players steal each other's existence?
No, unfortunately.
In a virtual world like Materialization
...Word Chain, it would be possible, but...
What if you collaborated with an elf?
Collaborate?
With those forest bumpkins?
During the great war, I leveled one of their
...capitals with a single blast! They're nothing but—
Could you do it?
Theoretically, yes.
Those bumpkins do have some small measure of skill
when it comes to constructing complicated spells.
So, Sora erased his own existence
by playing this game?
Yes.
Wouldn't that mean
he has already lost?
That's right.
If he'd won, he would be here.
What if it was neither?
You mean the game's still underway?
That can't be.
Jibril, see if you can detect
any magic in this room!
Very well.
I woke up here.
Even though Bro and I
sleep in a different room,
I woke up here.
He told me he
wouldn't leave me alone.
You're right.
Magic is being used here.
But I can't detect its exact position.
We just have to search
...everywhere we can—
There you go, Dola,
tripping over thin air.
You don't need to play
the klutz forever, you know.
Tripped? Me?
An Othello stone?
That has the elven rune
for "three" written on it.
Why are those stones
the only ones left?
Because they haven't been used yet.
Even if we can't
sense them, they're there.
But we don't have anything to
go by except two sets of three stones.
We don't even know
if we're white or black.
It's simple.
Bro told me that
the two of us are one.
I'm participating in this game.
I'll propose an important rule.
Each of our partners
will play in the game.
If one of us becomes
unable to continue,
their partner will play in their stead.
That's why I still had my memories.
You can see the board?
No.
...But I can see...
what Bro would do.
You're trying to lose
deliberately, aren't you?
Nope.
I've set it up so I can win like this.
I can see how he'd
lead his opponent on.
What is this?
Your memories?
Are you making me
steal your memories
to prove that there's
no other race working with you?
Not a bad answer.
I can see how he'd
tell me what he wants.
Now you can't continue the game.
I win.
But the game isn't over.
What's going on?
Why isn't the game ending?
What part of Sora do
those three stones contain?
I can see how he'd
deceive his opponent,
...and...
I can see how he'd win.
Bro, you're amazing!
...Nobody would ever figure this out...
except for you and me.
The parts of you that are contained
...in these last three stones are...
Three: the way to win the game.
Two: your absolute trust in me.
And one:
everything I am.
...Okay, Bro...
Come back to me!
...Bro...
...Shiro...
Okay!
You can punch me if you want!
...I'm ready—
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I should've come sooner.
I can't believe I forgot my master.
Why?
Clammy! Wake up! Clammy!
Clammy! Clammy!
Now then,
I'll make my demands,
just as we agreed.
Y-You can do whatever
you want with me!
...But Clammy...
...Nope! Demand one...
Don't!
We keep a copy of the memories
we stole from each other,
and return the originals.
Clammy!
What's going on?
They each keep the memories
they took from the other,
but they get their
own memories back.
Now that Clammy and Master
know everything about each other,
they can trust each other as well.
This is the last piece
that our master wanted.
...And...
Demand two:
You, elf.
Feel, I'm taking the right
to alter your memories.
...Wha—
Don't worry.
It's fine, Fi.
He only wants one thing.
You want us to spy for you, right?
Yeah, you've been
inside my head, all right.
Spy? What does he mean?
I'll tell you later.
After seeing what was in
your head, I changed my mind.
I'm in.
You're amazing, Bro!
Right? Tell me how proud
you are of your big brother.
I'm proud of you, Bro.
Wow, actually hearing it
from you is kinda embarrassing.
Master!
Shiro... It's okay now, right?
Yeah.
I'll stand by for you anytime.
Fi,
...Clammy...
I was so scared!
I'm never doing that again!
What's going on?
...I guess this might be...
our master's true colors.
I was so scared!
dare ni mo ienai
With a loneliness
kodoku wo kakaeta mama hitori de naiteta
That I could share with no one, I was crying all alone
dare ni mo jouzu ni waraenai bokura
We could never bring ourselves to smile
futari deatte waratta
But the moment we met, we smiled
mayonaka sugi ni souzou no oku ni
In the dead of the night, deep inside our imagination
dou shiyou mo nai kimochi wo tada oshiyatte
We pushed away the feelings we didn't know what to do with
sayonara bokura wa kitto umarekawareru kara
"We'll be starting our life anew, so farewell"
kanashimi ni te wo furun deshou
We waved goodbye to sadness
soshite itsuka
And someday
karappo no mama no kokoro ni akari wo tomosu you ni
We'll light up our empty hearts
togire togire no kotoba wo sagashite tsunagitometa
By finding and piecing together the fragmented expressions
sore demo tatta futari no sekai wa tsuzuite ikun da
Our own little world will never end
sora ni inoru you ni
As we pray to the sky
douka eien ni
For this moment to last forever
Blue Rose
It's way faster than Salamander!
Please wait a moment.
Shut up!
It's a sad thing, growing up.