It's morning, huh...
Yeah...
In the end, we couldn't sleep, huh...
All thanks to that...
What are we going to do about today's
"Scare Minorin, Enter the White Knight" plan?
Will we be able to scare Kushieda while we're scared as well?
Oh, shut up.
If we don't do it, the future won't change!
I know that, but...
What should we do?
Something Minorin will be scared of...
What do you mean by "something Minorin will be scared of"?
Ki-
You're up early, Kitamura!
What kind of foul plans are you plotting so early in the morning?
Foul plans, you say...
Huh? Could it be...
...that you two were the culprits of what Kushieda was fretting over yesterday?
So that's how it is, huh?
Sheesh, why is that?
Don't you feel sorry for Kushieda?
No, that's not-
I-It's a present.
Present?
M-Minorin is extremely fond of horror.
She said she loves being surprised and getting scared,
so I wanted to make some summer memories-
Hey, Kitamura.
I see now.
So that's why instead of her being scared,
her eyes were glowing with avarice.
All right! Make me your accomplice!
Huh?
Why don't we work together,
and make Kushieda genuinely frightened?!
No, look-
Oh, yeah. I'll invite Ami too.
Stupid Chi' too?
She's bound to be familiar with the area.
All right! We'll strike while the iron is hot!
No, but Kawashima won't do it!
Leave it to me!
I'll definitely talk her into it!
Worry not!
W-What should we do, Ryuuji?
"What", you ask...
There's nothing we can do.
Seaweed...
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Fireworks
Oh, my. I was planning to make breakfast, but I was beaten to it.
Morning, Takasu-kun!
Y-Yeah.
Huh? What are you making?
Ah, lunch boxes.
Everyone said they're going to be playing at the sea for the whole day today, you see.
You got up early for that?!
This won't do!
Chef, this unworthy Kushieda will be of assistance too!
Now, order me as you please!
Y-Yeah.
Then, can you slice up the onions?
Yes, wholeheartedly glad to do so!
What's on the menu?
Egg sandwiches and tuna sandwiches.
Also, soup from the leftovers of the curry, I guess.
Yeah! Good! Good!
You're good at that, Kushieda.
Oh? Did you just praise me?
Yay.
Your cleaning yesterday was good too.
You're rather skilled.
Both my parents work, you see.
When my little brother was at home, I had to make lunch boxes too.
You have a little brother?
He's an active high school baseball player, Akechi-kun.
Ah, it got in my eye!
Hey! You okay?
I screwed up.
Takasu-kun?
Huh? Ah, gotta peel the apples!
Takasu-kun's really skilled at cooking.
Yesterday's curry was the best too.
It wasn't that big of a thing, though...
I think that diligent side of you is really wonderful.
The rest of the class doesn't know this side of you.
I feel kinda special.
Whoever becomes Takasu-kun's bride will be really happy.
Kyusheda!
What is it, Takyasu-kyun?
A-About yesterday...
Well, about that...
Don't...
...tell anyone about that, okay?
I haven't talked about that with anyone else.
How should I say this...
I dropped my guard.
I said more than I should have.
But I'm glad it was with Takasu-kun.
Thank you for listening.
Oh! Not good!
You klutz!
Aren't you cute?!
D-Don't call me cute!
Just kidding.
But Chef, what shall we do next?
Oh, right...
Shall we mix it?
Shall we mix it with real force?!
The sunlight's burning today too!
Komachi Angel!
Minorin's so energetic...
Then, we'll do it according to plan.
Huh? What about Kawashima?
She's helping out, right?
Yeah! With Ami's guidance, we set up traps in a nearby cave.
Then, we'll get nowhere without her help.
What's she doing?
Dunno.
I'll go get her.
Taiga, take care of this.
H-Hey!
Here!
I'll carry it.
It's heavy for a girl, right?
I-It's fine.
I'll be fine.
Kawashima? You there?
I am.
Everyone's gone on ahead.
Sheesh, what are you do-
I was admiring myself.
Takasu-kun, do you want to look too?
You're really...
Hey, hey! Isn't this rather risqué?
Just look at this cleavage!
It's fine, isn't it?
That's all?
Ah, you already saw me in a bikini at school, right?
Not that.
But this part comes off, you know.
Look.
Put it back on! Put it back on!
Eh? Then, you put it back on.
I refuse!
How cold of you.
If you're going to be like that, I'm not going to help out.
Eh?!
D-Don't say that!
Hey...
Why does Takasu-kun want Minori-chan to enjoy herself?
W-Why, you ask...
If you're not going to tell me, I'm not helping out.
You've got five seconds, okay?
Five...
...four...
...three...
Are you sure?
Two...
...one...
...zero.
I'm not helping out.
Taiga!
Come at me!
Come on! Really hard, now!
Really, really hard, now!
It's cold!
Just what are they doing?
Hey, hey! Why?
Because it's, like, boring.
If you're not with us, we won't be able to get around in the caves, right?
Didn't I draw you a map?
I'm sorry, Yuusaku, but you'll have to do it on your own.
Hey...
No problems with that, right?
Takasu-kun was the one who chose, after all.
Sorry, Takasu. Ami suddenly...
It's fine.
I'll come with you.
Going alone will be difficult, right?
Even so...
If the two of us leave by ourselves, it might look rather suspicious.
It's all right.
I'll manage alone, somehow.
I've come up with three praiseworthy ideas for traps.
Kushieda will definitely go half-crazy from fear!
I-I see...
Hey! Kushieda! Aisaka!
What is it?
I'm going to the toilet!
Man! It's so good!
Takasu-kun sure is a cooking prodigy!
No, Kushieda helped me out, after all...
Huh? Minorin did?
Yeah!
That egg sandwich was mixed with force by yours truly!
Oh! Lunch while I'm not around?
Geez, Kitamura-kun!
Just what are you?!
Announcing to girls with a loud voice that you're going to the toilet...!
Yeah, sorry.
And besides, you were gone for so long. Just what-
Everything's all set.
Yeah.
Speaking of long-
What? What? What's this consultation?
Oh, Kushieda. You see, actually-
Hey, Minori-chan.
Towards the cove there's a really pretty cave, you see.
Cave, you say?!
It's my special place.
Special place?!
Want to take a stroll over there later?
Wah! A stroll!
Sounds good! Let's go! Let's go!
I can't wait!
Heh, so it's here!
Amin's special stroll...
Danger
What an atmosphere, huh...
Right?
Okay, let's try going in, then!
B-But, doesn't it feel like something will come out?
Oh! Like an encounter with an unidentified creature?!
No, if it was a living thing, it'd be fine...
Yeah, let's make sure to capture it alive!
Making him our accomplice was really the right thing to do.
That coaxing's cool too...
All right!
Here we go! Kitamura's Explorers League!
We're going to find the two-headed golden cobra!
It's dark! It's narrow! I'm scared!
I feel like I've heard that before.
It's unexpectedly spacious.
Around here, yeah.
Hey.
Stop losing focus.
We didn't come here for a simple test of courage.
Understand?
Y-Yeah.
From here on, it goes down a level, so be careful.
The first barrier.
What?
Fried tofu.
Oh yeah, that's right...
Kitamura's got the brains, but...
...he's an idiot.
D-Don't insult Kitamura-kun!
Hey, isn't it getting cold?
It's because we've come further in.
No, I didn't mean that...
What's up?
I smell ketchup.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
This...
Blood... writing...?
"Gyaaa," it says.
So this is the second...
Yeah, he's an idiot all right.
D-Don't insult Kitamura-kun!
Don't sigh!
What's this?
This is...
Hey, what's wro-
T-Takasu-kun! That's...!
No, um...
A woman's hair!
It's the curse of a broken-hearted woman who lost her way inside this cave...
...and died an unnatural death while on a trip of grief!
No! Let me out!
Let me leave!
Minorin, calm down!
Nice assist, Takasu.
Let me out!
Let me leave!
You set up some traps too, huh?
It's a curse!
No, um...
My final trap is fifty meters up ahead.
It's terrible!
Look forward to it!
Y-Yeah.
Come on, Kushieda!
Pull yourself together!
Kitamura-kun's skilled after all.
Minorin's really scared.
It wasn't Kitamura.
Of course, not me either...
T-Then...
It's not part of the setup.
It's the same as last night... No mistaking it...
One, two, three, four!
Minorin!
It's dangerous alone, so let's hold hands!
Really? Let's tie up! Let's tie up real good!
All right! I'm all warmed up now, so let's go on ahead!
Uh, um...
So stupid.
I'm going to use a shortcut to go back before everyone else.
Hey, Kawashima! Where are you going?
Kitamura!
Kawashima!
Hey, Kitamura-kun!
Are we going even further in?
This is the exit.
Right, Ami?
Where are Ami and Takasu?
Ryuuji?
I said wait, Kawashima!
Do you really know the way?!
Of course I do.
Are you that uneasy about being separated from the rest?
I'm not really good with...
...things like dark places...
Then,
what would you do if I left you behind?
What?!
Would you be scared?
Would you be uneasy about being separated from me?
Would you be lonely?
Would you think that you don't want to be separated from me?
H-Hey.
You need me?
This isn't the time for that.
Do you want to return to Minori as fast as possible?
Like I said...!
I don't think that girl suits Takasu-kun.
Wha- I-It's not like I...
The one who's suitable for Takasu-kun is...
W-What?
What?
Huh?
Where...
Where are we?
Huh?!
You're kidding! I'm lost!
Hey, hey!
You're kidding, right?
I wouldn't kid about something like this!
W-What should we do?
H-Hey...
I-It'll be okay!
I'm sure Kitamura and the others will come looking for us!
Don't be afraid!
I'm here with you!
I'm sorry.
No! You don't need to apologise!
What I said about being lost...
...was a lie.
Like I would ever get lost!
D-u-m-m-y.
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop it, Takasu-kun! It's slippery!
This isn't the time to be laughing!
But Takasu-kun was acting just like a kid!
I was really scared, you know!
Takasu-kun's...
...a very dull guy.
You, again...!
But I don't dislike...
...that part of you.
Earlier I said Minori-chan wasn't suited for Takasu-kun, right?
I really meant that.
I mean, Takasu-kun's the moon.
What the hell is that?
Minori-chan's the sun.
By being at her side,
I think you'd simply get burned away.
I mean, Takasu-kun wouldn't hit Minori-chan, right?
You can't be equal simply with admiration.
The one you could be equal with would be...
...someone like me...
That was-
-Kushieda's voice!
Wai- Takasu-kun!
Sorry, I...
It's fine. Let's hurry!
Y-Yeah!
Kushieda!
Ryuuji!
Takasu! Ami!
Were you all right?!
Kitamura, where's Kushieda?
What happened?
Well, that's...
Kushieda was taken by something...
What do you mean by "something"?
I don't know,
but there's something here.
Don't tell me that, Kushieda was...!
Flat batteries?!
Takasu, lend me yours.
Yeah.
What is this sound?
A voice?
Kushieda!
I'm coming now!
Hey! Kitamu-
Kitamura!
Kitamura-kun!
Kitamura-kun! Kitamura-kun!
W-What is this?!
Everyone, don't get separated!
For now, stay calm!
I don't care anymore. Since it's come to this,
I'm gonna beat it to pieces!
W-Wha-
Taiga?!
Tai-
Stop! Stop!
Kitamura, an accident has occurred!
We must rescue Taiga!
Acknowledged!
Are you all right, Aisaka?
Kita...
Kitamura-kun...
Kitamura?!
You're late, Akechi-kun.
K-Kushieda?
Yes. I am indeed Kushieda Minori.
Also known as Minorin.
The culprit is me!
And...
...my partner in crime...
...is him!
The hair in Takasu's room,
and the scattered clothes in Taiga's room...
All of them were our doing!
We're sorry.
Well, the way you were trying to scare me was so amateurish, you see.
So I ended up wanting to teach you how.
Showing you that this is how you scare people.
That means... You had discovered us already?
Yeah, since you two were lurking around like that by yourselves.
And that's why I made Kitamura-kun my accomplice,
and started trapping you, instead.
But I had fun. Thanks.
You're not going to get mad?
Nah, I won't!
After all, I really love horror!
Eh?!
You could call it the "Manjuu Kowai" method.
If I say "I'm scared of ghosts" and "I'm scared of the occult",
someone's bound to try to scare me.
And I would gladly receive it!
And now that we're done telling you about the prank...
It's lit!
It's beautiful, right?
Today really was one hell of a day.
You got that right. That was so much trouble.
About the conversation earlier...
I didn't really give you an answer.
Huh?
I'd be lonely without you around.
However, rather than whether I'd be lonely,
shouldn't it be about whether you'd be lonely?
I've never really considered whether I'm lonely or not.
Then consider it,
properly.
Isn't that a bit painful?
If it gets painful, just genuinely express that emotion.
I mean, we're...
Equal?
Hey...
Takasu-kun's really...
...kind sometimes.
What's wrong, Takasu-kun?
It's the last night.
Are you enjoying it?
Kushieda...
Um...
Yeah?
T-Thanks.
Huh?
I was completely fooled and utterly frightened,
but when I'm with you, it's fun.
No matter when.
That's my line.
I really had fun too.
And the curry was also really good.
And you listened to my strange little tale without laughing at it.
Takasu-kun really understood me.
I'm really sorry for scaring you.
I really wanted to show Takasu-kun ghosts,
and ended up kinda overdoing it.
Show me?
Yeah.
Because you said you wanted to see ghosts.
Eh? Ah...
Why did Takasu-kun want to scare me?
Eh?
W-Well, that's...
Taiga told me that you were scared of horror.
So you wanted to tease me?
That's not it.
Takasu-kun would never do something to someone that they would dislike.
You're the type who's always considering how to make someone happy.
Why did that Takasu-kun do something like this, I wonder.
I really want to know that.
I think it's really strange.
I wanted to show you one.
A ghost.
I wanted to make you believe that ghosts exist.
I think it's too early to give up just because you can't see them.
That's what I figured.
I see.
Takasu-kun, shall we go and find a UFO next?
One that isn't a man-made satellite. A real one!
Eh?
And after a UFO, yeah...
A Tsuchinoko!
And then, if we keep finding the things I want to see,
and if my world has been changed...
After that...
Kushieda!
Huh?
An exploded...
...UFO is...
It's like a dream!
I really saw one!
I saw one!
A sudden outbreak of a galactic war, huh?!
The Earth will be protected by us!
The trip continues until you're home, you know!
Everyone, don't let your guard down!
Maybe I should go home to my parent's house after this.
See you later!
Shall we stop by the supermarket and buy some stuff?
I'm tired, so don't talk to me about shitty housewife's tasks.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, there's a special sale today.
Shut up about that.
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
Oohashi High School Culture Festival (Part One)
Culture festival:
getting excited from band performances,
chests throbbing from a cosplay café,
heating up one's friendship
around a camp fire,
and an embarrassing leg-lock
at a pro-wrestling show!
What are you plotting?