Dyspaaaaaaairvil!
Today is naught but the end for you Precures!
Dyspairvil!
Why you...
Nice, Flora!
Dyspairvil!
Let's go!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
Next time!
I see it now...
The Precures are centered around her.
But what to do about it...
Oh!
Shoot, I've got work!
Sounds hectic.
Good luck!
You're following your dream, so give it your all!
Thanks!
Following your dream, huh?
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Bonjour.
Bonjour!
What flowers should we plant for winter?
Hmm, good question!
Hmm...
'Sup! Gettin' an early start, eh, Haruno?
Bonjour, er...
C'mon, you don't remember me?
I'm Claus from the class next door!
...Claus?
Well, I remember you.
The girl who wants to be a princess, Haruno Haruka.
Am I right?
How do you know my dream?
Everyone knows you! You tend to stand out.
Do I?
Well...
See ya, Princess! I'm rootin' for you.
'Sup!
Bonjour!
I've never met...
a boy who didn't make fun of my dream!
He might be the only one besides Kanata!
A Suspicious Trap...
The Lonely Princess!
A photo shoot... on a tropical island?!
Yep. I leave today, but I'll be back the day after tomorrow.
You're getting a lot more work, Kirara.
That means I'm getting closer to being Top Model!
Kirara, I'm rooting for you!
Thanks, Haruharu.
Minami?
Is something wrong?
Oh, well...
The truth is, my father requested I attend a party tonight.
My mother will be absent due to urgent business, so he asked if I could come instead.
You're getting closer to your dream, too!
However...
Now might not be the time for it.
Why not?
I won't return for two days, either.
Should something happen during that time...
You'd decline on our account?
But...
Minami, you should go!
Darn right!
That party'll lead you to your dream, right?
Y-Yes...
Then you don't need to think twice about going!
Claus...
Sorry, I kinda overheard...
But your dreams are important!
Right?
That's right!
I want you to follow your dream!
Then... I suppose I'll go.
You can trust us to handle the school.
Thank you.
Sorry for buttin' in.
Claus!
Thank you!
Who?
He's from another class.
Yeah, our dreams are important...
Dreams, huh?
Those... don't make much sense to me.
They don't? To you, Prince Kanata?
Well, I don't remember anything about myself.
Not my past nor what I held dear.
Prince Kanata...
Hey!
Kanata, don't you have anything you want?
Something I want?
Yeah!
I... can't say I do.
Dreamy 6              Noble Academy Bound
Welcome back!
Oh, Yui.
Oh, where are Perf and Aroma?
They said they'd stay the night with my brother.
They want to cheer him up, if only a little.
What is it that you've been pondering over?
Hey girls, how about tomorrow we...
Ah!
Get back here!
Nice, Haruno!
Dreamy Hill
Picture Book Museum
International Picture Book Exhibit
International Picture Book Exhibit?!
I wanted to check it out tomorrow.
I never knew they held such splendid events!
Oh yeah, your dream was to become a picture book author, right, Nanase?
We could go together if you want!
T-Together? W-With me?!
Sure!
B-But I...
You should go!
I'm sure it'll help you reach your dream!
Haruka...
Yeah...
Welp, let's meet by the museum tomorrow at 10.
Have fun, you two!
Sure!
By the way... Akagi, right?
Yes.
You've got a dream too, right?
What sort of question is that?
I haven't heard what yours is yet!
Maybe I can help you, y'know?
Indeed, I also have a dream of my own.
But I've no reason to tell you of it.
Well, I guess not...
Have a nice trip,
Minami and Kirara!
Good luck!
It will get a tad lonely here.
And Yui's going out with Claus tomorrow.
G-Going out?!
W-We're just meeting there, s-so it's no big...
Yui, your face is beet red.
I'm going back to the room!
Are you not going with her?
After I pick up Perf and Aroma tomorrow,
I want to go shopping around Dreamy Shore.
So I was thinking—
Perhaps I should visit the museum as well.
Huh?
That Claus boy strikes me as someone who's up to no good.
I'm worried about Yui.
Sure, he's kinda strange...
But... I think he's a good kid.
You're getting Prince Kanata a present?
Yeah! It's to thank him for helping with the play.
I'm sure Prince Kanata will love it!
What'll you get him?
I haven't decided...
I'd ask Towa for advice if she were here, but I missed my chance to invite her.
Good thing you've got us with you!
Thanks.
It looks so high class!
It'd look perfect on Prince Kanata!
Yeah, I'm getting this!
Wait out here while I buy it.
Excuse me! About that violin on display out front...
Thank you very much.
I'm back!
Huh? Perf? Aroma?
Perf! Aroma!
Where could they have gone?
Haruno!
What's up?
Lookin' for someone?
Claus!
What are you doing there?
Prince Kanata, we've got trouble!
It's Haruka!
Haruka's in danger!
Hmm... you're sure you saw them here?
Yeah.
I'd be happy to help you search!
Thanks!
But wait, what happened to your meetup with Yui?
Don't worry, I've still got plenty of time.
Oh, you do?
Ah!
What?!
Dreamy Hill
Picture Book Museum
You're not holding it?
No, we've never heard of it.
Oh...
Claus didn't come either, so what's going on?
Sorry for making you tag along.
But I'm glad I met you, Claus.
Earlier, I felt like I was all alone...
and I started to get a little sad...
You know, since I'm always with my friends!
I know, I'm pretty silly!
I mean, it's just for a day!
Oh, you're not silly.
'Cause you're about to be all alone for a long time to come.
Huh?
You chose to push your friends away.
And those friends chose their dreams over you...
their dear, delusional dreams.
Claus?
You said you wanted to protect dreams and help people follow them.
But...
when everyone puts their dreams first...
you'll be left all alone!
Your dreams are important!
Close!
I have an awful feeling about this!
Stop!
Freeze!
We shall not...
Let you through.
It is Dysdark's work!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
We'll let ourselves through!
Prepare yourself this instant!
This whole time...
Well, what now,
my abandoned little princess?
Precure!
Princess Engage!
You really think you can take me on alone,
Cure Flora?!
Over there!
It's Flora!
Y'know, I'm finally startin' to see...
just how wonderful dreams are.
You said you were sad? Of course you are!
Dreams tear your bonds apart!
Dreams shackle you!
Those dreams you hold so dear...
drive you into despair!
Nightmares are dreams, too!
Haruka!
Surge, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Flame!
This should do.
We've served our role.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What were they here for?
If they aimed to slow us down,
they must be after...
Oh no!
Yui!
Go on!
I shall.
Haruka...
How's it feel to be betrayed by your own dream?
You'll face defeat at my hands...
and despair.
All thanks to those wonderful dreams of yours.
Dreams are powerful things.
Haruka...
Never... give up on your dreams.
I'll never despair!
Maybe I was sad.
So what?
Because...
even when we're apart,
everyone stands with me in spirit!
Everyone chases their own dreams...
but that only motivates me to chase my own!
That's why they still support me even when we're apart!
That's all I need to hold my head high!
Got it?
A little gloom won't make me abandon my dream!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
I see.
Yes, your heart may have grown stronger.
And?
Your bravado means nothing in the end.
Haruka!
Hm?
Flora, stay strong!
That human...
He looks familiar, but there's no way he'd be in this world.
Besides, I sense no dreams from him.
Haruka!
Kanata...
You came for me...
Kanata?
Why?
After all the pain you must be in...
It's because you were there for me.
I'll be a princess...
with strength, grace, and beauty...
A princess who can protect everyone's dreams...
That's my dream, after all!
That man is right...
These dreams... they shackle you.
Huh? Kana—
Haruka, that's enough.
You don't need to fight anymore.
You don't need to put yourself through such pain!
What? Kanata, what are you—
If I caused you to turn out this way...
If I caused you to be so bound by your dreams...
then I was mistaken.
Huh?
Dreams will hurt you.
You don't need to dream anymore.
Stop it!
Haruka, I beg you...
don't become a princess!
Not ever.
And so, she finally despairs.
I don't know who he is, but he did a fine job.
My mission's finally accomplished.
Haruka!
Brother!
Haruka?
Princess Towa!
Prince Kanata... he...
What in the world happened?
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
The Forest of Despair has struck Dreamy Shore?
Haruharu's despair made it spread?
What happened to Haruka while we were gone?
Why? Why can't I transform anymore?!
Was it a mistake to become a princess?
But... Kanata...
Go! Princess Precure:
The Flower of Dreams is in Bloom!
Dance, O Reborn Princess!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!