♪ I THINK IT'S TIME
WE BLOW THIS SCENE. ♪
♪ GET EVERYBODY
AND THEIR STUFF TOGETHER. ♪
♪ OK, 3, 2, 1.
LET'S JAM. ♪
[BUBBLING]
FROZEN. FROZEN HARD.
YEAH. THEY'RE NO GOOD.
UGH.
FULL OF TOXIC DIOXINS.
I SAVED THESE FOR EVIDENCE
A WHILE BACK, BUT... HUH?
HEY, HOLD ON!
I KNOW YOU'RE HUNGRY,
BUT THOSE THINGS ARE POISON!
[MUNCHING LOUDLY]
A CONFIDENCE MAN
WHO CONS WOMEN
THAT'S WHO YOU WANT TO CATCH?
I DON'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE.
IS HE A BIG, TOUGH CROOK?
SMALLEST OF THE SMALL FRIES.
SPIKE'S GOING TO HATE IT
WHEN I TELL HIM ABOUT IT.
UGH.
EDWARD WANTS CHOCOLATE!
GUESS I'LL DO IT ALONE, THEN.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!
[PANTING]
[BARKING]
HMM?
OH, CUT ME SOME SLACK.
[BARKING]
[SNORING]
[SNIFFING]
[MOANS]
IT STINKS!
OOH!
UGH!
REALLY, WEREN'T YOU TAUGHT
TO CLEAN UP YOUR OWN POOP?
LIKE, BURY IT OR SOMETHING?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO IT IS YOU REMIND ME OF.
NOW I KNOW.
IT'S THAT GUY WITH
THE THIN EYEBROWS
WITNEY HAGAS MATSUMOTO.
I WONDER WHY I SUDDENLY
THOUGHT OF HIM OUT OF
THE BLUE LIKE THAT.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
A SECRET ABOUT MY PAST?
DO YOU?
[YAWNS]
MISS MANLY, DOES IT LOOK LIKE
THE PATIENT IS REVIVING?
WHY, YES, DOCTOR.
I BELIEVE SHE IS.
MISS MANLY, DOES SHE LOOK
LIKE AN OLD WOMAN TO YOU?
NO, SHE DOESN'T, DOCTOR.
DO YOU THINK SHE'S BEEN
SUCCESSFULLY UNFROZEN?
I BELIEVE SO, DOCTOR.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HUH? YOOHOO.
I AM DR. BACCHUS
BACCHUS, AS IN
THE BACCHUS THAT DROWNED
MORE HUMANS THAN NEPTUNE.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
ABOUT THAT BACCHUS?
HMM?
WELL, I USED TO BE
AN ALCOHOLIC BACK THEN.
BACCHUS WAS DROWNING
BECAUSE OF BACCHUS.
HEY, THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
[LAUGHING MANIACALLY]
OH. NOW, OPEN NICE AND WIDE.
AHH.
MMHMM.
YOU'RE HEALING BEAUTIFULLY.
NO WOUNDS LEFT, AND THE CELLS
ARE DIVIDING QUITE NICELY.
SO YOU ONLY HAVE
ONE PROBLEM LEFT,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THAT IS, HUH?
COMING UP WITH
30 MILLION WOOLONGS
FOR THE BASIC OPERATION,
IN ADDITION TO 54 YEARS
OF INTEREST PAYMENTS.
UH, HOW MUCH IS THAT?
273 MILLION.
ADD THE HOSPITAL FEES TO THAT,
AND THE TOTAL IS
300,280,000 WOOLONGS.
RIGHT!
SO WHEN YOU'VE PAID
THAT AMOUNT, YOU'LL BE FREE.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
GOOD! THEN EVERYTHING'S
JUST-- WHAT DID YOU SAY?
THIS PLACE... WHERE IS IT?
WHERE AM I?
WHO ARE YOU?
[LAUGHING]
MISS MANLY?
SHE IS NOT ACTING, DOCTOR.
I AM WITNEY HAGAS MATSUMOTO,
YOUR LAWYER.
LAWYER?
TOTUS INSURANCE COMPANY
BROUGHT ME IN ON THE CASE.
I'VE ALREADY
DONE SOME RESEARCH
ON YOUR PAST,
MISS FAYE VALENTINE.
IS THAT REALLY MY NAME?
IT'S AN ESPECIALLY
LOVELY NAME.
I THINK IT SUITS YOU VERY WELL.
AND SO...?
WE NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT YOUR MEMORY.
HMM.
THAT'S A MONITOR,
A HOT WATER POT.
THAT'S A CELLULAR PHONE.
SO I REMEMBER EVERYTHING,
REALLY... EVERYTHING
EXCEPT MY OWN LIFE.
I SEE.
AND?
AND ACCORDING TO
THE RECORDS THAT WE HAVE,
WHEN YOU WERE 20
WELL, IN A SENSE,
YOU STILL ARE 20
YOU WERE INVOLVED IN
A SERIOUS ACCIDENT.
ACCIDENT?
THEY COULDN'T SAVE YOU
WITH THE MEDICAL
TECHNOLOGY BACK THEN.
BUT I'M TOTALLY FINE.
YOU CAN SEE THAT.
I DON'T HAVE A SCRATCH.
"BACK THEN"?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE ACCIDENT
IT WAS 54 YEARS AGO.
[GASPS]
YOU WERE PUT
INTO A COLD SLEEP
IN OTHER WORDS, CRYOGENICALLY
PRESERVED, UNTIL NOW.
MEDICAL TECHNOLOGY HAS
FINALLY ADVANCED TO A POINT
WHERE YOU COULD BE FULLY
CURED AND REAWAKENED.
YOU MIGHT SAY YOU'RE A MODERN
VERSION OF SLEEPING BEAUTY.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
I'M VERY SERIOUS, FAYE.
THEN... I'M DREAMING.
[SIGHS]
LISTEN TO ME.
THE YEAR IS 2068.
THIS IS NOT A MONITOR.
IT'S A WASHING MACHINE.
[BEEP BEEP]
THIS ISN'T A HOT WATER POT.
IT'S A FACE CLEANER.
AND THIS IS NOT A CELL PHONE.
IT'S A BIOTHERMOMETER.
YOU PUT THE ROUND END
IN YOUR MOUTH, AND--
LIAR!
YOU THINK I'M GOING TO BELIEVE
A LOAD OF RUBBISH LIKE THAT?
UNH!
[BEEP]
TEMPERATURE 94.1,
PULSE 54, BLOOD PRESSURE 40/75.
IT'S STILL LOW.
HOLD ON!
YOUR MEMORY IS TRAPPED
IN AN EARLIER ERA,
WHEN CELL PHONES
HAD SOLAR ANTENNAS.
THEN TELL ME
WHAT KIND OF ACCIDENT?!
I NEED TO KNOW!
WHAT WAS I LIKE BEFORE?
CALM DOWN.
IF YOU GET TOO EXCITED,
YOU COULD--
WHAT? WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TO ME IF I...
UH...
[SIGHS]
YOU'LL PASS OUT, FAYE.
OH, BROTHER.
[TROPICAL BIRD CHIRPING]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
[VEHICLE SPEEDS PAST]
OH? OH.
AAH!
HEY THERE!
WANT A COLD ONE?
AAH!
[LAUGHING]
[PANTING]
OH.
OH!
HEY! HEY! HEY!
WAIT! COME BACK HERE!
[PANTING]
[WHIMPERING]
OH!
MISS VALENTINE!
HELLO!
UNH!
OH, OH, AAH!
WAIT! PLEASE!
STAY AWAY FROM ME!
WHAT DO YOU GET
BY RUNNING AWAY?
[WHIMPERING]
AAH!
[PANTING]
LISTEN,
MISS VALENTINE, PLEASE.
[CRYING]
I CAN'T PAY 300 MILLION.
IT'S NOT FAIR TO REVIVE ME
AND THEN EXPECT ME TO
PAY ALL THAT MONEY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT MYSELF.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
[SOBBING]
YOU CAN DEAL WITH THE DEBT
PAYMENTS LITTLE BY LITTLE.
I'LL DO EVERYTHING
I CAN TO HELP YOU.
AND, YOU KNOW, SOMEDAY YOUR
MEMORY MIGHT COME BACK TO YOU.
IF YOU HANG IN THERE, YOU
MIGHT MEET SOMEONE WONDERFUL.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S AN I.D.
IF YOU SHOULD DIE,
OR IF YOU FORGET YOURSELF,
THEY KNOW WHO YOU ARE
AND WHERE YOU'RE FROM.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE ONE.
I DON'T HAVE AN I.D. AT ALL.
[STOMACH GROWLING]
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK ♪
♪ OH, YES, I'D MOVE TO WHERE ALL
THE SHOOTING STARS ARE GONE ♪
♪ WITH ALL OF OUR WISHES ♪
♪ HOW COULD THEY BEAR ♪
♪ OH, NO, TO CARRY AROUND
THE STUPID HUMAN HOPES? ♪
♪ SO I'M GOING TO HELP ♪
♪ I WILL ♪
♪ GIVE ME A KEY TO LOCK THE DOOR
TO THE SECRET PARADISE ♪
♪ THERE ARE SO MANY QUEUING UP ♪
♪ AND I WON'T LET THEM IN ♪
♪ LOOK AT THEM ♪
♪ THEY ARE CHEEKY ♪
♪ THEY ARE NEVER
WORTHY TO BE SAVED ♪
♪ LAY YOUR HEART, LAY YOUR SOUL
UPON MY MAGIC CARPET... ♪
WHAT'S THAT?
COLLECTION AGENTS.
THE INSURANCE COMPANY
GOT IMPATIENT.
WHAT DO WE DO?
♪ REMEMBER, SURRENDER ♪
♪ THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO ♪
♪ 'CAUSE LOVE'S SUCH A JOKE ♪
♪ LIKE A LITTLE
JACK-IN-THE-BOX... ♪
IF WE STAY HERE,
WE'LL BOTH GET CAUGHT.
YOU'D BETTER
JUMP OUT AND RUN.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I'LL MEET YOU
AT THE MEDICAL CLINIC.
ALL RIGHT?
BUT WHY ARE YOU
HELPING ME LIKE THIS?
A PRINCE HAS TO PROTECT
SLEEPING BEAUTY.
THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS.
[PANTING]
[EXPLOSION]
OH!
[SOBS]
WE JUST WENT THROUGH
ALL OF HIS PAPERWORK.
IN THE EVENT OF
AN UNFORESEEN ACCIDENT,
HIS INSTRUCTIONS
WERE TO TRANSFER
ALL OF HIS ASSETS TO YOU.
IF YOU GIVE US
A THUMBPRINT HERE,
EVERYTHING HE OWNS
WILL BE YOURS.
OH!
OH, WITNEY!
HE REALLY DID CARE.
[CRYING]
SO... PRESS THIS
WITH YOUR THUMB.
[BEEPING]
[GASPS]
WHY ARE ALL THE NUMBERS
THERE IN RED?
HMM.
THOSE ARE ALL HIS DEBTS,
BUT THEY SAY DEBT IS AN ASSET.
HIS DEBTS?
[LAUGHING]
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING!
OF COURSE, I CAN SEE
NOW HOW STUPID I WAS.
I MEAN, IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
HE RISKED HIS LIFE TO SAVE ME.
AND HIS DEBT WELL, IT WAS A DROP
IN THE BUCKET COMPARED TO MINE.
ALL IN ALL, IT REALLY
WASN'T THAT MUCH.
HUH? OH!
[TOILET FLUSHES]
HOW LONG WERE YOU IN
THERE LISTENING, SPIKE?
TOO LONG.
YOUR STORY NEEDS EDITING.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED,
YOU KNOW.
I'M SURE THAT GUY'S CRYING
IN THE NEXT WORLD...
SINCE HE RAN OFF
WITHOUT PAYING HIS DEBT.
I CAN'T HELP THAT.
IT'S WAY MORE THAN
I COULD EVER PAY.
NOW SHE GETS HUFFY ABOUT IT.
WHY SHOULDN'T I?
REMEMBER, I'M A LOT
OLDER THAN YOU.
YOUR PAST IS ALWAYS CHANGING.
LAST TIME, YOU SAID
YOU WERE A GYPSY.
MAYBE YOU MADE
THIS STORY UP, TOO.
THINK WHAT YOU LIKE,
BUT IT'S NOT A LIE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW
THE WHOLE TRUTH, ALL RIGHT?
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
WELCOME BACK!
THIS GUY HAS A REP
AS A DON JUAN.
HE'S REALLY JUST
A CHEAP CONFIDENCE MAN.
GIRLS FALL FOR HIM?
TAKE NOTE, WHEN OTHERS ARE
SNOOZING, JET IS ON THE JOB.
MMMH.
MMMH!
OH... UH... UNH!
AAH!
WITNEY HAGAS MATSUMOTO!
UH, YEAH.
LONG TIME NO SEE.
ALL RIGHT, SHE KNOWS HIM,
BUT WHY DOES SHE HAVE
TO TALK TO HIM ALONE?
APPARENTLY,
THEY WERE VERY CLOSE.
WE TALKIN' EX-BOYFRIEND?
YEAH, AND THEY WERE
MADE FOR EACH OTHER.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN LIVING
VERY WELL, MR. LAWYER.
WHY, BECAUSE I'M
A LITTLE PLUMP?
ISN'T THAT BIASED?
I WANT A FULL EXPLANATION.
WELL, I JUST
HAD A FAT IMPLANT.
IT WAS RIGHT AFTER THE ACCIDENT.
THEY SQUEEZE IT IN THROUGH
THE ARMPIT WITH A PLASTIC
NOT THAT!
[SIGHS]
IT'S BEEN OVER 3 YEARS.
YOU LOOK... HEALTHY.
THANKS A LOT.
WERE YOU TRYING TO CREATE
A WHOLE NEW IDENTITY?
I WANTED TO START ALL
OVER... START FROM SCRATCH.
BY CONNING WOMEN
OUT OF THEIR MONEY?
WELL, YOU BECAME
A BOUNTY HUNTER.
I'D SAY IT WAS DESTINY.
SO EVERYONE WAS IN ON IT, HUH?
I HAD NO CHOICE.
THE DOCTOR WAS PROTECTING ME.
I OWED TOO MUCH,
AND NOW HE'S DEAD.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE JUST LET
THEM COME AND ARREST ME.
I COULDN'T ASK FOR MORE
THAN TO HAVE YOU HAND
ME OVER TO THE POLICE.
YOU THINK IT'S SAFE
TO LEAVE THEM ALONE?
WORRIED ABOUT HIM OR HER?
I'M AFRAID SHE MIGHT
LET HIM ESCAPE OR SOMETHING.
WELL, SHE'D HAVE TO
HAVE A HEART TO DO THAT.
DON'T BE FOOLED
BECAUSE SHE ACTS TOUGH.
BABES LIKE HER ARE
THE FIRST ONES TO GO SOFT
WHEN IT COMES TO
AN OLD BOYFRIEND.
IS THAT RIGHT?
WOMEN ARE HOPELESS.
THEY DON'T WORK ON REASON.
WE'RE HERE!
WELCOME, VISITORS!
SO, ARE YOU THE ONES
THAT CONTACTED US?
YEAH.
WANT TO CLAIM A BOUNTY.
HMM. I SEE.
MISS MANLY,
PREPARE FOR RENDEZVOUS.
YES, DOCTOR.
I'M GLAD I GOT TO SEE YOU ONE
LAST TIME... SLEEPING BEAUTY.
LET'S GO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THIS FOR ME.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
[GUNSHOT]
- HMM?
- HUH?
THEY OPENED THE HATCH ALREADY?
HE'S TRYING TO GET OUT.
SHE'S HELPING HIM.
WANT TO BET?
YEAH. I'LL GIVE YOU 4 TO 1.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
DAMN IT, HURRY UP, SPIKE!
I'M TRYING!
WHOA!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
YOU CAN'T SQUEEZE
TWO PEOPLE IN HERE.
JUST DON'T BREATHE SO MUCH.
EXHALE OR SOMETHING.
HEY, WAIT!
STAY BACK!
WE'RE LEAVING!
UNH!
SHE WANTS THE GUY
INSTEAD OF THE MONEY.
JET CAUGHT HIM!
IT'S HIS REWARD, FAYE!
I HAVE SOME HISTORY
TO WORK OUT WITH THIS GUY,
SO I CLAIM FIRST RIGHTS TO HIM
AND TO THE BOUNTY
THAT'S ON HIS HEAD!
IS IT JUST ME,
OR DID THAT NOT MAKE ANY SENSE?
JUST LIKE I SAID
WOMEN DON'T WORK ON REASON.
GET ME OUT OF HERE!
ARE YOU GOING TO
SET HIM FREE OR WHAT?
WE'LL SEE!
[GUNSHOT]
[BEEPING]
OH, MAN!
UNH!
VISITORS, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR ATTENDANCE!
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO WITH ME?
I WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
HUH?
TELL ME, WHO AM I?
TELL ME WHERE THE LIES END
AND THE TRUTH BEGINS.
[CRASH]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL,
I'LL HIT THE COCKPIT.
I'M NOT GOING EASY ON YOU.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS MY LINE.
UNH!
[GASPS]
AAH!
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
ARE A BIG PAIN.
WHO AM I?
ARE YOU SURE YOU
REALLY WANT TO KNOW?
IT'S GOING TO BE
HARD TO SWALLOW.
ARE YOU PREPARED FOR
ALL THE CONSEQUENCES?
I AM.
ARE YOU SURE?
SPIT IT OUT!
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
MYSELF. I SWEAR!
YOU'RE LYING.
WHO AM I
MY PAST, MY FUTURE?
THESE ARE QUESTIONS EVERY HUMAN
ASKS AT LEAST ONE IN THEIR LIFE.
WHO ARE YOU?
HOWEVER, PUBERTY
IS THE ONLY TIME
TO WORRY ABOUT
THINGS LIKE THAT.
ONLY PEOPLE WHO ARE BORED
THINK SUCH THOUGHTS
AFTER A CERTAIN AGE.
I'VE HEARD THAT VOICE
BEFORE SOMEWHERE.
HERE I AM. YOOHOO!
OH, GEES.
IS THAT THE DOCTOR
FROM THE CRYO CLINIC?
SURE SEEMS THAT WAY.
YOU TOLD ME THAT
DOCTOR WAS DEAD!
UH, UH, NOT DEAD
I MEAN, NOT COMPLETELY.
HOW MANY LIES ARE YOU GOING TO
TELL ME BEFORE YOU'RE THROUGH?
UH, UH, UH...
YOU WERE CRYOGENICALLY
PRESERVED IN OUR LABS.
HUH?
THAT IS A VERIFIABLE FACT.
I CAN GUARANTEE IT.
HUH?
WHAT ABOUT MY PAST?
WHO IN THE WORLD AM I?
ACTUALLY, I GAVE YOU
THE NAME "VALENTINE."
YES, I NAMED YOU AFTER
MY FAVORITE LOVE SONG.
ALL THE OTHER
DATA ON YOU WAS LOST
WHEN THE ASTRAL GATE EXPLODED.
SO, YOU SEE,
NO ONE KNOWS WHO YOU ARE
OR WHY YOU WERE PUT
IN A CRYOGENIC STATE.
IS THIS GUY A DOCTOR OR A COP?
HUH?
PILOTED PATROL SHIP 118.
YOU ARE IN A VEHICLE WHICH
HAS BEEN REPORTED STOLEN.
STATE YOUR DEPARTMENT CODE NOW.
I REPEAT, STATE YOUR CODE.
DOCTOR, THIS IS NOT GOOD.
WE'RE GOING TO BE
APPREHENDED HERE.
IT'S VERY UNFORTUNATE,
BUT WE'D BETTER CUT OUR
LOSSES AND MAKE TRACKS.
GOOD CALL, DOCTOR.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN, WITNEY.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
BYE BYE, WITNEY.
UH, WAIT.
WAIT A MINUTE, UNCLE!
DON'T GO!
HE'S YOUR UNCLE?
UHHUH.
[GASPS]
HUH?
HMM.
ARRGH!
I'LL TAKE MY BOUNTY
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
AH, THAT'S BETTER.
AND GOOD RIDDANCE.
WHAT A FITTING PAYBACK FOR
ALL THE SLEAZY LIES YOU TOLD ME.
WELL, THERE IS ONE
PART THAT'S TRUE...
THAT I FELL IN LOVE WITH
YOU WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING.
I FELL IN LOVE
WITH SLEEPING BEAUTY.
UH, NO! I'M LYING!
IT'S JUST ANOTHER LIE!
YOU KNOW.
HMM.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
YOU MUST REALLY WANT ME BACK.
YEAH. NICE TRY.
YOU WERE JEALOUS.
IN YOUR DREAMS.
I'M STILL IN THE DARK.
I MAY NEVER KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT MY PAST.
DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER, DOES IT?
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE A PAST.
AND YOU HAVE A FUTURE.
THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S YOUR SHARE OF THE BOUNTY
THE BIG 19,800 REWARD.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
THE SMALLEST OF
THE SMALL FRIES.
SO IT WASN'T 19,800.
I KIND OF PUT
AN EXTRA ZERO IN THERE.
HA HA.
SO I HAVE TO ADMIT, THE NEXT
EPISODE OF "COWBOY BEBOP" IS,
WELL... IT'S KIND OF DEPRESSING.
VERY DEPRESSING, ACTUALLY.
THE ONLY CHARACTERS WHO SHOW UP
ARE A BUNCH OF MUSTY OLD GUYS.
I HATE TO SAY THIS,
BUT IT'S KIND OF HEAVY-HANDED.
CHILDREN SHOULDN'T WATCH IT.
LADIES SHOULD AVOID IT, TOO.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
IT'S BETTER IF YOU YOUNG
GUYS DON'T TUNE IN, EITHER.
NEXT EPISODE
BLACK DOG SERENADE.
OH, ALL YOU OLD GUYS, I WOULDN'T
MISS THIS ONE IF I WERE YOU.