Sis...
I can't do this!
Doesn't that sword power up by taking goddesses' lives?
And you and I are the only goddesses left.
One of us has to be sacrificed in order to take that thing down!
Sis...
Do it, Nepgear.
Okay.
Got it.
Forgive me!
Ouchies!
Sis...
Sis!
What?
It's useless!
We're all still here!
Useless, useless, useless!
Useless,
Useless!
N-No!
I'll bweak...
Her fever's not going down at all.
The poor thing.
An illness where you keep having
nightmares about bad ends, was it?
Yes.
It took me three days to finally remember that the CPU
from three generations ago fell prey to it as well.
Apparently it's called "Bad End Syndrome."
Bad End Syndrome...
How was that, Sis?
My swordsmanship has improved quite a bit, wouldn't you say?
Indeed.
As a reward, I'll allow you to purchase this eggplant.
Who the hell are you?!
All they have in common is the pigtails...
Looks like Uni's caught
the same illness.
Looks like Uni's caught the same illness.
Looks like Uni's caught
the same illness.
Thanks for everything, Sis.
We'll live happily ever after.
Kekeke.
Come, my little lovelies.
Let us seal our vows with a little licking!
Please, no licking...
Gross...
No...
Same here.
I'm worried that this nightmare might
have a bad influence on them.
I want to cure them
as soon as possible.
Don't you worry!
Histoire remembered the remedy for it as well.
Right?
Yes.
If you boil a Walkthrough Flower and ingest it,
you'll be cured of this illness in no time.
Really?
Where can I find one?
Their numbers have really dwindled lately.
I hear they used to grow in some caves near the Lowee-Lastation border,
but I'm not sure if that still holds.
So long as we have
the slightest chance...
So long as we have the slightest chance...
...we'll go look for it!
So long as we have
the slightest chance...
...we'll go look for it!
But this isn't enough.
Don't you have any other information?
There's one other place that's rumored to have it,
but it's quite far away.
I'll go as far as I have to!
That's right.
We have to do this for the girls!
Is that so?
Well, the place in question...
Yahoo!
Who would've thought this "faraway" place would lie in another dimension?
I had no idea our Histoire had learned how to open dimensional portals!
Look!
That must be this dimension's Planeptune.
We can see Plutia there...
Yeah, and...
P-ko too!
Only 1 hour of games per day!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
Huh?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Wait, what?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
#.13 The Promised Happily
Ever After (True End)
Whaaat?
Ow...
And here I wanted to transform and make a graceful landing!
Why?!
Maybe we can't activate our HDD forms in this dimension.
Blanc! And...
Oh?
M-Me?
Zoinks!
Noire too?
Hey, what's the big idea?
An indecipherable algorithm
How could you just fall on me like that?
And a long-awaited installation
Don't you have an ounce of sense in your body?
There's nothing wrong with kicking back and relaxing
This is weird.
Noire and Blanc should be
over at the caves right now.
So pick the easy mode
Oh, I know!
We don't notice the missing pixels
This must be a fake Noire!
Impostoire for short!
Or what they signify
That's not shorter at all.
And before we know it, we're locked into nightmare mode
And I'm not a fake.
For that matter, who are you?
Me? I'm...
But you hold all the flags in your hand
Neppy!
A single button press can change everything
Vert!
So open up that hidden treasure chest
Hey, Plutia!
We meet again.
And complete this quest
I'm glad to see you made it.
Rules, regulations, and the end of the world
So you're the ones Plutia told us about...
Are all story elements we don't need
The goddesses of the other dimension, I take it?
Let's aim for a new world
We're the CPUs here.
What?
Twinkle, twinkle Gracie*Star
But I did tell you.
Build a bridge connecting the past
That there was a Noire, Blanc, and Vert in this dimension too.
To a brand new future
Really? Did you really tell us that they were such spitting images?
History keeps on repeating itself
I did too.
Deck it in the colors of a rainbow
Do I look that similar to your Blanc?
And grab hold
Totally.
You two look and talk the same!
Of a hyperdimensional victory
Looks like your personalities
are the same, too.
Twinkle, twinkle Fortune*Star
That means the Noire you know must also be a top-tier CPU.
And lead us to a brand new day
Right. I guess Noire's a loner over here too.
Let's aim for
Say what?
It really is the size that counts, isn't it?
A hyperdimensional victory
And grab hold
Indeed. Size rules the world.
Of an ultradimensional victory
Double boing!
She's twice as annoying today.
Man, it just wouldn't feel right without this.
Such a soothing sight.
Welcome.
Whoa! It's this dimension's Histoire!
So tiny!
So cute!
R-Really?
Hey, Plutia,
lemme have your Histoire!
No can do.
Spoilsport.
P-ko...
Come here, P-ko!
Nep... tun...
Oh, it's fine.
Both Neptune and Neptuna are fine by me.
Call me whatever you want.
You'll still be the same to me.
Now, come on!
Nep...
Neptuna!
P-ko!
Uncle!
So weak, Neptuna!
I see you've made a full recovery, P-ko.
That's where we'll find the Walkthrough Flowers?
Supermova
Book of Divine Skills
The Cursed Hell Devil Death Bloody Spectral Tower.
Apparently they're at the top of the tower,
on the 10,000th floor.
Supermova
Book of Divine Skills
The 10,000th floor?
That's one crazy name.
It must be filled with
super-dangerous monsters, right?
Indeed. I couldn't begin to tell you.
If it weren't for this situation,
we wouldn't want to go anywhere near it either.
Wait, "we"?
We're coming with you.
You can't transform, right?
P'll go too!
Gotta keep Neptuna safe!
Thanks, Plutia...
All of you...
Thank you too, P-ko.
Um, please don't forget.
The portal back to your dimension will open in three hours.
Here.
The next time we'll be able to open one will be three whole years from now!
So be sure to make it back to the Basilicom in time!
But, you know,
isn't it impossible to go up and down 10,000 floors in three hours?
It says here that there's a warp point near the top floor that'll let you get out in an instant.
Three hours is enough time for a one-way trip.
Still feels like cutting it close.
Not like we have a choice, though.
All right.
Let's head to the Cursed Blah Blah Spectral Tower!
Who'd've thought we'd find a newly-constructed elevator
that takes you directly from the 4th floor to the 9,999th?
But that two-and-a-half-hour elevator ride wore me out.
By the way, it says we have to use a warp point
to get to the top floor from here.
It also says there are some
formidable monsters on this floor.
Yes. They're already here.
These look tough.
Makes me wanna go wild!
I'll join you.
We'll take care of these scrubs!
Go on ahead, ladies.
Thanks!
We'll take you up on that offer!
There are two warp points, Bert!
You're right.
Wait, "Bert"?
Did you just call me Bert?
Yup.
Bert!
What's up, Vert?
She called me by a nickname for the first time.
Are you crying? Now, of all times?
Vert's been longing for someone to do that, huh?
Here are some more.
It's finally my turn!
Me too!
Now bring it on!
I'll hold them while you reach the climax, girls.
Glad to see you haven't changed.
Thanks anyway!
Whoa, that was close! This one leads upstairs.
Made it to the top!
There should be Walkthrough Flowers somewhere around here.
P'll look for it!
Yeah. Let's split up!
Make like a kangaroo...
and hop!
This is it! I found some!
Neptune?!
This thing's way too huge!
Run for it!
Not this way too!
We're done for!
Neptuna!
P-ko.
Neptuna, Bert, run!
Okay, thanks!
Almost there.
Stop that!
Lemme go!
Vert...
I'll take these, Neptune,
but you'd better make it back too.
Got it!
I'll be right there, P-ko!
Hey!
Let her go!
Neptuna...
P-ko!
Hurry, Plutia.
Oh, I should open the portal.
Wait. Neptune's not here yet.
Don't you have to get those flowers to Gear and gang?
Stop bullying Neptuna!
Let's go, P-ko!
Okay, Neptuna!
I'm opening the portal.
Please take care of Neptune.
I'm sure Neppy'll be just fine.
Neptuna...
Why didn't you go?
You were in trouble.
How could I possibly leave you behind?
But...
That's not all.
I wanted to fight with you.
This time as allies.
Neptuna...
Hey!
What are you still doing here?
Good work, ladies.
Don't give us that.
What will you do now?
Don't sweat it. Things'll work out somehow.
I'm the protagonist, after all.
Right?
Let's get back to the Basilicom for now.
Huh? That's weird.
Should I take it out and blow on it?
Don't be so rough...
That surprised me!
What just happened?
Neptune?
Peashy, too.
How?
Noire, Blanc...
Huh?
Huuuh?
What?
No way.
Me?
I'm here too.
What's going on?
Are they your dimension's Noire and Blanc?
Yeah. That means...
Did I just cross dimensions due
to a malfunctioning warp point?
Go me!
I'm not the protagonist for nothing!
Brotagonist!
You really do look just like me.
That's a cute outfit.
As is yours.
I can't believe this.
Hey, are you...
Wh-What is it?
Are you a loner?
Say what?!
Don't, Peashy!
I only just upgraded to the new model!
Gotta play with Nepgear!
I will, I will!
Please, just give that back!
That's P-ko for you.
No mercy, even for people
who've only just recovered!
I'm sure she's just really happy.
So the portal that opened due to that malfunction is still open?
Can we use it to go back
and forth all we want now?
Probably.
It should be fine for a while.
In that case, I'd like to meet Compa and my counterparts in the other dimension sometime.
Yeah.
I'd love to meet them too!
I thought this might come up,
so I brought a picture of them.
No way.
They're kids?
Iffy looks so cute!
N-No, Compa's cuter.
Oh, it's done!
What's going on?
You'll find out soon enough.
Here. For you.
Wait, is this...
Peashy made it.
P's pudding!
That's amazing, P-ko.
There's enough for everyone.
All right, girls.
Let's make a toast with P-ko's pudding!
To Planeptune,
to the two dimensions,
and to Gamindustri...
Cheers!
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!