What shall I do?
Takuto tried to let Mitsuki go to an audition
despite my efforts to stop them!
I had to do something about it!
Since then, I've tried to interfere
at every turn,
so that I could fulfill my duties!
That actually worked out.
And by the time they arrived
at the audition site,
it was all over and
the winner was about
to be announced.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
The Mermaid Tear image character
will be Madoka Wakamatsu.
No!
The assignment...is over.
Mitsuki!
Ms. Oshige...
Hey, you're running away?!
Mitsuki!
You...
I'm sorry, Ms. Oshige.
I'm really sorry!
Why didn't you tell me about
your throat illness!
What?
Dr. Wakaoji!
W-What?!
Dr. Wakaoji, Mitsuki's right here,
so please take her to the hospital quickly.
Mitsuki? Do you, by any chance,
mean Miss Full Moon?
Isn't that obvious?!
She's not the Mitsuki I'm talking about.
What?
Oh no, what should I do?
Who in the world...are you?
What are you saying?!
The genuine, authentic Mitsuki!
Run away!
What?
Mitsuki?! Wait a minute!
Mitsuki!
It seems they're not after us.
What should I do?
I think they realize that Full Moon
and the 12-year-old me are the same.
No way!
There's no way in the world
they'll think you transformed!
Oh, I can't go back to the two of them.
And I can't go on as Full Moon.
Mitsuki...
Here.
Lift your head up.
Let's get away from here.
Y-Yeah.
They're a little bit big,
but put up with it.
I also wanted to let her do what
she wanted with the time that was left.
I feel bad for her, but becoming
Full Moon was not a good idea.
Dr. Wakaoji, hurry!
The girl shouldn't have gotten very far!
Like I told you, I didn't come for that girl,
I came to look for Mitsuki.
And that's the girl, right?
I believed your phone call and came,
but it can't be helped if
the essential Mitsuki doesn't appear.
Anyway, I'll search for Mitsuki myself.
Oh, Dr. Wakaoji!
Fine! I'll look for her by myself!
Fool!
C'mon, why are you
so absent-minded?
It's dangerous!
Y-Yeah.
I can't let you die yet.
You're...you're...
Hey, isn't that Full Moon?
Huh? That can't be.
There's no way she'd be
in a place like this.
But...
What should I say at times like this?!
Ma'am, would you like
iced barley tea or something?
No, thank you.
But you must be tired from walking.
I'm fine.
Why?
I see, so you haven't seen her.
Thank you.
Where in the world are you, Mitsuki?
Yes!
As her promoters, we'd like to refrain from
any official comments at this time.
No, nothing like retirement.
Yes... Yes!
If that's all.
Jeez! What's going to happen?!
I'm sorry!
If this continues, we'll be all
off schedule starting tomorrow!
I understand.
I'll definitely find her today!
Hey, it's the manager's car.
Just this instant,
a car believed to be carrying
someone connected to Full Moon
hastily left the office.
Mr. Takeda,
you've met Full Moon
in interviews for magazines
and things, haven't you?
Yes.
It isn't long after her debut,
but she's a very pure, good girl.
She was too naïve.
She went into the entertainment industry
without taking it seriously.
She probably got tired of it
and gave up.
No, she's a singer who's tough
on the inside.
To think that it's over like this...
I don't want to believe it.
At last I've come to the edge.
Eichi...
I might not be able to reach you
with my songs anymore.
Where am I?
Oh, I'm in the lighthouse.
I wonder where Takuto went.
The moon pendant that Eichi gave me.
It broke.
I wanted to cherish it forever.
At that time I made a decision
to protect you.
A song?
Why can't I make this
a good memory?
Too far, too close...
That's my song.
I can't reach it.
"Let's forget about it."
The more I tell myself
to forget about it,
This voice is so soothing.
the memory of you becomes greater.
Who in the world is it?
What? What?!
Takuto...
Like a lost crying child
looking for something.
There's no eternity there.
"You don't have to trust anyone."
You said.
Are we both the same?
At that time I made
a decision to protect you.
Why can't I make this
a good memory?
Too far, too close...
I can't reach it.
"Let's forget about it"
The more I tell myself
to forget about it,
the memory of you
becomes greater.
Somehow it's heartbreaking.
That's right, I'm the only person
who can hear Takuto's singing.
That's right, even though that's
not the case for my singing...
To that many people...
Even to Takuto...
Furthermore...
Surely sometime to Eichi.
I still want to sing after all!
What are you doing?
What?
Umm... Well...
They've always said the early bird
gets the worm, so, uh...
What are you talking about?
Well? What are you going
to do from now on?
What do you mean,
"what will I do"?
Why don't we just
go to America?
What?
Going to America and singing
may be a faster way to reach Eichi.
America, huh?
Maybe I'll do that.
Huh?
I guess going to America is a good idea.
I've got nothing to lose.
Mitsuki...
But...I wonder if it's okay.
What?
My English.
You know, "Love Me Do."
I read it like "Rabu mee doh."
At last, your smile has returned.
You're better when you're laughing.
Takuto...
It's pretty.
Yeah.
Takuto...
Yes?
I think I'll confide in Dr. Wakaoji
and Ms. Oshige about everything.
What?
And if I tell them everything and
they don't forgive me, it can't be helped.
Even so, I want to sing.
But Takuto, I'm going to tell them
about Death Spirits, is that okay?
You should do what you want.
I'll always be there
to support your dreams.
Thank you, Takuto!
F-Fool! Don't hug me for no reason!
I...I like your singing Takuto.
I thought you were listening.
After all, it shows that
you're a kind person.
Again! Saying such
embarrassing things!
But it's the truth!
Don't use words such as "like" so easily.
Stupid Mitsuki.
Especially when
the one you like best is Eichi.
Mitsuki!
Dr. Wakaoji, Ms. Oshige...
I'm sorry that I've caused you trouble.
What?
Mitsuki, do you have a fever?
A cough?
I'm fine.
Well anyway, let's rest in a hospital room.
I'll call your grandmother
right away.
No, Dr. Wakaoji.
I came because I have
something to tell you.
Hm? Something to tell me?
You're Mikatsuki,
Mitsuki's little sister, aren't you?!
Isn't that what you told me
when we met once before?
I'm sorry, at that time...
I told a lie.
What?
Ms. Oshige, I'm Mitsuki.
Okay, well... What about Full Moon,
who I always meet?
That's me too.
Th-There's no way that's true.
That's why I came to talk to you.
Mitsuki!
Be firm.
Yeah.
Dr. Wakaoji, do you remember the day
that I asked you about the audition?
Yes.
The truth is, after you went home,
something happened.
A Death Spirit named Takuto
appeared before me.
He said that I had one year to live.
This talk of a Death Spirit saying you
have one more year to live, that's just—
Ms. Oshige, let's listen to a little bit
more of what she has to say.
Y-Yes.
Continue.
Yes, I heard that and thought that
this is my only chance
to audition and become a singer.
But...for that audition you
had to be 16 years old.
So then Takuto...
Okay.
I'll make you sixteen years old.
Since then, I've been able to transform
into 16-year-old Full Moon.
Only I can see Takuto,
so I understand why you can't easily
believe what I've said just now.
But if you don't believe me,
I won't be able to become Full Moon
and sing again.
I understand what you've said,
but I wonder if it's reality.
Well, well.
If you tell them and they don't believe you,
all there is to do is show them.
Takuto!
Okay?
Yeah.
Dr. Wakaoji, Ms. Oshige...
So you know that I'm not lying,
please watch.
Takuto... Please.
Yeah.
Dr. Wakaoji, Ms. Oshige,
this is the 16-year-old me.
Mitsuki?
Can you believe what I've said?
H-Hey, Mitsuki, is this true?
Are you possibly showing us
some magic?
You were shown right before your very
eyes and you still don't believe it?
What's this?!
It's Takuto.
I'm Takuto, the Death Spirit.
Normally I'm not in this form,
but I can't talk to you
unless I am in this form.
You're truly...a Death Spirit?
All we can do is believe it,
Mitsuki borrows this Takuto's power
and transforms into a 16-year-old.
If so, the things that
happened up until now...
It all make sense.
But...to say that you only
have one year left,
that alone I don't accept.
Even if that's not so,
she can't put stress on her throat!
But when she becomes
her 16-year-old self, she's perfectly healthy.
What?
Really?
Yes.
That can't be!
If you don't believe, you should give
her an examination later.
So that's why, Doctor,
I want to continue singing.
Please!
Not a chance, Mitsuki.
Why?!
I don't have time.
In the time I have left,
I want to continue singing.
I want to reach Eichi
as soon as possible.
And then...
That's not it.
What?
It's not singing or life.
You sing to live, and live to sing.
Ms. Oshige...
Dr. Wakaoji!
Can't you do something for Mitsuki?
Until she's realized her dreams,
if only for that interval.
Please! Dr. Wakaoji!
Mitsuki, can you give me a little time?
I'd like you to let me think.
I'm thinking that I'd like to do
everything I can for you.
It's your life, after all.
And I want to let you walk down
the road that you wish.
Dr. Wakaoji said what he did.
Cheer up, Mitsuki.
Okay.
Hey Takuto, are you going
to let things continue as is?
Meroko left.
Jeez! Aren't you angry?
It's her fault that you didn't
make the audition.
That's true
I'm sure that Meroko had
her own reasons.
C'mon, how easygoing
can you be?
I don't care! If she wants to come back,
she can come back on her own.
Oh, Takuto!
Next time on Full Moon:
"Meroko, All Alone."
- Look forward to it!