Hey, Hideyoshi, what are we doing for today's extra classes— Huh?
W-What didst thou say, A-Akihisa?
Suspicion
You look... different today.
D-Do I?
I'm— I do believe I am always like this, nay?
Are not my height and face the same as usual?
Umm... You usually look more feminine and cute—
A single or a couple without love, which one is...
FABULOUS?
Love!
How far do we take our chat
of my colorfully rotating future?
Pretending not to notice!
How far do we take our chat of my colorfully rotating future?
My feelings for this giant world are evergrowing
I'm loving today, too
I'm really looooo-ving it!
looooo-ving it!
My idiocy is truly more vast than the ranks of the stars
Honestly still cannot accept that
I had a dream of walking with you
Still I'm sorry
Because I did not know about love, you know.
Answer: You and the riddling me are an infinite jump!
So, Ms. Takahashi, how are things progressing?
Yes, Principal.
Episode 2
Me, that girl, and a plushie
Since you needed someone with good grades and social standing,
I recommend Kinoshita Yuuko from Class A.
Her twin brother, Kinoshita Hideyoshi, has done opera before.
Ms. Yuuko also has a great singing voice.
That's nice. It feels good as the school principal to have such skilled students.
Yes! She has irreproachable conduct, beauty, excellent grades, and social standing.
Finding another exemplary student like her would be impossible.
I'll be Waiting
I love girly boys!
Especially how bluntly Yuichi hits on Shinji.
Wait. I don't have time for this!
I'm home!
Dear sister!
Whatever is the matter, tossing thy favorite literature like that?
Favorite
I wonder why there are things you can do, but I can't.
What art thou talking about?
Ms. Takahashi talked to me today.
At once
She wants me to take part in a promotional video for Fumizuki Academy and sing the school anthem.
Fumizuki
Academy
Promotional video
School
anthem
Sing
Good Lord!
But thou dost not have the slightest sense of scale or rhythm.
Slightest
Guts
Fist
What's that? You wanna fight?
If it bothers thee, thou couldst have refused her.
No way!
All this time, I've been acting like an honor student who can do everything!
Thou always looked impressive and dedicated to me.
Impressive
Dedicated
Applause
Isn't performing arts in the Kinoshita genes?
You act on stage.
I act every day as an honor student at school.
I suppose we really are alike then, thou and I.
Of course we are! I don't want to admit it, but you and I are...
twins...
W-What now?
What is it, dear sister?
You're good at imitating people, aren't you?
I'd prefer if thou called it acting.
Dost thou mean?
Hideyoshi! Your dear sister has a dire request of you!
Body Language
Sister! That is not a request! That is a threat—
Are we really doing this, Sister?
I'm the one who has to go for extra lessons, aren't you glad?
But if our classmates ever find out...
So what if they do?
They will really start calling me a girl.
No one would think you'd swapped places with me, huh?
Here, take this.
What is that?
A listening bug.
This way, I can keep track of everything you do.
Sister! Where in the world didst thou get this from?
A classmate of yours.
I've received some new material.
Sure is a shabby classroom.
Escape in progress
Time left
HP
Sugawa's running away!
Sugawa broke the vow and touched a girl! He's no leader of ours. He's a traitor!
Yuuko (in shock)
Yuuko (really shocked)
Oh, Hideyoshi! We just had worksheets for homework today.
I see.
Man, that Sugawa sure did something stupid.
Urgent! Urgent!
Escape in progress
Time left
HP
We have acquired the testimony of the girl who interacted with Sugawa.
She testified that she has no interest in Sugawa, and that her real target is "Aki."
I repeat: It's Akihisa...
All of them are idiots.
Well then, I hope Hideyoshi's fine.
Thank you, Kinoshita.
That sounds like... Kubo?
You've given me courage.
Oh, I didn't do much, really.
What? What are they talking about?
Kubo
Oh, no! It's reassuring to know there's someone else in the classroom like me.
I didn't know you...
were also interested in same-sex romance.
Oh, Hideyoshi! What is it?
Dear sister! Can I have a moment?
Wait, Hideyoshi!
Sister!
Hideyoshi! I'd really like to know what you were talking about back there.
'Twas mere idle chitchat.
Just how did it become about me being interested in homosexuality?
But given the literature that thou reads—
Idiot! You idiot!
It's just that the doctor's love interest looks like a girl.
I had no such intention—
If you say one more thing that could be misconstrued...
I understand! I do indeed!
Did he really get it?
Yuuko, a moment please.
What is it?
The class representative?
Shouko
Hideyoshi, don't you dare give yourself away.
Yuuko, your skirt's slipping down.
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
You idiot!
Thank you, Class Representative, but... 'tis all right.
But... your skirt...
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
After all...
"After all" what?
I made sure to wear underwear today!
Dear sister!
Do you have anything to say?
I was saying that it was all right
because I'm wearing gym shorts underneath my skirt.
It's not all right!
It makes it sound like I usually don't wear underwear at all!
However, gym shorts are a type of underwear—
Stop blabbering and be more careful about your skirt!
'Tis just that thy skirt is loose around the waist and keeps—
I'll be careful! I'll be really careful!
Good grief!
K-Kinoshita!
Who's that?
Yokomizo
My name is Yokomizo Kouji.
Yokomizo Kouji? Don't think I know him.
I-I love you! Please go out with me!
Did he just confess?
Oh, dear! I don't want to hurt him, but...
Hideyoshi (Yuuko)
I'm sorry. I really appreciate it.
Good. Be evasive!
Then could you tell me what type of boys you like?
Yokomizo
I'm sorry. I...
"You" what?
I'm only interested in cute, childish boys.
I'm not into girls!
And I'm not into young boys!
From what I have analyzed about thy tastes—
That's my taste in fiction!
I've kept that hidden from everyone!
I understand.
From now on, I'll act as you usually do.
Hey, Hideyoshi!
All right... Akihisa!
Weren't thou running away with thy life at stake?
It's all right.
They heard Yokomizo confessed to your sister, so they're chasing him now.
I-Is that so?
Yokomizo, you deserve just as much pity as I do.
Yuuko
Yokomizo's so fickle.
After all, he got rejected by you, so now he's after your sister.
I take that back!
Yuuko
Speaking of your sister...
Your sister is wonderful, isn't she?
W-whatever dost thou mean?
Well, she's cute, good at school, really skilled at sports,
She's a first-rate sister.
T-Thou think'st?
And look!
She's always so beautiful.
Beautiful?
That's why it's such a shame.
I heard she's actually into girls and small boys and goes without undies—
Octopus hold
Forget about that!
What? Why?
I don't really get it, but there's this feeling...
A slight lump against my back.
What do you mean, a slight lump?
They're still developing, got it?
For some reason, there's a rumor at school that my chest is developing.
That's strange.
There are also rumors that I'm into girls and small boys and don't wear underwear.
What now? I shall be treated like a girl even more now.
You have it easy. I've become a third-rate pervert.
It was thy fault for suggesting we swap places!
You're the one who said all those stupid things!
Well, never mind. Let's just drop it.
Yeah, there's no point worrying about it.
There's so much gossiping at our academy already.
Question 3:
Answer the following
question.
Give the correct
intonation for the
underlined word
in the paragraph below.
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
-
Teacher's comment:
Correct.
Generally in words ending with
"-tion", the vowel before "-tion"
gets accented.
You should remember this.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
-
Teacher's comment:
Nice try, but emphasizing
every syllable hoping to get
the correct one won't float
your boat.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
-
Teacher's comment:
Every once in a while,
I have the mistaken impression
that you're actually a genius.
Let's go back one year to the past.
Let's go back
one year to the past
Don't move a muscle!
Put your bags on the desk and open them, so I can see inside.
Don't try anything stupid!
Sakamoto, show me what you have in your pockets.
Damn!
I'm keeping this.
Dammit! Why me?!
Yoshii! Take off your uniform. Change into your gym clothes.
Why? You're being too strict, Teach.
You ought to have more trust in—
Hey, Akihisa, you dropped your PSP.
Oh, thanks, Yuuji.
You ought to have more trust in me!
A jersey's too good for you.
Summoned being, summon!
The first-years have summoning training today.
Man, could this day get any shittier?
Dammit! I'd just bought it last month too.
He took my accessories and gadgets too.
Let's see... I've lost consoles, games, DVDs, CDs, manga...
What dost thou come to school to do, anyway?
It's Himeji's turn.
Huh? Aren't you going to take pictures, Voyeur?
My camera was confiscated.
That's too bad.
You don't get many chances to take a picture of her in gym clothes, since she isn't in our class.
Summoned being, summon!
She's cute and smart! I sure admire her!
By the way, don't you know her from before?
Yeah, we were in the same class in elementary school.
But I haven't talked to her since.
Next! Yoshii Akihisa!
Coming!
Your opponent will be... Shimada!
Shimada! Shimada Minami!
Ah! Here!
Yoshii!
Why were you spacing out like that, Shimada?
Feeling hungry?
I'm not like you.
I get it.
You're just disappointed that your familiar is so pathetic—
I'm glad you're my opponent, Yoshii.
It'll feel so great beating you up!
Our summons are supposed to be fighting, not us.
Oh, right. We aren't supposed to be fighting.
I'm glad you remembered.
I'll just... hit you, anyway.
Shimada.
Look. Even the teacher doesn't want...
Just today.
Thanks!
Why?!
Man, today was just one calamity after another.
H-Himeji!
This is your chance! Talk to her!
I... don't think I can handle this.
Never mind. Retreat!
Please, I beg you!
I really want that Noin! Please!
I can't really do that.
Is something the matter?
Well, this little girl wants that stuffed toy so badly,
but she doesn't have enough money.
Hey, why do you want it so much?
My sister has been down in the dumps lately.
Your sister?
Yes.
She once told me she really liked that doll. That's why...
I see. You wanted to gift it to her and make her happy again, didn't you?
Since we keep moving around, school is really hard for her too.
Even so...
Even so, she cleans the house, does the laundry, and plays with me.
Ah! Don't cry! Let Big Brother help you.
You will?
Big Brother, thank you!
So, how much does that doll cost?
Twenty-five thousand yen.
I'm sorry. Big Brother tried, but he just couldn't do it.
I do have 10,000 yen with me.
So if we add my entire assets of 1,000 yen, we'll have 11,000 yen.
That's almost half of 25,000, isn't it?
It's a... little short, though.
So what if we slice the doll... and take just half?
Are you really in high school?
Big Brother is an idiot.
Reserved
Well, at least we bought some time.
But if we don't get more money...
That's true. Twenty-five thousand yen...
That's almost the price of the stuff I had confiscated this morning.
I know!
What is it?
Hazuki, let's meet at this park tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Okay!
Good!
You want to get the confiscated stuff back?!
Yeah, and I'll need everyone's help.
Then thou do needst the key to Ironman's locker.
The key should be in his coat pocket.
In that case...
throw a bucketful of water on Ironman
and steal the key while he's changing. How's that?
That's the plan. Good luck, Akihisa.
Me?!
The target cometh!
Persevere!
Good luck!
Aren't you going to help me?!
In that case...
Oops. I... slipped!
What?!
Oh no you don't!
Sorry, I slipp—
I think I heard someone say, "Oh no you don't!"
Wow, he was brutal,
but I got the key.
Great! Let's raid Ironman's locker while we have the chance.
It's here!
Well then, grab it and let's go.
Okay!
Huh? Old books?
If they're junk, I might as well...
Phew! That was close!
If I hadn't sold those books, I wouldn't have made the 25,000.
Hey! It's Idiot Brother!
Sorry I'm late!
No biggie!
Huh? What's that?
You see... a pretty lady came here a little while back.
A pretty lady?
She told me to give this doll to my sister...
...but if you bought the big doll, then I could keep it for myself!
Umm, I guess this is yours then.
It... is?
Yep! And...
...this one is for your sister.
Noin!
I hope your sister becomes happy again.
Umm, Big Brother!
Could you bend down a little?
Like this?
Thank you, Big Brother!
Big Brother, you're an idiot, but you're really kind! I love you!
When I grow up some more, I'll make you my husband!
I have a question about yesterday.
It seems someone stole all the confiscated items and my old books.
He had the nerve to display his student ID when he sold them.
What do you think of this, Yoshii?
The thief sure had guts!
He sure did!
Yoshii,  clench your teeth!
I'm sorry! Like this?
Yoshii, I have just the thing for the likes of you.
Here.
Yoshii Akihisa, from now on,
Punishment Inspector
Reflect on what
you've done
you're the Punishment Inspector.
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go
I've fallen in love
I don't want any doubts in my heart
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway
Sparkling, glittering
The right answer is pop!
Big Sis, for you!
For me?
Are you happy now, Big Sis?
Thank you, Hazuki. I'm really happy now!
I know learning Japanese is hard for you, and everything else is too...
Yeah, let's handle it together!
Plus...
What is it?
Lately, I've been...
...interested in this one guy.
Eh? What's he like?
You know... He's in my class.
He's such an idiot, though.
Question 4:
Answer the following
question.
If the numbers in a
standard deck of cards
are added up, what is
the sum?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
There are many ways to
calculate this.
For example, consider
the 1-13 of Spades,
and line them up with
the 13-1 of Hearts.
There are now 13 pairs
of cards, where each pair
adds up to 14. There will be
another such set of pairs
for the remaining Diamonds
and Clubs cards, so altogether
the sum will be
14 x 13 x 2 = 364.
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
1 + 2 + 3 +... umm
Teacher's comment:
Good luck.
Question 4.
If the numbers in a standard deck of cards are added up, what is the sum?
One plus two plus three plus... Umm...
Good luck.
Next time: Me, the real motive, and a man's dignity!
This will be on the test.