We'll be taking the princess.
Princess!
Ann!
Regina!
Mana...
Let's go.
Your father is waiting.
Regina!
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Cheers!
There's nothing like the sweet taste of victory!
Once you're out of the picture,
it'll really be curtains for Trump Kingdom!
You'll finally be awoken, and yet we'll part just after...
It's such a shame!
I've been bustin' my butt the most around here,
so I'm gonna get the credit.
Bel and Mammo are gonna be my lackeys!
Speakin' of which...
Why's she still a popsicle?
We can't get to her like this.
Then let's get smashin'.
It's haaaaaaard.
Simpleton tricks won't work.
H-Hey, that's over the top!
Let go!
You let go! Just let go already...
Enjoy.
Seems we've no choice but to take her to your father.
Yeah...
Regina!
Oh? Something wrong?
Nothing!
Is that so? To me...
you looked like you were thinking about someone else.
No I wasn't!
I wasn't...
To Trump Kingdom!
Save the Princess!
Mister, where are you...
To Trump Kingdom.
I'm certain Ann was taken to King Selfish.
We don't have a moment to lose!
But we don't have a way to get there...
We're stuck...
Don't you worry!
Just stay positive!
It'll work out somehow!
The Royal Crystals!
Could that be...
Should we enter it?
The crystals have shown us the way this whole time!
They must be doing that now!
Let's go!
Allow me to look after Ai.
I wish you luck.
We'll definitely find...
the princess...
Ann...
and take her back!
And I'll have a heart-to-heart with Regina!
Charles!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
The light of wisdom,
Cure Diamond!
The warmth of the sun,
Cure Rosetta!
The blade of courage,
Cure Sword!
Listen to the heartbeat of love!
Dokidoki Precure!
King Selfish,
we have brought the princess of Trump Kingdom.
WHAT TOOK YOU?!
We are deeply sorry!
Still, Regina,
I must commend you.
You've made your father proud!
Thank you, Daddy.
Bring the princess.
Once you are eradicated,
there will be none left to stop me!
You yet resist in your pitiful state?
Regardless, the princess is ours.
For now, let us turn everyone in the human world into a Selfish.
Huh?!
You're going to do to the human world what you did to Trump Kingdom?
Naturally.
But you don't need to if you just want Daddy to move again...
Fool!
Trump Kingdom and the human world are but mere appetizers!
The main course is the universe!
I shall make all Egogy in the universe mine!
You awe me, King Selfish.
No...
You've been unlike yourself for some time, Regina.
We are selfish.
The fate of the human world is not our concern.
Should King Selfish take the gloves off,
neither the human world nor the Precures would survive.
Won't you be glad to say your goodbyes to those pests?
Why... won't it stop?
Those love-spreading Precures can just disappear.
You can't!
Daddy, don't hurt the human world!
What'd you say?
Opposing the will of King Selfish is indeed bold!
Now, apologize immediately, and...
Far too late!
Who do you think you utter your nonsense to?
But—
Silence!
You are no longer any daughter of mine!
A Selfish worrying about a human?
She turned into quite the fool.
Now be gone from my sight!
Leave the cleanup to me.
The heck? A bird?
A meteor?
No...
it's the Precures!
Why did it happen like this?!
Is everyone all right?
Somehow...
We've finally reached Trump Kingdom.
Our battle begins now.
The princess must be there!
Let's hurry...
Not happenin'.
You had to come all the way to Trump Kingdom?
You brats really are a pain.
Perhaps you have a death wish?
Our plans are nothing of the sort!
Those piercing, fiery eyes...
really irritate me!
Get them!
Selfish!
Precure Rosetta Reflection!
Diamond!
We'll hold these enemies off!
Go ahead to the princess!
There's no time for second guessing!
We'll follow you shortly!
Truly irritating!
My lady, if you need a dance partner, I'll satisfy you.
Stop getting in our way!
We could say the same to you!
Precure Sparkle Sword!
Now!
Save Ann!
Right!
Those two really are useless.
No matter.
Those despicable Precures are always spouting their love and friendship drivel.
If it means that much to them,
they can die in the name of love.
Regina!
What happened?
Stay strong!
Cure... Heart...
Good...
Sel...
fish!
Magma?
Fly to the surface ahead of me!
Sure!
I can't!
My powers must be sealed!
How careless.
Why you...
It's showtime!
Take a look, Precures!
Cure Heart!
Regina is with her as well!
How did that happen?
We'll climb up in a flash.
I've got this!
You sure you should move so much?
The thread's going to snap!
Stop!
Okay!
You two are hanging by a lone thread!
That thread is made by this Spider Selfish.
It can only handle the weight of one person.
Meaning it's impossible for the both of you to survive.
But it won't end that way if one of you falls into the magma.
There's no way I'd ever do that!
Your concern for others is your undoing.
You always put others first, allowing me to set this simple trap.
There really is nothing better than being selfish!
You're wrong!
You can't be happy if you can't trust others!
If I can show them how useless their love is by having them both fall into the magma, then that's fine too.
Even on the off chance that Regina sacrifices Cure Heart,
I can just cut the thread.
And once I do, I'll definitely be the #2 Selfish!
And one day...
Hey, Mana,
what are we... to each other?
We're friends.
Sure.
Let's be friends.
What are you talking about?
You're already our friend.
Because we're all friends!
You and everyone else!
Mana... you never change.
Hm?
It's like...
something's been wrong with me since I met you.
When you were nice to me, my heart started to race.
And when you looked sad, my heart started to clench.
What do these feelings mean?
It means you sympathize with others.
It's love.
Love...
maybe... it is.
Mana, I love you!
Regina!
What?!
You can't give up!
But...
No ifs, ands, or buts!
We're not at the end of our rope!
Who the heck do you think I am?
I'm Oogai First Middle School's Student Council President!
Huh?!
Does that mean a lot?
You bet it does!
When the student council fights for someone's smile,
we can be even stronger than your dad!
That's right!
Mana's the strongest in the universe!
That's nonsense!
Just fall already!
I refuse!
Don't worry.
If the thread snaps, we'll climb the wall!
And if the wall crumbles, we'll figure something else out!
Mana...
The two of us can do it!
Make that three!
Oh, sorry.
Yeah!
What?
Is she...
Why is it...
that my heart...
won't stop...
pounding?
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Way to go, pops.
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
You really are useless.
Every day it sparkles
Spider Selfish!
Dokidoki Precure
Eliminate Regina!
Seeeelfish!
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
Selfish!
Now that my powers are back, I'm unstoppable!
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
Seeeelf...
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
iiiiiish!
We've got no choice.
Destroy them all at once!
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
We'll fight all at once, too!
Love Heart Arrow!
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Precure Lovely Force Arrow!
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Love love loooove!
I'll be taking Ann back!
Get back to the gate!
Okay!
What should I...
Regina!
Daddy!
Curse you!
You not only oppose my authority,
but you befriended those Precures!
Are you all right?
Yeah...
Let us hurry!
Let's go.
Reginaaaa!
This way!
You shall not escape!
Precures!
We made it!
We won!
Princess...
This is... good, right?
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
We won't let you have Regina!
No matter how much you hurt and wound us,
We've already sworn to protect her!
That's why we absolutely will not lose!
Mana and the others are fighting for me...
I love my daddy,
but I love Mana and the others too!
I want to be friends forever!
Dokidoki Precure:
Arriving In The Nick Of Time!
A New Warrior, Cure Ace!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!