When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
It's smaller than expected.
This is small?
It is small.
It'd be small.
Then how big would your "big" be?
And... Is... Is...
Is this really Sakuya-san's personal belonging?!
You can see her terrible taste all over the place, can't you?
I was told the cruiser had a very familiar look and size,
but this is really amazing.
Hayate, you aren't thinking...
This isn't a cruiser. It's the Titanic, no matter how you look at it.
...in your head?
Sakuya-sama is expecting you.
Okay.
Hayate.
Klaus.
Yes, Ma'am.
Let's go, Maria, Klaus.
Right behind you.
C-Could you please wait, Milady?!
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
A passionate woman's red cruiser!
Let's go cruiser.
Just like White Bullet, right?
Hey, Hayate.
Yes?
Can you ask me, "Why a ship all of a sudden?"
Eh?
Just ask her for the sake of story development.
Milady, why a ship all of a sudden?
Um, well... You see...
You don't have to answer if you don't want to.
It's because-
She totally wants to answer it.
Hey, Britney...
You mind not clinging to me so much?
I can't believe it...
How could my senpai act like a stranger to me?
But... His distant attitude...
Somehow, it cuts me to the quick.
I get it.
The reason why Hayate doesn't look at me is...
What's important in a relationship is...
It's this!
Distant attitude!
So that's the development this time?
Indeed, in a relationship, rather than being the one chasing...
...the winner is the one who makes the other chase!
That Hon***-sensei once said, too,
"There are times when you learn from the manga you draw."
In that case-
Be ready, Hayate! I will enchant you with my distant attitude towards you!
Ah, Milady.
Hey, Hayate. Good mor-
No! No! What am I doing with a big happy face?
I must talk to him with much more of the attitude of a stranger.
Yeah... Good morning.
Um, Milady?
Wh-Wh-What?
I just noticed that your shoelace is coming loose.
Excuse me.
May I have your foot?
Yeah...
It's all good now, Milady.
Y-Yeah...
Don't let him get away like this!
Blast him with one hard stranger act!
Right.
Good work. You may go now.
Geez, that Hayate. He's too good.
Milady! Please don't leave me behind!
Isn't there a situation where Hayate would feel uncomfortable and come to me?
I'm scared!
You're so cute, Hayate.
Nagi, you have a call from Sakuya-san.
I absolutely don't have any time for that, but what did she say?
She's inviting you to a cruise on her cruiser.
That's it!
That was all flashback!
There's no way I can tell this to Hayate.
Let's hurry! Saku's waiting!
Um, what's the answer to the question?
Never mind.
Have a good trip!
Anyways, Sakuya's cruiser has departed.
God, I hate rich people. I hate them.
Wow, so many people are here to send us off.
They're probably just extras.
She's right.
What do you mean by that, Saku?
Oh, I get it. So it works like this. Then if I twist it back on...
It fits my character more to have it lively.
Ow!
What a waste of effort.
I'll give them a wave, too.
Stop it.
We have extras aboard, too.
It's the mood that sets things right in places like this.
You even have a band onboard?
Yup.
The one dancing there is an extra, too.
How many non-extras are there, then?
Milady, I searched for you everywhere.
Saku, do you have a female dancer who can dance aggressively?
Yeah, I do. What do you have in mind?
This ship is really big.
I almost got lost.
May I have a dance with you?
"Dance", right?
Yes. I won't allow you to turn down an invitation from a lady.
Milady!
What must I do in this case?!
Cruising requires lots of energy, eh, Milady?
Why?
Saku. This, that, and that.
I'll give it a try.
Trap C-5. Go.
Milady!
What are you doing?
Giving this ship a rock.
I don't understand what you're up to, but okay.
Milady, where are you?
Milady!
To the right?!
To the left?!
And to the right again?!
Why do I have to do this?
Hayate no... Gotoku... is a... good anime...
Milady!
I won't save him.
I won't save him no matter what.
Milady! This is my first experience on a cruiser, so I never knew it would rock this much.
Just as I thought. Hayate's so excited from his first experience on a cruiser.
But, everything is going according to plan.
And-
Ah, that felt good.
What else is there to see, Milady?
This is my chance.
Mila-
Don't ask me everything.
How's that?
What is deadly enough?
Have I carved it into him?
Did I wedge it in?
Did I smack it right into his heart?
I'm sorry.
Y-You idiot!
D-Don't give me those abandoned puppy dog eyes!
A-Anyway, I'm going to go drink some tea.
If you want to go tour around the ship, go do it yourself!
Milady!
What's the matter, Hayate-kun?
Um, did I do something to upset Milady again?
I'm not sure.
Yesterday, it looked like she was struggling to draw her manga like always,
so maybe something came up that she can't be satisfied about.
Something she can't be satisfied about?
Oh yeah, Hayate's breakfast this morning was nattou, wasn't it?
Anyway, Saku, this ship is very well-made.
You think?
That's nice.
Even if you act cold, I won't fall for you!
Where is this coming from?
Nowhere.
You don't make any sense.
By the way, I was told that you invited Isumi, as well, but...
I bet she's lost.
The ship's big, after all.
Where am I?
Just as she thought.
Will this ship be all right?
All right how?
The design is very prone to sinking.
You moron!
Listen! "Ti" for Titanic is...
"Ti" is?
Tai de ebi wo tsuru => Ebi de tai wo tsuru = Catch a red sea bream with shrimp.
A proverb meaning to make a big profit out of a small investment.
"Ti" of "Tai de ebi wo tsuru"!
No, it's the other way around.
This ship is so going to sink.
This ship had more money invested into it than the movie Titanic had budgeted.
Unless we're raided by terrorists, it won't sink.
Was that gunfire?
Listen, crew members!
We, the Piyo Piyo Terrorists, have taken over this ship!
Be quiet and listen to our demands!
So they say. What are you going to do?
Looks like there are adventurers in this world that don't care about their lives.
Hey, terrorists down there.
What do you want, kid! We have
no business with a midget like you!
So they say. What are you going to do?
Don't touch the crew or the guests.
If you want a hostage, it's to your benefit to have fewer.
Hey, Nagi. You aren't planning on...
What's this? You're nominating yourself as the hostage?
Nah, there's someone better,
namely the owner of this ship.
What? I'm going to become the hostage?
Look how calm she is. She can jab at every foolish little act one makes.
Stop making suggestions!
You fools who don't learn anything from robot animes shall...
Why you...
Wow, this ship really is big.
It's so big, I don't know where I entered from.
But, why is Milady so upset?
And yes~ I'm lost again~
Die Hard At Sea continues.
Detatoko shoubuya.
Detatoko shoubuya = We'll deal when it comes up.
Yamete
Yamete = Stop it.
Terrorists these days...
They think they can win if they fire guns.
They're nowhere close to where they should be.
You need to train more.
Wh-Why are these guys so strong?
Yet, they have gentlemanly attitudes.
Who in the world are you guys?
How foolish of you to come onboard without knowing who we are.
Listen well!
We are those who protect our Ladies.
Professional butlers.
Anyone who tries to hurt our Ladies,
we'll do whatever it takes to eradicate them.
Remember that well.
Yeah, you may have acted cool and all,
but your blunder of letting them on won't disappear.
So, what was their objective?
I don't know. Isumi-san's here, too,
so I can imagine all sorts of reasons for them to be here.
We came on since it looked like lots of rich people are on board.
To pay off our debts!
I don't want my wife and kids to go through any more hardships!
You have wife and kids?
Yes, actually I do.
Having a poor life?
Yes...
You got a problem with that?!
Nope.
Wow, he confessed everything.
We don't even see that happening often in Co***.
To explain your entire motive on your own...
Are you a criminal from ******?
Stop making fun of me!
Fine...
I'll put an end to everything!
Th-This is!
A bomb?!
Yup, that's right.
Everything's over!
My debt will disappear along with this ship.
Ready? Go.
Anyone scared?
I am, actually.
Yeah, me, too.
What should we do?!
I guess it is a design flaw.
It's no time to be saying that!
Where are Hayate and Isumi?!
Isumi-sama!
Ow...
Ouch.
What's going on?
Did we crash into an iceberg?
The design of this ship is, you know, it looks like it'll sink if anything were to happen.
You think so, too?
What the heck is this?!
Blood?!
A lot's coming out!
No, no. Calm down.
This is an anime.
In the next cut, it'll be like nothing happened.
Yes, I'm sure that's how the story goes.
I bet the storyboard will follow that, too.
I'm sure the original comic goes-
I guess not.
Wow, that was close.
If I had fallen into this cold water with this amount of blood loss...
On average, humans can last in cold water of about 4°C or 5°C for about one hour,
and at 0°C, it's said twenty to thirty minutes is the limit.
I might die.
My condolences.
That's...
Drifting...
Drifting with the flow...
Um...
Eh?! Isumi-san?!
What are you doing here?
Because...
Obviously, you're lost, right?
Are you all right?
I'm not all right.
Looks like you're not.
Please hold on. I'll be there soon to help you.
To jump into cold water when your body temperature is low from losing blood means...
...endangering one's life!
You can't find Isumi and Hayate?!
Yes. They're the last two we're missing, and all the butlers are panicking!
And this ship will probably sink
the way we all know it will in an hour.
"Way we all know it will?"
The way we all know it will.
Crap. Even DiCap*** turned into ocean debris in the end.
Stop saying something so ominous!
No, I'm saying I'm worried about the debt-ridden butler.
About Hayate?
Isumi-san is loved by the gods of fortune, so she should be fine,
but on the other hand, he probably has a grim reaper on his back.
I hope he won't do anything rash.
Milady!
I'll go find Hayate!
Hey!
Um, are you all right, Hayate-sama?
Yes, I'm fine. I'm in better shape than DiCap***.
Besides, this water was originally so cold that it hurt, but it's starting to feel warm.
I think that means your body's in critical condition.
I'm pretty sturdy, so I should be fine somehow.
But I see you bleeding a lot,
and I see large fish coming, attracted by your blood.
No way...
Hayate!
What in the world is going on here?
Are you all right... probably not, but... how are you doing, Hayate?
L-Let's see... I'd say... I'm in a... really... tight... spot...
Tight spot?! A big crisis, Hayate?
Wh-What should I do...
This fish is a man-eating fish.
Even if I want to save Hayate-sama, with him in the mouth...
If I could reach him with this branch...
The situation is totally hopeless.
And if I recall, I think there were two sharks.
If the other one comes right now, then...
...it's really all over.
Hang in there, Hayate.
I'll come... right now...
...and save you!
You mustn't, Milady. There's one more shark.
I have no choice!
Don't...
Don't you...
...touch my Milady!
Hayate...
Mi... la... dy...
Hayate!
Oh no...
I used up all the energy from that last move, and now I can't even move a finger.
Am I... going to die?
I'm sorry, Milady.
I couldn't be of much help for you.
I'm... really sorry...
So... rry...
If you have the energy to apologize, why don't you wake up already?
Gosh, you're finally awake.
Hayate!
Thank goodness, Haya-
Where is this?
On a rescue boat.
Haya-
You were one big load to carry, you know?
You saved me, Klaus-san?
I only saved you because Milady asked me to.
Haya-
I can't believe a Sanzenin butler would surrender to that.
Haya...
I-I'm sorry.
But... thank you very much for saving me.
Hey, Hayate! Why are you blushing?!
What's with the background?
I don't want to hear "thank you" from you.
For some reason, guys tend to like cold attitudes.
As such, Milady's...
You can't! I won't allow it!
What are you talking about, Milady?
...source of anxiety increased.
Next week, we'll fight against anime production schedules.
Let's down some fresh shark fin soup.
It's hot!
Nagi and,
Hayate and,
Katsura sisters'
Butler Network!
I'm the little sister for 100,000,000 people out there, Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Katsura Hinagiku.
Erotic terrorists, messages from supernovae, as well as the national beauty, Katsura Yukiji.
When there are four people here, it gets crowded.
But if we let Kastura-sensei loose,
things might turn into a mess like the last two times.
Ayasaki-kun, you're always harsh on me.
Onee-chan, you're a teacher, so act more like one.
Oh, it's time.
Bye bye.
What do you think of this complete version of Magical Destroy?
Um, I don't see much of a difference from before.
What? I went and edited it to target the audience for the general public, and yet you still don't understand?
Then I'll use the ultimate way to explain this as easily as possible!
Next time, mystery behind the 120% acceptance rate (temp.).
Where are we?
It's where this anime is made, the Syn-
Next time, come to Hayate no Gotoku with Get Setter!