Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Morning, Yuu-chan.
Homeroom's over already.
Already?
Where's Haruka?
Haruka-chan...
...left.
No, not like that!
She didn't actually leave,
she went to get tea with Yuzu-chan.
Roll
She left me behind?
I'm finally done!
Kotone, where did you go?
I was asked to help put away the books in the library.
It was tiring!
Sniff
Shizuku-chan, what are you...
Shizuku-chan, you're quite cruel, aren't you?
No, I don't think so at least!
Let's Have Tea with Onee-chan!
They're probably at the café nearby.
Let's go meet up with them.
After all, that shop's green tea cake is delicious!
Green tea?!
But I'd rather have their cheesecake,
but the strawberry chiffon cake and
the apple pie are super delicious too!
The blueberry tart would be nice too!
I like the bittersweet cake au citron too!
Tiramisu is slightly bitter and...
Let's decide when we get there.
Sakura
Why did Haruka leave me behind?
She should have woken me up!
I'll cling to you again like I did that one time, Kotone-chan!
Nice!
This kind of makes us seem like a family.
Maybe.
And if so,
I'm probably the wife.
Sorry for suddenly asking you to come with us.
What did you want to talk about?
Let's talk about it over some tea.
It's our treat!
I see...
We're here!
Still, it's really crowded today.
I thought it wouldn't be as busy if we came right after class.
Actually, it's crowded because we came right after.
Everyone thinks the same thing, huh?
A seat opened up over there!
I'll go take it.
Okay!
We'll go place the order, then.
Let's go.
Okay!
Big
Sister
Actually, it might be a better idea for you two to go reserve the seats, President Mitsuki and Haruka.
Leave the rest to us.
Not even a brush!
Uh, could we get to what you wanted to talk about soon?
Well, you know...
What?!
President Mitsuki, you really resemble Yuu-chan!
Your eyes...
...and your nose and mouth.
N-Not everything?
Not everything!
Yuu-chan's cheeks are more puffy!
I-I got it...
Stare...
She's staring at me so intently.
So, what...
Ah, your flower ornament!
Big
Sister
I'll fix it!
It's fine!
I'll do it myself!
It's okay!
That reaction...
Yuu-chan also blushes when my face gets close to hers.
You really are sisters in the way you react!
Speaking of your faces being close together,
under what kind of circumstances does that happen?
A
h
Sakura
You remind me of Yuu in many ways too.
I remind you of Yuu-chan?
These days, Yuu tries to avoid talking about you, Haruka-san,
but when she lets her guard down, you're all that she talks about.
You're the same.
Yuu is all you talk about.
Love ・・・
Yuu-chan talks about me even when I'm not around...
It's a little unfair.
Huh?
President Mitsuki just said that it's unfair...
In other words,
since her precious little sister only talks about me...
Little
Sister
Big
I won't let you
have my little sister
!
I won't let you have my little sister!
She's jealous of me?!
I texted her but she's not answering.
So I got her what Yuu likes,
but what if she doesn't like it?
I'm sure it'll be okay.
Sorry it took so long!
Thump
I got you a green tea latte, President Mitsuki.
How did you know what I like?
Success!
So, what business do you have?
You called me here, so can we please get to the point?
It's about the group presentations for the cultural festival.
What about them?
We thought we'd ask you to help us.
Huh?
We're doing Snow White.
But that's what you are doing.
Why do I have to play the huntsman?!
We haven't decided the cast yet.
President Mitsuki,
actually, Yuu-chan said...
Mem
ory
It's Onee-chan's last cultural festival,
so I'd like to do something with her!
This is the only year that we'll have all
three years doing a cultural festival together,
Even if you say that...
We helped you with all those things back then, didn't we?
So you should help us.
Guys, let's regroup!
What should we do?
It doesn't seem like she's as easy to trick as Yuu.
Maybe we just have to keep asking.
You're probably right.
Thank you, Yuzu-chan, Kaede-chan!
Let's head back!
Huh?
We're here!
Yuu-chan and the others are here?
We were going to return to school afterwards though.
And we were planning a surprise for Yuu-chan...
Should we not be here?
I wouldn't say "not", but...
By the way, Haruka, get me a refill!
Huh?
You drank all of mine?!
She drank it all...
What are you so happy about?!
Haruka, buy me a green tea latte!
Rus
tle
Huh, I wonder if I have enough money...
Rus
tle
I don't think I do.
Sorry!
Geez, Yuu...
Give me a second.
You're bothering Haruka-san.
Yuu, you want more to drink?
Come here, I'll give you mine.
I have green tea.
Wow!
Green tea!
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
Drink
discount
coupon
I had a discount coupon after all!
Huh?
Pat
Green tea is delicious!
Does this mean...
Pat
President Mitsuki is declaring war?!
I'll have President Mitsuki acknowledge me!
I'll do my best!
I wonder why she's so fired up...
I just did what any big sister should do.
I don't think we'll get it today.
You're right.
Yuu's here too.
Let's finish this some other day.
President Mitsuki.
Huh?!
It's probably about time we head back.
T-That's right!
Let's go visit the other place next time.
But their green tea is so delicious!
In the end, I didn't get President Mitsuki's acceptance.
Green Tea Baum
Is she going to feed me?
What is it?!
What happened?
Don't leave me behind like that!
I want to be with you,
so don't go without me!
Yuu-chan!
rub
You're so selfish!
So what if I'm being selfish today?!
Same as always,
if you don't say it properly, I won't understand.
Haruka, you meanie!
That was a lie.
I'll kiss you as much as you want.
Let's Have Tea with Onee-chan!                     The End
rub
Yuu-chan, good morning!
Morning, Haruka!
Hey, we're doing Snow White at the cultural festival, right?
Yuu-chan, which role do you want?
The witch!
Pew
The witch?!
What are you eating?!
I won't be distracted that easily!
The Witch and The Apple and Onee-chan
President Mitsuki!
Ah
Big
Sister
Ah!
Big
Sister
What happened?
You know those are the first-year classrooms, right?
Huh?
Ah, that's right.
I've got to go!
Yuu-chan wants to be the witch.
Hold on a moment!
The witch is the queen, right?
I wanted to do that too!
Why is the witch so popular?
And why are there sparks between those two?
Sheesh.
Yuu just wants to do something weird, right?
It's not weird.
It's cool!
But it's strange that you want to be the witch, Shizuku-chan.
Well...
Considering what the queen does...
She identifies with her?
Giggle
Talking to your own reflection is really weird, isn't it?
That's why?!
Snow White
Then let's do this...
How about both of you show us what you've got,
and then we'll decide based on that?
Okay.
Would the beautiful young lady over there like an apple?
I'll have it!
Haruka, calm down!
Snow White
Would the beautiful young lady over there like an apple?
So realistic!
I'm scared!
Yes
Yes, yes!
Shizuku-chan is so cute!
That thing's cute?!
So, which witch...
...do you prefer?
Yuu-chan!
Shizuku-chan!
Both are a bit questionable.
DING
I feel like I'm being watched...
Hey, Kaede.
President Mitsuki is looking this way.
You're right.
Is she here to watch Haruka and Yuu again?
Maybe she wants to act in Snow White after all.
She's totally not honest with herself.
You're definitely wrong.
And so..
She looked this way!
I wonder if she noticed.
I have to get out of here!
Hey!
For the student council president to be running in hallways...
No, um...
Onee-chan?
Why now?!
I was just taking big steps.
That's not okay either.
Sakura
What happened, Onee-chan?
Nothing!
I just happened to pass by.
I'm sorry I disturbed you.
See ya, Yuu!
That's suspicious.
Smirk
Huh?
I know the truth!
Even though you were interested in Snow White,
you couldn't bring yourself to say it, so you decided to just hang around.
Snow White
That's not it!
I was really just passing by!
You're lying to yourself.
Haruka-san just happened to see me!
I've been seeing President Mitsuki a lot lately.
Huh, where?
She was clinging to the door like that during lunch break too.
She was doing that?
Maybe she isn't as brave as she looks,
and couldn't get anyone's attention?
I wonder.
It's true!
Why didn't you say hi to her when she did that?
She must just be shy!
Why are you crying, Shizuku-chan?
Could it be...
...that you're going to participate in
Snow White too, President Mitsuki?
Where did that come from?!
Really?
Hooray!
No way!
I'm not doing it!
Onee-chan, this is the last time we can
participate in the cultural festival together.
Please!
Do it for Yuu-chan!
Unsure
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Big
Sister
Little
Sheesh, Onee-chan!
Hey-
President, how about it?
I think that you should participate so that you can watch over the two of them without drawing any suspicion.
That's right, if I participate, I can talk with Haruka-san-
No, stupid me!
Big
Sister
I'll do it to watch over them!
Thank you very much!
Huh?
Everyone!
President Mitsuki is going to be our Snow White!
Really?!
Onee-chan, thank you!
Wait a second!
I said I'd participate in the play,
but I didn't say anything about Snow White...
Snow White
Is there some other role you'd like to do?
Of course.
Pawn
The huntsman!
She's fixated on that, huh?
Could you decide after reading the script?
Thank you.
Come to think of it,
what kind of a story was Snow White again?
Snow White for Dummies!
No way!
There's a kiss scene at the end!
No, no, it's not like Haruka-san has decided to be Snow White...
But it would be fine even if Haruka-san were the prince...
Hey
Big
Sister
Hey,
that's not it!
Onee-chan, what happened?
Huh?
It's nothing!
Haruka-san, who are you playing?
Me?
Yuu-chan is playing the witch, so...
Maybe I could do a double as the queen's assistant and the huntsman prince.
I want to do the huntsman.
Maybe you should do some other role.
Huh?
Does she mean...
Growl
...that I'm not fit to be Yuu's attendant?!
Hey, President Mitsuki, I think the role of Snow White would suit you better.
N-No, I rather think it suits you better.
It's not really for me.
That's not true at all!
No, you'll see when we do it for real!
That's a good idea!
Huh?
Let's start from the scene where Snow White collapses from the witch's poison apple.
H-Hey!
Come to think of it, we were going to...
We have two witches, huh?
Let's do some other scene.
Snow White
So, the last scene, where the prince wakes up Snow White.
Wait, that's...
Haruka, you do the prince.
Okay!
Snow White
She collapsed!
Such true-to-life performance!
Snow White
Why Haruka-san again?!
Even if it's a play, to pretend to kiss with Haruka-san...
Snow White
But I said it myself, so declining now would be weird.
Big
Sister
Bring it on!
Snow White
She seems to be having fun.
Huh?
Snow White
President Mitsuki won't stand up.
Maybe she doesn't know it's a recitation?
Snow White
Come to think of it, I don't think anybody told her that.
What should I do?!
Snow White
W-What sh-
If you're going to do it, do it already!
Snow White
Y-Yes!
I'll just have to do what she wants first,
Snow White
and try to tell her afterwards that it's a reading play.
Ouch!
Yuu-chan, what are you doing?!
Onee-chan!
Onee-chan, wake up!
Snow White
How long are you going to lie on the floor?!
Huh, what?
Snow White
We're reading it through, so stand up!
Huh? What, readi...
Snow White
Say that earlier!
After
School
Sakura
Haruka, watch.
I'll be the witch.
I'm glad President Mitsuki is participating in Snow White.
Yuu-chan seems to be glad.
Did you see that?
It was pretty witch-like, wasn't it?
Huh?
Why aren't you watching?!
Take that!
This is your punishment for not watching!
I'm sorry!
I'll watch the next one!
Take it off!
T-That's not it!
H-Hey, you beautiful lady over there!
W-Would you like an apple?!
Do it normally!
Give it to me.
Your apple.
Do I have a choice?
The Witch and The Apple and Onee-chan                          The End
Big
Sister
Today's
Shizuku-chan
Today's Shizuku-chan!
Fanservice scene.
Today's Shizuku-chan                      The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
Shizuku-chan, why do you tie up your hair?
So that I can use cute hair ties...
But I think wearing your hair down would be cuter.
I-I wonder.
It'll definitely be cute!
So wear your hair down starting tomorrow!
Yuu-chan, are you worried that I'm your rival twintail character?
T-That's not it!
You looked away!
Next time, trick six!
Cultural Festival ☆ Sleepover
Cultural Festival ☆ The Real Thing!
"Cultural Festival ☆ Sleepover" and
"Cultural Festival ☆ The Real Thing!"
Look forward to it, okay?!
You're dodging the question!