Oh, no!
What should I do? This sucks.
You're so clumsy...
Don't just whine, help me pick them up.
Hey, can someone please help me pick these up?
Gosh, they're everywhere.
I'm really sorry.
It's this tiny idiot's fault.
Sorry.
What a shame.
W-What's wrong, Aisaka-san?
Taiga really loves Christmas.
She thinks she has to be good because Santa is always watching her.
I see.
All girls love Christmas, right?
Are you two finding time to study for your exams with all these party preparations?
Yeah, we've been studying as a group recently.
Well, Aisaka-san always has good grades,
and your grades are always good too, but...
I'm worried about Haruta-kun, Haruta-kun, and Haruta-kun.
Oh, Haruta?
And Haruta-kun too...
Haruta-kun hasn't been helping with the preparations, right?
Don't worry.
Kitamura ordered him to stay out of this so he could study.
That's great.
Promise me you two won't let your grades drop, okay?
I'm worried that you two might be
spending too much time on the party.
I'm sorry.
Speaking of which, are you coming to the party?
How could I?!
I don't have any dates on Christmas Eve,
but for the sake of my pride, I won't go!
However...
I really hope it's a success.
You guys are putting a lot of effort into it,
so you'll definitely reap the rewards!
My silky love
nijuuyon jikan zutto
24時間ずっと
Every hour of the day
My silky love
kimi no koto omou tabi
キミのこと想うたび
whenever I think of you
My silky love
modokashii kono kimochi
もどかしいこの気持ち
these impatient feelings
My silky love
tada afurekaetteku
ただ溢れかえってく
simply overflow.
suki to ieba kantan na no ni
スキと言えば簡単なのに
Even though it's easy to say "I love you"
kimi ga mae ni kichau to
キミが前に来ちゃうと
when you stand in front of me
kyara ga sobie watashi no koto wo jamashiteru
個性がそびえ　私のコトを邪魔してる
my personality stands up and gets in my way.
itsumo naraba tsuyoki de ikeru
いつもならば強気でイケる
I can usually pull through with my assertiveness
sonna seikaku na no ni
そんな性格なのに
that's just how I am.
donna ganbatte mite mo kabe wa kuzusenai
どんな頑張ってみても　壁は崩せない
But no matter how hard I try, I can't break the wall that's between us.
sasshite hoshii kono kimochi wo
察して欲しい…　この気持ちを
I want you to realise… my feelings.
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimi ni
だから私は　いつもキミに
So I always send a gaze
daisuki da yo to okuru shisen
大好きだよと送る視線
of "I really love you" your way
saidai no yuuki de
最大の勇気で!
with all of my courage!
yaburesou na shiruku no haato
破れそうなシルクノハート
My flimsy silky heart.
kimi ni atte kizuita yatto
キミに逢って気づいた　やっと
After meeting you, I finally realised
ai ni wa bukiyou dattan datte
愛には不器用だったんだって
that I'm really clumsy when it comes to love.
wasurekaketa koi no kizuato
忘れかけた恋の傷跡
The scars from love that I'd almost forgotten
kyuu ni uzukidashita no kyun to
急に疼きだしたの　キュンと
have started to ache all of a sudden.
itsuka wa watashi rashiku suki to
いつかは私らしくスキと
Someday, like how I normally would...
iwanakya ima yori yowaku nacchau yo
言わなきゃ…今より弱くなっちゃうよ
I must say "I love you", or else I'll become even weaker.
Beneath the Fir Tree
Yo! Taiga-chan!
Oh, Minorin! Club activities?
Yeah!
We spent the whole time working out in the gym!
Kushieda, hurry up or the coach will start complaining again!
Whoops...
See you later!
Oh, we really haven't been talking much lately.
Yeah...
See you later.
The party will definitely be fun!
You have to come!
Come on!
Sorry!
Minorin is being really weird lately.
Yeah.
I think she'll definitely cheer up if she comes to the party.
Yeah, you're right.
We have to do our best to make it an amazing party!
Yeah!
Let's do it, Taiga!
So slow!
What were you two doing?
We got held up, okay?
Wait, why are you here?
I'm in charge of the ornaments.
Look, isn't this great?
As expected of you!
Stupid! Stupid!
Go redo it!
Hey, should you really be saying that?
Weren't you trying to be good for Christmas?
Oh, what a shame.
Is that for the party?
Nope.
The P.E. teacher asked us to clean out the
storeroom in return for letting us use the gym.
All right, let me take care of that.
Kitamura, make the stars with Taiga.
Here are the scissors and glue.
Oh, okay.
Let's go, Aisaka!
Hey, wait a moment.
Don't hold scissors like that, it's dangerous.
Hold them like this.
My, my, they sure are getting along well.
Come on, let's go and help out over there.
Huh? What? Where?
Come on.
Sheesh, what are they trying to stir up?
Huh?
Stir what up?
Don't play dumb, you know I'm talking about Taiga...
...uh... liking Kitamura.
I don't really understand.
Lately, it seems like everyone is trying to pair them up.
You're really obsessed with this.
Are you jealous?
Huh?
Why would I be jealous?
I just...
...get pissed off when outsiders spread stuff about someone else's love life.
Or something like that...
This is how a father feels when his daughter is about to get married.
I wouldn't know.
It's not like I have a daughter.
Also, I've never met my father.
"Not allowing her to fall, get hurt, or cry."
"Watching the most precious woman of your life get taken away from you by another man."
"Not knowing if that man will treasure her as much as you do."
I've never had those thoughts.
Surely it won't be fun for you to
watch Yuusaku and Taiga date, right?
It's like the total opposite.
You're not her father, but you treasure the
woman you're determined not to lay a hand on.
You already have another woman in your heart.
It's like playing house. You three know exactly which characters you are.
Like pretending to be daddy, mummy, and the baby.
What are you saying?!
Why do you have to pretend to be daddy?
Your relationship with Taiga seems really unnatural.
I think you should stop playing this childish game of house.
You've been making mistakes all along.
Why don't you wake up before you get hurt even more?
You should forget everything and just start over.
Then...
...you could also give me another chance.
Huh? What?
Never mind.
Just pretend you didn't hear anything.
What was I even talking about?
Just forget everything I said.
Huh?
After all, what you really don't understand is yourself.
English Final
All right, put your pencils down.
Yes! It's over! It's finally over!
It's over...
Haruta, you're overreacting.
Quiet down and listen up.
Christmas! Christmas is coming!
There's normal school tomorrow and the day after,
so don't get too excited about Christmas.
Minorin.
Do you want to have lunch with Ryuuji and me?
Sorry, I have to go to practise.
Sadly, Minorin has club activities.
I know, I heard her.
I'm really sorry for turning you guys down.
W-Well, it's nothing really.
It just seems like we haven't had a chance to talk lately.
I-I mean, Taiga and you.
Well, our coach was taken over by the
dark side, so now our practice is harsh.
Later!
Minorin!
She ran away again.
Yeah.
I was planning to create a chance for you guys to be alone.
After we had left and arrived at the shop,
I would've said, "Sorry, I have something to do!"
You even planned a lie...
Angel Taiga sure is passionate.
But it can't be helped.
There will be another chance.
Let's go eat something before we go home.
No, I wasn't going to lie, I really have something to do.
What?
After I go home to get something, I need to go to the post office.
I'll help you.
Ryuuji, you don't need-
You're here, Takasu-kun!
Hey, are you free right now?
You are, right?
I need to have a talk with you.
Why don't you come and have lunch with us?
Okay? Okay? Okay?
No... Sorry, I have something to do.
I have to go to the post office with her later.
Wait, Ryuuji! I said you didn't need to come!
It's okay, let's go.
Wait! Takasu-kun!
Gosh!
Why did you lie?
Besides, what's with that gal girl pretending to be Kitamura's childhood friend?
Wait, scratch that.
I meant, the honest girl, Kihara-san.
It's all right, it won't be a lie if I go to the post office with you.
Huh? The thing you need to get...
Did you plan to take them all by yourself?
Don't touch them!
These are none of your concern! Just help me get the cart!
Aisaka Rikurou
Wai-
W-What are these?!
Aisaka Yuu
If it weren't Christmas, I would've beaten you up already,
but for the sake of being good, I'll forgive you.
These are Christmas presents for that family.
Why are you doing this?
Don't tell me you're planning to give them another chance.
It's not because of that, it's because it's Christmas.
It's because they're my parents.
What's with that?
I wanted to keep it a secret.
I also got presents for you and Ya-chan.
I'm not talking about that.
I know what you want to say, but I don't want to hear it.
I'm going to get the cart.
What's this?
Santa Claus
Santa Claus?
in line
I went to an all-girls Catholic school since primary school.
I was rejected by the high school because of bad behaviour.
At that school, you have to do volunteer work with the sisters.
Meaning...
I hate to put it this way, but we played with orphans and did some other odd jobs.
The present with "Santa" written on it is actually for those children.
First, presents for that family, and now for orphans?
I'm sorry, but I don't understand you anymore.
I want to tell them that there are
people who are watching over them.
Christmas is a chance to be good.
"Even if you don't have parents and don't believe in God...
Even if that's the case, there's someone watching over you."
That's what I want to show them.
I want them to know that someone cares about them.
That's-
I know.
You're right, it's self-satisfaction.
But it's because I believe...
...someone is actually watching over me somewhere.
To me, that person is Santa.
Santa, Santa...
Do you really believe in him?
I truly love Christmas.
The streets, shops... Everywhere is glittering.
It’s dazzling and beautiful.
Everyone looks really happy.
The world is overflowing with happiness.
I feel like I'm part of that happiness.
I want to be good.
I want to be part of the happy, glittering scene on Christmas Eve,
while wearing a happy face.
Also, you know,
I really met Santa before.
It was when I was little.
It was on a Christmas Eve when my parents were still together.
I was sleeping under the Christmas tree in the living room.
I woke up because it was cold,
then I looked out the window.
Santa was there.
He gave me a present and said,
"If you be a good child, I'll definitely come again."
Well, it might have been a dream.
But even so, it was a really happy dream.
That's why I want to be good.
Do you think I'm stupid for believing in a dream?
No, I don't think so.
It's a dream.
Whatever, it's not like its real.
It's not like I'm clinging to something real.
All right...
Stop!
Yes!
The Christmas tree is here!
Amazing!
This will be really awesome once we put it together!
I think the party will be a success.
Yuri-chan, are you going to come?
I said I'm not going for the sake of my pride.
Oh, yeah! I should buy a present for myself!
Watches, bags, or even accessories!
It'll be a reward for thirty years of hard work.
Uh...
What?
You're thinking that I'm wasting money, right?!
You're thinking that I'm just a single woman who's falling for advertising tactics, right?!
Aisaka!
I shouldn't waste money because I need seventy million yen for retirement.
But what if I stop myself from buying things,
then I can finally say, "Yay! I have a hundred million yen",
but before I know it, inflation in Japan gets so bad...
...that all the money I've saved becomes useless-
Wait, huh?! I just predicted the future!
Perhaps I should buy myself an apartment.
It's here! It's here!
Check if we have all the parts.
I can't believe you managed to get something like this.
It was a decoration in a model show I was on, so I asked them if I could have it.
What do you think?
Aren't I amazing?
Yeah, you're a Stupid Chi', but you're amazing!
This is the best tree ever!
No one could disagree!
It'll be even better once we put it together.
Everyone, come on, let's get moving!
Are the supporting parts all right like this?
Yeah.
Wow! I'm excited!
What's next?
What's this for?
That's the top part.
Aisaka-san, you look pretty light,
so can you get on my back and put this on?
With the shoes I just went to the toilet with?
Different people really do have different interests...
No, please take them off.
Hey, Ryuuji!
Why are you dozing off?
Come and help!
Sure, I think this is next.
Hey, what was that for?! It was dangerous!
What are you doing, Taiga?
But your reflexes are pretty good!
As expected from the Palmtop Tiger!
But it's because I believe...
...someone is actually watching over me somewhere.
Taiga, you're not alone.
Perhaps you didn't actually have someone
watching over you for the past seventeen years,
but it's different now.
You have new friends.
You have Kitamura.
You also have Yasuko, Inko-chan, and me.
Tomorrow, Kushieda will definitely...
You'll definitely reap the rewards!
That's right, we'll be rewarded.
Everyone will be happy,
and everyone will be rewarded.
It's huge!
It really is amazing!
Kitamura-kun!
I got this from my house.
Put it on the top.
It's so beautiful... Is it really okay?
Or should I say, it looks really expensive...
It's okay.
Although this is my favourite decoration,
I couldn't put it on my own Christmas tree because it was too big.
All right.
I'll put it on carefully.
Blackout curtains are okay!
The power source is okay!
All right, turn off the lights now.
We did it! We did it!
It's amazing!
It's so beautiful.
We did it.
I'm sorry!
No one got hurt, right?
Minorin, that's enough.
It was an accident, it couldn't be helped!
No, I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry...
Minorin, you're not at fault!
It was just an unfortunate accident-
No, it was my fault.
I think it was because I spaced out.
I lost control of the ball, and it broke something very important to you.
I beg you...
Although I might not be able to fix it, just let me do whatever I can!
Then, let Ryuuji hel-
No!
No! Stop! Not that!
Minorin...
Takasu-kun, just go.
Let me do this by myself.
Stop it, it's all my fault.
If you help me, I-
There's not much time left.
Do what you should do.
I'm not helping you, I'm just doing what I should do.
It's for my own sake.
Takasu-kun...
Yeah.
Takasu-kun... Takasu-kun...
I'm listening.
Takasu-kun...
I'm here.
Look, isn't it beautiful?
Even though it's broken, it can be fixed,
so cheer up.
We can't return it to the way it was...
But it's still shining.
I don't even know if I can fix it.
You can!
Don't worry, it can be fixed no matter what.
Everyone, we're really...
...sorry!
Thank you, Minorin.
It's cuter than before.
Kushieda!
You have to come to the party tomorrow!
It'll definitely be fun!
I want to go with you!
No, I can't...
I can't go after all the trouble I've caused.
I'll wait for you!
Don't wait,
because I won't come.
I will wait...
I will wait for you!
nemurenai yoru ni wa
眠れない夜には
On the nights I can’t sleep
hitori de tameiki
ひとりでため息
I sigh alone.
minna wa dou na no
みんなはどうなの？
How is everyone?
nandaka sabishii
なんだか寂しい
I feel a little lonely.
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
広い大地に　ひと粒の種
Within the vast world, a single seed
nekko nobashite
根っこのばして
extended its roots
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
まだ青い　実をつけた
and put out a fruit that was still unripe.
orenji iro ni hayaku
オレンジ色に　早く
The fruit that I wish would turn orange soon
naritai kajitsu
なりたい果実
The fruit that I wish would turn orange soon
kimi no hikari wo abite
キミの光を浴びて
is bathed in your light.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
理想や夢は膨らむばかり
The ideals and dreams just swell-
kizuite yo nee
気づいてよ　ねぇ
Hey, feel it.
orenji kyou mo
オレンジ　今日も
Today, I tried eating an orange
tabete mita kedo
食べてみたけど
Today, I tried eating an orange
mada suppakute naita
まだすっぱくて　 泣いた
but it was so sour I cried.
watashi mitai de nokosenai kara
私みたいで残せないから
I couldn’t leave it behind like I have been
zenbu tabeta
ぜんぶ食べた
so I ate it all.
suki da yo nakeru yo
好きだよ 泣けるよ
I love it… I feel like crying.
suki da yo suki da yo
好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it… I love it.
Next Episode Preview
Holy Night Party
Holy night! Holy night! Holy night! Holy night!
Yay! It's a party on the holy night!
I want more fruit punch!
Huh? Where's Taiga?