Crimson Crane
Pro Wrestling
Riki Douzan vs Lou Thesz
Kuramae Stadium
Student from Prestigious University Commits Suicide with Prostitute
South Garden Inn
One Month Later
You shouldn't get up yet, Uncovered.
He beat you pretty badly.
You probably still have a fever.
Mario...
Here.
Soldier said it's for you.
To pay for the glasses he broke.
Must be a parting gift for you.
Hey...
Can you tell Turtle I'm sorry?
I said some really mean things to him.
"Don't come back."
That's what Turtle said.
"We'll always be friends, so don't ever come back."
We'll be friends no matter where we are, Uncovered.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'll run away with Eri.
I'll run to the ends of the earth, no matter what happens.
Well, Mom, I'm going to work.
Oh, are you helping Maeda today?
Stay out of trouble.
Okay.
Sorry, Mom.
Okay, now that we're all ready, let's go get inspected.
Ryu, do you know where Senso Temple is?
A tree there got torched in the war.
A ginkgo tree with a burned trunk.
Let's meet there at 2.
I'll definitely be there, so wait for me, Ryu.
I guess I got here a little too early.
Oh, well.
You're up next, Eri!
Hey, Eri!
Where's Eri?
Eri?
Isn't she here?
Strange...
She was here just a moment ago.
Don't tell me...
Waiting is part of the fun.
I read somewhere that women are supposed to arrive late.
Come on, Eri.
I'm waiting.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Did you make sure no one saw you?
Yeah.
Go away!
Rain...
This is bad.
Hey, Turtle.
Sorry.
I was such a jerk.
But Turtle...
I also think you're my friend.
You're self-centered and nosy, but I think you're my friend.
Soldier.
I know you didn't sleep with Eri.
You hit me because you were really worried.
But I'm all right.
I'll be just fine if I'm with Eri.
I'll be happy with her.
Hey, Ryu...
Be a responsible man.
Wait for me at Senso Temple next Tuesday.
Turtle...
I wonder if something happened to Eri.
Hey, Turtle.
You knew this would happen, didn't you?
You knew.
Uncovered, let's go home.
Hey, Uncovered!
"Turtle, laugh at me."
"My own plan backfired on me."
"Unfortunately, that's what I'm made of."
Uncovered was drenched in rain to the corners of his heart.
Hey, Mario!
It's me!
Can you open up?!
I see.
She didn't come, huh?
He waited in the rain for hours.
Of course he caught a cold.
Hot!
Man, I'm impressed.
He doesn't even care about his life.
Yeah.
He really risked his life.
His fever's gone, so I think he's better,
but he hasn't said a single word.
I've got to go to work now,
so can you watch him for me?
Sure thing.
Hey, Uncovered, Riki Douzan's wrestling today.
Want to go find a public TV somewhere?
Well, I'll go buy some ingredients for dinner.
Let's have stew today.
I learned a tasty recipe at the dojo!
Sign: Student from Prestigious University Commits Suicide with Prostitute
Uncovered, I'm back!
The veggies were cheap, so I bought tons—
Huh?
He's gone.
Where did he go?
The bathroom?
Thank you for coming.
We hope to see you again.
It's you.
You saw the news?
Eri's not here anymore.
Why did Eri die?
I don't know.
She killed herself without paying off her debts.
Then what about her sister?
She was working so hard to put her sister through school.
Oh, right!
She deceived you completely.
What a ridiculous story.
She didn't have any family members.
No wait, she did.
She had one.
Her drug-addict mother sold her to me and took off with a man.
Well, I suggest you forget about that woman.
But since you're here, how about I show you a different girl?
I'll give you a discount.
Give me a break.
Don't give me that crap, you shit-head!
What do you know?
All you think about is money!
Hey, now.
Who bought Eri with money?
That's right.
I didn't understand her.
I didn't know anything about her.
Sadly, we're both the same.
I'm also a shit-head, just like you!
He didn't feel like a fool because she'd lied to him.
He wasn't sad because he'd thought that she liked him.
Uncovered simply pitied Eri from the bottom of his heart.
"A life without happiness is a terrible thing."
That was the only thought in his mind.
"Eri..."
"I didn't want to die with you."
"I wanted to live with you."
Uncovered is missing?
Sorry.
I left the room for just a bit, and...
Turtle and I are looking for him right now.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Sign: South Garden Inn
Mario!
Did you find him?
No, nowhere.
He's not at home.
I see.
What should we do?
He's not thinking about doing anything stupid, is he?
Are you dumb?
He's the kind of guy who wouldn't die even if you killed him!
Turtle...
He's right.
We know his toughness better than anyone.
Let's trust him and wait for him to come back.
Yeah.
One Month Later
Yes, Nomoto's doing fine.
We're almost done with the job, so don't worry about him.
I see.
Thank you so much for taking care of him.
Not at all.
I'm the one asking for his help.
U-Uncovered!
Ryuji...
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Ryuji...
Uncovered.
I stole money from the house.
I made Kazuo and Tatsuo worry.
And I lied to my friends to borrow money from them.
With that money, I...
I...
It will be time for lunch soon.
I have to start cooking.
Feel free to stay for lunch, Maeda.
Th-Thanks.
Mom.
Ryuji, welcome home.
Turtle!
Here.
Sorry.
It's only a little, though.
I paid Soldier back with a note.
Where were you anyway?
I was doing construction work in Yokohama.
I wanted to pay you back as soon as I could.
Really?
You were using your muscles?
Don't say that.
I did what I could.
I see.
All right, then let's go tell everyone!
We're drinking tonight at Mario's!
You're paying.
Let's drink till we drop!
Wait a minute. I don't have any cash left!
Don't rush, man!
There are a million women in this world.
Even the girls in school will become fine ladies in five or six years.
That's amazing!
You sure know your stuff, Soldier!
Take a look at this tree.
It got burned in the war, but it's sprouting new life.
What a will to live.
I waited here for Eri that day,
but she committed suicide with a different guy.
Everything she told me was a lie.
I completely blanked out, and...
When I came to, I was standing in front of this tree.
Then I noticed the buds on the tree,
and I heard a voice.
It wasn't my imagination or anything.
The buds told me to live...
in Eri's voice.
The Ginkgo buds on a battered tree encouraged Uncovered to live.
"Yeah. Why am I so blue?"
"People meet and part in life."
Uncovered made an oath.
"Eri, I'm going to live."
"Dad, Bro, watch me."
"I'll live well, and wisely."
sameta manazashi
With my empty eyes,
nani wo mitsuzukeru no ka
what can I
continue to watch over?
mamoru beki mono
I can even sacrifice
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
my life for those
whom I must protect.
Even if I rot away...
Just keep on praying!
So far away, but
I never give it up.
ima tokenai kizuna ga
Our unbreakable bond
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
has begun to entwine with fate;
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuiteyuku
guiding us to an endless
future that's laid out before us.
And I will get over it, it's now
a far-off distance.
Lily departs.
As Turtle begins to have new dreams,
his nightmare from thirteen years ago resurfaces.