Yato-sama!
Please, do your thing!
May our fates intertwine.
Nothing beats a fine cup of sake after a long day of work!
Look at all your worshippers, Yato-sama!
Isn't it amazing?
Yatoites as far as the eye can see!
At last, the world has come to its senses.
And yet, having your ambition fulfilled feels quite empty.
Only someone who stands at the very top can understand this loneliness!
"May our fates interwine"
It chills my heart.
Yato-sama...
Oh, won't someone warm my frozen heart?
Oh, allow me!
No, me!
Me!
Oh, settle down! Settle down!
There's plenty of me to go around.
Shut up already!
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Fantastic!
Thanks, Hiyori!
Offering
In exchange, I expect you to finally—finally—listen to my request!
It's shaped like an octopus!
Are you even listening?!
You're not, are you?!
Ugh...
I barely got any sleep thanks to all your stupid sleep-talking.
Man, that was a great dream!
Well, keep dreaming. There's no way "Yatoites" will ever exist.
I'd rather flee overseas than dress in something that humiliating.
No girl would ever think that's cool.
What was that?!
Who in their right mind would want to shake your hand?
Did you know? His hands are always sweaty as hell.
If that's what you think, I'll show you...
what a god is capable of.
Huh?
All of my dreams will come true.
Wanna know why?
'Cause I bought this!
Some random pot?!
A lady in town read my palm and said, "I'll sell this to you and only you!"
She said all I have to do is chant, "Happy-happy, cool-cool,"
every day while I rub it like this!
That was a scam!
And this will help me win lotteries if I
put it on the westmost wall of my room!
This bracelet will help me build my dream home,
and this will boost my test scores
and get me into my dream college!
With all these, I'll be happy-happy, cool-cool in no...
Hiyori!
Jungle Tornado!
How about you work for a change?!
It's not my fault.
I wanna work, but no one's calling me for any jobs.
You said gods and their Regalia share mind and body, right?
I don't think this is how a god should act,
especially after finding such a great Regalia.
You need to pull yourself together, for both you and Yukine.
Hiyori, go get your body.
Huh?
There's someone I want you to meet.
Chapter
Where Happiness Lies
Pi
ping
Hot
Oden
Soba-Dango
Shiruko
Sweet Sake
Is this the place?
Kofuku!
You here, Kofuku?!
Yato-chan!
Man! Long time, no see!
Wow! I missed you, Yato-chan!
Wh-Who's she?
I missed you too!
Judging from that vibe... Could that be his...
No, there's no way.
That's right, this is Kofuku...
my girlfriend!
I'm his girlfriend, Kofuku!
Nice to meet you!
Girlfriend?!
Are you serious?!
Anyway, Kofuku, I got a favor to ask.
Yes, Yato-chan?
Well, I recently turned this kid into a Regalia.
But... I still haven't caught
a break yet, you know?
I'd really like to give
him a nice, hot meal,
but I can't even provide
decent shelter for him yet!
Oh, that's terrible to hear, Yato-chan!
Don't worry! I'll help you out!
Will this be enough?
You're a life-saver!
A real sweetheart, seriously!
Yato-chan praised me!
That just makes me so happy!
All right! Time to hit the casino!
I'll come with you!
He really is the bottom of the barrel.
Son of a bitch!
You again?!
Keep your hands off my lady!
A-An affair?!
You hear me?!
Oh my! Don't fight over little old me!
I'm Ebisu Kofuku's Regalia.
Base name's Kuro. As Regalia, Koku.
As a person, Daikoku.
You're spilling it!
Awesome.
Ebisu's a real hotshot, isn't she?
Didn't I tell you to keep a hand on the lid?!
Yeah, she's one of the Seven Gods of Fortune.
Got it!
But she's nothing like the way she's portrayed.
What are you talking about?
O-Oh, uh, just how cute of a couple you two are!
Couple?
You're married, right?
We aren't.
Huh?! But earlier, you called Ebisu-san—
Just "Kofuku" is fine!
You called Kofuku-san your lady.
No, it's kind of like calling her "milady." She's my goddess.
Right?
Yup!
Oh, a standing tea twig! That's good luck!
That's just some leftover junk.
What, you got a problem?
I happen to like calling her that.
I-I think it's very nice!
Don't look him in the eye, you guys.
Huh?!
You're putting yourselves at risk.
Because, despite his tough
and intimidating appearance...
that guy is into kids!
Don't make it sound like I'm a bad guy!
Don't worry! He's safe.
My Daikoku just loves little kids so much.
He likes sitting and staring at them until they vanish from sight!
That doesn't make me sound safe at all.
Hey, boy.
Calm down. And you don't need to hide him.
Are you Yato's Regalia?
What's your name?
Y-Yukine.
Been a Regalia for a while now?
No, not really. I just started.
I see.
And you're still just a kid, too...
Daikoku-san...
Hey, hey!
Y-Yes?!
What about you?
I'm Iki Hiyori.
Oh! So your name's Hiyorin!
"Rin"?
You're a regular girl, Hiyorin.
What's your relationship with Yato-chan like?
Huh?! R-Relationship?!
I don't care about that jerk!
Oh, come on!
Why are you so upset?!
Why? Tell me! Why?
Sorry. My lady's a bit crazy.
Are you a B-cup, Hiyorin?
Stop!
Looks like she's happy that
she met someone new today.
So, what's it like living with Yato?
Yeah, I thought so.
He's not much of a people person.
I want to get a different job!
Then get one!
Could I work here?!
I'm all the help she needs.
Oh, right.
Oh, yeah! Yukki!
"Yukki"?
You should be careful.
I first heard about Yato-chan through some nasty rumors.
Nasty rumors?
Despite the way he looks and acts,
Yato-chan can actually be a terrifying god.
Don't scare the kid, Kofuku.
Good news! I got called for a job!
Let's go, Yukine!
Wait! Don't just leave me behind!
Thank you for having us!
Aww!
You're leaving already, Hiyorin?
Yato...
Why'd you bring those two here?
Will
I'm sorry, Mom.
I hope you can forgive me.
Thanks for your call!
Yato, at your service!
You knocked him off!
Oh, shoot!
NORAGAMI
Huh? I'm already falling.
Man, I can't even get my own death right, huh?
Not so fast!
Do your daily doldrums have you down, miss?
Are you torn between work and family, sir?
Wanna teach some bullies a lesson, kiddies?
I can solve your problems in a jiffy!
Fast, affordable, and reliable!
Delivery God Yato!
Yato
Call me anyti—
Damn it, Hiyori!
Skip the introduction and save him already!
It's handmade...
Yato
Oh, pardon my late introduction. This is—I mean, was—my card.
He's playing along?!
Ah, so you work—I mean, worked—at an ad agency?
Section EC1
Marketing Group
Yes.
Section EC1
Marketing Group
The company recently went bankrupt,
and this is the only option I had left.
Mom
Unknown Caller
I was trying to apologize to
my parents back home before I fell.
Mom
Unknown Caller
Unfortunately, I accidentally called you instead.
Mom
Unknown Caller
Ah, that telemarketing ploy—
Mom
Unknown Caller
No, I mean... This must be fate.
First, could you tell me how all this started?
Why don't you save him first?!
It happened last winter.
You're actually telling him?!
I happened to meet a young girl.
For whatever reason,
I couldn't take my eyes off her.
Why is it my face?!
Well, you kind of look like her.
You're right around the same age, too.
Ah, I see. She was wearing stripes.
Don't look!
Thinking she might be a runaway,
I offered to take her to the police when...
Sounds like you're hungry.
Would you like to get something
to eat before we go to the station?
No.
I'm not allowed to go out to eat.
It's one of the rules I have to follow.
But sometimes, I sneak out
and come downtown anyway.
I could tell she had grown up in a very strict household.
This young girl wasn't even allowed outside. She was like a bird in a cage.
You need a change of pace!
Where would you like to go?
And that's how we started dating.
Those were truly happy times.
You're a normalfag?!
Police! This guy has illicit
sexual relations with runaways!
It's not like that!
Our relationship is pure!
We haven't done a single
indecent thing! I swear on my life!
That's not very convincing!
Whenever we met,
I took her wherever she wanted.
What do you think?
It looks really nice on you.
Really?
You really don't mind buying all these for me?
Well, they all looked good on you, so...
Crap. I hope I can last
until this month's paycheck.
Thank you! I love you, Yusuke-kun!
You're just bragging!
Stop using my face!
Is it just me, or is this fall taking forever?
For me?
It's my way of thanking you!
Oh, you like Capypas?
Yup! I've never been to Capypa Land, though.
It's the "Kingdom of Dreams and Hopes," so I'm not allowed to go.
What horrible parents!
Let's visit Capypa Land!
Really?!
It was around that time when things starting taking a turn for the worse.
There, there!
Why?! Why are there middle-aged men wearing Capypa skins?!
Did they kill Capypas?!
They're just costumes...
I mean, don't worry!
A fairy used magic to make the Capypas all better!
Forget the Capypas!
Most of our dates suffered from similar bad luck.
My performance at work steadily dropped.
I stopped getting bonuses,
and my meager savings dried up.
Credit
cards
into
cash!
But I was just so happy to be there for her.
So, before I knew it...
Unknown caller
I know you're in there, Urasawa-san!
I was completely bankrupt.
Answer the door!
I want to stay with her!
But as I am now, I'd only be a burden to her!
I was planning to propose to her after she graduated!
But there's no way I can do that now!
Say, do you have a picture of this girl?
Huh?
Why do you ask?
There's something about this story...
This is her.
Kofuku-san?!
Huh?! How do you know her name?!
I should have known.
What do you mean by that?!
Oh, I didn't tell you?
She's the god of poverty.
G-God of poverty?!
Ebisu Kofuku is her professional name; a pen name, if you will.
Her real name would be
bad for business, you know?
Take my advice.
Just forget about that girl. Seriously.
Huh?
The god of poverty only brings disaster!
She'll spoil any luck you have! She's the Luck-Killing Queen!
On top of that...
She has a man in her life
you don't wanna mess with.
Kofuku's no spring chicken, anyway.
She's way, way, way older than
your mom... or even your grandma.
All right! Now to sever your ties with Kofuku!
Huh?
Sever his ties?! But that means...
He'll forget everything relating to Kofuku.
N-No! I don't want to forget her!
Absolutely not!
If you don't cut your ties,
you're gonna die, you know.
I don't care! I love her
from the bottom of my heart!
You dumbass!
Someone who chooses to kill himself isn't cut out for love!
Hurry up!
What is even happening here?
All right! You're up, Yukine!
Huh?
W-Wait! I've never severed someone's ties before!
It's okay! I know you can do it!
Have faith in me!
Come, Sekki!
Anything you want me to tell Kofuku?
"May you live a happy life, Kofuku-chan."
That's all.
Your request has been heard loud and clear!
With my advent, I, the Yato god...
hereby sever your ties using Sekki!
Sunder!
1 contact deleted
Are you serious?
That was all my fault?
Well, I did have a little fun with Yusuke, though!
A little?
Kofuku! You did all this behind your Regalia's back?
It's not my fault!
I was sick of you telling me
I can't go here or there or anywhere!
I told you that for a reason!
You spread disaster wherever you go!
Sheesh...
Anyway, you got some skills, kid!
A rookie like you, severing someone's ties...
Oh? Is it that big of a deal?
Yeah. Severing a bond is
much harder than making one.
A Regalia's abilities are a big part of it, too.
I thought it was a piece of cake, though.
That's good to hear!
Looks like you've found
yourself a good Regalia, Yato.
I know, right?! There's a reason I fell for him at first sight!
Right, Yukine-kun?!
Gross! Let go!
Don't be shy!
G-Get off me!
Sorry about everything.
This is for your trouble.
Pleasure doing business!
Later!
Bye-bye!
Let go! You stink!
Come visit again, Hiyorin!
Let us be off, my dear Yukine!
Of course!
Stop it!
Let go!
Um, about what you said earlier...
Hm?
When you said Yato's a scary god...
That was just a joke, right?
It's the truth.
Yato-chan killed a Regalia a long time ago.
The first time I heard about Yato-chan, it was from a nasty rumor.
Plus, since Yato-chan is a god of war...
he kills people too.
He kills... people?
Quit it.
That was a long time ago,
back when it was all "kill or be killed."
What do you mean?
Gods only exist to fulfill people's wishes.
Distinguished gods enjoy
constant worship and wishes.
Lesser known gods don't have that luxury.
They can't even remain in people's memories.
So what do you do so that
people will remember you?
You do whatever's asked of you...
so long as it's what someone wished for.
What someone wished for...
You stayed there for quite some time.
What were you talking about?
Yato.
Why did you bring me to see Kofuku-san?
Listen...
If anything happens to me,
go straight to those two.
Okay?
G-Got it!
He...
He smells so nice!
There's a reason I fell for him at first sight!
My, you have nice eyes.
What do you want, Nora?!
No, no. Call me by my name.
I love the name you gave me, Yato.
D-Don't tell me she's...
Is she your Regalia too?!
I'll always be waiting...
Waiting for you to call my name.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
Hey, Kofuku. Say "Yato" ten times fast.
Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato,
Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato!
Who's the coolest guy in the world?
Daikoku!
Who's the toughest god in the world?
Me!
Damn...
On the next Noragami: "Borderline."
Next Episode
Borderline