Seconds!
Sure thing!
What the hell am I doing?!
What?
How did you end up eating breakfast at our place?!
And you! Why aren't you bothered by it?
Why would I be?
Since Taiga-chan is so small, she takes up so little space.
Besides, it tastes even better when everyone eats together.
Give me another helping already.
I cooked enough for three.
How much do you intend to eat?!
T-Timoten.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
Ryuuji And Taiga
Seriously, are you trying to make your pet moult from stress?
Don't let it get any uglier.
Don't call it ugly!
In truth, pets are similar to their owners.
Why, you...
You ungrateful little-!
Have some respect for me!
I made you breakfast and prepared a lunch box!
Shut up, you mongrel.
Mon-! Calling me that again!
Give the lunch box back! Give my kindness back!
Shut up and rot.
Wait up, Aisaka!
Ever since that late-night attack,
Aisaka Taiga has been a frequent guest at our dinner table.
I told you to wait!
And now...
More importantly,
once we get to school, make sure that you properly...
...um, mediate things...
...between Kitamura-kun and me.
You promised me you'd work like a dog for me, after all!
...things have ended up like this.
If things seem to take a bad turn...
Minorin!
You're late, Taiga!
Good to see you're perky today as well!
Good morning, Minorin.
Huh? What? You're kidding me!
I'm so sorry, I had no idea that Taiga and Takasu-kun...
...are now in a companioned, commuting relationship!
You've got it all wr-
You know, people don't use "companioned" like that these days.
That wasn't the problem!
Oh, you're right.
These days, they say...
Egads, I don't know what they call it these days!
Wait, how about "togethered"?
I'm telling you, that's not it!
I just happened to stumble upon Aisaka over there.
Isn't that right, Ais-
Oh, so it was just a coincidence?
Apparently we live close to each other.
Really?
Um...
Well, see you later, Takasu-kun!
Yesterday, I was watching TV and...
I get it now.
In order to get closer to Kushieda,
I'll first have to mediate between Aisaka and Kitamura.
Let's bring it!
And that's it for shooting practice.
Next, we'll pair u-
Hey, Aisaka. Let's pair up.
Yes, let's pair up, Takasu-kun!
Yeah!
-p and pass balls!
Takasu and Aisaka, you two are really fired up.
Taiga?
Is it that kind of day today?
The plan is simple.
I'll lightly hit Kitamura's partner with the ball,
and then...
...you'll cause a big fuss and take his partner to the infirmary.
So, Aisaka and Kitamura will lose their partners and pair up instead.
Maruo! Let's pair up!
Who'll want to team up with Haruto-kun today?!
Sure thing. And stop calling me that.
But you're so similar!
What the?
K-Kitamura-kun's pairing up with that weirdo!
What's up with that?
Events have taken a turn for the weir-
Kushieda!
Want to pair up?
Okay, let's do this!
Even Kushieda...
The plan will continue regardless.
Wha-? But then...
It doesn't matter what gender his partner is.
And the swelling bulges drawn in the Jouan era...
What's wrong, Haruta?
I'll throw the ball without using my thumbs!
That didn't reach me, Kushieda.
The road to understanding the Satoru-ball is steep.
Huh?
Don't mind me, it's not something just anyone would know.
That Noto-!
Hey, pass!
Hey, hey! Pass, pass!
Here I go, Maruo!
Yeah.
Nice form.
What are you saying, Maruo?
No, really, that was very good.
Hey, pass!
Pass, you say...
There you go again!
But hitting a girl with the ball...
Here I go!
Pass!
I'm sorry, Kihara. I will atone for this.
Clone...!
I'm sorry, Maruo!
What happened?
The Palmtop Tiger got taken down by Takasu-kun!
O-Oops.
Home Economics Practice Room
The Palmtop Tiger snarls at whoever's around.
Even so, she tries so hard that she makes a fool of herself,
so you just end up wanting to help her.
Listen up, you have  to hand them over casually.
Don't overdo it.
O-Okay.
As nonchalantly as possible, right?
Thoughtlessly, informally, frivolously...
Let's go.
Huh, where's Kitamura?
If you're looking for Kitamura,
he said he had some business over at building B or some-
T-Takasu-kun!
He just left, so he might be that wa-
There he is!
Follow him!
Y-Yeah!
What?
Get out of the way!
She's fast!
At that speed, she'll catch him-
Ryuuji!
Are the cookies okay?
Huh?
Just as I thought. It's swollen.
Did you find the cookies?
Were they safe?
I-I see...
Hey.
I might just be a klutz.
She wasn't aware of that already?
If I write a love letter, I end up putting it in the wrong bag.
If I try to invade a house, I fall over from hunger.
If I play basketball, I get a ball right in the face.
If I try to hand over some cookies, I fall down the stairs,
dropping the cookies...
Now, now, there's more.
Like forgetting to put the love letter inside the envelope.
There was that too...
Give me one of those.
Huh? Wait, they were smashed into pieces...
And besides they t-
They're great!
They came out okay, didn't they?
It's a shame.
Let's try harder next time.
I did  see them.
They were buying things like spring onions and radishes at the supermarket.
Statement, Witness #1, Year 2 Class C, H-To K-ji
Are they like, married?
Statement, Witness #2, Year 2 Class C, K-hara M-ya
They left the same apartment building together with naughty looks on their faces.
Statement, Witness #3, Year 2 Class C, N-to H-mitsu
Also, they were feeding each other home-made cookies saying, "Here, open up!"
Statement, Witness #4, Year 2 Class C, K-shii N-nako
Really? Are they like that? No way!
Hey, Minorin. What's up with your best friend?
What the?
Hey, get inside already.
My.
"My"?
May I have a moment?
The sun is dry...
What's up with Kushieda-san?
I don't know.
Takasu-kun.
Yes! What, me?
Please take good care of Taiga!
Huh?
Taiga is my dearest best friend!
Please bestow happiness upon her!
Wait, Kushieda. Are you saying you're-
Happiness?
So that's how it was.
You must be happy!
Kitamura? What're you doing up there?
I was wondering why you were together so often,
but now that I think about it, you two fit together so well!
Aisaka! Pull yourself together!
You! Stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you make Taiga cry... I won't forgive you.
Kushi... eda...
I'm sorry.
Minorin misunderstood everything
because I was intruding at your house.
No, that's-
Your place was...
...really cosy.
You see, I struggled so much with my
parents that when I said I wanted to leave,
they simply gave me that apartment.
I knew they were those kind of parents, but...
The cookies were salty, weren't they?
I was frustrated when I found them in pieces, so I ate some.
They were horrible!
Yet you ate all of them.
You even lied about their taste.
Even if you're a mongrel, your fur will shed if you keep being so nice to everyone.
Mind your own business.
Hey, do you also feel frustrated when you think about Minori?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I guess you would...
Aisaka?
Why doesn't anyone understand us?
Even when we're so troubled, why doesn't anyone support us?
Really, everyone...
Everyone's... Everyone's...
Pissing me off!
Who's the Palmtop Tiger?!
I'm not okay with being that at all!
Minorin, you idiot!
Kitamura-kun, you idiot!
Why won't you listen to me?!
Even Mum, even Dad, no one...
...understands me...
I'll help out.
Do you have a problem with me being small?!
Stop calling me a delinquent just because of my appearance!
Do you have a problem with us being together in front of everyone?!
I'm sorry for having evil-looking eyes!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey Ryuuji, isn't this pole tilted now?
Huh? That's not poss-
It is tilted!
See?!
Yes!
We won, we won!
All right, I've decided!
Tomorrow, I will confess to Kitamura-kun.
It'll all be over then.
Over?
Your services as a dog will be over.
As of tomorrow, we're just classmates who live close to each other.
And that's all there is to it.
Bye bye, Takasu-kun.
Yeah...
Ryuu-chan...
Aren't we having breakfast really early today?
Ya-chan likes canned mackerel...
Is Taiga-chan still sleeping?
I don't know.
Did you have a fight?
No, we didn't.
I'm so bored.
Right?
Yes.
H-Hey.
Did she...?
T-Takasu, we're sorry.
We spread all those weird rumours...
Aisaka-san got mad at us.
Huh?
"There's nothing between me and Ryuuji."
Saying you're not a delinquent, making a huge mess...
She really is scary, that Palmtop Tiger.
But I said that Takasu isn't as scary as he looks, right?
What, when did you?
More importantly, If we don't clean this up, won't we be in trouble?
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun, I'm sorry.
A-About what?
You see, Taiga was saying...
"I'm absolutely not going out with Takasu-kun."
"So this is all a misunderstanding."
She especially wanted me to be aware of this...
And she had this kind of desperate, serious look about her.
But does that mean she...
Does that mean she-
Do you know, Takasu-kun?
Takasu-kun?
What does she think she's doing?
Weren't you going to confess to Kitamura today?!
This isn't the time to be worrying about me!
As of tomorrow, we're just classmates who live close to each other.
And that's all there is to it.
"And that's all there is to it"?
Kitamura-kun!
I... Kitamura-kun...
I have feelings, um...
I, uh... That is...
Why are you doing it right after arriving at school?
If things don't turn out well, this will be one hell of a bad day, you know.
Um, uh...
Wait up.
I think I know how this conversation's going to end.
But before that, I'd like to confirm something.
Aren't you dating Takasu-kun?
That was just Minorin misunderstanding things!
There's nothing between us!
So you don't like him?
It's not like that!
Our houses just happen to be close to each other.
It has nothing to do with me liking him or not.
Then, do you dislike him?
I don't dislike him.
But it's not about that!
Um, you see, Takasu-kun is...
Yes, fried rice!
Ryuuji made me delicious fried rice!
He cheered me up...
He even lied to make me feel better...
Being there for me...
Because Ryuuji was there, because he was supporting me...
Because of that, I'm able to stand here like this!
I'm in love with you, Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka, you're amazing.
I see.
It's okay, I think your feelings were properly relayed.
Kitamura-kun?
Do you recall one year ago. Aisaka?
Yeah.
Unlike that time, you now have this...
...funny-looking face!
Funny face?
Yeah, when you're around Takasu, you have this funny-looking face.
Takasu's a great guy,
and you thinking of him like you did earlier...
...makes you a wonderful girl.
Like I did earlier?
What did I say?
But I'm relieved you're on such good terms with Takasu.
W-Wait up!
Ryuuji doesn't have anything to do-
My face was funny-looking?
My feet, what about my feet? Wait, what am I saying?
Was I able to tell you I love you?
It's going to be okay, Aisaka.
It's okay.
W-What's going to be okay?!
You haven't understood what I was saying!
It'll be okay.
From now on, I'm sure we'll be great friends.
Like I'm saying, not friends, I was confess-
Friends?
Yes, friends.
Oops, we'll be late for homeroom.
Better hurry up, Aisaka!
I thought you were going to start crying.
Y-You! D-Did you see all of it?
I did, but I didn't mean to...
"Didn't mean to"? You-!
But what are you going to do?
I'm going home.
I see.
I'll make you food.
You haven't had breakfast, have you?
And did you even eat last night?
I'm sure you went to the convenie-
Stop it!
Why? If you do that, people will start misunderstanding again.
I told you you don't have to do this any more!
I don't get it either,
but I can't leave you alone!
I'm telling you it's enough already!
You're no longer my dog!
I see.
Yes, I'm not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
So, I'm able to be by your side!
Ais-
Taiga!
"Taiga"?
Since the ancient times, the dragon has been the only beast that could stand equal with a tiger.
I'll become a dragon.
And thus, as a dragon, I'll be able to stay by your side, tiger.
There's a limit to how impudent you can be!
Ow...
Know your place already!
Why, you...
Hey!
Hurry up. I'm hungry, you know.
And we're going to make a new plan.
I'm not going to give up on Kitamura-kun after just this.
Does that mean...?
It doesn't matter whether you're a dog or a dragon...
Since you said you'd be at my side, you better work hard, Ryuuji.
Did I decide on this too quickly...?
Come on already!
Yeah, yeah.
He said, "Taiga."
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira soruto de
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
Your Song
Club activities-girl, Kushieda.
Heart-warming girl, Kushieda.
Ah, you're Kushieda!
Who always shines so brightly with joy!
We want a home run!