Under the night sky, lit by countless stars and the fleeting crescent moon,
Exit
Entrance
Fumizuki
Academy Group
the girls of our class, being a little forceful, were on the attack.
Aki, should we do it?
Please! I want to go further!
I can't do that.
Why not?
Don't you like it?
I won't be able to handle it.
If you can't, then I'll have to ask Tsuchiya instead.
Are you okay with that, Aki?
Yeah. I don't mind.
You heard him! Tsuchiya, you'll let us, right?
Peeping Toms
One more slab!
Groan
Ishidaki, also known as soroban-zeme, is a method of torture from the Edo period.
I won't forgive infidelity.
Akihisa, you too.
No!
The girls really are quite bold tonight.
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Let's rewind to this morning, as it was a bit unusual.
Question 5
Me, a Peeping Tom, and Training Camp!
An intensive academic training camp was due to begin the next day,
and Yoshii Akihisa had received a letter.
Within, was a message that
made his heart skip a beat.
I know your secret.
Why me?
What's wrong, Akihisa?
You look pretty down this morning.
N-Nothing's wrong, really!
You're acting strange, Aki.
What are you hiding?
Come on, Minami! I'm not hiding anything!
Maybe you got a love letter from someone?
Watch what you say, Minami.
They're waiting for the kill.
But I know you'd never get something like that!
That's not true!
In my shoebox this morning, I found many—
I won't miss next time.
I'm deeply sorry.
Then give me an honest answer!
Th-The truth is, I got a letter—
I shouldn't tell people about
blackmail letters, should I?
On TV shows, the perpetrators...
What letter?
L-Letter?
When a person is in a bind,
they replay past memories.
Games
Fun
( omoshiroi )
White Tail
( o mo shiroi )
Cats
( neko )
Koalas
( koara )
Wrapper
( rappa )
Their life flashes by, so to speak.
Panties
( pantsu )
Swimwear
I-It's a letter of invitation from the
Competitive Swimsuit Appreciation society!
What?
Documentary
Competitive Swimmers!
24 Hours
For Glory at the Olympics
Last night, Akihisa watched a documentary called "A Day in the Life of a Competitive Swimmer".
You're joining that society?
W-Well yeah, I've always had an interest.
This is looking bad. I can't take it back now.
What about competitive swimsuits piques your interest?
What stood out the most was...
H-How tight they are?
I sound like a total pervert!
Shimada, that was all a lie.
Really? It was so realistic I almost fell for it!
Crack
This is your last chance!
What are you hiding?
The truth is, I got a blackmail letter.
Oh, that's great to hear.
What did the blackmail letter say?
Oh...
it warned me not to get any
closer to the girls around me.
Hmm, going on that, it's probably jealousy.
It has to be someone in love with one of the two girls in this class, Himeji and Hideyoshi.
Akihisa, Shimada's gone to get a metal bat.
I got it wrong?
So, what are you being blackmailed with?
Actually, I don't know.
If you don't heed my warning, I'll publicize the enclosed photos.
If you don't heed my warning,
I'll publicize the enclosed photos.
If you don't heed my warning, I'll publicize the enclosed photos.
That's from the cultural festival!
Wh-When did they...
These aren't too bad, I think.
It's all right since I'm in boxers!
What's the matter, Akihisa?
It's okay, I can still handle this.
No!
Noooooo
Don't look! Don't look at my dirty photo!
I'm not sure what's going on, but calm down Akihisa.
Such a fear inducing plan;
why such a dastardly scheme?!
You're over thinking things.
Everyone has worn a maid outfit
at least once in their life.
Good morning, Akihisa, Kinoshita!
Oh, Himeji.
Perfect timing, let Himeji reassure you that this photo is nothing to worry about.
What's the matter?
Himeji, what would you do if there was a picture of Akihisa in a maid outfit?
Well let's see, first I'd go and buy a scanner.
Huh?
Otherwise, I'd be unable to share Akihisa's loveliness with people on the Internet!
Calm down, Akihisa!
Let me go!
I can't live any longer!
How about asking Voyeur?
Oh, thanks for the nice advice, Hideyoshi!
As I'd expect of my bride!
I think you mean the groom.
I think you're both mistaken.
Oh shit.
There you are!
Voyeur, can we—
Come back later, I'm first.
Huh? First?
Apparently, Yuuji will be marrying soon.
That's yesterday's news.
I'm in more trouble!
At this rate, people will treat me
like a cross-dressing pervert!
That's last year's news!
Shut up, you henpecked loser!
Go back to your ball-and-chain!
Shut up, you pervert!
Hurry up and go work in a maid cafe!
You should both keep quiet
rather than hurt each other.
So, I took this from Shouko.
I'll propose to you if I win the contest!
I love you, Shouko!
It's a line Akihisa and Hideyoshi fabricated on the
second day of the Fumizuki Academy school festival.
Kirishima sure is cute!
She must have wanted to
treasure that as a keepsake.
No, she'll make sure her father listens
to it as proof of our engagement.
Shouko's terrible with technology;
she can't have recorded this!
It must have been someone else.
Akihisa, what's your problem?
Well, the panty shot of me in a maid outfit might be put on the Internet.
What happened?
Sorry, I cut the story short.
I know your secret.
What happened was blah blah blah blah.
Fun
Swimwear
For Glory at the Olympics
If you don't heed my warning, I'll publicize the enclosed photos.
I see, and the photos?
They're right here.
These are—
What's wrong, Voyeur?
They're from better angles than mine!
I didn't know I was under attack from you too!
Rest assured, I don't distribute mine for free.
So it's fine as long as you're getting paid?!
I see.
Akihisa, our situations are quite similar.
You're both being blackmailed.
One through eavesdropping, the other through peeping.
Eavesdropping
Peeping
Voyeur, can you investigate this?
In return, I'll get a porn ma—
I'll get on the case.
I'll give you something from My Treasured Collection II—
I'll definitely investigate the case.
Academic training camp
That's all you need to know about
the academic training camp.
The camp takes place in Uzuki Plateau, huh?
It's a very nice summer resort!
I'm looking forward to it!
Each class gathers in a different location, so make sure you know where to go.
I'm sure Class A gets to ride a
limo bus there or something.
I guess Class F will get a cramped micro bus.
A fold-up side seat or strap,
or even the trunk or bike rack.
Too bad
Class F will gather on site.
You're not even giving us directions?!
It's an unequal society.
There's nothing to do.
I'm bored.
Minami, what are you reading?
Find Happiness With
Psychological Tests
A book of psychological tests.
Oh, that sounds interesting!
Test me!
Sure.
Find Happiness With
Psychological Tests
Anticipation
Find Happiness With
Psychological Tests
Name the girl that each color makes you think of.
First, green;
second, orange;
and third, blue.
Green, orange, and blue, huh?
Well let's see, orange is Hideyoshi,
blue is Himeji,
and Minami, you're green I guess.
Find Happiness With
Psychological Tests
Mind explaining why Mizuki is blue and I'm green?
She'd just get mad if I said her
underwear was green the other day.
I won't get angry, so be honest.
You had green underwear on the other day!
Sakamoto, open the window.
Sure.
You're going to throw me out the window?!
Let's see what it says.
Green is a friend, orange is a
source of energy, and blue is—
No, give it back!
Akihisa, it said to name a girl
for each color. Who is orange?
You, Hideyoshi.
It bothers me a little that that makes me happy.
So, Minami, what does the blue girl represent?
Question two!
She probably doesn't want to answer.
Pick the first two numbers, in order, that comes to mind from one to ten.
Five and six.
Two and seven for me.
I'll say one and four.
I'll pick three and nine.
Yuuji
Hideyoshi
Akihisa
Mizuki
The first number indicates
how you appear to others.
Sakamoto, five means you're cool and cynical.
Kinoshita, two means you're calm and sensible.
Aki, one means... die.
Mizuki, three means you're gentle and careful.
Was I the only one who was
verbally abused right now?
Yuuji
Hideyoshi
Akihisa
Mizuki
The second number is your true
nature that you keep hidden.
Sakamoto, six means you're fair and kind.
Kinoshita, seven means you're charming.
Aki, four means you should die a brutal death.
Mizuki, nine means you're strong willed.
Did mine just get even worse?!
I think he woke up.
Morning, Voyeur.
I woke up because I'm hungry.
Yeah, it's about that time.
Let's have some lunch!
In that case, I actually brought some lunch.
If you'd like—
No!
Th-Thanks for the offer but I made some too.
Sorry, I've got my own as well.
I've already cooked mine.
You can give it to Akihisa, Himeji.
Actually, I brought sandwiches.
Chomp
Sorry, Akihisa, my hand slipped.
You bastard.
Be careful, Yuuji!
Oops, my hand!
Argh!
I'll hold it tightly so it doesn't slip.
Jeez, stop fooling around, you're so helpless.
Aki, want some of this?
That looks delicious!
Y-You can have as much as you want.
Thanks for the food!
Um, Aki, I'm kind of hesitant to admit it, but I actually put a lot of...
Munch munch
mustard in it!
Fire! Are you an idiot?!
This is so spicy! Spicy!
Akihisa, in a way, you actually got lucky.
I see now! That completely nuked my taste buds!
Akihisa, try mine too.
Thanks!
Here I go!
300 joules, charge!
What... happened?
I thought you were a goner when you
started repenting your sins in your sleep.
Where am I?
We're at the training camp.
We arrived here while you were
drifting between life and death.
This is our room.
Since Akihisa has awakened, let's get started.
Started... with what?
Our operation to seek out the
one responsible for the crimes.
I've obtained new information.
Really, Voyeur?
I found traces of the tools,
which I believe the culprit used.
Given the perpetrator's modus
operandi plus what I've discovered,
Culprit
I have absolute proof the culprit
is the same for both crimes.
So, who's the culprit?
Sorry.
Oh... you can't know right now...
What I do know is that the culprit is
female and has a burn mark on her ass.
Just what have you been searching for?
This is one of my hidden cameras from school.
Look at this.
This is...!
The girls' changing room.
Mosaics?
You have to pay to remove them.
Aren't we buddies?
Hey! Isn't that Shouko?!
That's her cellphone!
You're right. I'll zoom in.
Let's see...
Request:
Request: Another proposal from Yuuji, please.
Another proposal
from Yuuji, please.
Send.
That Shouko!
She got a reply.
Thanks for the business. I'll cut you a deal since you're returning.
Thanks for the business.
I'll cut you a deal since
you're returning.
I'll pass it to you next
monday, as the camp will
be starting tomorrow.
I'll pass it to you next Monday, as the camp will be starting tomorrow.
That was close!
This camp saved me!
There are pictures too.
What the hell is this?!
I can no longer marry!
This confirms that the crimes were perpetrated by the same person.
Here's the biggest clue.
There's more to it.
You have so many wonderful pictures.
Won't you be in a lot of trouble if
Won't you be in a lot of trouble if you're found out?
you're found out?
Message sent.
A new message has arrived.
So quick!
This is just between you and me, but my mum found out
about this the other day, and my ass got moxied.
Thanks to that, I still have the burn marks.
Isn't this a horribly cruel thing to do to a young maiden?
This is just between you and me, but my mum found out about this the other day and my ass got moxied.
This is just between you and me, but my mum found out
about this the other day, and my ass got moxied.
Thanks to that, I still have the burn marks.
Isn't this a horribly cruel thing to do to a young maiden?
Isn't that a horribly cruel thing to do to a young maiden?
That's as much as I know.
I see, by maiden, it could only refer to a girl or Hideyoshi.
Uh... haha...
A girl with burn marks on her ass, huh?
I can't just flip their skirts!
The marks won't show up on my IR camera either.
Oh yeah! We can get Hideyoshi to
check them out in the baths!
Why do you assume that I'd be
able to go in with the girls?
Akihisa, have you read the information
pamphlets about the camp?
These will be the bath times for each class.
F Class Kinoshita Hideyoshi
Private Bathroom 4
They've even prepared a separate bath for him!
Why do I get special treatment?
Freeze! Don't move!
Put your hands behind your head
and get down on your knees!
What?!
I said, hands behind your head
and down on your knees!
Kinoshita, come with me!
Hey. Wait!
What is this?!
We know that you're the ones who did it!
Did what?
I'm talking about this.
It was installed in the girls' changing room.
Isn't that spying?!
Who would do something li—
Who else would've done it?!
You're wrong! They wouldn't do something like—
That's kind of...
undeniable.
Eh?!
Is that true, Akihisa?
So it really was you?
It's a lie, isn't it?
I trust you.
Why...
did you bring that torture gear then?
You're so mean, Akihisa!
To think you tried to see my body
after we'd just finished dinner...
I'm normally much slimmer!
That's what you're mad about?!
Me too! My breasts are normally big—
That is a LIE!
Girls, get him!
Damn it! I didn't think!
Yuuji! Do something!
I won't forgive...
infidelity!
I guess you can't.
It's too late for him.
Him too!
We will...
...take good care of you boys.
That was quite the injustice, albeit
I was treated as a victim and spared.
Really, it was a huge misunderstanding.
We hadn't even seen anything yet.
I've done nothing to compromise my operations.
That answer's going to give you away.
So be it!
What's up, Yuuji?
I've already done the crime,
so I might as well do the crime!
Do it? You don't mean—
Exactly! We're gonna spy on them!
Yuuji, if you wanted to see Kirishima's body, I'm sure you could just ask.
Cut the crap! I don't give a damn about her body!
So, we're going in to find the culprit with the burn mark?
Yeah! I didn't want to do this at first, but after what they've done to us; there's no need to hold back!
We'll spy on them as much as
we want and find the culprit!
Judging from the camera and the mic, it's the same person who blackmailed you.
What?!
So, the blackmailer and the
peeping tom are the same person?!
They've got nowhere to run now.
All right, let's go!
Women's
Bath
They're only in the bath for 30 more minutes.
This leads to the girls' bath.
There's no time! Make a run for it!
Stop right there!
Where are you going?
It's Mr. Fuse, the science teacher!
Never mind! Just charge through!
You should at least worry a little...
Summoned Beast: Summon!
Isn't that...
...a Summoned Being?
A teacher's Summoned Being can interact with
physical objects, just like a Punishment Inspector's.
Since it's come to this, we'll just have to beat him!
Leave it to me!
Wait.
Just to be safe, tell me your score for science.
In the last test, I only needed one more point...
One more to?
...to get a two-digit score.
Tell me that sooner, dumbass!
It's gonna be tough taking on
a teacher one-on-one, I'll help.
Thanks, Hideyoshi.
Summon!
Okay, Voyeur, we'll go on ahe—
He's gone!
Stop right there!
Mr. Ooshima, the PE teacher!
Give up, Tsuchiya!
Mr. Ooshima, I'm not here to peep!
Then what is it?
I'm here for the PE practicals.
Summon!
Go, Akihisa! I've got this!
Voyeur...
Hang in there!
For sure, I'll...
I'll...!
I-Iron Man!
Man, you guys are such a pain.
I can't lose here!
Summon!
Huh? Mr. Nishimura, where's your Summoned Being?
Well, shit happened and I ran out of points.
I see, with the rage of a thousand beat-downs:
Fist of Death!
Yoshii...
Do you know why I won't cancel your status as the Punishment Inspector?
I'm glad you're the Punishment Inspector.
Because it doesn't count as hitting a student if I do it through your Summoned Beast!
Brace yourself!
Supplementary lessons for the insolent fool!
You three too.
Thus, the first day of camp ended.
However, the boys have failed
to clear the false accusations.
Will the real culprit ever be discovered? Stay tuned.
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
shinten shinai yo
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Question 5
Training Camp Diary
Write down what happened on your
first day of Training Camp.
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
The train stopped, and a
sudden dizzying feeling
overwhelmed me as I
stepped out onto the
platform. The scenery
and the scent of the air
is different from the town
we live in, and I could feel
that something wonderful
was about to happen
before my very eyes.
Teacher's Comment
I see that a change of
atmosphere has been
good for you. I hope you
will be able to have
many cherished memories
during this time in your
life.
Tsuchiya Kouta's Answer
The train stopped, and a sudden
dizzying feeling came over me as I
stepped onto the platform. What was
that feeling, I wonder?
Teacher's Comment
Probably motion sickness.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
I took a deep breath as I
stepped onto the platform
and could smell a curious
odor, which was somewhat
sweet, yet was also a little
sour. I wondered deeply,
"Is this the scent of this
town?"
Teacher's Comment
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
You would probably have
experienced quite a different
smell had Tsuchiya not been
vomiting beside you.
That was a good bath.
It feels great to soak in a large bath, doesn't it?
Question 6
Answer the following question.
State the idiom which has the
meaning: "Things can happen
over and over again".
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
What can happen twice can
happen thrice.
Teacher's Comment
Correct as always, Himeji.
There are other idioms as well,
such as "Things always happen
thrice", "Calamity happen not
once, but twice", and so on.
These idioms are often used to
describe the repetition of an
unfortunate event.
Remember to learn from your
mistakes so as not to repeat
them again.
Yoshii Akihisa's Answer
Teacher's Comment
Next Episode
Question 6: State the idiom which has the meaning:
"Things can happen over and over again".
The cycle of death
The cycle of death and rebirth.
and rebirth
and rebirth.
Do you want to be in Class F in your next life, too?
Do you want to be in
Class F in your next
life, too?
Next episode: Me, a Peeping Tom, and the Brotherhood of Men!
Me, a Peeping Tom, and the Brotherhood of Men!
This will be on your test.