[heavy metal music playing]
GREAT EMULATION
BEFORE THE START OF THE SECOND BOUT
IN THE FINAL BATTLE BETWEEN GOD AND MAN
[chuckling]
The next round's mine.
I just have to make sure
I keep a cool head.
If I let myself get fired up, I'll burn
my enemy before the match begins.
Hm?
[laughing]
What is it, old man?
You come all the way here
to cheer me on in person?
This second round is mine.
What are you even talking about?
I'm the one set for round two.
This second round is mine.
We agreed.
You said that you would
take the final round.
If you're asking to trade spots,
then forget it.
It is the first time
my blood has boiled like this in years.
[shouting] So get
your damn hand off of me!
This second round is mine.
[growling with frustration]
[chuckling]
[cackling]
Are you deaf or just senile?
I told you that I'm the one who's up n--
[grunting in pain]
This second round is mine.
[grunting]
[wheezing]
[chuckles] I understand.
You won't take no for an answer.
Well, if it's a fight you want, then let's
do this, old man. Right here and now.
[Hermes] Oh, now this sounds like fun.
[Shiva shuddering]
[inhaling sharply]
[sighing]
All right, then. Guess I have no choice.
Round two is yours.
Age before beauty, as the saying goes.
Don't forget, you owe me one.
[laughing]
[sighing] Seriously?
They're not fighting then? Too bad.
[laughing continues]
[Hermes] In all the universe,
is there anyone more shameless?
[gods chanting] GFOC! GFOC!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
My goodness, what a troublesome man he is.
- [smashing]
- Hm?
ARES
ONE OF THE 12 GODS OF OLYMPUS
[Heimdall] Now, it's the battle
you've all been waiting for.
Round two's a real dream match.
Zeus versus Adam!
The mightiest of Gods
against the first man!
[male god 1] Get him, Zeus!
[male god 2] This match'll
be over like that!
[man 1] Adam!
[man 2] Kick his ass!
[man 3] Don't let him win!
Hey, you're going to do that
fancy little trick, aren't you?
Ho-ho! It's my favorite, you know.
The trick where you
and a Valkyrie merge together.
If you don't...
little man,
this won't take long.
See for yourself.
Hmm?
Pegasus?
Ah! Those glasses are...
Yeah, the Valkyrie best suited
to the father of mankind.
Our sister,
she who was abandoned by the gods.
Reginleif.
REGINLEIF
SEVENTH OF THE 13 VALKYRIE
She looks so awesome up there.
[humans gasping]
Adam, please give me your hand right now.
It's vital that we create
a bond between us.
With that complete,
I will then become a part of you.
[church bell ringing]
[exclaiming in wonderment]
- In this moment now, our hearts are one!
DIVINE TREASURE FORGE
Völundr!
[laughing gleefully]
Oh!
Is that Adam's chosen weapon?
[Heimdall in disbelief] Brass knuckles?
[humans groaning]
Hm.
Are you kidding me?
[laughing]
Hmm.
These are pretty sweet.
THE FINAL BATTLE BETWEEN GOD AND MAN
[cackling]
THE SECOND BOUT
ZEUS VS. ADAM
All right. Let's get this rolling.
The ultimate battle between god and man, Ragnarok,
round two.
Representing the gods, Zeus.
Representing humanity, Adam.
Let the battle begin!
What a twist!
The Valkyries have used
their Divine Treasure Forge Völundr
to bestow Adam with some brass knuckles!
It would seem as though this man
really intends to fistfight Zeus,
the king of gods himself!
And my, what a man he is.
Truly a man among men.
[man 4] Hey, Dad!
Give his wrinkled old face
a good punch for us!
ADAM'S SECOND SON - ABEL
ADAM'S FIRST SON - CAIN
Take him down, Papa!
[laughing]
Well now, you really picked a good one.
Hmm. It's a pretty solid weapon.
So, what's yours, chuckles?
Huh?
[gods clamoring]
[male god 3] Did that human
just call Zeus "chuckles"?
[whimpering]
Ho, ho, ho! Oh, me?
I want my fist to hear the cracking of
your bones as they shatter into bits, so...
My bare hand should suffice.
[twinkling]
Mmm. Okay, then.
But I think you're gonna regret that.
[laughing] Well, I'll give you
credit for your spirit!
All right, I'll go first!
And for the first strike...
Try this baby on for size!
0.01 SECONDS
Ho, ho, not bad.
That last attack was
Zeus's near-light-speed jab!
Adam just dodged it
without breaking a sweat!
[Zeus laughing]
- [humans cheering]
- Nice job, Papa!
Hell yeah!
Hm. Listen to them cheer.
All that noise
because he dodged father's punch.
A warm-up strike.
These humans are pathetic.
Tragically foolish creatures.
Wouldn't you agree, Hermes?
Yes, brother Ares.
I most certainly would.
Ho, ho, ho, ho! Pretty good.
No more pulling punches.
Time for the real beatdown!
0.001 SECONDS
[Zeus grunting]
0.0001 SECONDS
[Zeus grunting rapidly]
0.00001 SECONDS
[Zeus] Ha! Ha!
Hya!
Meteor Jab!
[Heimdall] Zeus lets loose with a flurry
of jab, jab, jab, jab, jabs!
What an unbelievable flurry of fury!
But against all odds, Adam keeps dodging,
dodging, dodging and dodging again!
Zeus's fists keep
flying faster and faster!
But Adam rises to the occasion
and dodges every single strike.
0.00000001 SECONDS
And next up is...
Divine Axe!
Hm. Looks like
he's about to be cut clean in half.
[Zeus straining]
Huh?
[Heimdall] He... He dodged it!
Adam dodged Zeus's combo attack!
- [crowd screaming]
- What a spectacular, picture-perfect jump!
[chuckling]
Well done! Oh, you are good.
I'm very impressed.
But you know,
you cannot win this fight
simply by running away.
Oh, I'm keenly aware of that.
Huh?
So, how about... this.
0.01 SECONDS
[Zeus] That speed.
The way he moved just now.
Could he be...?
Oh-ho! Pretty good.
No more pulling punches.
0.001 SECONDS
0.0001 SECONDS
Here I go.
[exhaling sharply]
0.00001 SECONDS
Meteor Jab!
But, that's my...
[both] Huh?
[Zeus grunting]
Next up is...
Huh?
Divine Axe!
[straining]
[gods gasping]
Huh?
Oh, dear! That looked painful.
[groaning]
- [shimmering]
- Not bad.
[stammering] This has got to be
some sort of miracle!
Not only has Adam dodged Zeus's attacks,
he used those same attacks against him
and scored a direct hit!
- Yeah!
- Yeah, he did!
- [humans cheering wildly]
- That's the way!
[woman 1] You've got this, Adam!
[Göll] That... That was amazing!
I was kind of worried about him
when he showed up all naked,
but he's really strong.
I can't believe a human could use
a god's own attack against him.
- Oh, Göll, how easily we seem to forget.
- Huh?
The birth of Adam, the father of mankind,
that was the beginning.
The beginning?
Uh!
[narrator] "So God
created man in his own image."
The Old Testament, Genesis 1:27.
Yes, mankind was created
in the image of god.
In other words,
Adam is a copy of the divine.
And so, he is able to flawlessly replicate
any technique he sees a god put to use.
So if the gods try to shit on him,
he can smear it on their smug faces!
That is Adam's greatest power!
[narrator] Correct. And the power's name
is Divine Reflection.
[Zeus chuckling]
Well done. Well done.
- I haven't had this much fun...
- [bones cracking]
...in at least ten millennia.
But, no more playing around.
Ah, those bizarre stomping movements.
If he's getting his legs limbered up,
does he plan to end this with a kick?
[shimmering]
Dodge this!
Oh!
[gods gasping]
[tapping]
Oh... How did you...
[exciting rock music playing]
[Heimdall] He's... He's down!
Against all odds, against all logic,
Zeus the almighty has been taken down!
[humans cheering]
Once more, Adam has perfectly replicated
one of Zeus's signature attacks!
Shh. Who the hell
does that human think he is?
Huh?
[giggling]
Hm.
[sighing]
[Ares] This battle...
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
...it's like looking into a mirror,
and trying to fight your own reflection.
[Adam sighing]
To be honest with you,
I didn't want to have to resort to this.
But this is a fight after all.
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
I'm sorry about this, gramps.
Huh? "Gramps"?
- [Hermes laughing]
- [Ares gasping]
- [Göll whimpering]
- [Brünnhilde giggling]
[laughing]
I'm so happy!
Just so happy.
So happy, I...
So happy, I can't...
take it anymore! Ha!
[ominous piano music playing]
[squealing] No matter what he says,
that guy is definitely not happy!
He's so mad, it's just plain scary.
[sobbing]
All right. Let's see
if you can copy this one.
Brace yourself!
- Is he really...?
- So it seems. And on a human no less.
Our grandfather's move.
[Brünnhilde] A long time ago,
somewhere in the galaxy,
in the final round of the Titanomachy,
the battle to determine
the most powerful god in the universe,
the young Zeus won a definitive victory
over his father,
Cronus, the guardian of time and space.
Robbing him of his title
of the strongest god in the universe.
[Zeus] My father's last attack,
I never even saw it coming.
[sighing]
Before I'd noticed, he'd shattered my jaw.
[Brünnhilde] Zeus had won
every round without getting hit,
with this as the sole exception.
[Zeus] What even was that?
[Brünnhilde] His father Cronus's attack
Gotta say you were a shitty father
to the last,
but still...
you were one hell of a fighter.
[narrator] As a young god,
Zeus learned how to perform
his father's final attack.
making it his own.
He gave this attack a name.
A name imbued with the respect
he felt towards his father,
as well as the hatred.
[whooshing]
The attack that rules over time itself.
The Fist That Surpassed Time!
THE FIST THAT SURPASSED TIME!
[splashing]
[Zeus] Oooh.
Now that was cool.
Thanks for the attack.
Goodnight, gramps.
[clock ticking]
Huh?
[both gasping]
[wheezing] How can this be?
Zeus, the father of the entire universe,
has fallen!
Laid low by the first of men!
[gasping]
[giggling]
[Japanese pop ballad playing]