Erika, would you like to come to the botanical gardens with me today?
You mean your grandma's botanical gardens?
Yeah!
She said a really rare and beautiful rubellum lily has bloomed, and invited us over to see it.
Okay then!
Now that it's settled, let's cut the chit-chat and go!
E-Erika! Wait just a second!
Peek-a-boo!
Hi! We're here, Tsubomi's grandma!
Welcome.
Yuri!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
And here's something for you, Chypre and Coffret.
Yay!
It's so sweet and delicious!
Still, what a coincidence this is.
It's amazing you all just happened to show up on the same day.
Grandma, you invited Yuri too, didn't you?
Well, the plant's genus is otome-yuri after all.
That's so funny!
Tsubomi!
Tsubomi, this is our opening!
Opening?
Yuri was Cure Moonlight, the Precure before us, right?
There's so many things I wanna ask her.
Right, but...
I cannot fight alongside you.
My mother is probably worried about me, so...
Yuri!
Just leave her alone for the moment, all right?
Grandma?
The damage that Sabark and Dark Precure inflicted on her heart has not yet healed.
And since she lost her Seed of the Precure, Yuri...
can't become Cure Moonlight anymore.
Oh, this won't do!
We're all out of tea cakes!
In that case, I'll go and buy some more.
But you're a guest, Yuri! I'll go instead.
Grandma, the usual shop's fine, right?
Fine by me.
I'll come too!
It's fine, really.
You two only just arrived, so please take it easy for a bit.
I want to get some fresh air anyway.
But...
Why don't you all go together then?
Okay!
We'll be off, then!
That's fine, right, Yuri?
Sure.
Please Recognize
Our Precure Spirits!
Yuri!
What is it?
U-Um...
We were hoping you'd be able to give us some advice.
Like how to fight better, or what the Desert Apostles' weaknesses are, or anything you think could help us!
Please help us!
Please!
I told you, didn't I?
I'm not going to concern myself dealing with you two.
I'm not a Precure anymore.
But...
Besides, the Desert Apostles are only going to become more fierce in their assaults.
If you're really seeking advice from me, then you might as well give up now.
Moonlight!
I've continued fighting all on my own, no matter how hard or how painful it gets!
All so I could protect this world!
Do you really have that kind of resolve?
I've never seen you put it on display.
Cure Blossom, Cure Marine,
I don't recognize you as Precure.
What the heck? She didn't have to be so rude.
Right?
Yuri, this is the place!
Harano Confectionery.
Their daifuku mochi are simply the best!
Their soy beans are boiled with just the right amount of salt,
and there's this subtle, refined sweetness to the bean paste.
And it's all wrapped up in a smooth shell, like a rhapsodious trinity!
It's enough to melt your heart.
I wanna try one already!
Show a little restraint!
Let's just buy some and head back, all right?
Good afternoon.
Oh, it's Tsubomi!
Good afternoon, Chizuko!
We'd like our usual daifuku, please.
Coming right up!
Like I said, what's the difference?
Oh, what's with you, Bro?
Tsubomi, can you just hold on a second?
O-Okay.
We've got customers. Keep it down!
Just answer me, Dad!
What's the difference between your daifuku and mine?!
Have you tried so many of your own that
you've forgotten how they're meant to taste?!
Bro...
Chizuko, you mustn't keep our customers waiting.
Right!
I'm terribly sorry. You shouldn't've had to see that.
It's fine.
Is something the matter with Masahiro?
He's been training for a while, and they finally
said he could start making the Harano daifuku,
but it looks like it's not going as well as he'd hoped.
Harano Confectionery
Thanks for stopping by, anyway!
Well then, Cure Flower will be waiting for us!
Hey! Hold on a second!
Tsubomi, I'm sorry about just now.
Um... the thing is, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Could you ask your grandma to try these, Tsubomi?
Oh, thanks very much!
What are these?
The daifuku I made.
I want to get some feedback from our regular customers.
They're delicious!
Jeez, Erika!
It'd be nice if everyone was as easy to please as you.
My old man and gramps are always so tough on me.
They never tell me my stuff's tasty or give me a single word of praise.
Really?
I'm third in line, so I'm gonna end
up inheriting the shop eventually.
I wanna make great daifuku so they'll recognize me as a deserving heir!
So I'm counting on you, Tsubomi!
And these are the Harano daifuku he made for you.
I can't believe little Masa's all grown up and started making his own daifuku.
Time really does fly, doesn't it?
Let's see here.
H-How are they?
They're nice, but he still has a ways to go.
That's all you have to say?
I think so.
That's harsh, Grandma.
Right?
Right.
I suppose Yuri thinks we still have a ways to go too, huh?
This is really irritating!
I want Yuri to recognize how much effort we put into this!
How do we do that?
Well, we just gotta beat the stuffing out of the Desert Apostles and make ourselves look really cool!
Come get some, Desert Apostles!
Don't tempt fate!
Ow...
Achoo!
I guess someone's talking about us.
Hmph!
It has to be my fans revering my beauty.
What are you talking about?
This sneezing was caused by manly spirits
crying out in admiration of my magnificence!
It was because of me!
It was me!
No, it was me!
Hmph!
I'm not gonna sink to your level.
After all, if someone's calling for us, it'd be rude to keep them waiting!
What's the matter, Tsubomi?
Yuri...
Come in.
Oh, Tsubomi. What's the matter?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Grandma, you used to fight the Desert Apostles as Cure Flower, didn't you?
Yes.
Why exactly have the Desert Apostles appeared again?
The fact is, throughout history this world has been attacked by the Desert Apostles many times.
And every time, a Precure has arisen to defend it.
I was chosen as a Precure when I was researching the Great Heart Tree,
and I was somehow able to drive the Desert Apostles away.
Then time passed, and the next Precure who
would defend the Great Heart Tree was chosen.
That was... Cure Moonlight.
She was truly powerful.
I was certain we'd be able to defeat the Desert Apostles for good.
But then...
Cure Moonlight was...
Yuri was defeated by Dark Precure.
When I was Cure Flower, they didn't
have such might amongst their ranks.
A Dark Precure created for the purpose of defeating Precure...
And the one who created her, Sabark.
We have to defeat them, no matter what.
Grandma, Yuri told Erika and me that she doesn't recognize us as Precure.
I see...
Will she recognize us if we become stronger?
Perhaps so.
If you became stronger as Precure,
then Yuri might have to eat her words.
But is becoming stronger really what's important here?
You should think about what's really important to you.
What's really important to us...
All right!
Harano Confectionery
You're really gonna do it, Tsubomi?
I promised him I would!
I've gotta give him Grandma's verdict.
You're just gonna hurt his feelings.
Yeah, I know...
But he won't understand unless you tell him.
You're right!
Good afternoon!
I'm terribly sorry, but my brother's kind of busy at the moment.
This is no good. Start over!
Why?
Why, Dad?!
Just tell me what's wrong with them already!
I cooked the beans just as long and I put in exactly the same amount of sugar!
I did everything the same way you did!
It should taste exactly the same!
Even with the same ingredients, changes in weather, temperature, and humidity
can all make slight changes in the flavor.
If you'd just told me that beforehand, I could've done a better job.
An artisan learns from experience, not by being told everything!
B-Bro!
Leave him, Chizuko.
We'll go after him!
Let's go, Tsubomi!
Fishie-wishies!
I worked so hard to get my old man and gramps to recognize me...
I've found a sad little man!
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Spa! Tula! Spa! Tula!
Th-That's...
Spatula!
Take a look in the crystal!
Masahiro Flower of the Heart is the one that was stolen!
No way!
Erika, let's go!
Let's do it!
Go, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Noooooooo!
Spatulalala!
Sasorina!
We're gonna take back the Flower of Masahiro's Heart!
Just 'cause you've gotten stronger lately doesn't mean you can be so cocky!
Go get 'em, Snackies!
Marine Dynamite!
Tch.
Desertrian, smash them!
What's wrong with them?!
Stop playing with your food!
Now just hold on a sec!
Spatula!
That's it! Go wild! Let the petals from the Flower of your Heart fall away!
I have to become a worthy third in line!
Why can't my old man and gramps just recognize how hard I'm trying!
You're looking at this all wrong!
What's really important isn't to be recognized by others!
Spatula!
Masahiro!
Isn't the most important thing to a confectioner like you to make delicious sweets that make people happy?!
Spatula?
What's the matter, Desertrian?!
Take revenge on those who don't recognize your talent!
We'll give this our all, no matter what!
Yes!
With hard work!
And guts!
With courage!
And friendship!
Sometimes, people may never recognize just how hard you're trying, which can be disheartening.
But that effort will never, ever be in vain!
Because it will serve as the foundation for your unlimited potential!
That's chilling!
Stop spouting such chilling nonsense!
If our blazing hearts aren't reaching you, then the Flower of your Heart's already withered beyond repair!
Precure exist to protect the Flowers of people's Hearts!
We'll take back the Flower of Masahiro's Heart!
Well, you're right about one thing! My heart is pitch black!
Now get them, Desertrian!
Spaaatulaaaaaaa!
What?!
Yuri!
Spatula!
I can't hold out for long with
only half a Seed of the Precure.
Cure Moonlight, a loser Precure like you won't be able to do anything!
And yet, Sasorina...
you're going to lose to that very Precure!
Seed of the Precure!
Yuri!
Are you all right?!
What are you doing?!
Keep your mind on the task at hand!
Get up already, you big lump, or I'm gonna end up as the loser!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
I won't forget this!
Yuri!
Thank you so much!
Thanks to you, we got the Flower of his Heart back!
I didn't do anything.
Now, hurry and return that Flower to its owner.
All right!
Bro!
Thank goodness you're safe.
Yeah.
Dad, Gramps...
I was wrong.
Confections have to be made to
please the people who eat them.
That's right, kiddo!
The only reason we can work as hard as we do is the knowledge that we put smiles on our customers' faces.
If you can do that, then people will always appreciate what you do.
Right!
All right then!
Let's make some daifuku and put smiles on peoples' faces!
Yeah!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
In the language of flowers, an azalea means "passion."
I can't wait to try Masahiro's Harano daifuku!
Nor can I!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
Tsubomi, another legendary person has appeared!
What, they're not a Precure?
No, the boss of a gang!
A gang boss?!
If you two team up with him...
...something amazing will happen!
With one sharp look from him...
...a storm brews across the school!
He's the real thing, make no mistake!
HeartCatch Precure:
Legend of the Strongest Boss!
It's a Pleasure Meeting You!!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!