All right, everybody!
Kaleido Star is going to start!
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well. Rosetta here!
Did everyone watch my trapeze act?
I was so happy to perform
with Sora, the person I admire.
I'm going to do intense training
like Sora did, and become even better!
I'm giving the trapeze another
try during my next circus tour,
but I've met a certain person there.
That person is...
Okay, let's make a great show
together again today! Let's! Let's!
Tattoo Kiss, the beginning
is red and black passions
Sometimes, we rely on our contrary hearts
Tattoo Kiss, the last resort is a
mission which changes the future
There is no place for
ambiguous answers in love
Even while pretending not to
see the impossible reality, we bet
Hard-to-obtain-truth
Can you feel me now?
What should I say to myself,
who gets excited easily?
I'm confused about what to say
Dreamin' the never-waking
dream, the falling fate
Don't stop lovin' can't stop lovin' you
Ya ya ya
I believe in you, even
if I lose everything for it
Still lovin' can't stop lovin' you
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Um...
Okay, that's how it is.
I've gotten the Boss' approval too.
Wait...
I've got to meet my mom,
so I'm going on ahead.
Oh...
That's right, that's right...
These are eight plane tickets. Here.
Thanks. Uh, so...
There's information about
the place we're going, too.
Okay. So...
Okay then, see you in France!
Uh, yeah...
France...
France?!
"Leon's Amazing Past."
I see.
So she had her mother,
Miss Anne, manage it all.
Mr. Kenneth's show really lit a fire.
Apparently the condition is that she has to
do diabolo in the show Miss Anne has planned.
Ah, so that's why she left a week early.
Well, the clown team never
even dreamed of having this chance.
Isn't this great, Ken?
This time I'm only along as your manager!
We haven't been to France
since the Circus Festival, huh?
This time we have to make it
a France full of smiles, don't we?
Yep!
Yeah!
Excuse me...
A smile?
How long are you people
going to stand around chatting?
Let's get going already!
But her words are still sharp...
The taxi stand is this way. Don't dawdle.
Let's go, everyone.
Okay...
I figured it out at that show.
As Sora performs, she watches the audience.
I was always just watching Sora or Leon.
What Sora has that I was missing
is the power to please the audience.
The power to create smiles.
In order to develop that power,
I have to first get back my own real smile.
That's what Miss Layla was trying to teach me.
Um... Um... Um...
Um, cirque, um, noir, um...
Oui, mademoiselle.
Oh, great! He seems to understand!
We'll have to split up into two taxis, won't we?
Um, cirque, um, noir, um...
Come on now, wake up!
Don't be taking a nap
when you've got customers!
Oui! Oui oui oui, mademoiselle!
Welcome to Noir Circus, Rosetta!
The others should arrive soon too.
Can I wait here until then?
But of course!
By the way...
Could you do just a little diabolo performance
for us in the show that starts tomorrow?
That would entail a separate fee.
You were able to contract
former top star Sora Naegino
and Circus Festival winner
May Wong at this price
on the condition that you cast me
as a trapeze artist, isn't that right?
Okay, I get it, I get it!
Pretend we never had this conversation.
I'm inexperienced, but I'll do my best
not to disappoint you or the audience.
I've got high hopes for you.
That's our star, René.
Wow, that was a beautiful move.
Looks like you're in top form today, René.
I'm the same as always.
Hey.
Alain...
You again?
Don't get so angry. I'll leave soon.
I've asked you not to come here.
That's cold, with the
relationship you and I have.
I'm not your pupil anymore.
You see, I've sort of run out of cash...
You'll just buy alcohol
with whatever I give you.
You understand well, don't you?
Come on, please.
For goodness's sake...
Thanks. I'll be by to pay you back, I promise.
You don't need to repay me!
Just never show your face in front of me again.
You're so generous. So long.
That bastard...
Who is that?
Alain Rubel. He used to be a
famous trainer of trapeze artists.
Trapeze artists?
Alain was what you'd call a freelance trainer.
He'd scout kids who seemed like
they had a future ahead of them,
and then bring them up to
be first-class trapeze artists.
René there was one of his students.
Actually his skill as a
trainer was world-renowned,
but he quit doing that several years back,
and you've seen what he's become.
A trainer with world-renowned skill...
Huh? Hey, Rosetta!
Wait!
I'm Rosetta, from Kaleido Stage.
Teach me the trapeze!
I want to be able to do it right away!
Wait!
You're the Kaleido people? You're late!
But doesn't the show start tomorrow?
What are you talking about?
We're starting rehearsal right away!
Okay!
You can follow me,
but it won't do you any good.
I'll never give up until
you teach me the trapeze.
This place... It's a circus rehearsal space?
Right now it's only a roomful of junk, though.
Can I get on the trapeze?
You're pretty bad.
Kaleido Stage is slipping,
if they let an amateur like you in.
Don't make fun of the Kaleido Stage.
I'm doing the trapeze because I want to!
Even though you have such talent...
You're an interesting girl.
What is this?!
Sora!
Nobody told us about this!
What are you talking about?
This is our main attraction!
You're joking!
3, 2, 1!
You're kidding me!
Wait a second, what's with this?!
Stop it!
This is the best!
So... This is the Noir Circus, right?
This is the Etoile Circus.
Sorry we're late!
We're the Kaleido Planets,
the group scheduled to perform today!
Excuse me!
I thought I was going to die...
Oh, but it was interesting! It had thrill.
Welcome to Noir Circus!
We've been waiting for you!
We're sorry we're late! We're the
touring team from Kaleido Stage.
Is Rosetta here yet?
Yes, if you're looking for her
I think she might be at Alain's place.
Alain?
What's the matter? Going to quit already?
I won't quit. Sora never complained
about Leon's special training.
What?
So I'll also...
Leon? You mean Leon Oswald?
Yes, that's right.
How do you know him?
He's with the Kaleido Stage right now.
Do you know Leon?
I certainly do.
He was my last pupil.
Bonjour!
Excuse me, is there anyone here?
Sora!
Rosetta?
Sora...
Mr. Leon learned here?
Yes.
It's almost ten years ago now since
Leon and his little sister Sophie were here.
Little sister...
Their parents died when they were very
young and they were taken in by relatives,
but apparently they weren't
on good terms with them.
When I said I'd like to take them in,
their adoptive parents agreed right away.
They were brilliant students.
They mastered the basics
of the trapeze in no time.
Leon! Throw Sophie up in the air!
No good! Do it over again from the beginning!
Leon...
Did Sophie have enough
ability to be Leon's partner?
Yes. Or rather,
Leon didn't have what it
took to be Sophie's partner.
So she was more amazing than Leon?
I can't imagine it.
Sophie might have been able to really do it.
A perfect Angel's Maneuver...
The Angel's Maneuver?
Yes. It was my dream.
I thought that in order to make
the Angel's Maneuver a success
it was important for the
woman's partner to become strong,
so I set about training Leon thoroughly.
Sheesh.
Here, I'll pick them up for you.
What's with this ball?
Is it leaded?
But no matter how much I trained Leon,
the Angel's Maneuver just wouldn't gel.
That was when I started to think that
maybe it was impossible for Leon after all.
Sophie!
Leon!
Sophie jacked herself up, as
if she were as light as a feather.
When I saw that, I finally understood.
The Angel's Maneuver didn't just
require the partner to be strong;
it also required a
performer with an innate instinct
that sensed the flow of that
strength during performance.
Then if she could just
perfectly maintain the pose,
I was sure we could really
produce the Angel's Maneuver.
So after that, I trained
Sophie very harshly too.
Sophie! Are you okay?!
Get off the stage!
I'm sorry.
Give us our money back!
Sophie's been training
hard and she's exhausted!
She can't help it!
Is that our problem?
You're here to entertain us!
You're being impertinent!
My, now we can't pay them their fee.
Stop the special training.
What did you say?
Sophie can't withstand this.
It's okay, Leon.
Sophie! But you...
Say, do you know about "true stars"?
"True stars"?
The circus troupe we were
working with before told me.
They said the performance of a true star
brings everybody's hearts together as one.
I have a feeling that the Angel's Maneuver
could be a maneuver to become a true star.
Leon, I want to try doing it.
I want to perfect the Angel's Maneuver,
and try to become a true star.
The people who see it, the audience and the
other performers, all their hearts will be one.
Even if they're not related by
blood, they'll be just like family...
The Angel's Maneuver is a
maneuver to become a true star...
At the time I thought
she was talking crazy talk,
but somewhere along the
way even I started thinking
that I wanted to bring
a true star into the world.
"Only a demon can raise an angel."
I remembered hearing that saying
from a circus troupe I was in long ago.
As we aimed seriously to
perfect the Angel's Maneuver
the special training became
more and more merciless.
That special training...
It's the same as the special
training I did before the Festival.
Sophie...
Do you think you can do a
perfect Angel's Maneuver like that?!
No, sir...
You say you're going to leave?
There's nothing more for us to learn from you.
What?!
I'll perfect the Angel's Maneuver,
and make Sophie a true star.
You're just a stepping stone on the way to that.
Do you think you can do it?
Do you think you can become a real demon?!
When some years had passed and
I heard a rumor that Sophie was dead,
my dream was over.
To think Leon had that kind of past...
I thought Leon's special training
was just him trying to break Sora...
But it did have a point after all.
The Angel's Maneuver is connected
to the path to becoming a true star...
No, this "true star" thing is a fantasy.
It's impossible to become a star without
being hated or begrudged by anybody.
Even if you have completely
perfected the Angel's Maneuver.
That's not so. I think
true stars can really exist.
Miss Sophie's belief that
beyond the Angel's Maneuver
lies the path to being a true star...
I believe that too.
Please teach me to do
a perfect Angel's Maneuver.
I don't believe in such a thing now.
I'd just drag you down.
If we'd met at least three years ago...
Rosetta, will you keep practicing?
Yes, of course!
All right, that's the end of
boring stories about the past.
Sora's eyes are burning more
than I've ever seen them burn before...
I've finally found the path to
becoming a true Kaleido Star.
I'll walk this path!
No matter how much time it takes,
I'll become a true Kaleido Star!
Do it like you've become a part of the trapeze!
Don't go against the flow!
Watch where the bars will be
three seconds into the future!
How many times do I have to
tell you before you understand?!
The bars three seconds into the future...
I did it!
Don't relax your efforts now!
We're going on to the next stage.
Hey, pretty good.
She came this far in just one day?
Cater!
Pill-ill-ill-illar!
Huh?
Any villain who tries to kill
the princess will have to fight me!
Interesting!
But why am I the villain?!
Amazing!
Scary!
Weird!
Evil queen, say your prayers!
I'll turn the tables on you!
Her move is on a larger scale
than it was in the rehearsal.
Sora's movements are
getting more and more lively.
The last show was like that too,
but this isn't just making the audience smile.
As another performer,
I'm getting excited too somehow.
This is Sora's true power...
Southern Cross Illusion!
Gigashock Explosion!
Infinity Tornado!
Fanatic Firestorm!
Four Thousand Legend Cosmic Dream Spin!
She's pretty into it
Super Beauty Hurricane!
for someone who didn't want to do it...
Galactica Unbelievable Splash Thunder!
That girl's performance is
drawing out other people's charm.
If you don't let me defeat
you soon, we'll run out of time...
I don't want to, but fine, I will!
Okay, then...
Was that in the script?
I think she's having fun, in her own May way...
I won't forget what you've done to me!
On the next one, Rosetta.
Right.
Good!
Wow!
She did it blindfolded!
That's just like you, Sora.
You've bounced back from your depression
after the Festival as if it was nothing.
I'm sure that's...
Hello.
Say, that player named Sora
Naegino is pretty good, isn't she?
Judging by your physique,
you're a trapeze artist too, aren't you?
She certainly does have a strange charm.
She might just make that
"true star" thing a reality.
You think so too?
I've seen you somewhere before...
Oh! You're Yuri Killian!
Yes.
Is the Kaleido Stage plotting something?
Something big?
Well now, who knows.
I've decided on the path
that I'm aiming to walk.
I'm going to master the Angel's Maneuver.
Someday, I'll do it for sure!
All kinds of hard luck flocks
your way as if it's spurring you on
Swept away by it, time is over
Just as predicted, take it easy
I will get you out right away
Hurry up (Here we go)
Forcibly only (Drive with the fastest speed)
The view I look down at every day is the best
Sunset point (Favorite)
Harbor light (Stormy night)
Escape for the sake of tomorrow
Even I don't have a vacation, I've got an oasis
I'll turn off the cell phone and charge my love
Because some pain,
you can't soothe with just kindness
We are alone, we pass each other by
What's going on?
At the far end of regret,
I encounter my true heart
Whether I'm crying or
laughing, I will be with you
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
I thought I'd give you a
chance to take your revenge.
And so, the Kaleido Stage is reopening!
But...
The truth about what happened between Leon
and Yuri three years ago will finally be revealed.
The cruel demon who slashed
an angel's innocence to pieces.
Both of you, stop it!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"The Amazing Fated Duel."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...