Rio-senpai!
Thank you. How did it go?
I found them easily.
You can find anything if you look for it.
It's warm!
Like coming back to life...
By the way, wasn't it Rio-senpai's turn to manage the garden today?
I had something to burn.
It's been half a year since Kanata arrived at the fortress...
Her skills have improved a lot.
The teacher is good after all.
Hot!
In the end, we don't even need earplugs anymore.
Wouldn't it be better for you to stay in the city during winter, Madam?
I'm fine.
I will not die so easily...
I've been living here on the mountain alone for 50 years already.
Departure
Time of First Snow
Down. Down. Down. Stop!
It finally looks like it should.
Can you finish the rest on your own, Noël?
It's my pleasure.
Let's have a cup of tea then.
Hey, Kureha-chan.
Huh?
Eh?
Where is it?
It should be here...
Oh, what's the matter?
The military chronicle should be here, right?
Kanata said that she wants to know more about Princess Iliya.
I'm sorry, if it's not there, I have no idea either.
Oh...
Oh!
Naomi-san may have one.
I'll ask her later on.
Princess Iliya is the elder daughter of the present King Arkadia.
I should have told you before that she's a famous tanker.
Klaus-san said something last time, if she was still alive...
She died around 2 years ago.
During a war?
Nope.
The Princess had been allocated to Team Guardian...
But she was also responsible for publicising the National Prestige and had to travel all around the Republic.
When she was on her way to a certain city, she died while trying to rescue a kid who'd fallen into a river.
But, I felt a bit relieved...
Though this is only a rumour...
Iliya...
Kanata-san!
Yumina-san and... Well...?
Excuse me, it's Kanata.
Yumina-san ... err... has come with Yuuko-chan...
Yuuko-chan is the daughter of Martin-san and...
Actually, a lady named Jakotto...
Jakotto-san is living on the mountain alone...
I bought some vegetables from her as well, at the market...
Oh! You said that the pickled food was nice, didn't you?
That was made from Jakotto-san's vegetables.
But Jakotto-san disappeared recently...
They're worried since her health is not that good...
They said that she's living in a remote area in the mountains...
And also...
That's enough! I've got it!
I'll help them. Just give me a minute.
Yes Ma'am!
Princess Iliya...
To improve the relationship between the two countries, she married the Emperor of Traditional Rome.
But she would've been the third Queen!
The third! The third Queen!
That's ridiculous!
She seemed like nothing but a hostage.
After she died, the marriage was cancelled.
And war went on until the beginning of this year.
Oh cool... We've finally arrived.
A house under construction...?
Isn't she living alone?
She should be...
Madam!
I see. So Yuuko went to you?
Yes.
She's really a nice girl.
Martin should be proud of her.
This is a really nice house.
Thank you.
I built this house myself.
That's amazing! Eh...?
What about the one over there?
That's for my son.
You have a son?
Yes. He's in a city far away from here.
I am preparing the house so he can have a place to live once he's back...
So he can live comfortably with that person.
I have to finish building the house.
When will your son come back, Madam?
He will come back soon.
Winter will come even sooner!
You'd better leave the mountain before the snow.
That's not possible.
Because... I have to finish building that house.
I won't leave this place before I die!
But...
This is no joking matter!
How are you going to prepare for the winter?
The firewood?  How about food?
You have not prepared yet, have you?
There will be a way out.
I'm glad that you're worrying about me, girls.
Madam...
What a stubborn old lady.
You two are really alike.
Give me a break.
Why should I be doing this...
Because you're not honest enough with yourself.
That's enough.
Hey... Why did you show me the letter?
It's also mentioned in the regular liaison...
That the Roman Army in the Eastern area is moving...
Oh really? For Jakotto-obaasan?
Right. Please take these with you too.
Thank you very much!
By the way...
Do you know how the peace conference is going?
I... I'm sorry.
It would be great if Princess Iliya was still alive...
By the way... Martin, I heard that Princess Iliya had a younger sister...
Your change, 4 million.
I haven't heard about that.
They say that she's an illegitimate child of the King and thus her existence was not publicised...
And that she is of the third heirship.
Excuse me. The younger sister you just mentioned...
Oh. See you.
See you.
Thank you very much.
Would you like to take a walk?
Hey, Kanata...
What does the village you were born in look like?
It's a normal village.
There are farms. There are a lot of cows and lambs.
But there aren't very many people.
It's different from this place.
But it's a nice place, right?
Your parents are nice too, right?
I can tell from you.
What does the place where Senpai grew up look like?
I grew up in a place not too far from the capital.
There are beautiful forests and lakes.
It's a small village.
I lived with my mother in such a place.
The days were simple and boring. Nothing surprising ever happened.
The only pleasure was the visit of my older step-sister.
She came to play with me sometimes.
I wanted to be just like her.
She was prestigious and gentle.
And she was easygoing about her fate.
She was the one who taught me the trumpet.
But she was too gentle...
Her gentleness got her killed.
When I first arrived at the city, I thought it was a labyrinth.
I lost my way, and finally, I came here.
I thought that I reached the goal line.
But, I soon realised that this was just an impasse.
That's not true.
I always get lost.
But... I love to be lost.
Getting lost is nothing bad! Even if it is an impasse!
I met you because of this, Senpai!
Sometimes, I'm really envious of you, Kanata.
If I could be as honest as you...
It should be fine now.
Why are you worrying about a person like me?
Because you resemble my mother.
But I don't remember having a daughter as pretty as you.
I was born from a forbidden love.
She had been waiting,
waiting for a man who might not even come once a year.
And she died in this misfortune and misery.
How do you know she was miserable?
That's because...
I am happy.
Because that person promised to come back one day.
He promised that he would come and take me with him.
That's enough for me.
But...
What else is there for me to do?
That's right.
If there were anything else, I might have done it already.
However...
Are you satisfied with this?
Are you happy with this?
I still remember that I love him.
The memory of him is still in my heart. And so is the hope that we will see each other again one day.
That's enough for me...
That's enough...
Just when I thought it was getting cold...
It was snowing as well, when I first met you.
When Madam was young, Seize was a nice place to rest.
She fell in love with the honorable son of a merchant.
Soon, she was pregnant with his child. However...
That young master was already married.
As luck would have it though, his wife was sterile.
And the young master went back to his hometown with her child.
And promised to take her with him one day.
Madam!
When you get to my age, it's common to think that...  If, at that time...
Jakotto-san!
Life... is to lose repeatedly.
But you have to gain something to lose it.
However, the more happiness you have gained, the more terrible it is to lose.
But, with the memory of happiness...
As long as the memories are with us... We can keep living...
By the way... This may not be a good time, but...
I've found it. The photo of Princess Iliya.
Naomi-san!
Felicia... It's fine...
It was around 5 years ago.
It was taken when the Princess came to Seize.
This is... Shuko?!
Rio-senpai!
I think that my parents actually wanted me to get married...
And inherit the family property.
But... I was fascinated by the sound of the trumpet.
And I could never forget it.
That was Iliya-san, wasn't it?
So you did meet her.
It was really nice...
Iliya-san's music rings in me.
And then, we met each other.
Perhaps, I used this city as an escape.
That's why, in the beginning, I didn't care about anything.
I knew that I would leave one day.
But now, I truly want to stay here.
In the same sense, I must go.
I should be able to do it, and there are things only I can do.
I am not going to say goodbye.
No matter how far apart we are.
The music will ring out...
And... reach... one's heart...
Kanata... Was I a good senpai to you?
Yes!
And so, Rio-senpai left us...
And left that amazingly beautiful sound of the skies ringing in my heart.
A Visitor - A Burning Field of Snow
Next Time :
A Visitor
A Burning Field of Snow