(breathes heavily)
(intense music)
KISAKI: How's it feel to be entrusted
with the fate of Toman?
- Don't worry.
-(Takemichi gasping)
You'll be joining him soon enough.
(whimpering)
(grumbles)
What the hell is wrong with you?
(Takemichi gasps)
Is that all you've got?
KISAKI: How disappointing.
(grunting)
So long...
my hero.
(clanks)
MAN: What the hell?
-(thumping)
-(man grunting)
(body thuds)
(Takemichi gasps)
(soft gasp)
(gasps)
(panting)
TAKEMICHI: Where am I?
(grunting)
Shit!
TAKEMICHI: That's right!
Kisaki shot me in the leg.
Wait...
But after that, someone...
KAZUTORA: I gave you first aid.
What?
(dramatic music)
(wind blowing)
(gasps)
TAKEMICHI: Baji?
TOKYO REVENGERS
(gasps)
TAKEMICHI: No.
Kazutora...
(earring clinking)
TAKEMICHI: Oh, right.
It's been 12 years, so he's out of prison.
(grunting)
It's been a while...
(groans)
Kazutora...
(grunting)
-(thumping)
-(Takemichi groans)
(Takemichi grunting)
(grunting stops)
The other day,
some guys were beating the crap
out of a chick like this in the street.
(breathes heavily)
When I jumped in to break it up,
they said they were members of Toman.
When did your Toman
turn into a gang that beats on women?
I don't give a shit about you.
It was...
Chifuyu I wanted to save.
(soft gasp)
(car approaching)
-(car horn honks)
-(soft gasp)
It's you...
It's been a while, Kazutora.
- Need a ride?
-(gasps)
(car engine revs)
CHIFUYU: Toman has gone to the dogs.
They're a criminal gang with zero ethics,
and the cops can't touch them.
I want us to turn Toman back
into what it used to be.
He'd been fighting all alone
this whole time.
But you...
What the hell were you doing?
(gasps)
TAKEMICHI: I get it now.
In this timeline,
I ended up so rotten,
Chifuyu couldn't rely on me.
KAZUTORA:
Toman got so big, it lost its way.
Still, you guys were the first
to serve as Kisaki's lackeys.
(sighs)
Draken, our only hope,
ended up on death row.
And nobody knows where Mikey is now.
So, Takemichi,
where is Toman headed?
Remember how Mikey once said
he'd build a new era for hoodlums?
Just like he said, Toman has gotten huge.
Drug dealing, prostitution,
illegal casinos, loansharking, murder.
Toman does every kind of crime
and has grown huge doing it.
But... But...
Is this the era that
Mikey wanted to build?
Is this the Toman that
Baji wanted to protect?
(gasps)
So, I'm going to build
a new era for hoodlums.
I want a gang
where each of us is
willing to risk our lives
for each other.
KAZUTORA: Back then, this wasn't the kind
of Toman they wanted to build.
Isn't that right, Takemichi?
TAKEMICHI: He's right!
It's not!
The Toman I loved wasn't like this!
It was always something to be proud of!
Yes.
KAZUTORA: Let's take back our Toman.
-(Takemichi groans)
-(car door closes)
Kazutora, I...
I don't really remember things well,
so I might ask some weird questions.
How did Toman end up like this?
(soft grunt)
Well, I mean...
I'm still kind of in shock,
so my head is pretty fuzzy.
- It was Mikey.
- What?
Mikey changed completely.
Toman changed because Mikey changed.
It can't be!
Someone else must be behind it!
Isn't Kisaki pulling
the strings or something?
A month ago, Mitsuya went missing.
Oh?
Mikey sent for him,
but he hasn't been seen since then.
What?
(cell phone ringing)
Hello?
I see.
While Kisaki had you tied up last night,
- Pah-chin and Peh-yan were murdered.
-(gasps)
(foreboding music)
This means Mikey has started
purging the old Toman members.
-(breathes shakily)
- He doesn't trust his old friends anymore.
It can't be...
How could Mikey do that to everyone?
It's all being done at Mikey's command.
Kisaki is just carrying out the orders.
Mikey has gone truly evil.
As one of the people who changed him,
I want to talk to him.
He needs to get away from them!
"Them"?
KAZUTORA: The violence of Kisaki
and the money of BLACK DRAGON.
Unless something is done about them,
- Mikey will never return to normal.
-(soft gasp)
He's not a hoodlum anymore.
(beeps)
Help me out, Takemichi.
It's my turn to help Mikey now.
I want to save Manjiro Sano.
(soft grunt)
The remnants of the old biker gang,
BLACK DRAGON,
joined up with Toman and
became Mikey's heavy hitters.
Those guys will do anything for money.
Well...
Wasn't BLACK DRAGON
the reason why Toman was formed?
That's right.
I had connections with
BLACK DRAGON in the past.
But they're definitely
not like they used to be.
The mounds of cash they can produce are
one of the things that corrupted Mikey.
I used my connections
to find their hidden bank account.
I plan to solve this
by stopping the flow of that money.
And the one who was going
to handle Kisaki, Mikey's right-hand man,
was Chifuyu.
KAZUTORA: Chifuyu was killed because
he'd backed Kisaki into a corner.
Really?
That's why I went to that
building to rescue Chifuyu.
How did Chifuyu...
How did he have Kisaki cornered?
One day, a police detective approached us.
What?
KAZUTORA: He's the brother of a woman
Kisaki had murdered.
(gasps)
I want revenge.
TAKEMICHI: That's Naoto!
Wait! You mean you and Chifuyu
helped that detective?
Yeah.
We looked into the murder
of Hinata Tachibana.
We figured out who gave the orders.
Atsushi Sendo, a Toman member,
rammed a car into a microcar
driven by a school teacher.
They caught fire and blew up.
They both died in that accident.
You remember it, right?
TAKEMICHI: It's seared into my memory!
KAZUTORA: Kisaki gave the order.
But he has an alibi.
He was meeting with you guys
in the top brass that day.
What?
TAKEMICHI: He was meeting with us?
That must mean in this timeline
when Hinata and Akkun died,
I wasn't even there.
But Chifuyu had proof...
that it was Kisaki who gave the order.
Proof?
We had Kisaki cornered
and were on the verge of getting him.
But it's Chifuyu's fault
for letting him slip through our fingers.
-(brake squeals)
- What?
Get out, Takemichi.
KAZUTORA: There's a guy in that alley
I want you to see.
TAKEMICHI: Me?
(Takemichi grunts)
(grunts)
TAKEMICHI: He wants me to see someone?
Who could it be?
(gasps)
TAKEMICHI: Naoto!
I've found him at last!
I've been waiting for you,
Takemichi.
Naoto...
(handcuffs rattle)
TAKEMICHI: What?
Takemichi Hanagaki,
I'm placing you under arrest
for instigating murder!
What?
NAOTO: I'm sorry, Hanemiya.
(grunts)
You bastard!
I'm under arrest... for murder?
Too bad, Takemichi.
Naoto...
Why?
Watch this.
TAKEMICHI: That's Chifuyu.
What's this a video of?
(door opens in video)
-(door closes in video)
- CHIFUYU: Good afternoon.
HAKKAI: You too.
It's sure as hell hot.
(exhales deeply)
Go on, sit down.
I didn't want
to have to call you about this,
but it was ordered.
We got no choice.
Is that... me?
NAOTO:
Chifuyu Matsuno secretly taped this.
(grunts)
I don't know how to explain this.
But in any case,
as always, the moment
you returned to the present,
my timeline changed in an instant.
The changes you made in the past
made big changes in the present.
I'm still a cop, just as before.
But you don't work
at a rental shop this time.
You're a bigwig in Toman.
Yet, just like before,
on August 10th,
my sister was killed in her car
by Atsushi Sendo.
Then, I teamed up
with Kazutora Hanemiya and Chifuyu Matsuno
to arrest Kisaki for my sister's death.
(Takemichi breathes heavily)
I'm sorry, Takemichi.
You must be in shock.
Considering my position,
I had no choice but to arrest you.
Watch the rest of the video.
- Okay...
-(clicks)
There's only one reason I call you here.
I want you to kill someone.
MAN: Who?
I don't know who it is.
I couldn't care less either!
What's important is that
they're a nuisance to Toman!
It's not like I want to make you do this.
If it's not done,
Kisaki will be on my ass.
Got it, Atsushi?
(gasps)
Atsushi?
That's Akkun!
AKKUN: Who am I supposed to kill?
TAKEMICHI (in video):
I told you! I don't know!
Someone will contact
you with the details later.
We'll get you everything
you need to do it.
- AKKUN: Actually...
- TAKEMICHI (in video): What's it?
AKKUN: I haven't heard from my wife
since last night.
TAKEMICHI (in video): What?
AKKUN: Come on, Takemichi!
Talk to the bosses for me!
My wife is pregnant with our second...
TAKEMICHI: Shut up!
It's your duty as a plebe
to do what you're told, goddamn it!
I ordered Akkun...
to kill someone?
Here is another video.
Chifuyu Matsuno secretly taped this too.
Watch it carefully.
-(yelling in video)
-(gasps)
(yells)
CHIFUYU: Cut it out, Takemichi!
TAKEMICHI: Fuck off!
CHIFUYU:
Destroying the furniture won't help!
Goddamn it! I was set up!
That Kisaki is the devil!
I didn't know he was supposed to kill her!
(Takemichi sobs)
Naoto, that's enough.
(Takemichi grunts in video)
We were after evidence proving
Kisaki's involvement in Hinata's murder.
These videos are proof.
I told you, that's enough!
Chifuyu Matsuno had been
hiding these videos from me.
(gasping)
He was protecting you.
(breathes heavily)
(ominous music)
(gasping)
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
TAKEMICHI: This time, it's me.
I'm the one...
who killed...
Hina.
(exhale deeply)
NAOTO: Isn't that right?
Takemichi.
You were used. That's all.
TAKEMICHI: I've had it.
I can't do this.
How many times had this been?
But nothing has changed.
In fact, it has gotten even worse.
I killed...
Hina.
And Akkun and Chifuyu
and all those guys died too!
(both grunt)
And there's nothing
I can do for Baji either!
I can only go back to today 12 years ago!
There's no way I can save him!
Screaming and crying won't help!
(breathes heavily)
This is just as rough on me.
No, it's not!
I murdered your sister!
Let's just give up, Naoto!
I can't change anything!
You saved me!
NAOTO: What you've done has helped!
In the first timeline,
neither Toman nor Ken Ryuguji existed.
There was no Chifuyu Matsuno,
no Kazutora Hanemiya,
and no Keisuke Baji either.
None of them still existed, Takemichi.
NAOTO: Without their influence,
we would never have
gotten this far into Toman.
The one who kept their influence alive
was you!
(sobs)
You're the only one
who can change Toman
and who can save Hinata!
Please, transform this hellish world,
Takemichi!
Naoto,
the last time I traveled back in time,
I became the captain of
Toman's First Division.
I was a step closer to
becoming the leader of Toman.
So, I thought things would
be better in the present.
But Hina was still killed.
And what's worse,
it was me who killed her.
This is just conjecture,
but do you think Kisaki
had you kill my sister on purpose?
What?
NAOTO: Don't you think it's odd?
No matter how many times you go back,
Kisaki always ends up
having my sister killed.
(gasps)
Could it be a coincidence?
No.
It has happened too often
to be a coincidence.
It never fails.
You mean...
Tetta Kisaki clearly...
has some obsession with you and my sister.
TAKEMICHI: What?
...my hero.
(gasps)
-(knocks on door)
-(grunts)
I want us to plan things out,
but there's no time.
You'll be sent
to the detection center now.
The detention center?
It'll be difficult for us
to meet like this anymore.
Now is your only chance to go back.
(knocking continues)
What? But...
(sighs)
All right.
Whatever happened between you
and Tetta Kisaki in the past
must be the key to the mystery
behind my sister's death.
Right.
(dramatic music playing)
(electricity crackles)
(gasps)
TAKEMICHI: Thank you, Chifuyu...
and Kazutora.
Thanks to you two,
I know who the enemy is.
The ex-BLACK DRAGON members
and Tetta Kisaki.
That's what corrupted Mikey.
I'll drive them out of Toman
to save Hina
and save everyone!
(thuds)
What?
Another strike!
What? Bowling?
You're amazing, Takemichi!
That's a turkey!
Yeah...
(light music)
I'm just awful at this.
TAKEMICHI: After seeing just how
horrible the present is,
Hina's smile makes me want to...
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
HINA: Go!
TAKEMICHI: She's so cute!
Darn it! Another gutter ball!
TAKEMICHI: Come to think of it.
I was really into bowling at this time.
I had my own bowling glove
and shoes, and even my own ball.
I was really serious about it.
Okay! I'm still just as sharp as then!
It's your turn, Takemichi!
(grunts)
TAKEMICHI, HINATA
BOWLER:TAKEMICHI
Watch this, Hina.
This will be my fourth!
I'll get four strikes in a row!
What?
Oh, wow!
TAKEMICHI:
The next lane gets a strike too?
HAKKAI: We both got strikes.
(gasps)
(upbeat music)
We were perfectly in sync.
(gasps)
(closing theme music playing)