It's summer...
I wanna die.
You sure are gloomy, Toru!
Seaside Resorts
It's summer, so we should go
to the beach! Right?
I don't want to show this scrawny body in public.
Oh, come on! You worry too much.
Everyone has their unique qualities.
You just have to use yours!
Run-chan...
For the fetishists out there.
That I didn't need!
Cloudy and ephemeral
Becoming one with the glittering, faraway sky
My wind-reading, willful destination is far away
Let's go together
I'll inhale deeply and go, the world's spring breath
The smiling faces of everyone gathered in the sun
In between "Good morning" and
"Goodbye," there is only us
We can do anything, can't we?
Transparent beams of sunlight, a newborn sky
A morning arch at which we promised to meet
To you, waving your hand, I'll give a special today
And the talking will begin
Ta-daa!
I bought a swimsuit just for you, Toru!
I chose the smallest size they had.
Now we can go to the beach!
Here.
It's sure to look great. C'mon, try it on!
Yeah.
It's perfect!
But it's a little... loose.
Hey, everyone! I got us some ice cream. Um...
Huh?
Toru, it's ice cream!
I-I-I can't eat a-a-anything now.
Say, what's wrong with Toru?
Well, she's sort of...
Oh! This is the flavor that
came out this year, right?
I've been wanting to try this.
Me too, so that's why I got it.
What a coincidence.
We should split it.
Yeah!
Actually, I CAN eat!
Wh...
Why're you naked?
Toru Nagi
A-CHANNEL
Yuko
Run
THE BEACH
PE
Math I
Jpn Eng I PE
POOL!
It's the pool!
You sure changed fast!
Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool!
You're a high-schooler now, but you still like
getting worked up over the pool, don't you?
Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool! Pool!
What are you saying?
Summer is all about the pool!
You haven't forgotten this is CLASS, have you?
A pool's a pool!
Huh?
Toru, your swimsuit is a different color here.
Is this a hand-me-down?
This is...
I've been using it since elementary school.
Ow!
Hey! That's dangerous!
Floating sure feels good.
Yutaka, your breasts are so big...
Oh, you think?
It must be nice to have all that fat
to help you float easily.
Someone's got claws. You jealous?
N-not at all!
Zero fat!
It's so hot!
PE in summer sure is tough.
The first-years have pool, huh?
Ah! That's Toru!
You're right. That pool looks cool...
Okay, gather 'round.
Must be nice.
I'm jealous.
What gives, Nagi? Don't you hate pools?
I DO hate pools. Rather,
I don't like wearing swimsuits.
But!
Toru!
Splash water on me!
Grab a bucket and douse me!
The heat's done Nagi in!
Quit it, Nagi!
Let go! Let go!
Toru! Water! Water!
Aah, whatever.
Huh? The beach?
Yeah! Summer vacation
starts next week, so let's all go!
Agreed!
Huh?
I don't have a swimsuit I can wear to the beach.
I don't want to wear a swimsuit.
What're the two of you sayin'?
That can't be right!
Wh-what?
Did you hear that? "Because I have a nice body!"
"Because I have fair skin!"
What're you sayin'?
That's not it at all!
Oh, such modesty.
Come on!
I wanna go to the beach, all of us!
Thank you very much.
All this walking around has made me hot!
Sorry for makin' you come along.
No, I bought one, too.
Wanna rest somewhere?
Huh? Nagi?
What's wrong? You feelin' bad?
The cold air collects here. It's cool!
I'm resting HERE.
Hey! Nagi, stand up! Please!
That girl just now is big, huh?
More than 170 cm, right?
Sure enough, people think of me
as a big woman...
They're jealous. Yuko, you're tall,
slender and big-breasted.
The breasts make it worse.
Just being like THIS is bad enough.
Really? Oh.
Lingerie
These are good bras, huh?
They're cheap, so maybe I'll get one.
You're right. I'd like one, too.
What's the matter?
Lingerie
They only go up to a D cup.
Limited stock
Sizes B - D only
They only go up to a D cup.
Sure enough, smaller ones are more convenient.
Let's hurry up and go.
Say, let's take a look.
What the heck? We already decided we're not
going to the beach, right?!
Where's the harm? They're cute.
I'm not buying anything.
Hiii!
Nagi!
How 'bout this?
Yeah, it's good.
Really? I'm gonna try these on, so let me know.
Okay.
How is it?
Perfect.
Really? Okay...
And this one?
It's just right.
Okay...
How 'bout THIS one?
Spot on.
Aah, I can't choose! I'm gonna try another one.
Give me a minute, okay?
Yeah.
Okay!
Nagi, sorry for the wait. Huh?
No! I'm just, that is!
I just wanted to look.
I'll try some on.
I bought one...
So what? It looks great on you!
Thank you.
Oh!
A text?
Yup, to Run and Toru. "Let's go to the beach!"
Looking forward to it, huh?
Two kilograms to go...
Impossible, huh?
Run said "Okay"!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Run-chan came over a little while ago.
Did she already leave?
Yes. She said she came to drop something off.
This is an old swimsuit of mine.
I think it'll be perfect for you!
I'll race you to that island, Toru.
Play hard and study hard.
I look forward to seeing you all again,
reenergized for the new semester.
Summer
vacation!!
Wait!
The beach! The beach! The beach! The beach!
The beach! The beach! The beach!
You a kid?
The beach!
The beach.
Pretty, isn't it?
It's running along the street.
They have streetcars here, huh?
You're right.
Amazing, right? It runs on the street!
I wonder when they traded them out!
What's that?
Well, the tires!
There ARE no tires.
Gimme
Sunlight
We're here!
The beach!
Well, let's swim!
The beach sure makes me excited!
Me, too!
Run-chan.
Thank you for lending me your swimsuit.
Sure. I'm glad it was the right size.
Sorry it's kind of a kiddy design.
No.
After all...
I've had that since elementary school!
Hey! What are you doing? Come on, hurry!
Okay!
Elementary school...
Hyaa!
Now you've done it!
Jeez, that tickles!
Oh, you're so tall! So tall!
Note: A game played with (little) children
What are you doing?!
It's fun, huh, Toru?
Put me down!
Toru? Nagi?!
Ow...
What's with that hair?!
What?
Seaweed.
Looks good on ya, Nagi!
It looks good!
Seaweed...
I need a timeout.
What gives, Nagi? You tired already?
I was up at 5:00 this morning.
I'm about out of energy.
I'm doin' fine.
I'm kinda frail.
Well, let's take a break. I'll go get some drinks.
Oh. I'll take a melon soda, please.
Roger!
Sports drink for me...
Beach House - Enojima Center
Okay!
Sure enough.
She's pretty tired.
Cola Grape Melon Yakisoba Takoyaki
Welcome!
Whoa...
Beach House - Enojima Center
They have a lot, don't they?
What should we get?
Oh. Run-chan. That.
Cola Ramune Sweet Citrus Shaved
Sugar Soft Ice
Candy Serve
Soda
Wow, I never thought we'd encounter the elusive
sugar candy soda at a place like this!
Yeah.
Nagi-chan, we got some.
Oh.
Huh?
Yuko's asleep.
You're right.
Jeez. She only just said "I'm doin' fine,"
but the second she sat down, she was out!
Looks like a good sleep.
Oh!
Mmm, this feels great!
It's quiet and there aren't many people around.
The southern islands are the best!
Huh? What?
Leaves?
What the heck, Toru? That tickles!
Y-you're heavy!
Agh! You're heavy!
A dream?
I was asleep?
A sandcastle?!
Nooo!
Don't move. It's almost finished.
Hurry and get this offa me!
Hyaa!
Attack!
Here!
Sorry.
No worries!
What's the matter?
It's like I'm being pulled. It's fun!
Is that really fun?
Huh? Nagi?
M-me, too!
Lunch time!
At the beach, it's gotta be ramen, huh?
Yakisoba.
Latin-inspired taco rice.
I packed a boxed lunch.
It's the same as always, huh?
Really?
Not to worry! Leave it to me!
What're you gonna do?
It's the beach, after all. The beach!
Fish!
Donna keshiki kitai shiteru?
What kind of scenery are you hoping for?
Hora, miete kita, suiheisen
Look, the horizon has come into view
Atsui suna ni kokoro haneru
our hearts skip from the hot sand
Mabataki no tabi utsuru taiyo
The sun projects with each blink
Hashagikirenai kimochi kakureta mitai
It looks like a feeling of unending merriment was hidden
Miseta koto no nai jibun, hashiridasu yo
A side of me I've never shown will race outward
Mune ni blue sky, nami o kakete
A blue sky in our hearts, chase the waves
Hajikeru feeling
A feeling that bursts forth
Yukou, sisters, mizugi no ato
Let's go, sisters, swimsuit tan lines
There are a lot less people now, huh?
Yukou, sisters, mizugi no ato
Let's go, sisters, swimsuit tan lines
Well, it's nighttime now.
I feel like we've had a LOT of fun.
Yukou, sisters, mizugi no ato
Let's go, sisters, swimsuit tan lines
Well, it's nighttime now.
I feel like we've had a LOT of fun.
Kokoro tsunagu
our hearts bound
Well, it's nighttime now.
I feel like we've had a LOT of fun.
Takusan no kirameki de
By so many sparkles
It's a good thing we came so early this morning.
Takusan no kirameki de
By so many sparkles
Right?
Takusan no kirameki de
By so many sparkles
The beach was a lot of fun, huh?
Takusan no kirameki de
By so many sparkles
The beach was a lot of fun, huh?
Niji o egakou
Let's paint a rainbow
Yeah.
Niji o egakou
Let's paint a rainbow
I guess...
It was fun.
Let's all come again, okay?
Yeah.
Yuko, hurry!
H-hang on!
Faster, faster!
We made it.
It's empty, huh?
Yuko, you're not gonna sit?
Uh, no, I'm fine here.
We've got a long way to go.
Nah, I've got lots of energy.
You all right, Yuko?
Yeah, looks like it.
Your cuticles!
Are your cuticles all right, Yuko-chan?
She can't SEE them, can she?
I think they're okay.
You gotta be careful, because
your hair is long and pretty.
And your skin is alabaster.
Uh, thank you.
Oh. I wonder if I got a little darker...
No, not to worry. You put sun block on, right?
Oh. What about you, Run?
She didn't get dark at all.
Run, what did you use for sun block?
I didn't use any.
You didn't use sun block?
What's up with this skin?
I don't believe it.
That tickles!
I don't get darker 'cuz of my genetics!
Really?
What are you, an alien?
No, I'm not!
Run is an Earthling.
Really?
Really!
Silhouettes, taller than us,
line against the madder tree
The end to an enjoyable day
There's lots, lots of this long story left
But it's about time I have to get home
Okay, see you tomorrow
I'll e-mail you
On today's page, everyone had matching smiles
Okay, see you tomorrow
Thanks for everything
I'm glad we could be together again today
La-la-laa, humming to our hearts and the wind
At the next corner, a bye-bye
while looking over our shoulders
yup!
What is it about swimming
that makes you so tired?
Especially at noon after swim class, right?
That's how the fear begins, isn't it?
Saved
Meaning?
If you sleep at noon, you won't
be able to sleep at night,
but if you don't sleep at night,
you'll get sleepy at noon...
Oh, that totally happens!
Next time, on A-Channel:
"...at Night in the Middle of Summer"
Next
Episode!
Next time, on A-Channel:
"...at Night in the Middle of Summer"
Next
Episode!
When that happens, you can break the cycle
by sleeping from noon to the next morning.
How many hours do you sleep?!