More!
Comin' right up!
Hey!
Wait a minute!
Why're you eating breakfast
at my place now!?
And, hell...
Why are you acting like
it's perfectly normal!?
Who cares?
Taiga-chan's tiny, so she isn't
taking up much space.
Besides...
Meals taste better when
people eat together.
Gimme my rice already.
What!?
I cooked more than enough for three!
Just how much do you eat!?
S-Sowwy.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Taiga and Ryuji
Jeez...
Are you trying to make your own
pet go bald from stress?
Don't let it get any uglier.
Don't call her ugly!
They do say that pets can start
to resemble their owner...
Dammit...
You ungrateful brat!
I made you breakfast and
packed you a lunch!
Shut up, mongrel.
Mon—
There you go again!
Return the lunch!
I take back all the kindness
I've extended you!
Shut up.
And rot in hell.
Hey!
- Wait up, Aisaka!
- Ever since that midnight encounter,
Aisaka Taiga has been showing
up for meals at our home.
I said to wait up!
And...
Listen up.
Once we get to school,
you better do a good job.
Helping me to, you know...
get closer to Kitamura-kun...
Don't forget your promise
to obey me like a dog!
This is where we are now.
If it doesn't go well...
Minorin!
You're late, Taiga!
But wow, as energetic as ever, I see!
Morning, Minorin!
Huh? No way! What!?
S-Sorry!
I had no idea!
Taiga and Takasu-kun are chummy
enough to walk to school together!
No!
Nobody says "chummy" anymore.
That's not the point!
Oh, right.
Then, I guess...
These days, people say...
I'm so befuddled that I dunno
what the trendy way to say it is!
Now I remember! Lovey-dovey!
Still not the point!
Aisaka and I just happened
to run into each other.
Right, Aisa—
Oh, it was just a coincidence.
He lives near me, I guess.
- Ooh...
- U-Uh...
Okey-dokey. See you later, Takasu-kun!
So, I was watching TV last night...
I get it now.
If I want a chance with Kushieda,
I have to help Aisaka with Kitamura first.
Bring it on!
Okay!
Enough stretching!
Next, you should pair up
and practice passing—
Hey, Aisaka! Let's team up!
Sure! Let's do it, Takasu-kun!
Right!
—the basketball.
Oh? Nice to see you both so
pumped up, Takasu and Aisaka.
- Taiga?
- Sports are a big part of your youth!
- The plan is simple.
- And sports require muscles!
I'll clip Kitamura's partner with the ball.
And then...
You overreact and take his
partner to the nurse's office.
Leaving you and Kitamura paired up.
Maruo!
- Pair up with me!
- Stop the finger to pair with Haruta!
- Sure, fine by me.
But stop calling me that.
You look just like him, though!
Huh?
Whoa, what!?
Kitamura-kun's with some weird girl!
What's going on!?
R-Right in my gut...
Kushieda!
Wanna partner up?
Okay! Sure!
Kushieda too!
Whatever. We stick to the plan.
Huh? But that's...
Don't be sexist.
And the two bulges in
my upper arms are...
Oh? What's wrong, Haruta?
Don't use my thumbs as I...
pass!
Not even close, Kushieda.
The road to mastering the Satoru Ball
is long and treacherous, indeed.
What...?
Oh, don't mind me.
Those who'd get it will get it.
Damn Noto...
Pass!
C'mon, c'mon!
Pass the ball!
Incoming, Maruo!
Gotcha.
Wow, nice one.
What was that, Maruo?
- Hey, pass!
- You serious?
- But I can't hit a girl...
- Here it comes!
Pass!
Sorry, Kihara...
I'll make it up to you!
Cleft in twain...!
Oops! Sorry about that, Maruo.
Hey, what happened?
Takasu-kun took out
the Palm-top Tiger!
C-Crap.
Home Economics Room
The Palm-top Tiger will
bite anything in her way.
Even so, no one can deny she
works so hard it makes her look silly,
leaving you inclined
to silently root for her.
Listen up.
When you hand this over,
you've gotta act natural.
Don't tense up like that.
G-Gotcha...
Take it easy...
Yep, be bold, casual, relaxed...
Let's go.
Huh? Where's Kitamura?
Oh, Kitamura said he had business
to take care of in building B...
Ta-Takasu-kun!
He just left, so he should still be nearby!
There he is!
After him!
R-Right!
What!?
Outta the way!
It's Takasu!
She's fast!
I guess she should be able
to catch up, then...
Ryuji!
The cookies...
Ouch...
Great, now there's a bump on my head.
Hey, you find the cookies?
They survive?
I...I see...
Hey.
Am I actually a big klutz?
She had no idea?
I write a love letter, but put
it in the wrong bag...
I attack you, but collapse from hunger...
I play basketball, but get hit in the face...
I try to give him cookies, but trip
over myself and drop them...
Hey, you missed a few things!
Like when you forgot to put
the letter in the envelope.
Oh, right...
Uh...
Give me one of those.
But, wait...
They're crushed.
Besides, um...
Delicious!
They came out fine.
It's too bad.
We'll try harder next time.
I definitely saw them.
They were buying stuff, like onions and
radishes, at the market like a married couple!
Witness #1 Class 2-C
H***ta K*ji
I saw them walking out of an apartment
building together this morning.
Witness #2 Class 2-C
K*hara M*ya
I smell teen promiscuity.
And they were eating homemade
cookies together!
Witness #3 Class 2-C
N*to H***mitsu
Like, practically feeding each other!
What? Really, really? No way!
Witness #4 Class 2-C
K*shii N*nako
Hey, Minori.
What's going on with your buddy?
What's going on?
Hey.
Go in already.
Squeal.
Squeal?
Do you have a minute?
Sweet bird of youth...
What's up with Kushieda-san?
No clue.
Takasu-kun.
Yes!
Er, me?
Please take good care of Taiga!
Taiga is a very dear friend!
Please make her oh-so-very happy!
W-Wait, Kushieda!
You're not saying that...
Happy?
So that's what's going on.
Congratulations, you two.
Kitamura!?
Why are you up there!?
I did notice the two of you spending
a lot of time together.
But now that I think about it,
you make a perfect couple.
Aisaka!
Get a grip!
Hey! Stop laughing!
Takasu-kun.
If you make Taiga cry,
I'll never forgive you.
Kushieda...
I'm sorry...
Minorin got the wrong idea because I
kept inviting myself over to your place.
No, that's not...
I just felt...
so at home at your place.
I don't get along with my
parents all that well.
When I told them that
I wanted to move out,
they set me up in that apartment.
I knew my parents would act like that.
Those cookies were salty, weren't they?
I stared at the crumbs, and they
were annoying me, so...
I tried some.
And man, were they gross!
But you finished them all.
And you even lied.
A mongrel doesn't need to worry
about others. You'll go bald.
Mind your own business.
So...does thinking of Minorin ever
make you incredibly anxious?
Yeah, of course.
Of course, huh...?
Aisaka?
Why don't they understand?
We're nervous wrecks here,
and they don't have a clue.
Honestly, they're...
They're all...
They're all, they're all...!
Pissing me off!
Pissing me off! Pissing me off!
Screw the Palm-top Tiger crap!
I'm not okay with it!
Stupid Minorin!
Stupid Kitamura-kun!
Why won't you listen to me!?
Not Mom, not Dad, not anyone!
Nobody understands me...
Let me in on this.
What's wrong with being small!?
I'm not a delinquent!
What's wrong with having a weird name!?
Don't blame me for my scary eyes!
Screw you all!
Hey, you okay?
Ryuji, isn't this thing tilted now?
Huh? That's impossi—
It's tilted!?
Right!?
Yes!
We win, we win!
Okay, I've made up my mind.
Tomorrow, I'm going to tell
Kitamura-kun how I feel.
And that will be the end of this.
The end?
No more serving me like a dog.
Starting tomorrow, we'll be classmates
who happen to be neighbors.
And nothing more.
Bye-bye, Takasu-kun.
A—
Bye...
Ryu-chan...
Isn't there something funny about breakfast?
I mean, I like canned mackerel, but...
Is Taiga-chan still asleep?
Beats me.
Did you two have a fight?
No.
It's kinda boring...
Right?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Y-Yo.
This is...
Ta-Takasu...
Uh...
Sorry about spreading
those weird rumors...
Aisaka-san chewed us out.
"There's nothing between Ryuji and me."
"Ryuji isn't a delinquent."
She was livid.
That Palm-top Tiger's freaking terrifying.
But didn't I already tell you that there's
nothing scary about Takasu?
You did!? When?
Anyway, we'll be in trouble
if we don't clean up.
Kushieda.
Takasu-kun...
I'm sorry.
A-About what?
Taiga told me.
"I would never go out with Takasu-kun."
"It's all a misunderstanding."
She really wanted to make
that clear to me.
She had this earnest, almost frantic,
look on her face.
But that's...
That's...
Hey, Takasu-kun?
- Takasu-kun?
- Man...
What are you doing?
You said you'd confess to Kitamura today.
It's no time to worry about others.
Starting tomorrow, we'll be classmates
who happen to be neighbors.
And nothing more.
And nothing more, huh...?
Kitamura-kun!
I'm...
Well, I'm in...
Um, well...
Seriously?
First thing in the morning?
If he turns you down, the rest of
the day'll be incredibly awkward...
Hold on.
I think I know where this is going.
Let me ask you something first.
Aren't you going out with Takasu?
That was just Minorin's mistake.
There's nothing between
Takasu-kun and me.
Don't you like him?
Of course not!
We just happen to live near each other.
There's nothing romantic between us.
Then, you dislike him?
I...
I don't not like him...
But it's not like that.
You see, Takasu-kun is, well...
Oh! Fried rice!
Ryuji made this awesome fried rice for me!
He cheered me up...
He even lied to make me feel better...
He was there for me...
And it's because of Ryuji...
Because Ryuji was there...
That I...
That I have the courage to
stand here and say...
that I like you, Kitamura-kun!
Aisaka...
You're really something.
I see.
Don't worry.
I'm pretty sure I understand how you feel.
Kitamura-kun...
Do you remember what happened
a year ago, Aisaka?
Yeah...
Compared to back then...
you have a more fun look on your face.
M-More fun...?
Yeah.
Whenever you're with Takasu, you get
the most fun look on your face.
Takasu's a great guy.
And...
I find you to be a wonderful girl...
for thinking of him the way
you did a moment ago.
A moment ago...?
Wait! What did I say!?
In any case, I'm relieved to hear that
you and Takasu are getting along.
H-Hold on!
Ryuji has nothing to do with this...
And, um, a fun look on my face?
Wait, that's not important right now.
So you're relieved? But why?
Huh? No way. What am I saying?
Wasn't I able to say that I like you?
It's okay, Aisaka.
It's okay.
Wh-Wh-What's okay!?
I don't know what I said!
It's okay.
I'm sure we'll become very good friends.
I said I like you, not that I want to be...
Friends?
Yes.
Friends.
Oh.
We're going to be late for homeroom.
You should hurry, Aisaka.
I expected you to cry.
Y-You!
Wh-Why!?
W-W-Were you watching!?
Not intentionally.
What does that even mean!?
Anyway, what now?
I'm going home.
Okay.
Then I'll make you something to eat.
Since you probably haven't had breakfast.
Did you even eat anything last night?
Probably something from the
convenience store ag—
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
People will get the wrong idea again!
You don't have to do
anything for me anymore!
I can't explain it...
But...
I can't just leave you all alone!
I said to stop!
You're not my dog anymore!
Yeah...
You're right. I'm not a dog.
I'm a dragon.
That's why I can stand by your side, Ai—
Taiga!
Wh-Why Taiga...?
Since ancient times, only dragons stand
on equal ground with tigers.
So, I'll become a dragon.
And then...
I'll stick by your side.
You've got some nerve.
Know your place!
Hey now...
Hey!
Move it. I'm hungry.
And we'll need to concoct our next strategy.
What happened today won't make
me give up on Kitamura-kun.
Meaning...?
I don't care whether
you're a dragon or a dog.
You said you'd stick by me, so you'd
better work your ass off, Ryuji.
Maybe I spoke too soon...
Hurry it up, would ya!?
Yeah, yeah.
He called me Taiga...
Add vanilla salt.
banira sorutode
Burning love.
BURNING LOVE
If it's too sweet,
amai dakenara
we can add some salt.
soruto kakemashou
I tell you all these things because
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
This is so frustrating.
modokashi sugiru
But a love that's purely sweet
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
If you say white,
shiroto iwaretara
I say black.
kurodatte icchau
A little imp
sunaoni narenai
who can't be honest to herself.
amanojaku
If you say love,
sukito iwaretara
I say hate.
daikirai datte
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
It's like adding salt
amai banirani
to sweet vanilla...
soruto kakeru youni
Kushieda the athlete...
Kushieda the workaholic...
Oh, my dear Kushieda.
Ever brightly, you shine!
Big hit comin' up!