It's been five days since
I debuted as a professional hero.
There haven't been any serious incidents so far.
However, Genos is now staying at my house for some reason.
What are you writing over there?
I'm recording the details of your lessons and training regimen.
Crap. He's raising the bar again…
I can't think of a single thing I can teach the guy.
I feel like I'm scamming him or something.
Come on, think.
At least make up some techniques
or a spiritual theory.
Bah, strength training is all I've got!
But I know Genos won't be satisfied with that.
Plus the dude's a cyborg!
By the way,
at the seminar they said C-class heroes
who are not active for a week
will be removed from the Hero Registry.
Aren't you cutting it close, Master?
They said that?!
Yes.
But I was watching TV and
there wasn't anything going on.
The news only reports major incidents,
like natural disasters, terrorism, and dangerous monsters.
You always fight the most powerful enemies,
so this is probably new to you,
but C-class heroes primarily
take care of purse snatchers,
robberies, and random attacks.
With Class C so full of heroes,
they must actively look for cases to resolve in order to survive.
I hear many of them get discouraged
and change careers.
Like a salesman doing cold calls,
nothing will come your way without legwork.
This is no time to be reading manga!
So we're going?
You stay here!
If I'm with an S-class hero,
a C-class like me won't get any credit!
But as your disciple—
Genos, from the beginning,
my intense desire to be a hero was
what drove me to strength training.
That's how I made it this far.
Perhaps things will change for you too
if you set higher goals for yourself as a hero.
Frankly speaking, you're a cyborg,
so there's no use training your body.
Instead, a change in mindset
may lead you to greater strength.
Damn, I'm just making all this crap up.
So… in other words,
it's not about having raw power or technique.
It's about training your mind.
To do that, you must first fight your way through the professional hero industry.
Aim to break into the top ten of Class S.
That's a good place to start.
I understand. I will try!
Thank god he bought it!
After that, I sped around town,
frantically looking for bad guys.
I ran,
and ran,
and ran.
But!
There was no sign of trouble anywhere!
I give up.
Just one more day left.
Guess I'll head home.
Future Saitama can deal with tomorrow's problems.
one punch
three, two, one, kill shot
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
Are you talking to him? Frustration
nan datten da, frustration
He's not going to stop
ore wa tomaranai
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
power, get power
On to the very edge
girigiri genkai made
hero
There are voices praising him
ore o tataeru koe ya
but he's not doing this for acclaim
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
hero
So he just fight evil without end
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
hero
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
A fighting hero
tatakau hero
A lone hero
kodoku na hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
THE FOLLOWING DAY
It's all quiet today too!
There's nothing to do!
I'm gonna lose my registration!
Hey! You're that guy…
What was it again?
"Seed-on-the-Ground"?
No wait, "Lost-and-found"?
Jack-o'-lantern Panic!
It's Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
I've finally found you, Saitama.
Today is the day we—
Sorry, I'm busy. See you 'round.
Huh?
You think…
you can run from me?!
What the—?
I didn't see what happened.
His face should have been
sliced open, but the blade…
I told you, I'm busy.
Plus I'm pissed, so anyone in my way…
gets a knuckle sandwich.
That's him!
He's very, very dangerous.
Please stop him.
You're the offender, eh?!
Well, your hero the Tank-top Tiger is here now!
Hero?
Sonic, they think you're some sort of criminal.
Maybe getting tossed in a cell
will cool off your hot—
She means you, cue ball.
Huh?
He's been running around town with this scary look on his face since yesterday!
But I'm a hero too!
I've never heard of a hero like you.
So what? I just started!
In any case,
you're causing problems for everyone.
If you really are a hero,
then don't go around frightening people.
You're hurting all our reputations.
Hey isn't that the Tank-top Tiger?
Oh yeah, it is the Tank-top Tiger.
No way!
Awesome, he's the real deal!
Even Class C heroes get recognized
if they're in the top 10.
So how about it, new guy?
Wanna go a little wild here and make me look good?
Exploding Shuriken.
What the—?!
Exploding Shuriken
Tank-top Tiger?!
Is this really happening?
What are you doing, Sonic?
He was interfering, so I put him to sleep.
Hey, call a hero!
A hero!
Run!
Saitama…
So you've become one of these
worthless "heroes" too?
In that case, all I have to do is
create a situation where you have no choice
but to fight me, Saitama the Hero!
Hail of Carnage!
Huh?
Hey! Cut it out!
Saitama, come stop me!
Aren't you a hero?!
I'm gonna kill 'em all!
Dammit.
Can't everyone just let me do my job?
I don't have time for this!
I gotta find a bad guy to take down.
A bad guy?
If you're not coming, I'll come to you!
I'm right here.
I wonder if this'll count as work?
The man apprehended in Z City by the Class C hero
is suspected of being involved in several heinous crimes, including assassination.
Z City…
What's the status of the investigation I requested?
The one for the ghost town?
Yes.
Let's see…
We've submitted an official request.
Well now, doesn't that sound interesting?
Want me to go?
T-Tornado?
Where'd you come from?
Why? Aren't I allowed in here?
Of course.
But the Z City investigation is just a formality.
What?
You think I'm not good enough?
Not at all.
The Association decided that
this was not an S-class matter.
Yes, precisely.
You'd better tell me if you find
anything that looks like it can fight.
It'd be so much faster if I just went myself.
You're such an idiot.
A CITY  HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Reports have come in from
each location under investigation.
First is Watchdog Man, S-class hero,
investigating Q City.
"Nothing unusual."
Nothing unusual?
That's right.
That's hard to believe.
We all know Q City is a hot zone with more
casualties and monsters than any other area.
Knowing him, I'm sure he's implying that he'll
be able to take care of anything that happens.
Though he has focused his efforts on Q City,
his track record in monster elimination is top-notch.
S-class heroes don't pay much attention to details.
They're not cut out for writing reports.
Next, W City.
Class A hero Heavy Kong reports:
"Nothing unusual."
For H City, reports from Mushroom, Class B, and Horsebone, Class C:
For D City, Lightning Genji, Class A:
"Aside from slow restoration after the devastation caused by the gigantic creature, nothing unusual."
B and D Cities both sustained extensive damage.
The Association took a lot of heat for that.
In order to prevent future disasters such as those,
we must detect any covert activity
that could threaten the community.
Well, this investigation was
requested for that express purpose.
But early detection of monsters is proving difficult.
F City, Class A hero, "Snakebite" Snek.
"Hammerhead, former leader of the Paradiser terrorist group, has been spotted in a suit and tie."
"Further investigation is being conducted."
No other reports.
What of Z City?
I hear rumblings of a potential disaster
brewing in the abandoned district there.
No reports available.
However, two highly capable A-class heroes have been sent to the area to investigate.
Here we are in Z City.
CLASS A, RANK 33
SPRING MUSTACHIO
Shall we begin our little inquiry?
CLASS A, RANK 29
GOLDEN BALL
Yeah, let's get on with it.
Z City is quite expansive,
but further ahead lies the uninhabited district we were told about.
Compared with other areas, City Z has an
abnormally high rate of monster-related incidents.
BEWARE OF
MONSTERS!!
The frequency has been gradually increasing over the past decade,
while the last few have seen more and more
highly advanced monsters appearing.
The residents have entirely fled for the city center.
I know all that.
The place is a real ghost town,
just with the water and electricity still intact, yeah?
On the lookout for a cheap house?
Come off it.
People say something real nasty's living 'round here.
Even you would've heard 'bout it.
But of course.
I assume that's why we have been
assigned this investigation.
Once we hit the abandoned district, we better be ready to fight.
Indeed, we mustn't let our guard down.
But why here? Why the increase in monsters?
That's the mystery.
Many theories have been proposed,
but my own is this:
A colony of monsters here is naturally reproducing.
Or perhaps a queen exists, birthing more of her kind.
Of course, I have no proof yet,
but there is something to this ghost town.
Or rather, something in it.
There is no denying that.
The proximity alarm?
If we can hunt down this mysterious being,
we'll go straight to the top of the rankings.
That's true.
We can't let Mr. Handsome Mask remain first for—
Behind us?!
Was that a monster?
No way to be sure.
But it's hard to imagine a human still living in these conditions.
Let's pursue it!
Seems they are not after us.
Is this the place I heard about?
Sure don't seem like it…
Aw man, I came all this way.
Isn't anyone around?
A monster.
It popped up out of nowhere.
Golden Ball, are you ready?
Hell yes.
Victory to the swift!
Hey, people!
My golden shape-memory bullets can blast through a 20mm steel plate!
Eat this!
He flicked it away like it was nothing!
Golden Ball!
Wow!
Tomboy…
thrust!
I-It slipped past my Tomboy?!
Not bad.
Those tentacles…
Judging by the way they behave,
they're as tough as steel.
A monster that can use its infinite tentacles like steel whips…
Such power!
I must call in reinforcements from the Association.
May I ask if you were born in this neighborhood?
Nah, I'm from out of town.
I heard a bunch of crazy strong monsters were all getting together here.
Looks like it was just a rumor though.
But now,
I feel like it'd be kinda fun to stick around
and make the rumor true.
"The Ghost Town Monster"…
It's got a nice ring to it!
We have a backup request from the heroes dispatched to Z City.
Class A rank 29, Golden Ball, has been knocked out.
Class A rank 33, Spring Mustachio, is in trouble.
They're in the abandoned city.
Call in all nearby heroes for immediate assistance!
Class A and above!
See the monster alert for Z City?
The threat level seems to be Tiger or even higher.
Is it the ghost town monster?
They're not sure yet.
I'll go.
I want to catch the tiger by the tail.
Now I see…
If it meant running into monsters like this all the time
I wouldn't want to live here either.
Man, how boring.
This is so boring!
I finally kick a hero's butt and I don't even get one scream.
Now that I think about it, even if I start living here,
I'll never be famous if there's no people.
Guess I'll keep going.
Gotta find where they live.
Someone's here.
Another hero?
Or a regular guy?
I thought all the humans cleared out.
If all those monsters really were living here,
there's no way he could live here.
I guess that means it was just a rumor.
Shoot…
I forgot to buy konbu soup stock.
Master, I saw a lot of konbu right outside the door.
Oh yeah, I just…
just happened… to get it for cheap.
People do say that konbu is good for hair growth,
but since there is no real scientific proof,
its real effects are yet to be confirmed.
I did some research, so I am sure, Master.
For example, according to this site—
No one said anything about hair!
Z City Investigative Report.
"Nothing noteworthy about the downtown or residential areas.
During our investigation, we encountered a ferocious monster in the abandoned district,
but we were unable to exterminate it.
We escaped death,
but the monster we encountered disappeared and it is possible that it still roams the area.
Also, according to this monster,
there's a rumor that powerful monsters
already exist in this area."
Sounds like it was pretty brutal.
A monster?
Yes.
I think I'll pass this time.
See? I told you I should have gone!
But…
faced with this,
I'm sure even you would have had a tough time.
I would have been fine, idiot!
The rumor has not been confirmed,
but the reinforcements witnessed signs that point to the existence of some horrible monstrosity.
Holy crap, what is this?
What kind of monster could cause such destruction?
I'd hate to face off against this thing.
Hey, what's this?
Is it a part of the monster Spring Mustachio fought?
There may have been a territorial dispute between the monsters.
Seems like there's definitely something here.
We must continue our investigation and maintain vigilance over Z City.
Hey, did you hear?
There are monsters living in the Z City ghost town.
Yeah, rumor has it the toughest ones are secretly plotting something.
No, no. There's a rumor about an even more dangerous monster.
What's that?
You haven't heard?
Apparently, the place has now become
terrifying for both humans and monsters.
The Terrifying City
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
I close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you... I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope these feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you work all the time
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, but I'm still worried
tsuyokute shinpai
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before any stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come back home straight
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Master, I filled in the holes in front of the house.
Oh, thanks!
Also, you're no longer the lowest ranked hero.
You've gone up from 388th to 342nd.
Oh? Because of that Panic guy?
Guess he boosted my ranking.
So it's been a week now.
Have you done anything?
No, not yet.
I guess it's only been a week.
I'm still ranked last in Class S
for ability… 17th place.
Sounds like you've still got
a lot of training to do, Genos.
But in the public polls I rank sixth for popularity.
Why?!
"A genius who, at the tender age of 19,
made his debut in Class S."
"He'll do great."
"He's so handsome."
"Love how he refuses to do
media interviews. Very cool."
That's what the comments say.
Aren't you embarrassed to read those aloud?
These comments are based on impressions from my photo, not evaluations of me.
I think nothing of them.
Oh yeah?
They continue.
"The Cyborg Prince."
"Behind the steely exterior, I feel his fragile soul."
"Among the top five handsomest heroes."
Enough already!
Next Time
The
Ultimate
Disciple
The
Ultimate
Disciple
This is Fubuki.
Perhaps you know me better as the Blizzard from Hell?
Well, I only had a small part this episode.
Next time, on One Punch Man : Episode 7,
"The Ultimate Disciple."
The Blizzard Gang will finally make its appearance.
Miss Blizzard, we're not scheduled
to appear next week!
That can't be right!