I'll rely on numbers!
It's here!
This is the Dollars?
What is this? They can't all...
For example... marry me?
You're keeping our big secret, after all.
Celty...
It's more than I thought. It's fun.
I'm shouting!
"Here am I born!"
Give Celty back to me!
Yin and
Yang
I have to thank you.
If not for you, my sister would've locked
her up in a cramped lab again.
Yagiri-kun...
Are you OK?
Give Celty back to me.
I need to escape with her
before the cops arrive.
Does that make this OK-
What do you know?
I've watched her since
she was a little girl.
I wanted to free her...
To free her into the big wide world,
where I would live with her.
That's what I always, always, always,
always, always, always thought I would do!
Man, no one can stop the power of love.
What about you?
A moment ago and now,
you're still relying on numbers.
It will take more than
that to stop our love!
It won't work!
It hurts, but I'll forget!
There's no need for pain
in the life Celty and I will live!
So I don't feel any pain in
the pain I endure right now!
That's insane!
Stop!
Please stop it!
Seiji-san is violent and strict
and different from others,
but he's not a bad person!
And there's someone he loves!
No...
No way... No way, no way, no way.
No, that's not...
No. She's...
This isn't my head.
This girl... Her name is...
Harima Mika-san?
You're Harima Mika-san, right?
The one Yagiri-kun supposedly killed?
No way.
Hey. That isn't true, right?
I'm sorry!
Hey! You're in there,
aren't you, Seiji-san?
I'm back!
Oh, no! You forgot to leave
the door open for me.
I can't come in!
Are you asleep?
Do you remember?
I sat next to you during our exam.
The kid to my right had some weird
name like "Ryuugamine,"
so I wondered what the
guy to my left's name was,
and when I first saw you, I fell in love.
When our eyes met, you smiled at me...
So Seiji-san, show me your face!
Please, please!
Are you maybe unwell?
Is that why you can't answer the door?
Then I'll open it up for you right now!
After the day we took that exam together,
I did some investigating.
I know your birthday and your family...
S-Seiji-san?
You saw it, didn't you?
Um, well, I...
I won't tell anyone!
It's OK!
Whatever kind of thing
you're into, I'm cool with it!
Um, so...
It's OK.
Seiji-san.
Seiji-san...
It's OK.
I'm so sorry!
I wasn't dead!
And then your sister...
You want Seiji to love you?
Good girl.
And then...
And then a doctor came...
And they said that with some plastic surgery
and makeup, I could look like that head...
The one Seiji was in love with.
Your name is Celty, he said.
Because that's the head's name.
So I tried to be Celty for your sake,
but Namie-san said it wasn't good enough!
She said she'd use drugs and surgery
to erase my memory.
But I...
A doctor who knows my name
and that I'm a Dullahan.
There's only one person
like that in this town!
I wanted to be with you!
So I did my best!
That's a lie.
Then...
Well, you couldn't even tell the difference
between the real one and the fake.
I guess your love wasn't all that much.
Nice work...
Seiji-san!
Um, I think it's amazing how you
risked your life to get her back...
I was wrong about Harima-san.
She's a bit strange, but she's not a stalker.
You risked your life to save Yagiri-kun!
I don't think you could do that if you
were thinking only of yourself.
I think it's amazing how you can
like someone who nearly killed you,
In many ways, I think you're
a lot like him...
Welcome back.
What the hell were
you thinking?
And then you want to say this...
You knew, didn't you?
That my head was in that lab.
You and your dad were working with
Yagiri Pharma from the start.
Maybe your dad was the one who took
it from me in the first place!
But you hid that from me and
chopped up a dying girl's face.
I'm a monster, but you... The way you devour
people, you're the real monster, right?
Oh, just so we're on the same page here,
I don't know if my dad stole your head,
and frankly, I don't care.
And that little bit of surgery
was voluntary.
Though it's quite possible
Yagiri put her up to it...
That's not really my problem.
Do you know what I'm
thinking? Maybe?
Yes, I do.
I've loved you for twenty years.
I can tell.
But then why... Why didn't you
tell me where my head was?
Because I love you.
That's why I didn't tell you.
If you had it, you would leave me.
I couldn't handle that.
I can't give up on this just
to make you happy.
This is a battle for our love.
I'll never let you go. And I'll sacrifice other's
loves, their lives, even myself.
It sounds paradoxical,
but I'll even use your emotions.
I would never leave you,
even if I had my head.
That may be your will,
but it may not be your head's.
I've thought about it a long time.
Why does a faerie, like you,
show herself before humans?
Perhaps it's only because you've lost your
head that you can take physical form.
Then, maybe once you
had your head back,
you'd vanish into thin air,
as if this were all just a dream...
I'm scared of that.
Will you believe what I say?
I believe you.
In fact, you're the only
person I do believe.
I'm scared, too.
I'm scared of dying.
As I am right now, I know
no one can kill me.
That's not arrogance. It's a simple fact.
I take no joy or emotion from that fact.
But... No, that's why I'm scared.
There's nothing inside me
that controls my death.
My head contains it!
Someone will destroy my head.
And then I'll die, too, no matter
where I am or what I want...
Do you believe me? I don't have eyes
or a brain, but I have nightmares.
Do you believe that I have nightmares
and shudder with terror?
That's what scares me. I want to be able
to control my own death.
That's why I wanted my head.
Would you believe me?
I told you.
You're the only one I believe.
What a truly bewildering situation.
Both of us were getting upset over what
was nothing more than a hypothesis.
We're fools, aren't we?
Hey, Shinra.
What?
Let me hit you!
OK.
Then I'll hit you, too.
See? You're prettiest when you're
not hiding your face.
That punch took the place of a kiss,
to celebrate our vows.
Are you crying?
You really are an idiot.
Man, it's amazing.
Yo, Izaya.
Oh, Dotachin. 'Sup?
Don't call me that.
By that way, you know the origin
of the name "Dollars"?
It's not like, "Give me all your
dollars" or something?
It's not, actually.
They do nothing. They just do nothing,
"dara-dara," all day, so they're the "Dollars."
That's it.
Dotachin, did you see it?
The black biker was all like...
Did that really happen?
I didn't imagine it, did I?
Was it like some kind of CG or something?
That CG's part of the Dollars, too!
Wow!
Is that true?
To be honest, I'm surprised.
I knew there were quite a few people
calling themselves Dollars on the net.
But I didn't expect to see so many
show up when you called a meeting.
Humans really are beyond imagination.
But, Mikado-kun, you seem to dream
of an escape from the "everyday,"
but life in Tokyo will be everyday
in about six months or so.
And so, if you want something different,
you'll have to go somewhere else or
seek something more underground.
But once you're on the other side,
three days of that and
it's the new normal.
If you really want to escape the everyday,
you must constantly evolve.
Whether you're aiming higher or lower...
Enjoy your everyday.
But as a token of my respect,
I won't charge you for Namie
Yagiri's phone number,
and I won't sell the information that
you're the founder of the Dollars.
It's your organization.
When you want to use it, do so.
Izaya!
Looks like it's time to go.
Good luck, Tanaka Tarou-kun!
Damn you, wait!
Izaya!
Wait. No way...
The next day, our lives returned to normal
so quickly that it was amazing.
For him.
And him.
And the boy...
Hey, Mikado.
I heard there was a meeting
of the Dollars yesterday!
Supposedly, Simon and Shizuo
were part of it, too!
And the rider on the black
bike had no head!
And it was riding down walls,
flinging around this big scythe,
and it was all like bwah!
I heard it was amazing!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
And for them, as well.
I don't like you.
But as long as I look at you,
I'll never forget my love for her.
So I will accept your love,
until someday, I get her back.
Tanaka Tarou-san joined
<Tanaka Tarou>
Hello.
Hi.
<Setton>
We've been on standby.
Thanks.
I'm tired today, so I'll be leaving early.
Not enough sleep?
You stay up all night?
Yeah, kinda.
Kanra-san isn't here yet.
I wonder if Kanra-san will come...
Looks like I've gotta take
care of something.
I see.
Sorry, I've gotta run.
See ya.
Sorry to spoil your fun.
Got a job for you.
It's fine.
And my daily life came back, too.
Running into people I'd rather not see,
like always...
Looks like you're over it.
Spooks are scary 'cause of how they
lay low, then jump out at you.
After that entrance,
you won't scare anyone.
Thinking back, you didn't
kill anyone, did you?
What's with that scythe?
It can't cut anyone?
Are you after that woman?
If you ever need me, I'll help you out.
Gimme a call.
See you.
I don't know where Yagiri Namie is.
But I don't care.
I'm me.
That's enough.
My days were always the same,
no real big hopes or fears.
Nothing changing.
But how full they seemed!
I'm here.
You're there.
If I am your salvation,
then you are mine.
And the young boy thought of what
Orihara Izaya had told him.
As he longed for the impossible,
the extraordinary,
would he be able to seek
the new for an eternity?
And would that eternity
then become everyday?
Sorry for everything.
Thanks.
Hey! That's my seat!
The spot behind the class rep is open.
What's with you?
You can't just show up and...
Certainly, she won't spend her days
with Harima Mika anymore.
Only she knows if that's good or bad.
But is that really the case?
In the end, people never
understand their hearts.
They must continue to evolve,
just like he had said.
After he'd done something so bold,
he thought he could do anything.
But the young boy hadn't had any idea
that asking a classmate out would
require so much courage.
It would be 30 seconds
before he found her.
It would be 35 seconds before
he found his friend hitting on her.
It would be 40 seconds before
he drop-kicked his friend.
It would be 74 seconds before she
refused his offer to get some drinks.
It would be 78 seconds before she invited him
to have lunch with her on the roof.
And how long before he
fell in love with her?
How long before he confessed to her?
You were a fool, though.
You threw it all away for your
brother's insane love.
As long as you stay in contact with them,
you two will never be alone.
Be careful. You're still being chased.
Where are you now?
Or should I say, your insane
love for your brother?
So yeah, isn't that a problem?
You're merging with Nebra.
Bring something like this to light,
and maybe the mafia, maybe
some crazy-skilled sniper,
or someone will put a bullet
right between your eyes... Pow!
Cleaners?
Yes. That's the same squad
they always use.
Got it.
Hello?
Things are getting kinda bad.
Would you please leave that room now?
I wonder if they won't ever make a rule where
two "king" shogi pieces take each other out.
I think your uncle is just like me.
He denied the afterlife
more than anyone,
feared death more than anyone,
and longed for heaven more than anyone.
But you know,
I'm certain.
The afterlife exists.
We'll leave it at that.
It's said that there are only
female Dullahans.
You know why?
No...
Some of my men researched the myths,
but I thought it futile.
You're quite the rationalist, of course.
There's a heaven called Valhalla.
Well, maybe "heaven" isn't the exact word for it...
In Northern European myths, there's a legend
about armored female angels, Valkyries,
who take the souls of courageous
warriors to Valhalla.
A woman who comes to the dead...
Sound like anything you've heard?
There's a theory that Dullahans are these
Valkyries, wandering the Earth.
Which, I'm sure, means it's waiting.
Waiting to awaken.
Waiting for war.
Waiting to find a holy warrior
it can take to Valhalla...
The reason it's alive, but its eyes are closed,
is that we aren't on a battlefield.
I wish I could be chosen
as one of those warriors...
If there's a Valhalla awaiting
me after death,
what should I do?
I don't expect I'd be capable
of any battlefield heroics.
Then, I'll have to cause a war
that only I can cause.
Right?
How lucky I am!
I, who don't believe in any heaven...
I, who have lived life far from its glory...
To think that it would bring me to an
angel of death, fallen to Earth.
No way... That's just your theory!
Whosoever believeth... You know?
And it's insurance, is what I'm saying.
Even if it's hell,
even if there's nothing but pain...
If I exist there, it's fine with me.
But you know, I'd prefer heaven...
Hey, Namie-san! Let's all go to heaven!
As a member of the Dollars,
I'm taking this.
No one will think to look for it there.
Celty will never expect that it's in the hands
of the organization she belongs to.
Hey, I know!
You should join them, too.
Our boss takes anyone he can find.
Of course,
I was partially the one who
started gathering people.
Let's let the fallen angel fly again...
Why don't we?
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
Takes a
Sudden Turn
Her everyday...
Nothing happens...
Nothing changes...
Even though, in the town, things are born every day
and vanish every day.
Next time:
Takes a Sudden Turn.