I'm convinced that this development is a sign that Biribiri will become the heroine!
You're...
Help me!
What do you want from that "head" that's living as a human, as a whole entity?
I want to see her!
I believe it's from Yagiri Pharmaceuticals.
It's okay. Leave everything to me.
To be honest, I wasn't really sure...
I've gathered all the pieces.
I have to go.
I have to get her back.
My sister can't do it.
It has to be me...
It has to be me.
She wasn't there?
No.
According to the subcontractors, she was already gone by the time they arrived.
The student who's living there...
Ryuugamine, was it?
What about him?
They were going to question him when he returned,
and depending on the situation, bring him here,
but he had other people with him.
Why didn't they drag him here with his friends?
They're useless!
What should we do now?
Hello?
Are you Yagiri Namie-san?
Who are you?
I am Ryuugamine Mikado.
Would you like to make a deal?
I'm starving.
My~
Welcome! Welcome!
Russia Sushi is yummy!
It's cheap!
"What is life?"
"Why do people live?"
Someone pestered me with those questions, and I beat the crap out of him.
Right.
I would've let it slide if it was some poetry-spouting brat still in school,
but a yakuza past his twenties asked me that. It's got to be a crime!
Right.
Hey Simon-san, you don't understand a thing I'm saying, do you?
Righto!
Have I changed...
in the past twenty years I've been in this city?
It wasn't for nothing!
Those twenty years you spent here weren't for nothing!
Nothing is pointless as long as you keep going.
"Keep going"?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
For example...
Marrying me.
Shinra...
Are you Mikado-kun?
You're more timid than I imagined.
Or are kids like you even more dangerous?
So...
what was the deal you wanted to make?
I know where to find the person you're looking for.
Really?
How much do you want?
No.
I don't want any money.
Then what?
The truth.
What did you say?
I want you to acknowledge what your brother did to Harima Mika-san,
and what you did to Mika-san's body.
Unfortunately, I have only circumstantial evidence.
I'll cut to the chase:
turn yourself in.
Oh, I see.
So you're that kind of person.
I won't allow you to get in my brother's way.
That just won't happen.
No one is allowed to get in his way!
Aha... So she's that kind of a person.
Tell me.
Where's my sister?
I have to go.
That girl needs me.
I have to be by her side!
Hey!
Tell me!
That's the reason?
People died for that?
They even messed with her body.
And went as far as trying to kill me.
You killed people because of that?
Will you destroy Yagiri-kun's happiness just to satisfy your ego?
What did you just say?
You're too young to venture into this twisted world.
I'll be fine.
Keep your damn mouth shut,
if you're just going to get on your soapbox.
Yes, maybe I'm just being idealistic,
but so what?
You're the one who doesn't even understand the obvious:
that you should think about what you've done when you've killed someone!
Kid, you watch too much TV.
You're just babbling on about ideals and pre-established harmonies.
Wake up, boy. This is reality.
I hope this works out.
This isn't a movie.
You're not some kind of hero.
Know your place!
What's wrong with that?!
I love pre-established harmonies, ideals,
rules, and even forced happy endings!
What's wrong with desiring them?!
I'm not claiming that it's for the good of others or the world.
I just want to see it for myself.
I want to believe in that!
Yes... I will believe in that.
I will believe!
They all will...
I might be beating a dead horse,
but that proves that people care about it!
Are you done?
I don't have the power and wisdom to make someone as ignorant as you to see reason.
You won't even give me a chance to prove myself.
That's why...
I'll rely on others!
What?!
Whoa!
Is all that because of the cellphones?!
Awesome!
This is like the supernatural phenomenon from "Missing"!
Young master, you've got mail.
Do you want to try dying once?
There it is!
Are you serious?
Well then...
Togusa, take care of the rest.
Okay.
Let's go.
How many people are there?!
Man, I never would've imagined that so many people would come to the first meeting.
So this is...
the Dollars?
Hey, Isaac!
Yeah, Miria?
Are they members of the Dollars too?
Precisely, Miria!
All right, listen up.
Now we're part of the group the kids talk about!
What the hell?!
Don't tell me they're all...
No way! You've got to be kidding me!
And! We just met for the first time like, today!
Wowzers!
Wowzers! Wowzers!
The sky in my hometown was vast.
However, there was nothing.
When I was a kid, this town was full of adventures.
I wonder when I started feeling like this.
I wanted to change something.
But I didn't have a reason or the courage.
It was around that time...
Uh... Double-click...
With a few clicks, a whole new realm opened its gates to me.
An arcane realm that I had been unaware of was within my reach.
I got back in touch with Kida-kun, who had moved to Tokyo.
I even made some new friends.
One night, I had an idea.
It started off as a joke though.
A gang?
Yes.
I hear that Tokyo has lots of gangs.
You're going to create an Internet gang?
No, no. I'll make people think it really exists.
Uh, I'll say they're based in Ikebukuro,
and spread that rumor on the Net.
We won't say we're in the Dollars.
We'll just start rumors and pretend we heard them from someone else,
and spread the name of the Dollars that way.
I even made a webpage for it,
and protected it with a password.
I leaked the password through email and BBSes.
I also pretended to be a member and made fake posts on BBSes.
Of course, most people didn't believe it.
Soon, there were people supporting us.
Everyone was having fun.
But I had a bad feeling.
People who called themselves "Dollars" started appearing.
That wasn't all.
Before I knew it, there were a lot of new members.
Even though we stopped giving the password out,
it seemed like someone on the inside was leaking it.
Guys, can you see this?
Hello?
Maybe they got scared.
The people I created the Dollars with disappeared.
Even so, I didn't stop.
No, I couldn't stop.
I don't really know why.
That's not true!
There might be some bad people,
but they're not all jerks.
Why don't we turn it into a group of decent people?
Like doing good deeds to outweigh the bad things.
Like picking up trash,
or erasing graffiti.
The people were astonished.
This graffiti was definitely there last night,
but now, it's completely gone.
It's impossible to remove graffiti as large as this on your own.
Of course not...
I came to Tokyo after Kida-kun invited me.
And there...
Dollars?
I don't know the details either,
but they have a lot of members scattered everywhere.
I heard they're one of the color gangs, but no one knows their color.
You know the deal with curiosity and the cat.
You shouldn't dig deeper.
But the Dollars are the strongest in the city, right?
So, what kind of gang are the Dollars?
Uh, if I had to describe it...
Colorless?
Dollars?
Yeah, I know them.
Well, I'm actually one of them.
I got a girlfriend after joining the Dollars!
They post crap on BBSes.
There's always someone who responds.
Well, once you're an old fart like me, you don't have any other social contact apart from work.
Ya know?
The Dollars saved someone who was about to be abducted by kidnappers!
Dollars forever!
So?
It's fun, so who cares?
This is more fun than I expected.
This is fun.
Huh? What?
What are these people doing?!
Hey, who's the founder of the Dollars?
Do you see an Arabian oil magnate?
Nope.
Togusa-san, the one who responded to us is the real founder, right?
Yeah... I think.
Togusa! The light!
It's red! Red!
Pretty talkative, aren't we?
Dotachin! Dotachin!
I told you to stop calling me that.
Someone replied on the Dollars' BBS.
I've made the arrangements.
You can meet her.
But in return, I want you to help me.
Celty.
He's gone!
Stop looking around like idiots!
Go find him!
Yes ma'am!
Move!
Where did he go?
Damn!
Move!
Enough is enough!
Who's talking?
I don't have a head!
I'm a monster!
I don't have a mouth to speak with, nor do I have eyes to show my passion!
I hear something.
Whose voice is this?
So what?
So what?!
Celty...
I'm here.
I do exist!
Who the hell are you?
If you say I don't have eyes, then behold carefully how I act!
Die!
Engrave the screams of those who enraged a monster into your mind!
Th-The Headless Rider!
It's the Headless Rider!
That?
The Headless Rider?!
I'm here.
I'm right here! I do exist!
I'm already screaming.
Screaming even louder!
I was born here,
in order to engrave my existence into this city!
Are you Ryuugamine Mikado?
Give...
Give Celty back!
That's right.
I've discovered a truth about this city.
Something so evanescent, something so normal.
I guess that boy...
Next time: Mutually Existing and Not.