See? See?
It goes really fast!
Y-You're a surprisingly good driver.
Aren't I?
You may not believe it, but I practice all the time.
Of all the toys Kiritsugu brought me,
this is my favorite!
Toys?
At the castle, I could only drive around the courtyard,
so this is great!
Shouldn't we have hired a chauffeur?
No, that would be boring...
I mean, dangerous!
What if the enemy attacks us?
That's true.
Stop!
Irisviel...
Get out of the car and stay close to me.
This presence...
That's a Servant.
No matter how often I reach out into this world of repetition
empty tears always melt my ebon heart
Once the emotions borne within me resonate inside my chest
I will stand beside you to protect you, and not be indifferent
When we pick up the pieces of the hope we lost
and walk towards a brighter future
our entangled, twisted wishes will come undone and shine
We held up our lights and dismissed our hesitation
I wished to meet you, and did
Embrace these tearful nights
and rage in grief
Slowly the future before us cures us of our poisoned ideals
Accept the kiss you feel and let us march forth
to wherever we need to go
Stained miracles hold the promise of true life
I've come for you, my holy virgin.
You know him?
I've never laid eyes on him.
Oh, no!
You say you've forgotten this face?
Forgotten? I've never met you in my life.
Perhaps you mistake me for another?
It's me! Gilles de Rais!
My one prayer has been for your revival,
and I've spent my life waiting for a miracle to reunite us!
To that end, I've come all this way, to the end of time!
Jeanne!
Jeanne?
I know not your name,
nor have I any idea who this Jeanne might be.
No...
You can't have forgotten...
Not your former identity!
As you've given me your name,
in accordance with the knight's code of chivalry, I must give you my own.
My name is Arturia.
Heir to Uther Pendragon,
and King of Britain.
I enter this battle in the Saber class.
How tragic!
How sad...
She's lost her memory and gone mad!
Curse you...
Curse you!
What cruel tortures God inflicts upon my beautiful maiden!
Enough! You embarrass yourself!
Awaken...
Call yourself Saber no longer.
The Holy Grail War has ended.
The Grail has chosen me, Gilles, with no fighting at all!
For you see,
my only wish, the revival of Jeanne d'Arc, has been granted!
If you further mock all the other heroes' prayers,
the next strike will be real.
Now rise!
Has your heart been sealed so tightly, Jeanne?
Very well, then.
If drastic measures are called for,
I will have to prepare.
I swear to you, Jeanne...
I will release your soul from God's curse.
It's difficult to deal with one who doesn't listen to your words.
Next time, I shall strike before he can speak.
Those types infuriate me.
However, this may have been fortunate for me.
He felt too dangerous an enemy to face without use of my left hand.
Following Saber's Master has yielded an unexpected reward.
We found Caster, as well.
Of course, we must follow him.
Ah... No, no.
Here is what you do with the thumb.
Nice...
Perfect.
Welcome back, man.
No way...
Accursed God!
He keeps an iron grip on Jeanne's soul, refusing to let go!
By Jeanne, you mean your girl in the crystal ball?
We must prove it to her!
That God's power is gone... That my love is wasted!
That no foul deed, no horrible crime, is worthy of God's punishment!
Yeah, I get it.
You're even cooler than Him!
Therefore!
We require greater depravities, greater blasphemies.
We must erect a Tower of Babel of sacrificial corpses!
Uh, so basically...
From now on, it's quantity of quality?
Indeed... Exactly so!
Impressive, Ryuunosuke.
Our first step will be sacrificing the eleven in their cells.
And then we'll get some more.
Kind of a waste...
We interrupt this program
to bring you breaking news.
Unexplained Explosion
An unexplained explosion just occurred
in the warehouse district, off the coast of Fuyuki City.
We go live to the scene...
Why weren't you able to finish Saber tonight?
You've failed me not just once, but twice.
You made me waste a Command Seal, yet you still couldn't finish the job.
Was your fight with Saber that much fun?
That isn't...
I swear, by my honor as a knight, to bring you Saber's head.
You don't need to promise me that!
It's a necessary step...
You made a contract with me for the Grail!
And now, you swear to defeat Saber?
What about this do you not understand?!
Aren't you the one who's mistaken, Lord El-Melloi?
Sola-Ui...
Lancer did well.
You were the one who made the mistake.
Saber is a powerful Servant...
I couldn't allow a chance to defeat her slip by.
You inflicted a wound that cannot heal.
By letting her go, you can defeat her whenever you like.
If you were that concerned about her, why did you not go after her Master?
You merely stayed hidden and watched from afar. Pathetic.
Kayneth...
You do understand your advantage over other Masters, right?
You made a special alteration to the usual Master-Servant contract.
You get the Command Seals, and I act as an additional Master to supply prana.
You weren't the Evocation Division's brightest star for nothing.
But we must take care at the start.
Oh, must we?
So you'll hide, while making Lancer assume the risks...
That's enough.
Any more will be an insult to my Master.
As a knight, I cannot allow it.
No, I didn't mean it like that...
I'm sorry. I've said too much.
What? What's going on?
Understood.
A fire on the lower levels.
Arson, without a doubt.
Arson?
Tonight of all nights?
They wish to empty the place.
Then it's an attack?
Saber's Master will want to eliminate the spear's curse as soon as possible.
Lancer, go down and defeat her.
Don't just drive her off this time.
Understood.
Let's have our guest enjoy the magical atelier of Kayneth El-Melloi.
A perfect atelier, requiring an entire floor.
Twenty-four layered barriers.
Three prana generators.
Dozens of ghosts and evil spirits, roaming as guard dogs.
Thousands of traps.
Parts of hallways that open onto other worlds.
We shall both be able to avail ourselves of all our magical techniques.
You said I was pathetic...
You will take those words back shortly.
I look forward to it.
Lord Archibald!
Lord Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald!
Are you present?
Yes.
That's me. Don't worry.
Both Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and his wife, Sola-Ui, have evacuated.
I see.
Yes, that's fine.
Everyone has evacuated.
Excellent.
Everything is ready.
And with you?
Everything's fine. Ready immediately.
Maiya.
Target never even moved.
He didn't leave the hotel.
A free-fall from 150 meters...
No magical barrier could have saved him from that.
Maiya, withdraw.
To blow up the entire building... I can't believe a magus would do that.
Rather, I suppose you are a master at outsmarting magi.
Kotomine Kirei...
I don't believe we've met.
Do you perchance know me already?
In that case, I can guess who you are.
Don't make me do all the talking, woman.
One word will suffice.
Where is the man who should be standing in your place?
Not bad.
You seem to have training.
She didn't throw this.
Very well...
Just the knowledge that someone came to save her
will do for the night.
My lord Kirei...
I told you not to expose yourself without good reason.
I'm sorry, but there's something you should hear.
We located Caster.
After having Assassin perform a detailed investigation,
We learned that Caster and his Master have kidnapped children
from Miyama and the next town over.
By dawn, they had fifteen.
I'd imagine
them to be the serial killer
everyone is all worked up over.
They use magic, without the slightest hesitation,
doing nothing to conceal their deeds.
Quite possibly, they're not even thinking of the Holy Grail War.
A mad Servant, out of control, and a Master who cannot control him.
Why is someone like that participating in the Holy Grail War?
We cannot ignore them, Tokiomi.
Their actions violate the rules beyond what we can ignore.
Of course.
As one responsible for guarding the secrets of magic, I cannot allow it.
We shall have to eliminate Caster and his Master.
The problem is that defeating a Servant requires a Servant.
And we can't send my Assassin.
Minor rule changes fall within my power.
We'll have all the Masters work to defeat Caster.
Archer?
There are fewer bottles, but of higher quality than those in Tokiomi's room.
Some apprentice he has.
What do you want?
Apparently, somebody here,
other than myself, has too much time on their hands.
Time on their hands?
Why else would a Master under Church protection
wander about so late?
What are you talking about?
Are you dissatisfied with your contract, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi summoned me to this world, and he maintains my form here.
And his greeting was worthy of my station. I had to respond to that.
But I never thought he'd be such a boring person...
You are unhappy with him as your Master?
To reach the spiral of the Akashic Records?
What a wasted effort.
The desire for the Akashic Records is unique to magi.
It's not for outsiders to comment upon.
In a sense, the path to the Akashic Records
is the path to escape from this world.
For we who are interested only in the world itself,
it may well be a wasted effort.
Is that so...
Then what of you, Kirei?
What do you want from the Grail?
I...
I have no real desire for it.
Impossible.
Doesn't the Grail select only those who are worthy?
So they say.
But I do not understand.
I have no ideal or other desire, so why choose me for this battle?
No ideal or other desire...
Then why not wish for joy?
Ridiculous. Joy?
You'd ask me to long for something that blasphemous and sinful?
Blasphemous?
Sinful? That's going a little far.
Why draw a connection between joy and sin?
I...
True, joy gained by evil means could be a sin.
But joy may be attained through good deeds, as well.
What kind of philosophy calls joy itself a sin?
Joy is another quality I lack.
I see, but I do not find it.
Kotomine Kirei...
I find myself taking an interest in you.
What do you mean?
Exactly what I said. Be seated.
Joy, you see...
One might say it's a form of the soul.
The question isn't whether it exists, but whether you know it.
Kirei, you still have yet to see what form your soul has taken.
That's what it means to claim that you lack joy.
So a mere Servant means to lecture me?
Don't get cocky, mongrel.
These are words of a king who has tasted all the pleasure and luxury the world offers.
You should take heed.
Kirei, you ought to learn what pleasure is.
Look first to the outside.
I know...
Why not begin by joining me in my entertainment?
I have no time to waste on trivialities.
Don't be like that.
You can do it between the jobs Tokiomi assigns.
To begin with, Kirei,
your task is to watch the five other Masters, yes?
That's right.
You should learn not only their plans and strategies,
but their motivations, as well.
Then report back to me.
That would be possible if I asked the Assassins.
But, Archer, what does it matter to you?
I told you. I enjoy watching humans.
One or two are sure to be interesting.
Compared to Tokiomi, at the very least.
Very well, Archer. I accept.
But it will take some time.
That's fine. I shall be patient.
And avail myself of these drinks...
My reason for seeking the Grail?
I said far too much.
It certainly isn't joy.
But...
If I can learn about them,
will I be able to also learn what it is I seek?
Emiya Kiritsugu...
Episode 6
Night of Stratagems
Quietly my distant memories shift
when I picture you and seek comfort in my past
Reflected in the window I know so well
are eyes that look at tomorrow
I know that we are doomed to our fate
but still there is faith in my fearless heart
Quietly my distant memories shift
and in them I can find the proof that we spent time together
You taught me what it means to have passion
so I will live inside your memories even if the world should end
I'll explain the temporary change in rules.
They'll kill Emiya Kiritsugu...
We can escape! If we go now, we can still...
It will be my lance that takes Saber's life!
I'm not interested in fighting you for the Grail!
Don't get any ideas, bitch!
Next Time
Evil Forest