Dela
This is Dela's Bar.
A friendly bar where you may immerse yourself in moody music and fancy conversations.
What's wrong, Dela?
I'm deeply concerned, my girl.
Concerned?!
What's gotten into you, Dela?!
Call me Bartender.
Well, that aside...
That aside?
As you girls are well aware,
I'm a noble bird who has served the Mochidis Gusting family for generations.
Dashing good looks and great wisdom—
The heavens have granted me both of these!
Huh? Really?
Really! 'Tis a bit late for that question, don't you think?
I had no idea!
Yeah, yeah.
Then drill this into your brains!
That's who I am, but now I'm deeply concerned!
What should I do to reach even further heights?
You wanna break through the stratosphere?
That's not what I meant!
Then what'd you mean?
What should I do in order to become cute?
So you knew you weren't cute, huh?
No!
I'm plenty cute as it is!
But I'm looking for a way to be even cuter!
Much, much cuter than ever before!
That silence lasted too long!
What was that, the calm before the broadcasting storm?!
I was just surprised.
I thought I'd gotten used to your antics too.
So you were supposed to be cute?
And here I thought you were a bird.
Hm...
You're white, round, and soft...
I think you're plenty cute.
What's left? To grow larger?
Kids like elephants, monsters, and the like.
Oh? Larger, eh?
Nope.
Just no.
I don't want to frighten people!
I just want them to fawn over me.
How about you grow smaller instead?
Oh? Smaller, you say?
Scary!
Being tiny is scary!
Huh? Really?
Let's see...
Would a change of color help?
Color?
You're telling me to dye these beautiful, lovable feathers of mine?
Yeah!
I'd like polka dots.
Dye your entire body yellow and have black polka dots.
I'm talking about that "gap rule" thing.
"He looked like a delinquent at first glance,
but he's actually quite cute when you talk to him."
That totally happens!
It does.
It seems more surprising than when a normal person does something good, so it makes you look better in their eyes.
Hold on!
I'm sorry, Shiori, but I'll have to disagree.
What I want to be is even cuter,
not surprisingly cute.
But I think that element of surprise is all you can bank on.
The "I don't know why, but he's cute" thing, huh?
Like, "He's foul-mouthed, but cute,"
or "He's acts high and mighty, but he's cute,"
or maybe even "He's like an old man, but he's cute."
Notes
Oh, I see.
Huh?
H-Hold on a second, Shiori.
What's that supposed to mean?
"He's Dela, but he's cute."
Ohhh...
Hey!
Don't agree with her!
Dela's Bar.
It's a dangerous bar where even the slightest remark could lead to disaster.