- Fukuhara:
TODAY IS THE SECOND DAY
OF FUMIZUKI ACADEMY'S
ACADEMIC TRA--
HEY, I WASN'T FINISHED YET.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Fukuhara:
AT THE ACADEMIC CAMP,
CLASSES "A" AND "F"
ARE TRAINING TOGETHER.
- YUUJI, YOU LIKE
STUDYING TOGETHER, DON'T YOU?
- SHOUKO, YOU KNOW THAT'S
NOT YOUR SEAT, DON'T YOU?
- SO WHY DO WE HAVE TO HAVE
LAME STUDY HALL AT CAMP, ANYWAY?
AREN'T WE GONNA HAVE
REGULAR CLASSES?
- NO, WHY WOULD WE?
UNLESS YOU CAN MIRACULOUSLY
UNDERSTAND CLASS "A's" MATERIAL.
- YOU SHOULD HAVE
A LITTLE BIT MORE FAITH
IN YOUR FRIEND, FRIEND.
AFTER ALL, CLASS "F" AND "A"
AREN'T REALLY
ALL THAT DIFFERENT TO ME.
- YEAH, WELL,
COLOR ME IMPRESSED.
- MAINLY 'CAUSE I CAN'T
UNDERSTAND EITHER ONE.
- HOW COULD I NOT
HAVE SEEN THAT COMING?
- DID THEY NOT TELL YOU
THE REASON WE'RE HERE?
THEY'RE TRYING TO MOTIVATE
ALL THE DIFFERENT CLASSES.
- IF THEY MAKE EVERYONE STUDY
IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER,
SUPPOSEDLY, CLASS "F"
IS GONNA BE INSPIRED
TO TRY TO BE MORE
LIKE CLASS "A."
AND CLASS "A" WILL SEE THAT
THEY DON'T WANT TO BE LOSERS,
LIKE WE ARE.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THOSE "A" GUYS,
BUT I DON'T THINK THIS PLAN
WILL WORK ON OUR CLASS,
LIKE AT ALL.
- SHOUKO.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU EVERYWHERE.
HEY, GUYS, I THINK I'M GONNA
STUDY IN HERE WITH YOU.
- IT'S AIKO KUDOU.
- WHAT'S UP, CREEPERS?
HOW WAS LAST NIGHT?
I HEARD YOU PERVS TRIED
TO PEEK IN THE GIRL'S BATHROOM.
IF YOU WANTED TO
SEE IT SO BADLY,
YOU COULD HAVE JUST TOLD ME.
ARE YOU STILL UP FOR IT?
I'LL LET YOU SEE
MY UNDERWEAR RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT? YOU WHAT?
- Shouko: I DON'T THINK SO.
- ( groans )
- KOUTA, ARE YOU
FEELING SICK OR SOMETHING?
YOU LOVE THIS.
I'M TALKING PANTIES.
PANTIES ON A GIRL, YOU KNOW.
I CAN'T BE THE ONLY ONE
LOSING MY MIND OVER THIS, CAN I?
- DON'T LET HER
GET TO YOU, AKI.
SHE'S WEARING LEGGINGS
UNDER THAT SKIRT.
- WHAT?! AIKO, YOU MONSTER.
HOW COULD YOU BE SO HEARTLESS?
- SORRY TO DISAPPOINT, BOYS.
BUT I STILL HAVE SOMETHING
YOU MIGHT LIKE TO SEE.
- LIKE WHAT?
- IT'S A MINI-RECORDER, RIGHT?
- Aki: Kouta, are you
feeling sick or something?
- COOL, HUH? YOU CAN HAVE
A LOT OF FUN WITH THESE.
- Aki: I love-- Aiko--
I'm losing my mind over--
a girl.
- ( gasps )
- YEAH, THAT IS PRETTY FUN,
ISN'T IT, MIZUKI?
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER
HAD MORE FUN THAN THIS MOMENT.
- OH, BY THE WAY, WOULD YOU
HELP ME WITH SOMETHING?
- OF COURSE.
I'D BE HAPPY TO.
- YOU SHOULD RUN NOW.
THEY'RE GOING TO COME BACK
WITH MORE STUFF
TO TORTURE YOU WITH.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME.  GO!
- I DON'T GET IT, HIDEYOSHI.
I DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING WRONG.
- HEY, AKI, LISTEN.
- HEY, YUUJI.
- WE NEED TO FACE
THE POSSIBILITY
THAT AIKO IS THE WIRETAPPER.
- GOOD POINT.  SHE'S GOT
MAD SKILLS ON THAT RECORDER.
- AKIHISA, IT'S UP TO YOU TO
FIND OUT IF SHE'S THE CULPRIT.
- UNDERSTOOD.
I HAVE A QUESTION.
- AWESOME, ASK AWAY.
- ARE YOU--
WAIT, IF I JUST WHIP OUT
"ARE YOU THE BLACKMAILER,"
SHE'S PROBABLY NOT
GONNA BE HONEST ABOUT IT.
- AM I WHAT?
- WHAT? I MEAN,
ARE YOU ESPECIALLY--
- ESPECIALLY?
- THINK, AKI.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
LET'S SEE,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
WITH A BURN MARK ON THEIR BUTT,
SO THERE'S THAT.
AAH!
- HMM?
- AIKO, I'D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU WOULD SHOW ME YOUR BUTT.
THANK YOU.
- THAT'S SOME SMOOTH
TALKING THERE.
- YOU ARE THE MAN, MY FRIEND.
- WAY TO PUT IT OUT THERE.
I BOW BEFORE YOU.
- Aki: Aiko, I'd appreciate it
if you would
show me your butt.
Thank you.
- THIS IS STARTING
TO GET EMBARRASSING.
- NOT HER FAULT.
SHE JUST RECORDED IT.
- PLEASE, AIKO, YOU HAVE
TO DELETE THAT ONE!
Please, Aiko, you have to--
show me your butt.
( screams )
- Minami: WOW, DID YOU
HEAR WHAT I HEARD?
- Mizuki: WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
- YOU KNOW, THE SOUND
OF A DEAD BOY
DIGGING AN EVEN
DEEPER HOLE FOR HIMSELF
THAN THE ONE HE'S ALREADY IN.
- OH, YES, I DID HEAR THAT.
AND SUCH A PERSON
CANNOT BE ALLOWED TO ESCAPE
WITHOUT THE PROPER PUNISHMENT.
- YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
LET ME EXPLAIN.
IT'S JUST THAT...
THIS IS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
- I love butt.
- IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
AIKO!
YOU'RE GONNA GET ME KILLED
IF YOU DON'T STOP.
- SERIOUSLY, AIKO,
STOP MESSING AROUND.
- HELP ME, KOUTA.
- ( laughs )
- DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL TAKE HER ON.
- THANK, OLD BUDDY, OLD PAL.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
LISTEN TO ME.
YOU BOTH HEARD WRONG EARLIER.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO SAY
THIS WAS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
- I love butt.
- OH MY GOD!
- Especially Yuuji's butt.
- I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
KOUTA, YOUR NOT HELPING.
- AIKO KUDOU, YOU STILL
HAVE MUCH TO LEARN.
- NOT TOO BAD.  YOU'RE JUST
AS GOOD AS I THOUGHT YOU'D BE.
- AKIHISA, I WILL NEVER
LET YOU HAVE YUUJI.
- I DON'T WANT HIM THOUGH!
- AKI, TELL THE TRUTH.
DO YOU REALLY LIKE
HIS BUTT THAT MUCH?
WHAT'S SO WRONG WITH MINE?
- I MEAN, I SORT OF
ALWAYS KNEW IT, BUT HEARING
THE WORDS OUT LOUD
BREAKS MY HEART.
- NO, GUYS, LISTEN!
I'M NOT INTO THAT
KIND OF THING, I SWEAR!
- YOU'RE NOT INTO IT?!
HOMOSEXUALITY IS NOT A FAD.
- MIHARU? WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
- I WANTED TO SEE YOU!
SO I SNUCK OUT OF CLASS "D"
AND CAME HERE!
I COULDN'T GO ANOTHER MINUTE
WITHOUT SEEING MY BABY.
- SUGAWA BARRIER!
- ( coo's, kisses )
OH! GROSS!
YOU MAKE ME SO SICK.
YOU STUPID, UGLY,
FILTHY PIG!
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT
TO ME, DARLING?
ALL I WANT IS
TO LOVE YOU FOREVER AND EVER
UNTIL THE END OF TIME.
- FOR THE THOUSANDTH TIME,
I AM NOT INTO GIRLS.
I DO NOT SWING THAT WAY.
- EXCUSE ME.  WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE STUDYING.
COULD YOU PLEASE TRY
AND KEEP IT DOWN?
- OH, SORRY, KUBO.
- ALSO, IN THIS DAY IN AGE,
MAKING FUN OF HOMOSEXUAL LOVE
SEEMS LESS THAN TOLERANT.
JUDGING INDIVIDUAL PEOPLE
WITHIN A SOCIETY
BECAUSE OF A DIFFERENCE
IN PREFERENCE IS UNNECESSARY.
A PERSON CAN'T HELP
WITH WHOM THEY FALL IN LOVE.
AND NO ONE SHOULD
ASSUME OTHERWISE.
IF YOU'RE MOCKING THEM,
YOU'RE MOCKING NATURE ITSELF.
- HE'S RIGHT, LOVE DOESN'T
CARE ABOUT GENDER, BABY.
- LOVE MIGHT NOT,
BUT I SURE DO.
- LOVE CERTAINLY DOES NOT
CARE ABOUT GENDER.
NICE.
- OKAY, I'M FEELING
KIND OF AWKWARD.
- LOVE DOES NOT CARE
ABOUT GENDER.
I SEE.
- WHY DO YOU KEEP
LOOKING AT ME AND
YUUJI LIKE THAT?!
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
FOR THE LAST FRICKIN' TIME,
I NEVER SAID ANY OF THAT...
- I love Hideyoshi.
- ...STUFF YOU HEARD.  STOP!
DAMN IT!
- OH, AKIHISA, I REALLY DON'T
KNOW HOW TO RESPOND TO THAT.
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING IT.
HIDEYOSHI, YOUR NAME WAS...
ON THAT MINI-RECORDER THINGY.
- Butt is what I...
especially love, Kubo.
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?!
( cries )
- Show me your butt, Kubo.
Show me your butt.
I love Kubo.
Kubo, show me your butt.
- WELL, THIS IS UNEXPECTED.
NOT THAT I DON'T PROFOUNDLY
APPRECIATE IT OF COURSE.
- Fukuhara: THIS IS HOW
RUMORS GET STARTED, KIDS.
- I THINK I'VE GOT IT.
I'M PRETTY SURE AIKO'S
THE ONE WHO'S BLACKMAILING US.
- IF SHE HANDLES EXTORTION
THE WAY SHE HANDLES
HER LITTLE RECORDER-THING,
THEN THAT MAY VERY
WELL BE THE CASE.
- LET'S TAKE HER DOWN
RIGHT NOW.
- WE ONLY GET ONE CHANCE.
WE DON'T WANT TO SCREW IT UP.
- RIGHT, BECAUSE IF WE DO,
THE ACTUAL BUTT-BURNED CULPRIT
COULD END UP BEING LOST
TO JUSTICE FOREVER.
- YEAH, AND ON TOP OF THAT,
SHE'LL KEEP BLACKMAILING YOU.
- UH-HUH, THIS IS DEFINITELY
A BETTER-SAFE-THAN-SORRY
SITUATION.
- SO WE CAN'T GO BARGING IN
UNLESS WE'RE 100% SURE.
I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
- IF ONLY WE COULD
SEE HER BOOTY,
WE COULD FIND OUT
IF SHE HAS THAT BURN MARK.
- I BET SHE GETS PISSED,
BUT WHY DON'T WE JUST TRY
FLIPPING HER SKIRT UP?
- SHE'S WEARING LEGGINGS,
REMEMBER?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT!
- AT THIS POINT,
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE HAVE TO PEEK IN
ON THE GIRLS BATHING.
- THIS IS GETTING
TO BE A THEME.
- HOW DO WE PEEK, THOUGH?
WE NEED TO HAVE A GOOD PLAN
BECAUSE THOSE GUARDS
ARE GONNA DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET IN OUR WAY.
- Hideyoshi: WELL, THAT
HALLWAY'S A STRAIGHT SHOT.
A FRONTAL ATTACK
IS OUR ONLY OPTION,
UNLESS YOU KNOW OF
ANOTHER WAY IN THERE.
- Yuuji: OH, THERE'S
ALWAYS ANOTHER WAY.
THE FRONT IS JUST
GONNA BE THE EASIEST.
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO HAVE
A STRONG FORCE
IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT THROUGH.
- YOU MEAN, WE NEED
REINFORCEMENTS?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- Aki: I'M ON IT.
- ( door opens )
- FELLAS, WHAT DO WANT FROM US?
- WELCOME, EVERYONE.
- SIMPLE, SUGAWA.
FELLOW CLASS "F"-ERS,
WE HAVE A LITTLE PROPOSITION
TO MAKE TO YOU.
- PROPO-- WHAT?
- I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO DO ANYTHING.
- YEAH, I'M KIND
OF UP FOR NOTHING.
- REALLY?
SO YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED
IN WATCHING THE GIRLS
TAKE A BATH?
- WE NEVER SAID THAT.
KEEP TALKING.
- LAST NIGHT, WE TRIED
PEEKING ON THE GIRLS
WHILE THEY WERE
IN THEIR BATHROOM,
BUT A COUPLE OF
JERK-ASS TEACHERS
THAT WERE GUARDING THEM
AMBUSHED US
AND RUINED EVERYTHING.
- SO, WHAT NOW?
- WE'RE MAKING
ANOTHER ATTACK TONIGHT.
YOU'RE JOB, IF YOU
CHOOSE TO ACCEPT IT,
IS TO ELIMINATE
THE GUARD IN QUESTION.
AFTER THAT, YOUR REWARD
WILL BE THE CHANCE
TO SEE UTOPIA.
- WE'RE IN!
- ALL RIGHT, KOUTA.
WHAT TIME ARE WE AT?
- IT'S CURRENTLY 20:10.
ABOUT 10 MINUTES HAVE PASSED
SINCE THE TARGETED LADIES
FROM CLASS "A"
STARTED GETTING
THEIR LATHER ON.
- THIS IS PERFECT TIMING, MEN.
WE'RE GONNA SPLIT UP
INTO FOUR GROUPS NOW.
GROUP "A," FOLLOW ME.
- "B."
- GROUP "B," FOLLOW AKI.
- "C."
- GROUP "C," FOLLOW HIDEYOSHI.
- "D."
- AND GROUP "D,"
FOLLOW KOUTA DIRECTIONS.
UNDERSTOOD?
- ROGER THAT.
- LISTEN UP!
FINALLY, BROTHERS,
THIS IS OUR TIME,
OUR TIME TO REACH UTOPIA.
NO MATTER WHAT
MAY GET IN YOUR WAY,
YOU MUST NOT
ALLOW IT TO STOP YOU.
USE EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
GODS AND DEMONS ARE MORTAL TOO.
WE WILL SLAY THEM.
WE'RE ABOUT TO
CHANGE THE FUTURE, MEN.
AND NOTHING
IS GONNA STOP US.
- I WAS QUITE FIRM
WITH THEM YESTERDAY.
SURELY, THEY WON'T TRY
ANYTHING AGAIN TODAY.
- ( running footsteps )
- HMM?
- ( roaring )
- APPARENTLY, THIS PACK
OF PERVERTS IS PERSISTENT.
I'M SUMMONING MY AVATAR.
SUMMON!
- ( grunts )
- YOU SHALL NOT PASS!
- SUMMON.
- Group C: SUMMON!
- BAD NEWS.
HIDEYOSHI AND GROUP "C"
HAVE ALL BEEN STOPPED
BY MR. FUSE.
- THIS IS THE PERFECT
CHANCE TO PASS THROUGH.
FUSE IS DISTRACTED.
HEADS IN THE GAME, GUYS!
- YEAH!
- ALL TOGETHER,
ATTACK THE FUSE!
- ( shouting )
- Aki: NOW, FORWARD HO!
- Fuse: STOP RIGHT THERE, YOSHI!
- IN YOUR FACE, SUCKA!
- Class F: IN YOUR FACE!
- NOT ANOTHER STEP!
YOU GUYS MAKE ME SICK.
GUYS AREN'T ALLOWED
PAST THIS POINT.
GO BACK TO YOUR GRODY,
GROSS PIGSTY WHERE YOU BELONG.
- AKIHISA, THEY'VE
GOT MORE PEOPLE
AND THEY'RE SMARTER THAN US.
- I'M ASKING NICELY.
OUT OF OUR WAY.
- AND PUT MY PRINCESS'S
FLAT CHEST ON DISPLAY
FOR YOU TO SEE?
HELL TO THE NO!
- YOU'RE WRONG.
MINAMI'S FLATTER
THAN FLAT CHEST
ISN'T WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
- YOU'RE LYING.
HER SUPER FLAT CHEST
HAS CAST A SPELL ON YOU.
BUT IF YOU MAKE ANOTHER MOVE,
THEN I'M GONNA FLATTEN YOU.
- BELIEVE ME.
HOWEVER FLAT,
A FLAT CHEST IS
JUST A FLAT CHEST.
RIGHT NOW, I HAVE MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO FOCUS ON
THAN MINAMI'S FLAT,
BOY-LIKE CHEST
LIKE HOW MY ELBOW'S ABOUT
TO BE FUSED INTO MY SPINE!
- GO AHEAD, SAY IT AGAIN.
I DARE YOU.  ONE MORE TIME.
- HE'S PRACTICALLY BEGGING
FOR PUNISHMENT, ISN'T HE?
- YOU CRACK ME UP, YOSHI.
WHAT EXACTLY DID
YOU WANT TO SEE?
KNOW WHAT WOULD
MAKE ME HAPPY?
IF IT WAS ME.
- Shouko: I DON'T THINK SO.
- ( groans )
- I WILL NOT PERMIT AN AFFAIR.
- DAMN IT, SHOUKO
IS EVEN HERE TO STOP US.
THIS IS BAD.
- IS IT AT ALL POSSIBLE
THAT YOU CAME HERE
TO FIND THIS?
I FOUND A PREVIOUSLY
UNFOUND HIDDEN CAMERA
THAT HAD BEEN LEFT IN
THE GIRL'S CHANGING ROOM.
I JUST STUMBLED ACROSS IT.
AND IT'S NOT MINE.
- CRAZY.
- SO THEN, WHAT ARE
YOU THINKING, KOUTA?
SHALL WE DO THIS NOW?
- HELL, YEAH.
- ( laughs )
SUMMON!
- Aki: TELL ME YOU
GOT THIS, KOUTA?
- I'M ALL OVER IT.  GO!
- TIME FOR SOME
SENSITIVITY TRAINING!
- ( groans )
- I KNEW YOU WOULD
TRY THIS AGAIN,
YOU LITTLE IDIOTS.
- IRON MAN.
- DO WE HAVE TO GET THROUGH HIM
WITHOUT USING OUR AVATARS?
- NO WAY, WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
- YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
SOME SERIOUS COUNSELING, KID.
YOU HEAR ME, YOSHI?!
- CRAP, THIS IS WHERE I DIE.
- DON'T GIVE UP, MY BROTHER.
- SUGAWA!
- LET GO OF ME NOW.
- DUDE, YOU CAN'T LET YOURSELF
GET TAKEN OUT HERE.
YOU'RE A PROBATIONARY STUDENT.
YOUR AVATAR IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN TAKE OUT THE IRON MAN.
PLEASE, AKIHISA.
RUN AWAY FOR NOW.
LIVE TO TELL THE TALE.
- WE'RE DONE LISTENING TO YOU.
- ( groans )
- YOU MONSTER!
SUGAWA!
- Boy #1: SUMMON!
- Boy #2: SUMMON!
- Boy #3: SUMMON!
- Boy #4: SUMMON!
- Boy #5: SUMMON!
- Boy #6: SUMMON!
- BACK UP AKIHISA'S WITHDRAWAL.
- CLEAR A PATH
FOR HIM TO ESCAPE.
- RUN, YOSHI,
AND DON'T LOOK BACK.
- YOU GUYS.
- ( grunts )
- YOSHI'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
PROTECT HIM NO MATTER WHAT.
- ( guys cheer )
- GO, YOSHI.
RUN.
( screams )
- ( screams continue )
- OKAY, I'M TRUSTING
IN MY FRIENDS.
I'LL SURVIVE.
I'M GONNA DO THIS.
I WON'T FAIL YOU.  I WON'T.
I'M SORRY, GUYS.
I'M SO SORRY.
( groans )
( cries )
I SWEAR IT.
I SWEAR I'LL REACH UTOPIA.
NOTHING IN THE WHOLE WORLD
CAN STOP ME.
- ( chimes play )
- Fukuhara: Akihisa Yoshi
of class "F."
Please come to the
counseling office immediately.
- WOW, HOW COULD I
NOT SEE THAT COMING?
- IT'S MORNING ALREADY?
THAT SUCKS.
I FEEL LIKE I JUST
WENT TO SLEEP,
LIKE, FIVE MINUTES AGO.
( gasps )
( laughs )
IT WAS ONLY A DREAM!
SO WEIRD.
( gasps )
NO WAY
THAT'S GOING DOWN!
- ( screams )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS YUUJI SLEEPING
IN SOMEONE ELSE'S BED AGAIN?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AGAIN"?
- HE HAS A TENDENCY
TO MOVE AROUND A LOT
WHILE HE'S SLEEPING.
AT DAWN, IT WAS ME.
TURNED OVER AND
THERE HE WAS.
- YOU BASTARD!
HOW DARE YOU
TAKE AWAY INNOCENCE!
I WILL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
- ( muffled screaming )
- OH, I FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
AIKO TOLD ME
SOMETHING INTERESTING YESTERDAY.
- OH, YEAH, WHAT?
- SHE SAID THERE'S STILL
A HIDDEN CAMERA
IN THE GIRL'S CHANGING ROOM?
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
- DO YOU THINK THAT MAKES
HER THE BLACKMAILER?
- I DON'T.  THAT WOULDN'T BE
A SMART MOVE.
WHY WOULD SHE
GO OUT OF HER WAY
TO MAKE HERSELF LOOK SUSPICIOUS
IF IT WAS REALLY HER?
- WE STILL HAVE TO
CHECK IT OUT THOUGH.
- EITHER WAY, IF WHAT
SHE SAYS IS THE TRUTH,
THIS IS GOOD NEWS.
- WHY IS THAT?
- BECAUSE IF WE GET OUR
HANDS ON THAT HIDDEN CAMERA,
WE'LL BE ABLE TO SEE
THE GIRL'S CHANGING,
WHICH MEANS WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO FIND THAT BURNED BUTT.
- GOOD THINKING.
- I'M PRETTY SURE
I CAN FIND THAT BAD BOY
IN UNDER FIVE SECONDS.
- YEAH, ME TOO,
BUT THAT'S IF
THERE REALLY IS A CAMERA THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- THE LAST ONE WAS FOUND BY
THOSE ANGRY CHICKS
THE NIGHT BEFORE LAST, RIGHT?
DOESN'T IT SEEM ODD
FOR A PERSON WHO'S SO GOOD
AT SNEAKING PICTURES
AND WIRETAPPING
TO LEAVE SOMETHING WHERE IT
COULD BE FOUND BY AMATEURS?
- A FALL-BACK PLAN.
- IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN.
THAT FIST SO-CALLED "HIDDEN"
CAMERA WAS JUST A DECOY.
IT'S WHOLE PURPOSE WAS TO MAKE
THE GIRL'S SUSPICIOUS OF US.
THE ONE AIKO FOUND
IN THE CHANGING ROOM
HAS GOT TO BE
THE MAIN CAMERA.
- AND ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS GET THE NEW-FOUND
HIDDEN CAMERA
AND WE'LL KNOW FOR SURE.
- NO CAN DO.
IT'S LOCKED OUTSIDE OF
BATHING TIMES, REMEMBER?
- CAN'T WE JUST KEEP TRYING
THE WAY WE HAVE BEEN, THOUGH?
- THINK ABOUT IT, AKI.
DO YOU KNOW THE REASON
WE LOST YESTERDAY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE BECAUSE HALF
THE GIRLS WERE SENT
TO OFFENSIVELY DEFEND
THE BATHROOM.
- WHICH MEANS WE SHOULD DO
EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO STRENGTHEN OUR FORCES, RIGHT?
WE NEED GUYS FROM THE OTHER
CLASSES TO HELP US.
- I COULD GET BEHIND THAT.
- AND GAINING A LITTLE
BIT OF MANPOWER
ISN'T THE ONLY REASON
WE NEED TO GET
THOSE CLASSES INVOLVED.
WE'RE GONNA NEED SOME
PROTECTION AFTER THIS THING.
- WE ARE?
- EVEN IF WE FIND THE CULPRIT,
EVEN IF WE DO SUCCEED IN PEEKING
IN ON THE GIRL'S CHANGING,
WE ARE GONNA BE PUNISHED
LIKE NOBODY'S BUSINESS.
- I GET IT.
IF THEY'RE A BUNCH OF US,
THEY WON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHO DID THE PEEKING.
- EXCEPT THEY ALREADY KNOW
THAT WE'RE BEHIND IT.
- Yuuji: FUMIZUKI ACADEMY
IS A PILOT SCHOOL
THAT'S GETTING
A LOT OF ATTENTION.
IF A SCANDAL HAPPENS,
THEY'LL HAVE TO EITHER PUNISH
THOSE INVOLVED OR HIDE THE FACT
THAT ANYTHING HAPPENED.
- SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS ATTACK IN A BIG GROUP
AND THEY WON'T BE ABLE
TO PUNISH ANYONE.
GOOD CALL, YUUJI.
WHEN IT COMES TO
MAKING UP DIRTY PLANS,
YOU ARE THE MASTER.
- I JUST CALL IT
BEING RESOURCEFUL.
LET'S GET OUR COMRADES
TOGETHER BEFORE TONIGHT.
FOR CLASS "A," WE SHOULD
PROBABLY TRY KUBO.
AKI, THAT'S GONNA
BE YOUR TERRITORY.
- IF ANYONE CAN DO IT,
YOU CAN.
- SO TRUE.
- I'LL DO MY BEST.
BUT, GUYS, WHY ME?
- USE THIS TO PROTECT YOURSELF,
JUST IN CASE.
- OKAY.
WHAT'S GOING ON, KUBO?
YOU GOT A MINUTE?
- I'VE GOT MORE THAN ONE.
PLEASE SIT DOWN.
- THANKS, BUT I'M GOOD HERE.
- YEAH, THAT'S OKAY.
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO IS FINE.
- I HAVE A QUESTION.
IT'S MORE OF A FAVOR.
WILL YOU--
- I WOULD BE HAPPY TO.
- THAT WAS FAST.
- I APOLOGIZE.
I UNCHARACTERISTICALLY
LOST MY COOL.
NOW LET ME HEAR WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
- YEAH, SURE. WILL YOU HELP
US PEEK ON THE GIRLS?
- I WON'T HELP YOU!
- THAT WAS FAST.
WHY NOT?
- I JUST LOST RESPECT FOR YOU.
AMONG A GROUP OF PEOPLE,
THEY'RE RULES TO FOLLOW.
THIS FOLLOWING OF SAID RULES
IS HOW SOCIETY AS A WHOLE
IS FORMED, YOSHI.
BASICALLY PLANNING ON BREAKING
THOSE ESTABLISHED RULES
MEANS THAT YOU HAVE
NO RESPECT FOR SOCIETY
AND ARE UNFIT FOR IT.
IS THAT REALLY THE KIND
OF PERSON YOU WANT TO BE?
THAT BEING SAID,
TRYING TO LOOK AT GIRLS
WHILE THEY'RE BATHING
IS DISGUSTING
AND MAKES ME
WANT TO PUKE.
- OH.
I FAILED.
I FAILED BIG TIME.
- FIGURES.  I'M GLAD
YOU'RE OKAY, THOUGH.
- OF COURSE I AM.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING DANGEROUS.
- SURE YOU DIDN'T.
SO SINCE CLASS
"A's" A BUST,
LET'S MOVE FORWARD WITH
THE OTHER CLASSES.
- ALL RIGHT, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU UP TO, LOSER?
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN?
WHAT WOULD I BE UP TO?
- I'M SO NOT GONNA
WASTE MY BREATH
TELLING YOU NOT TO
CAUSE ANYMORE TROUBLE,
BUT, YEAH, DON'T DO IT.
- PEEKING ON GIRLS WHILE
THEY BATHE IS SO CLICHE.
- WHAT?
- YOU'D JUST COMPARE ME
WITH EVERYONE ELSE
IF WE'RE ALL NAKED.
I CAN'T STUFF NOTHING.
AND THEY'RE FAR LESS PERKY
WHEN BRA-LESS.  IT'S TRAGIC.
- I NEVER IMAGINED
YOU'D TRY TO PEEK ON US.
SO I DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO GO ON A DIET.
THAT'S BEYOND
MEAN OF YOU, AKIHISA.
- WHAT I WANT TO SEE HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
- Yuuji's butt.
- IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING
TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
STOP DOING THAT!
- Fukuhara: ONCE AGAIN,
THE NIGHT OF THE SHOWDOWN
HAS ARRI-- WHAT?
- SERIOUSLY, WE COULDN'T GET
ANYONE TO HELP US...
- Fukuhara: NOT AGAIN.
- BESIDES CLASS "D"
AND CLASS "E"?
- CLASS "B's" REP
IS KYOUJI NEMOTO.
SO THERE'S REALLY
NOT MUCH UNITY.
CLASS "C's" REP IS THAT
FREAKIN' HARD-ASS YUKA KOYAMA.
DUDE, I DON'T BLAME THOSE GUYS
FOR BEING TERRIFIED OF HER.
- STILL THOUGH,
IT'S BETTER THAN YESTERDAY.
THE GIRLS CAN ONLY SEND OUT
HALF OF THEIR GROUP AT A TIME
TO DEFEND WHILE
THEY'RE BATHING.
AS LONG AS WE CAN
HOLD BACK THE TEACHERS,
I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
- I'VE ALREADY LET
EACH CLASS KNOW
WHEN WE'RE PLANNING
TO START THE OPERATION
AND WHERE THEY NEED TO BE.
- PERFECT.
LET'S GET THIS THING DONE.
- WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM!
WE'RE TOO LATE.
THEY WERE WAITING TO AMBUSH US
IN THE DINING HALL.
- WHAT?!
- OUR FORCES ARE
CURRENTLY SPLIT UP
AND SCATTERED
AROUND EACH FLOOR.
- WHO FIGURED
THEY'D MOVE FIRST?
- THEY'RE LIKE MIND READERS.
- DAMN, I BET IT WAS SHOUKO.
- YEAH, SHE DOESN'T LIKE
YUUJI PEEKING ON ANYONE BUT HER.
- THERE'S NO TIME
FOR HESITATION NOW.
WE NEED TO REORGANIZE
OUR FORCES.
THEN WE'LL MAKE OUR MOVE.
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA
PEEK ON US, LOSERS.
- WHY ARE THE GIRLS HERE?
- ( chatter, fighting )
- GUYS, CONCENTRATE ALL
YOUR ENERGY ON ONE POINT.
WE'LL BREAK THROUGH THERE.
LET'S GO.
- Guys: YEAH!
- YUUJI!
WE'VE GOT ENEMIES
AT THE FRONT.
- THEY PROBABLY SET TRAPS FOR US
THROUGHOUT THE HALLS.
SO STAY ON YOUR TOES.
BE READY FOR ANYTHING!
- YUUJI, WE'VE BEEN WAITING.
- SHOUKO, CRAP.
THIS IS WHAT
I WAS AFRAID OF.
- I TOLD YOU I WOULD
NOT PERMIT AN AFFAIR.
YOU IGNORED ME,
BUT YOUR BODY WON'T.
- YOU BOYS ARE IN NEED
OF SOME SERIOUS
MENTAL AND EMOTIONAL
COUNSELING.
- MISS TAKAHASHI,
THE YEAR-TWO HEAD TEACHER.
YUUJI, WITHDRAW!
- SORRY.
THAT IS SO
NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
- AIKO! MR. OOSHIMA!
- YOU NEVER LEARN, DO YOU?
- AKIHISA, IF YOU WANTED
TO SEE IT THAT BAD,
WHY DIDN'T YOU ASK ME?
WE COULD HAVE WORKED
SOMETHING OUT.
- NO, YOU DON'T FRIGHTEN ME.
I'LL FIGHT MY THROUGH
TILL THE END.
SUMMON!
- SUMMON!
- YO!
- HE'S FAST.
- ( screams )
WHAT? NO WAY!
- HER SCORE IS IN THE 7,000's?
- THAT'S HIGHER
THAN ANYONE.
- ( smirks )
- WHAT DO I DO?
- NOTHING ELSE TO DO.
WE'RE GOING AFTER THEM
WITH EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT
AND GRANTING NO MERCY.
- WE ARE?
- EVERYONE, LISTEN UP.
FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
FORGET ABOUT THE PLAN.
DO WHATEVER COMES
NATURALLY TO YOU.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
THINK USING YOUR HEART.
JUDGE USING YOUR BRAIN.
AND ULTIMATELY,
DO WHAT YOU THINK IS RIGHT.
FROM HERE ON,
YOU GUYS CALL THE SHOTS.
ALL RIGHT, MAKE YOUR MOVE NOW.
- PLEASE FORGIVE US!
- ( gasps )
AREN'T THE FOUR OF YOU
GOING TO BEG FOR FORGIVENESS
LIKE YOUR LITTLE FRIENDS?
OR HAS YOUR PRIDE
GOTTEN THE BETTER OF YOU?
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
WE DON'T HAVE PRIDE.
WE HAVE KNOWLEDGE.
- HE'S RIGHT.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT US
BEING PROUD.
SOMEDAY, MAYBE YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO UNDERSTAND.
WE HAVE NO REASON TO
APOLOGIZE HERE TODAY.
- WHY IS THAT? BECAUSE
HELP IS ON THE WAY?
- AKI'S WRONG.
YOU'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
- HELP ISN'T ON THE WAY.
BUT IT WOULDN'T
MATTER IF IT WAS.
- Fukuhara: THEY BOTH KNEW
THEY WERE DEALING WITH PEOPLE
WHO WOULD MAKE THEM SUFFER,
EVEN IF THEY GOT DOWN
ON THEIR HANDS AND KNEES
AND BEGGED FOR FORGIVENESS.
ALTHOUGH, THIS IS THE THIRD
NIGHT OF THE TRAINING CAMP,
THE GUYS STILL HAVEN'T
BEEN ABLE TO FIND OUT
WHO THEIR BURNED-BUTT
BLACKMAILER IS.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT?
WHAT WILL BECOME OF
AKIHISA AND YUUJI'S--
YOU'RE CUTTING
ME OFF AGAIN.
- ( music plays )
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME
WITH THIS?
- ( singing in Japanese )
- BAKA AND TEST.
- Fukuhara: QUESTION 7:
"WHAT DO YOU CALL PHYSICAL
AND MENTAL TORTURE
USED TO MAKE
A PERSON OBEY YOU?"
- Yuuji: I'M SORRY, SHOUKO!
- Fukuhara:
( hums wedding march )
- Aki: NEXT EPISODE, "ME,
PEEKING, AND FAR AWAY PARADISE."
- Fukuhara:
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.