It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
We met each other in the storm.
Feelings that cannot
touch one another.
But even if the words don't reach,
I felt that I wanted to share
the wishes, and the sadness.
There is a feeling I want
to deliver to your heart,
to the only you in this world.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
And so...
As of 00:00 today, the entire crew's
mission will be changed
to the search for and retrieval of
the Lost Logia, the Jewel Seeds.
Now, concerning this case,
we have made a special exception,
and welcome the discoverer
of the Lost Logia,
a barrier mage...
Yes. I'm Yuuno Scrya.
And helping out his efforts,
a mage from the local world...
I'm Nanoha Takamachi!
These two members will be
treated as temporary staff
to help with the mission.
Nice to meet you all!
Episode 9:
The Decisive Battle Above the Ocean
We will determine the locations
of the Jewel Seeds.
When we find them, we'll
have you head to the site.
Okay!
Captain, your tea.
Thank you.
By the way, Nanoha,
is your school all right with this?
Yes.
I already gave an explanation
to my family and friends.
And so, due to family circumstances,
Miss Takamachi will be absent
from school for a few days.
But she's not out due to illness,
injury, or personal tragedy,
so there's no need to worry.
While Miss Takamachi is absent,
note-taking and
collecting hand-outs...
Yes, I'll do it!
Miss Arisa, I'll leave it to you.
Okay!
Now, let's start today's homeroom!
Rise!
Bow!
Nanoha...
I wonder if she's still cheerful?
Be seated!
Caught it!
Nanoha!
Okay!
Sealing Mode, set up.
Stand by ready.
Lyrical, magical...
Jewel Seed, Serial VIII,
seal!
Sealing.
Receipt No. VIII.
Situation has been settled.
Jewel Seed No. VIII
has been safely captured.
Good job, Nanoha, Yuuno.
Yeah!
I'll make a gate. Wait there.
Both of them are rather excellent.
At this rate, I might
want to keep them!
This girl in black was named Fate?
Fate Testarossa.
The same family name as
the great mage of yore.
Oh... is that so?
It's a story from a long time ago.
In the central city of Midchilda,
during a magical experiment,
a great mage created dimensional
interference, and was banished.
And this has something
to do with her?
Who knows? It might
not be her real name.
It's no good after all. I can't find her.
Fate must be using a very
efficient jamming barrier.
The canine familiar...
Most likely, she's
supporting her master.
Thanks to that, two of the
Jewel Seeds that we've found
have been taken by them already.
Do a thorough search to
make up for the loss.
We're counting on you.
Got it.
Fate isn't showing up.
Yeah. She seems to be collecting
different Jewel Seeds.
Yeah...
It's no good, Fate. Looks like a dud.
I see.
After all, it's pretty hard
to search in hiding,
so that they can't find us.
But we should do our best
for just a little longer.
And, on the tenth day after
we boarded the Arthra...
We've obtained three Jewel Seeds,
VIII, IX, and XII.
And Fate and Aruf found themselves
two more, serials II and V.
Another six...
The last six... We haven't
seen them around yet.
We have expanded the search area
to cover more than just land.
Since we are near an ocean,
they might have sunk into it.
Amy is searching for them,
along with that girl in black.
I see.
We came up empty-handed
again today.
It might take a long time
to find them all.
Nanoha, I'm sorry.
Aren't you lonely?
Not really. I'm not lonely at all.
I'm here with you, Yuuno.
I'm more or less okay
being by myself too.
When I was little, I was all alone a lot.
Back when I was really little,
Dad got into a huge accident at work,
and for a while, he couldn't
move out of bed.
He had just opened up the café,
so it wasn't as popular
as it is today, either.
So Mom and big brother
were always really busy.
Big sister was always
taking care of Dad.
So until recently, I was all alone
at my house a lot.
That's why I'm kind of used to it.
I see.
Come to think of it, I don't know
much about your family, Yuuno.
Yeah, I was all alone to begin with.
Really?
I didn't have parents,
but everyone in the clan
took care of me.
So everyone in the
Scrya clan is my family.
I see...
Yuuno, when everything
is taken care of,
let's talk a lot more
about all sorts of things.
Yeah, when everything
is taken care of.
When everything is taken care of...
When the Jewel Seed
problem is solved...
Right... I'm sure that we...
Emergency!
A large magical reaction
has been spotted
above the ocean within
the search area!
What are those kids doing?!
Alcus Curtas Agias...
Swift glimmering thunder,
fall under my guidance now.
Paruer Zaruer Brouzel...
The Jewel Seeds are
probably under the ocean.
So your plan to pour a stream of
electrical magic into the ocean,
to force an execution to
determine their location,
isn't a mistake...
But Fate!
To pound is lightning,
to echo is thunder.
Alcus Curtas Agias...
Found them...
The last six!
Pouring in this much magic, and
sealing them all on top of that...
Even with Fate's magical powers,
we have to be past the limit!
Aruf, please set up a spatial barrier
and back me up.
Sure, leave it to me!
So no matter who comes,
no matter what happens,
I'll protect her for sure!
Let's go, Bardiche. We'll do our best.
What's she's doing is
so unreasonable, it's disgusting.
It's quite reckless.
She's sure to ruin herself doing that.
It's beyond the limits of how much
magical power one person can emit!
Fate!
I'llhurry over to the site!
That won't be necessary.
Leave her alone, and
she will ruin herself.
Even if she doesn't ruin herself,
we can smite her when
all her power has been spent.
But...
We should prepare
to capture her now.
Roger.
Fate! Fate!
We must always make the
best choice for the situation.
Even if it seems very cruel to you,
that's the reality.
But...
Go.
Nanoha, go.
I'll open the gate, so go and get her...
But Yuuno!
The fact that I want to talk to Fate
has nothing to do with you!
It may have nothing to do with me.
But I want to be of help to you,
if you're in trouble.
Just like how you were for me.
You're...
I'm sorry.
Nanoha Takamachi is going
to disobey orders,
and take action on her own!
Transport to a location
within that girl's barrier!
Let's go, Raising Heart!
Winds to the sky,
stars to the heavens.
Glimmering light to these arms...
And the unyielding soul to this heart!
Raising Heart, set up!
Stand by ready.
Don't get in Fate's way!
You're wrong! We're not here
to fight against you!
Yuuno?!
That's absurd!
What are you two doing?!
I'm sorry. I'll apologize properly
later for disobeying orders.
But I can't leave her alone!
I'm sure that she's all on her own!
It's lonely, being all on your own.
I understand that, even just a tiny bit!
We have to stop the Jewel Seeds first,
or we'll be in a bad situation!
So for now, support their sealing.
Fate!
Help me. Let's stop the Jewel Seeds.
Power charge.
Supply complete.
We'll split it evenly into halves!
Yuuno and Aruf are stopping it for us.
So now's our chance!
When I say ready,
let's both seal it in one shot!
Shooting Mode.
When I was all alone,
and feeling lonely,
the one thing that I wanted
people to do most
wasn't to ask me if I was all right,
or to be nice to me.
Sealing Form, set up.
Bardiche?
Divine Buster, full power.
You can do it, right?
All right, my master.
Ready, set...
Thunder...
Divine...
Rage!
Buster!
The sealing of all six Jewel Seeds
has been confirmed.
What an irresponsible action.
But it's still amazing!
To share the same feelings...
To split the loneliness,
the sadness in half...
So that's it. I finally understand.
I want to share with her.
I want to be friends with you.
Dimensional interference?!
A magical attack is
headed towards our ship
and the combat air zone
from another dimension!
Impact in six!
Mother?!
Fate?!
Don't get...
..in our way!
There's only three?!
They're escaping! Capture them!
It's no good!
The lightning strike has stopped
the flincher from functioning!
Twenty-five seconds until
all functions are restored!
We can't keep up with them!
Put up anti-magic defense until
all functions have been restored.
Prepare for the next attack!
Yes, ma'am!
And also,
we will retrieve Nanoha,
Yuuno, and Chrono.
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
The situation is reaching its final turn!
Each hold their own
feelings in their heart,
in order to withstand the final storm.
And I also tell Fate how I really feel.
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 10:
Everybody's Separate Heart-felt Vows
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 10:
Everybody's Separate Heart-felt Vows
Episode 10: Everybody's
Separate Heart-felt Vows
Episode 10:
Everybody's Separate Heart-felt Vows
Lyrical, magical, in order
to start my true self.