Everyone, good job during practice today!
Yeah!
Somehow, I feel like I've improved a lot!
Summer vacation will be over soon, but we want to work harder on basketball.
Oh~!
We can't slack off!
Everyone's full of energy!
By the way, is everyone ready for the summer festival?
Of course!
My yukata is ready too!
I also asked my mum.
Oh~!
Hina wants to use a goldfish-patterned sash.
After all, it's the last event of the summer, right?
The people from my shopping district are really enthusiastic, too.
I'm sure it'll definitely be fun!
I wanna eat apricot candy again this year!
Oh~!
Hina will eat them too!
I want to scoop some goldfish!
Let's make some great memories, OK?!
Oh!
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Invoke the big halation
ano hi no chikai wo hatasu tame
あの日の誓いを果たすため
To fulfill that promise you swore on that day
hirake! new formation
開け! new formation
Open out, the new formation!
shisen no aizu yobiau
視線の合図呼び合う
Call out to each other with eye contact
kibou o nosete hanate arch
希望を乗せては放て arch
Bear and release the arch of hope
itsumo no toori ni ne
いつもの通りにね
Just like always
shinjiteru (makasete)
信じてる (まかせて)
I'll believe in you (Leave it to us)
mune ni te wo atete
胸に手を当てて
Bring your hand to your chest
hikiyoseta heijoushin
引き寄せた平常心
and tug at your usual attitude
kanaete dekita koto
叶えて来たこと
The things I fulfilled,
sorezorega oboeteru
それぞれが覚えてる
I can remember them all.
ano hi hisoka ni naita koto mo
あの日密かに泣いたことも
Including that day when you cried in secret.
onaji yumemiteru no wa
同じ夢見てるのは
Surely, we can't be the only ones
watashi tachi dakeja nain dayo ne
私たちだけじゃないんだよね
having the same dream.
me no mae ni arawareta
目の前に現れた
Appearing in front of our eyes,
yuru ganai hitomi hibana chirashite
揺るがない瞳火花散らして
is an unfaltering spark that's dispersing.
okose big halation
起こせ! big halation
Drop the big halation!
hiraku space e hashiriko me
開くスペースへ走り込め
Run into the open space!
wazukana sensation
僅かな sensation
The slight sensation
senobi shite ita kinou e
背伸びしていた昨日へ
when you were overstretched yesterday
wakare wo tsugetara
別れを告げたら
Announce your goodbyes,
egao wo tsunagete
笑顔を繋げて
Connect your smiles,
yume mita basho e hanate arch
夢見た場所へ放て arch
Release the arch to where you see your dreams
An Elementary Schooler's Innocent World!
I've been coaching these five girls at Keishin Academy for three months already.
It doesn't seem that long ago since I became their coach.
Every single day has been really fulfilling.
The five of them have taught me many things.
For me, the time spent with them is irreplaceable.
Shooting guard, Minato Tomoka.
Point guard, Nagatsuka Saki.
Centre, Kashii Airi.
Oh!
Small forward, Hakamada Hinata.
Oh~! Maho!
Power forward, Misawa Maho.
They're progressing and developing every day.
Everyone!
I've got some snacks!
Let's eat!
Delicious.
So good!
Everyone, eat up!
Yes!
Miho-nee, this makes you seem like a good person.
Well of course, since I'm the club advisor.
However, you're not a student, so you can't eat!
I take my words back.
Airi-chan, you look less intimidated.
Thank you!
Saki-chan, Tomoka-chan, both of your linkups are pretty good.
Looks like you're getting used to it.
However, Saki-chan, you gave Airi-chan too much leeway, right?
Yup.
I did a spin move out of instinct, but I would have wanted to see a showdown between Saki and Airi.
R-Really?
A direct 1-on-1 would've been more fun, I guess.
Let's do it next time, Airi!
Yup! I won't lose.
As usual, Aoi's so precise.
Well, since we're all girls, I understand a lot more things.
Honestly, it's great to have you here.
It's not like I'm doing it for you...
I'm back!
Welcome back.
Father wants to speak to you.
I'm back.
Tomoka, sit there for a moment.
OK.
You've been rather obsessed with basketball lately.
Studies, tea making, Japanese dance...
There'd be problems if you slack off on these things.
She missed twice in a row.
What happened?
Actually, yesterday...
My father scolded me.
Eh?
You can actually do something that warrants a telling off?
It happens a lot.
I see.
I was told not to go out so much during the rest of the summer vacation.
Actually, there is the summer festival this Saturday.
But he said "no" and refused to let me go.
Oh no... But why?
From the very start, my father was against me playing basketball.
And recently, I've been playing all the time.
It might have annoyed him.
I feel bad since everyone's going, but there's nothing I can do.
What?!
Mokkan, you can't come anymore?
That's boring.
You idiot, obviously Tomo wants to go as well!
Sorry about that.
Every family has its own circumstances, but Tomoka-chan, you're doing well in studies and your other activities.
Oh~...
Tomoka is a hard worker...
It might not work, but should we help you ask?
I'm happy that all of you want to help, but it's fine.
Everyone, enjoy yourselves at the summer festival, OK?
Nee-sama, is this OK?
Oh~!
Don't make it too tight!
Yanbaru!
Is it too short?
Genuine Okonomiyaki
Nagatsuka
Okonomiyaki
Tomo still can't make it?
At this rate, it'd be such a pity for Tomoka.
I should be minding my own business, but still...
Inbox
Nagatsuka Saki
Subject: To Hasegawa-san
Did Tomoka
Contact you?
Did Tomoka contact you?
No, I'll head over to Tomoka's house and find out.
Inbox
Nagatsuka Saki
Subject: To Hasegawa-san
I'll leave it to you.
All right!
Subaru-kun, you have a call.
It's from Tomoka-chan's mother!
Eh?
[Name] Minato Tomoka
[Birthdate] September 9th
[Blood Type] A
[Class] Grade 6, Class C
[Height] 142cm
[Chest Size] N/A (She is very concerned about this)
[A phrase about Subaru] Utmost respect from the heart!
Tomoka!
Subaru-san.
Subaru-san!
Growing my determination
Don't give up and do your best
Try your luck and fight! Chin-up!
wakatteiru yo
わかっているよ
I know perfectly
hitori no muryokusa nante
一人の無力さなんて
How weak a person is on their own
It's great to be young.
Good afternoon, Subaru-san.
Erm, thank you very much.
It's quite sad for Tomoka to be the only one at home.
Also, if you're with her, I'm more relieved.
Thank you, Mum!
I'll be off!
I didn't think that I'd be allowed out, so I was really surprised!
Yeah.
It's great.
I got to see you too.
The yukata looks really good on you.
Did we arrive too early?
Where are we supposed to meet?
It's supposed to be in front of the Apricot Candy stall.
But I can't reach them on my phone.
It'll be fine. We'll meet up soon.
Since we have time, let's take a look around.
Oh, that's...
A free throw stall, huh.
Since we're here, do you want to try it?
I'm in a yukata, so I might not be able to do well...
Okay, I'll give you a reward.
If you score two out of three, I'll listen to anything you say.
A-Anything?
Yeah, anything.
How about it?
Oh!
A winner!
All three, perfect!
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
That was amazing, Tomoka.
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
Free Throw Game
Perfect Score Prize
Suzuran
Gift Voucher
It was thanks to your support, Subaru-san.
Erm, Subaru-san.
Also...
What is it?
Erm...
About your promise...
I see.
The reward, right?
Y-Yes...
Actually...
Please watch the fireworks with me!
The ones that get launched at the end of this festival?
As close as possible...
...next to Subaru-san!
All right.
Let's watch the fireworks side-by-side.
New message
Minato Tomoka
Ah, it's from Tomoka.
Oh~!
Did Tomoka get here already?
Yeah, she's with Hasegawa-san, and they just left the free throw stall.
All right, let's meet up quick!
No, since they're finally alone together.
Then let's do our favourite things!
I want to go and scoop goldfish.
Oh~! Hina wants to go to the goldfish, too!
I want to eat chocolate bananas after that!
All right, let's split up. We'll meet afterwards.
Yup!
I want to eat cotton candy!
Wasn't this the meeting place?
Where's everyone?
Tomoka?
What's wrong?
Erm...
Could it be... You need the toilet?
Yes.
I've been holding it in, so...
You can't move?
All right, got it!
Er...
All right then.
Let's go.
Thank goodness we made it.
Old man, you're in the way.
Excuse me, but are you all right?
Yeah, but I dropped my glasses.
Oh dear.
Excuse me!
Someone dropped his glasses, so please help find it!
Ah, there it is.
Are these yours?
Yeah.
Thanks for helping me out.
Not at all.
It's great that we found them.
I came to find my daughter, but I'm just not used to the crowd.
I understand.
I'm not very good around them either.
Thank you. You helped me a lot.
Go for it, Nii-tan!
You're distracting me!
Man.
Hey, isn't that Matsuhi?
What are you doing? Shooting?
Oh, that looks interesting.
I wanna play, too!
Pass it over!
What's up with you, idiot Maho?!
Don't get in Nii-tan's way!
Why not?
Just because!
Maho's not allowed!
Tsubaki, Hiiragi.
Here you go. Do whatever you want.
Well, I don't think you can do anything with that though.
Let's go.
Wait up, Nii-tan!
As usual, Tsubaki and Hiiragi are still so harsh.
Don't worry about them!
All right, let's do this!
If you do it like that, you'd fall!
Ah, Maho, Saki!
Oh, shooting?
Maho!
Your underwear!
Subaru, don't look!
Congratulations!
That was mean, Subarun!
S-Sorry.
Maho, you were the one who leaned forward so much that you exposed yourself.
Then why don't you give it a try, Saki?
If you do it without showing your panties, I'll forgive him.
There's no way I could do that!
Why did it become like this...
Here, try it by locking your armpits more.
OK!
Ah, that was close.
Just a little more.
Yes, but thank you for teaching me!
Oh~!
It's delicious!
Hey!
What a great view!
This place is surprisingly good.
It's almost time for the fireworks.
Yes!
Tomoka.
F-Father!
I said that you are not allowed to leave the house.
I'm sorry, but...
We're going back.
Please wait.
Who are you?
I'm the coach of the Keishin Academy girls' basketball team, Hasegawa Subaru.
I'm extremely sorry for bringing Tomoka-san out on my own.
That's...
No, I was the one who got Mum-
No.
In the end, I broke your promise.
Sorry.
But Tomoka-san is not a bad girl!
She is well-mannered, and also serious in basketball.
Subaru-san...
Oh.
You make it sound like you know her very well.
She might be here, but that doesn't mean she's forgotten her promise to you.
It's simply her desire to be together with her teammates.
These are her precious friends.
Friends?
Tomoka doesn't need friends who play basketball.
Father!
How could you... That's horrible!
Oh, didn't you just...
You're Tomoka's coach?
Yes.
I'm their coach.
Tomo is important to us.
That's right!
If it weren't for Mokkan, I wouldn't have known basketball was so cool and fun!
Hina also likes Tomoka.
I like everyone a lot!
Because of Tomoka-chan, and thanks to Tomoka-chan, we're all able to play basketball!
I apologise for going out!
But please don't say such bad things about everyone.
Thanks to everyone and Subaru-san, basketball has become fun for me again.
That's why...
Don't take Tomoka away from everyone, and everyone away from Tomoka!
Please!
I understand.
Do as you like.
Father.
Excuse me!
I believe you know. Tomoka had painful memories because of basketball.
However, it seems like this time, she has made some great friends through basketball.
This might be a shameless request, but please take care of my daughter from now on.
I will!
Everything's going to be fine.
All right, about our promise...
OK!
Looks like you're at your best today.
Really?
Did something good happen?
My father told me to do my best at basketball!
I see.
Très bien.
Who are you?
Please have a match against me.
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつずけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show your guts cool say what it's the best! Yay!
karada mo kokoro mo SS dakedo
カラダもココロもSSだけど
Although our bodies and hearts might be small in size,
yume wa LL datte ii jan! ii jan!
夢はLLだっていいじゃん! いいじゃん!
isn't it good enough that our dreams are large!
seishun miman no onayami ippai
青春未満のお悩みいっぱい
We are full of worries about growing up
hitori janai kara norikoerareruyo
ひとりじゃないからのりこえられるよ
We're not alone, so we can get through this!
motto umaku naritaina
もっと うまく なりたいな!
I want to become better!
(motto)
(もっと)
(Much)
(umaku)
(うまく)
(better)
anatano (oh...) odoroku (sugoi) kao ga mitai no
あなたの(おぉ...)おどろく(スゴイ) 顔が見たいの
I want to see (boo~) your surprised (Impressive!) face!
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
chikyuu wa okki na Basket Ball
地球はおっきな Basket Ball
The Earth is just a big basketball.
ashita wo shinjite ikuyo! (hai i-ku-yo)
あしたを信じていくよ! (ハイ い・く・よ)
Believe in tomorrow and move forward! (Yes, let-us-go!)
mawase mawase mawase mawase
まわせ まわせ まわせ まわせ
Spin, spin, spin, spin
uchuu wa okkina Basket Court
宇宙はおっきなBasket Court
The universe is a big basketball court.
anata ni todoketai na... (se-no!)
あなたに届けたいな... (せーのっ)
I want it to reach you... (One, two!)
pasu! pasu! pasu!
パス! パス! パス!
Pass! Pass! Pass!
uketometekudasai!
受け止めてください!
Please receive it!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing! Ah-
Rolling! Rolling! hazumitsuzukero
Rolling! Rolling! はずみつづけろ
Rolling! Rolling! Continue bouncing forward!
Rolling! Rolling! Growing!
Show you guts cool say what saikou daze! Yay!
Show you guts cool say what 最高だぜっ! イェイ!
Show you guts cool say what is the best! Yay!
It has begun!
It has finally begun!
Maho, calm down!
Wow!
The preview is also really tight this time round!
Bark, bark!
Erm, when Subaru-san and I were practising in the morning-
Meow!
Wait, Tomo, be careful not to spoil!
Paooon!
Let's at least make a greeting!
One, two!
Next Time:
Flying Duel!
Please watch the next episode as well!