What do we do, Rider?
What now, mad dog?
Tokiomi...
I'll kill you!
Saber!
This isn't going in our favor.
If only we could use Saber's left hand...
You know that one more miracle will occur
With a gentle voice you predict a twisted future
So that nobody would have to cry ever again
we all scream and pray on fields stained red with blood
yet our pleas reach no one
I will be able to leave my solace behind
The moon's beautiful light
shines on all that makes up
the beginning
With eyes kept barely open I still see you far away
and trust your grief
Hey, Saber!
This isn't working.
Withdraw.
Don't be stupid...
We must stop him here!
We've run out of options.
Fall back for now.
I have an idea.
Listen, all.
Regardless of what our plan may be,
we must start by buying ourselves some time.
I shall draw him inside the Ionian Hetairoi.
However, not even all my fierce warriors together
will be able to slay that thing.
At best, the Reality Marble will stall him.
What then?
No idea.
Huh?
If I take in a thing of that size,
the Reality Marble will only last a few minutes.
You'll have to come up with a plan during that time.
Heroic Spirits,
I want you to find a path to victory.
Hey, kid...
You stay here, too.
Hey...
Once I deploy the barrier, I won't know what transpires outside.
Kid, should something happen, focus your mind and call me.
I will dispatch a messenger.
Saber! Lancer!
I leave the rest to you.
Very well.
Such a futile effort.
Mom!
What?
You may as well dive headlong into that mass of filth,
mongrel.
After all that talk,
this is all you have?
Is he expecting to die?
Kariya.
Here is my gift to you.
Intensive Einäscherung.
I-I'll kill you...
Tokiomi!
Zouken...
What should we do?
He will buy us time,
but if we can't use it to think of anything,
we'll be right back where we started.
Hey, Einzbern,
got any ideas?
Hey!
Well, um...
How does this work?
Iri.
No, I'm...
I mean...
I understand.
You are Rider's Master?
Perfect.
I wanted to talk to you, too.
Wh-Who are you?
It doesn't matter.
Caster's disappearance was your servant's work, yes?
That's right... I guess.
A question, then.
When Rider releases his Reality Marble,
can he deliver what it contains
at a specified location?
To a degree.
Within a hundred meters or so.
But it's possible.
Rider can decide where it will materialize.
Very well.
I'll wait for the right moment, then fire a signal flare.
Send Caster back directly under it.
Can you do that?
I can... I think.
Probably.
One more thing.
I need you to relay a message to Lancer.
Tell him that Saber's left hand holds an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Well, there was a message for you.
Something about Saber's left hand holding an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm...
Is that true, Saber?
Can it destroy Caster's monster with a single strike?
It can.
However, Lancer...
The weight of my sword is the weight of my pride.
The wound from my battle with you
is an honor, not a fetter.
Trading my left hand for the help of Diarmuid Ua Duibhne is worth ten thousand men.
Now, Saber...
I cannot forgive Caster's actions.
He would spread despair to all,
rejoicing as terror descends upon the world.
By the vows I took as a knight,
I cannot abide such evil.
Lancer, you mustn't.
Is it Saber who must win this fight?
Is it Lancer?
No, it is neither.
What must triumph here is the knight's path of chivalry.
Am I wrong, Heroic Spirit Arturia?
Lancer...
I shall rest my hope of victory upon your blade, King of Knights.
I place my faith in you, Saber.
I accept, Lancer.
And upon my sword,
I swear victory.
That's... from King Arthur's legend...
Saber!
Berserker?
He's...
You dare turn your back on me, mongrel?
Insolence!
What?
Saber!
What is Berserker doing?
I regain use of my left hand, and now this?
Regardless of whether it knows it or not,
a soul seeks joy.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin to minutely investigate
in order to shed light on his complicated circumstances.
This was due to your unconscious interest.
It's still too soon.
That shaking...
Rider's Reality Marble approaches its limit.
Rider...
I am Mithrenes, of the Hetairoi.
I have come as the King's ears.
I-I want him to wait for the signal,
then place Caster at the indicated point.
He can do it, right?
It's possible.
But we're nearly out of time.
Within the Reality Marble,
our forces cannot restrain that strange monster much longer.
I know!
I know that!
Damn it!
That stupid Berserker.
Can't we do anything about him?
I will go.
Lancer...
That's enough, mad warrior!
I have but one chance!
Archer...
That's it...
Right under that!
As you wish.
Really...
What took so long?
Now, Saber, show me.
I shall judge the true worth of your Heroic Spirit's glow.
The light...
It shines.
That sword...
It is the dream that all warriors—past, present, and future—
hold as their deaths approach.
A sad, exalted dream.
She carries their will as her pride,
bidding them to remain steadfast in their loyalty.
Now, the undefeated King sings aloud
the name of the miracle she holds in her hand.
Its name is...
Excalibur!
This light...
That's it, without doubt.
This light is...
This was the light, the blessing of bliss with Jeanne...
What have...
I...
Did you see that, King of Conquerors?
That was Saber's glow.
Even after such a display,
do you still refuse to accept her?
That light comes from her having taken all her people's hopes upon herself.
Its brightness is painful to look upon.
And when you consider that she who must bear that burden
is merely a dreaming little girl...
That little girl
forwent a happy childhood,
never fell in love,
and instead was cursed by her ideals only to end up as she is now.
It is too painful to gaze upon.
Is that not why she is so beautiful?
Her dreams were too much for her.
I imagine that, in the end, they destroyed the dreamer.
The tears of lamentation she surely shed as she died...
They must have been quite sweet to the taste.
Truly, you and I will never get along,
Babylonian King of Heroes.
Oh?
So you finally realized?
Then what will you do, Rider?
Will you let your steel give shape to your rage?
I'd very much like that...
But I have already exerted myself too much tonight to face one such as yourself.
Of course,
should you refuse to allow me passage,
I would have to fight back.
I don't mind.
I shall allow your retreat, King of Conquerors.
I wouldn't want to destroy you at anything less than your full strength.
I take it that your wounds suffered during your fight with that black thing haven't healed yet.
I repay provocation with death.
We can decide this next time, King of Heroes.
Our battle will be that which determines the winner of this Grail War.
I wouldn't be so certain...
I have yet to decide, Rider, whether you are indeed the only one worthy of facing
my ultimate treasure.
You fool, yearning for dreams beyond the reaches of mankind...
Only one in all of creation is worthy of appreciating its destructive powers...
and that is I, Gilgamesh.
Ephemeral and brilliant one,
fall to my embrace.
Such is my decision.
Episode 15
Golden Glow
Why is the sky so blue
as if it knows nothing of sadness
Each day our ruin advances a step, yet we do not falter
We are forever reborn, only to fail
You touched my soul when I had run from battle
and together we will walk into the future
with a strength empty of sin and vice
The sky is all around me, the wind sings in it
Will men one day
find the happiness they dreamed of?
You had faith when you saw the eyes of a child
I'm here right next to you
Making our way past this icy forest
I pray that the grief of this world will not sway your determination
I am Diarmuid Ua Duibhne, first spear of the knights of Fianna!
I am glad that I could meet you.
Indeed!
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain, accept your challenge.
Next Time:
The End of Honor
Come, then!
Here I go!