When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
please keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
So he's out training again?
He did say he would learn a
lethal technique this summer,
so he seems to be feeling the pressure a bit.
Namidabashi
It's so early in the morning.
What is he? An old boxer hitting 60?
I better work hard for Hinagiku, too.
Yeah, you're right. For
Hinagiku, too... Wait, what?
But his dedication is
what's so great about him.
It is not great!
Summer break is about to end soon,
so shouldn't he want to spend more
time with me because of that?!
He should give a little thought to
how Rocky felt when he lost Adrian!
Honestly! What in the world is he thinking?
Miss!
Hayate Ayasaki has arrived!
What's the big idea, Klaus?!
Well, I thought that I should
not let you be lonely.
So you came up with this plan to annoy me?
Yes!
Mr. Klaus, isn't your character
growing more and more distorted?
Kinda like this?
No, I don't mean that kind
of character distortion.
Besides, I am not feeling lonely.
I am just a little bored.
Oh-ho! If you're that bored,
why not just take the plunge and
establish an SOS Brigade or something?
You shouldn't be getting anime and
reality mixed up at your ripe old age.
Ouch!
Being told such a thing by the Miss...
I cannot go on living as a human being!
No helping it. I guess I'll
kill time by reading manga.
Study!
Hayate the Combat Butler
Fishing Lover Sanpei
A butler is one who serves.
A butler is one who waits upon others.
A butler is a formal guardian,
who is there to support his mistress
in all aspects of her life.
Yes!
This is about a boy who fights and puts
his life on the line for a girl...
A super combat battle story!
That was it for my screen time.
Oh, this was Klaus.
Daichi ni kaketa bokura no yukue
Our destination that we've
staked upon this earth
Tsuki-nukeru hayate no gotoku
Like the sudden gale that cuts across
Unmei ni makete
Giving in to fate
Shagami-komu nante tsumannai yo
And hunkering down is no fun
Sore ja kakko warui yo!
That's just not cool!
Uso kara deta makoto
Many a true word is spoken in jest
Koukai wa kitto mi kara deta sabi
Regret is probably reaping what you sowed
Zettai, nase ba naru!
Where there's a will,
there's definitely a way!
Ooki na hamon ni nomi-komareteku
As a great rippling wave swallows us up
Karada nami ni makasereba
Just let it take you
Kanchigai no yume
Dreams that are misguided
Mato-hazure no kitai
Hopes that are way off base
Tsuyoku omoeba itsuka tsukameru sa!
You'll grab them someday,
if you just have conviction
Daichi keri-age hashiri-dasou
Let's kick up the earth and start running
Kimama ni mau kaze no gotoku
Like the capricious breeze that dances about
I Wonder Who Came Up with the Sound
Effect 'Kapooon'. It's Awesome
What? The Miss said that?
She was acting quite sulky.
That summer break is almost over, but
you aren't paying any attention to her.
I see.
I've been too distracted by the
issue of my lethal technique lately.
Um, so, what is she doing now?
Reading manga without studying, as always.
Then I shall go keep her company right away.
There's no need for that.
What?
Usually, after she's read some manga, she...
Fishing Lover Sanpei
Hayate!
...gets influenced by it.
Let's go fishing!
Huh?
Sanzenin
Secret Base
Racetrack
Sanzenin
Residence
Sanzenin Lake?
Yes!
Sanzenin
Lake
Dome
Are there other lakes as well?
Yes. It's a tiny lake, though.
About 2km in diameter.
I-I see.
Tiny...
But can you really catch fish
in a lake on the property?
You can.
What?
The water comes from a spring, so it's clean.
And also, her grandfather brought
fish from all over the world,
which have created a unique ecosystem,
so the lake is like its own little cosmos.
It's easy to determine the dinner
menu based on what you catch,
so it's a very convenient lake.
What? Does that mean...
...you're the one doing the fishing, Maria?
Wait, so we're self-sufficient when
it comes to fish dishes at this house?
Sanzenin
Lake
Private Forest
Sanzenin
Dome
Ah! This is quite the lake!
It really is a nice, beautiful place.
Now, we're going to fish like crazy!
First, we'll do fly fishing!
What? Fly fishing? Aren't we starting
with something far too advanced?
Not to worry!
Sanpei in "Fishing Lover Sanpei"
was catching tons with fly fishing.
If Sanpei could do it,
there's no way I can't!
Miss, it's not good to get
manga and reality mixed up.
Not so fast!
But well, this is an anime.
Can't show you!
We'll start with fishing using
some kind of bait, like worms.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Fishing using worms is scary!
Then, instead of worms...
...how about some paste bait?
What?
In fishing,
it begins with crucians
and ends with crucians.
Crucians = Crucian Carp
Uh, could it be that you intend
to fish as well, Maria?
Yes, I think I'll enjoy
fishing some crucian carp
without having to think about
dinner ingredients for once.
That statement kind of muddles the issue
as to whether the Sanzenin household
is actually impressive or not...
Let's see...
First...
Oh, paste bait.
Hayate!
Yes?
I just saw something huge in the lake!
What? "Something"? Like what?
It's probably the guardian of
this lake! No doubt about it!
Oh, please.
I'm not lying!
Maria, is there such a thing in this...
She looks so focused, I can't
bring myself to disturb her.
More like, she's scary.
Well, that's fine.
Hayate, you just putter around
and catch some little fish.
Just watch! I will go catch
the guardian of this lake!
Yes, yes.
Then I think I'll use a lure.
I'll need to watch the Miss, so she
doesn't get tangled up in the line
and get hurt...
What? Pop?
Hayate, the rod went flying.
It's dangerous if you don't
hold on to it tightly.
I got one! Yaaah!
What?
What the?!
Ah, quite a shapely crucian carp.
Wow! You caught one already!
Oh, I seem to have gotten one, too!
Wow! Miss, this lake is really
good for fishing for some reason!
I-I see! Is that right?!
All right! I'll do it, too!
Fishing is boring.
You got tired of it incredibly quickly.
But my rods go flying!
That's because you don't hold on properly.
In that case, it might be better
to take a boat out into the lake.
A boat?
We're all alone out here, Miss.
I'm so happy, Hayate.
But fly fishing from a boat is difficult,
so perhaps it would be better to stay here...
Let's go, Hayate!
Miss?!
Please watch closely. This is
how you hold the rod and...
What do you think?
This way, you can cast properly, right?
R-R-Right.
B-But I never imagined that
the moment we were left alone,
that Hayate would sidle up to me...
He's bolder than I thought.
She's bound to fall off if she
swings a rod around on the boat,
so I need to make sure I keep her steady.
I suppose summer is almost over.
Y-Y-Y-Yeah...
A lot happened this summer, didn't it?
Like going to that seaside camp with everyone
and going to the amusement park with you...
T-True...
I had intended to come up with that lethal
technique during the summer break,
but in the end, I was unable to do it.
Even though you were so kind
as to offer your assistance...
I'm such a good-for-nothing, aren't I?
Tha... That's not true...
Shall we set off some sparklers
together after this?
Little cute ones, like you.
But well, I hope we catch the
guardian of the lake before that.
I don't... really care if we
don't catch him at this rate...
What?
Oh! Miss!
You got one!
Look, Miss! It's quite large! It just
might be the guardian of the lake!
Wha... What the?!
W-Watch out, Miss!
You idiot! Hayate, where do
you think you're grabbing me?!
Miss, let go of the rod!
You're the one who should let go, you idiot!
Are you all right?
You really shouldn't have pushed your limits.
You're tiny, after all.
Shut up! Hinagiku's about the same size, too!
Huh?
Miss?
Anyway, let's quickly collect
Maria and go home...
I told you, didn't I?
In fishing, it begins with
crucians and ends with crucians.
Y-Yes, you did...
It's the guardian...
So, how did you catch it?
That is classified information.
Incidentally, they apparently released
it because they couldn't eat it.
I'm telling you, it's all about the crucians.
(Dakara hera dattsuuno, hera.)
Lucky Cha Cha Cha! No, wrong!
(Rakkii cha cha cha! Ja nai!)
Miss, you need to get out of
those wet clothes quickly.
Shut up! This all happened
because of you, you know!
P-Pardon me.
You should both take a bath
before you catch a cold.
Y-You idiot! Take a bath
together with Hayate?!
Like hell I could do such
an embarrassing thing!
No one said anything about
bathing together with Hayate...
What'll I do? I've made the Miss angry again.
Come on, Hayate, you, too.
Don't be so depressed.
Let's get warmed up quickly.
Huh?
Uh, um... When you say,
"Let's get warmed up"...
Could it be that you're inviting
me to bathe with you...?
Huh?
Yeah, like that would happen.
What have you been thinking about?
I am a coward.
What?
Why did I act in a way that
seemed like I was rejecting him?
It sounds like there was yet
another episode between these two
that was open to misunderstanding.
Baths are great.
It's the crowning achievement of the
civilization that the Lilim created.
Monopolizing this enormous
bath all by myself,
I can feel all the little
mistakes floating away from me.
Though, it'd be even better if
I could enjoy this with Maria.
What?
It can't be...
...Maria?
M-Maria, this is so...  bold...
You go to such extremes to
avoid temporary contact.
What?!
Are you afraid of connecting
with other people?
What was that for?!
Shut up!
So, how've you been lately?
How have I been? Fine...
Say, don't you think the
water's a bit lukewarm?
What? You think so? Isn't this about normal?
Are you crazy?! This is totally lukewarm!
The water's got to be hot for us Edoites!
(Water-resistant)
Push.
H-Hey, are you sure about this?
If you mess around with that stuff...
Don't worry!
Let's see...
It's pretty DANGEROUS, man!
All right, I take this and...
Huh?
Damn! It's hard to press with my paw!
Hey! You shouldn't be so rough with it!
What was that noise just now?
I'll go check.
Hayate?!
We just heard a really loud noise...
Maria...
Crap!
Hey! Tama!
You're planning on running
away by yourself, aren't you?!
Hold it, Tama!
Tama?
What?
Hey! Don't run!
Hayate, what in the world...
What?
Uh, um...
Would you like to use this for now?
Th-Thank you...
It's over...
I wonder if I should apologize
to Hayate, after all.
And tell him I feel bad for acting
cold towards him earlier...
Hayate...
Of all people, to be seen
like that by Maria...
Hey! Hayate!
Hayate?
I can't go on living at
this residence any longer!
What?!
Maria...
What'll I do?
I never thought Hayate would
get that depressed over me...
At this rate, our love will come
to an end along with the summer!
I have to do something about it!
Hey, there, butler-in-debt!
What're you so down about?
You!
Now, now, you're still
young. Don't brood so much.
Whose fault do you think this is?
Then how's about making up for it by dying?
Isn't there something I could
do before I consider death?
Then how about something like this?
Let's start by fixing the bath
you broke along with the boiler.
That's fine, but you're the
one who broke everything.
Boiler Room
Caution: It's flammable, ya know!
What?
The Sanzenin residence
boiler is powered by AKIRA?
It's this mansion's boiler.
It's no ordinary beast.
Or more like,
I see markings that clearly indicate
messing with things will be a bad idea...
Don't mess with things here,
amateur. It's dangerous.
I don't want a tiger telling me that.
H-Hey, are you really sure about this?
Quit your grumbling.
Let's see...
Is someone here?
Maria!
M-Meow...
Hayate! And Tama...
What are you doing here?
Well, um, I thought I'd
fix the bath that I broke,
so I came down to the boiler room...
Actually, what are you doing here, Maria?
Well...
I had the same thought
as you to fix the bath...
She turned away from me!
This is terrible! She probably doesn't
even want to see my face anymore!
Somehow, I feel awkward seeing him
after that episode in the bath...
Huh?
What?!
Wh-Wh-What are you crying about, Hayate?!
Because... Because I...
Aw, man, this is kind of
becoming a pain in the butt.
No guy should bawl like that.
This is the boiler, right?
I'll fix this and get on out of here.
Huh?
Damn it!
What the hell?!
It's so hard to press with my paw!
Maria!
Are you all right, Maria?!
Maria?!
Hayate...
We're going to drown at this
rate, so I'll drain the water!
What?! But how?!
I'm going to borrow this for a bit.
What?
If I put a small crack in the wall,
the water pressure should do the rest.
We'll ride that wave.
Hang on to me tightly!
Hayate!
Here we go!
Are you all right, Maria?
Y-Yes, somehow...
But...
The boiler room is a mess now...
P-Pardon me.
Fireworks Set for Slightly Good Kids
Hayate!
Hayate?! Where are you?!
Right now, this is about all I
can do to return his feelings,
but someday, for sure...!
I really am a good-for-nothing, aren't I?
I'm always making trouble for others...
Maybe I'm not suited to
being a butler, after all.
You really are a strange one.
You're capable of doing anything flawlessly,
but you're unable to do anything
passably without making mistakes.
But the way you dedicate
yourself to these things...
I can't say it's not appealing.
Th-Thank you very much!
I'll continue to work hard to
be worthy of your kindness!
But well, please do fix the bath.
I will! Let me get right to it!
Oh, it doesn't have to be now...
M-Maria...
Hayate...
Ha-ya-te!
M-Miss...
To think you would go for Maria
when you already have me...
For real?!
You despicable scoundrel!
And thus, the butler-in-debt's
fond summer memories
met an untimely demise in the night sky.
So anyway, next episode, we finally
enter the new school term.
He will be fighting the
student council members
as well as the teachers' conspiracies!
Good show!
Naida kokoro no ho ni kaze ga fuki-nuketetta
A breeze crossed the wilted sail of my heart
Kimochi yureru soshite Lose My Way
My feelings waver and then I lose my way
Zutto kimi ga iru nara ii ka
I guess if you'll always be here, it's okay
Sore mo waruku wa nai So I Go Together
That's not so bad, so I go together
Tenki-yohou nante nai
Weather forecasts don't exist
Zenbu kibun-shidai
It's all mood-dependent
Nanimo shinpai nai
There's nothing to worry about
Makasete! Jiyuu-jizai
Leave it to me! Perfectly free
Keri-ageta kutsu ni
On the shoe that I kick up
"Put A Wish" Zettai hareru!
"Put a Wish" it'll definitely clear up!
Kekka wa... I'm Looking At Nothing...
And the result is, I'm looking at nothing
Mou ichido, yari-naoshi!
One more time, a do-over!
Tama ni wa kakete-miyou
I'll try betting once in a while
Nee kimi ni yudanete-mitai
Hey, I want to try entrusting you with it
Sassou to kake-nukete To Fly
Running through gallantly, to fly
Harema ga mieru The Sky
I can see a break in the weather, the sky
Shinjiteta yo
I had faith
Soshite Make My Way
And then, I make my way
Sotto sashi-dasu kimi no te de
With the hand you quietly reach out
Muteki ni nareru kara So I Go Together
I can become invincible, so I go together
Hoshi ga kirei da ashita mo hareru sa
Stars so beautiful, it'll
be clear again tomorrow
This is Isumi...
...and Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
A good morning to yogurt! I'm Nagi Sanzenin.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Isumi Saginomiya.
Isumi, this song is so soothing, isn't it?
Oh, my dear Hayate!
Hayate, you said the same
thing to Maria, too!
What? Did I?
Serving as a main host in this
segment is too much for you, Hayate!
Pardon me, Miss.
You both seem to having such fun.
And so, Sakuya will be
appearing starting next time.
Fare-well-pickled scallions!
Preview
Nice to meet you!
I'm Makimura and I'll be in charge
of this class starting today.
The next episode of "Hayate
the Combat Butler" is...
What?! What's the developer of
the caregiver robot doing here?
This is bad. At this rate,
my position at Hakuou...
No, my position in this very
anime is extremely precarious!
So there you have it, Ayasaki!
You're going to help me!
No, thank you.
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"A Non-Kiddy Genius Teacher Appears".
Don't get depressed, Hayata!
You know, how do I say this?
I like being punished, too.
A Non-Kiddy Genius Teacher Appears
Can you believe it?