Please—
Marry me!
Well, well, I guess it can't be helped.
If you insist so much, I'll marry you.
Look, look, Ryu-chan.
Taiga-chan had this many babies.
They're your kids.
It was a dream.
This is what happens when I rent crappy DVDs over my summer break.
It was just a dream, but that would be the worst future ever.
Hey, Taiga.
I had an unpleasant dream.
Huh?
You were a dog, and the dog was my husband…
Anyway, it was the worst dream ever.
A warning dream?
Yeah, the worst possible future is waiting for us unless we take countermeasures against it.
It's a warning.
So, one of us should give our full support to the other starting tomorrow during the trip.
I get that, but... why badminton?
Like I said...
We're going to decide on the supporter.
Don't ever use fire, understood?
Don't forget to mix the pickle paste.
Don't forget to change Inko-chan's water every day and night.
Read my note for the rest.
Well, I'm going now.
Go... where to?
I told you before, the trip.
See ya, Ya-chan.
Looks like the weather will be pretty nice.
I'm counting on you for that so-called plan.
Hey...
are you really sure?
Yes! I'll let you be winner so just get this off of me!
If it wasn't for that stupid dog's intervention, I would have won.
You were punished for trying to compete with me in your strongest sport.
Sheesh, nothing good happens when dogs are involved.
But, is this really going to work out?
Just leave it to me.
By the time this trip is over you and Minorin will be—
What is it, is something wrong?
Good morning!
You two are right on time!
Well done, that's admirable!
What's wrong, where's your energy?!
Come on, raise your voice!
What the hell is that?
Y-Yeah...
What the—?
Wow, the weather is perfect, too.
You mustn't look!
Yeah...
Oh yeah, Amin isn't here yet.
We still have a bit until our meeting time.
Oh, I know!
Huh, what's with them?
Nobody's here.
H-Hey.
You're two minutes late, Ami!
Good morning, Amin!
You're late, you stupid chihuahua!
I wonder where everyone is?
Hey! Stop running you stupid chihuahua!
We're right here Ami!
Wow, this is really delicious!
It has a plum in it, and it's really tasty!
That's Takasu for ya.
Would you like to be my bride?
No way.
Aww, you're so mean.
Oh, now that I think about it...
Aisaka-san doesn't seem to be here, is she late?
Takasu-kun, you should conta—
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, you were awake stupid chihuahua?
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open.
Wha—?
You don't have to fight on a trip, too.
More importantly, what were you doing over summer break, Kawashima?
Me?
I was stuck working the whole time.
So, you started working again?
What about you Minorin?
After school club, part-time job...
...after school club, part-time job...
...after school club, after school club, part-time job...
...after school club, part-time job, after school club—
What about you Taiga?
I was making...
Huh, what is it Taiga?
...this.
I just heard a weird voice say, "senpai," what is this?!
It's a collection of songs that have mysterious ghost voices in them.
I knew it!
No, it called for me!
Aisaka, you like horror related things?
Wha—?
Umm, I might.
That's unexpected.
Although, it's also unexpected that Kushieda can't stand scary stuff.
Yeah, yeah, I totally can't stand it!
I can't stand it sooo much that I—
Minorin really can't stand occult, horror, and ghost related things.
That's why the two of us will scare Minorin to bits!
Once she's fallen into the depths of fear, you'll save her.
"I'll protect Kushieda!" That's what you'll say.
The "Scare Minorin and Have a Knight Save Her" plan.
Anyway, I absolutely forbid scary stories!
Wow!
The sea!
Damn it... how far are you going to make us walk?
Can't you see it yet?
Head around behind here.
You should be able to get straight onto the deck.
This is Amin's villa?
We get to stay here?
That's right Minori-chan.
That's awesome, it's great!
Although, we have to clean up first.
No one has been here since last year.
S-Since last year?!
Y-Yeah.
This... will be a gruesome battle.
What?!
But this beautiful beach is right in front of our eyes!
We can clean later, later!
That's true, we can clean afterwards!
M-Me, too!
I'm going, too, What about you Takasu-kun?
Why am I cleaning… alone?
It feels sooo good!
Hey, hey.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Doesn't that kind of look like someone's head?
It's a beached corpse!
What should I do?! I let myself touch its juices!
Looks like they're having fun.
So you really came, Yuusaku.
Of course I would.
If Takasu's going, there's no way that I, his best friend, wouldn't come along.
What about the student council?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Takasu!
Ami said to go buy the groceries.
Apparently there's a bike in the storeroom.
A bike?
Oh, take Taiga in that case.
Aisaka's going?
I-I'm not going.
B-Bikes are scary, so...
What?!
Drive carefully.
Yeah, got it.
Later!
Aww man.
You blew the chance to be alone together.
I have a reason!
We have to find a place to use for our plan before those two get back.
Why can't you be honest and just say you were shy—
There was a mosquito, a mosquito.
Sheesh...
A good place we can use...?
This is... the wash room.
I need to clean this place, too—huh?!
W-Who is it?
Sorry!
I just didn't notice!
Takasu-kun?
I-I'll get out now.
Wha—
You're pretty daring...
Barging in when a girl's showering.
I-It wasn't on purpose!
It's okay, we don't have to tell anyone.
What are you talking about?
Come on, don't you want to do it?
Wha—do what?!
Clean the bathroom!
Oh my, what on earth were you expecting?
What's with that face? It's hilarious!
Taiga~!
Huh?
The stupid chi?
Made it look like she was showering...
and fiddled with your pure heart?
So, are you done investigating the second floor?
Useless!
This is why you get manipulated so easily by that stupid chi!
Fine, I'll have a look myself.
While I'm at it, I'll go complain to that stupid chi!
Hey, stupid chi!
That stupid chi was really showering this time…
She was just like, bam... bam...
and BAM—!
That's unnecessary!
I'm back!
You sure bought a lot.
Where's Kitamura?
He said he was going to park the bike.
I-Is that so?
Oh, I'll hold it.
T-That's alright.
You did the shopping for us.
You sure?
W-What's wrong?
W-Well, something just... something was on my neck.
It's just your imagination.
You're right.
It has to be, right?
No, I definitely felt something there!
It was slimy or rather seaweed-ish.
It does smell like seaweed! It is seaweed!
It's like a creature's ghost that was entangled by seaweed—
Entanglement by seaweed means it's an otter's corpse.
An otter full of seaweed?!
Is it the curse of the otter and seaweed?!
No!
I don't want the spicy flavor!
I want the spicy one!
I can't eat it unless it's sweet!
Hey, Ryuuji!
I know, I'll make a sweet one for you later.
Are you giving special treatment to Aisaka-san again?
Girls won't like you if you do stuff like that.
Say for instance... Minori-chan.
Did you call me?
It's almost ready?
You're well prepared.
Y-Yeah...
All that's left is to put the sauce in.
Hey, you guys should get ready to eat, too.
Oh, is it time to prepare for dinner already?
I'll help set up the table.
Y-You...
H-Hey, Taiga?!
Yuusaku, are you insane?!
Oh, sorry, I just heard Takasu's voice and...
I forgot that there were girls here, too.
What are you stupid?!
Taiga, get a hold of yourself!
Sorry, sorry.
You god-sent child of narcissism!
Give me your nudies!
Oh come on, cut it out.
You can't say that when you look like that.
Stop pretending to be innocent!
Hey, stop it.
That's good, that's good!
I think... I just saw something... black and fluffy...
I-It was probably the seaweed ghost.
Sea—
weed?
Kushieda?!
Yuusaku, you are the worst...
Sorry...
Just get out of here you!
Oh.
Beware everyone, there's an evil spirit in this building.
Is there something I can do?
Make the curry as spicy as you can.
Alright.
Wow, it looks good!
I just made it with what was at hand, but I made it as spicy as I could.
Alright!
Let's eat!
Thanks for the meal.
Yeah, this works.
Yeah, it tastes good.
Hmm... it's not as spicy as I thought it'd be.
Is that so?
Yeah.
You want some, too, Taiga?
You're right, it's not that—
Minorin?
It's freakin' spicy!
My throat is—!
It's hot—No, it hurts!
Here it comes! Wam-bam thank you very much!
Alright! Here it comes again!
A-Are you guys okay?
Takasu-kun!
You're freakin' awesome!
It's insanely spicy and insanely delicious!
You're right, it mysteriously lures me in.
I feel kind of strange.
Oh, there are seconds, too.
Seconds!
Man, I thought I was gonna die.
Alright, I'll wash the dishes.
Oh, I'll—
What is it?
I wonder if it's because I had something spicy.
I want some medicine for my stomach ache.
A stomach ache?
But the medicine is—
Aisaka, you're not feeling well?
I brought some stomach ache medicine.
You want to come along?
It's in my room.
W-What, t-that's—
Alright, I'll leave it to you.
Wha—Hold on—!
It's a chance to be alone together, right?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing really.
Well, I'll leave it to ya.
Alright.
Hey-hey.
My stomach hurts, too.
Huh?
Just kidding!
What's with you?
Nothing.
You were just spaced out.
I wouldn't get bored looking at you.
Was that a compliment?
Hmm, I wonder...
What's that supposed to mean?
More importantly, would you like to go out to the bea—
Hey, Takasu-kun.
Can you get the cup over there?
Oh, I'll do it.
Sorry, what were you saying?
Nothing.
Was that enough water?
How is it?
Does it seem like it's working?
Probably...
Really? I'm glad.
When I see you in pain, I feel painful, too.
Oh yeah, you want to lie down since you're in pain?
Wow, your washing techniques are amazing.
Well, I do it a lot at my part-time job, you know.
Your curry was amazing as well, Takasu-kun.
Oh, not really.
I know.
I'll give you something nice for helping me.
Don't tell anyone, okay?
Takasu-kun, does the maccha taste good?
Uh—Yeah, it's good.
The red beans are iffy.
Aren't the stars amazing?
T-They're beautiful.
It's just the two of us.
Is it my chance?
K-Kushieda, do you h-have a b-boyfriend?
Do you think that seaweed ghost is still around?
What?
Takasu-kun, have you ever seen a ghost?
Huh?
No... I haven't.
I believe that ghosts are real.
But I've never seen one and I don't believe those that say they have.
Okay...
And there's another thing that I think about similarly.
I believe that one day I'll fall in love, marry, and live happily.
But I've never had that feeling with someone before.
The people out there who fall in love like it's so normal... seem so far away.
Because I can't see it.
There aren't ghosts after all.
I'll never see any for the rest of my life.
I've kind of almost given up.
So the answer to your question is that I don't have a boyfriend.
What about you, Takasu-kun?
Can you see ghosts?
I think...
I might just want to see them.
That's why I go to haunted places and watch scary DVDs.
I also think...
People with the sixth sense were probably surprised the first time they saw a ghost.
Some people probably see them, but pretend they don't,
and some may have worked so hard and were finally able to see them.
That's why you shouldn't decide that you'll never see any for the rest of your life.
What's that?!
A UFO?!
Huh? Oh, that's a satellite.
A satellite?
Aww, I thought it was a UFO.
I hope you get to see a ghost one day, Kushieda.
I-I think there's a ghost out there that wants to be seen by you.
I guess that's why weird stuff keeps happening today.
The seaweed ghost—it's trying to attract my attention.
What's with you all of a sudden?
I wonder if I'll see one someday.
Huh?
Oh, nothing!
You're a strange one...
Hey Ryuuji, It seems like my stomach's feeling better.
Okay... and?
Phew, I ate a lot!
And for some reason I did, too.
Hey, what should we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm talking about the plan.
It's not going well for you at all.
And what about you?
I-I'm supposed to be the supporter this time.
Sheesh, but I sure am tired.
I was wondering how blissful it would be to be with Kitamura-kun all day long, but...
It seems I'd probably die young of nervousness.
That's true.
Even though I'm totally fine when I'm with you.
What's that supposed to mean? That's rude.
It's so stupid. Even though we're in this huge room, we closely sit together.
I guess my body's used to that cramped apartment.
Heh, you...
Ryuuji, I thought about it, but...
That dream... it might be...
Hey, what's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm going to sleep.
Huh?
Oh, good night.
What the—?
Did I leave my bag in here?
What the hell is this?
And it's kind of slimy, too.
Ryuuji! What'd you do make to this?
It was in my bag, but, it was warm when I touched it just now.
It's as if someone's just been wearing it.
M-My room's strange, too.
There's long hair on my pillow.
W-What was that?
I-It must be—
T-This has to be a dream, right?
Y-Yeah, it's a dream.
It's the continuation of that dream where we're dogs living in a dog house.
If that's the case, we'll wake up eventually, right?
We will, we will!
Won't we?
Scary, scary, scary!
Horror's scary! Ghosts are scary!
Demon beasts are scary!
Calm down Kushieda!
But... the scariest thing might be a UFO.