It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps god's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
What's yer name?
Original
Kofune Mio.
When were ya born?
Who gave birth to ya?
Yesterday, at the wake.
Mother scanned Mio there.
Later that night...
I was born in the cave.
When ya say "Mother,"
ya mean Haine in Shiori's body, right?
Yes.
Did ya cut the brakes on Mio's bike?
To kill me?
Nurse's Office
Not necessarily.
It was just more convenient if ya were in the hospital.
It's more convenient to kill Mio in the hospital and take her place?
Yes, since Dr. Hishigata is an ally of the shadows.
Was that Haine's order?
No, I just wanted to do that.
But I failed.
I didn't know that they were gonna make a shadow of Mio.
Don't worry, Tokiko.
I don't even know why I wanted to kill her anymore.
Haine created ya to find Ushio's shadow.
She is a traitor.
I can't copy people.
Can ya do it?
There are two types of copying.
Taking the form of the person we copy, or giving birth to a new shadow.
Giving birth?
We children can give birth to a new shadow only once.
"Children"?
Haine can give birth as many times as she wants,
but since she's become weak, it's no longer easy fer her.
Shadows at the grandchild level can't give birth.
Day 1
Shadows can transform multiple times.
Day 2
Regardless of which type of copy we are, we have one week to erase the original, or we turn into mud and disappear.
Day 3
Day 4
Day 5
Day 6
Day 7
I have six more days to live, although I don't really care.
That's all I know.
Sorry, Shin.
I don't have much useful information.
Oh, that's fine.
Y-Ya don't need to apologize!
Hey, that's a shadow, Sou.
What? Uh, but...
Sou?
Dammit!
This is confusing!
Haine needs to consume a lot
of people for her to be revived.
She's giving birth to build an army for that.
Dad and I tried to revive Haine for my mother's sake.
We thought she needed the meals for that purpose,
but they had a different objective.
And the old man knew everything?
Unbelievable.
He doesn't care if we all die.
Dad...
It's hard to take it in,
but Dr. Hishigata must know Haine's true objective.
I'm meeting him tonight at 10 o'clock.
Okay, then we know what to do next.
We're going to Hishigata Clinic.
It's so itchy!
There are so many mosquitoes here!
Protect Mio.
Is that an order?
I dunno if I'd call it that...
but yeah, I guess.
Shin, are ya afraid of me?
Yer so far away.
I-I'd be lying if I said no.
Ya killed me over and over, ya know.
That was in another world.
I haven't killed anyone yet.
Can I ask ya something too?
Sure.
Did ya have a girlfriend in Tokyo?
A girl—
Girlfriend?!
Wh-What are ya asking him?!
He sometimes speaks like they do in Tokyo.
Ain't it suspicious?
I ain't got a girlfriend.
People just don't understand the Wakayama dialect in Tokyo.
I try to blend in with the locals.
Well, I was just joking.
Have ya ever wondered why I don't call ya "Brother"?
Listen, I'll follow yer order and protect Mio.
But yer the only one who can really protect Mio.
I-I don't know what she's talking about!
Let's just go, Shin!
Okay...
Hishigata Clinic
It's open.
What's going on?
Everything in our house is gone.
Our rooms are empty too.
Desks, closets, beds... everything.
Ms. Nagumo, is this...
Yes.
Fortunately, there aren't any human stains.
It seems that only things were erased.
Was there something that they didn't want us to see?
Although it seems like they erased everything.
They had to hide something but didn't know where it was.
That's my impression.
This has to be my old man!
That's why he's not here!
Our mom is gone too.
What the hell is happening?!
Shinpei!
Ya felt a shadow over here, didn't ya, Ushio?
Yes.
Ow!
Don't squeeze so hard! It cuts off the blood flow!
Are ya scared?
O-Of course I'm scared!
I hate hospitals at night...
I hear something.
It's not coming.
What's that sound?
Is something stuck in the door at the basement level?
Bullet holes.
It looks like there was a fight here.
Be careful.
I sense shadows below us.
What's in the basement?
The morgue.
The morgue?
It's fine.
The only thing down there is Ushio's body that Dad didn't cremate.
Oh, right.
I guess it ain't scary if it's my body.
That's how it works?
Feeling fear shows that your survival instincts are functioning properly.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Shadows are scarier than ghosts.
Brace yourselves.
That's Mom's wheelchair.
Why's it here?
Behind ya!
Morgue
Did ya see its face?
No.
Th-There's nothing here.
Seriously?
I had no idea this place was under our house.
It's gone.
Ushio's body was here?
Yes.
Ushio could've recovered if she was able to scan the original.
They must've decided it was best not to leave it here until tomorrow.
Want to restart?
No, let's keep going.
We need to find Sou's parents.
Understood.
What's this passage, Toki?
It connects to Hiruko's grotto.
There was an entrance here.
We used it to bring meals to Haine.
It's a different route than the old path from the old clinic.
I feel a subtle presence of shadows.
The one from earlier must've gone in here.
It's close.
We're almost upon it.
Mom?
Summer Time Rendering
What's going on?!
Don't shoot!
Please don't shoot her!
But yer dad will die!
Ushio!
It's okay, Sou.
I'll bring her back.
Dad!
He's not breathing.
Lemme do it!
C'mon, old man! Don't die on me!
Don't go without explaining yerself!
Wake up, old man!
Sou?
Stop keeping secrets.
We're family.
How is Chitose... your mother?
I cut her link with Haine.
She'll wake up soon.
I see.
I never thought...
you'd reach this point so soon.
So Haine must've thought...
that I'd talk.
No point in hiding anything.
We can just copy yer data.
Tokiko, kill them.
Dad!
Kill them!
If you kill them, Haine will trust me again.
No, Dad.
Ya got it all wrong.
They have no intention of keeping their promises.
I'm so disappointed in you, Tokiko.
Step back, Sou.
Your gun is too close.
Doctor...
What... the...
You...
Too bad.
Do ya think they'll be okay?
No need to worry.
They've got Ushio and Ms. Nagumo, plus yer shadow.
That's my biggest worry!
I still can't trust that thing.
I'm surprised ya let it copy ya.
When a shadow copies ya, it sees yer whole body and heart.
Yeah.
I wanted ya to know all of me.
I-I can't believe ya can say that with a straight face!
I'm done keeping secrets.
Mio.
Do ya trust me a bit now?
Yeah, thanks.
Really?
Ya can copy me if ya don't believe my words.
Never.
I don't wanna know what's in yer heart.
Sou!
Ya shot Tokiko!
How could ya?!
Kill me.
Ya old fool!
Playing with people's lives...
Kill me.
Aren't ya a doctor?
How can a doctor talk about killing so easily?!
Tell me!
So ya won't say anything.
Fine.
Mio, do it.
I can't copy him.
He has immunity.
I see.
Then we'll have to make him talk.
Wait.
That can't be!
You can't copy me?
Ya already had a shadow, but it died.
People like y'all have immunity and can't be copied again.
It can't be...
My shadow can't be created?
That's what I'm saying.
Doctor...
Chitose...
What was it all for, then?
Negoro.
Doctor, I'll be leaving now.
I got what I came for.
She's out of range.
Doctor, I have a message from Shide.
"We appreciate the Hishigata family for the support you provided.
However, it's over now.
Take care."
I also have a message for Ajiro Shinpei.
"It seems you didn't die.
I'm fed up with your stubbornness.
There's nothing you can do.
Everything will end in two days."
Stop, dammit!
Don't go!
Don't go after her.
But...
She was using Ushio's body as bait to lure us in.
Bringing up the time limit was an attempt to provoke us.
If we take the bait, we're done.
But I can't just let it go, Shinpei!
That was the shadow we saw earlier!
Calm down, Sis.
Shin feels the worst about this.
Ya can't just let yer emotions drive yer actions.
Take a bird's-eye view of things and turn yer anger and regret into weapons.
Shinpei...
Dr. Hishigata, does it mean anything for you to keep quiet any longer?
Get my daughter.
Bring me the real Tokiko.
Are you awake?
Sei.
Wh-Where am I?
I gave Chitose the same memories I showed ya.
I'm sorry, Chitose.
Sou's mother didn't realize that she was a shadow.
She was created that way.
I know you're trying to stop the ceremony,
but should you really kill Haine?
What do you mean?
All the shadows will die with Haine.
That means your Ushio will die too!
Ushio.
It's fine!
I should've been dead fer two days already.
I'm lucky to even have this bonus time being alive.
If I can, I want to use the time to help save everyone.
Defeating Haine will solve everything, right?
That's good news!
In that case, I'll gladly take her down!
She's right.
I'm embarrassed that I even hesitated.
Right?
Yeah.
Dr. Hishigata, what is Haine planning after being revived?
She just wants to go back home.
Back to her hometown, across the deep and dark ocean.
No being from this world can reach that place,
unless it's a shadow.
Haine wants to just take shadows.
Just the family that she chose.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
B-But that's...
It's possible if she regains her power.
But even now I still see visions of you
It's a land without time.
Chitose and I were going to become shadows and live there forever.
In reality I only have vivid memories
Sou and Tokiko were also supposed to join us in the end.
To play in my head over and over again
That's why ya thought it was okay if ya killed us?!
Yer so selfish!
Are ya a fool?
Even if it's all just a lie
That's the reason?
Please be close by my side
Yer so self-centered and hopeless.
Right next to me
Thanks fer saving me.
I fell for you before too long
But time alone was what progressed
Chitose...
But we need to finish this.
I wanna go back
Sou, Tokiko.
I'm so glad to have seen ya grow until now.
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
No, Chitose!
I have no reason to live if you die!
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
No, ya have our children.
Ya have the people of this island who need ya.
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
Like Shinpei said, this ain't over.
Ya can still make up fer yer mistakes.
True to myself
But it's too late for that
What is this?
This is the clinic's secret records that Tokiko hid for me.
Diagnosed with Capgras syndrome,
or the local disease of shadow sickness,
the people on this list are actually
those whom Haine has consumed.
Your parents' names are on the list, Shinpei.
But my parents' boat accidentally sank when they were working.
They found Hiruko's grotto and planned to make it public.
That's why they were killed.
It was made to look like an accident.
Shide killed them, and I switched the bodies to deliver to Haine.
I'm sorry.
What? Is that all ya have to say?
You know the true identity of Shide, don't you?
Yes.
Look at this photograph.
Shide is Haine's protector and the first child she bore.
His original name was Hishigata Shidehiko,
the founder of Hishigata Clinic and its first director.
Next time
Decision