Ah geez.
It's like I'm stuck between a rock and a hard place.
What's up?
TL Note: Purin is like custard pudding.
Well, my producer and cameraman have had a disagreement about purin.
Who cares, you should just say you don't care as always.
You don't have to tell me that, but it's kind of tiring.
It's not like they're kids. Who cares about purin anyway?
Both of them are custard-brain idiots!
Sweets are the best medicine when angry.
Don't you mean calcium?
It's been scientifically proven that it's good to drink milk.
Palmtop Tiger, I think you should drink milk.
It'll make your breasts bigger.
Really?
I'm absolutely, seriously sure!
How about we go get some tasty purin?
Sure thing.
Hurray for Gluttons
Purin, a child's sweet
Purine, is there a lot ? Is there little ?
Toradora SOS!
Hurray for gluttons!
Purin, a child's sweet.
Purine, is there a lot?
Is there little?
The purin here is superb!
This is great!
Seconds please!
Minorin!
I've come again!
Hey, Taiga, I've been waiting for this day.
Minorin, you were waiting for me?!
Wah! The Super Fast Brr Brr Belt!
You can get rid of cellulite just by wearing it for ten minutes.
That's amazing, Minorin!
Hey, let me have a look.
Of course, of course,
I'm always a friend of those trying to lose weight.
Let me have it!
I said no!
There's no need to fight for it.
So what are you up to today?
Right, Takasu-kun suggested we go get some tasty purin.
The purin here is delicious.
It has the smooth taste I remembered from my childhood.
You blockhead!
You've got no idea about tasty purin!
Smooth taste?!
Let me tell you something about that!
You and me are having a purin duel!
Oh, it looks so yummy.
To tell you the truth either one is good.
It's all the same in your stomach.
First you should have a bite of "Jonny's Custard Pudding" which I chose!
It's tasty, tasty, oh so tasty!
Oh, it certainly was good.
TL Note: Purine is a colourless crystalline organic base.
It's called "purin" but, it turns out that there is no purine in purin.
It can be found in fish and meat.
For example, 100g of chicken has 312.2mg of purine,
TL Note: Chicken grunt is a type of fish.
There is also 305.5mg of it in the soft roe of chicken grunt.
When purine is metabolised it turns into uric acid, which is the reason for flatulence.
It is said that if the patient has excessive flatulence from overindulging in purine, it may lead to deteriorating symptoms.
Incidentally, flatulence is said to arise due to a rise in crystallising uric acid within bent pockets in the gut.
In my opinion, the pain is a by-product from the body trying to expel the trapped air.
I don't get it, is he trying to be a nutritionist?
He's really knowledgeable, but somehow sounds really stupid.
We're past the era where more calories meant a better taste.
Try the masterpiece of B-class gourmet, the puccina purin!
It's tasty!
Tasty!
So tasty my soul's gonna pop out!
Oh, it certainly was good.
This puccina purin looks a bit like Mt. Fuji.
Mt. Fuji is a dormant volcano but has erupted several times in the past.
The last eruption was in the Edo period, Genroku era.
The volcanic ash reached the city of Edo about 100km away.
There was no lava, but after that Edo looked like a waste land...
Her explanation is too long. Is she pretending to be a professor?
This one looks stupid as well.
Um, what should we do?
I don't really care who wins anyway.
As always, we can't quite choose the winner.
A great dual from both sides. I was very moved.
In the Yamagata dialect "abododogewa" means "do you eat sticky rice cake?"
Which is why this duel is a tie!
Purin, purin, pu~ri~n~!
Hey, is it true that if you eat eel and dried plum together you'll get sick?
What? Really?
I've never tried it.
Oh yeah, I heard that it's really good for you.
Really?
No way!
I'm going to give that a try.
Today's Inko
Pig
B-b-b-b-bbb-b-b-b-buta
Buta-buta-bu-bu-bu-buta-buta-butaman-butaman-butaman
Steamed yeast bun with minced pork filling
Man-man-man-ma-mangekyou.
Kaleidoscope
To be continued