Yahoo!
Oh, my...
I got it!
Yo, whatcha making?
A graduation album!
Graduation Album
A graduation album?
For the School Living Club!
Huh.
Oh, that looks great!
Megu-nee said it'd be better if it were hand-drawn!
But your drawings are just so bad, Yuki.
Wh-whaa...?!
You're helping her with it too, Miki-san?
Only if she does her part in our other activities.
Oh, Miki's way better at drawing than Yuki!
These are great!
Miki's reading a book here, and...
Oh, who's this?
A close friend of mine.
Class ended early that day,
but the sky was so pretty and blue,
we figured it'd be a waste of a good day
to just head home.
So we stopped somewhere on our way back.
C'mon, Miki!
Coming!
Where do you want to go?
There's a book I'd like to get.
Okay, the bookstore it is!
Can we hit up the arcade after that?
Sure.
...cut to a camera on the scene.
Let's take some pictures at the photo booth, too!
There's one with some new features!
While the reason behind them is still unknown...
Oh...
wait up, Kei!
Huh?
School Living Club
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Issho ni (Hai!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Houkago nara atarimae no koto
Saa sa, atsumare!
Kossori kaeruna! (Kora!)
Bukatsu dou dane? Katsudou shichau ne!
Asonderu nja arimasen
Tadaima tte ano ko ga iu yo (Okaeri!)
Minna de ireba daijoubu (Bu!)
Everybody say: tomodachi de iyou ne
Shitai kara shitai nara
Shitai toki shitai desho
Daisuki (Hai!)
Watachitachi wa tanoshinderu
24 jikan hashaideru
Okujou ni wa akana taiyou
Kanari sakendemita (Genki desu!)
Watashitachi wa koko ni imasu
Koko ni wa yume wa chanto aru
Friend nara tomodachi desho (Sou da!)
Sukitte itte mita (Daisuki!)
Field Trip
Thank you, come again!
What, what?
It's nothing.
Seriously, what?
Man, I just love the mall!
You still have a CD player?
Hey, don't make fun of me!
The sound is totally different!
Aww, you're so cute!
Do you like CDs better, too?
See?
Oh my, did you find a playmate, Taromaru?
Sorry, he was just so cute.
It's alright. Thank you for playing with him.
Come on, say bye-bye to the nice girl.
Bye-bye!
Goodbye!
Western Books
Wow, you can read this stuff?
I read the translated version,
so I wanted to know if I could read the original...
What's going on?
Attention all customers.
An incident causing serious injury has occurred.
Please follow the directions of our mall staff
as we work to control the situ-
Hey, this is pretty bad.
Is that the fire alarm?
Wait, for real?
Let's get out of here!
We should go, too!
Hey, why's everyone stopped?!
The escalator's off!
I hear someone's going around attacking people.
Doesn't look like we can get down.
That way!
Excuse me, is the elevator working?
I don't know, we just got here ourselves.
I see...
I don't think it's working.
It hasn't moved from the first floor at all.
It's going up!
I'm sure this is all a big misunderstanding.
Yeah, you're right...
What was that?!
What was it?!
Do you think those people in
the elevator were dead?
Probably, they had blood all over them.
That wouldn't happen in a fire
or a regular accident, right?
It's the doggie from earlier!
You're okay!
K-Kei!
Is he hurt?
Huh?
No, he looks like he's okay.
So what's this blood from?
I didn't realize what had actually happened
until a little bit later.
But I did understand that it was something
that would forever change our lives.
Let's eat.
I wonder if it's infectious. Like in the movies.
If it's a disease, then they can make a vaccine, a cure.
I'm sure some foreign country will
bring their military and come help us.
Yeah.
Well, there's no use in getting down about it.
You're right.
But no matter how long we waited,
nobody came for us.
There were no signs that help was coming.
What're you listening to, Kei?
The radio.
Huh.
That's right, you can listen to
the radio on that thing, too.
Yeah.
But I haven't been able to get any stations on it.
Kei!
They're here!
I wanna go outside.
Huh?!
What?! But it's dangerous out there!
But we don't know how much longer we'll be safe here.
Kei!
Okay, Miki.
I...
really do want to go outside.
We've still got food and water here.
Let's stay together until help comes.
They won't know we're here unless we go outside.
And I haven't taken a shower in forever...
We're lucky to have running water here,
and we can use as much as we want!
We're using a little washbin for a toilet!
It's so gross!
Sorry, but I...
And we're going to run out of food eventually!
Then what?
Then...
Why is it always me? It makes me look so selfish.
Kei...
I'm going to the bathroom.
I just got a great idea!
What, jeez...
It's a reeeally fun idea!
Okay, okay, what is it?
Scoot
All three of us club members...
All three of us...
I'll tell you tomorrow!
My, what's the ruckus?
Grumble
My, my, what's wrong?
Kurumi-chan's karate chop
made my hair antenna cave in!
It did not!
No violence!
Sniff!
It's her fault for being so uppity!
But isn't it much more fun if you've got
something good to look forward to tomorrow?
Okay, just leave that kinda stuff for before we pass out.
That's right. Let's get to sleep.
Okay!
Go to sleep!
Aw, man!
You're keeping all of us up!
Right, Ri-san?
Ri-san?
Zzz...
That's our Ri-san.
What're you doing?
I'm going.
Going? You mean, going outside?!
Hey!
Wait!
Do you plan on staying here forever, Miki?
Well...
Taromaru...
I should be fine if I go now.
Kei...
Are you happy, living in here, shut away?
I'll be fine.
I'll definitely bring help back for you.
Until I'm back, hold on to this for me, okay?
See you later.
Shut up!
I'm sorry...
I-I'm sorry...
Morning!
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
Oh, rice!
Pick whatever canned food you want to put on it.
Huh?
Oh, canned beef!
I didn't know we still had some!
G'morning.
Hey, Kurumi-chan, look! Canned beef!
O-oh.
Starting the day off with beef!
What a luxury!
What is this, the 1930s?
Treasure it. That's our last one.
Let's eat it together!
You can have it, Yuki-chan.
No, it's the last one, so we have to share it!
Alright, then we'll split the other cans
into three parts, too.
Yeah.
Yup!
Let's eat!
It's so good!
You're in a good mood this morning, Yuki-chan.
Mm-hm, because I thought of
such a great idea last night!
My, what could it be?
Let's go on a field trip!
A field trip?
Don't you think it's the
perfect season for a field trip?
Yuki-chan.
Isn't it a great idea?
That's bad manners.
Oh, whoops!
And did you forget that the School Living Club rules
say we can't leave school?
I've realized something!
We can't leave school,
but there's an exception to the rule!
If we leave for school purposes,
then it's not leaving at all!
Tadah!
Right, right?
I don't think that line of logic really works.
And clubs don't do field trips, either.
You're so closed-minded, Kurumi-chan.
We're leading the way with our club!
I see. Then let's write up the paperwork.
Megu-nee has to take a look at it.
Ta-da!
School Living Club Field Trip
A field trip is a school event, so I think
it would work great for our club activity.
We can also learn a lot of things
by going outside. Also it's really fun!
School Living Club Representative Yuki Takeya
I've already put the paperwork together!
School Living Club Field Trip
A field trip is a school event, so I think
it would work great for our club activity.
We can also learn a lot of things
by going outside. Also it's really fun!
School Living Club Representative Yuki Takeya
Alright, then she just has to look at this, then?
Yup!
Thanks for the meal!
I'll go get Megu-nee!
So, what should we do?
Wait for Megu-nee, I guess.
Let's leave it to Yuki.
My, you've gotten much more positive about this.
Yeah, plus Yuki seems to be doing well.
And there's some stuff I want
that I can't get from around here.
And that's what's important in the end.
Teacher’s Room
Now, how will we get there?
I guess we'll have to use Megu-nee's car.
She said okay!
Oh, that's great, Yuki-chan!
Alright, guess it can't be helped, then.
If we go in my car, all four of us will fit.
You're gonna let us ride in your car, Megu-nee?!
But I'm a little nervous since I
haven't driven in so long!
Oh, then I'll drive.
What?!
You can drive, Kurumi-chan?!
It's fine, I'm definitely a better driver than Megu-nee.
Oh, that's right.
H-h-hey!
Oh, sorry, Megu-nee.
Well, I think it'd be good for Kurumi
to get used to driving,
just in case something happens, Sensei.
Th-that is true...
But when did you get your license?
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Yuki-chan, can you go get the car keys?
Okay!
M-my car...
School
Get down from here Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â
Cooking classroom
Parking lot Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Front entrance
Field
The safe place closest to the parking lot is the
cooking room right next to the second floor barricade.
Taking a ladder down from there
would give us the shortest path to the car.
School
Get down from here Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â
Parking lot
Field
Can you sprint there with your shovel on your back?
I can
School
Parking lot
Field
I can, I can.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Are you all ready?
We can go, right?
Here's the key to Megu-nee's car!
Thanks!
Be careful!
Yup, I'll be back.
Okay...
They're doing construction on the stairs?
That's right.
And on the entrance to the school?
Everyone's in class, so stay quiet, okay?
Okay!
Kurumi...
Crap! Which one is Megu-nee's?
Calm down, calm down...
That's it!
Oh, no!
I'm... really...
sorry... 'bout...
this!
Hold on tight!
Wait, seatbelts!
Hold on, hold on!
Try not to dent my car, okay?
Kurumi-chan, are you really okay to drive?
It's different than what I'm used to, but I can handle it.
Different?
I'm used to using a gamepad
instead of a steering wheel.
Huh? Wait, you mean a video game...
I told you, it's fine!
Just watch my awesome spinout!
Don't spinout!
My poor car!
Kurumi?!
I got it!
The road's all bumpy!
Are they doing construction here, too?!
We've got an opening!
It was like the ending of a movie
I saw a long time ago.
Two people jumped in a car and
drove off towards the distant horizon.
When you were by my side
They'd thrown their lives behind and were
starting off on a new journey in the evening sun.
That kind of movie.
I never felt so complete
From deep inside
One day when I wake up from this never-ending dream
Taromaru, where are you?
Taromaru?!
I wanna see you again
All of your warm tender days
So many memories with you now gone
I feel so lost without you here by my side
When I wake up from this dream
I wanna be with you again
Remember that moment we took each other’s hand
If I’d never let you go so far away we’d still be the same
Next Time!
Megu-nee, you really like that bear!
His name's Mr. Bear! Isn't he cute?
Man, Megu-nee, you really are...
Really are what?
...such a kid!
I'm a teacher!
A Meeting
Next time on School-Live, episode 5:
"A Meeting"