There exists a room of sorrow.
The view from the window is clear.
Everyone else but me looks happy.
It feels like I'm the only one who
doesn't move in this ever-changing world.
Inside that secluded room,
I waited for the day I could go outside.
But...
that room has no doors.
So I wish
for the world outside the window to stop, just like it did in here.
That is my...
one wish.
ubaware kanatte risou wa kurikaesu geemu surinuketeku
The acts of theft and granting are entwined within the endless games
nichijou wa utarete ana darake tatteiru no ga yatto kana
You finally take a stand after your quiet life was beaten to a pulp
ketsuron no nai kuuron mienai ruuru no ue de odotteru suteppu de
Dance upon the unseen rules with endless speculation
kuzurete iku kyou tsunagitomeru saishuu beru ga naridasu
The final bell rings out to bind together this crumbling world
ukabu omoi no joukei ni wa kimi ga irun da yo
Within my memories you're always there
waretterun dayo
Simply laughing
yurushitakunai no? motometenai no?
You say you can't forgive? That you have no desires?
soredemo mada
So why can't you stop?
We cry OPEN torimodoshitai mirai kowashitai sekai
We cry "Open!" to take back tomorrow and destroy the world
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
akehanashitai negai GOT IT? ima
Do you finally know your deepest wish?
akehanachitai negai GOT IT? ima
kurosu suru I wish you don't cry
We cross and I wish you don't cry
hikari to yami no saki kasanatte mata iro ga tsuku you
Another color lies at the point where light and darkness cross
"sono saki" wo shinjitemiyou ka
And I choose to believe in it
You surprised me.
I didn't think you'd really come.
You're the one who tipped us off.
Well, yes.
I do have something
I want to talk about with you.
Talk?
You... hate me, right?
Yuzuki...
How far did you go?
How far?
We... kissed.
Ki—
K-Ki...?!
W-Well, naturally!
That was my wish, after all...
All Hanayo-san did was make my wish come true.
I mean, I did want to ki... kiss him sooner or later!
Kiss him...
H-Huh? What is it, Hanayo-san?
You haven't changed one bit
even after becoming a LRIG.
You're as straightforward and naive...
Wh-What?!
...and easily hurt as ever,
as you desperately try to look strong.
You really are similar,
you and Kazuki.
I got close to Kazuki so I could fulfill your wish.
He really reminds me of you.
Ew...
Gross...
At first, making your wish
come true was all I had in mind.
But soon,
I realized I was actually in love with Kazuki.
Hanayo-san...
That's why I can't keep this up anymore...
I still love Kazuki, but I love you, too!
If I turn finding happiness
with Kazuki into my own wish,
it'll be the same as betraying you, Yuzuki!
Hanayo-san—
I don't want that!
I can't betray you... I can't deceive you!
Kazuki still believes that I'm you!
If I keep doing this to someone dear to—
Kazuki?
What was that about, Yuzuki?
What were you just saying?!
Uhm...
No—
Yuzuki?
What's going on here...
Kazuki, wait!
Kazuki isn't a Selector, so he can't hear your voice!
Hanayo-san!
Yuzuki's voice? Hanayo-san?
Yuzuki. I'm sorry.
I can't fulfill your wish!
Wait, Hanayo-san!
Yuzuki!
Please, wait!
Please listen to our and Yuzuki's story!
Yuzuki's story?
Why don't they understand?
Even the ones I created are leaving me behind.
I will be by your side.
Hanayo-san!
Ruuko!
Where's Hanayo-san?!
Hanayo-san!
Keep fulfilling my wish!
I don't care if you betray me, just do it!
You're going to die if you don't do it!
Calm down, Yuzuki...
It's okay.
She's going to be okay, Yuzuki.
You really believe us?
I can definitely feel Yuzuki's presence in this card.
If an Eternal Girl doesn't
fulfill a wish, she disappears.
We need to save Hanayo-san!
I have to hurry and become a LRIG.
Ruuko, you already have one win.
If you can win a few more battles, then—
There's not enough time!
You can fight me once!
Because you have a different LRIG,
we should be able to fight one more time.
Then all we have to do is split up and find Selectors—
It'll be too late!
While we're running around, Hanayo-san will...
Maybe...
you don't have to win more than once.
Ruuko, you're in the same position that I was in as a Selector.
The conditions for granting your wish are already fulfilled.
It's only because Tama didn't accept
your wish that an Eternal Girl wasn't born.
You mean that...
Ruuko's wish can come true if Tama is willing to accept it?
But you can't go to the white-windowed room without becoming a LRIG, right?
The battlefield is linked to
the white-windowed room.
I'll try to call out for Tama during our battle.
If my voice can reach Tama...
...then my wish can be granted.
Yuzuki...
Hey, Hitoe?
Can you ask Kazuki something for me?
I'm wondering whether it's me he loves
or if it's actually Hanayo-san in my form.
Yuzuki...
W-Wait, nevermind!
I'll ask him myself! I'll do it once I'm out of this card.
Right, Ruuko?
Yeah!
Open!
Is it... all over now?
Can I... never meet Ruu again?
Hitoe! You mustn't try to lose on purpose.
Only a serious battle will make Ruu shine
and light the way to Tama!
I got it! Yuzuki!
Sure thing! I'm not gonna go easy on you!
Fiery Ambition!
Yuki!
Who's there?
That voice!
Tama?!
Who is... Yuki?
Tama...
It's me. Kuro.
But I'm not Kuro anymore. I'm Yuki now.
Ruu gave me a name, just like she did for you. It's Yuki!
Tama. We two were born from Mayu.
Yup...
But the one who gave us our names...
The one who showed us the world outside...
That was Ruu!
Yup...
So let's thank her!
Let's grant her wish together!
Yuki!
We'll win this battle with the next turn!
Yuzuki!
Tama!
Yuki!
I accept...
Ruuko.
...the Laws of the Selector.
And now...
...a new Eternal Girl will be born!
Yuzuki!
What?
That's...
Hitoe-san!
Did Yuzuki come back, too?
Ruuko!
Was... her wish granted?
B-But something's weird...
Yuki's card is still the same.
It should've changed if her wish was granted!
Hey... I might be off the mark, but can I say something?
Ruuko-san entered this battle so she could go to the white-windowed room
and meet this Mayu girl, right?
Y-Yes...
Is that really the only place where she is?
Huh?
Mayu created the world of Selector battles as
a means to escape her own harsh reality, didn't she?
That must mean she's suffering
here somewhere, in the real world...
Y-You're right!
Even if we don't go to the white-windowed room,
we can still try to convince the real Mayu!
But why didn't Yuki tell us
about that if it's really possible?
What's the matter, Hitoe?
That place we got a glimpse of before we left the battlefield...
The white-windowed room!
If it was that room, then I think I've seen it before...
You're...
Mayu.
You're so stupid.
Shiro is playing hide and seek right now.
Even if Kuro and Shiro's feelings are connected,
your wish can't come true without Shiro herself!
Mayu, please listen to what we have to say!
What did you just say?
P-Please listen to—
Kuro. Did you just say "we"?
You are meant to be alone, Kuro.
"We" is no word you can speak.
Her name isn't Kuro! It's Yuki!
"Yuki"?
How strange!
As if seasons have any meaning when you're trapped inside a card.
That's so dumb!
She's just a LRIG!
Yuki's feelings are your feelings.
Tama's, too.
Both of them were born from you.
And they both make up your true feelings.
You wanted to be protected by the snow that covers everything in silence
and embraced in its gentle grasp.
But that's not all you felt.
You longed for the pleasant summer sun,
filling everything with light.
Yuzuki told us that it's really lonely inside a card.
She was shut off inside the walls
keeping her from getting outside!
That must be the same pain
you've been feeling all this time!
You hated being the only one locked inside that room, so you had everyone—
So what you're saying is that I'm all alone?
I'm not!
Mayu isn't alone at all.
Been a while since I've looked like this, hasn't it?
Ulith!
You wanted to become the LRIG of a strong Selector.
That's what your wish was, right?
But it's different for me.
Rather than strength, I wanted to become the LRIG of a Selector who can bring despair to others.
And what can I say, my wish came true.
The endless suffering of countless girls... Mayu brought me all their stories!
She's my true Selector!
Come on, let's have a battle!
I've been waiting to slap that fake
goody two-shoes face of yours!
Hurry up, will you?!
We didn't come here to battle! We're here to talk!
Please, Mayu! Put an end to all these sad and cold battles!
There's a more fun way to battle!
"Fun"?
Ah, you're talking about that one time?
When you fought in the library courtyard with no wishes at stake.
A battle so boring it made me yawn.
I know all about it.
Right...
Let's do it there, then.
Now, let's begin.
Show me how fun battles are, Ruuko.
Why?!
Fighting you won't change anything...
It won't even help my wish come true!
There could be meaning to this fight.
Mayu used to play WIXOSS all the time,
but she's never battled against someone else before.
Alone as she was, she only ever battled
against imaginary opponents in her head.
Ruu.
It was our battles that changed me.
Yuki...
The way you battle is so brilliant that it can move people's hearts.
What is it with this incessant babbling?
We're going to go first.
Ulith. Grow.
She's strong. But...!
It looks like what you said was true, Yuki.
If we don't make the moves she expects us to,
she'll get agitated and fall apart.
Turn End!
Wh-What was that?
Mayu! The next order, hurry!
What? Why?
Why isn't she attacking now?
If Kuro attacked now, I would've gained
enough Ener to unleash my Arts on my next turn...
Why—
Mayu!
But... I won't lose.
Because it's almost time...
Attack Ahriman with Brionac!
Now that was a complete flop, huh?
Kuro, did you forget the rules of Selector battles?
What?
Take a look at yourself.
There was someone else to be
worried about besides Hanayo.
Now that Urazoe Iona has
returned to her own body, Yuki,
you've failed as an Eternal Girl.
Yuki?
It's fine.
It was bound to happen, sooner or later.
I'm a being that appeared from out of nowhere.
Nothing more than a character from a story that Mayu made up.
I'm Yuki,
and like snow I will melt.
No!
We can't let that happen, Yuki!
Ruu...
Tama!
I can't escape from here.
Take me to where Yuki is.
Please!
Tama...
What's holding you up?!
Get back to fighting already!
Ruuko! What are you doing?!
You can't quit in the middle of a battle!
This way!
The library?
This courtyard...
It's right up ahead!
There's another building here?
This library looks old, but it's still new.
I heard it was remodeled from someone's mansion.
It looks so familiar...
Yes.
It feels similar, doesn't it?
So Mayu's in there, then?!
I don't know, but...
Let's go!
Yuki! Stay with me!
I'll take you to where Tama is right away!
Why?
That place was identical to the library courtyard,
but this place is so foreign!
I think I understand now.
Mayu didn't allow Tama to fight in
Selector battles and kept her sealed away.
I was asking myself why
Tama suddenly awoke one day.
But I think I understand now.
Yuki?!
Mayu...
No Trespassing
That house isn't inhabited?
What are you kids doing here?
Um... We're friends with the girl who lives here.
Huh? The girl here...
Mayu...
is probably already dead.
That's right, Kuro.
I'm a dead girl now.
M-Mayu!
Kuro... you won't ever leave me to be truly alone, will you?
You'll disappear with me, won't you?
Grow. Ulith. Level 5.
Yuki?!
Yuki!
No! Say something!
No... No!
No!
That
Window
is
Locked
Life
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
I walk through
this endless street maze
life deguchi no nai meiro no machi naru suzu no oto
to the sound of bells
I will
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
shed the life
that I was given
i do ataerareta ima wo sutete arukidasu asa
for a brighter tomorrow
I now feel catharsis in a world
hikari to yami kowasaseru sekai de
that will allow neither dark nor light
mezamehajimeru catharsis
With fear in my heart I swore
furueteiru mune de chikatta
that I would never again
mou dare hitori
lose anybody
nakushitakunai
The morrow may be drenched in tears,
ashita namida afuretemo
but I will face the wind
kaze no naka wo
with pride
kakenukeyukou
I will do what must be done for my future
hanate eranda mirai he
I will remember my wish,
torimodosu yo
and I will never give up
kono negai wa akiramenai
This
Selection
..is...
This selection is...