The Cooking Club has
already lost its ladle. Jumonji
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
The Jumonji Affair
"'A' Capella Club"
"'I'-go Club"
"'U'-ranai Club"
"'O'-ryori Club"
"'E'"
A Capella Club → (drink)
Igo Club → (Go stones)
Uranai Club → (Unmei no Hi)
Engei Club → (water pistol)
Oryori Club → (otama)
Biology Prep Room
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
Hyouka
When light findeth equal measure
with darkness.
Program
5. 'Close-up Card Magic'
1st-years Takamura Yoichi / Nagai Kaori
5th Performance: 14:30
Earth Science Prep Room
Magic Club
Welcome to the Manga Club!
Secret Exploits of the
Phantom Thief Jumoji
"Moreover, ah, the nerve of this rascal! He even went so
far as to take a cutter knife from the Wall Newspaper Club."
"This is a clear and unambiguous challenge to the news
media. A way must be found to stop Jumoji's thievery..."
"This is all the information
we have at present."
As such, gentle reader, it can be supposed
that Jumoji's final misdeed will take place"
"on the third day between noon and 2:00, with either
the 'Classic Lit Club' or the 'Industrial Arts Club.'"
"Classic Lit Club"
Remaining: 137
Welcome to the Kanyasai Homepage
Mail order
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having
antennas is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
The Final Target