I appreciate that you fixed me
a box lunch for a change, but, Sis,
why ethnic?
Mm...
Oreki-san!
Thanks for minding the store.
Yeah.
Hey...
We won, we won!
It went down to the wire, though.
Congratulations on your victory.
Hm?
Thank you very much. It was all
thanks to your help, Oreki-san.
Nah... Well...
You know, I was shocked.
Hotaro, you would have been
the last person on earth
that I'd expect to do something like that.
I was just caught up in the
festival mood. I won't do it again.
So anyway, Oreki-san,
there is something I'd like you to look at.
Here it is.
The Cooking Club has already
lost its ladle.... Jumonji
You hold your breath to make it through
the bewildering day that confronts you
You know what this is, don't you?
What do you want to do?
The pain from shrugging
it all off as nothing
urges you on enough to be encouraging
Catching hold but making a mess,
we're still inadequate
but as long as we can forge
our shining, unseen future selves...
Awaken and run where it takes you,
leaving mirages behind
Run with your desire to change,
from your comfort zone into freedom
Start choosing between now
and the brilliance you can attain
Unaware of your destination,
deep breaths following shallow ones
Hm... Your ladle was stolen, was it?
The Jumonji Affair
Mm-hm. But only from our table.
Someone sure has a lot of free time.
It's not just the Cooking Club!
The same thing has been foisted upon
the Go Club and the A Capella Club!
And the Fortunetelling Club, too!
It had the same kind of note.
Um, the confession note said...
Someone sure has an awful lot of free time!
Hm, this spiciness is so good...
Oreki-san!
Oh, no. It's no use.
It's the same as always.
Chitanda Eru's curiosity
is about to kick in.
Who could do something like this
in the middle of the culture festival?
Why are they appropriating
Jumonji-san's name?
Why are they stealing
one thing after another?
I am curiou...
We don't have time to chase after that.
These anthologies...
About these anthologies...
Even publicizing them
low-key during our events,
I don't think we're going
to sell a whole lot of them.
That's true.
We're going to have to do something
much more attention-grabbing.
Yes! So I was thinking:
What if we pitched this phantom thievery
to the Wall Newspaper Club?
And if possible, have the
school radio put it over the air, too.
If we do all that, our anthologies
will be in high demand, won't they?
That follows.
That is a good idea.
When you say "pitch it,"
what are you going to do?
This incident has nothing to do
with the Classic Lit Club.
We do it like this...
The Classic Lit Club's master
detective, Oreki Hotaro,
will catch Jumonji, the phantom thief
upsetting the culture festival!
To learn more about his exploits up to now,
see the Classic Lit
Club's anthology, Hyouka!
That would be a fantastic way!
Yeah, not bad, I guess.
Right? This will unmask
Jumonji's true identity
as well as publicize the Classic
Lit Club... Give me a break!
Who are you calling a master detective?!
There is no way I'm playing panda
to lure in customers! Hmph!
Let's give it a try, Oreki-san.
Even assuming I'm willing
to become a clown,
there are 1,000 students alone,
and if you add in all
the visitors, it's even more.
How are we going to catch anyone
among all those people?
Is it that hard?
It's impossible.
If only this so-called phantom thief
targeted the Classic Lit Club.
Yeah, well...
Then what if we hit ourselves?
Overruled!
Yow...!
I-I'm kidding, I'm kidding!
Target, huh?
Which clubs have been
stolen from so far?
The Go Club, the A Capella Club,
the Cooking Club, uh... What else?
The Fortunetelling Club.
Yeah, yeah.
Hm...
Hm?
The A Capella Club, the Go Club,
the Fortunetelling Club,
and the Cooking Club, huh?
ABC!
Huh? Huh?
Hello? Suzuki-kun?
Clubs that go with "E" are the
Film Club, the Gardening Club,
Have you had anything stolen from your club?
Yeah, like a robbery.
And the SF Club.
What's going on?
Okay, never mind, then. Bye.
The regularity.
And it's an extremely simple one, too.
The A Capella Club;
'A' Capella Club
the Igo [Go] Club;
'I'-go Club
the Uranai [Fortunetelling] Club;
'U'-ranai Club
skip a letter to the Oryori [Cooking] Club,
'O'-ryori Club
'E'
and if an "E" club pops up next,
there's no question about it.
Ah! Japanese alphabetic order, right?
Water pistol? Ah, mm-hm. Thanks!
That's what it is.
The Gardening Club has been hit.
They were gone for a moment,
and one of their water pistols was stolen.
Water pistol?
For fire safety when
roasting sweet potatoes.
A customer yesterday from
the Gardening Club had one.
Just a second.
In Christie's The A.B.C. Murders,
the "A" person is killed in
the "A" location, right?
An otama [ladle] was stolen from
the Oryori [Cooking] Club...
Yeah, just a second...
Chitanda-san, did you ask what was
stolen from the Fortunetelling Club?
Oh, yes. It was the
"Wheel of Fortune," a tarot card.
Okay. Which means...
A Capella Club → (drink) Igo Club → (Go stones) Uranai Club →
(Unmei no Hi) Engei Club → (water pistol) Oryori Club → (otama)
The Gardening Club's water pistol
was an "eikei" [AK] wasn't it?
AK? What's that?
A Russian-made assault rifle.
If that counts for that,
then the Igo [Go] Club gets
"ishi" [stone], doesn't it?
Could be. What about the A Capella Club?
Doesn't matter. If we look
into it, we'll find out.
Why's that?
What's the culprit's name?
It says "Jumonji."
Why read it like that?
The usual reading would be "Jumoji," right?
"Jumoji" [tenth letter]!
That's it! A-I-U-E-O, Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko,
up to the tenth letter!
In other words, the last letter will be...
"Ko"! The Koten [Classic Lit] Club!
Don't you think this is enough of
a pitch for the Classic Lit Club?
I'll go discuss this with the
Wall Newspaper Club right away!
She's pretty excited about this, huh?
What's wrong?
Huh? Oh... I just thought of
something. This whole thing is...
Nah, never mind. I'm going
to go check something.
What's with him?
Who knows?
Ibara, aren't you going
back to the Manga Club?
Yeah, I am.
Hm...
What? Is there something
wrong with me being here?!
Why are you so mad?
I'm not mad!
Biology Prep Room
The trick to negotiating...
First, look as though you expect
something of the other person.
Second, downplay your benefit from it.
Third, ask someone of the
opposite sex, away from public view.
All right!
As you wish! I'll go interview
the Gardening Club!
Hey, what about the A Capella Club?!
I'm calling them now!
Jeez, hurry it up!
The Cooking Club! We're looking
into it now. Yes, that's right.
Hello, Tomita? I need to ask you something...
How many times
do I have to tell you?! If you have time to chat, move!
Excuse me... Excuse me...!
Sorry about this, Chitanda-san,
but we're a little busy right now.
Could you come by again later sometime?
Oh, yes. Well, another time...
isn't going to work!
This is about the Classic Lit Club!
If it's that again, you need to
have a special angle or else...
But we do have an angle!
And what would that be?
We're a little short on time.
Could you make this brief...
Whoa, hey! Where do you think
you're taking me? Huh?
This is something I can only discuss
with the Wall Newspaper Club.
Which is to say, um, I...
am pinning my hopes on you!
Y-You are? Thanks...
But there's not much in it
for the Classic Lit Club.
Uh-huh...
What do you think? Isn't this
something you'd like to get behind?
Er, well,
I'm not sure what you mean.
Yes, of course.
Like I said, we're busy.
If you don't have a story,
I'll talk to you later.
P-Please wait!
Yes, the story! There is someone
at the culture festival
who is stealing things
from different clubs!
The culprit is...
Jumonji!
You're talking about Jumonji, right?!
Do you know something?!
Huh? Um, well...
I see. Japanese alphabetical order.
And the Fortunetelling Club was hit,
too, you say? So that's why.
So that's why what?
Oh, this is the Kabe [Wall]
Newspaper Club, right?
Ah! Then you mean...
They got our katta [cutter] knife.
Is that the reason why
you're so busy right now?
Yeah. I do hate that it happened to us,
but we've been waiting
for a story like this.
I have to admit, though, I'm
impressed that you picked up on it.
Oh, yes. Oreki-san did.
Yeah... You don't say.
Anyhow, thanks. You've been helpful.
Togaito-san, please wait!
I've already told you as much as I did,
so please be sure to write
about the Classic Lit Club!
All right? Please?
Belaboring the point there was
the same as doubting Togaito-san.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ah! Excuse...
Chitanda-san! Well? Did
you get any results?
Yes, well...
That's a good question.
Sorry, inside joke.
Oh. Ah, more importantly, I
heard from the A Capella Club.
It was apple juice that was stolen.
I also heard from the
Wall Newspaper Club
that they had their cutter knife stolen.
That covers "Ka." It's Japanese
alphabetical order for sure.
Which means that the next one, "Ki,"
can only be the Kijutsu [Magic] Club.
It's almost time for the
Magic Club's next performance.
If we keep our eyes peeled...
We can catch them in the act?
Mm-hm.
That's this kind of phantom
thief's Achilles' heel.
He's bound by his own rules.
It won't be hard to uncover
who "Jumoji" is now.
But if we find him out at "Ki"...
The culprit won't ever reach
the Classic Lit Club, right?
There are any number
of ways to deal with that.
Maybe so, but...
In any case, I'll stake out the
Magic Club. No time like the present.
Bye, now!
Shuubun ('Middle of Autumn')
When light
findeth equal measure with darkness.
Hyouka
Program
5. 'Close-up Card Magic'
1st-years Takamura Yoichi / Nagai Kaori
5th Performance: 14:30
It's still only 2:00, huh?
Oh, if it isn't Fukube.
Hey, Tani-kun.
If you're here, then it means
you must know, right?
Know what?
Don't play dumb! About the
phantom thief Jumoji!
Well, yeah.
Ha, ha! Then this will be
our next competition.
You know about the
Wall Newspaper Club?
The cutter knife, right? Yeah, I know.
Yeah, the Wall Newspaper Club
has joined in on the game.
The next issue's top story is on Jumoji.
What's more, they apparently
plan to run an extra
covering exclusively any group
that catches the phantom thief.
Mm-hm.
Well, I hate to say it, but
I'm going to win this one.
Appearances to the contrary,
I'm actually quite the mystery fan!
Go easy on me, okay?
Earth Science Prep Room
Ibara, you've
read Christie's The A.B.C. Murders, right?
Of course I have.
Then I have a question for you.
Was there a reason why the
killings were in ABC order?
Spoiler alert. Are you sure?
Go ahead.
"He wanted to kill in ABC order,
so that's what he tried."
Do you think that would make a good story?
Hm...
Are you thinking that this
matter is the same way?
Maybe.
In time, anyone could have figured out
the Japanese alphabetic order rule.
That's something "Jumoji"
must have expected.
Sure, that's true enough.
I was thinking there's a possibility
of some hidden purpose
or meaning in the way
things are being stolen.
That is, if it's not just some
crime for the fun of it.
Oreki, do you want to
catch this "Jumoji" now?
Who, me? Why?
You seem intent.
I don't care either way.
But once Chitanda says she's curious,
it becomes an issue that
ultimately can't be avoided.
You could ignore her, couldn't you?
She's not someone I can just ignore,
which is why it's a hassle.
How silly. Okay then...
You're leaving?
Mm-hm. Oh, come to think
of it, thanks for the flour.
It really helped.
Oh, that's right.
Are you asking for money?
Don't make it sound sordid.
I got that flour through
the Warashibe Protocol.
What's that?
Give me something in return.
Or you could just break the protocol.
Oh, I get it. Let's see...
You can have this.
Are you sure?
Mm-hm.
But without that you can't cosplay...
Don't call it cosplay, idiot!
The Magic Club's 5th performance
will be starting shortly.
Magic Club
Irisu-senpai, hello!
Ah, it's you.
Do you like magic tricks?
I don't know them well enough
to say I like them. Is that weird?
Hm? No. Just a bit surprising.
Could she be...?
No, that's crazy.
But still, he didn't have
to say it like that, did he?
That's Mayaka's Senpai.
Mm-hm.
I saw her at the Manga Club yesterday.
This looks entertaining.
Hey, look at that.
Huh? Ah!
Hey, Mune, don't go deciding this yourself.
Oh, that's Tanabe-senpai and... Ten-hut!
Now, now, don't get mad.
It's Student Council President Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Hey, Miss Empress.
Hi.
Yeah.
Hm? Hey, Fukube.
Hi!
Thank you for waiting! The Magic Club's
performance will now begin!
Thank you so much for
coming together here today.
Please enjoy watching the tricks
that we in the Magic Club
have been practicing daily to master.
Now then...
With this many people watching,
how are you going to commit your theft,
phantom thief "Jumoji"?
All right, first off,
Takamura Yoichi will
perform "Living Dead"...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Well...
"Kyandaru" [candle]!
Get a spare...
Ah, excuse me.
Damn!
But when?
"When" nothing. Nobody but the
performers went near the stage.
Which means it was taken
before they started.
Ugh, why did I even
come here, then?
Now that I think about it,
there's no evidence to show
that Jumoji steals
during a performance.
Welcome to the Manga Club!
Thank you very much.
Are we selling more than we did yesterday?
Mm-hm, we are. Maybe the
posters are having an effect.
Thank goodness.
We should have just done as
Senpai said, shouldn't we?
Yeah. If a certain someone
hadn't objected,
we could have sold even more yesterday.
Now, now, it's so sad
to say it like that.
There's no reason to mind them.
Mm-hm.
And that business about
not being able to find it?
That was a lie, right?
I'll bet she actually got
scared all of a sudden
about the manga she was going
to show off not being that great.
Bringing up a doujinshi
nobody's heard of
just to try to look like
a know-it-all, you know?
That's her, that's her!
I'll bet that manga
doesn't even exist.
Now, hold on...
Stop! That's enough.
If you've never heard
of it, then keep quiet.
We're back.
B-But, Senpai...
Didn't you hear me?
I said if you don't know it,
then keep quiet.
Oh, President, how
was the Magic Club?
Mm, it was fun.
Oh, yeah? Maybe I'll go
and see it tomorrow.
Mm-hm, go right on ahead.
What time does it start again?
They do it several times per day,
so I think you'll be fine.
Really? Well then...
Sorry, but I need to
step out for a bit, okay?
Mm-hm, okay.
Fu...
I'm so pathetic, huh? I want to go
running to Fuku-chan and the others.
Ibara?
Y-Yes, Yuasa-senpai?
I'm sorry things have
gotten so awkward.
Why are you apologizing, Senpai?
For not saying anything sooner.
I wanted to take your side, but...
But if you did that, there'd be friction
between you and Kochi-senpai.
I wouldn't want that to happen.
I think it's better this way.
Ayako doesn't really mean it.
Ayako?
I mean Kochi. Kochi Ayako.
Oh.
How do you know she
doesn't really mean it?
Because Ayako and I are friends.
And that's all?
Ayako and Haruna were friends, too.
Haruna? Who is that?
Anjo Haruna. One of the authors
of A Corpse By Evening.
It was a collaborative work?
Someone else was the artist.
Ayako would probably know who.
What year and what class is she in?!
Oh, Haruna isn't around anymore.
She transferred away.
Oh, I see.
But just because Kochi-senpai
was friends with Anjo Haruna-san,
how can you be sure that
she doesn't really mean it?
Hm, that's a good question.
I'm sorry, but I can't say any more.
I mean, Ayako is my friend after all.
Then explaining why would make
you speak ill of Kochi-senpai?
Once I cool off a bit,
I'll come back inside.
Ibara...
I'll be right back in, okay?
Extra! Extra!
Must-read!
Secret Exploits of the
Phantom Thief Jumoji
Moreover, ah, the nerve of this rascal! He even went so far
as to take a cutter knife from the Wall Newspaper Club.
This is a clear and unambiguous challenge to the news
media. A way must be found to stop Jumoji's thievery...
This is all the information we have at present. As such, gentle reader,
it can be supposed that Jumoji's final misdeed will take place
on the third day between noon and 2:00, with either
the 'Classic Lit Club' or the 'Industrial Arts Club.'
Classic Lit Club
Togaito-san...
I've been had, Hotaro.
A candle was stolen from the Magic Club.
They even found a confession note.
That's good, isn't it?
We don't want Jumoji caught before
he gets to the Classic Lit Club.
Well, I guess that's true.
I thought I could catch
him in the act, though.
That the theft would happen
during the performance?
Yeah.
Jumoji didn't reveal anything about
the exact time of the crimes.
That was true of the
Cooking Club's ladle, remember?
If you realized that, why
didn't you say something?
I didn't know you were trying
to catch him in the act.
Yeah, I guess not.
I'm back.
Irisu-san said that the 20 volumes
of Hyouka that we gave to her
are selling at a favorable pace.
Yeah, that's just how Irisu works.
There is one other thing, too.
In the Wall Newspaper's 4:00 edition
there's a story that
covers the "Jumoji" case.
It even covers the Japanese
alphabetical order rule.
Oh, yeah?
The Classic Lit Club's name also appeared.
It said that Jumoji's last crime would
be against the Classic Lit Club
or the Industrial Arts Club.
Industrial Arts Club? We have one of those?
Yes, we do, now that I think about it.
If they get hit, our whole
plan goes up in smoke.
I'm thinking of making a deal with
the Broadcasting Club tomorrow.
If we can get them to
cover the Classic Lit Club
on their schoolwide broadcast...
Huh? What is it?
Oh, you look exhaust...
Way to keep at it.
Oh, Mayaka.
How were our sales today?
Not counting the ones we
gave to Irisu, we sold 16.
Remarkable, isn't it?
Remarkable? Yeah.
You may be right.
Remaining: 137
It is on me to go around
making requests...
but somehow, I feel so tired.
Body Talk.
It is a step below A Corpse By Evening,
but it's still pretty good.
Ugh. My stuff is a hundred steps below.
Hotaro has changed. Or rather,
he's exhibiting his true worth.
All because of meeting Chitanda-san.
She's someone who holds that sense
of unpredictability that I love so much.
Is that something that I can look at
and just think, "That's nice"?
There are over 1,000 suspects.
No one could possibly be led to
the culprit by simple deduction.
Which means that catching them
in the act is the best we can do.
Hotaro really isn't cut out
for a case like this,
so I'll solve it myself.
Hotaro, I'm going to catch
Jumoji, just you watch.
Welcome to the Kanyasai Homepage
Mail order
Oh, they do mail order, too?
This situation is an unscientific
montage of emotions
Who is calling whom?
Your gaze darts away when I turn around
(I can feel it)
It's unkind to tell me I'm imagining things
They say having antennas
is a talent, right?
I mean I want to know
(I mean) (don't you?)
I'll turn up the heat on your youth
for you now, while there's time
If we can solve this tomorrow,
why not solve it right now?
I want to solve your mystery
Track down that secretive boyish figure!
(Today) you are a fantasy,
drawing me to you, no fair!
My curiosity is expanding,
lack of tricks notwithstanding
I'm fascinated, and I have to know, why?
Next time, "The Final Target."
The Final Target