oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
"You know, Teddy, vacation is called vacation because it makes you stupid."
"Oh please, what are you talking about?
"Going on a vacation can make you relaxed, but stupid?"
"Vacation means that something is vacated.
"And that something is none other than the common sense in your head.
"Thus, vacation makes you stupid."
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Family Play
It was quite obvious...
See, you've been abroad!
I should mail that to my friends!
Friends?
Sorry, Kigu!
Thanks for the mail!
It's cold. Cut it!
Sorry, Kigu!
Just once more!
I feel cold as a snake.
Should I put some warm water in?
How can you keep drinking such cold stuff now, Gan?
Why are there always two straws in tropical drinks?
So that couples can drink them together!
I want to go on a vacation like this when I find a boyfriend!
This is the dressing room, you know.
Marii, don't crush her dreams.
Anyway, you know what's more pressing than this vacation thing?
Wearing such ordinary swimsuits!
Yours is the most ordinary...
It's a school swimsuit...
For some people,
this is more exciting!
Well, for some people...
School swimsuits always look the same. Are there regulations?
"This and this is what we call a school swimsuit." Something like that.
There might be, but you better not ask the people who would know.
They'll never shut up once they start...
They'll be arguing about how the old or new designs are superior and stuff.
What does that even mean?
On the old design, the upper and lower parts are separate,
New design
and there's an opening in between.
Old design
Some people are peculiar about where the name goes.
Marii
Does it go on the breast? Or on the back?
Real pros may even consider the small tag.
There are even white school swimsuits.
Sorry! I didn't know it was such a deep topic!
But they still look the same wherever you go.
The uniforms are so varied, so why swimsuits the same?
I would even say that swimsuits are the summer uniforms!
They should be unique to the schools just like uniforms!
Yeah, some people choose their school based on its uniform,
so I guess it'd be okay if some people decided based on the swimsuits.
But wouldn't swimsuit fetish perverts flood schools?
True, while the performance percentage is so different between schools,
it's weird per se that the swimsuits look the same.
A
Performance
The angle of the swimsuit should be the same as their performance!
That's quite reasonable, actually.
True...
Marii, there's no way your performance percentage is so high...
How can it even be over 100?
You're more like 40 or so.
Stop...
Stop!
What do you think you're doing?!
Just accept it, Marii.
This shows the failure of post-war Japan's performance education!
I oppose it!
You oppose performance education? Then what?
Loose education?!
Look at how pitiful the swimsuit of the loose education generation is!
Gan, you don't have to go so far...
You were one of the loose generation?
Such a loser.
I guess you just bought an oversized import swimsuit.
How would I be able tell the size accurately from the catalog?
You only checked the bust size, I bet.
Better than having them not fill the swimsuit!
Yeah, but it looks like Kigu could fit in there too...
Perfect fit!
Tandem swimsuit!
So gross!
Stay still! Don't tickle me!
I'll butcher you!
See, you made Kigu cry!
Wait, what?
For some reason, I thought of her as my daughter.
The daughter I gave birth to through such pain.
Your maternal instincts awakened from piggybacking her?
Hey, could you please
call me Mommy?
Mommy!
My child!
Now I feel like you're my real mom too!
We can be a real family now!
What now?
You're asking me?
I'm so... jealous.
Mom...
Mom must smell so good!
That's just in the song, so—
Let me... Let me smell you!
Stop! Don't smell me!
Let her...
Kukuru just wants to remember her mom.
You must smell like soap bubbles, right?
Don't smell me!
No smell...
That can't be...
We can't let Kukuru down!
It's time for this!
What's that?
Soapy water!
The smell of soap bubbles!
I'll butcher you!
A
Sakai Five
Gan, sorry I kept you waiting!
You goofed up, right?
You took the express from Mitaka.
Yeah!
It always happens with Musashi-Sakai.
I'm sorry, did it take long?
You messed up and missed the station on the express, right?
Yeah... I ended up going all the way to Kokubunji.
It always happens with Musashi-Sakai.
Why is there a Musashi-Seki and a Musashi-Sunagawa too?
I got it wrong and took the Seibu line!
Didn't we go over that in an earlier episode?
Now we're only waiting on Teto.
Maybe she went to Musashi-Mizunokuchi or somewhere?
Huh? Teto?
What are you doing?
Hey, Gan!
You know, I'm trying to feel like someone from around here,
and it's a lot of fun!
March 25th 2012, 4:20 PM
Opening of the new entrance of the Musashi-Sakai station
(The long dreamed-of passage between the north and south sides)
The people of Musashi-Sakai have wanted a passage for a very long time.
What's so remarkable about that wish?
Don't belittle them!
This was like the wall of Berlin for the people of Musashi-Sakai!
They had to take the long way around for decades!
Shall we get going?
Street
Skip
This is the Skip shopping street.
Street
Skip
Why Skip?
You have to skip along!
Skip-skip-skip!
What's so great about skipping?
Could it be...
that you can't skip?
She's not the type for it either.
The Skip shopping street...
I feel like something is coming for me.
In Narimasu there's a Skip Village shopping district.
What kind of a village is that?
No one's skipping...
We'd pass all the stores in a flash then.
Back in the days, August meant that men flashing their bellies were walking down this street.
That's not what I'm describing!
I'm talking about the Musashino Belly Dance!
They wore nothing past the waist, painted a face on their belly,
and danced with a shade over their face.
Oh yeah, I saw that in From the North.
They just stole the Hokkai Bel—
They're paying their respect.
The Skip street is scary.
I think samba is the fad now.
So they switched to samba from belly dance?
That's because samba dancers show their bellies too.
Is that supposed to be convincing?
Past here is the Doppo Boulevard.
Doppo Blvd.
I read it as "a lonely road"...
The only reading I've ever known...
There's a memorial for Kunikida Doppo and his works down that way.
Kunikida Doppo's works
"Kunikida Doppo's works"
That's a pretty funky name.
The same goes for yours.
What did he write?
Plains of Musashi and Kamakura Wives and some other things.
Beef and Potato too.
He wrote about food too!
You're thinking of Noppo, not Doppo.
Kamakura Wives sounds so lewd!
Doppo's turning in his grave.
By the way, are you hungry?
Let's grab some food.
They don't really have anything famous here, do they?
They do! Musashi-Sakai is where the oily soba was born!
The Dong
This is where oily soba was born.
Some others say it was the Sankou in Kunitachi.
How is oily soba different from tsukemen?
You put a thick sauce on the noodles,
then add vinegar and oil to your tastes. Thus, oily soba.
That sounds like bukkake udon.
What's that?
You add toppings and garnish, then splatter the broth over it.
You're right, it sounds similar.
Whatever, let's just go in and eat.
I don't want to!
Why not?
You don't like noodles?
It's the restaurant's name...
The Dong?
What's wrong with The Dong?
We shouldn't just stand in front of The Dong.
Could you just stop repeating it?!
Don't you ride trams that go ding-dong?
Don't the bells on dog collars go ding-dong?
Will you refuse to pay for drinks in Vietnam?
The currency there is called dong.
That was so good!
Let's go here again!
Let's not make a spectacle out of it next time.
Musashi-Sakai could be called the Mecca of noodles.
They have Marukou, Kiraboshi, Musashiya
and of course GT Ramen.
GT?
It stands for Good Taste.
But you see, GT Ramen closed on the 21th of July.
I'm full!
I wanna take a rest.
I know the perfect place!
What is it? A cafe?
A cake shop?
Well, we're sitting down, but this isn't really the kind of relaxation I expected.
I'd have loved some tea...
And some yummy cake.
Don't you know the proverb?
If you want to have fun for a day, get drunk.
If you want to have fun for three days, get married.
If you want to have fun for a lifetime, go fishing!
You want to stay here for life?
They're taking it seriously.
They're going after the crucian carps.
And we are?
After carps.
Monsters!
Then don't feed them!
But I'm bored. They won't bite either.
Looks like the kiddo doesn't understand the true depth of fishing.
You're bored too!
The water purification plant.
Recently they started selling Tokyo Water, right?
That's bottled tap water.
In Kyoto they're selling Kyoto Water too,
and in Osaka they sell bottled tapwater called Yarly.
Then the water here should be the Musashi-Sakai Water!
Who'd buy that?
The Japanese Veterinary and Life Sciences University.
There's a manga artist who studied here!
The Asia University.
You can probably get in with bilboquet alone.
They prefer specialists?
The Musashino Place.
There's a library, music studios,
dance and performances areas.
Is there one for rakugo too?
I doubt that.
This was quite fun.
Careful with the Seibu line trap on the way home.
What do you mean?
At Musashi-Sakai, in addition to the JR Chuo line,
there's the Tamagawa line as well.
Tamagawa line?
First it was the Tama line,
then the Koremasa line,
then it was called the Musashi-Sakai line,
and currently it's the Tamagawa line.
That's like fish that get different names as they grow larger.
Plenty of people still call it the Koremasa line though.
Should we go home then?
Wait, wait! We must first do what we came here for!
And that is?
Why do you think we've come all the way out here?
What about that building?
Look!
The company in that building is responsible for animating us.
Today we're here to pay our respects!
The schedules must be cramped now after eleven episodes, but...
Please take good care of us.
Ah, it's Christmas, the day when no one feels alone,
but all I can feel is the weight of my loan...
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Tree Tragedy
Wow, you got a party barrel!
To tell the truth, it actually contains...
chicken skewers.
I forgot to make a reservation.
So all you got was the barrel?
Well, it's chicken either way.
Let's all say cheers!
You get the kiddie champagne, Kigu.
Merry Christmas!
So, did everyone bring presents?
Sure!
Then let's exchange!
Hand them around!
It's a foregone conclusion.
Teto'll get the best, no matter what.
This shit sucks ass.
Okay, stop!
Open it!
It's from me! Isn't it Christmas-y?
That it is, but what am I supposed to do with it?
Wear it, of course!
What good is that once Christmas is over?!
Aww...
Sweet chestnuts...
Those are from me.
Christmas
It's Christmas, so the presents should start with "ch" too.
What happened to the rest of the word?!
That as may be, is this supposed to make me happy?
I'm not made of money, you know.
It's Christmas, so the presents should start with "mas".
Christmas
That's an even worse pun!
Wow, mine's huge!
It's from me!
Toilet paper! Triple-ply for softness!
That's just what I'd expect from our masscot.
But what the fuck does it have to do with Christmas?!
Sorry. I didn't have time to go buy anything.
It's okay, thank you!
That was pretty much the best of the presents anyway.
Marii, your nose is red. Like a certain reindeer.
I caught a cold...
Blow your nose!
By the way, why isn't there a Christmas tree at our Christmas party?
I bought one on the 'net.
It's supposed to arrive today...
You should've ordered it earlier.
Teto, what're they recommending for you?
Don't look!
Ah, so that's where you get the jokes for your routine!
It isn't easy coming up with new jokes all the time, you know.
People can see the kind of things you buy with a single glance.
I don't even know why Jungle has that feature.
They build a profile of our interests and add to it every time we shop.
And they offer discounts, so you really do end up buying them.
There was this one I preordered, then forgot about it,
then clicked on it in my recommendations and ended up buying it twice...
But it's nice that they at least show you what you bought and when.
I can hardly breathe...
Marii, your nose is so red!
Your delivery is here!
Here it comes!
Whoops.
What's this?!
I think it's the tree I ordered!
It's too big!
I couldn't see how big it was on the website...
You should have made sure!
This is almost like the Amazon jungle...
Yep, that's Jungle for you.
Girls, you alive in there?
I am!
Still breathing!
The leaves are like thorns! They hurt!
Anyway, now that the tree's here,
why don't we begin our Christmas party?
How are we gonna do that with this tree everywhere?!
Are you kidding me? Have some common sense!
The branches are in the way!
It's pitch black!
It's a world of perfect darkness.
We're surrounded by blackness and branches.
What should we do now?
I see a spark of light in the darkness!
Now Marii's nose can do some good!
Everyone laughed at her red nose,
but now she helps us all by bringing light to the dark!
I'm no reindeer!
Let's nosedive into the tree and have a meeting at Marii!
Meeting? Noses? What do you mean?
Like the Maori people, who greet each other by rubbing their noses together!
We nosedive and meet!
Nosewipe?
Why?
We nosedive and meet! Marii's nose will lead the way!
Go into the light!
Into the light!
So I can just leave it all behind and go into the light?
That's a different light!
The tree hit her head.
Don't do it, Kukuru!
To the light... To the light...
A
Ebizou
Sorry, sorry!
Sorry,
I can't go tonight!
> <
- Ebizou
It's a friggin' phone!
What are you doing?!
I was using my phone as a light...
You're so stupid, you violent four-eyes!
Hey! Come out here and say that!
Goddamn it, the tree's in the way!
Now I've got the upper hand.
Only I can use my light to see in the dark!
The light vanished.
Say your prayers, you violent four-eyes!
You've had this one coming for years!
Ouch!
Oh, wrong one.
Marii hit me!
Sorry, Kigu. I didn't see it was you.
Marii turned into a jungle guerilla!
Taste the fear of never knowing when I'll strike in the dark of the jungle!
Who are you, Rambo? Where'd you get that gun?!
From the Jungle!
Now I have the upper hand!
What are you, a Predator?!
Stop! You'll ruin the dressing room!
Why do you look like that?
Fluorescent paint I got from the Jungle.
This is a mud pack I got from the Jungle.
What the hell are you lot buying?!
Gan, are you okay?
Yeah, but you can't have a jungle movie without...
Cannibals!
The Myrtle Tribe!
A
This anime is
full of ordinary dialogue
so that viewers can fully
enjoy how cute the girls are.
That's terrible.
I must stop her, and fast.
There she is!
I can see her!
How...
Are you retarded?
On the battlefield the one with the light is at a disadvantage.
It's gotten even brighter.
Her nose swelled up even more from the punch!
And the light grew along with it!
Amazing!
But it's still too dark.
I could use a bit more light.
It's for the greater good.
The light was so bright that many and more were drawn to it.
A delinquent who mistook it for the lights of a convenience store.
I hope they're not out of fried chicken...
A couple who went to DonQui at night.
Don Quibochi
Isn't that awesome?
The spirits of the dear departed.
I just have to go into the light, right?
The Warrior of Light, Haraguchi.
A CEO who wanted permission to use the light circuit.
Tanaka, as he followed Oota "Light" Hikari.
Bugs.
Squids.
This is one amazing Christmas tree!
A whole lot of people came to our Christmas party! Right, Kigu?
This is the first time we've had so many guests...
Don't make it sound like it's a good thing!
Now all we need is some Christmas boots and it'll be perfect!
I ordered those too.
Your delivery is here!
It's too big!
I couldn't see how big it was on the website...
I don't even want to think about New Year's!
I ordered the decorations already!
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
My name is concealed by my mask.
But people call me the benevolent spirit of Joshiraku,
the true main character who hides in the background.
The twelfth performance of Joshiraku, the one before the last:
The Dreamer Strikes Back, Gotta and Blacks
A
The Dreamer Strikes Back
Gotta
Blacks
will be up for you to see.