This strange story began
on a blistering hot day.
I had received unexpected mail
from an old acquaintance of mine,
but the message was just this:
"Seek the sacred beast from Anzan.
I am at the meeting place
of the four gods. "
Pao, the sender of the message,
was an acquaintance of mine,
but it didn't mean
we kept in touch all that well.
I grew suspicious, and started to research
Pao's current whereabouts.
They say that Pao is one of the three
greatest feng shui masters here on Mars.
But when I found his whereabouts,
he had already left this world.
Are you sure you weren't the one
that sent me this mail?
The one who visits from
the inauspicious back door.
Receive the word from the heavens,
and lead me to the sun stone.
Just like what the Pa Kua told me!
Look out!
Where are you shooting?!
They sure are disrespectful fellows.
The escape route!
Hey? Hey, hey!
- Idiot!
- Shit!
Hey, hey, hey!
Escape route!
Chi of Earth!
That was really close!
I'm glad you're safe.
What are you doing?
Hey, over there, who is that?
I wonder if she's a new girlfriend.
She's rather young for that.
Weird one, hot-dog bun, loved one!
- Maybe she's his secret love-child?
- She's rather old for that.
Child, mild, wild!
But I'm surprised.
I wasn't expecting Pao's daughter
to be this old already.
You probably don't remember,
but I met you once
when you were this little.
How do you know my father?
How?
Just an acquaintance.
It's been ten years already.
But your father sure was unlucky
to be in a traffic accident.
On the way to Jupiter, there was a sudden
spatial fluctuation in hyperspace.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Are you the girlfriend?
Are you the secret love-child?
Rejected!
Mr. Jet, why were you at the graveyard?
Nobody outside the family knows
he got into an accident.
"Seek the sacred beast from Anzan.
I am at the meeting place
of the four gods."
This is...?
Pao sent me this.
- When?
- Three days ago.
Right before the accident.
Please! Can you help me?!
I'm sure this is the whereabouts
of the sun stone!
Sun stone?
The direction, day, and time you arrived
was the best combination for feng shui!
Especially when
you're searching for something!
It was?
It was! Please, Mr. Jet!
Yes. About that, we will have it soon.
Yes, I understand.
How was the boss feeling?
Well...
- There's no way it could be good.
- Of course not.
Let's go!
I didn't have any particular favors
to repay to Pao or this girl,
but I decided to help them for now.
There were too many things
that made me suspicious to leave it alone.
Why did Pao send me mail
right before his death?
What do those words mean?
Who were those guys that attacked us?
And there was something about this girl
named Meifa as well.
This universe is made
of three different Chis.
One is the Chi of Heaven,
the energy that comes from the sun.
One is the Chi of Earth, the energy
that comes from a planet's surface.
And lastly, Chi of Magnetism, the Chi
that organisms like ourselves produce.
Chi from organisms?
The human body always produces
a magnetic field.
That magnetic field
and the magnetic field of the earth,
react to one another to create energy.
Universal feng shui is
the technology that reads
the energies of nature such as this
to use them in everyday life.
Ice cream.
Universal feng shui.
It's not the same thing as fortunetelling?
Other fortunetelling methods
only predict or prognosticate.
However, universal feng shui has the power
to make the bad into the good.
For example, if you were a feng shui
master as powerful as my father...
What's wrong?
I just realized that I never
spent time like this with my father.
Hey, now!
Let me point out that I'm not that old.
If anything, I would be a boyfriend.
No, wait, that would be bad.
What am I saying?
At least I can be an elder brother
or something.
Ice cream.
Let's go, Mr. Jet!
I believe that Anzan refers to here.
The Mountain Hotel Building.
There!
Blue Dragon.
White Tiger.
Black Turtle.
Scarlet Phoenix.
Hey.
I know, the cross-zenith method!
The sun stone is here!
Are you sure?
- There they are. They're right over there.
- All right.
I finally found it.
This must be the sun stone.
This thing?
Mr. Jet?
Out of the way.
What are you doing?
One bottle of lao chu.
I don't need a glass.
Take that!
Hey, who are you guys?
You think we would tell you that easily?
We're from the Blue Snake.
So, you are from a syndicate.
Why are you following us around?
I wouldn't tell you that
even if you killed me.
It was because we couldn't get Pao.
So they told us
to get the recipient of his mail.
I'm telling the truth!
We're on the low end,
so we don't know any more than that!
I'm sure.
Mr. Jet.
My father... is alive?
Pao's words showed us
where this stone was.
Does that mean
Pao is still alive somewhere?
Did he want me to find this stone
and do something with it?
It feels like I created more mysteries
instead of solving them.
For now, I decided to check out
this stone, which was our only clue.
So, this is a piece of the moon
from that gate accident 50 years ago.
We feng shui masters
call it the sun stone.
It's absorbed the fluctuations
of time and space
and conceals a tremendous amount
of energy.
I can only think of it
as a plain old rock.
So, how much would it be if we sold it?
Hey, guys. If you're gonna smoke,
go smoke outside.
What?
You always smoke in here, too!
This into a non-smoking area
starting today.
Hey, now, you're kidding, right?
This ship is my ship... remember?
So, what are you gonna do
with this stone?
I... have no idea.
I don't know what my father is thinking.
Oh, hey, wait!
Ein! Wait!
The Luo Pan.
What?
That can't be. I took the magnet off.
I see. I get it now.
So that's it!
That's it!
If I remember correctly,
my father owned a sun stone as well.
I'm sure that
the two stones are resonating
to show me the whereabouts of my father.
And that's why
Pao made you look for this stone.
But...
I don't know why
my father sent the mail to you, Mr. Jet...
and not to me.
- What do you think?
- They make a good couple.
It's a dangerous combination.
What is?
The more righteous a guy was in his youth,
the more likely he's gonna fall
for a young girl later in life.
Is that so?
Really, guys are so clueless.
My father...
believed in universal feng shui,
but not other people.
So, my mother left the house,
and took me along.
That was seven years ago.
I'm sure my father was able
to find our whereabouts easily.
But he never even tried to look for us.
I'm sure there was a reason behind it.
Why was my father targeted by those men?
Was it because
he was friends with bad people?
Please, tell me the truth!
Who my father really was.
Pao... was the consultant for a syndicate.
That's the truth.
Pao had leaked information to me
about the syndicate,
back when I was a detective.
Pao already wanted out
of the syndicate back then.
However, it's impossible
for someone who knows
important syndicate secrets
to ever leave the group.
I'm sure Pao was afraid that more
bad things would happen to his family.
Well, I'm sure you can confirm it all
when you see him.
Here!
Around here.
There isn't anything here.
How about the radar?
No response.
That can't be. I'm sure this is the place.
Wait. Hold on.
- Do we have guests?
- They sure are persistent.
- Spike, Faye, please take care of them!
- Aren't they your guests?
Help me out
if you don't wanna die with this ship!
What rotten luck of the draw.
Sometimes it's good not to ask
"What's in it for me?"
We're fairies who are going
to grant the princess's wish.
We are?
Unmanned fighters?
So, these would be the seven dwarves.
Shit! They're trying to scare us!
I got it!
- Spike! Come back here!
- What?!
Apparently, if we apply lots of energy
to that stone,
we can draw out all the forces
trapped inside it.
And what are we going to do?
This is an all-or-nothing plan, but...
I don't care what it is, just hurry!
I put it in!
All right.
Blast this rock with your plasma cannon.
What a great plan this is.
Looks like you made it in time, Jet.
Pao! You're...
Meifa. It's been a while.
Pao, you're in unstable territory.
I can't approach any closer than this.
I know. There isn't any oxygen left
in here anyway,
I sent you that mail because
I wanted you to bring my daughter here.
Then, you willed us to be here like this
using feng shui?
Yeah.
That's not true, Pao.
This wasn't your doing.
Meifa is here now...
because she wanted to come here.
You might be right.
Perhaps I was being too hotheaded.
Meifa...
it's wonderful to see you one last time.
I hated you all this time.
I despised you all this time.
But...
Papa.
Now, I don't know if it was a good thing
or a bad thing that we took her along.
In any case,
that's how this strange case ended.
She went back to Mars.
And the smoking ban was lifted
from the living quarters.
Once again, unchanging daily life
has returned, just as it was before.
One thing that has changed, though...
I no longer read the horoscope pages
in magazines.
Too much time has passed by
To lament that we were deeply in love
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart
Cannot heal all the tears in it
Someone cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues
I only want to know
What true sadness is
Sitting in muddy water
Isn't such a bad life
If it ends
After the first time
He came with a whistle.
A man, Andy, made a sudden
appearance on horseback.
Who in the world is he?
Is he an ally or a foe?
Or is he a true cowboy?
The next episode is a shocking sci-fi
macaroni-western epic saga, "Cowboy Funk."
Wait a minute,
isn't this world view a bit different?