THE MURDER CASE
THAT WAS TOO IMPOSSIBLE
THE ZOMBIEMAN MURDER FILE
THE DAY BEFORE
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
kateru katenai janaku
It's not about winning or losing
koko de ore wa omae ni tachimukawa
nakucha ikenai n da!
It's about me taking you on
right here, right now!
seigi no jitensha nori
mumen raida sanjo!
The righteous cyclist,
Mumen Rider, is here!
sorezore kikkake aru keredo
Although we have different motivations,
kokorozasu no wa onaji koto
our goals are the same.
shimin no anzen mamoru tame
warera hiro wa yuku
We heroes are here
to protect the citizens.
jisseki. noryoku. kokedo
zara ni wa ninki made
Accomplishments, skills,
contributions, and popularity!
aa S kyu A kyu B kyu C kyu!
Ah, S Class, A Class, B Class, C Class!
S kyu nana i ore wa kingu!
Seventh in Class S, I am King!
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
kono onsoku no sonikku ga hiro
to issho ni uta nado utaeru wake ga nai!
There's no way I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic,
would sing with you heroes!
tsubekobe ittenai de ma omae mo utae!
Don't be such a smartass,
just sing, alright?
fussorenara chijo saikyo no otoko,
kingu ga soro de utatte yaruze!
Hmpf! Then I, the strongest man on Earth,
King, shall sing the solo!
ikigomi wa yoshi!
naka yoku minna de utao u!
Well said, guys! Let's sing together!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March