THE MURDER CASE
THAT WAS TOO IMPOSSIBLE
His guard may have been down,
but even so, there aren't many humans
who could take out an S-class hero.
Indeed. The killer is probably…
one of us here!
But who was it?
THE ZOMBIEMAN MURDER FILE
THE DAY BEFORE
The story begins a day ago.
We were honored as persons of distinguished service
for stopping an alien invasion and
preventing the largest disaster in history.
In appreciation, the Hero Association
took us on an overnight trip.
That feels good…
It was very generous of the Association to
take us to a hot spring to celebrate our victory.
Though some of us left
the field without fighting…
You're right.
How come we're sharing this place
with a pack of jackasses who didn't lift a finger?!
We had other tasks.
What's more important than fighting aliens?
It's none of your business.
They were taking down
violent criminals and monsters
with bounties on their heads in other towns.
It's all been confirmed.
They left because they figured
the rest of us could handle things without them.
Yeah, well, it all worked out.
I left because I was hungry.
I just want to protect my own town.
I've always got a pile of requests
to get rid of monsters.
I can't lie around all day like you.
What'd you say?!
I had to skip my little sister's piano recital!
Come on, guys. Let's try to get along today.
I could have handled it all by myself.
Hey! You're not supposed to wear swimsuits in a hot spring!
Who cares?!
Jeez…
I doubt that the danger foreseen by Madame Shibabawa has passed.
I've asked you all here today
under the pretext of discussing this matter.
But be that as it may,
I am deeply grateful for your heroic acts
on the day of the attack.
I'd like you all to let loose
and enjoy yourselves tonight.
All right!
Cheers!
I believe this is "Dragon Slayer"!
A truly great sake!
Yeah. Easy to drink, but strong.
Who is it? Who's number one?
Muscle pose!
Are they ever not
putting on a muscle show?
Having fun, Child Emperor?
Oh yeah, kind of.
I see. That's good.
No one would have believed it at the time,
but our peaceful party was about to
turn into a gruesome crime scene…
Let's start with the murder weapon.
Yeah, that's mine.
But I left my katana in the banquet hall.
Someone must've taken it.
You don't believe me?
For starters, we were drinking over there
'till just a moment ago, right?
True.
What? You think we're all
conspiring together?
Atomic Samurai is innocent.
What?
Sitch and I were there too.
You can ask him.
I suppose he can't be a suspect,
so his testimony would be credible.
Besides, we have no motive.
A motive, huh…
Speaking of motives,
I just remembered, Prisoner…
You were staring at Zombieman rather suspiciously!
Yeah… I was thinking it'd be so great…
What would?
If little Zombie here were mine.
However, I restrict myself to violent criminals.
Even then, I never kill them!
What a waste!
But you're the only convict amongst us.
And you escape from prison like it's nothing.
So society would say
the least trustworthy is—
That's discrimination!
I'm just reasoning via
the process of elimination.
In that case,
I have someone in mind too.
I overheard an ominous remark
when you and Zombie were talking.
You asked dear Zombieman if he really
wouldn't die even if you punched him.
Yeah, Genos told me there's a rumor going around that he's immortal.
Don't tell me Master Saitama is a suspect?
I'm just looking at different possibilities
from a rational perspective.
We don't know much about Saitama.
He could be a spy from another organiza—
Well, maybe not with that face.
Look, even if Master Saitama
wanted to kill Zombieman,
he wouldn't need a weapon.
A single punch would—
Wait.
If Master wanted to
test Zombieman's immortality,
he might have used a weapon
to go easy on him.
That would make sense!
Master, do not worry.
I will defend you at your trial.
I didn't do it!
Now, now. The others haven't been cleared yet, either.
Flash has fallen silent
as he stares at the dead body.
Pig God is eating breakfast.
Watchdog Man is still sleeping.
And as for Metal Bat…
I didn't do it.
Unlike the others, I'm underage,
so I didn't drink.
I couldn't have gotten drunk
and done anything stupid…
Wh-What?
You're unusually quiet today.
Lay off! I'm just not
a morning person, that's all!
Now, now…
So who first discovered the body?
Wouldn't they be the prime suspect?
It was the waitress here,
so that's a dead end.
Well… I just ran over
because someone told me…
What? So someone else
discovered the body first?
King!
You…
Why didn't you say anything?
No one asked me.
Please tell us how you found the body.
I was on my way to the vending machine to get a drink
when I found a body on the ground.
I let the front desk know.
That's it.
King, what were you up to last night?
I soaked in the bath in my room,
then went to sleep.
What? This inn is known for
its large outdoor bath.
Why would you use the bath in your room?
Such decisions are mine to make.
There was always something sketchy
about this King guy…
I'm not trying to hide anything.
That sound…
You call it the "King Engine," right?
Am I to assume
you're ready to fight?
If my innocence is under suspicion,
I'm left with no choice.
Jeez!
You're still at it?
If you're all under suspicion,
then I'll just restrain all of you!
Just a moment, Tatsumaki!
Restrain? What's going on?
What?!
Could someone pull this out?
Who attacked you, Zombieman?
Well, I drank quite a bit last night,
so I don't really remember.
But, if I'm not mistaken,
that katana came flying
through the air and impaled me.
Then, because I was drunk,
I must have fallen asleep.
So you're saying my sword
was floating in the air?
Yeah, surrounded by a green light.
Just like that.
Wh-What?
Tatsumaki, what were you doing
after dinner last night?
I don't remember!
Were you perhaps drinking?
I don't know.
I said, I don't remember!
You think you're gonna get away
with a lame excuse like that?
What?!
Look, I know Zombieman doesn't die
when he gets killed!
If I wanted him dead,
I wouldn't do something this half-assed.
Let's just forget it already.
As we can all see, Zombieman is fine.
Yeah, doesn't bother me.
Stuff like this happens all
the time when you drink.
Nah. Not really.
Okay, let's break it up.
Let's hit the baths, Iai.
Oh… right!
Child Emperor, do you have a minute?
Th-This is…
So it really was Tatsumaki who did it.
She looks pretty drunk.
But why on earth would she do this?
I know Zombieman doesn't die
when he gets killed!
Oh, I get it!
She knew about Zombieman's regeneration and was just enjoying herself…
Then again,
what would make Tatsumaki let herself get that drunk?
So the little brat caused all that trouble?
But why would she do something like that?
That is…
…most likely your fault, Master.
I'm done.
Here.
I still don't like drinking…
Don't like drinking?
Stop acting grown-up.
You're a kid.
Of course you shouldn't be drinking!
Kids should drink orange juice or something!
Huh? How dare you—
I'll go order one for you right now.
Tatsumaki's pride got hurt,
so she forced herself
to drink more.
You know, that hot spring
sure felt great, huh, Genos?
Yes!
aa, sore
Ah, c'mon
aa, yoisho
Ah, heave-ho
aa, sore sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon!
kateru katenai janaku
It's not about winning or losing
koko de ore wa omae ni tachimukawa
nakucha ikenai n da!
It's about me taking you on
right here, right now!
seigi no jitensha nori
mumen raida sanjo!
The righteous cyclist,
Mumen Rider, is here!
sorezore kikkake aru keredo
Although we have different motivations,
kokorozasu no wa onaji koto
our goals are the same.
shimin no anzen mamoru tame
warera hiro wa yuku
We heroes are here
to protect the citizens.
jisseki. noryoku. kokedo
zara ni wa ninki made
Accomplishments, skills,
contributions, and popularity!
aa S kyu A kyu B kyu C kyu!
Ah, S Class, A Class, B Class, C Class!
S kyu nana i ore wa kingu!
Seventh in Class S, I am King!
wanpan ondo
One-Punch March
kono onsoku no sonikku ga hiro
to issho ni uta nado utaeru wake ga nai!
There's no way I, Speed-o'-Sound Sonic,
would sing with you heroes!
tsubekobe ittenai de ma omae mo utae!
Don't be such a smartass,
just sing, alright?
fussorenara chijo saikyo no otoko,
kingu ga soro de utatte yaruze!
Hmpf! Then I, the strongest man on Earth,
King, shall sing the solo!
ikigomi wa yoshi!
naka yoku minna de utao u!
Well said, guys! Let's sing together!
aa, sore sore sore
Ah, c'mon c'mon c'mon!
ichigeki hissatsu one punch
One-hit KO, One Punch
One-Punch March
wanpan ondo
odore ya utae ya tatakae ya
Dance! Sing! Fight!
wanpan ah ondo
One-Punch March