Review
Akihisa and friends, suddenly involved in an inter-grade test of courage,
were putting up a tough fight against the clever ploys of the third-years, including the Eversummer pair.
Roll, roll, roll... Boom!
Whoa! Please stop it, Lord!
Thump.
What should we do, Yuuji?
The third-years already got a bunch of us.
It'll be fine.
We have a secret weapon.
A secret weapon?
A se-ret weapon?
hi!! mondai: hitori to futari docchi ga suteki?
Hi!! 問題: ひとりとふたりどっちが素敵？
Hi!! Here's a question:
Alone or together, which one is more wonderful?
(hai! oh~ let's go)
(はい！Oh~ Let's Go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go)
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future starts to spin.
dokomade hanasouka? minai furi? (nande)
どこまで話そうか?見ないふり？（なんで）
How long do we intend to just talk?
And pretend to not see each other? (Why?)
ah soo, ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Ah yes, the wide world expands, depending upon my feelings.
kyou mo daisuki (suki)
今日もだいすき（すき）
I love you today, as well. (Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you.
watashi no baka (baka) hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da
わたしのバカ（バカ）星の数よりもバカだっ
My idiot (idiot!) So much more stupid than there are stars in the sky.
sunao ni narezu ni
素直になれずに
I had a dream, in which I walked together with you...
kimi to aruku yume wo mita (hai)
君と歩く夢を見た（はい）
being my honest self.
gomen ne datte! koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね だって!恋としらなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but it's just... I hadn't known it to be love then.
kotaete kimi to
答えって 君と
Answer me this: You and
nazo tasu watashi wa
?+私=
something unknown plus me equals
mugen no jump!! (hai! oh~ let's go)
無限のJUMP!! (はい！Oh~ Let's GO!)
an infinite jump!! (Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai! hands up)
（はい！Hands Up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
(hai! all right)
(はい！All Right!)
(Yes! All right!)
Question 13
Idiots, Tests, and Summoned Beings!
So…
we wound up together.
Th-This isn't r-really scary at—
A-Are you all right, Minami?
I-I'm just not used to these Japanese ghouls.
If they were German—
I can't breathe, Minami!
Aki!
Let's go back, Aki!
Wh-What is this?
Minami's different from usual.
Why is my heart beating so—
That was a pretty close call.
Akihisa
Any pig that seduces my darling shall be eliminated.
Let's run, Minami!
I won't let you get away, Darling!
I'll do everything I can to...
Shimizu-san, right now you look more monstrous than any ghoul or specter.
They couldn't have gone this way.
Oh well. Let's look somewhere else, Shimizu-san.
Darling!
The coast is clear.
Are they really gone?
It's about time you got used to Japanese ghouls, Minami.
It's fine. I can just go live in Germany.
But it'd be kinda lonely.
I won't be lonely at all!
I have friends in Germany, you know.
Um, that's not what I meant.
I'm saying we'd be lonely without you.
Y-Yeah, right. You're just saying that to be nice.
It's the truth! We're always together,
so it's hard to imagine you not being there.
Always together...
What's wrong, Minami?
Then what if I said I'd always be by your side?
My table's always cold 'cause
the wind blows straight through the legs?
That's not it! I'm asking if...
You're asking if?
I'm saying I... I...
Minami? What—
I'm back.
Welcome back, Akihisa-kun.
Where's Minami?
I left her to sleep in the nurse's office.
I think she pushed herself a little too hard.
Well done, Akihisa. The operation was a success.
Checkpoint
Hand over my darling!
M-Monsters...
By secret weapon did you mean...
Yeah, them.
Huh? I get that Shimizu-san is looking for Minami,
but what's Kubo-kun doing there?
Could Kubo have a thing for Shimizu?
Akihisa, you're so cruel.
You'll make him cry.
Too mean.
You've made us wait quite a while.
We let our guard down this morning,
but let us show you everything we third-years are capable of—
Excuse me, but did Yoshii-kun and Shimada-san come this way?
Bastard! Wait 'til we're finished talking!
Don't you look down on us!
We'll teach you how to respect your elders! Summon!
Physics
Oh well. Summon!
Summon!
What?!
They have over four hundred points?
Unbelievable!
They must be total math and science nerds.
Damn it! Quit dodging!
Cut it out already!
You're next.
Eversummer Pair Wins
I can't believe Kubo-kun lost.
Next is...
our turn.
Right! You haven't gone yet.
But Shouko aside, my physics score is 150 at best.
It'll be a tough match.
If only there were another pair left.
There is another pair.
Right here.
Me?
Well, I didn't get disqualified since I just withdrew,
but Minami...
Oh, right!
There's one more person here who hasn't been disqualified.
One more?
Um...
Might you be referring to me?
But Himeji-san is afraid of ghouls. We can't force her to—
I'll do it!
Watching Minami-chan has inspired me to do my part.
I'll go through the haunted house with you!
Walk slowly, okay?
S-Sure.
I'm not scared. I'm not scared since I'm with you!
I'm not scared at all! Not in the slightest!
Um, Himeji-san?
Y-Yes?
Thanks for participating.
I should be thanking you.
I'm always so helpless, and I rely on you constantly.
Oh no, not at all. I'm glad that you can rely on me.
You're cute, smart, and even kind.
I feel like I'm guarding a princess.
Well, the problem is you're with someone like me, who's—
Himeji-san?
I'm nothing like a princess.
I'm slow and jealous, and I fall down at the critical moment.
I'm full of faults.
That's not true—
It is true!
And you don't even realize it.
Isn't the reason you never notice my faults,
the distance you keep between us?
The distance between us?
You try to be nice to me and hold back.
You look at me, but I don't think you really see me.
Akihisa, how do you feel about me—
Himeji-san?
Question 12
Imagine the following situation
and answer the question.
It's been decided that you'll go on a
couples' trip with your beloved
boyfriend. As the plane is taking off,
you remember you forgot
something.
What was it that you forgot?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Medication, such as headache pills
and stomach medicine.
Teacher's Comment
This was a psychological test to see
what you desire from the person
you love.The thing you forgot indicates
qualities you lack. The fact that you
didn't notice before take-off means
that you believe the one who
accompanied you will be your
supplement. It seems you are looking
for comfort from your boyfriend,
Himeji.
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
Handcuffs.
Teacher's Comment
The problem here is that you wanted
to bring them in the first place.
Kudou Aiko's Answer
To wear underwear.
Teacher's Comment
What exactly do you want from the
person you love?
Himeji-san!
Huh? Was there a wall here?
Thank God.
Are you—
Ugly?
Shut up. And hands off.
Wait, Yuuji?
Huh? Where's Himeji-san?
Wait, huh?
Where are we?
Himeji's probably met up with Shouko by now.
Could that be...
Yeah, it's that Eversummer pair again.
It'd be tough to make Shouko or me scream, after all.
You have a point.
So they turned off the lights for a second, separated us,
and switched our partners.
I see.
Well, I'm sure Shouko and Himeji will make the strongest pair.
It's all cool.
So, what's the truth?
For some reason, being alone with Shouko in here,
makes me think of being attacked with a bat covered with nails.
Oh, I see Kirishima in the corner over there.
Akihisa Barrier!
I can totally see through you.
Mizuki, are you all right?
Y-Yes, somehow.
This voice is...
Hi—
Himeji!
I don't hear anything!
I don't hear anyone whispering to me at all!
Stop it. It's making her worse!
They'll be disqualified if we waltz up to them and make them scream!
Oh yeah.
Let's keep our distance for now.
Mizuki, it's not scary. It's not scary.
Ooga booga booga!
I'm all right. I'm not scared!
I'm not scared...
Mizuki, there's a good girl.
Himeji-san.
Well, you might be worried,
but I'm sure she's trying, in her own way.
Trying in her own way?
To get close to us so we can help each other out as a team.
Yuuji, then what you said earlier was...
Himeji was worried.
She thought she might just be a burden to everyone.
Himeji-san...
It's all right, Mizuki. They aren't scary.
They aren't scary. I'll try my best!
Do your best! Do your best, Himeji-san!
Final Checkpoint
Where are we?
What?
Damn, you girls weren't disqualified?
This is gonna be a pain in the ass.
I thought those scum, Sakamoto and Yoshii,
would be first up for a beating.
They ran off, right?
They're garbage, after all.
They aren't garbage.
Huh?
They aren't!
Not garbage?
They're nothing but troublemaking dumbasses!
What else could we call them?
How 'bout this?
The dregs of society?
That's an insult to dregs.
They should just let themselves get picked up,
with the rest of the trash!
Totally, a pair of brain-dead 'tards like them need—
Why must you be so cruel to them?
Certainly, their grades are bad, and they do cause trouble,
but how can you dismiss them as garbage just because of that?
You don't even know!
You have no idea how kind they are!
Huh?
Shouldn't you know better than anyone,
just how dumb they are?
Why are you judging them based solely on their scores?
They have many good qualities,
that simple grades can't measure!
Cut the crap! We don't care about scum like them!
Akihisa-kun and Sakamoto...
aren't scum or garbage...
no matter what you say!
How annoying.
Beat it, you losers!
We're going anyway.
Let's go, Mizuki.
You heard her, Yuuji.
She thinks we're kind.
First I've heard of it.
I'm not as much of a slacker as you,
but I thought I was a pretty cool slacker.
Same here. I'm not as useless as you,
but at least I'm aware of my shortcomings.
Man, what a waste.
Himeji just wasted all the effort,
we put into getting them together.
Exactly. I can't believe they got under her skin like that.
Shall we go, Akihisa?
Sure, Yuuji.
It's all-out war now, you bastards!
Jeez, when are they gonna show up?
With our scores, they'll prob'ly chicken out.
'Sup, guys!
Took you long enough!
Let's get started then.
Summon!
Before that, why don't we decide on the penalty?
Penalty?
You guys scheming again?
Don't let that frighten you.
You guys were the ones who wanted the penalty game.
Fine. What about it?
"The losers do whatever the winners want." How about that?
Fine with us.
Let's rumble!
Summon!
What's with those scores?
We'll crush 'em like ants!
Keep on yakking. You'll see.
Let's go, Akihisa.
Okay, Yuuji.
Dash!
What the—  they ran away!
After them!
Stop right there!
Where did they go?
Tsunemura, over there!
Damn, what a pain in the ass!
You guys getting tired already?
Over there!
Where are they?
Yoohoo, we're over here!
Damn it!
You take running lessons from a turtle?
Hey, that's rude!
I didn't know they were that slow.
They're just holding back.
Right, guys?
Yoshii! Sakamoto!
Show yourself!
Why don't you try actually using that brain you're so proud of?
I'm getting bored here.
You haven't found us yet?
We can read you guys...
...like a wide open book!
They disappeared!
Did we step out of the physics field?
Too bad.
This is just a trap.
It's we who've seen through your plan.
When did they—
Hasegawa-sensei, your permission to start the battle!
Granted!
Summoned Beings: Summon!
This is now the math field!
Now you can't rely on your great physics scores!
That's cheating!
I don't remember any rule saying we had to,
fight at the checkpoint.
Or are you guys just too scared to fight,
in any field but physics?
We excel in science and math!
We won't lose in math!
Summon!
Shit!
We got thrashed by that girl and the four-eyes!
And you took advantage of it! Damn you!
Don't screw with us!
Too late to whine about it now.
What did you say?!
There's one good thing about being an idiot.
When they really get into something,
they can simple-mindedly devote all of their attention to it.
I guess some people would just call them obsessed,
but to them that's high praise!
Shut the hell up!
What I'm getting at is...
He booted the head!
...you switched these idiots on!
Why...
did we lose to such idiots?
We've won.
You do remember our promise, don't you?
What're you going to make us do?
That's obvious.
Himeji-san...
Yoshii.
Kirishima-san?
if you're looking for her, she's on the roof.
Hurry up; she's waiting.
Thanks, Kirishima-san.
That's pretty considerate of you.
Not really.
I just like those who try their best,
even when they're afraid.
I really like people like that.
I can't be bothered to do my best,
even if it's nothing scary.
I'll leave it at that for you.
Akihisa-kun...
We're all going out for crêpes to celebrate our victory.
Just now, those two third-years came to apologize.
I have you to thank for that, don't I?
I'm sorry for always troubling you!
It's nothing!
You're certainly no princess.
Huh?
Well, no princess would have the courage,
to snap at those third-years.
Uh, that was...
Thanks. I was really happy.
We were able to do our best, thanks to what you said.
Thank you for saying that.
Should we go? They're probably waiting for us.
Um, there's something I wanted to ask you.
To ask me?
Yes.
Um...
When are you going to start calling me "Mizuki"?
Wha...?!
You always use Minami's given name,
but you never do the same for me!
The reason is, well, it's kinda complicated—
Then explain.
Uh... we went to elementary school together, remember?
Yes.
So if I called you "Mizuki-chan" just like back then,
it'd be kinda embarrassing for me.
You're lying!
You haven't called me by my name even once,
since we started high school!
That's because...
You won't laugh?
I won't!
No matter what?
No matter what!
Actually...
Yes?
I was practicing...
calling you by your name...
Okay...
Argh! Forget about it! We never had this conversation!
Well then, I'll tell you one of my secrets.
Actually...
I haven't given up on my first love.
Hurry up, Akihisa!
Wait! Wh-What did you just—
Aki! Why did you go running off without telling me?
Minami!
You promised to be by my side forever, didn't you?
Ehhh?!
What's going on, Akihisa-kun?
Get lost, Akihisa!
We didn't complete the challenge together.
That means instant marriage.
No way in hell!
Yuuji, wait!
Let's complete it together.
Hey, wait up!
You owe me an explanation!
Stop there!
Jeez, it always ends up like this, doesn't it?
Yep.
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) den (Po!) kyuu (Pa!) pikkanko (Hai)
閃いて (Pa!) 輝いて (Pi!) 電 (Po!) 球 (Pa!) ぴっかんこ （はいっ）
Flashing (Pa!) Sparkling (Pi!) light (Po!) bulb (Pa!) That's right (Yes)
shinten shinaiyo
進展しないよ
I can't move ahead,
dare ka jyama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
because someone is hindering me... No, no!
zenzen tarinai sorega mondai no koubaisuu
ぜんぜん足りない　それが問題の公倍数
Nothing that I do is enough, which is an all too common problem.
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I will come to understand it.
naniga hontou no koto... Baby?
何が本当のこと... Baby?
What is the truth of it... Baby?
mitetara kokode zukai shite yo Baby!
見てたらここで図解してよBaby！
If we were to see each other, I would draw you a schematic of it, baby!
kotobamo kazumo kimi wo arasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
I wouldn't show you words or numbers.
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to (kyuuu Paaaaaan!) N no jiryoku de
心がビリビリする  S と（きゅーっ　Paaaaaan!） N の磁力で
Our hearts are flittering about from the
magnetic force of the North and South Poles.
S, S, Super kuttsuite Number I say No.1 boy!
(S, S, Super くっついて Number I say No.1 boy!)
S, S, Super numbers close together. I say No.1 boy!
omedetou!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ima kara kimi wa my, ma, my otakara
いまから君は My, ma, my ゛お-た-か-ら゛
From now on, you're my, my, my "treasure."
tokubetsu nanda dounattemo
特別なんだどうなっても
Just for you, no matter what happens,
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I will hold you tightly, tightly and never let go.
watashi wa koishitai yume ni kenkai wa iranai
私は恋したい　夢に限界はいらない
I want to be in love, and dreams have no need for boundaries, so...
tokubetsu dayone acchattamon
特別だよね　会っちゃったもん
just for me, since we met here by chance...
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
you will forgive me, won't you?
Hirameite (Pa!) kagayaite (Pi!) sei (Po!) kai (Pa!) pittanko (gyuu)
閃いた (Pa!)　輝いた (Pi!) 正　(Po!)　解　(Pa!)　ぴったんこ（ぎゅっ）
It flashed (Pa!) It sparkled (Po!) right (Po!) answer (Pa!) That's right (Embrace)
Don't run in the corridors, dammit!
Good grief.
They really are a bunch of idiots.