Translator
midsummer
Song
Translators
midsummer
Korokun
Translation
Checker
midsummer
Editor
Sumiregawa-kun
Karaoke FX
euronymous
Quality Checkers
phoenixmyst
mattchewwu2
Rika-chama
Tressflin
Timer
Yuurisan(s)
Typesetter
ThaEagle
Encoder
Bachstelze
Presented by
www.yuurisan-subs.org
&
www.m33w-fansubs.com
Please purchase the media when it becomes available in your region!
Come on now!
And that's how we'll do it.
Roger.
As for the initiation of the mission—
Are you headed out, Kana-chan?
Good morning!
Immediately going to spend her pay, I see.
Not all of it!
I'm finally able to send some back home so I thought it'd be nice to send a present along with it.
And then after that...
A little reward for yourself as well?
Yes!
Because the first month was training, you didn't get paid for it.
You must be happy!
Yeah.  But I was surprised!
I had heard that it's expected for wages to be late, and that it's normally provided in the form of military currency...
Here you are!  Good work.
Thank you very much!
I didn't think I'd get real money, and on time too!
Obviously you would!
I mean, that's why our platoon has—
Kanata!  That is—  Uh...
There's been a market set up in town today!
You've never seen one before, right?
Your first paycheck and your first day off.  There are all sorts of firsts for you today, aren't there, Kana-chan?
Forget about work and go enjoy yourself!
Right!
Okay!  I'll be back later!
I told you not to make her suspicious!
But really, common sense tells you it's impossible we'd be paid on time out here, in the middle of nowhere!
And yet, Kanata believed it so easily...
Her innocent gullibility is one of her best qualities.
Yeah.
Unlike you guys, who were immediately suspicious of where the money came from.
Don't you know it!
Yeah.
All right then.
Let's forget about our serious jobs too, shall we?
Well distilled!
Isn't it?
But there is one problem...
I won't be lowering the price any further.
I-I'm sorry!  I got a little too caught up—
Seems like all the preparations are complete?
Yeah.  All without a hitch.
There's a problem on my end though.
And I have a suggestion as to what you should do about it.
Will you accept it?
Could you possibly explain yourself more clearly?
Of course.
This one is cute too!
So you all are the ones selling these?
Have you taken a liking to the goods then?
They're not bad.
But you see, there's just one little problem.
Oh?  And what might that be?
To sell even just this many of them would take a lot of work.
And when we think about it, it's a little too much work for us...
And so—
Not giving discounts is part of our policy.
The price itself is a part of its delicate flavor.
No one's asking you to lower the price.
We'll take all of them!
Hold it right there!
If you want to shoot, go ahead and try it.
Of course, before you manage that, this thing will blow a hole right through your head instead.
Then—!
Not very intelligent, are we?
This is your punishment for looking poorly on us.
Sleep well, boys.
I tried to tell you.
Hey.
Are you two with them?
Mishio-chan!
T-The car!
Boss!
Give it up!
But what about the Big Boss' gifts?!
That's only worth something if we're still alive to give them to him!
Boss!
No one told me that there were such dangerous people here!
I'm never coming back to this town again!
They're gone.
Is that so?
Then that's all, everyone!
Man, my heart was pounding!
Looks like we managed to fake them out, huh?
We thank you for your cooperation!
Oh, no.  No need for thanks.  With the central mafia out of the way, our business will go up as well.
You watch out for us and we'll watch out for you!  Right?
But of course... you'll be reimbursing us for our roles in this little play, won't you?
Oh, dear!  Mikael-san, you're such a joker.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not joking at all.
We're now in the realm of business, aren't we?
Should I take care of this?
Were you guys the ones who crushed those vagrants' car?
It wasn't you?
What happened?
No...
It looks like someone crushed their car pretty well.
And inside there's a heap of war spoils they've hounded up and bought.
I'll pretend as if I bought them and we'll split the profit equally.  How's that?
Great.
Then we have a deal.
Wonderful.
Guess this farce is finally over.
But I was just a bit surprised.
At what?
'Cause, well, you seemed to really be into it, Rio-sempai.
If it were to get out that we illegally distilled this, we
wouldn't get off with just a court-martial.
Violation of monopoly and tax laws, too.
At worst, treason, as well.
Isn't that right?
This is a sidejob that we took over from our predecessors, but Rio's never once opposed it.
I found it somewhat unexpected, also.
Well, I was shocked at the beginning, too.
When I learned that the calvados my mother so loved was made at the bastion.
Then the reason why you ended up assigned to this troop...
might have been perhaps because your mother guided you here.
Okay!  I'll be back later!
Yumina-oneechan!
I'm ready!  Look!
It looks wonderful, Seiya-san.
Mishio-san?
Today's their first visit to the church.
The priest will also be present.
So for today at least—
No!
Don't cause trouble for Sis, Mishio!
What's so bad about just doing up your hair?
No!  I won't!
Why not!
You always tell me to be good and just do it!
Shut up, Seiya!
You mustn't do things like that, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10 yen and 25 sen...
What the hell, missy?
I-I'm sorry!  I got a little too caught up—
Man.  Watch yourself.
They're the problem.
It seems they've managed to get wind of the deal.
Are you all right?
Yes.
But more importantly, Naomi-san—!
What should I do?
Huh?
This is the first time I've had enough money in my wallet to buy it.
If I asked for it now, I could actually end up buying it, couldn't I?
Say, what would you do if someone came by and snatched it up?
Is there someone who said they wanted it?!
No, that was just a "what-if" situation.
Mm, let me see, if that happened...
Right!  I would tell them that dolphins are very scary animals that will even eat humans!  And make them give up.
You're a genius!
Oh, and that dolphin?
I'll set it aside for you until you say that you don't want it anymore, so don't worry about it, okay?
Then I suppose I'll pick up everyone's presents first!
Let's see... Poppa and Momma, Grandpa and Grandma, Grandpa and Grandma from Waren, Great-Grandma, and...
one for Grandma Nanae next door, too!
Wow... they're selling all sorts of things!
Something like this!
Sorry...
Oh... Mishio-chan?
Are you shopping?
She says she's looking for a box or something.
"A box"?
Have you seen anything like this?
Sorry, I haven't.
Shall I help you look for it?
Kanata, what are you doing?
Ah!  Well you see, I came here to buy some presents.
I was hoping to find some wonderful things to send back to my family in the country.
But I'm not in a hurry, so—
I don't need your help!
I wonder what happened with Mishio-chan...
T-This is really...
Pretty, isn't it?
This one's cute too!
Yumina-san...?
Ah, Kanata-san... have you seen Mishio-san by chance?
What?
"A box"?
Yeah.  She said it was something important.
I see...
When her mother passed away, all of their belongings fell into other people's hands.
That box is supposedly a memento of her mother that was also taken at that time.
Every time there's a market that comes in,
she thinks that maybe, just maybe...
I've... said something I shouldn't have.
I received my wages for the first time yesterday.
And so I told her that I was here to buy presents to send home to my family.
That's just fine.
Right now, I — actually, we have every intention of being Mishio's family.
If Mishio is still envious of others, that's entirely because I haven't reached that goal yet.
Hey, Mama!
Which is more important, me or your treasure box?
This one right here!
Mama...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
And these are the famous Treize firecrackers!
They sound great!
How about it?
Sis...
Yumina-oneechan...
Sis!
Mishio-chan!
T-The car!
I'm sorry it wasn't Yumina-san.
Sis!
Yumina-oneechan!
Thanks.
Job well done!
All right then...
Um...
O-Oh!  What's the matter?
It couldn't be that... that's your car, is it, Naomi-san?
No way, it was you guys who—!
We're so sorry!  Ah!  Here's 150 yen as compensation...
Well done, you two.
Keep that safe, will you?
I've already gotten my payment.
N-Naomi-san, that box!
Huh?
These ideograms mean "beautiful stalk of rice."
If you carve these into her seal, I'm sure she will have a plentiful, thriving life, like a full field of rice.
My...
Miho, it's good that you received such a nice name, isn't it?
Did you find Mishio-san?
I had planned to devote myself to becoming family for that girl, but I'm still an amateur.
No, you're doing your best.
Mishio-san!
Oh, how wonderful!  You've found it, haven't you?
Treasure it.  Treasure those irreplaceable memories of your mother.
That's not it!
This... I want Yumina to have this.
Mishio is a child who lost her parents and so was taken in by the church.
First, her father departed for the front and did not return...
And her mother?
Mishio's family lived on the eastern border, in a town named Vingt.
You don't mean—
Yes, they lived in the town attacked by that invisible death reaper.
And when the two of them came to Seize, her mother was already showing symptoms of illness, so soon after...
Mama said to me...
that she was sorry she couldn't do my hair for me anymore.
And also... and also, that I should have the person who would care for me the most from now on to do it for me.
Will you do it for me, Yumina?
People live on.
Even if we are parted from our loved ones and so go through
times so tough that we think we'll pass on,
despite that, we will still live on.
We're still able to live on.
That strength is a very sad, very precious thing.
I'm... sorry.
Thanks, Sis.
Everyone's already in there.
Right!  I'll be right there!
You're tired, aren't you?
Yeah.  If I could've, I even wanted to skip on washing my hair, but... well, things happened.
Okay then!
In that case, sempai, please let me dry your hair for you!
I've always wanted to touch it!
In the end, you didn't end up buying the dolphin, did you?
I had thought that was going to be your reward to yourself.
Rio-sempai, do you believe in fate?
What's this, all of a sudden?
It's just that... something happened today which made me think of it.
And that was more than enough for my reward.
I don't believe in it, actually.
I hate things that are already decided ahead of time,
or given to you from the beginning.
Really?
Only... well.
It might be possible that the pure coincidences that someone creates may cause ripples
that could in turn cause big changes in other people's lives.
If you can call that fate, then maybe...
D-flat.
It looks like you also had a wonderful day today, too, sempai.
Next time, Crickets Chirping: Offerings to the Deceased!