Starlight.
It's the story of goddesses drawn by the glow of the heavens.
They may fight and argue and disagree,
but there are ties that bind them together.
Yet their story is a tragedy.
An eternal parting waits at its end.
Let us go,
to pluck that Star together!
Their dream could never come true.
That stage and those singing voices
draw us in and compel us.
Let's go to that stage.
To that shining Star,
together!
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Who shall be the one to grasp hold of that Star?
To stand at the peak of that tower?
A quietly kindled flame now blazes and consumes my heart
Whatever fate might bring
We dance on this stage of our own will
to
bi
ta
te
And we take flight!
I AM REBORN
I'm certain of what I saw on that day
The sparkle of those scattering stars
Shine on me until my fingers touch yours
From across a promise faded by time
The true story begins before the curtain rises
And it unfolds before our very eyes
It's here, in the place where I was reborn
That I found you once more
Dear Kagura Hikari-sama,
As the days of cold weather continue, I hope the season finds you well.
Today finds Aijo Karen, Girl of the Stage,
in good cheer as always.
Huh?
Oh, guess what?
The 99th Seisho Festival's performance of
Starlight went off without a hitch!
It was our very first performance here at Seisho Music Academy,
but we all worked together and created a really great stage.
Now isn't the time be resting on my laurels, though.
I'm definitely getting the role of Flora next year,
and I want you here to see it, Hikari-chan.
Wouldn't that be nice?
I'm working hard every day to keep my promise with you, Hikari-chan!
Really, I am!
So you should do the same.
Oh, but overexerting yourself is a big non, non!
I'll write again soon.
Sincerely yours, Aijo Karen.
Off I go.
Karen, thank you for all your letters.
Every day is busy with lessons, but I too am running forward.
Towards the stage we promised on.
This is where I came to become a Star—
the Royal Academy of Theatrical Actors.
Acting, directing, and playwriting,
as well as set, lighting, and sound design.
It is a theatrical school where those aiming for
a future on the stage may study every aspect of its craft.
In classes divided by discipline, we study a specialized curriculum
covering everything from the latest stage theory
to practical costume and stage construction.
We receive world-class instruction from a teaching staff made up entirely of working theatre professionals.
My classmates gathered here from
all over the world following the same dream.
Not a moment's slack is permitted.
We approach every day in earnest,
as if we are standing on a real stage.
I can't be satisfied with the supporting role in the midterm performance.
With ever greater skill, with ever greater beauty,
always aiming for the stage on which we promised...
Hikari-chan!
You can't go away!
Karen, you know crybabies don't get to be Stars!
What?!
But Hikari-chan, if you go to Dondon—
London.
I can't do Starlight all by myself!
I made up my mind!
You're not going to London?!
Until I become a Star, I'm not coming back!
I'm not gonna see you, either!
But why? But why?
Why? Why?
Why?!
If I stay here, you'll never stop making me spoil you.
Don't say that!
Can we talk on the phone?
No.
O-Okay then...
What about letters?
You don't even have to write any, Hikari-chan!
Just read the ones I write to you!
Okay?
Okay.
Karen.
Hikari-chan!
Let's meet on the stage.
Yeah! It's a promise!
No, that's not it.
It's destiny!
Destiny?
Yeah!
Tokyo
Souvenier City
I was putting up a front for Karen then,
but unless I said those things and pushed her away,
I wouldn't have been able to resist wanting to see her too.
"I love the stage, and I love Starlight."
It's because Karen said those words to me
that I can run.
We'll meet again in the spotlight.
On the stage, where Karen waits for me.
To become Stars, together!
So I can't let myself get complacent over what I've already achieved.
Higher, higher, higher!
Towards even greater heights!
What is this place?
Revues are enchanting stage performances
with songs and dances.
A giraffe?!
It seems you'd prefer Japanese.
I understand.
A Revue.
Song and dance interwoven on the mesmerizing stage.
In the auditions which will be starting henceforth,
the one who presents us with the most radiant Revue
shall obtain the Star Tiara
and find open to her the path to the Top Star.
Top Star?
The one who stands upon the fated stage,
who lets forth unending radiance,
who brings all her abilities to full bloom,
who shines across time itself—
an eternal leading lady.
The fated stage...
Will you participate in the auditions?
I understand.
Karen, I'm waiting for you.
On the fated stage!
This can't be...
The auditions are hereby concluded.
Huh?
Wow, what's up with Judy?
She's really blossoming lately!
That jump and the pirouette she just executed were gorgeous!
What on earth were those auditions?
The oppression of our countrymen,
the ravages of incessant war,
and the despotism of our emperor!
No longer shall we turn a blind eye to your tyranny!
And what on earth happened to me?
Our brotherhood of knights will see justice carried out
and the dignity of our people restored!
This stage is so important to me,
but I feel nothing.
No nervousness as I take the stage.
No exhilaration as I sing.
My right-hand man,
dearest friend of my own son—
so you, too, betray me in the end!
Every radiant thing I've ever felt on the stage...
Why?
Why don't I feel a thing?
Even if one day I must face him in battle,
Are they... all gone?
The 130 grams I lost.
A tube of my favorite hand cream.
A salmon sandwich from Cross Town.
My paperback edition of Macbeth.
Eleven two-pound coins.
The weight of one kidney.
What have I lost?
What happened to me?
I feel nothing.
I was rushed into it.
It feels like I just jumped
into it without any preparation.
But now I can't remember anything.
What was I standing on the stage for?
What did I come to this school in pursuit of?
Oh, that's right. I know.
Karen and I made a pro—
Karen.
No...
Just now,
the promise I made with Karen, I could barely—
What's wrong with me?
What's happening?
The audition!
No.
No!
Answer me.
Answer me!
Answer me, giraffe!
I'm not going to forgive you for this.
At this rate, I'm...
"In the auditions, the one who presents us with the most radiant Revue
shall obtain the Star Tiara
and find open to her the path to the Top Star."
However, those who are defeated will have everything taken from them.
Everything, down to their dearest radiance.
I understand.
You deceived me.
A considerable amount of fuel is necessary for the birth of a Top Star.
And that was the radiance you took from me?
For you to retain this much radiance was beyond my estimation.
Allow me to offer you another chance.
The next auditions.
They will take place in Japan.
The one who presents us with the most radiant Revue
shall find open to her the path to the Top Star.
I can participate again?
But why?
A Girl of the Stage who has lost everything.
A fated stage that defies all estimation.
I wish to see it.
I'll participate.
Then let us begin the proceedings.
Where in Japan?
Even if, one day, you must face her in battle?
Hey!
Answer me!
A Revue of Loneliness
Slipping through my bravely outstretched hand,
the oath I took that day that fell into the deepest depths.
I rise again to the stage of my destiny,
even if only tragedy awaits me there.
Student of the 99th cohort, Kagura Hikari!
Everything is for Starlight!
We will now begin the sixth day of auditions with this Revue of Loneliness.
Sing, dance, and take from one another as you aim to become the Top Star!
For the promise on which I swore
chikatta yakusoku no tame
All is well; I'll be afraid no more
ii no, kowagaranaide
The sword I hold at the ready quivering
kamaeta ken ga furuete
How pitiful.
All you have is that tiny little sword.
You must have gone through so much pain.
To my hands descends a tiny, sparkling thing
chiisana kirameki ga atte
But it's alright.
Don't worry,
I've got you now!
Farewell to this world that turns with such sorrow
kanashinde mawaru sekai ni sayonara wo
Solely to protect the one I treasure
daiji na hito dake wo mamotte
There's nothing to fear.
You're one of us now, Hikari-chan!
(And then)
(soshite)
Time after time
nandomo
(Time after time)
(nandomo)
I'll turn back again in the face of despair
zetsubou no mae de orikaesu
Sorrows, farewells, and frustrations—
everything that causes a Girl of the Stage pain.
My repeat performance will protect you from it all!
Karen.
What's driven you this far?
I made a promise with Hikari-chan!
Tell me why, Hikari-chan.
What are you doing this for?
Karen is... My destiny is...
It's waiting for me!
I only meant to try and impress Karen a little.
The stage.
Plays.
Musicals.
I knew about a world just a little different
from what the other girls had seen.
I wanted to surprise her by showing it to her.
Hikari-chan, let's go to that stage!
Huh?
Let's become Stars together and bring everyone Starlight!
That was the moment I was born.
As Kagura Hikari, Girl of the Stage.
Never again
will I lose!
When I lost everything,
it was my promise with Karen that brought me back to the stage.
I will become a Girl of the Stage once more.
The first thing I desired became our destiny
hajimari no katsubou wa unmei
In order to do that, I must defeat all the other participants and become the Top Star.
Joined by two dreams, hers and mine, now one
sono aida ni yume ga kasanau
That was the only way I could fulfill my promise with Karen.
The moment I began to run was my awakening
hashiridashita shunkan mezameta no yo
But...
(Each girl must)
(shoujo wa)
Karen, you idiot!
Take that step
arukidasu
Even though in these auditions, it's take or be taken from!
Even if it can't be granted by her power alone
hitori de kanaerarenakutemo
To protect me...
We absolutely will become Stars, together!
I can't take Karen's radiance.
But...
Unless I defeat everyone, her radiance will...
Then let's pass it together!
If we sparkle brighter than anyone else, then I'm sure we'll both be able to pass!
Together!
If we sparkle brighter than anyone else...
I'd never thought of that before.
But!
But even so, I saw it!
Now the dream both of us held bursts into bloom
futari no yume ga hiraku wa
Our own...
Starlight!
Second Curtain
When the Flower Opens
Her radiance is reborn.
issho ni osanai hi
The little seed we planted in the earth
ueta chiisana tane
Together in our childhoood days
ookiku hanahiraite yuku
has blossomed into a radiant flower
hoshi ga michibiita
Guided by the stars
mou makenai
I'll never lose again
akiramenai
I'll never give in
te wo nobasu, kimi no hou e
I'll reach out my hand, to the place where you are
nigedasanai
No more will I run
namida shinai
No more will I cry
yakusoku no basho e
I will go to the place of our promise
aitakatta yo, kimi ni zutto
I wanted to see you all along
mou ichido tsunagu hoshi no kizuna
Once more, the bond joined by the Stars
kiseki okoseru
Will give a miracle rise
Position Zero!
The sixth day of auditions is over!
Do you understand, Hikari-chan?
Starlight is a tragedy.
At the end, you know you'll have to part.
Will you be able to accept that?
Even if, one day, you must face her in battle?
Even so, I...
and Karen...
I've always had my eye on you
Seeing you let me leave my loneliness behind
But the moon bites back its laughter again tonight
Won't you turn my way?
Star
Oh, fly me to the Star
I've never been able to tell you how I feel
I've sung the songs of so many other lives onstage instead
Because I want to capitivate you
Star
Oh, fly me to the Star
Quite the meteoric rise.
The fated two, hmm?
I understand.
On the Eve
of the Festival of the Star
Shoujo Kageki
Revue Starlight.
I see.