Oceanus...
Here we are, just strolling into town.
Why the change of heart?
No reason.
I just felt like it.
Besides, you keep talking about
going out and seeing the sights.
Exploring the exotic markets
of a foreign land
is just as exciting as fighting a war on its soil.
I find it rather pathetic for one
country to invade another
for a reason like that.
What's that, boy?
You speak as though you've
experienced it yourself.
Never mind.
It's nothing for you to worry about.
No...
This is too cruel!
We devoted ourselves to this masterpiece...
They've gone too far!
How...
How can they call themselves human?!
Ryuunosuke...
Only a very select few are capable
of understanding true beauty and harmony.
To the vulgar masses, the philistines,
such beauty is but a target for destruction.
Maybe we had too much fun with it.
And now, we're being punished.
Heed my words, Ryuunosuke.
God does not punish humans!
He merely toys with their lives!
S-Sir?
Once, I committed atrocities so numerous
that I was like an embodiment
of blasphemy in this world.
But no matter how many
I killed or maimed,
my punishment never came!
And when I finally paused,
I realized my pursuit of the
most heinous cruelties
had gone uninterrupted for eight years.
In the end, it was not God
who brought ruin unto me,
but the selfishness of my fellow man!
The Church and monarchy
convicted and executed me,
under the pretense of justice,
so they could rob me
of my wealth and my land!
My rampage was halted not
by divine judgment.  Far from it.
It was simple thievery!
But, sir...
God still exists.
Why would you, a faithless man who knows
nothing of miracles, say such a thing?
Because, on the surface,
this world looks bland and boring.
But the more you look, the more
fun and surprising things you find!
That's how I've always felt.
This world, full of strange
and wonderful things,
could not have happened by chance.
All you need to do is resolve to enjoy it,
and this world is the
finest entertainment!
You can't have a story
of five billion characters
without an entertainer for an author.
And if we're talking about this author,
God is the only name that fits.
Then tell me, Ryuunosuke,
do you believe that God loves humans?
From the bottom of my heart!
This world is filled with God's love.
If God spends his every moment
writing a script of the world,
it must be a labor of love.
I bet he's having a blast!
God is creating a work of art.
He loves mankind's ideals,
like bravery and hope.
And, by the same token, he loves despair,
bloodshed, and cries of anguish!
If he didn't,
he wouldn't have made the insides
of all creatures so vibrant.
That's why I'm sure that this world
is filled with God's love.
In this era when mankind shuns faith
and states become secular,
I have witnessed the birth
of a beautiful, new creed!
You have impressed me, Ryuunosuke.
My Master!
Aw, come on, you're making me blush.
But according to your beliefs,
my blasphemies were
mere comedy, correct?
No, a true entertainer embraces
the villain's role
and leaves the audience smiling.
I believe that God loves playing wise guy
to your unrelenting straight man.
Therefore, blasphemy and praise
are equal forms of worship?!
Ryuunosuke!
You are the prophet for a new philosophy!
A God who holds all mankind
by the marionettes' strings,
yet is himself a part of the act!
I understand...
His cruel designs finally come clear.
Very well.
Then let us create more despair and terror
to dye his gardens in even brighter shades.
We shall teach our Heavenly author
that he is not the only one
who knows how to entertain!
That means we're gonna do
something wild again, right?
So cool!
"After his victory,
the king left the governing and politics
of his new territory to the local nobility,
while he continued leading his army
on their eastward march."
Just like in my dream.
All he wanted to see was
the ocean at the world's end.
He continued his campaign
to see Oceanus with his own eyes.
Hey, boy!
Where are you?
There you are.
You're such a shrimp, I keep losing
track of you amidst these shelves.
I've been searching for a while!
Normal people are shorter
than bookshelves, idiot.
What did you buy?
Look...
The new Admirable Grand Strategy
game came out today!
And this is the first-run special edition!
My luck stat must be pretty high!
You know...
You can buy the game by itself, but you
still need to have a console to play it.
All taken care of.
Let's go, boy.
We'll play each other when we return.
I bought two controllers.
I'm not interested in playing
with low-brow toys.
Sheesh...
Can you never be a bit more open-minded,
every once in a while?
Do you never try to find something fun?
Shut up.
If I had the time to waste,
I'd spend it searching for Truth.
And so, your search has led you to...
This book?
Hey, this is about me!
What a funny kid you are.
You have the genuine article before you.
If you want to know something, simply ask.
Fine, I will!
The history books all say
you were extremely short.
So why did you materialize
as a ridiculous giant?
It states that I was short?
Well, I suppose you cannot trust a book
if you do not know its author.
So it's wrong, but you're not mad?
No, I really care not.
Is that strange?
Those of power always try to leave
their mark on history,
in any era.
I suppose that having your
name recorded in books
is a form of immortality.
But if that means that my name
will appear in books for a couple thousand years...
I'd like to receive
one percent of that time in
added to my lifespan.
So it's true that you died
in your early thirties?
Yes, that one is right.
Sir!
Show God a straight man routine
that will leave his jaw on the floor!
Sir!
You shan't be disappointed, Ryuunosuke!
This will be, as you might say,
the coolest thing you'll ever see!
Really?
I can't wait!
This is gonna rock.
Why so quiet?
Nothing...
I was just lamenting how boring you are.
Oh, yeah?
So you admit you're bored.
Stop being obstinate, and try
this game with me.
No!
Claiming the Grail just because I
have such a powerful Servant...
I don't feel like I could be proud of that.
I would've been better off
summoning Assassin instead.
Somehow, I think not.
You'd likely be dead by now.
That suits me fine!
I have no qualms about dying
while fighting my own battles.
That's why I'm fighting
in the Holy Grail War.
But now...
What would you have me say?
Had you perhaps impressed me
with a more ambitious wish,
I would have been more
willing to obey you.
But if all you want is to be taller...
I never said that!
Don't be in such a rush.
No one said the Grail War
must be your life's most important event.
What?
Someday, when you find the path in life
in which you can take true pride,
you must fight for it,
whether or desire to or not.
Then you'll have the chance to
seek your own battlefield.
I know I'm not the only one dissatisfied
with our contract.
You don't like it, either!
Stuck with me for a Master!
If you'd made a pact with
a different Master,
you could've breezed your way to victory.
Probably.
Look at this, boy.
This is the opponent I'm fighting.
Now draw a picture of us two,
right next to this enemy.
And do it to scale, that we
may compare ourselves.
That's...
Impossible, right?
Compared to the enemy we're facing,
you and I are the same.
No more than dots!
What's the point in comparing our heights?
That is what makes this exciting!
The smallest, the weakest...
It doesn't matter!
I should still wish to go and
take over the world,
with nothing more than
my tiny dot of a body!
Within my chest beats the heart
of the King of Conquerors!
So then, you don't care
who your Master is?
It doesn't matter to you how weak I am.
Who said that?
Your own feeling of inferiority
signals a fine military leader.
Despite your grumbling,
you recognize how small you are.
And even still,
you choose to ignore it,
to claw your way to greatness.
That's not a compliment.
It's an insult.
That's true, boy.
You are a fool, through and through.
Your desires are beyond your abilities.
"Glory awaits beyond the horizon."
In my day,
that was one of life's basic tenets.
That's why you kept charging east,
like a crazed maniac?
Indeed.
I wanted to see Oceanus with my own eyes.
Unfortunately, my dream never came true.
He cannot see the ocean?
Oceanus is still my final destination.
A dream that never ends.
That ocean is the place
Rider keeps in his heart.
Go ahead and laugh.
Two thousand years later,
and still I have the same dream.
Every bit the fool, as well.
And so, boy...
A pact with a fellow idiot seems ideal.
The river.
Caster...
Caster must be performing some
kind of incredible spell,
judging by the extreme use of mana.
It can be nothing else.
Welcome, my holy virgin.
I am thrilled to see you again.
You will not learn, monster.
What are you playing at tonight?
My apologies, Jeanne.
You are not tonight's guest of honor.
Of course, if you wish to
attend the festivities,
it would please me to no end.
I, Gilles de Rais,
have prepared a feast of
death and decadence,
where all may eat their fill!
Once more, we set out to
raise salvation's banner!
Caster is being absorbed?
You, who have been abandoned,
gather once more.
I shall lead you.
I shall control you!
We have been degraded and humiliated,
and God himself will know our fury!
Oh, God in Heaven,
I praise your holy name,
even as I denounce it!
That's...
Insolent God!
Cruel God!
We shall drag you down from your throne.
Greetings, King of Knights.
King of Conquerors...
Easy, easy.
Let's call a truce for tonight.
We shall have no chance
to fight each other,
if we cannot first obliterate that beast.
I've said as much to the other Servants.
Lancer has agreed.
He'll be here any moment.
Very well.
We shall fight by your side.
King of Conquerors, though it
will be a short alliance,
for tonight, I pledge my loyalty.
Hey, Einzbern, do you guys have a plan?
Lancer said you fought Caster before.
We must defeat him as quickly as possible.
Right now, Caster is providing the mana
that creature needs to maintain
its form in this world.
But if it finds its own food source and
becomes able to sustain itself, all is lost.
We must kill Caster before that happens.
I see.
So we must end this before it reaches shore
and starts to feed.
But Caster has hidden himself deep
inside the creature's body.
What is your plan?
We force him out.
That is our only way.
If we can expose his Noble Phantasm,
my Gáe Dearg can break
the spell in one strike.
Lancer, can you throw that spear through
Caster's Noble Phantasm from this coast?
If I can see it, that is simple.
Then Rider and I shall meet it headlong.
How sounds that to you, King of Conquerors?
Fine by me.
My chariot can travel anywhere,
with or without a road.
But how will you attack, while the enemy
remains in the river, Saber?
I have the Lady of the Lake's protection.
No water can impede me,
no matter its depth.
That is rare indeed.
I want you for my army even more.
You'll pay for that line later.
But now, we must pull Caster from that monster.
Indeed!
Then, I shall strike first!
Good luck, Saber.
This ends now, Caster!
Episode 13:
The Forbidden Feast of Madness
Go get them, Sir Bluebeard!
Such a failure is unprecedented.
You wish me to draw Ea,
my greatest treasure, here?
Saber!
Please wait, King of Heroes!
What a guy...
I'll slaughter you all!
Kill every last one!
Fate/Zero, 2nd Season: Starting April, 2012