[NARRATOR] Alchemy...
the science of understanding,
deconstructing, and
reconstructing matter...
However, it is not
an all-powerful art.
It is impossible to create
something out of nothing.
If one wishes to
obtain something,
something of equal value
must be given.
This is the Law of
Equivalent Exchange--
the basis of all alchemy...
In accordance with this law,
there is a taboo
among alchemists.
Human transmutation
is strictly forbidden.
For what could equal
the value of a human soul?
[NARRATOR] In order
to learn more about
the field of bio alchemy,
Ed and Al visited the
home of Shou Tucker,
the Sewing Life Alchemist...
There, they befriended Tucker's
young daughter Nina
and her dog Alexander...
The day of Tucker's
annual State Alchemist
certification assessment
was drawing near.
In his desperation to pass,
he used Nina and Alexander
to create a talking chimera.
Knowing that nothing he did
could ever change Nina back,
Ed was grief-stricken
at his own powerlessness.
[ED (AGE 5)]
Hey, Mom...! Mom!
What do you
have there, Ed?
It's a present!
I transmuted it!
[TRISHA] You did...? You're
your father's son, all right.
Thank you very much.
That's an amazing
thing you did...
Creating something as
neat as this takes talent.
[TRISHA]
But...
[TRISHA (CHIMERA)]
If you can do that...
why couldn't you
make Mommy better, Ed?
[NINA]
Big brother!
Let's play!
[AL]
Brother, are you all right...?
You were dreaming.
[RAIN HITTING THE GROUND]
What's the matter,
you two...?
You're up awfully early.
We... need to know...
[ED] What's going to happen
to Tucker and Nina?
Mr. Tucker was scheduled to be
stripped of his certification
and stand trial
for what he did to Nina.
[HAWKEYE]
But... they're both dead.
[AL]
Dead?!
[HAWKEYE] You'll
find out anyway, so
I might as well tell you...
They've been murdered.
They... How? By who?!
We don't know.
[HAWKEYE] I was just
heading over to the scene now.
[AL]
We're coming with you.
[HAWKEYE]
No.
Why not?!
You don't need to see this.
[RAIN POURING]
He's always
one step ahead of us.
We'd better catch up
to him quickly,
because the way
things are going...
[ROY] You sound as though
you were expecting this...
Fill me in.
[CORNELLO] God has given us
a great trial, my children...!
Wicked heathens have
spread insidious rumors,
trying to shake our faith...
and now the military
seeks to oppress us!
But we must hold
tight to our faith!
The time has come to
rise up, weapon in hand,
and fight in the name
of the great god Leto!
[MAN A] Yeah...! We fight under
the protection of Leto!
Down with heathens and heresy!
[MAN C]
No...! Don't be fooled!
[MAN D] That man speaks
nothing but lies!
Can't you see that?
[MAN E]
Hold your tongue!
[MAN F] We aren't pawns of the
heathens like all of you are!
[LUST LAUGHS]
Human foolishness
never ceases to amaze me.
[GLASS BREAKING]
[CROWD FIGHTING AND RIOTING]
[CHILD CRYING]
[LUST] Wouldn't
you agree, Gluttony?
[GLUTTONY]
Fools, all of 'em!
Fools indeed. Sad but true.
Well-well,
if it isn't the father.
Yeah, "Father."
[LUST] Sorry to have put
you to all of this trouble.
As soon as we have
everything handled here,
I have my own responsibilities
I need to get back to.
The Fullmetal boy's
interference was irritating,
but at least we were able
to make it work in our favor.
[LUST] Looks like we'll finish
up ahead of schedule.
[CORNELLO]
Manipulate a little information,
spout some empty
rhetoric to the believers,
and you have a fine
recipe for instant violence...
Humans are
such simple creatures.
[LUST] Bloodshed gives way
to more bloodshed,
hatred breeds more hatred,
until all of the violence
soaks into the land,
carving rivers of blood.
And no matter how
many times it happens,
they never learn...
The human race
is made up of violent,
miserable fools.
[CORNELLO] Who seem more than
willing to play into our hands.
[LUST SMIRKS]
[GLUTTONY] Are lots
of people gonna die again?
[LUST] Yes, they will.
Ooh! Can I eat all
of them after they die?
[LUST]
No, you may not.
By the way Envy,
could you lose the
old man costume...?
It's rather unattractive.
Come on,
I was just staying in character.
But if you insist...
This time around I'll go
with a younger, cuter model.
What do ya say?
[ENVY CHUCKLES]
[ASSISTANT PASTOR
REACTS WITH SHOCK]
[ASSISTANT PASTOR]
A... a monster!
What's going on here...?
What have you done...?!
What have you done
with the real Father Cornello?!
It's your call.
He said I was a monster.
I think that's
quite rude, don't you?
Can I eat him? Can I?
Oh, hey, did ya
hear the news...?
Shou Tucker, that
alchemist in East City...
he's dead.
[LUST] Tucker...?
Why should we care about a
little nothing like him?
Because it was him who
was responsible for the murder.
Speaking of East City,
isn't that where the Flame
Colonel's staying right now?
[ENVY]
Yeah...
...and apparently the
Fullmetal brat's there too.
Oh, is he?
[LUST] As furious as
I am that he interfered
with our work here, we can't
very well let him die.
He's an important sacrifice.
Ooh! That was so yummy!
[LUST] We'll find some way
of handling the situation.
The other one we were speaking
of... what was his name?
[ROY]
Scar?
Because of his face?
Yeah, we don't really know
anything else about him,
so that's what
we're calling him.
Our target is both
unidentified and elusive.
The only information
we've been able to obtain
about him is that he has a
large scar on his forehead.
Yes, I've heard stories
about that man...
That's who you're
trying to hunt down?
[HUGHES] By order of the
military police command center.
Meanwhile, all my
other work is piling up...
Ugh, my head hurts.
[ARMSTRONG] He's killed
five people in Central,
all State Alchemists...
His body count
nationwide is up to ten.
[HUGHES] Five days ago,
he took down old man Grand.
The Brigadier General?
[ROY] But-- he's an expert
in weapons transmutation!
That shows you how
dangerous this guy is.
[HUGHES] You should
increase your escort
and lay low for awhile.
Nobody will blame you.
[HUGHES] Please...
I'm asking as your friend...
You and Tucker
are the only
State Alchemists of
note in this area, right?
Oh no!
[ED] I've been thinking
about this for a long time.
We put all our trust
in alchemy,
but in the end, what is it?
"Alchemy is the science of
understanding the flow of matter
and its laws...
the process of comprehension,
deconstruction, and
reconstruction."
"The world flows, too.
It must also follow laws.
Everything circulates...
Even Death is a
part of that circulation.
You must accept the flow."
Teacher sure drummed
that into our heads, didn't she?
[ED]
I thought I understood it...
but I didn't
understand anything.
[ED]
Mom proves that.
Now here I am again,
trying desperately
to figure out a way
to do the impossible.
[NINA LAUGHS]
I'm such a hopeless idiot...
All this time, and I haven't
grown up one bit.
I thought maybe the rain
would wash away some
of this gloom
that's following me.
[ED] But right now,
every drop that hits my face
is even more depressing.
[AL]
I don't even get that much.
Without a body,
I can't feel the
rain hitting my face.
That's something I miss...
All the time...
I want to get my
body back soon Brother...
I just want to be human again.
Even if it means going
against the flow of the world
and trying to do the impossible.
You, boy, you're the
Fullmetal Alchemist
Edward Elric, correct?
[AL]
Brother!
[BELLS CHIMING]
[EXPLOSION]
What the hell is going on here?!
[ED THINKS]
Who is this guy...?
What does he want...?
This is bad...
This is really bad...
I have to move... Now...
Let's go, Al! Run for it!
[EXPLOSION]
[SCAR]
No you don't.
[STRUCTURE CRUMBLES]
[AL AND ED YELL IN PANIC]
[AL]
Got you!
[AL AND ED PANIC]
Al, grab on!
[AL AND ED YELL OUT
AS THEY TUMBLE]
Damn it, what the hell is
this guy's problem...?!
Making enemies
isn't something that I--
Well...
I never really avoided it.
But there's no reason someone
should be trying to kill me!
[ED]
Who are you, anyway...?
Why are you after us?
[SCAR] As long as there
are 'creators' like you
in the world, there must
also be destroyers.
Then it looks like
we're gonna have to fight.
Gutsy one, aren't you...?
But...
Too slow.
[METAL SHATTERING]
Al!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SCAR THINKS]
There's nothing inside!
[ED]
You bastard!
You're too slow!
Damn it!
An automail arm...
Then that explains
why my attacks didn't
do the damage I expected...
Most unusual.
[AL]
Brother... don't...!
Just run away!
You idiot!
I'm not gonna
leave you behind, Al!
You press your hands
together to make a ring,
and then you perform transmutation...
Now I see.
[ED BELLOWS]
[SCAR]
Then I will have to start
by destroying this
abhorrent right arm of yours...
Brother!
[METAL HITTING THE GROUND]
Now you will not be able
to use your heretic's alchemy.
I will give you a
moment to pray to god.
Brother...! Run away!
Brother!
[ED]
Unfortunately...
there isn't any god
I'd like to pray to.
Am I the only one
you're trying to kill today?
Or are you going
after my brother Al, too?
If he interferes,
I will eliminate him...
but, Fullmetal Alchemist,
you are the only one
who's receiving judgment today.
You alone.
[ED] Okay...
In that case, I want your word.
Promise me you
won't hurt my brother!
Brother!
I will keep that promise.
[AL]
No, Brother, what
are you trying to do?
What are you thinking...? Run!
Get up and run!
Stop...!
Don't touch him!
No...! No, you can't...!
Stop it!
[GUN SHOT]
[ROY]
That's enough!
You won't be killing
anybody else today, Scar.
I'm taking you into custody,
where you will answer
for the murders of
at least ten State Alchemists.
[SCAR] Alchemists alter things
from their natural form,
perverting them
to something else,
something grotesque...
They profane God, the
true creator of all things...
As an agent of God...
I am here to hand
down his judgment.
If you interfere, I will
eliminate you as well.
Oh, is that right?
[ROY]
You guys stay out of it.
Colonel Mustang, sir!
Colonel Mustang...
so this is the Flame Alchemist.
[SCAR] Volunteering yourself
to receive judgment.
This is truly an auspicious day!
So you know who I am
and you still want
to challenge me? Bad decision.
[HAWKEYE FIRES WEAPONS]
Hey, Hawkeye, what the
hell did you do that for?!
You know as well as I do,
you're useless
on rainy days.
Please stay back.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
It's kinda hard
to get a spark going
when it's raining, huh?
It is fortunate that you
can't create your
blasphemous flames,
State Alchemist.
For I will destroy all
who interfere with my mission,
right here and now!
[ARMSTRONG]
I'd like to see you try it.
[IMPACT]
A newcomer.
[ARMSTRONG] You have to be
quick to avoid my fist...
Not bad... not bad at all.
You said you were
going to destroy us all...
In that case... why don't
you start by defeating me?
We'll see how you fare
against the Strong
Arm Alchemist,
Alex Louis Armstrong!
Yet another State Alchemist...
God is putting them
in my path for me.
Not backing down...?
In that case,
your courage will earn
you a demonstration.
I'll show you the
art of alchemy;
that has been passed down
the Armstrong
family for generations!
Who is he?
That's the same man
who murdered Mr. Tucker
and his daughter.
It's him!?
Major, watch what you're doing!
We don't want to
destroy the city, do we?
What do you mean?!
[ARMSTRONG]
Destruction and creation
are two sides of the same coin.
You must destroy to create.
That is the law of the universe!
Did he have to strip?
Are you surprised?
He's clearly insane.
(Hmph!) Non-alchemists
may fail to see the
inherent truth of that statement...
But we understand,
don't we, Scar?
So this killer is
an alchemist, too?
That's it...!
The stages with the
transmutation process
are construction, deconstruction,
and reconstruction...
This guy just must stop
at the deconstruction phase.
But if Scar is
an alchemist as well...
doesn't that mean
he's strayed from
whatever his
'ways of God' are, too?
[IMPACT]
And what would
be his reasons for only
targeting alchemists
with state certification?
[SCAR THINKS] He's unusually
coordinated for his size,
and his strength is
almost superhuman...
That, combined
with his alchemy...
He won't be an easy one.
I have you cornered, Scar.
[SCAR THINKS]
But there's a moment
when his swing is too wide.
There it is!
[GUN SHOTS]
You get him?
He's too fast.
I only grazed him with one shot.
Red eyes, and brown skin.
That means he's--
Of course! He's an Ishvalan!
Perhaps there are too many...
You might as well give up, Scar.
You're not getting away...
[IMPACT BLAST]
[CRIES OF PANIC FROM SOLDIERS]
[HAVOC]
Bastard is in the sewers.
[ROY
Stay put.
[HAVOC] Sure. You don't
have to tell me twice.
Sorry Armstrong...
but thank you for
buying us enough time
to surround him.
I was hardly buying time.
It was all I could do to
keep myself from being killed.
Oh! Is it
over now?
Lt. Colonel Hughes, where have
you been this whole time?
I thought it
best to lay low.
[ROY] You didn't think about
maybe backing us up?!
Of course not!
A person like me shouldn't
get dragged into a
freak show with you
pack of pseudo humans!
It's bad for
my health...!
Don't just stand there!
We've got things to do!
[HUGHES]
Deploy troops!
Circulate his description!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes sir!
Oh no, Alphonse!
Alphonse!
Al! Talk to me!
Are you all right?
That suit of armor is
Elric's younger brother, is it?
There's gotta be a really
long story behind this one.
[ED] Come on, Al!
Al, do you hear me?
[AL PUNCHES ED]
[AL] Why didn't you run away
when I told you to?
What kind of idiot are you?
No way! I'm not just gonna
run away and leave you behind.
Which is exactly
why you're an idiot?
What do you keep
punching me like that for?
If I'd run away,
you could've been killed,
you know that?!
[AL] And maybe
I wouldn't have been...!
Making the decision to die
is something only an idiot does!
Hey, easy on the idiot stuff!
I'm still your
older brother, got it?!
[AL]
I'll say it all I want to.
Survival is the only way, Ed...
Live on, learn
more about alchemy...
You could find a way
to get our bodies back
and help people like Nina...
You can't do that by dying!
[AL] I won't allow you to
abandon the possibility of hope
and choose a meaningless death!
[AL]
Oh great...!
And now my arm's come off
because my brother's
a big, fat idiot!
We're really falling apart...
aren't we, Brother?
We look like we
belong in a junkyard.
But we're still alive.
We are.
Good grief. I've
stumbled into an
extra special kind
of freak show, huh?
Yeah, sorry.
Don't worry, I won't
tell anyone upstairs...
[HUGHES] If this got out,
things would get complicated.
[ROY] Yeah... The older brother
aside, I wouldn't even
know how to explain the
younger brother's body.
I don't envy you...
[HUGHES] This is one tough
customer you're dealing with.
And now we know he's Ishvalan.
[ROY] The Ishvalans
were a race of people
who lived to the east of us...
They believed that their
god Ishvala was the one,
absolute creator.
Even after they were
annexed into the country,
there were still conflicts
between us and them...
Then, thirteen years ago,
a military officer
accidentally shot
and killed an Ishvalan child...
And that led to
a full-blown civil war.
[GUNFIRE]
[ROY] One uprising led to
another, and before long,
the rebellion had spread
to the whole eastern sector.
After seven years of this...
an order came down
from the military
high-command...
...to exterminate Ishval.
Many State Alchemists were
brought in to act
as human weapons.
[PANIC AND SCREAMING]
[ROY] Needless to say...
the State Alchemists
produced striking results.
That man is an
Ishvalan survivor.
In a sense, his
revenge is justified.
No way!
There's no justification
for taking revenge on people
who had nothing
to do with it...!
He's just dressing his
ugly lust for vengeance
in the mantle of his God and
calling himself
an agent of justice.
Still, the fact is, he's coming
at us with full force...
We can't let ourselves
be killed for his cause.
Next time there
will be no more talk.
Got it?
Yes sir!
Well Ed, Alphonse...
what are you two
going to do now...?
What's the plan?
We're going to
keep moving...
We can't just sit around,
not as long
as we're still alive.
Brother...
Before we can make
any headway on getting
your body back, we have
to get my arm back to normal
[ED] After all, I'm the only
one who knows how to
bond your soul to the armor.
[AL] Uh-huh.
We've got no choice.
[ED]
It's been a long time...
But we need to pay a
visit to our mechanic.
[NARRATOR] In order to repair
their injured bodies,
Ed and Al set off
for their former
home in Resembool,
where they are met
by their mechanics,
Winry and Pinako.
On the way there,
they happen across
a doctor with a troubled past
who may have clues
to offer in the
brothers' search
for the Philosopher's Stone.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood--
Episode Six. Road of Hope
What would young Ed discover,
and how many questions will
still remain to be answered?