A sudden incident has befallen me,
Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I was handed a red gem, and with it
I was given magical powers.
Coincidences led by new meetings
start to move in silence.
So that I don't look down on the days
where one stands up and fights...
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
Good evening, this is
Nanoha Takamachi!
I'm usually an ordinary
third-grader, but lately,
all sorts of things have been going on.
Stand by ready.
Lyrical, magical...
Jewel Seed, Serial 20...
Seal!
Sealing.
Nanoha, thanks for the hard work.
Well, I'm now working as
what you'd call a magical girl.
Nanoha, are you all right?
I'm all right, but I'm a bit tired.
Nanoha! Nanoha, are you all right?
Episode 3: The City's
In a Lot of Danger?!
Nanoha, it's morning.
You should get up soon.
Today's Sunday, so let me
sleep in just a bit more.
Nanoha!
I'm Nanoha Takamachi,
a third grader.
Thanks to an introduction
and a series of coincidences,
I met Yuuno, who is a mage
from another world.
During the day, I'm an
ordinary grade-school girl,
and at night, I'm a magical girl,
searching for the Jewel Seeds,
which Yuuno is looking for.
Confirmation.
It's been one week since I met Yuuno.
We've collected a total
of five Jewel Seeds.
I seem to be getting the hang
of this magical girl thing, but...
Nanoha, for today, you should
take care and rest up.
But...
We're taking a break today.
You already found five for me,
so you need some rest,
or you won't last.
Besides, you have a promise
to keep today, right?
You're right.
Then today we'll take a break
from the search for Jewel Seeds.
Yeah.
Today, the soccer team
that my father,
Shiro Takamachi, owns and coaches -
the Midoriya JFC - has a game.
Arisa, Suzuka, and I
promised that we'd all
go to the game to
cheer the players on.
Now that a lot of the stands
are getting full,
would you like to start the game?
Shall we?
Go for it! Everyone, do your best!
This is one of the sports
on this world, right?
Yeah, that's right. It's called soccer.
You kick the ball with your feet,
and you score a point when you
get it into the opponent's goal.
Only the one in front of the goal
is allowed to use his hands.
I see... It looks like fun.
Amazing goalie!
Really!
Get upfield, get upfield!
Are there sports like this on the
world where you come from, Yuuno?
There are, but I was so engrossed
in research and excavation
that I didn't play much of anything.
Just like me! I'm not
too good at sports.
Midoriya J Sakuradai
Game set! Midoriya JFC wins,
two to nothing!
All right!
All right, all of you did a great job!
That was a great game,
just like in practice!
Yes, sir!
Then, to celebrate this victory,
let's have a feast!
You know, upon a second look,
don't you think this guy's
a bit different from a ferret?
Come to think of it,
maybe you're right?
The vet also said that he was
slightly different from usual.
Well, I'm sure he's just
a slightly different ferret.
Here, Yuuno, shake!
How cute!
He's so smart!
So cute!
Isn't he great?!
I'm sorry, Yuuno.
Good boy!
I'm fine...
Thanks for the meal!
Thank you so much!
Everyone, today you did
a really good job!
Let's practice hard again next week,
and win the next tournament
just like we did today!
Yes, sir!
Then that's it for today! All of you,
be careful on your way home!
Thank you very much!
Good job, guys!
Good job today!
You too.
That was just me, right?
Oh, that was amusing!
Here, Nanoha!
Now, I guess that's it
for us today as well?
Yes, I think so.
That's right. Everyone has
things to do this afternoon.
I'm going out with my sister.
I'm going shopping with Papa!
That's great! Tell me
all about it on Monday.
Oh, you guys are
calling it a day as well?
Oh, Dad!
Thank you so much
for inviting us today!
The game was really cool!
Thanks to both of you, Suzuka
and Arisa, for cheering us on.
If you're going home, would
you like me to drive you?
Oh no, I'm getting picked up.
Same here!
I see. What about you, Nanoha?
I'll go home and relax!
I see.
Your father's getting a quick bath
at home, then it's back to work.
Would you like to
come home with me?
Sure!
See ya later!
See you tomorrow!
Nanoha, did you grow taller again?
Dad, you asked me that
just the other day!
I don't grow that quickly!
I see...
Nanoha, if you're going to bed,
at least change out of your clothes.
You should get some rest too, Yuuno.
I'm going to take a nap until dinner.
Using magic when you're not used
to it must be very tiring after all.
If only I were a bit more reliable...
You were amazing today too.
No, that's not true. See,
we always have good defense.
But you were really cool!
Oh, that's right.
Here.
It's pretty!
I think it's just a normal stone,
but since it was so pretty...
Nanoha?!
Did you feel that?
What's up, Nanoha?
Want to come in with me?
Sorry, Dad, maybe next time!
I'm gonna go out for a bit!
Is that so? See you later...
Raging Heart, please!
Stand by ready. Set up.
How terrible...
A human probably activated it.
When someone with a strong will
activates it by wishing hard into it,
the Jewel Seed displays the
strongest amount of power.
So it really was that boy that had it!
I had noticed it, too!
I might have been able to stop
all of this before it happened.
Nanoha...
Nanoha?
Yuuno, what should I do
at a time like this?
Yuuno!
Right.
You have to get close to it
in order to seal it.
First, you have to find the
root area for all of this.
But when it spreads out
to such a large area,
how do you search for it?
So I just have to get to
the root of it all, right?
What?
Area Search.
Lyrical, magical...
Search for the root of the misfortune!
I found it!
Really?!
I'll seal it right away!
It's impossible from here!
You have to get closer!
I can do it! It's all right!
Right, Raging Heart?
Shooting Mode.
Set up.
Go and catch it!
Stand by ready.
Lyrical, magical...
Jewel Seed, Serial 10...
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt: No. X.
Mode release.
Thank you, Raging Heart.
Good bye.
Long-range magic
even I couldn't use...
Just how much magical talent
does this girl have?
We troubled all sorts
of people this time.
What?
What are you talking about?
Nanoha, you're doing a fine job!
I'd noticed that he had it.
But I thought it was
just my imagination.
Nanoha!
Please, don't look so sad!
In the first place, it's all my fault,
and you're just helping
me out, Nanoha!
Nanoha?!
You're doing a fine job, Nanoha!
Nanoha...
My first failure since
I became a mage...
It's really tough for someone
to be troubled because of you.
That's what I thought when
I decided I would help Yuuno out.
Not just with my best, but
with everything I have...
I decided to collect the
Jewel Seeds of my own will,
and not just to help Yuuno out.
So that something like this
never happens again.
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of
cellophane and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying
inside a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining on
the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something I
can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
We all visited Suzuka's house.
She has an older sister, a maid,
and lots of cats and kitties!
But one of the kittens seems to
be involved in some trouble?!
And a second mage appears!
What is her motive?
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 4:
A Rival?! Another Magical Girll
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 4:
A Rival?! Another Magical Girll
Episode 4: A Rival?!
Another Magical Girl!
Episode 4:
A Rival?! Another Magical Girll
Lyrical, magical, I'll do my best!