How long do you plan on sleeping?
School is already over.
What's going on? I'm sure there are better ways to wake someone up.
What is it?
The thing is...
...I need your advice on something.
Is that how you ask for someone's help?
Don't mind the details, ok?
You'll see this is a great bargain for you.
What's with the skeptical look?
Alright, I'll hear out whatever story you have.
First of all, I'd like you to go up to the rooftop.
Why do I have to follow you there?
What are you hatching?
Come on, come on.
Um... I think you're from next door's class, right?
Eh, Sanae... I don't think I can...
No, no, I can't hear you!
Alright, see you later!
You're Elen's friend?
Fujiwara-san, is it?
It's Fujieda... I'm Fujieda Mio.
You also know Sanae?
Yes.
We used to be classmates in our first year of high school.
Is that so?
By the way, did you want something with me?
Um, you see, I want to ask you something...
Does it have something to do with Elen?
No, that's not it.
I want to ask about you.
Reiji-san, right now...
Do you have someone you like?
I'm sure it wouldn't be someone like me.
So basically... eh... ah... well...
Mio?
Elen!
Brother, what are you doing...
...in this kind of place?
I wonder who you're talking to.
Do you know Mio, Brother?
No, um, by the way, what are you doing here?
I was looking for Mio.
I suddenly wanted to eat waffles at Kanekoya.
I was just wondering if Mio wanted to come along.
Hey, wanna go?
I have business to take care of today.
Well then...
Oh, okay.
Did I disturb you?
Kinda.
What happened?
She confessed to me.
What?
Fujiwara-san was...
It's Fujieda. But, really?
Mio confessed to you?
Um, yeah, sort of.
Mio has weird tastes.
What are you saying?
And then, how did you reply?
I couldn't because you barged in and...
Chase her!
Eh?
Mio would want to hear the answer right away.
It's me who was disturbing you, but...
Don't let her leave!
But what should I tell her?
You have to think about that yourself.
Like I said...
Come on, just go!
Even though I set up a meeting...
...why can't you two make any progress?
Sorry.
You should have done like we practiced.
"I love you, please be my boyfriend!"
Say that, and watch him as he's forced to nod.
Time taken, 5 seconds.
A confession is like a surprise attack.
What made you drag it out?
But, I...
I can't.
Oh damn it, this is our last spring of school life.
Do you want to waste this chance?
Sanae.
Awesome timing.
I was just about to go look for you.
A good thing you found me.
I have something to talk about with Fujieda-san.
Make yourself scarce.
Huh?
I-Is that so?
In that case I'll grant your wish and get out of here, mister.
I wish you luck.
What were you doing, Sanae?
Well... well...
Fujieda-san, um...
Yes!
The answer to back there...
It was all a bit sudden, so I didn't know what do say.
Don't eavesdrop!
Ok.
Therefore...
Yes.
Um...
So, what did you tell her?
I told her we could start off by being friends for now.
What a commonplace answer.
Where's your sense of style?
Drop it.
So... did you set up arrangements with your "friend"?
We'll head out to town together tomorrow.
Brother.
What is it?
Escort her well, will you?
Mio is my friend.
And if you do something embarrassing,
Bam!
A bit violent.
I'll cheer you on.
Mio is a good girl.
Yeah, from our little chat I felt so already.
So, give me a special allowance!
I already gave you this month's worth.
What?
Oh really, really...
You already agreed on a date.
That's a big step for a late bloomer like Mio.
Nice job!
What were you all talking about?
Oh, hey. Thanks for having me!
Me too!
Anytime.
Huge scandal! There's big news.
What is it?
Tomorrow, Mio will...
Don't say it!
Well, you have a date?
How do you know?
Do you have the lunch box?
Check! Well then, I'm heading out!
Wait a sec.
Alright, with this your grade is 40 points.
What a low score.
Do you remember what I taught you yesterday?
I like you!
I love you.
It's not about money.
Are you a host or something?
Thanks for the food.
It was really delicious.
Originally I wanted to invite you to a restaurant, but...
You live with Elen, right?
Both our parents died in an accident.
Sorry I asked.
It's okay.
It happened when I was young. I'm over it already.
You're strong.
I live with only my mother too.
But when I see her being so busy with work...
If only my father were here...
That's what I think then.
You have to support her well.
When you need a man to do something, call me up.
Thanks, I'll be counting on you.
Mm, next thing up is...
What is that?
Isn't that Sanae's handwriting?
"Go to a place you shouldn't mention."
Reiji-san.
What's the place you shouldn't mention?
Eh...
You finally step up the ladder of adulthood like Cinderella did.
I'm a guy.
If you finish it according to the plan, today's date will be perfect.
Sanae that little broad...
A woman is riding it.
It's incredible how she can handle such a huge motorcycle.
Riding such an expensive bike is impossible for a beggar like me.
Huh, when did it fall down?
Reiji...-san?
The silencer concealed most of the sound.
Maybe a 9mm parabellum round?
I've woken...
...from my dream.
I went from Mexico to Peru and from there to the Philippines via Palau,
and came to Japan half a year ago.
We came here,
to this city, trying to forget the past.
This is your homeland.
After you returned to this country, you really changed.
I know by looking at you.
You are opening up your heart.
It's probably only natural...
...in your homeland.
This is as far as it gets, though.
They're coming after us.
Inferno?
I don't know.
But I got a silent warning.
I see...
So it is time for us to wake from the dream.
If at all possible,
I had wanted you to remain fast asleep in this dream.
Forgetting about your past.
And you?
I...
I still need to confess.
Confess?
Who are you repenting to?
To God Himself.
Someday I will meet Him.
Elen...
Inferno is coming for us at last.
I don't want to do this, but...
I will use Fujieda-san's feelings.
Fujieda-san's feelings?
Elen, what do you mean?
Right after she was born, Fujieda-san's parents...
Yeah, I heard that from her as well.
Her father went missing and was never found.
She grew up being told that.
She still believes that lie.
Lie?
Her father...
...is worth being written of in newspapers.
Who is he?
Godou Kaiten.
He's the leader of a large-scale yakuza group, the Godou clan.
Godou clan?
Yes.
Fujieda was brought up by her mother.
But, the Godou clan?
About that, does she...
She doesn't know.
Even within the clan, only a handful of people know of Mio's existence.
Godou Kaiten hid his wife and their daughter...
...in order to protect them from his enemies.
Then Mio is Godou Daisuke's...
Yes.
They're siblings from different mothers.
Godou Kaiten won't let his daughter get caught up in his organization's battles,
but he can't protect her out in public.
Mio is Godou Kaiten's biggest weakness.
Where did you get that information?
I heard it from Scythe Master.
Scythe Master?
It's a long time ago.
After he fled from Inferno,
he hid himself in Japan.
I told you that before, didn't I?
Yeah.
At that time, Master investigated the Godou clan thouroughly.
He planned to exploit Kaiten's only weakness for his own ends.
Weakness?
Elen, don't tell me you plan to use Fujieda-san to threaten the Godou clan.
At the right time, she could be an trump card.
The young leader who stands at the top of the Godou clan, Shiga Toru,
is loyal to Inferno.
Do you understand the situation now?
Even if it's Inferno that stands in your way,
you hold Mio captive.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You're right.
I should have told you earlier.
If I knew Mio had feelings for you,
I would have told you earlier.
If I had known they would come after us...
In the end our normal life didn't last very long.
We have to make arrangements for our escape.
Yeah.
You're right.
We need to run away.
Don't strain yourself.
In these times, you can cry.
Now you can be like in the days of old.
That would be selfish.
I'm prepared for this.
We are being chased.
No, you've forgotten something.
But maybe that's for the best.
I...
...was happy because of that.
Elen.
For the last half a year,
your smile and your sleeping face...
...showed true happiness.
By watching them alone,
I was happy too.
This thing called homeland...
...puts you at ease.
Someday, I too will...
That's why I can keep on living a dream.
Because you promised me...
...that someday you would find my homeland as well.
I don't want your happiness until now to have been a lie.
Someday, we can come back here.
Even if we go abroad, this country will remain.
I'm sure the day will come when you can return here.
The day when we can truly live a normal life.
That time just hasn't come yet.
What?
Reiji went home in the middle of a date?
It wasn't a date.
And Reiji-san said he had urgent business.
For young people in the full bloom of their youth,
there's nothing more important than love!
You're a bit loud.
Even though I went to the trouble of setting up a plan for you guys.
Maybe that was a bit unnecessary.
It's a pity the date went bad.
I guess so.
Oh, "I guess so"?
Speak of the devil,
there he is!
Hey, hey,
it hurts.
Sa-Sanae?!
Sanae, geez...
Reiji-san, yesterday was fun.
Yeah, I think so too.
Did your urgent business go well?
Yup, it went well.
You're pretty good to block my attack.
You get second place after me.
I have some business with Elen.
I have to hurry.
See you.
Hey! Where are you going leaving your girlfriend behind?
Oh, did I upset you?
Something is different about him.
He's not his usual self.
Why?
Why is she here?
No... is it really you?
You were alive?
Cal.
Nice to meet you, Ein.
Or should I call you "ex-Phantom"?