I have no wishes anymore
Chaika - The Coffin Princess
My hope was hard as rock, and now it is brittle
My body is battered and broken,
and I will not last long
But I will look back on my proud life
with a mask of false courage
The reason flowers blossom
is to say goodbye and wither
This is the law of the world
All of mankind is cruel
We betray and we are betrayed
Goodnight, let us sleep now
You will hear a song
A sad, sad song
A song about you
Fill the blackness
Your Majesty.
I have brought the assistant director of the Institute of Magic, Viktor Izhmash.
Izhmash.
Y-Yes?
I order you to produce the tools necessary to achieve my goal.
We already have the technology and the plans.
All that remains is to carry it out.
Yes.
However, it must be carried out in utmost secrecy.
I have arranged facilities and funding outside the country.
Begin immediately.
Understood.
There is one more thing you must know.
"Chaika"?
All will be set in motion for my sake.
It may appear counterintuitive to that end,
but that in itself is my intention.
I will die soon.
Five years ago, the eight heroes assembled by the Alliance of the Six Nations
eliminated Emperor Gaz.
This brought an end to the war that had raged for 300 years,
but even now, five years after the war's end,
the deceased Emperor Gaz, the so-called "taboo emperor",
maintains vast influence upon this continent.
You say the floating fortress incident was his doing as well?
Yes.
It is safe to say that Chaika, along with the emperor's remains, caused it all.
Isan, hizan, yadwavi, ama...
Come, that which overwhelms!
The Overwarming!
The Princess Who Gathers the Remains
Elum... Naikt inte... Naint...
As you know, the chaos of the last month
resulted not only in countless deaths, including the general,
but put us on the brink of war once again.
Blow, powerful gust!
The Heavy Wind!
Chief Konrad of the Kliemann Organization charged with postwar restoration,
give your report of the details.
Yes, sir.
Ricardo Gavarni, the son of Duke Gavarni,
most likely used Emperor Gaz's remains to power the floating fortress.
According to our investigations,
the remains were obtained from a girl believed to be Chaika.
Girls calling themselves Chaika began appearing across the continent
three years after the war ended.
Regardless of whether their claims are true,
they all work toward the same goal of gathering
the emperor's remains from the eight heroes.
Are you really the daughter of Emperor Gaz?
I am real! Real daughter!
Your father was the most powerful wizard of all.
Elum... Naikt inte... Naint...
Bertolt... Infant...
Come, swirling vortex!
The Tornado!
Shock... Incantation time, short...
Chaika?!
Elum... Kolt...
Come, that which bursts and scatters!
The Buster!
Natow!
They're ex-soldiers.
What are they doing out here in the sticks?
They're pretty good with weapons.
Yeah.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear.
Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy these.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
What?!
That glow...
I've seen it on the battlefield!
You're saboteurs of the Acura clan?!
What of it?
Why are you conspiring with Emperor Gaz's daughter to gather his remains?!
We're not conspiring. It's our objective.
Her objective is my objective.
Have you guys lost your edge?
Looks like their battle's over.
Sadly, I don't think you'll be able to take the remains from me.
Blow away! The Blow!
What are you afraid of?
I told you at the start that I would fight you,
but not to the death.
Total defeat.
I may not look it, but they once called me a hero.
I have far more experience than you.
Yes...
And did you two win your fight?
Impressive!
You took us far too lightly.
One win, one loss. I guess it's a draw today.
Shall we try again tomorrow?
Rematch, gladly!
Toru! Akari! Try, recommended!
Huh? You're...
I apologize for before.
Mm, s'good.
We can't do business with this.
No good.
Please check the flavor of this wine.
She owns a vineyard and a winery...
Definitely someone I would call a success in life.
The grapes are delicious.
So both her life and her grapes are top notch...
Brother, are you jealous?
Not really.
I am.
Looking at you makes me think about many things,
and I've come to the conclusion that nothing beats having money and a good home.
Well, sorry.
Just look at how lively she is.
Yeah... Is she really a hero?
Unknown person, not lie.
But maybe not all people who have remains are heroes...
Lady Claudia is indeed one of the eight heroes,
but that is a thing of the past.
Now, her days are spent managing this winery.
When soldiers were left without purpose after the war,
she offered work to people everywhere who had nowhere to turn.
She is a truly benevolent woman.
So even if you show up and challenge her to a fight for the remains...
Besides, it's like a badge of honor to Lady Claudia.
Nuisance?
It is a nuisance, yes.
It's no badge of honor,
and you're not a nuisance.
In fact, the whole fight was my idea.
This has a good acidic quality.
Well done.
You can harvest the south vineyard now.
The north isn't ready yet. It'll need a few more days.
Yes, ma'am.
As you can see, I'm quite busy.
So I think tomorrow's fight should have a time limit.
If the three of you can score a single victory against me
in the time between breakfast and tea,
it's your win.
How's that?
Understood!
Still, I had heard that girls
calling themselves Chaika were gathering Emperor Gaz's remains,
but I didn't expect one to come to me.
The remains possess immense magic fuel.
You know that, right?
Some say the Chaikas intend to avenge their father by attacking the
Alliance of the Six Nations with a weapon powered by the remains.
And you have them in there?
Yes. Already found several.
What do you intend to do with them?
Father, funeral.
I see.
If you're his daughter, I can understand why you'd want to do that.
What was Father like in end?
I don't know what his last moments were like.
I was tending to my injured companions.
You didn't see him?
I did, but it was the captain of our squad who finished him.
He was supposed to have beheaded the emperor's daughter then, too...
Then, perhaps the girl he killed was a fake?
Real one, me...
Oh, yes. I'll give you some good advice.
Your magic focuses on attacks, but neglects defense.
You need to defend yourself better.
Right...
And your incantations are too long.
If you can choose only the necessary words,
a short incantation is enough to invoke magic.
Appreciate advice.
Need more work.
It's hard for me to react to such open gratitude...
Oh, would you like some wine?
We'll pass. We have tomorrow to think about.
Oh, that's too bad. It's delicious.
Delicious?
One glass, please!
Don't you dare!
So we have until tomorrow afternoon...
Less time than it seems.
She told us to take her three-on-one, like we were a joke...
Akari, we need to have a good plan, or she'll beat us.
What are you doing?
Claudia is a hero, and a powerful wizard.
All the vineyard workers, including her butler and secretary, are strong ex-soldiers.
Yeah.
Which means we must spend this night in the palm of our enemy's hand.
You must be terribly worried.
But there's no need for concern.
I will rest close to your side tonight.
Oh... Sorry.
What's wrong?
Incantation shortening, problem.
That's true... Her incantations were really short.
Is that a skill born of experience?
Yes.
As always, we'll have to buy her time, Brother.
Not enough.
Claudia, immediately interrupt.
And if she cuts off our movements, it's over, huh?
So we'll need to set a trap.
This is taking too long.
What is?
If you'd just make a contract with me
and become a dragoon cavalier, you'd win easily!
That again?
Ask our employer.
Well?
Appreciate sentiment...
But Claudia's terms, three-on-one fight.
If you win, what's the problem?
You want the remains, don't you?
I keep promise.
You're so serious.
And Toru's obsessed with staying a saboteur...
I don't know about you guys.
I'm not obsessed!
Well, whatever! If you change your mind, let me know!
Fredrica, if you were with Claudia when the Gaz Empire was subjugated,
don't you know her weaknesses?
Nope.
We were allies, so I didn't fight her.
I guess...
Okay.
Let's practice your magic as much as we can before the rematch.
Right!
So, what do those incantations mean, anyway?
All things in world have meaning.
Temperature, humidity, wind, terrain,
and all other things affect magic.
Many conditions required to invoke magic.
Precise incantation necessary.
In magic fuel, memories of living things even after death.
Through precise incantation,
wizard's strong feelings can extract memories from magic fuel.
Magic is art of making phenomena appear by consuming living things' memories and thoughts.
What do they mean when they say Emperor Gaz's remains are the most powerful magic fuel?
Stronger memories and thoughts, higher quality magic fuel.
Father's feelings while alive, probably very strong.
First, try shortening incantations!
Incantations, many similar words.
Try revising combinations.
That sounds really tough.
Yes.
What's the most important incantation?
Wait.
Looking up.
Are we gonna get this done in time?
Lai braga... Iatavi... Kamal al...
Ifun... Elstel... Rankali... Bunkali...
Roh... Task... Am... Il...
Glokka! Tamult!
Naints... Ahman... Isaka...
Flakinekt... Trinelil...
We've got a long road ahead...
I've read your report.
Regarding Captain Gillette...
What actually happened?
The captain...
During the floating fortress incident,
he was trying to save Zita and Vivi, who were still inside Soara...
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
I will have you delay your attack by any means necessary!
But then the battle began...
Sir Gillette!
Run, Leonardo!
The Captain was caught in the blast.
And when Vivi found out about it...
You're lying...
Vivi?!
She transformed into Chaika right before your eyes?
It's ironic.
Someone pursuing Chaika came to look like her...
Why her?
I looked into her background to see if she had any relation to Emperor Gaz, but...
She said she was an orphan raised as an assassin,
and taken in by a noble family as a guard.
Yes. Beyond that, her origins are unclear.
In any case, considering what happened with the floating fortresses,
we can assume the continued existence of Chaika and the Emperor's remains will bring nothing but trouble.
On that note...
I would like you all to carry on with Nikolai as the new captain,
and continue investigating Chaika.
Understood.
But please, let us keep being the Gillette Squad.
Very well.
Who are you?
Guy... is what I call myself.
It appears they stopped you from fully transforming into Chaika.
But there is proof that you are Chaika.
Stop it! I am not the daughter of the taboo emperor!
You don't want to admit it, but...
It's the truth.
Half is enough,
provided you fulfill your role as Chaika.
Role?
To gather the remains of the emperor.
You know that.
What does that mean?
You'll find out once you gather them.
Just what are you?
An informant.
Vivi!
Vivi, what's wrong?
I'm...
not Chaika...
Chaika.
Incantation shortening, not successful.
Very worried.
Don't think I can win.
Don't worry.
We'll get the remains, no matter what.
Brother's right.
Even if we lose the fight, we know where she keeps the remains.
We can always just steal them.
Appreciate sentiment.
But I fight as wizard.
Ready to go?
Yes.
It looked like you were practicing magic late into the night.
Did you have any luck?
Not successful.
I see. That's a shame.
But I fight, full strength!
And trust Toru and Akari in battle!
We'll be taking the remains,
no matter what we have to do.
Truly the words of a saboteur.
Toru and Akari, saboteurs.
Also, both precious to me!
Oh?
How nice to have such reliable partners.
Are you ready?
All ready!
Then, shall we begin?
Furom, iestrov...
Elmuto... Eril!
Natow!
Come, The Shtola!
What?
Come, tense atmosphere!
The Strays!
Jentol, winsica!
The sky grows dark
The bell of the beginning rings out
I live on in you
I live inside you,
twisted and tainted
The ark of our genes
rocks on the water,
sailing for the end times
All that I can offer you
is the day our curse was broken,
but one day, one day,
we will meet again,
as long as you wait for me on this Earth
What is there to be lamented?
I think on the proof we lived together
and bite into my beautiful lips
I will devote my life, my love,
and whatever time I have left
to you
Claudia's advice, very beneficial.
I spare no effort!
This manor, full of grapes!
Cakes, cookies, tarts... Want to stay forever!
A Wizard's Pride
Next time: "A Wizard's Pride".