Hot!
That day...I learned the secret of the bento.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Cracking and crumbling.
warete baribari
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Man, this isn't bad every once in a while.
Bento Battle
Us four gays getting together and eating lunch, I mean.
You mean "us guys."
There aren't even four of us.
Professor Kitamura planned this whole thing, so where is he?
Thanks for waiting!
Sorry about that. I had to drop by the student council room to get this.
It wouldn't fit in my locker.
Wh-What is this...?
Could it be...
Y-Your bento?
Yup!
And so...
What do you mean "yup"!?
The only ones with bentos like these are rich kids in gag mangas.
Yeah. But Haruta, it's rude to laugh at someone else's lunch...
Manga bento!? No!
A bento from another dimension!
The inside is just as wild!
What's all the hubbub?
Why not talk to gramps, here?
Minorin!?
What!? Maruo is eating a feast!
What is this, a party?
Yuck, those antennae are long.
This thirty-nine... Could it be...?
The "-saku" in "Yusaku"!?
That's right!
Yusaku, your grandma made this, right?
Huh? Your grandma made this?
Yeah, my parents went to Guam on business.
- My grandma was psyched to care for me,
- A lunch of this quality was made at home!?
and that's about all there is to it.
She really loves her grandkids.
And I appreciate it, but she can go a little overboard...
So basically, I'd like you all to help me finish this!
We can eat this?
Seriously!?
Of course!
Leaving leftovers would make my grandma sad...
Oh! This one's for the ladies.
Thank you for the food!
What is this!? It's so good!
So gooood!
Yusaku's grandma is something else.
So tasty...
- I have a separate stomach for fruit!
- What's wrong? Dig in, Takasu.
S-Sure. I'll try this fried chicken...
Taiga?
What's up, Aisaka? Don't hold back!
Huh? O-Okay, then I'll try...the lobster.
What!? Pretty arrogant of you to be eyeing the main course this whole time!
Stay out of this!
Well, but...
Go for it! Take it all!
Amazing! The more I chew, the more flavor I taste! Pure bliss...!
What happened to your bento?
I ate it, of course. But I have a separate stomach for lobster!
No, a whole different digestive system!
Lobster is the best word ever!
Not only does it look perfect, but it tastes perfect, too...
Takasu?
Can I take a picture of your bento?
Well, I want to show my grandma what a regular bento looks like.
Huh? But I was in a rush this morning and couldn't—
C'mon, it's fine.
- Cool, thanks. C'mon, everyone! Feast!
- I can't let anyone think...
Lobsters are so stupid,
- that this is my best...
letting themselves taste good...
Same goes for crabs.
Ugh, that damn Yusaku...
I ate way too much.
Ka-Kawashima, um, y'know...
What? Out with it.
About Kitamura's grandma, um...
Is she like a cooking teacher, or does she have her own restaurant?
She's got to be a pro. Right...?
She's just your average housewife.
Your average...housewife...
Yeah. I'm pretty sure, anyway.
So...what's her name, anyway?
What? Why would I know that?
And yuck, what's with that face?
Jeez, what a shock. That venomous glare just sparked my memory.
Her name is Miyo, born in the year of the snake. Yep, Miyo-chan.
Miyo-chan, huh?
Let's see what your "best" bento is truly like, boy!
Bring it on! Our next battle will be for real, Miyo-chan!
Hey, are you okay...?
Kitamura-kun! Let's eat together.
Your grandma made you lunch again, right?
Yep. But look. It's a normal sized one today!
Right... It can't be too expensive, or take too much time to make...
It must be the perfect size for a high schooler...
Using these rules, we can have a fair fight.
All right, let's see...
Huh? What's up?
Okay... Bring it, Miyo-chan!
Whoa! Nice, Takasu. Fried cutlets today?
Yeah.
They're last night's leftovers, quickly and easily cooked up with some fresh eggs.
Neat!
Let's see what you got... Gonna break the rules again for your grandson?
- Caviar? Shark fin?
- Now then...
Huh?
P-Pretty simple, isn't it?
I did tell her that rice balls would suffice, but she really took it easy.
This lunch is too simple. It's not enough for a high schooler.
I think I've won...but wait!
That shine...is it sesame oil!?
Hold on, could it be...!?
S-So good!
It's filled with barbecue beef and wrapped in
Korean-style seaweed! What a surprise!
This bento is perfect. And is this a plum?
And this is... Yay! Tuna and mayo!
My absolute favorite!
You actually said "yay"...
The barbecue beef is exciting, the plum is a rice ball staple, and it has his favorite dish...
A perfect merging of simplicity and variety...
Compared to that, my cutlet will taste the same...
For the whole. Entire. Meal.
Ryuji, thanks for the food. The fried cutlet with egg was really tasty.
Huh? O-Oh, no problem.
Wow, those rice balls look good!
Rice balls for dinner doesn't sound bad.
I mean, lunch was good and all, but eating this day after day ruins its luster.
Y-Yeah, I know that, but...
We had leftovers, so...
No. I let Miyo-chan get into my head, making me think luxurious fried food was king...
But to accommodate that thought,
I needed a reason to make fried food.
So I cooked it for dinner last night...
Yeah...I made fried cutlet last night just so I could use it for lunch today...
A true housewife needs to think about food for an extended period of time.
I went a tad overboard yesterday, but...I got my groove back.
Miiiiiyoooo!
Are you shouting my grandma's name!?
Bento... Bento... How...?
What do I need to do...?
Hey, what're you gonna put in the rice balls?
Salmon is a must, but it can't be salted. Just regular.
Rice balls!? How can I win if I make the same things she does!?
I'm talking about dinner, not lunch.
Dinner can wait!
I was proud of my housewifery...
I took real pride in it!
But... I'm still a high school level one...
I might be great in the junior circuit, but I can't even compete in the senior circuit.
I am but a small fish in a big pond...
I was thrown into the open sea,
only to be met by a shark named Kitamura Miyo...
Bonito flakes wouldn't be bad, either.
Hey, what are you doing?
Huh? Since you're howling like a useless mutt, I'm doing the shopping for you.
The shopping...? C'mon, this is all junk food.
What? I put some bonito flakes in there!
And that one's for dessert.
Oh, did you know that if you put soy sauce on pudding, it tastes like melons?
Old news, and you even got it wrong.
Huh? Really? What was it, then?
- I can't be wasting my time like this...
- Not melons... Just watermelon?
Oh! I know what this small fish has that the old shark doesn't.
That would be...
My youth.
Hey, Taiga! Seen Kitamura-kun?
Hey, it has to be five millimeters below this line! No more, no less.
Okay, a little more.
Shut up! You're the one always telling me to not eat this stuff!
Are those cup noodles?
Oh...Minorin.
You brought a pot, too? That's pretty hip, makes me wanna do a flip and take a dip.
What's this? Having cup noodles for lunch?
I want some. I'm tired of cold food.
That smells nice.
- I want some.
- Looks good...
Eating this at home is normal, but eating it at school is new.
Lunch time will become fun time.
This youthful way of thinking must be foreign to Kitamura's grandma...
This victory...
Is all mine!
Minorin, you can't eat with us today?
We have a lunch meeting for softball today...
Hey, hey! Bro-amura, let's get going, bro.
Sorry, sorry.
H-Hey, Kitamura.
I overslept today, so I had to bring cup noodles...
Huh? You have hot water, then?
Y-Yeah.
Mind if I...use some of it?
What a lifesaver. My grandma gave me cup soup.
She was like, "Some kids eat cup noodles, right? Just ask them for hot water."
I thought there'd be no way, but...score.
It's this and a sandwich today. Perfect for munching on while in a meeting.
Kitamura-kun!
Sorry about the wait. Let's go.
'Kaaaay. See you later, Taiga.
'Kaaaay.
A sandwich sounds good.
Then don't eat that.
I mean, give it back to me.
What are you doing!?
- What're they doing?
- No! You can't! Don't eat it!
You're not even making sens—ow, hot!
I don't think they'll get enough vital nutrients from cup noodles.
Hot!
Hey, hey. Thanks for waiting!
No extra...
Sans extra...
But then...
Pow! Extra-extra on another plate!
Thanks, Minorin!
No thanks necessary. If that's still not enough, I can give you even more.
Super extra-extra.
Yeah!
Anyway, gorging on carbs after school, are we?
Cup noodles can't fill my stomach.
Not to mention I wasn't able to eat it...
Why doesn't Ryuji just make his regular bentos?
He's thinking way too hard, that mongrel.
Boo-hoo Taiga, you poor girl. You can't survive without his food anymore, can you?
Whaaat!?
Now, now. Eating is the basis of all things. It's normal to be fed.
I'll be around. Take your time!
Bentos, huh...?
No... No... No... This isn't it...
Wow! It's like a food party!
This looks really good, but I can't eat it all. Where's Taiga?
No idea.
Oh, can I take some to work?
Mr. Yaegaki's wife left him. I'm sure he'd be delighted. Your food's really good, so—
See you later!
Time for me to eat.
What the heck? She should've come over for dinner.
She's probably still mad about lunch.
I can't be doting over her...
I need to create the ultimate lunch and defeat Kitamura Miyo...
No matter the cost.
Maybe I can stuff some curry into some rice...?
Chugu.
Maybe I can bring some sashimi and make a sashimi bowl?
Chupepu.
- Or maybe some nice cracker appetizers!?
- Pubebo po!
Hey! Stop making those garbage noises!
S-Seconds?
You want more? I mean...
Garbage... Leftovers...
I already failed with my cutlet...
Then, maybe... Maybe I simply need to make something fresh.
Yeah, that's it... That has to be it...
In...
Indecent rulebreaker, am I!?
Judge me all you like, Inko-chan!
I-In... I-In...
Inzaghi.
Whatever!
- Filippo Inzaghi... You know him?
- Yeah, so what if I cheat a little bit...?
I'll take it...to the next level!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
"The Hayabusa Bullet Train debuted March 5 on the Tohoku Shinkansen line,"
"thrilling rail fans and people living in northern..." Huh?
That smell...
What is it...?
This is...?
That sound... There's no way, right?
I mean, it can't be...
But...
- A...rice cooker?
- You serious?
Rice cooker?
No way...
It did smell good.
- Oh man, it smells good...
- I'm getting hungry now...
So...why did you do this, Takasu-kun?
Takasu?
Silly Taka-chan. You don't cook rice in the classroom.
That's too funny.
Wait a sec, you guys! And you too, Teach!
How do you know it's me!? Don't assume!
Come on, who else would possibly try to do this?
Fine! I'm guilty! Please let it slide!
Please don't pull the plug! It's too cruel!
Wh-What's going on!?
Idiot.
It's all over.
Such a waste. Can't you just plug it in again?
That'll ruin the rice's taste.
Who cares? You've already hit the bottom of the barrel.
The taste of autumn...
Maitake mushrooms... Oyster mushrooms...
So many mushrooms...
I thought that...I could win with freshly prepared mushroom rice...
That's not a bento.
I know. I was the one who created the rules, and I broke them. So, I lose by default...
What do you mean, default? You lost it, started huffing like a cur, and self-imploded.
Here.
I had a feeling that I wasn't going to be able to eat lunch today.
This is my blessing for an over-thinking, wayward mongrel.
You...made this? All by yourself?
Ungrateful fool! Even I can make rice balls!
You...taught me before, remember?
Hot! Freshly cooked rice is dangerous!
Just grab it! We need to have hot rice or it won't be any good! Go for it!
What? If you don't want it,
I won't force it on you.
I-I'll take it. Thanks!
So?
What is it? Why're you shaking?
Saaaaaaaaaaaaalty!
Add some broth, and...that should disintegrate the salt.
Hurry, hurry!
Hold on, let me add some garnish.
Okay.
Thanks for the food!
Hey, you gotta let it soften up...
So...gooooood!
The added plum accents the dish nicely! I must be a genius!
I see... You're right...
Genius?
Right...
The first manga bento aside...
No, including that one...
Miyo-chan's lunches were made for Kitamura to enjoy.
The rice balls were to comply with his request...
The cup soup was because she knew he had a meeting...
Everything was tailored for his enjoyment.
But...as for me...
That was so good.
You're the one...who eats my bentos.
Huh? What are you saying?
Eating a little made me even more hungry!
Now I want to eat something heavy...
Maybe I can eat cutlets now!
Cutlet rice and soup!
Three times in a week? Well, I do have some thin-sliced meat.
Nice! Make a layered-meat cutlet!
Oh, let's try the mushroom rice, too!
They can go together.
By your command.
Aren't you gonna eat my rice balls with the soup?
Um, I'll eat them as-is. I was surprised the first time, but they're not inedible.
Wait, did you just insult me?
No, not at all.
Yes, you did! You just badmouthed me!
Now I demand cheese in my layered cutlet.
And so, I learned the secret of the bento.
They should be made for someone.
Bentos are made with someone in mind.
And I'm sure...that's what makes them delicious.