oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nai
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudou ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
"I can't eat anymore!"
"If you can't eat, you should have a drink!"
"Thanks for the meal."
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Praise the Girl
What's more important, me? Or rakugo?
Don't ask stupi—
You are, of course!
Compared to you...
...rakugo means nothing!
Come on, don't say that!
Both are important!
But...
But?
When I asked her for a bite, she wouldn't give me one.
When I complimented her outfit and said that I wanted one just like it,
she wouldn't tell me where she bought it from.
She promised to introduce me to a guy,
but then she called off the party because
everyone else was already going out with someone!
Oh, shut up!
This isn't about choosing between you or rakugo!
You're just whining!
So rakugo really is more important!
I'll kill rakugo, then die!
A forced double-suicide with rakugo?
Doesn't that mean rakugo really is more important?
Hey! Let's focus on birth instead of suicide!
Let's all celebrate together!
Don't rub
A Christmas party!
Sounds good.
Let's do it!
A
Piles
The writers aren't even trying to match the season.
As they say, "Time and tide wait for no man".
The real question is whether they're trying to match the broadcast or the sales.
Yeah, don't worry about minor details like that.
It's not minor!
By the way, who are you gonna spend the real Christmas with?
With E**zou.
E**zou.
Oh? Figures we'd all pick E**zou.
At least try to lie!
He's a kabuki actor. He's got the biggest share in my heart.
No he doesn't!
But anyway, even if we were to hold a Christmas party,
A
Share Prices
Plummet
I wouldn't be able to get in the mood. The world's in an economic crisis.
It's not just E**zou.
If we fail to act in indulgenge and don't do our share of spending, things won't get better.
What do you mean?
A
Piles
During a crisis, everyone spends less, so the whole situation just gets worse and worse.
The trick is to buy so much crap that you can say you've had more than your fair share.
That oughta make the economic situation better.
Freelancers especially should spend a lion's share!
I won't say names, but if you've gotten rich from drawing manga,
then don't buy a cheap corner store parcel! Spend your fair share!
So, in order to have a merry Christmas, we need to act in indulgence?
Meaning doing something like going overboard on your honeymoon and buying all the first class cabins on a cruise ship,
or buying a huge diamond for your bride.
Actors should hide some extra in their underwear too.
That's not right.
What three things show a kabuki actor's tension?
Tenses? Act, acting, acted?
No.
Being dead drunk. On tequila. Also, national treasure.
No!
I know!
Consume, gamble, and buy.
You mean booze, black jack, and hookers?
No. Overconsume, gamble with your life, and buy help.
A dead-in-the-wool kabuki actor!
Are you serious?!
So that's why people go to church on Christmas.
The Father listens to your problems.
That's a whole different story!
Even if you feel that you're useless and you've hit rock bottom...
"It's all right. You're a wonderful person!"
They sing odes to you.
So that's why they sing odes and hymns at church!
I think you're getting it all wrong.
Let's sing an ode about Kukuru to cheer her up!
It's...
It's all right!
It was supposed to be an ode, not a musical!
You're wonderful!
It's all right! It's all right!
They were here before!
You're wonderful!
It's all right! It's all—
How dare you disturb my song!
You ruined our wonderful ode!
I'm sorry. I'll start again.
It's okay...
You're all just making fun of me!
Kukuru!
What's this Rubens-style painting doing here?
Patrasche, I've had enough...
It was then that a Christmas miracle happened.
High spirits descended upon Kukuru.
High spirits? Not holy?
Yeah, she sure is in high spirits now.
A true miracle from 34th Street, Shinjuku!
Now we can sing odes together with her!
It's all right!
This is chaos!
You should sing too, Marii!
I'd rather not.
It's all right!
Do you think Marii is...
...tone dea—
It was then that a miracle happened.
Marii's spirits fell.
Her spirits have fallen! She's in low spirits!
Fallen spirits? So she's a demon?
Fallen angels are demons...
We must purge the demon! Call an exorcist!
I came when I heard that a demon causes you great suffering.
A real demon emerged.
Even this year, the fight between high and low spirits continues.
We must exorcise demons!
But how...
There's a way!
Rubbing her boobs will purge the demon!
And if you use that rubbed photo as your wallpaper, you'll be blessed with happiness!
When I did this,
I became happy!
You should try too!
No you shouldn't!
Harajuku Station
A
Stylish Little Town
Is this the fabled Harajuku?
I hardly leave the house except to buy groceries,
so when I go to a place like this, I get so nervous...
Me too.
People from the countryside are invisible to them.
Don't worry, we're humans all the same!
Yeah! Just look down the road!
That's some human garb—
Get a grip, Marii!
Don't reveal your power level.
This is hipster town.
You have to be kidding me!
Miyazaki is the best! No one can argue with that!
Yeah, I guess the father plays in his own league, but I'm not sure about ***.
But he only got really famous with Nausicaa.
Yeah, no one knows Cagliostro or Go, Panda...
What do you think about Howl's? Nobody really knows ***.
Dunno...
That reminds me, we have to go to a talent shop!
You mean the idols'?
Yeah, like Kunichan's and Mashi's, or Tacchan's pickled veggie shop.
But it's the Bamboo Dancers that define Harajuku!
What age are you even living in?
They've been gone since forever.
My Harajuku debut is up in flames...
You're better off this way.
Let's have fun now that we're here.
There are interesting shops in Back-Hara'.
Back-Hara'?
Back-Harajuku. Shortened as Back-Hara'.
Hold on. Who's calling it the back?
Everyone...
Back-Hara', huh?
You see, the word "back" is usually associated with
"back-door enrollment" or "backside" or "backstreet".
You know, generally something with a bad meaning. You know that, right?
Like "backstabbing" or "backhander".
Or "backdoor trojan".
Or have a  "backlog"!
How many animators had to take a bullet train to deliver the SR tapes from the offices out in the sticks?!
Well, since it's a Harajuku that is no longer part of ordinary Harajuku, how about Top-Hara'? Or Toppara.
That's good! We shouldn't call it Back-Hara'!
It's Top-Hara', you hear?
That's what I expected of Back-Hara'...
I mean Top-Hara'!
Blue girls are the majority here.
Blue?
It's a way of classifying fashion magazines.
Magazines featuring girls like them have blue designs.
Magazines with more ladylike or mature fashion are called red for a similar reason.
Huh? Blue mags? Red mags? Yellow paper?
That sounds like a tongue-twister.
You know, like that Harajuku-ish idol. What was her name... Lucky... Pamu-pamu?
Like the cute cat cured the queued Cuban cube?
Then how about singing Sammy sung songs on sinking sand?
Bus bucksaw blast!
Buck buskaw bast?
The trick is to say it like, "busback soyblast".
A soy blast in the back of a bus?
Busback soyblast...
Bus bucksaw blast...
Bus bucksaw blast! It works!
But imagine what'd happen if you did it like that...
Sushi
Busback soyblast.
Busback Soyblast
Burnt soy almost smells like vinegar!
Yeah, it's not nice.
Feels like I'm in a darkroom.
Let's eat crepes!
Custard Choco Special
Huh? Crepes? Like what Harajuku's famous for?
Sure, Harajuku is famous for them,
but it's been a while since I had any.
The basic kind is choco-banana, right?
There are lots of other yummy flavors too!
What? Mango? Almond jelly?
Red beans with soy flour? Salty caramel?
It's a mere crepe!
It's just flour, water and eggs!
Behold the purity of octopus balls!
Strawberry custard with extra whipped cream, a medium-sized brownie, chocolate spray and a maple syrup caramel sauce rollup!
Kigu recited the resurrection spell!
What? What language was that?
It's just strawberry with chocolate.
Then say so!
Also a shot of topping and a shot.
A shot?
It's a mere crepe! Why are there so many choices?!
Ordering is a pain in the butt!
Other people will laugh when they see me despairing!
So lame!
A plain crepe, please.
Plain?
Is that like how when you order pizza delivered,
you could pick a half-and-half one or a quartered family pizza as well,
but you go with a simple cheese pizza?
A hero! A hero is among us!
It's been a while since I had a crepe.
I guess. Not like it's a big occasion.
Could it be you've never eaten crepe before, Marii?
I feel like my life's gonna change if I eat this!
What do you mean?
Is it such an epochal event?
No!
It's just so embarrassing to eat this in public...
You know, it's like going to a festival,
or waiting an hour to buy donuts,
or buying a mascot character's goods,
or waiting for foreign celebrities at the airport...
It feels like a big deal for me.
Don't puff it up like that.
Yeah, we're all eating it.
Why is that hill in Kunitachi "Creamy's"?! It pisses me off!
Tell me, is it Creamy? Or Krimii? Or Kriimi?
That pisses me off.
What's the big deal, Marii? It's just flour!
Yeah! Consider it a sweet fried squid!
Osaka's famous specialty!
Fried squid...
Mix squid with flour, then fry it...
Add soy sauce and eat.
You'll be fine.
No, it's just not the same!
Fried squid comes on a plate! They wouldn't wrap it in a lame piece of paper.
Happily spending 500 or 600 yen on this thing is like spending 3000 on a simple ramen!
The value is totally off!
It's weird the moment you've gotta eat it standing in a crowd!
It's bad manners!
Don't you think so?
Shut up and eat!
And now for the weather forecast.
Today's pressure pattern will shift to one typical of winter,
Nation-wide dry-conditions advisory
and the air will become dry.
Continuing with the regional—
A
Farewell to Glasses
It really is very dry.
My fingers dry out, and my skin cracks painfully.
But if your skin cracks,
you can't have anything at your fingertips!
Huh?
Young performers are all poor, so if they couldn't have
fire at their fingertips, for example, they'd be in trouble!
I hope you know that's a metaphor.
It's their last lifeline!
The scariest part is that she actually seems serious.
Well, if you literally had fire at your fingertips...
You could make a living out of showing it off.
You'd have secure income! A get-out-of-poverty-free card!
Anyway, my skin is so dry that it cracks. Like paper.
That must be hard for you.
I'm so envious! Your skin is as soft as silk!
Please, stop poking me!
Lucky her... My skin is dry and rough, like a shark's.
Yeah, I can even grate things on it!
That hurts! Stop grating wasabi on my skin!
But if you grate wasabi on shark skin, it ends up smooth and full of aroma!
Paper skin.
Silky skin.
Shark skin.
It's nice that you all have your own unique style of skin.
I wonder what I am, then?
Well, I'd say you're...
Like a bigger sister?
You talk like one, that's for sure.
So I have sister skin?
But what kind of skin is that?
Is it clean? Or dry? Or soft? Or rough?
No, it's not a kind of ski—
Well, I'd say it's...
like a girl with a dragon tattoo.
Dragon as in the Kurikara dragon god,
and by tattoo I mean an Eastern-style tattoo.
How do you know so much about tattoos, Teto?
Could it be that you have one on your ankle, just like you-know-who?
Let's not talk about that now.
Let me etch it into you!
Let me etch it into you as an amateur!
Let me etch it into you with harsh brutality, just like during middle school
when I accidentally stabbed my hand with a mechanical pencil,
the lead broke and the mark's still there to this day!
Don't you want to have big sister skin for real?
I don't! Stop!
Gan, stop it already.
She's already got a mark of her own.
That's different!
If she had tattoos, she couldn't go to her favorite bathhouses like the Oedo Spa,
the Hakone Yunessun, the Marine Spa Atami, or the Hawaiians' Spa Resort.
She couldn't become a public servant in Osaka either.
But this is so childish. It's not like a big sister at all.
Then let's draw something in paint, so it can be washed off.
But what kind of drawing would be big sister-ish?
Why not just draw a big sister to keep it simple?
That's more like a hag than a big sister.
I guess this'll do.
Don't draw stupid things on me just because I can't see them!
Then how should a drawing of a big sister look?
Let's see, when I think of a big sister, I imagine...
I don't think the Afghan hound belongs there. Nor does Hiroshima's seal.
Really?
Anyway, just try drawing A***mi.
That's a hag too!
That's such a mean thing to say to A***mi.
I'm good at drawing, so let me try!
You react, you lose.
But now that we've got so many kinds of skin here, is there something we can do?
CM plan
Dry Squad: Skin Arranger!
Dry Squad
Skin Arranger
Paper skin!
Paper skin
Bouhatei Tetora
Shark skin!
Shark skin
Anrakutei Kukuru
Silky skin!
Silky skin
Haroukitei Kigurumi
Big sister skin!
Big sister skin
Buratei Marii
Together, we are the Skin Arrangers!
What?!
Cream?!
I'll smear it on thick!
Beauty
A
Cellular Revitalizer
Moisturizer
Skin Cream
compound
I see, it's a skin care product ad!
You came up with this?
You're a genius under your skin!
But superhero squads are always five—
And Genius Skin over there makes five!
Let me join too!
But there's nothing special about your skin...
You could be the glasses-wearing enemy soldier.
Yeah, that could work.
Yep, if we had to squeeze her in the cast somehow, we'd do that.
Oh, shut up!
Like a goose!
See, you can do it if you try!
Now you're one of us too!
Her goosebumps are gone! She's back to normal!
That won't do.
Without distinctive skin, you can't join our squad.
But... I can't keep up those goosebumps all the time...
You must! That's your job as a Skin Arranger!
Let's get together enough creepy things to give her goosebumps for a lifetime!
The liquefied rotten veggies in the fridge,
the sound of nails on a chalkboard,
the results of a Google image search for "bugs"...
With that terrifying visage, you must be one of the enemy's monsters!
And whose fault is that?!
In the first place, surely there are ways to give me goosebumps not from horror, but from emotion!
Like a Susan Boyle song or something!
There's only one way we know to move someone to goosebumps...
This is it.
Congratulations on your graduation!
I'm so moved!
Hey...
This really does give me goosebumps!
Hey! Hey! What do you mean I'm graduating?!
We'll still be friends, even after you graduate!
We'll never forget you, Gan!
But why am I graduating?!
Let's go out to eat sometime, okay?
Take care!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Though we can't go with her, we'll all work extra hard in her place!
Hey! What do you mean... I'm graduating?!
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
A
Preview
I'm Haroukitei Kigurumi!
How are you all doing?
Do you pity the puppy that stands soaked in the rain?
Or do you pet it?
I'd pity it and pet it!
Thanks to your support, we present the splendid sixth performance of Joshiraku:
A
Four Wows
Musashi Scenery
The Servant's Vengeance
Four Wows, Musashi Scenery and The Servant's Vengeance.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again!