The newspaper association hasn't shown any signs of movement.
They won't let us get a sniff that easily.
Speed Rankings
First
Among the
slowest
Lemme go!
Speed Rankings
First
Among the
slowest
What are you guys after?
I hear you were calling Mizushima your sworn enemy.
Do you have something against her?
She's a monster.
When we went to protest against our minuscule budget...
The newspaper club's currently planning something interesting!
For that, we need a DSLR,
a top-end computer, and design software!
Oh, and a scanner and a laser printer!
Mind if I say something?
Money doesn't grow on trees.
Before the day was over,
we were downgraded to an association.
We lost our clubroom too.
The way she said it aside...
...didn't she do the right thing?
I thought you were allies of the weak!
You disappoint me, Fuji's Princess!
"Fuji's Princess"?
Oh, they've given you that embarrassing nickname.
I'm disappointed in you too, the Wild One!
You guys're awful!
"The Wild One"...
Is that me?!
Hang in there, Riko.
Riko!
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
Get over here, everyone
What should we talk about?
Well, you see, this is...
How did things end up like this?
These free-flowing conversations
Give birth to the greatest bonds and happiness
You're free to delude yourself
I'll take you on (bring it)
Let's give each other all we've got
You wanna be the happiest you can be, right?
I wanna fall in love
My feelings start pouring out of my heart
Where do I need to go to see my prince?
I wanna fall in love
Set flight to that sky of freedom
With my wings spread wide
My racing heart can no longer be stopped
Let's study this feeling
As we are Love Lab
A still invisible love
You wanna know more about it, don't you?
To the Wild One.
I don't think they mean much
when they say, "The Wild One."
Come on, don't take it so seriously.
It's actually a sign of your popularity!
So could you stop that?
Goodness.
Whatever could you be talking about?
Well, to be perfectly honest, you're creeping me out here.
Jeez, you're such a meanie!
Take that!
Whap, whap, whappity-whap!
Sh-She's adding her own sound effects!
Get a hold of yourself!
If you don't play the straight man here, who will?!
I can't handle this. No way.
Such pretty little flowers!
Wh-What?
My folks said you were the perfect example of girly,
so I'm examining your behavior.
Me?! No way...
I won't let them call me that anymore!
Can you blame them for it? That's what you're like.
Besides, it's not an insult.
Well, I have to say I don't like it!
"The Wild One"? What in the
world is that supposed to be?
It's like they're saying I stuff my face with raw meat!
I had no idea she'd hate it this much.
Used to
call her
"The
Wild
One"
Shorten it and you get "Wine," you know?
Wine?
Gulp.
Used to call her "Wine"
Come to think of it, you called me that before.
Et tu, Suzu?
You're wrong!
I just thought your underarm ravines were wonderful, and that I'd love to have ravines like yours!
No, that's not it!
Anyway, let's get off this topic for now.
R-Riko, let's have a discussion about the newspaper association, okay?
Yes, let's do it.
Okay?
Actually, let's save it for another day.
Huh? Why?
Going by what Ichikawa said,
they resent you for their demotion from being a club, I reckon.
Yeah, I reckon.
It's all because you went too far,
you know?
Your obnoxiousness is off the charts.
I was the one who gave the verdict to demote them.
They must resent me for it too.
During your phantom reign as president, yes?
Yeah, your obnoxiousness truly is off the charts.
Looks like the newspaper association is currently borrowing space from the broadcasting club.
Why did they start enacting their revenge now?
If I had to identify a reason,
could it be due to the...
broadcast we did?!
Stop messing around!
That's what I'd like to say!
No, it's what I'd like to say!
Excuse me.
I'm from the broadcasting club.
How can we help you?
We've had a request box set up outside the broadcasting room since last week.
And, well, this was one of the requests.
"I'd love to hear a duet sung by
Fuji's Princess and the Wild One."
Whoops, that's not the right one. I meant this.
"Ever since I heard the broadcast the other day,
I've been wanting to ask the student council something.
Do boys not like darker girls?"
"What if one were to be just a little bit chubby?"
Who was it that suggested you put that box up?
It came up when I was talking to Minami from the newspaper association.
We'll take care of this.
However, the contents are rather problematic, so please don't tell anybody about it.
Sure.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
There's now a new avenue for suggestions. This is a problem.
They're trying to see what we'll do.
If we answer the previous requests and ignore this one,
then they can accuse us of favoritism.
That said, if we don't answer them,
then they'll keep making requests and put pressure on us.
Come up with a solution, Mizushima!
Take that!
Whap, whap, whappity-whap!
Stop it!
You can't come up with one?
This is quite the pickle.
Oh, right.
I could ask the pretty little flowers!
Flowers, flowers in the pot,
what's the best idea of the lot—
Riko.
You're so cute.
Truly the ideal woman.
O, sweet Riko, will you be my princess?
You're going to mimic Maki, aren't you?
Do it.
Go on.
Like hell I could mimic Makio!
The next day
That was harsh, my soul sistah.
May the gospel of my soul echo far and wide!
Dammit, why does it sound so good? That pisses me off!
Anyway, what the hell are you up to?
I gave the question we got about darker girls some thought
and became a soul singer to see if they really weren't popular.
My big brother said that their hips were wonderful.
My big bro said he wanted them to step on him with their long legs.
Well, they seem popular enough with your brothers.
What about "girls that are just a little bit chubby"?
If my memory serves me right...
...Suzu's conscious about her weight.
I don't think they need to worry about that, right?
Yeah, they say guys like women
with a little meat on their bones.
And they prefer well-endowed girls to anorexic ones.
Hey, say something to her.
Wh-What should I say?
Oh, right!
A girl being conscious of and
embarrassed by her small breasts
is super lovely, super cute, and super killer,
or so my big brother said.
R-Really?
Eno Bro was useful for the first time in his life!
I-Is it that good? Can I do that too?
But you've got breasts.
Suzu turned to the dark side!
I can't, huh?
You could just substitute it with
something else you're conscious of.
I'm so ashamed by how often I get hangnails on my pinky!
I'm so ashamed by having a friend like this!
It's done.
Newspaper
Association
(Temp)
Let's take it over to the student council's office right away!
Faced with this harassment,
they'll soon crumble and promote us to a club!
No need to rush that much.
But we won't make in time otherwise.
I can't stand your articles going unappreciated.
Fuji Girls' News
Nana...
I'll be right back.
Oww...
I'm sorry.
Looks like it's going to take her a while to get there.
Ever since I heard the broadcast the
other day, I've been wanting to
ask the student council something.
Do boys not like darker girls?
Looking forward to your answer!
Still, those two are being too open about this.
They could've just told the teachers about us giving love advice if all they wanted to do was crush us.
And if they want a scoop to publish,
they should be more secretive about it.
But they went out of their way to tell us about their investigation
and created a troublesome avenue for requests.
They also showed off what they were doing by making requests in a way that made it obvious it was them.
Maybe they want to strike a deal with us?
A deal? Like promoting them to a club and increasing their budget or something?
I hope you're not going to give in to those demands.
Of course not!
We, the student council,
hold authority because we use it the right way!
"Use it the right way," you say?
Announcement
Starting today, Kurahashi Riko
from Class 2-3 will be the Student
Council President's assistant.
Student Council President
Maki Natsuo
Love Lab Results
Oh?
If you ignore certain unavoidable circumstances, that is.
We need to find out if that broadcast was what caused them to make a move now.
Maybe they had to make a move for some reason?
My homeroom teacher, Ms. Sugihara,
used to be the newspaper club's advisor, so I'll see if I can get anything out of her.
I'll look into whatever records we
have on the newspaper club, then.
Riko, we should split up and go ask the other students for information.
Sure.
I'll help too.
Thanks.
Let's prepare to counterattack!
Did you find anything?
Nah.
Me neither.
I heard from one of Minami's classmates that when the club got downgraded, it lost some members.
We might figure something out if we talk to them.
Where are they now?
They joined other clubs.
Then let's split up and—
Yo. That was a surprise!
Why are you here?
I spotted you all during my trip to the bathroom.
This isn't like you, Sayo.
Look at you, having all this fun with friends.
I thought this wasn't your world.
Aren't you gonna say anything?
Nah, it's fine.
Why?
Because it'd just make her happy.
Just kidding!
Didn't those lines sound straight out of a novel?
Huh?
See?
So you guys are friends, huh? Good for you, Sayo.
Oh, right.
You probably haven't seen this yet,
so you can have mine.
Later!
Wha—
President's Assistant Gone Mad?!
Well, ain't that a good picture?
What?
I guess it's because they had a good model.
I wouldn't mind doing that again—
"A good model," my foot!
This picture isn't as bizarre as the real thing was,
but take a look at this title!
"Gone Mad?!"
My thoughts exactly!
Don't you think you're going a bit too far?
So did they print this out planning to hand it out all over school?
There's no way this article would get approval, though.
This is kinda interesting.
"We can't call her 'The Wild One' like this."
Very nice!
"The Mild One"!
That's not much of a difference.
I-It's okay!
Look, you can shorten "The Mild One" and be "Mine"!
President's Assistant Gone Mad?!
She's so slow.
Wait!
I won't!
This is my chance!
Now is the time!
I'll get her this time!
Is this some new kind of game or something?
Stay back!
Wait!
What do you want?
"What"?
What is this supposed to be?
This is a great picture...
Riko was acting so weird,
but in this picture she just seems so naturally cute.
Y-You think so?
I'm sure Riko will love this picture!
W-Will she?
She will!
What are you two doing?
Mizushima! This is what these people were up to!
Mizushima!
The newspaper club?
Yes.
It seems they're not happy with their association status.
Have you heard anything from them?
I-I just want to know as a student council member.
How I'd like some lunch right about now.
Take this seriously!
Minami was already prepared for the downgrade since nobody joined the club this year.
Losing the clubroom didn't hurt, either.
It was just being used as a storage room.
They lost some members, but those two were the only ones putting in any effort, anyway.
Ichikawa didn't mind either. All she wanted
was to make up for what happened last year.
"Make up"?
If I remember correctly, they didn't get
selected for last year's newspaper contest.
That so? You sure know a lot.
Why don't you know? You were their advisor.
They're not really unhappy or anything.
Oh yeah, apparently the contest rules changed this year.
"Associations can no longer take part."
See?
They are unhappy!
I got my hands on some vital information, and yet...
Forgive me!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
The newspaper contest is next month.
That's definitely why they're acting now!
Their goal is to get reinstated as a club!
I won't say it again!
Listen to me!
I've had such rotten luck this week.
And it's not gonna get any better.
What's gonna happen?
I'm meeting my boyfriend after school.
For real?!
You finally gave up and decided to act like a couple, eh?
I ignored our six monthiversary and his birthday,
after which he sent me a text asking me if
he could ambush me on my way back home.
He's your boyfriend and your stalker.
Ambush?
I was lying in wait for you!
Come with me!
I was lying in wait for an ambush!
From now on, I only want to lie in wait for you!
Please do.
Riko
learned
a new
slapstick
technique:
"Delusion
Breaker"!
Maybe I should postpone meeting my boyfriend.
What's wrong with you?
We'll be fine here.
You finally felt like it, so go see him.
Okay, then I'll ask him for a guy's opinion on the request we got before.
You know, the "What should I say to go back
to just being friends with my boyfriend?" one.
Don't do it!
You're seeing him for the first time in six months.
Where are you meeting him?
At the park.
The park!
Did you wait long?
Nah, I just got here.
Stop having delusions about me!
Hey! Break this delusion at once!
What? But it's so cute.
You'll give him a birthday present, won't you?
Like hell I will!
Too naive, Suzu.
The time you get to spend with me
is my gift to you.
Stop it!
Am I having a string of unlucky days?
See you later!
Okay, now that we've sent Mizushima on her way,
let's figure out how to deal with the newspaper association.
The registration deadline for the contest is in ten days.
I'm pretty sure they'll soon start
considering putting a deal on the table.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
Anyway, in order to seize the
initiative in those negotiations,
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
"What if one were to be
just a little bit chubby?"
Student Council's Opinion:
"Do boys not like darker girls?"
Apparently that's perfect.
Student Council's Opinion:
Singer-songwriters
are popular.
we'll beat them to the punch and go give them the answers they wanted.
Those are some rather irresponsible answers.
Let me see.
Did you give me the "chubby" one because I'm chubby?
Just a coincidence.
Newspaper
Association
(Temp)
Oh, I forgot my little brother's baseball game was today.
What about a baseball game?
My parents told me to go take pictures, but I've still got work to do.
I could go instead.
Huh?
The secretary said my picture was good,
so I might've gotten a little bit better.
Maybe.
I'm sure it'd make my brother very happy!
Leave it to me!
It's at the local elementary school.
Got it!
Good grief.
Come in.
Oh, welcome.
We brought what you asked for.
I don't remember asking you for anything.
Those two requests about the
dark ones and the chubby ones.
Here you go.
Did you give me the "chubby"
one first because I'm chubby?
Just a coincidence.
This is the first I've heard of this.
Also, isn't your answer too half-assed?
We got the wrong person?
Sorry.
We did our best to come up with that answer,
but these love advice requests are really getting to us.
We were thinking of going to the teachers if these kinda requests kept coming in.
Don't you feel sorry for your clients?
They're anonymous,
so we can't even give them an answer.
Do you want me to use this to tell them, then?
Like, an underground newspaper that only gets distributed to students.
Tell us more!
Basically, it'll be structured like...
This is bad. We need to seize the initiative!
Our opponents' Achilles heel is time.
We can't decide right away.
Let's see. It'll take at least ten days of careful consideration.
All right.
What?
It's too bad I can't enter the summer contest,
but that's not all that important to me.
Wasn't their objective to give the contest another go?
It's not like she asked us to promote them to a club if she made us an underground newspaper either.
The underground newspaper thing sounds kinda interesting, though.
Let's all put our heads together and think about this tomorrow.
After we hear how Mizushima's date went, that is.
Gonna drown her in a sea of questions!
I got some great pictures.
I think I've gotten a lot better.
It won't be long before I get my hands on a scoop that'll shake Mizushima to her very core!
Core
Pow!
The next day after school
I went and took this picture last night,
but who would've thought she'd have a boyfriend?
She just went on a date yesterday.
Maybe she'll still be in high spirits and let us have a bigger budget!
Um...
The hell you want?
W-Well...
Acting like the paparazzi again?
Is this how the newspaper association does things?
What about you? Running off on dates with your boyfriend despite being a student council member!
How'd you get that picture?
It's my scoop from yesterday!
Gimme that!
I'll submit it to the special summer program, "Terrifying Doppelganger."
I know you just wanna delete it!
Mizushima! Ichikawa!
Come with me to the counseling office.
He's just a friend.
Even so, staying out late alone with a guy is outrageous!
How could a student council member get into an illicit relationship?
Were Enomoto or Maki aware of this?
If so, this is a huge problem.
My streak of unlucky days continues.
Nah, I guess I should call it an unlucky week now.
What are you talking about?
I kept it all to myself since it'd cause
problems if people found out about it.
If I knew this was gonna happen,
I would've told Enomoto or the rest of them about it.
I lied.
He's my boyfriend.
What?
Mizushima!
Also,
I'll quit the student council.
What's taking Mizushima so long?
I want to hear how her date went quickly!
Come on, S-S-Suzu. Don't be so restless.
Celebrating Mizushima's
six monthiversary
S-S-Stay calm and wait for her.
You're the one who needs to calm down!
Celebrating Mizushima's
six monthiversary
Don't get your hopes up. They might get dashed.
Anyway, Sayo sure is taking her time.
We share a special relationship
Our friendship is the subject of great envy
A little bit of curiosity will lead to great things
Don't you see?
In a flash, we'll get closer to what we seek
Let's laugh in our anguish
And in our depression
Let's keep exposing
More and more of our feelings for all to see
Run faster than your teen spirit can make you (go)
All together now (go)
Hand-in-hand
It doesn't matter if you fall
As long as we stand together (here we go!)
Don't be embarrassed (don't)
Of the best days of your life
Yell out what you wanna say
If tomorrow
And long into the future
You wanna keep smiling
These irreplaceable bonds
Will stay strong
Forever
Preview
Mizushima can't help with the
preview because she's on a date.
I'm so jealous.
Riko, what kinds of stuff have you done on dates?
What?
Well, soccer and baseball...
I see. You go to watch sporting events!
Yeah, that's it!
I wonder what kind of date Mizushima is having.
Last time, she went to banks, stock brokers, and real estate firms around town.
Those are all places that deal with lots of money.
That Smile...
She never loses focus, does she?