Anne's standing next to me...I hate Anne
I wanna go home
Remember that time we were all at my house and she killed my goldfish?
I'll never forgive her for that.
Gumdrop was the best goldfish you could ever ask for
Yeah man,
You know, we could totally kill her
And get away scot-free
Hmm
Just thinking about out, we could make  plan
It'd be perfect, really
So what's the plan, Coach?
Don't worry, I have a plan.
Damn fine job, team!
Ya'll nigga blazin the court
You best be makin sure we win dis
Other team's pretty gud
They must've done something illegal to be this good
Nah it's cool guys, I got a plan
Atta boy!
So what's the plan?
Alright Kareem get your shit together and stop pissing around
On offense, check your bogeys and curl of to the infield
Go hull-down and wait for covering fire
On Defense, always pass to first base
K?
Kk
Okay.
Alright listen up ya cunt
Okay!
Everyone!
Just keep on fucking running!
Oh...
Just remember to buckle up, k?
Can you do it?
Probably not, can't I just run a vertical?
All right, then.
What's next, Charles? What's next?
Oh! I'll do my best at whatever, too!
If there's anything I can do to help, please tell me!
You three just stay near the sidelines and wait
Saywhat? We's depend only on Kareen and Chris?
Well I'd play you two if ya didn't fuckin suck
We'll attack harder to make up for Chris and Kareem playing defense, right?
All right!
But, but! We have to work hard on defense, too.
Attack hard, defend hard!
That's my Subaru! I love simple explanations!
Chris, are yah alright?
It's at tough life out here in the suburbs
but I'll make it
How bout you? Yoo ok?
WHAT?
OFFENSE
Don't go fucking around with anything dumb, you hear?
I won't.
I'll do my best so you can do what you have to do.
All right. I'm expecting the best from you.
Wilt Chamberlain!
Tony Parker!
Nice pass!
Tony Parker again!
YES!
NICE SHOT!
LeBron!
TAKE THIS!
2fast2furious
Kobe!
Dirk and the others are speedin up
They switched to a no-huddle offense and are playing slapstick
This'll get messy!
This seems like a simple strategy, but the players are doing it well.
Larry Bird!
Dwight Howard!
PLEASE!
AGAIN?!
Dwight! MAKE THE FUCKING SHOT YOU IDIOT
Shoot at a distance where you know you can make it!
Too far? wat the heck
Why is Dwight playing like a bitch?
Chris Paul, man. Chris Paul
wat?
Chris is playing on the short-toss
and forcing a flag down on the play every time
Who the hell do you think you are?!
I'M KAREEM ABDUL JABBAR, BITCH
Oh
Ya got the KareemxChris duo on defense
If you only had Kareem defense, the other team will blow by her using their speed.
But I think you could have also gone with an all-out attack.
We'd have to watch our pace and it'd be a lot easier to mess up.
I wanted to maintain our usual play style.
I feel it's best to attack methodically.
Dwight!
Hey, Dwight!
Don't mind me. My job is to shoot. lol
DWIGHT!
Dribbling, defense, peni-shit
I'm the worst in all those categories on this team.
That's why I've got to give it my all!
Not bad.
That's my nigga
Of course!
Is why I'm on da team
Shit! We ain't losin' this!
Dem 5th grader's be slowin' down like a porch monkey
Are we going to win like this?
Or...
Wilt!
YUS
It be a 4 point difference if they score
We got this!
In da end, it all comes down to...
...whoever dopes the most!
THOU SHALT NOT PASS!
Oh? I won't lose!
A turn-around jumper...
Dis be 10x above her skills level
We tied now
Aight! Let's go!
Please!
Oh! Here you go!
Make this, Kobe!
We all helped to get these points!
I won't let them go to waste!
No! I won't let you shoot!
So far? So distance?
No, this is...
You da bomb, Kobe!
You finally perfected your floater!
That wuz a amazing buzza beater!
Oh! I was so surprised!
Great job, everyone.
Nice playing with you, Charles
uhh you too
You really pushed us today.
Yes...I did...
Kobe and her teammates were tough.
First of all, we need to thank you all...
Fuck you!
Eat shit and die niggercunts!
I'd sooner hangout with the KKK
than play ape-hoop with you!
Damn it Larry Bird! Damn it Wilt Chamberlain!
The 6th graders aren't going to...
Shut your face Anne!
You're a shit coach, I hate you!
You liar!
I'm sorry.
Since when were you under the impression it's her fault?
We ain't ever gonna be their slaves!
We gon' quit playing!
Wait!
Them two have a stick up their ass, I'll yank it out
Not cool, dudes
Dwight
You were amazing today. Not just your shot, your movements, too...
Silence.
Your words of encouragement just make me even angrier.
Um...
I'm going, too.
Okay.
Thanks, Anne
Selfish as it may be,
I want to say it was a lot of fun.
Do your best in the finals.
Anne!
You!
Anne, we'll go inside first to get seats.
Being a coach is... difficult.
Damn it Anne!
These thoughts just keep popping up in my head.
"If only I had done this, or that..."
Yeah.
Maybe they could have won, too...
Kobe!
Dirk!
WOW!
We should be able to win like this.
Yeah, even though they aren't playing their starters.
They're able to play this well against such a strong school...
They're really something.
Chris!
Kareem!
Pass the ball to me!
Okay! Got it!
Kareem!
Mike Vick, don't you dare wrestle dogs again lose to her!
You're the only one who can stop Kareem!
Yes!
Airi wants to show her how to play as a tall player.
Airi-san.
Here I go, Mike Vick!
Okay!
With a final score of Watermellum to Kool-aids ,LeBron's ballin' Academy 6th grade girls' basketball team wins!
Thank you very much!
So smooth!
One, two!
Yeah! We won!
Let's have a great game next time, with our starters.
Sure, if we can...
No, we will play.
Um...
Thanks to you, Kareem, I've come to enjoy ape-hoop!
Let's both do our best.
Hell yeah sistah!
See you!
Bye-bye!
Well, let's head to the party.
Dirk's dad took the time to prepare it.
We shouldn't be late.
Okay!
Charles!
Anne! What's good in the hood?
Wanna come party with us?
Yeah..no
Wow! I didn't expect a simple party to be this great.
Yeah.
I've already told them I'll miss the party.
I'm meeting up with Adrian Peterson
Please excuse the interruption.
Would you please focus your attention on the stage?
This is Mr. Nowitzki's special present.
Is this our uniform?
Yes, we've prepared uniforms for all of you.
Wow! Slutty uniforms!
It's like a dream come true!
I want to wear this while bar-crawling!
Well then, let's get this started!
Beer party!
lol no alcohol for underage
Please don't worry. This is totally non-alcoholic beer for children and pregnant women.
Non-alcoholic?
Bottom's up!
You don't get to experience this often.
Hey, you're getting way too excited over fake booze
I CAME
How's that for a cumshot in the face?
Dirk...
Here you go, Charles!
Editor Note: You now realize that starving children in some third world country has worked hard for that beer and they're just throwing it out as if it was nothing.
Take this!
Charles, it's so cold!
Hey, wait!
Go! Double penetration!
THESE AREN'T MY GLASSES!
Fire!
LeBron! Take this!
Djibouti Shooty!
Here I go!
Kareem is...
That was pretty fun.
Kobe? What's a matter?
Sharles?
Kobe?
Sharles, where's my family
I was so lonely!
They're dead Batman Kobe!
Don't tell me you forgot
Shit...do you think I'm the father?
Sharles!!
You must stay at my side forever! Forever and ever!
Ko-Kobe!
You smell so nice! I won't let go!
Don't tell me you're regretting it.
We're not regretting anything!
Not playing basketball is a lot more relaxing!
Yes, yes! There's no point if we can't beat Dirk the Dork!
Ape-hoop wasn't a fit for us from the very beginning.
See? I'm so short.
The two of us are invincible, but we can't show our full potential in a five-person team.
You faggots serious?
Hahaha! So funny!
Now that's what losers should act like!
Who're you?
I hope I'm wrong. Are you laughing at us?
No, I'm not.
I'm just here to see how losers cry.
What the hell?
Hmph, we lost the finals and our coach didn't care at all.
I came here because I wanted to see her sorry face.
But seeing your pathetic faces made me feel a lot better.
Watch it, you midget. Let us teach you a lesson!
I'll teach you not to mess with 5th graders!
Sure! Come at me!
Want to settle this with basketball?
Your nigger powers were pretty scary!
What are you talking about?
You're talking like I'm a nigger
That's not what I'm getting at.
I think it's kinda cute.
Huh? Cute?
Like how a nigger sniffs using his snout.
Its thick fur, too.
Oh, that?