It looks like you took a real beating...
Anchan! Please don't blame Mario!
Is your right hand all right?
It's late. Go to bed.
We start training tomorrow.
We can't let you end on a defeat, can we, Mario?
Anchan...
Every day, the two focused on training for the next fight.
Faster...
Mario was completely absorbed in mastering
a right feint followed by a left punch.
Anchan held the sandbag in place, despite not being fully healed.
Put more into it!
Will the god of delinquents smile upon these reformatory fugitives?
Hey, Mario! Anchan!
I set up your next fight!
Saturday, January 28th!
Anchan!
Yeah! Now let's win this time!
Well, I'm off to work!
Hey! Can't you take a break first?
You're gonna earn lots of money! So I gotta earn a ton, too!
--Be careful!
--I will!
Turtle took Western cigarettes that Lilly's U.S. Army officer lover gave him
and sold them on the black market to earn a daily income.
And, at the Shonan Special Reformatory...
Tadayoshi Toyama.
Your request to join the Self-Defense Force has been officially approved.
As such, you will be released from the reformatory
in ten day's time, on January 28th.
Soldier.
I'll tell you where Anchan and the others are later.
If I were in your shoes, I'd want to go straight to see them.
There's no need to worry about us.
No, I think I'll pass.
If their location got out because of that,
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
Plus I doubt Ishihara will stay nice and quiet forever...
Soldier...
Hey, Setsuko. What's this?
Oh, that?
It's a photo of my family.
Oh? Your family?
We take a picture of all of us every New Year.
This must be your little brother.
And is this your little sister?
Yes. She turns ten this years.
Check it out, Turtle. Her sister's really cute!
I'm going to work.
Turtle?
You're not a kid! Don't get excited just because of a picture!
What's the matter? Did I say something to annoy him?
I'm sorry, Setsuko. Turtle doesn't mean any harm.
He lost his family in an atomic blast.
He doesn't even have one photo with them left..
I'm sorry. I didn't know...
There's no reason for you to apologize.
It's only natural you didn't know.
Don't worry about it. Knowing Turtle, he'll be perfectly fine tomorrow!
Say, why don't we all take a picture together?
We're going to have lots of good memories from here on out!
This way, even Maeda will have a photo!
That's a good idea! Don't you agree, Anchan?
Y-yeah...
Okay! Then it's decided!
"Shonan Hospital"
"Several days later"
Here you go! Is this all right?
Wow! Thank you!
It's my husband's treasure, so take care of it, okay?
I really appreciate it!
So, Setsuko! What's he like?
Wh-what are you talking about?
I know the score!
You want to take a picture with the man you're in love with, right?
You don't have to hide it!
I-it isn't like that!
You let Sakuragi go?
Are you worried about him?
You were always tending to him, after all.
Could it be that she knows where...?
Hold on, Mario! Why do you get to be in the middle?!
Just be quiet!
Come on! Stay still.
Smile, Anchan! This is a commemorative photo!
--What are you acting so big for?!
--Shut up! I'm the star today!
--What?!
--Quit fighting, you two!
Sheesh! Now we have to take another one!
What did you hit me for?
--Okay! Line up again!
--Okay!
No fighting, you two! Smile, Sakuragi! Understand?
Okay! Here we go!
Smile, everyone!
"Shonan Hospital"
Just as I thought...
Yes, you were exactly right.
But we can't make a move just yet. We'll have to watch and--
Ishihara... Are you...?
Damn that Sakuragi, acting all happy-like..
I'll kill him!
I'll kill that bastard!
Why don't you come in? You'll catch a cold out here.
They've been gone a long time...
That idiot, worrying about me..
Why do I hafta come with you?!
Man, you're dense!
Don't you think we should leave Anchan and Setsuko
to themselves once in a while?
Oh, now i see..
Setsuko was considerate of me and the whole photo thing..
Someone nice like her deserves to be with Anchan!
What's the matter? You've been really quiet.
I just can't stay calm, ever since we broke out...
Honestly, I'd probably accept this kind of life with open arms.
But... I'm not used to being happy.
Don't be silly. You're going to be even happier from now on.
Next year you'll meet under that tree. All seven of you.
Yeah...
I'm very happy, actually.
You made it out safely...
...and we're able to be together like this...
You must be cold. Let's go inside.
"Can we ever be as happy as regular people?"
In the hideout, the injured and ill Rokurota loved his cherished Setsuko.
With nothing visible ahead but uncertainty and frustration,
love was the only thing he had to guide him.
What do you think? It's my father's old coat.
It'll be chilly tomorrow,
so I thought it'd help keep you from catching cold.
Hey, Mario. This is discrimination, isn't it?
I have some for you too!
What? Really?!
Yes! It looks good on you!
--It is discrimination after all.
--Yes.
This is it.
Yeah. But with you in my corner, I can do anything!
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow with some good food!
Plus those photos from the other day should be ready!
Really?!
Yahoo!
"Tomorrow, we'll start climbing the seven-colored rainbow
that spans the sky after the rain.
What sort of world stretches beyond the rainbow?"
The morning of January 28th was a foggy one.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
I know.
Doesn't she know you're the one who's fighting?
It's okay.
You guys can have this if you're feeling hungry.
Thanks.
No, it's nothing.
Well, take care!
Yeah. I'll see you later.
Live it up now, while you still can!
I'm personally going to put an end to your happiness!
Mario Minakami.
125 pounds. Okay.
Anchan!
I got into lightweight on the first try!
That's good.
Huh? Where's Turtle?
He went into town to sells smokes.
He said he'd be back in time for your fight.
Oh.
Man, that black marketeer's a cheapskate!
How am I supposed to throw a victory party with this chump change?
Guess I'll just have to earn some more...
Noboru Maeda, yes?
What are you talking about? You have the wrong person.
Let's just see what's in the sack first.
This? This is...
He's running away! After him!
Damn it! How do the cops know who I am?!
There he is!
Hey, now! Why are there so many cops here?!
--Stop!
--Get back here!
It's really coming down.
Hey, Anchan...
How do you feel about Setsuko?
What brought that on?
You plan to be with her, don't you?
That's a good question.
There isn't a whole lot I can do for her,
but I do want to make her happy.
She went through a lot of trouble just for me,
So I really want her to be happy.
Anchan... Watch me. I WILL win!
Sorry, Anchan.. Looks like I screwed up big-time...
Mario... I don't think I'll get to see your fight after all...
"Shonan Special Reformatory"
Tadayoshi Toyama! Someone from the SDF is here to pick you up!
Go to the director's office at once!
Wow! Congratulations! You're getting out!
--Cabbage...
--Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Don't forget now.
Next year, on June 6th, 1957... I'll be waiting under that tree!
Coffee.
Ol' Maeda...
All I did was give a quick mention to the cops
and they caught him like it was nothing..
That's good to hear.
Incidentally, about the will...
I searched their hideout but couldn't find it. Which means...
Yes, I know, Dr. Sasaki.
Then that simplifies things.
I'll clean up everything afterward.
Let's take care of 'em.
"Shibuya Police Station"
"Interrogation Room"
Rokurota Sakuragi! Mario Minakami!
You broke out with them! Surely you know where they are!
Say something, damn it!
You don't want to disappoint your teacher or whoever, do you?
Teacher?
Yeah, the instructor who works at your reformatory.
He was kind enough to tip us off about you.
The phone! Let me use the phone! Hurry!
It's him! He's taken action!
Ishihara's making his move, Anchan!
Looks like that fight's over.
Let's go, Mario!
Yeah!
Hold on you two!
Lilly?
That little runt friend of yours... the cops took him away.
They took Turtle?!
We received a call from a boy named Maeda.
He's apparently being held at the Shibuya Police Station.
The Shibuya Police Station?
You're Rokurota Sakuragi, correct?
Yes.
He says he needs to talk to you.
Anchan!
Go on, Anchan. Something bad must've happened.
Or else he wouldn't try and call us here
Mario...
Don't worry about me.
Hurry and answer Turtle's phone call.
All right.
Make sure you win, Mario.
Of course I will!
Sorry to suddenly ask you to be in my corner, Pops...
No, it's no problem.
Think you stand a chance this time?
I'll win. Especially since I owe you money and all..
Plus...
...I'm filled to be brim here with Anchan's knowledge!
Anchan! I will win! I will!
"Kobayasi Photography"
"Tachikawa Police Station"
Are you serious?!
This guard named Ishihara is addicted to speed.
He and the fugitive boys are working together
to illegally sell guns from the U.S. Army base.
If you don't believe me, then why don't you
lie in wait outside the base tonight?
I'm sure they'll make a deal with some local hooligans.
I appreciate your help.
You're very welcome.
What's up, Jap?! Too scared to fight back?!
What's the deal?! All you're doing is blocking, not fighting!
Listen, Mario! Make it through the first round!
The second round is where the real fight is!
I know, Anchan...!
He's used to bad situations.
His only focus now is to do what Anchan taught him.
The unwavering trust of a trainer and student
linked Anchan and Mario together.
Anchan rushes to answer Turtle's phone call
as Mario begins setting a trap inside the ring.
Sameta manazashi
nani o mitsuzukeru no ka
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
Even if I rot away
Just keep on running
So far away
But I never give it up
ima tokenai kizuna ga
unmei to kousaku shite yuku
kagirinai mirai e tsuzuite yuku
And I will get over it, it's now
A far-off distance
Mario fights alone.
Ishihara and Sakuragi face off.
Things are about to be settled once and for all.