A sudden incident has befallen me,
Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I was handed a red gem, and with it
I was given magical powers.
Coincidences led by new meetings
now emit light, and begin to move.
Feelings that intertwine,
and the story that begins...
The start of the days where magic
and ordinary life are in parallel.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin!
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden
deep within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
You're kidding. What is this?!
What?!
Episode 2: My Magical
Incantation is Lyrical?
What is this?
It's coming!
Protection.
Our powers, called programs,
are magical equations
that are embedded into executors.
The caster's mental energy is
needed to execute those equations.
And that is a thought entity,
created under an ominous power.
To stop its activity, you need
to seal it with that staff,
and turn it back into its original form.
I don't really get it.
What should I do?
Just like what you did earlier,
basic movements
such as attacking and defending will
happen just by wishing for them.
However, to use magic that
requires a higher level of power,
you need spells.
Spells?
Open your heart.
Your own spell should come
to mind within your heart.
Protection.
Lyrical, magical...
What needs to be sealed away
is the ominous container,
the Jewel Seed!
Seal the Jewel Seed!
Sealing Mode.
Set up.
Stand by, ready.
Lyrical, magical...
Jewel Seed, Serial 21...
Seal!
Sealing.
This is a Jewel Seed.
Touch it with Raging Heart.
Receipt: No. XXI.
Hey...
Is it over?
Yes, all thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
Hold on! Are you all right?! Hey!
Maybe...
It's not such a good idea
for me to stay here?
For now...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
Sorry for being so rough.
Are you hurt?
My wounds are fine. They've
almost completely healed already.
No kidding. Most of the
wounds are gone.
That's amazing.
Because you came to help me,
I was able to use my remaining
magic power to heal.
I don't really get it, but okay.
Hey, can I introduce myself?
Sure.
Ahem.
I'm Nanoha Takamachi.
I'm in third grade.
My family and my close friends
all call me Nanoha!
I'm Yuuno Scrya.
Scrya is my clan name,
so Yuuno would be my name.
Yuuno? That's a cute name.
I'm sorry, I got you...
Nanoha.
I got you, Nanoha,
involved in all of this.
Well, that's...
Well, I think I'm okay!
Oh, that's right!
Since you're hurt, Yuuno,
you can't relax here.
For now, let's go to my house.
We'll figure out the rest there, okay?
Welcome back.
Big brother...
Where did you wander off to, so late?
Um, well, um, uh...
My, it's so cute!
Big sister?!
Oh, it doesn't seem to be so cheerful.
Nanoha, did you go visit there
because you were worried about it?
Well, um...
I understand how you feel.
But you still can't run off
without telling anyone.
Come on, it's all right.
She made it back safe and sound.
Besides, Nanoha, you're a good girl,
so you won't do anything
like this again, right?
Well, um... Big brother...
I'm sorry I made you worry by leaving
the house without telling anyone.
Right.
Okay, that settles everything!
This is a very cute little animal!
Wouldn't Mom roll around
in panic because it's so cute?
I won't deny that possibility.
Morning, Yuuno.
Er... Good morning.
Well, for starters, kudos on
the hard work last night.
Likewise.
Last night, when I showed
Yuuno to Dad and Mom...
It's so cute!
He's adorable! He's just too adorable!
Mom, take it easy!
This is a rather wise-looking weasel.
He's adorable! He's just too adorable!
It's a ferret, Dad.
Can it do any tricks?
Here, shake.
It's really intelligent!
And so, the family was in a frenzy.
Afterwards, we were running around
deciding on things like Yuuno's food,
so I didn't get to talk
to him much last night.
Are you used to calling me
by my name now?
Right, Nanoha.
The only conversation I got in
was to call me by my name,
and talk to me like a friend.
Okay, I have to go to school now.
But I'd like to hear more
when I get home.
That's all right. We can have a
conversation even if we're apart.
Nanoha, you're already a mage.
It's like when you called for me.
Right.
Keep Raging Heart with you,
and talk to me within your heart.
Let's see...
Like this?
Right. Isn'tit easy?
You're right!
I'll talk to you when
you have free time.
About me, about magic,
about the Jewel Seeds...
Lyrical Nanoha!
Good morning!
Nanoha! Did you hear about
what happened last night?
Last night?
Apparently there was a car accident
at the veterinary clinic that
we went to yesterday,
and one of the walls got destroyed.
I'm worried about whether
that ferret is still okay.
Yeah...
Well, about that...
I see! So he's fine,
and at Nanoha's house now.
But that was some coincidence.
Coming across him in the streets
after it ran away from the clinic!
Right?
I'm not lying, I'm not lying!
I just fudged the truth a tiny bit.
Oh, and it seems like that ferret
wasn't anyone's pet,
so we'll be taking care
of him for a while.
I see!
We've gotta give him a name.
Did you already decide on one?
Yeah, he's named Yuuno.
Yuuno?
Yeah, Yuuno.
I see.
As I said in a previous lesson,
a kanji is made up of a
foundation and an annex.
By combining the two parts together,
a kanji can have different meanings,
even though it is only one character.
That is because a foundation
has its own meaning,
and the annex has its
own meaning as well.
Examples of foundations are: the
ninben which stands for a human,
the sanzui which represents water,
and the kihen which stands for a tree.
Now, here's a little quiz.
The Jewel Seeds are ancient
treasures in our world.
They originally were magical stones
that granted wishes for their holders,
but their execution
of power is unstable.
Just like last night, they go
out of control on their own.
They can harm their environment
in their search for a valid user.
Sometimes they go out of
control using the powers
of mistaken executions by people or
animals that randomly find them.
Why are such dangerous things
sitting around in my neighborhood?
It's all my fault.
Back where I came from, my job
is to excavate ancient ruins.
And one day, I found them
in an ancient monument.
I had asked the research group
to hold onto them.
However, the time-space
transporter carrying them
met either an accident or
some kind of artificial tragedy.
Twenty-one Jewel Seeds were
dispersed all over this world.
So far, I've been able to find only two.
So there's nineteen more?
Rise!
Isn't the balsam getting
much bigger now?
How many centimeters tall is it?
Wait? Hold on a second.
Listening to that story,
the Jewel Seeds getting dispersed
wasn't really your fault at all, Yuuno.
But I was the one that found them,
so I have to find them all,
and return them to the
place where they belong.
Just a little...
Just a little, I think I understand
how you feel, Yuuno.
Yuuno, you take things very seriously.
Oh, that's right.
Did you put up signs saying these
plants are under observation?
It would be quite the problem
if someone plucked them out,
thinking they were weeds!
Oh, and of course, make sure to
write your name and the date
you planted the seed on the sign.
Well...
I'm sorry I roped you into it
last night by having to save me.
But all I want from here on
is a little bit of time to rest,
until my magical powers
are back to full strength.
A week...
No, five days should be enough
to get my powers back,
so until then...
When they come back,
what will you do?
I'll go on my search for the
Jewel Seeds again, alone.
I won't allow that.
You won't allow it?!
It's impossible for me to help you
during school and cram school,
but other than that, I can help.
But there will be dangerous times,
just like last night.
I mean, I've gotten
to know you already,
and I've heard your story.
I can't just let you go.
Besides, if something like last night
were to happen here often,
it would trouble everyone
around us, right?
Yuuno, you're all alone and have
nobody around to help you, right?
It's lonely to be all by yourself.
So let me help you.
If someone needs your help,
and you have the power
to help them out,
you shouldn't debate
whether to help or not.
That's what Dad taught me.
Yuuno, you're in trouble,
and I can help you out, right?
With the power of magic.
Yeah...
I'm not sure if I can be
a proper mage or not, but...
You're already a mage, Nanoha.
I think you have much more
talent for it than I do.
Really?
I'm not really sure about that myself,
but for starters, please
teach me all sorts of things.
Bye-bye!
I'll do my best!
Yeah... Thanks.
Okay, I'm almost home now!
For now, how about we have
some snacks together?
Sure. Thanks.
I wonder what today's snack will be?
Excuse me...
Yuuno, that thing just now...
A new Jewel Seed has been executed!
It's really close by!
What should I do?
Let's head over there together.
Please help me.
Okay.
Nanoha! Raging Heart!
Okay!
It's already taken in one
of the local creatures.
What's going to happen?!
It will be tougher, because
it has a physical body!
It'll be all right, I think.
Nanoha!
Boot up the Raging Heart!
How do I boot it?
Start at "I am the one who has been
given a mission!" The boot password!
What?!
I can't remember such a long spell!
I'll tell you again, so repeat after me!
Got it!
Raging Heart?
Stand by ready.
Set up.
She booted up the Raging Heart
without a password?!
Nanoha, the protective armor!
Barrier Jacket.
Nanoha!
Protect condition: all green.
No damage dealt from that blow?
Just as I thought, this girl has
an amazing amount of talent.
Ouch... but it didn't hurt
enough to make me say it.
Let's see. I need to do
that sealing thing, right?
Raging Heart, please?
All right.
Sealing Mode, set up.
Stand by ready.
Lyrical, magical...
Jewel Seed, Serial 16...
Seal!
Sealing.
Receipt: No. XVI.
Is this good enough?
Yeabh, it couldn't have
been any better.
What? Did I trip and hit
my head or something?
I guess this is where you say,
"Thanks for the hard work"?
Yeah, that's right.
The first long day after I,
Nanoha Takamachi,
became a mage is about to end.
About my new friend Yuuno...
About magic...
About being uncertain, and
what I don't understand...
All in all, there are lots of things.
Come to think of it, I'm starving.
For now, I think I just have to
do my best in all sorts of things.
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of
cellophane and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying
inside a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining on
the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something I
can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
This and that as a mage,
such and such as a magical girl...
I, Nanoha Takamachi, will do
my best with lots of energy!
But problems are piled up
like a mountain!
Next up is an incident so big
it involves the entire city?!
Geez, it's so tough!
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 3:
The Town's In A Lot of Danger?
Next episode of Magical
Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 3:
The Town's In A Lot of Danger?
Episode 3: The Town's
In a Lot of Danger?!
Lyrical, magical, I'll do my best!