I am a man of sin.
A single woman comes to my doorstep to court me.
A friend through long years
of language study—
is it time to move beyond?
Have I ever been the recipient of an attack
by a person of such charms before?
However, before my eyes is another woman.
She came to me out from under that
other man, and she speaks all but naught.
And indeed, there is yet another woman whose feelings are wedging into a corner of my mind.
She is, even now, waiting and waiting
for me to come to her.
Dear God! Is it a sin for
a man to be so popular?
What ever shall I do?
Come on out!
Decide already!
Outside the door is the sexy Hanuki-san.
In the boarding house is the silent, exquisite, Kaori-san.
And waiting at the café is my
yet unseen pen-pal, Keiko-san.
Unless I plan on becoming
a renaissance man of the sexual arts,
I must narrow it down to one of them!
In that case...
In that case!
I choose Keiko-san!
Why?!
I will not succumb to the flesh!
What I should do now is to strip away all veneer and reveal myself as I am at this moment!
Keiko-san, please wait for me!
Then I was a brand-spanking-new freshman university student,
and countless doors to that rose-colored campus life lay open before me.
However, devoting my life to a single circle
poses a chance of wasting
my entire college life in vain.
One must spread out the risk!
I will join many circles and experience a diversified rose-colored campus life!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
Reading
Circle
Set sail on the sea of the printed word!
And for the journey you will need friends.
Yes! All you need for the trip is yourself.
If you are interested,
you're welcome aboard!
As I have always been of the indoor variety,
I will search for encounters through reading!
Books are the ocean! Now is the time to set sail on the sea of the printed word!
The waves of life, the wind, the sad rain,
the storm of trials, the hopeless Sargasso...
The meetings and partings of a ria coast!
The morning sun of hope...
Then, one day, I encounter a single small ship.
And on that ship, a raven-haired maiden.
It's quiet.
Reading is, after all, a solitary journey.
But don't you think this is a little too quiet?
The seeds of love can't sprout here.
I'm alone adrift on the Pacific!
Thanks, come again.
Appreciate the business.
If you'd like, read this.
"The Night Is Brief, Go Forth Maidens," by Morimi Tomihiko
It's a silly little young-adult novel,
but feel free to use it as
a bad example to follow.
Get out of my sight!
He said he'd bought it at a used book store
and didn't need it anymore, so I should read it.
Its content was that of
a silly little young-adult novel,
but on the final page was an address and name,
written in exquisite penmanship.
It seemed to be that of the previous owner.
I become strangely curious of this Higuchi Keiko-san person.
I have long been envious of those
engaging in the exchange of letters.
The dreamer in me itched to trade carefully crafted communiques
if, by some unforeseen chance, an opportunity should arise.
When I expressed this wish
to Ozu in the past...
It must be exciting to send off lewd prose
to a woman you don't even know.
You're such a hopeless deviant. What am I to do with you?
You ribald writing wretch!
...is how he called me a giant pervert.
But I saw it as an excellent chance.
Is not this, indeed, the command of heaven?
Is not forming a pen-pal with an unseen woman
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity?
Exchange
Letters
But sending off a letter unannounced is,
at the least, unrefined, or simply freakish.
And so I purchased stationery
that was beautiful,
and to make up for that freakishness overflowing with sincerity,
I wrote a letter containing harmless pleasantries.
First, I apologized profusely
for sending a letter uninvited,
then added a note explaining
how I was a hardworking student,
and, neither praising or criticizing,
gave my impressions of the novel I finished.
I wrote nothing of requesting to receive a response.
As a lengthy missive would give off
a somewhat freakish vibe,
I wrote revision after revision, aiming for a mere half a page.
It requires considerable resolve to send a reply to a letter
that was sent to you from an unknown person
in this world of corrupt morals.
Even more if it's some maiden
raised among butterflies and rainbows.
I was prepared not to feel hurt if a response did not come.
Dear you, thank you for the letter.
Through this letter,
I could tell from her modesty
that Keiko-san was herself
a lovely raven-haired maiden.
Bingo!
And so, from such an unbelievably simple start, my two years exchanging letters had begun.
The hot and humid days continue on,
like summer is coming
just a step ahead, don't you think?
In my boarding house,
there is quite poor ventilation,
so it is considerably hot.
It became quite humid after
the Hollyhock Festival ended, yes...
Before the rainy season comes,
I have a sense we're stuck
wandering in the doldrums of summer.
I think being able to study
whatever you'd like in college
is a really amazing thing.
What are you studying there?
My studies are nothing particularly special.
I am majoring in agriculture.
I am deeply interested in
the world of science.
I feel it a shame that one is not able to
survey it all because it has grown vastly.
Such progress is what enables
our modern way of life, however,
so I must make due.
It sounds like your studies are quite wonderful.
As for me, a lecturer who has been in Japan for three years was returning to his home country,
and we threw a farewell party at an Irish pub on Oike Street.
I cannot imbibe,
but the fried whitefish was very delicious.
I have never been to an Irish pub before,
but I do wish to go one day.
I have much interest in the culture of England.
I hope to one day go there myself and
test out the fruits of my language study.
Thanks to my father's work, I spent a short time
in New York during my childhood.
I was raised greatly admiring Miles Davis and Magic Johnson (has it already been so long?),
and I remember skating there.
I use that experience to teach at an inter-college English-conversation circle.
I feel like my experience might be of
some small help to the other students.
So you've lived overseas?
I think that's really amazing.
But it's not good for your health if you strain yourself by studying too much.
Be careful not to overdo it.
Thank you for your concern.
As you say, I am also engaging in
what physical activity I may.
Actually, as a way to relieve stress,
I enjoy playing the part of an action star.
I know it's childish and laughable,
but it's a Hero TV show!
It gives me a chance to train my body,
and at the same time,
I can let children live their dreams!
It is a job worth doing, indeed.
I wish to teach children that justice will prevail!
Hey, save Mochiguman!
Oh, what's the matter?
Those bad guys are trying to kidnap the girl, right?
Everyone, make them change their ways!
Change your ways!
Change your ways! Change your ways!
Look, they ran away!
Change your ways!
Good job, everyone!
Thank you, Mochiguman!
Thank you, kids!
Who's that?
Weirdo.
Think he's some freak?
It sounds like a wonderful activity.
I also love heroes that make children happy.
Although I, too, am embarrassed by my childish taste.
As the letters came from Keiko-san,
so too did my glimpses at her personality.
She was, indeed, my ideal woman!
I wrote about myself,
trying to be as appealing as possible.
Although there were some slight embellishments,
they were all for the sake of
classy presentation, yes?
You've been beaming lately.
Something happen of note?
Of note or notes,
it's none of your business.
Oh, that's not like you.
You are exchanging letters with
a mystery woman you've never met, right?
How do you...
Seems I hit the mark.
Well, doing it by exchanging letters is
probably perfect for a spineless wimp like you.
I am not doing these
rude things you think I am!
Now, now, I know you.
Porn comprises half of you!
Even now, you're anguishing over wanting to meet her.
You wouldn't be able to understand!
It's a platonic relationship!
Said I, while at the same time being in
a close relationship with two other girls.
You should just go with your feelings.
Hanuki-san's English was left
a bit too much to her feelings;
a miraculous master of soul talk who expressed herself perfectly to the instructor.
Oh, so you and Ozu-kun are in the same year?
It's a small world, you know?
He's a patient at our practice.
Thanks to his meddling,
I've gotten in a ton of trouble.
Tell me about it. That's his hobby.
And he has a habit of keeping secrets about himself, right?
I don't even know where he lives!
He won't tell me no matter how much I ask!
Oh, I've been there.
Really?
Yeah, it's in Joudoji.
A bit farther in off of Shirakawa Road is an
apartment building that looks like it's made of candy.
Looks like Ozu-kun gets
a lot of money from his parents.
Can he piss me off any more?
Hanuki-san, with whom I was having frank conversations, is an older, lovely dental hygienist.
We started going to a café together after class.
Then, because of the Hero Show,
I came to take care of a certain woman.
Let me introduce you.
This is Kaori.
Kaori is a very elegant woman.
I want you to be very courteous to her.
Well, I'm counting on you.
Don't go getting any weird thoughts now.
According to Mr. Jougasaki, who hired me, I was exceedingly cautious and a safe bet.
Her hair was carefully combed,
and her clothes were neat and elegant.
I couldn't think of her as a doll at all.
It's not like I couldn't understand how
Mr. Jougasaki could be so enthralled with this beauty.
Ozu-kun doesn't drink, you see.
What about you, Hanuki-san?
It causes problems for me,
so I only drink with people I'm close to.
If you need a drinking buddy, I'd be happy to, anytime!
I'm not so easy to handle...
Someone she's close to, huh?
I haven't entered that category yet.
No, one day, Hanuki-san and I will drain a barrel of Yamazaki Distillery whiskey!
Man, your place stinks!
Continuing from long ago, an enemy of the Masochistic Proxy-Proxy War
had infiltrated Mr. Jougasaki's
boarding house and with hidden cameras,
filmed scenes of him caring for his
dear Kaori-san and screened an exposé.
I'm not sure you got the balls for it,
but my place isn't safe.
Hold on to Kaori here
for a little while, will you?
Kaori, I'm sorry.
I know this place is filthy,
but please endure it for a little while.
Suddenly, we began living together.
The game of Love had taken
such a sudden turn,
but my letters with Keiko-san also continued unabated.
There are two crucial points about exchanging letters.
The first is that they must be handwritten.
And the second is that,
for example, even if the cauldron of hell is unleashed and the world comes to an end,
to ne'er meet your partner in correspondence.
Says I, but it is only human to
become curious about your partner.
What is she like?
What does she wear? What is her home like?
How does she walk? What does she look like?
I want to know more!
Only once did I head toward her address.
It was impulsive.
White Garden Joudoji 306
White Garden Joudoji
What are you doing here?
Sorry!
Wasn't that Akashi-san?
I wonder if she recognized me.
Akashi-san was in the class
one year below me,
together with Ozu in the engineering department.
I had thought it a pressing question as to
why she ended up hanging out
with a person like him
and visiting a person on the second floor of Shimogamo Yuusuisou they call "Master."
Anyway, I had thought I would continue
my platonic relationship with Keiko-san, but...
Greetings.
Spring sure is in full bloom.
It's already been two years
since we've started this
back-and-forth of letters.
There is something I want to ask.
Could we meet up, face to face, one time?
Yahoo!
I surely caught her fancy
through my genius literary skills.
I am entirely a man of sin.
But I cannot meet her.
The me in the letters had walked far away from the me in reality.
I had originally written the
high expectations of myself
I predicted would be true
by the time I met Keiko-san,
but at some point, it had become pure fabrication.
Just do it!
I cannot disillusion Keiko-san.
I have lied far too much.
I can't show my face to her.
But she gathered the courage
and wrote "I want to see you!"
Why am I, a man, being so indecisive?
It's still not too late!
I'll become the me who's in the letters!
That's it, I'll do it!
Then I'll become a man worthy of her!
However, the hurdles were far too high.
Why did I even write those things in the letters to begin with?
Keiko-san kept repeating the invitation,
and I kept dodging the issue.
Hey, wanna go out for some drinks?
I was finally asked out
for a drink by Hanuki-san!
This certifies that she feels close to me now!
But!
I have a report that I need to write today.
Oh, I see.
Right. Good luck on your report!
I can wait no longer. I want to tell you. I'll be waiting
at Cafe Collection on August 13th at 8 p.m.
_If perchance you do not come, let us no longer
_persist in this exchange of letters.
'
That meeting is tonight.
But today is my last day with Kaori-san.
The other day, Mr. Jougasaki came to say he was taking Kaori-san back.
We are being torn apart.
I wonder if you'll forget about me.
I was being forced into making a decision
about all three women at once.
I think about the past two years.
What a sweet, innocent two years I had led.
Now that it's finally come to this,
everything is hurtling toward the climax!
Do I go for drinks with Hanuki-san?
Do I take Kaori-san and run away?
Do I meet Keiko-san and
reveal the whole truth to her?
Unless I plan to become
a renaissance man of the sexual arts,
I must narrow it down to one of them!
So if it's like this, I'd rather have
some guy who asks me out every day.
Kubouzuka
I'm in the hotel lounge right now.
Want to come for a drink? (^_−)〜☆
I had a sinking feeling like she was falling
into the clutches of that perverted dentist.
Hanuki-san must've wanted moral support!
I can't let her be ruined by the
invitations of the perverted dentist!
This is a matter of life and death!
I cannot stand idly by and watch it unfold!
First thing: consult the old woman!
That'll be 6,000 yen.
I've made up my mind!
I'll show her my true self!
Searching for someone?
It's you! Didn't I just...
The opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
6,000 yen + 2,000 yen = 8,000 yen
Surcharge
Her apartment! You have to
surprise her at her apartment!
Out of the question!
Visiting the home of your pen-pal is completely unacceptable!
That's breaking the most fundamental rule!
I absolutely will not!
Go! Yahoo!
Rules are made to be broken.
Keiko-san lives up there, in room 306.
I am going to show Keiko-san
the real me if it's the last thing I do!
It was then that I saw Keiko-san with an extremely eerie face—
an unhealthy looking face
that seemed like it belonged to
a human from the dark side of the moon.
It had an ominous smile rising up that seemed like it was entreating other's misery.
I'd say it was strangely slippery
like some youkai's.
She almost looked like Ozu.
She and Ozu were two peas in a pod. Or rather she was exactly like Ozu.
No, that is Ozu!
Swallowing the conclusion
I had come to within my mind
required a great amount of effort from my soul.
I needed a whole cup full of sugar to make this unimaginably bitter medicine go down!
Higuchi Keiko-san did not exist.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
I had been exchanging letters
with Ozu these past two years.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
An apartment building
that looks like
it's made of candy.
Could there be a more cruel conclusion?
Senpai! It's you, right, Senpai?
Akashi-san...
I apologize for deceiving you!
I am sorry,
but I participated in the exchange of letters.
I wrote the letters at the request of Ozu-senpai.
As I felt pained from these actions,
I could not bring myself to say it.
Wait...
So it was you, Akashi-san?
That's correct.
I'm sorry!
But Ozu is the only one at fault, right?
No, Ozu-senpai got bored of it after a while.
It was just a random prank to him.
I could not bring myself to simply fade out,
so I took over writing
the letters as Keiko-san.
So that's what it was.
It was quite difficult
capturing Keiko-san's character.
After all, Ozu-senpai knew
your tastes extremely well
and had used them to
create the character.
It's true. Keiko-san was my ideal woman,
far too good to be true.
But to think that it was
Ozu who created her?
Since you didn't come
to where I said to meet,
I thought you might stop by here,
so I staked it out.
I was saved by you once.
Do you remember the Mochiguman Show?
That was you?
I was still in high school.
I thought you were really cool
back then, Senpai.
That... was me while I was in the suit...
The real me is...
It was a lot of fun exchanging letters.
It's true you like to show off a little,
but I was lying as well,
so we're even.
These come in sets of five,
but I lost one of them.
I really love Mochiguman.
It's kind of embarrassing, though.
Opportunity is always
dangling in front of your eyes.
I collected Kaori-san.
The castella is a reward
from Jougasaki-san.
Ozu
Why'd you go straight home?
That was a pretty nice moment!
Why didn't you at least
ask her out on a date?
Don't misunderstand.
Akashi-san just likes Mochiguman. That's all. It's not me she likes.
Dammit!
I'm tearin' outta here!
Damn you, Ozu!
When I think about it, enough Keiko-san, enough Hanuki-san or Kaori-san...
Could it be that I was just
dancing in the palm of Ozu's hand?
That goddamn monster!
Eating the unhappiness of others
as a topping on his three helpings of rice!
Now that I think about it,
he must've had quite a delicious feast
from me these past two years!
He deserves to die
a thousand times over!
I'll roast him into coffee
and grind him to bits!
Silently, I ate the entire castella myself
and, through my actions,
sank deeper into a hellish solitude.
As I devoured the castella,
I took on the form of a devil.
That's right. Don't misunderstand.
I was enamored with Keiko-san whom was created by Ozu.
It was most definitely not Akashi-san.
Don't change the subject.
Longing for others, transiently wishing for a partner... I will not accept it!
After all, it is my fate to be dragged down forever together with Ozu.
The Mariana Trench
When I thought that,
I found myself strangely relieved.
I'm not suited to stand on
love's victory podium.
This is how it should be...
Like hell it is!
I want to stand on the victory podium, no matter what methods I have to use!