Hey, show that to me!
Geez, why do you have something like this?
You don't have to be sneaky.
If you want it that badly...
Sorry, sorry! What I actually wanted was Hideyoshi's picture, and yours was—
I won't forgive you today!
I won't always be beaten up!
Sensei! We want a mock summon battle!
Give us permission to summon!
Fine. Approved!
Summoned Being, summon!
Huh?
Summon! Summon!
Summon!
That's weird. What's going on?
Summon! Summon! Summon!
SUMMON!
Approval canceled.
What? I can't control the field.
Accidents occur without any prior warning.
Who's there?
What's the secret password?
Uncontrollable desire.
Okay.
Where are the goods?
I'll exchange them for cash.
Hideyoshi's waitress picture!
I'm glad to be alive.
That's only the beginning.
The changing room shot is double the price.
Eh? Give me a discount, Ninja Pervert.
I've only been drinking salt water this week.
This comes as a set right now.
If that's the case...
Damn it, they've caused me trouble.
Security again? The password is...
Crap!
Damn, that surprised me.
It looks like something's happened.
Excuse me.
Principal, there's a problem with the Summoned Being System.
Yeah, I know.
Even over here...
What's going on?
It's in the way.
Go away.
Ouch, ouch! Stop it!
Yoshii, what did you do this time?
Why do you suspect me first?
What did you do, Akihisa?
It's better to confess quickly.
No one will blame you.
You guys too...
Your Summoned Being is the only one affected.
Huh, why?
The system is probably unstable.
I'll try to summon too.
Summon!
An adult version, huh?
Please don't look!
Sign: Eyes
Yuuji can't look.
I wonder if Himeji-san will grow up to be like this too.
A specific part has grown exceptionally.
Me too!
Summon!
Minami's has inconsistent growth, just like her.
What if...
I do this?
No, no!
Under the clothes.
Good thinking, Ninja Pervert!
You can't take that!
Stop it!
It's the skeleton.
Well, the idea wasn't bad.
If I reposition the camera...
Looks like fun. I should summon too.
Summon!
No! You can't, Mr. Wolf.
A beauty.
I said stop.
Just as I thought, Hideyoshi!
I wasn't wrong at all.
There's obviously something wrong!
The system is down.
I guess I'll try too.
Summon!
Wonderful.
Me too.
Summon!
A good match.
What about Ninja Pervert?
Summon.
Wait a bit! The Summoned Beings did this on their own.
Stop!
Traitor.
What's your Summoned Being like, Yoshii-kun?
Show us, Aki.
I'll give it a try.
Summon!
How odd. Why is mine different to everyone else's?
They're back to normal.
What's wrong?
We can't control them!
Where are they going?
What's going on?
The teachers' Summoned Beings that are close to the system's core are completely frozen and cannot be summoned.
The students' Summoned Beings are in chaos.
I give up.
I can't access the security system.
And since the door won't open, we can't even get inside to fix it.
What if we turn off the system's power?
It'll last on its own for a month because of the uninterruptible power supply.
Then is destroying the wall the only way?
We have to show the system to the Academic Society tomorrow.
It'll be a disgrace if there's a hole in the wall.
Then what should we do?
Let's see... Let's have the idiots do the work.
You want me to fix it?
The Probate's Summoned Being runs in a different part of the system, so it's not affected like the others.
I see. So that's why Akihisa's Summoned Being was acting differently.
But I couldn't summon properly.
That's because you summoned inside the flawed teachers' field.
But you have your own field, right?
I see. If I use the Black Golden Bracelet...
Enter the sever room with your Summoned Being and connect the cable.
Then I'll stop the security system with the computer and open the door.
It's a plan that is possible to carry out thanks to the Probate's Summoned Being's ability to touch objects.
But my Summoned Being can't walk through walls.
There's a vent to cool the system.
A Summoned Being can fit through it.
But he won't be able to control the Summoned Being if he can't see inside the vents.
Here.
A video camera and transmitter.
You can see inside the vents if you give this to the Summoned Being.
You're smart, Ninja Pervert!
I'm surprised you had such things.
What do you use them for?
Don't blame Ninja Pervert! He's actually a good guy!
But he's a bit...
I haven't said anything yet.
Akihisa is a regular customer, after all.
You'll need to take control in front of the server room, since the radius of the Black Golden Bracelet's effect is small.
We'll guide you from here.
So that's the entrance.
Awaken!
Summon!
Go!
The Summoned Being has entered the vents.
Route is clear.
Head straight, Akihisa.
Roger!
Will it be okay? He's a probate—a problem student.
We must rely on him, because that idiot is the only one who can use the Black Golden Bracelet.
Turn right three meters ahead, and go left at the next intersection.
It's like a maze.
Why is it so complicated?
It's a security measure.
I feel numb! My score's dropping!
What is this?!
It's the poisonous swamp area.
Why is something like that there?
It's a security measure.
Let's make a detour around the danger zone.
Turn right at the next corner.
I can see a light.
Almost there. Just keep heading straight.
Huh? What's that?
Summoned Beings?
Rampaging Summoned Beings appeared!
Here they come!
Make it stop, Yuuji!
It's no good; I can't control it.
Why?
No, I don't like this.
Stop. Make it stop!
Hey! Yuuji! Hideyoshi! Minami! Himeji-san! Dad!
Stop it! Please stop it!
Those who have fallen, go take supplementary classes!
Why?!
Are you all right, Yoshii-kun?
I saw Hell.
What kind of supplementary class was it?
We'll continue the plan.
Take the recovery exam and replenish your score.
But you'll be taken out by the enemy again unless you get a really high score.
If you'd like, Yoshii-kun, shall I help you with your studies?
A one-on-one lesson?
Really?
You have quick thinking when it comes to mental conversions like that.
It's no use if it doesn't take effect immediately.
If that's the case, I have a good idea.
I see. Aki can rack up points if the questions are easy enough for even someone like him.
But it does feel like cheating.
Akihisa's never gained levels like these before.
You're amazing, Yoshii-kun!
Do your best, Aki.
What'd you get wrong?
The Taika Reforms were in 645.
You still haven't memorized it even though we went through that much?
That's why I got confused about which was which.
But didn't his level increase a lot?
Wouldn't he be fine if enemies appear?
Continue the plan.
I'll clear it for sure this time.
Okay, turn left at the next intersection.
Roger!
It's the poisonous swamp area.
So, he still gets numb even though he's stronger now.
Don't test that out!
Turn right at the end.
Roger.
Be careful Akihisa, if you touch that...
Yoshii-kun!
Aki!
It's tight!
I told you to be careful.
I couldn't help it!
That's...
Okay, I won't lose this time!
I can win this, I can win this!
Please don't get off guard.
Tsuchiya's coming.
I'll be fine, since the battle subject is history.
If Ninja Pervert can't use Physical Education and Health, he's no match for the current me!
It's the poisonous swamp area.
Those who have fallen, go take supplementary classes!
That's not fair!
Our Summoned Beings lost on their own!
Stop complaining!
I'm here.
There should be a disconnected cable.
Please connect that.
Roger!
Found it.
Minami!
Aki!
Please run!
But...
Hurry! If you don't, I'll—
Himeji-san.
Wooden Horse!
Yoshii-kun.
Yoshii-kun!
Aki!
Damn it!
Something's coming!
The summoning field is synchronizing with a transfer.
A Summoned Being is appearing!
Onee-sama!
Miharu?
Even though they are Summoned Beings, I won't let you touch that pig!
Please touch me instead!
Now!
Supplementary classes!
Yes!
Eh?
Yoshii-kun, it's impossible! Please run!
But to have come this far... This is just...
Yoshii-kun!
Just a little bit more...
It's impossible to go further. Let's stop them.
As an instructor, to let a student go through futile pain is—
Not yet!
I still have some points left.
There's no way that you can win with that score.
Your abilities are different.
But, because of that...
Abilities?
That's right! Just like how my Summoned Being got stronger—abilities aren't necessarily linked to scores.
Himeji-san, take the recovery exam!
Please!
I see what you're up to.
Takahashi-sensei, please.
If you increase your score any more, he has no chance of winning.
Please mark this!
Yoshii-kun.
Himeji Mizuki.
Zero points.
Good job.
The system has recovered.
I guess it's been solved for now.
Yoshii-kun, are you all right?
Yup. This is nothing.
Those who have a zero, go and take supplementary classes!
I'll be going, then.
Yeah.
Himeji-san.
What are you looking down for?
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
Ah, my score!
Don't cling to that fractional number.
Go and take supplementary classes too.
Eh?!
Yoshii-kun.
Yeah.
To rely on the Class F students for such an important job was a huge gamble, but aren't you glad that it went well?
I didn't think of it as a gamble.
One day you'll understand
how to get along with idiots.
Sensei, me too.
Preview
Question nine.
The measurement "cup" is used to measure a woman's bust size. Explain the size of the standard A cup.
Shimada Minami.
I'll refrain from commenting.
Next week: Kiss, Bust, and Ponytail
This will be on the test.