Sel... fish!
I couldn't protect anything...
Not a thing...
Happy go lucky girls! Precure! Yeah!
The world is like a merry-go-round
Love makes it turn, 3, 2, 1
Every day it sparkles
Dokidoki Precure
I wear my new clothes and walk a path I've never walked before
My heart races and I greet the scenery around me
The color of the flower on the corner will be my lucky color for the day
Leave it all to me, because today I'm blessed
If your friends are in trouble
isn't it normal to help them?
Happy lucky Precure
Only Precure makes my heart pound
Our happy love will change the world
What's more than just cute
is our promise between girls
I will fight for you and believe in you
Gather your unparalleled tenderness, yeah, Precure
Take a look, everyone.
This is the Tokyo Clover Tower that was just finished last year.
It's 999 meters tall!
It's the tallest broadcasting tower in the world.
Wow, it's huge!
Man, it's crazy big up close!
Now then, you're free to walk around until 2 P.M.
Oogai First Middle School
Orientation
Make sure you all don't return late!
Oogai First Middle School
Orientation
Okay!
Oogai First Middle School
Orientation
Hm?
Sir, should you be here?
The students have already gotten off.
Don't worry.
Our student council president is extremely reliable.
President?
The Earth's in Danger!
The Last Precure Left!
What'djoo say, punk?
You callin' me a punk, punk?
President!
Nikaido is picking a fight with students from another school!
I think Yashima got carsick on the ride here!
President!
Mimura lost his wallet!
She's fast!
Almost a national record!
Mimura!
Huh?
Here's your lost wallet.
So don't worry.
Thanks, you're a lifesaver!
It was kind of hot in that bus, huh?
It's a bit cooler here, so take a break.
Thank you.
Nikaido, what are you fighting over?
Th-These punks just bumped into me!
Nuh-uh, you did!
Stop!
If you all fight over something so tiny,
that ginormous Clover Tower will laugh in your face.
Who the punk are you?
Why, hello there!
I'm the student council president of Oogai First Middle School,
Aida Mana!
Talk about loud!
And a handshake to show we're friends!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
S-Sure...
A pleasure to meet you, too!
We're friends!
She tamed those beasts in the blink of an eye!
Our president's as reliable as ever!
Aida, please reconsider our offer.
Please join our club!
Okay, sure!
Mana!
Rikka!
You've got enough work with the student council!
Why do people like you always try to solve everyone's problems?
The lost and found can handle lost items.
The health representative can handle carsick kids.
And there's certainly no need for you to stop a fight yourself.
You're the student council president after all,
so learn to say no...
Huh? Mana?
If you're looking for Aida,
she's watching over a lost child over there.
Let me show you a good luck charm.
Just draw a heart in your palm like this, and make a wish.
"I hope I find my mommy."
Heart?
Yeah. And when you do—
Michiko!
Mommy!
Michiko...
Thank you, lady!
Sure!
Oh, Mana...
Why do you try to help other people so much?
Well, when I see other people looking happy,
it makes me happy too!
Mana, you're spreading your love too thin.
Whoah!
What is it now?
That's Makopi, isn't it?!
Who?
A celebrity?
You don't know her?
It's Kenzaki Makoto!
Mixed with the flavors of nature.
And no caffeine to make your body shine.
Ace Tea.
Let's drink together!
Let's drink
together!
I see, so she's an idol who's all the rage right now.
I've seen those before.
But I've never seen a celebrity in the flesh before!
She's so cute!
Her face is so petite!
Wait, Mana!
Excuse us! Please let us through!
Don't push!
Now, hurry!
It's dangerous, so don't push!
Excuse me!
U-Um...
We're too busy for you.
An autograph can—
You dropped something.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Makoto?
You're acting strange.
I'm sorry.
I'm fine now.
I heard it!
That was the dark heartbeat of a Selfish!
So the Selfish have come to this world too?
We have to hurry and find the star of hope!
We have to find our final trump card!
This is serious!
Ah, Makopi thanked me!
My heart's never beaten so fast in my life!
Excuse me, my blissful looking lady.
Wha?
I have some accessories that would look perfect on you.
Would you like to take a look?
Oh...
Hi there!
Wow,
they're great!
This is cute!
Ma'am, you have an eye for quality.
That's a curio known as the Cure Lavies.
Cure Lavies?
It looks like what Makopi was wearing...
Huh?
You seem to like it.
You can have it if you want.
What? But I couldn't!
My grandfather always told me that you never get something for nothing!
The one who prices an item can change it if he wants.
Mana!
Rikka!
Geez, where have you been?
If we don't hurry, we'll miss our chance to see the viewing platform!
You're right.
Anyway, thank you very much!
Enjoy it, my sweet heart.
Talk about a line!
And it's all because you wandered off on your own.
Sorry about that...
Man, how nice of 'em to line up.
It's gonna take hours to reach the viewing platform.
If we cut in line, we can cut that time to zero!
Nikaido! Over here!
Wanna line up?
That's right, the longer you wait with everyone,
the greater the impact it'll have!
We have arrived, Madam.
Good day.
Now then, allow me to show you to the viewing platform on the top floor.
Huh? Madam!
Madam! What are you doing there?
Waiting in line.
People who want to visit the viewing platform must do this, correct?
There is no need for you, the owner of this tower, to wait in line!
The longer you wait, the greater the impact it will have.
I feel Mana would say the same thing.
M-Mana?
A dear friend of mine.
We're almost there.
It's that lady!
Michiko!
Have fun!
I will!
How long do I have to wait?
If only I could ditch the line and cut in front...
But I guess I can't do that.
Sure you can.
Wh-Who's there?!
Don't hold back.
Release the darkness in your heart.
What happened?
Somebody passed out!
Are you all right?
Not bad!
This should give birth to an excellent Selfish!
Run wild!
Release the darkness in your heart!
Selfish!
Line!
Cutting!
What the crab is that?
This is absurd!
Cutting!
Run even wilder!
That's...
A Selfish!
We're too late!
My, what a large crab.
Sebastian, perhaps we could raise him at home?
We could not. Now, this way.
Thank you all for waiting!
Selfyselfy Selfish!
Get outtaouttaoutta the way!
It's headed for the viewing platform?
Michiko...
Sharu!
Cutting!
Michiko...
Michiko's in danger!
Cutting!
All guests, please take turns enjoying the scenery in an orderly fashion.
To heck with bein' orderly!
I'll save you...
Cutting!
This view is all mine!
Michiko!
Mommy!
Cutting!
Lady...
Are you all right?
Michiko!
Hurry!
Take Michiko and run away!
What about you?
I'll be just fine!
Now, get going!
Let's go!
Thank you so much.
I'm beat.
I can't move a muscle.
But...
this really is a great view!
Right?
This view is all mine!
What was that for?
This view doesn't belong to one person!
It's for everyone!
It's too selfish to say you want it all for yourself!
She's scolding that Selfish!
I can't believe it!
She's...
Now, you may be a crab,
but even crabs are better off making friends with people!
Sharuru!
You over there!
Who?
Down here!
I'm a fairy from the Trump Kingdom, Sharuru!
Oh, hello. I'm Aida Mana.
She accepted that quickly...
This girl is definitely no ordinary human!
I'm used to it.
Use my power!
You can fight the Selfish with it!
By Selfish, do you mean this crab?
Yes, now transform!
Got it.
Let's give this a shot.
Transform!
... Huh?
Trans... form!
Who d'ya think you are!?
Why?!
Selfish!
Dabyi!
Glitter!
Holy Sword!
Love.
Looooove!
It's gone.
I purified it.
Where am...
I was waiting here in line, and then...
what happened?
Is everyone safe?
Teacher, the president still hasn't returned!
Is that true?
Mana...
Um, thank you for saving me.
I'm Aida Mana.
And you are?
What was that crab?
Why was it running amok?
So there you are, Cure Sword!
How dare you defeat my Selfish!
I'll get you for this!
Cure... Sword...
Look out!
Selfish.
Another one?
Your work is as sloppy as ever, Ira.
Marmo!
But I was able to smoke out the final Precure thanks to you, so good job.
Selfish.
You even hid your Selfish until you saw mine get beaten, too!
You selfish jerk!
Tell me, where is the princess?
Talk!
I have nothing to tell you!
Playing the faithful patriot to a ruined kingdom?
You're quite the fool, I see.
Then Selfish,
end this now!
Selfish!
Stop that!
Let her go!
Who the crab're you?
What?
Fool.
Yoink.
Normal humans should stay out.
What do I do?
It's my fault she's there...
Mana...
Please...
give me courage and strength!
I beg you!
The Cure Lavies!
Mana, set that light in me and shout along!
Precure Love Link!
Right!
Sharuru!
Precure Love Link!
L-O-V-E!
What is this light?
Brimming with love,
Cure Heart!
Cure... Heart?
Oh poor crab who knows no love,
I, Cure Heart,
will make your heart race!
It seems she's awakened.
My sweet heart.
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I have faith in our endless future and it will be mine
P-P-P-Precure P-P-P-Precure
P-P-P-Precure Let's enjoy it! Yeah! Yeah!
What do I wish for, with my tiny hands?
Hey, where are you? What are you looking at? What do you feel?
A few ten thousand light years aren't far in the future
It's not even a unit of time, I know that
Our sparkling wishes will be faster than light
Love is what connects the world
I'm not making that up, it connects us all
What are dreams like beyond the sky?
I'll put the love I feel into my song
P-P-P-Precure We'll meet with a smile
Mana, are you doing something behind my back?
I'm sorry, Rikka!
I have to keep the fact that I can transform into a Precure a secret!
Precure? Transform?
Mana, what are you talking about?
Ah, I said it out loud myself!
And the Precure are supposed to be a secret!
Dokidoki! Precure:
Dundundun!
Cure Heart's Secret Identity is Exposed!
That knot in your heart won't come undone!
Watch Us Again!