Starlight.
It's the story of goddesses drawn by the glow of the heavens.
We can fight and argue and disagree,
but there are ties that bind us together...
Yet we may just as easily be pulled apart, never to meet again.
It is a sad story.
The tale of those eight women captivates us.
The song of those eight women draws us in and compels us.
Let's go.
To that stage.
To that shining star, together!
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Karen-chan, get up! It's time!
You can't be late today, right?
Day Duty
Karen-chan, come on!
Okay.
Jeez!
You asked me to get you up, so you need to get up!
Okay.
It's not like I can be on wake-up duty forever, you know!
Yeah. Sorry.
Okay, let's go!
Mahiru-chan, stop!
What?!
Karen-chan!
I can't believe you came back for that...
Good morning, Karen-chan.
Yup. Good morning!
Nice! First!
Seisho Music Academy 99th cohort,
Student No. 1, Aijo Karen!
Student No. 1 — Aijo Karen
Ready to begin!
Stage center, position zero.
Mahiru-chan!
Huh?
C'mon, let's stretch.
Yup!
Student No. 17 —Tsuyuzaki Mahiru
Student No. 17, Tsuyuzaki Mahiru.
Ready to begin!
Ow...
Try to focus on your thighs and butt.
This is impossible!
Student No. 25 — Hoshimi Junna
Oh. It's open.
Of course! After all, I'm on day duty today!
Aijo-san, didn't you sleep in and get here late last time you were on day duty?
To think the day would come when Karen-chan
Student No. 11 — Saijo Claudine
could actually get up on time!
That's a big non, non!
Aijo Karen, Girl of the Stage, is evolving day by day!
I'm at my newest right now!
I'm gonna give it more than ever!
Karen-chan, I swear...
You ended up having to wake her up, right?
You're the only one who gets it, Banana-chan!
Student No. 15 — Daiba Nana
It's easy enough to get. If you're me, that is.
Come on, wake up already!
Kaoruko!
How boorish to disturb a young maiden's slumber...
Cut it out with that half-asleep talk!
Student No. 22 — Hanayagi Kaoruko
Even Karen is awake!
Student No. 2 — Isurugi Futaba
My, what a handful.
I'd say you're the one with the handful, Futaba-chan.
Having such a sleepyhead for a roommate...
You're one to talk.
Futaba! Could you not just let me go like that?!
C'mon, cut that out!
What if I had really gotten hurt?!
Oh, it's squishy. Squish, squish.
Good morning.
Student No. 18, Tendo Maya.
Ready to begin.
Student No. 18 — Tendo Maya
Student No. 11, Saijo Claudine.
Ready to begin.
Student No. 25, Hoshimi Junna. Ready to begin.
Student No. 22, Hanayagi Kaoruko. Ready to begin.
Student No. 2, Isurugi Futaba. Ready to begin!
I'm gonna give it my all today!
Year 2 Class A Teacher
Sakuragi Urara
Okay, is this everyone?
Yes!
The 28 students of Class 2-A of the Actor Training Department.
No absences! Everyone, greet our teacher.
Good morning!
May 14 Day Duty
Aijo Karen
Good morning.
This is Seisho Music Academy.
It's a respected girls' school with a 100-year history.
It was founded to foster the next generation of theatrical talent!
a
Actor Training Department
Group A in the Actor Training Department works daily to improve their singing,
acting, dance, traditional dance,
as well as elocution.
Stage Production Department
Group B in the Stage Production Department studies presentation, scripts, costumes, and props.
They work hard to learn the technical aspects of putting on a play!
We in the academy's 99th cohort are in love with the theater,
so it's the life we've chosen to pursue.
Yes, we're girls of the stage!
We all work together to bring the theater to life,
but we're all rivals aiming to become the next star!
Aah! Banana-chan, your lunch looks delicious!
I've got plenty of it, so...
Man, those lessons wore me out!
Karen-chan, we haven't even
started afternoon classes yet.
What's our first class again?
Um... English!
English, huh? I think I'll fall asleep.
Hoshimi-san!
Here.
The Seisho Festival!
We're about to start prepping for it.
But that's not till next year.
You can never have enough time.
Audition notice for all members of the 99th class.
A production of Starlight for the 100th Seisho Festival.
There's a lot that has to be done.
Yeah, but we're still doing Starlight, right?
I already know all the lines.
What's more important is that we do it better than last year!
Oh, yeah.
Still, that sure was fun. Doing Starlight as first-years...
Yeah!
With Group B backing us up,
Group A got to sing and perform...
The 99th cohort did a production
that was all our own.
It was a single, unforgettable moment that will last forever.
But it was completely amateurish.
Next year, our performance has to be more polished.
That's why, for our three years here,
we're doing Starlight.
It's the only show we'll put on.
Yeah...
She's right. We get to do Starlight over again!
Talk about bliss!
You sure do like that story, don't you, Karen-chan?
I mean, it's beautiful but it's sad and passionate and...
What's not to like?!
W-Well, I do like it.
Right? I sure hope we get named roles again!
M-Me too. Maybe this time we...
I mean, you and I, we could even be the fated couple!
Nah, I bet Tendo-san and Claudie-chan
will be the leads again.
Huh? Oh, yeah...
I mean, those two are in a whole different league from us!
Their singing, their dancing,
their sparkling stage presence.
There's no way we can compete with 'em.
We haven't even had auditions yet.
Don't assume the leads have been decided.
Uh... Okay.
J-Junna-chan!
Did I make her angry or something?
When she gets worked up, she's all over the place.
Let's put on the best show we can, okay?
Like when we did Starlight before.
All right!
Aijo Karen, Girl of the Stage,
is getting better day by day!
For our next Starlight, I'm gonna show
you even more wow factor!
Let's do our best.
You okay, Karen-chan?
I just can't stop thinking about sandwiches.
It's way too early for you to be throwing in the towel.
Karen-chan! That's the wrong textbook!
Tokyo Tower?!
Wow...
Huh? But, why the great view?
Oh, yeah. This is where I bought my barrette.
But will it ever come true?
Our promise...
K-Karen-chan!
Are you okay, Karen-chan?
She's fine. The girl's a rock!
You're so heartless, Banana-chan!
Hey, you all right, Karen?
Sure, no problem. Thanks!
Day
Uh, so we have a transfer student who'll be joining us here in the Actor Training Department.
I know it's unexpected but please give her a warm welcome, everyone.
That sure was a weird dream...
I'm Kagura Hikari.
Huh?
Hikari-chan?
Student No. 29 (Transfer)
Kagura Hikari
Hikari-chan?
Aijo.
Sit down.
I'm sorry!
Kagura-san is a transfer student from
the Royal Drama Academy of England.
What?!
It's been about twelve years since she's been back to Japan, so help her out with everything, okay?
Yes, ma'am!
Let's see, today for day duty we have...
Me! Right here!
I'll help Hikari-chan with everything!
What? Do you know her?
Aijo...
I'm sorry!
Oh, it's that girl...
When homeroom is over,
please show her around the dormitory.
And there's no need to stand up.
Yes, ma'am!
Tsuyuzaki, go with them.
I worry about her doing that alone.
You're really, truly Hikari-chan, right?!
It's been a super long time! How many years now?
Twelve years.
What?! That long?
You left for England when we were five,
and you're back so suddenly.
I was so surprised!
But this is amazing.
Isn't the Royal Drama Academy
the hardest institute in the world to get into?
Huh? For real?
You don't know about it? It's famous!
You sure are amazing, Hikari-chan!
Not especially...
But you haven't changed it at all!
You wore it the whole time!
You know, the thing we promised on.
That's right.
Yay! We're here!
Karen-chan, this is our room, you know.
Yep! From now on, there'll be three people in our room.
Mahiru-chan?
Wait, Karen-chan! This is all out of wack!
But she'd be lonely by herself, right?
I don't want three people in here!
I mean... it's impossible!
Huh?
Hikari-chan?
It would be an inconvenience, right?
That isn't true, but...
Hikari-chan!
Hikari-cha—
Sorry. I'm going to get ready now.
Hikari-chan...
Welcome back.
From here on out, let's do our best.
Let's become stars together.
We promised.
Karen...
Wow, Hikari-chan was so good!
Her jump was amazing!
Oh man, she was like a grasshopper!
Her grand fouetté was really pretty, too.
Your old friend is pretty good, Karen!
Isn't she?
But she seems to be acting awfully cold towards you...
That just means she's cool and mysterious!
What? What are you saying?!
Kagura Hikari...
Huh? So they're performing it again?
It says that the villain from last time
will be the lead this time.
Huh?
What?
Karen-chan?
Banana, do you know where Hikari-chan is?
I see, thanks!
Kagura Hikari, huh?
It's like a rival has appeared, right?
But, that girl...
I can't see her heart.
Huh?
Hikari-chan? Hikari-chan?
Hikari-chan?
Oh, look at this.
Excuse me! I forgot something in there!
Hikari-chan?
An elevator?
We have something like this?
Huh?
Seisho Music Academy
Underground Theater
Well then, we will now begin the first day of auditions
for this Revue of Passion.
Underground Theater Center Stage
Position Zero
Let us compete in song and dance,
and aim to become the Top Star.
The rage which at first shone upon the dark
yami o sakitomotta gekikou ga
Now ignites the maidens' yearning hearts
shoujotachi no katsubou o terasu
Hoshimi-san?!
Hikari-chan, too?!
Is this Starlight?!
But, what are they doing?
Stop, Hoshimi-san!
I understand.
A giraffe?!
The Revue has already begun.
This is the Revue?
That fire as it rises up to heaven
ten made todoku honoo
Yes, song and dance interwoven on the mesmerizing stage.
Consumes me within its flames
watashi o yakitsukusu no
The one who presents us
with the most sparkling revue
The stars that shone upon the gate
tobira ni hikareta hoshi ga
Until the World is Turned to Ash
shall find open to her the path to the Top Star.
Fall burning to the Earth
ochitekuru toki
A Revue of Passion
I have a dream that I hold so dear
yuzurenai yume ga aru
Who will obtain that heavenly tiara
Above lies the sky I must keep near
mamoritai sora ga aru
and become the Top Star? I wonder...
The arrows which shoot like stars will chase them down
ryuusei o katadotta ya ga oikaketeiku wa
What are you talking about?!
I understand.
But their desperation is palpable, isn't it?
That's why they've become Girls of the Stage.
A slowly fading memory
tooku chiisaku naru
Huh?
Will someday be left behind
itsuka kiete shimau omoide
The normal happiness and pleasures of a young girl...
They burn all of it to ash so that they might reach for that distant luster!
A fierce headwind blows against our sacred and secret vow
mukaikaze ni hidoku aorare hisoka ni tateta chikai
That is a Girl of the Stage!
Do you hold that determination within you?
I won’t let it block our path
kitto jama sasenai
Until the whole world is turned to ash
kono sekai o hai ni suru made
That cloak!
If it falls, the Revue is over.
My passion will burn so hot that nothing will compare
dare yori atsuku moetsuzukeru watashi no jounetsu wa
Hikari-chan!
You can't stop them.
Those who cannot wake up on their own in the morning.
Those who are content standing on the sidelines.
Those people will never be called upon.
Well then, I must ask you to leave.
Huh?
Giraffe! Outta my way!
I made a promise with Hikari-chan!
I—No, we...
We absolutely will become stars, together!
I AM REBORN
On the stage that overflows with stardust,
a magnificent flower of love shall bloom!
I adorn myself, my person remade!
I will dive into the sparkling arena!
Student of the 99th cohort...
Aijo Karen!
You will all gaze upon my ✨Starlight✨!
Stay out of this!
I believe I also have a dream that I must hold dear
yuzurenai yume nara watashi ni mo kitto aru shinjiteru
No...
No, Karen!
Deep in this violently beating heart of mine
takanaru kono mune no oku fukaku
Yet bold as anything, a quiet passion shines
tomotta no shizuka ni jounetsu ga ima
Position Zero!
The first day of auditions is over!
Hikari-chan!
Stupid...
Dorkaren!
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Shoujo
Kageki
Revue Starlight
Who shall be the one to grasp hold of that star?
To stand at the peak of that tower?
A quietly kindled flame now blazes and consumes my heart
Whatever fate might bring
We dance on this stage of our own will
to
bi
ta
te
And we take flight!
I'm certain of what I saw on that day
The sparkle of those scattering stars
Shine on me until my fingers touch yours
From across a promise faded by time
The true story begins before the curtain rises
And it unfolds before our very eyes
It's here, in the place where I was reborn
That I found you once more
Next time: The Stage of Fate
Shoujo Kageki Revue Starlight!
I understand.