Today is
Self-study
It's the second day of Fumizuki Academy's school trip and Class A is—
Hi! Question: Being single or a couple, which one is more...
FABULOUS?
My future slowly cycles
though a rainbow of colors
Can I talk about it as much as I want?
Will you ignore me?
Oh, the wide world fills my heart with new feelings
I love you today, too
I really love you!
I'm an idiot... More idiotic than there are stars in the sky
I had a dream of walking with you
but I wasn't being honest with myself
I'm sorry! After all...
I didn't realize I was in love with you
Answer me. What do you, me and something unknown add up to?
An infinite jump!
Classes A and F are in the midst of their study camp.
Episode 6
Me, peeping, and friendship amongst men!
I'm so glad we're studying together.
Shouko, that's not your seat!
I wonder why we had to come all the way out here just for self-study.
Don't you feel like studying in class?
Of course I don't.
It's not like we'd understand a word of Class A's lessons.
Hah! That may be so for you, Yuuji,
but I don't see any difference between the lessons for Class A and Class F.
My, that's impressive.
I don't understand either of them.
Still impressive, but for a different reason.
The purpose of this school trip is to motivate us to study more.
By making us study together, the teachers hope that we'll look up to Class A
Self-study
and follow their example.
Boring
Class
I don't know what Class A thinks of us, but we sure aren't looking up to them.
Boring
Oh, Class Rep! There you are!
Maybe I should join you.
Kudou Aiko!
Hello! I heard you guys tried to peep on the girls' bath yesterday.
If you wanted to see that badly, you could've asked.
Shall we start with my underwear? Here you go.
No looking.
Huh? What's wrong, Voyeur?
You say you love porn, but you seem unfazed by this.
Look how excited I got.
Don't let her fool you, Akihisa. She's wearing gym shorts underneath her skirt.
You're so mean, Kudou! You took advantage of my innocence!
I'm sorry, Yoshii! Let me make it up to you.
What's that?
A miniature tape recorder.
Huh? What's wrong, Voyeur?
This is gonna be hilarious.
Kudou! I love you.
I'm excited.
That was gut-wrenchingly hilarious.
It was, wasn't it?
Mizuki, give me a hand with something.
Sure, let's go.
Akihisa, make haste before they return with their torture devices.
But Hideyoshi, I haven't done anything wrong!
Hey, Akihisa.
What is it, Yuuji?
I wonder if Kudou is the girl we're looking for.
That thing was pretty suspicious.
Akihisa, confirm this somehow.
All right!
Hey, Kudou.
What is it, Yoshii?
Are you—
I can't just ask her if she's the culprit. There's no way she'd answer honestly.
What's wrong?
Umm... I... was wondering if you would...
I would what?
What should I say?
The burns are the identifying feature, right?
Um... Uh...
I'd really appreciate it if you'd show me your behind.
Good going, Akihisa.
Well done, Akihisa.
Thou art most brave, Akihisa.
I'd really appreciate it if you'd show me your behind.
How embarrassing.
He just outright said it.
I beg you, Kudou! Please erase that!
I beg you, Kudou! Show me your behind.
Did I hear something just now?
I wonder.
It sounded like a moron digging his own grave.
Oh, my! I think he really needs to be punished most severely.
You're misunderstanding! I just want her to—
erase it so that no one misunderstands that.
show me her behind.
That's all!
Don't do that, Kudou!
Kudou Aiko, enough of your games!
Voyeur!
I'll help you! Leave it to me!
You will? Great!
Listen, you two. That was just a misunderstanding! I wanted her to—
erase it so that no one misunderstands that.
show me her behind.
I really didn't say that!
But I prefer Yuuji's.
Voyeur!
Kudou Aiko, you are nothing before me!
I'm impressed! You're good at this, Voyeur!
Yoshii, I won't let you have him.
I don't even want him!
Aki, do you really like Sakamoto's rear that much? Don't you like mine at all?
I always had a feeling, but it's still a big shock.
You're making a huge mistake! I don't have such perverted hobbies—
Behind
Yuuji
Don't make fun of pure, homosexual romance!
Miharu, what are you doing here?
Sissy, I missed you so much!
I ditched Class D's study session just to meet you!
Sugawa Barrier!
Yuck! You're disgusting, unforgivably disgusting!
How mean, Sissy! Look at how much I love you!
Hey! Stop it! I'm straight as a board!
Guys! We're studying. Can you please be quiet?
S-Sorry, Kubo.
Still, I cannot allow anyone make light of romance between the same sex.
It is merely a matter of individualistic tastes, varying slightly from social norms.
I can only hope that, one day, we rise above the society that scorns us.
Exactly! Gender doesn't matter at all!
I said I'm not a lesbian!
"Gender doesn't matter," huh?
I feel a chill all of a sudden.
So gender doesn't matter at all to you?
Don't look at me and Yuuji like that!
I keep telling you it's a misunderstanding!
It's just that I—
love Hideyoshi!
That's all!
Wait a second!
Akihisa, I do not know how I should answer thee.
Don't get me wrong!
I just—
love Hideyoshi's behind.
This is just making it worse!
I want Yuuji and I to see each other's behinds.
Homosexual
Kubo
Kubo! Show me your behind!
Kubo! I love you!
Kubo! Show me your behind. Kubo! I love you!
Goodness, Yoshii! I didn't know we were so close.
I don't think that's the problem here.
Show me your behind.
I think Kudou's the girl who's threatening us.
Well, from the way she handled her tape recorder, that seems highly likely.
Should we make our move and capture her?
We better not. We only have one chance.
If we mess it up, the real culprit might become more careful about leaving any more clues.
Yes, she will. The threats could also escalate.
The situation would only get worse.
We can't make any big moves unless we're absolutely sure of who it is.
We should focus on confirming the presence of the burns.
We'll take the risk of making her mad and flip her skirt.
But she wears gym shorts!
That she does!
We have no way of confirming the burns other than peeping on the girls' bath.
Aye. 'Tis the only way.
But how do we do it? We need some sort of plan to get past the teachers.
'Tis hard to make a plan, for there is but a single path to our goal.
Boys' bath
Girls' bath
Boiler
room
Corridor to the boys' bath
Corridor to the girls' bath
Changing room
Stairs
Japanese
Math
Civics
Science
PE
Japanese
Math
Civics
Science
PE
What can we do but break forth en masse?
We do have a way.
The only thing we can do is charge forward, so we'll just have to plan accordingly.
You want to get more people to help us?
Exactly.
But that would take forev—
What did you want to talk to us about?
Sugawa! Guys!
Thank you for joining us, my fellow classmates.
I have a proposal for you.
A proposal?
What do you want, man? I'm pooped!
I wanna go to bed!
Would you be interested... in peeping on the girls' bath?
Let's hear it.
The four of us tried to peep on the girls last night,
but we were ambushed by an army of teachers and defeated.
I see. And?
We'll attack again tonight.
That's why I want you guys to help get rid of the teachers.
Our reward... will be a glimpse of paradise!
Paradise
Hell yeah!
Voyeur, how much time do we have?
It's 2010 hours.
Minutes           Seconds
BATHING
GIRLS
STARTED
SINCE
It's been 10 minutes since the girls of Class A started bathing.
The timing's just right.
We'll split up into four groups.
Group A will come with me.
Group B with Akihisa.
Group C with Hideyoshi.
Group D with Voyeur.
Roger!
Listen up! We have but one objective! Paradise!
We'll defeat everything that stands in our way! We won't stop for anything!
We fear neither gods nor demons!
Seek and destroy!
Tonight is when you'll decide your fate!
8:14 PM    Corridor to the girls' bath
I scolded them a lot yesterday. They wouldn't try that again.
The perverts are coming in formation!
Chemistry
Corridor to
the girls' bath
Summoned being! Summon!
Pervert
None shall pass!
Summon!
Summon! Summon! Summon!
Hideyoshi's battalion is in battle with Mr. Fuse!
We'll charge while Hideyoshi has him charmed!
Don't fall behind!
Surround him!
Good job! Go!
Wait up, Yoshii!
Keep moving!
Hold it right there, you filthy pigs!
Boys aren't allowed here. Shut up and go back to your pigsty!
Yoshii, we can't beat them in numbers or marks!
I beg of you, Shimizu. Stand aside.
You just want to stare at Sissy's deliciously flat chest, don't you? Filth!
You're wrong! I'm not doing this to see Minami's ironing board!
You lie! You pigs just want to feast your eyes on Sissy's washboard. I'll punish you!
Believe me. I have no interest in Minami's lack of man-bait.
I have more pressing matters than her flat horizon— My elbow! She's twisting my elbow-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Flat
chest
How many times are you gonna say it, huh?
He really needs to be punished.
Hey there, Yoshii. Just what are those pressing matters of yours?
Were you going to peep on me in the bath? I'd like that.
No looking.
I won't forgive cheating.
Kirishima is here too?! We didn't plan for this!
Well then, Yoshii. Is this what you were after?
There's still a camera hidden in the changing room.
It's not mine. I just happened to notice it.
Kudou?
All right, then. Shall we begin, Voyeur?
Fight!
Summon!
Thanks, Voyeur!
I'll take care of this!
You kids need to be taught a lesson!
So you came after all, you bunch of fools!
I-Ironman!
We'll have to defeat him to move on!
There's no way we can do that!
I'm gonna give you quite the lesson today. Get ready, Yoshii!
So this is how it ends.
Don't give up, Yoshii!
Sugawa!
Let go, Sugawa!
I can't let you be defeated here!
Only your summon has the power to defeat Ironman.
That's why... I beg of you...
Run!
You must live on!
Don't get in the way of my lesson.
Sugawa! Sugawa!
Summon! Summon! Summon!
Cover Yoshii's retreat!
We'll make you a way out! Run, and don't look back!
Guys!
You're our only hope, Yoshii! We'll protect you with our lives!
Yoshii!
I understand. I'll leave him to you!
I'll survive and complete our objective!
Forgive me... guys! Forgive me!
I promise... I promise I'll find a way to paradise!
Uh, Yoshii Akihisa of Class F, please come for remedial classes immediately.
Well, we should have expected that.
Is it morning already? I hardly got any sleep. Ironman's lessons were so long.
Why did I wake up now?!
Dammit.
What the fuck am I doing?!
What's this? Was Yuuji sleeping in your futon too?
Too?
He tosses around a lot in his sleep. Last night, he rolled over into mine.
I won't forgive you! How dare you mess with my pure feelings?
By the way, Kudou said something strange to me yesterday.
What did she say?
She said there's another hidden camera in the changing room.
What the?
I guess she really is the culprit.
Nay, we cannot be so certain.
Why wouldst the culprit reveal her own crimes?
We'll have to confirm it ourselves.
But it'd be a big help if that information is true.
How so?
If we can get that camera, we can see the girls by ourselves.
We might spot the culprit herself.
I see!
I'm confident that I can find the camera in 5 seconds.
But doth that camera really exist?
The girls said they found a camera the day before, didn't they?
I don't think a skilled spy would have her devices discovered so easily by amateurs.
It was part of her plan.
Right. The camera they found was a decoy to make us look like the peeping toms.
The camera Kudou found in the changing room is the real one.
Then we should go get that camera right now, shouldn't we?
We can't. The room is locked when it's not in use.
But we can't try charging through again—
Akihisa, why do you think our strategy failed yesterday?
Corridor to the Boys' Bath
Corridor to
the Girls' Bath
Stairs
Why?
I guess it's because half the girls stayed outside to stop us.
Then all we need to do is increase our forces even more.
We'll get the other classes to join us.
The other classes?
But increasing our forces isn't the only reason I'm suggesting this.
Self-protection
It's also to protect us.
Protect?
Even if we succeed in peeping on the girls, we might not find the girl who's threatening us.
The
real
culprit
In that case, we're gonna get caught and be punished.
I get it! Since there'll be so many of us, they won't know who was really peeping.
Culprit
Ringleader
But we already have a record.
Fumizuki Academy is well known for its highly successful exam preparation courses.
They will either have to punish everyone or cover the whole thing up.
Punish
Cover up
That's why you want us to attack with so many people that they can't punish us all.
You're awesome, Yuuji! No one can think of dirtier schemes than you can!
I'd prefer you called me "ingenious."
Let's start recruiting while we still have time.
We'll have to talk to Kubo about Class A.
Today is
Self-study
Akihisa, go talk to him.
Aye, he's the best man for the job.
Please do it.
Sure, but why me?
Use this to protect yourself if things get out of hand.
Hey, Kubo. Do you have a moment?
Yes, of course.
Come. Have a seat.
It's okay. I'll sit here.
If you say so. I don't mind.
I have a request. Could you—
Of course I will!
So fast!
I apologize. I lost my composure for a second.
Please, what did you want?
Oh, yeah. Could you get your class to help peep on the girls—
Of course I won't!
So fast! Why not?
I don't believe my ears, Yoshii.
Society has sacred rules for one's conduct in public.
If you dare break those rules, you will be shunned from society.
Is that what you want?
The very thought of peeping on women during their bathing rituals is impure!
Sorry, I couldn't do it.
That sucks, but at least you're okay.
I didn't feel like I was in any danger, though.
If we can't get Class A to help us, then I guess we'll have to make do with the other classes.
You boys are planning something bad again, aren't you?
N-Not really. Not at all.
I don't really have the willpower to continue asking you to stay out of trouble.
To think you were trying to peep on us!
I know I can't compare to the other girls in the bath, since I can't even have breast pads on.
Plus, you'd be watching from far away.
I didn't even go on a diet because I never expected you'd peep on me!
You're so mean, Akihisa!
What I really want to see is—
Yuuji's behind.
That's all! No, wait!
Shhhhhhhh
School trip
Night time
Day 3
Decisive battle
And thus, a decisive moment has come once more—
So, in the end, only Classes D and E want to help us.
Class B's rep, Nemoto Kyouji, couldn't make up his mind.
Class C's rep is Koyama Yuuka, and there's no way the boys would oppose her.
But we still have more men than yesterday.
Only half of the girls will be patrolling on defense.
If we can handle the teachers, we should be victorious.
Each class has been briefed on the details of the operation.
Good. Let's get ready!
Bad news! They got us! They ambushed us in the dining hall.
What?!
The 4
boys' room
Dining
hall
Stairs
All our forces on every floor have scattered!
They made the first move!
They knew our strategy all along!
It must've been Shouko!
She would never forgive you for peeping on the girls, after all.
We have no time to waste!
Reorganize our troops into a new formation.
We're going in.
You can't go through here!
Damn, the girls are here too!
I don't care! Just run for it!
We'll attack at once! Follow me!
Yuuji, there are too many enemies in front of us!
The places with fewer girls are full of traps! This is our counter-strategy!
Yuuji, I've been waiting for you.
Shouko!
You had a counter-counter-strategy!
I already told you that I won't forgive cheating,
but it seems I must beat it into you.
You boys are just begging to be given extra classes.
Year Two's Head Teacher! Ms. Takahashi!
Yuuji! Let's retreat—
Sorry, I can't let you do that.
Kudou! Mr. Ooshima!
You really don't learn, do you?
If you really wanted to peep on us, why didn't you just talk to us about it?
I'm not going to give up! I'll fight you if I must.
Summon!
Go!
He's fast!
Ouch!
Points:
How?
Whip
Head Teacher
Seven thousand points?!
'Tis out of our league!
What do we do?
It's obvious!
We'll do what we can! The best we can!
Yuuji!
Listen up! We don't have any more strategies!
All of you can make your own decisions!
Believe in yourself! I know you can do it!
Think with your heart, decide with your mind, and choose what seems right to you!
I'll trust you to use your best judgment!
Got it?! Let's go!
I'm sorry!
Y-You boys aren't apologizing like the others.
Does your pride as their commander prevent you?
No, that's not it. We've realized something.
Yes. It's just like Yuuji said.
We've realized...
that we don't need to apologize.
Do you really think someone's coming to save you?
Hah! You don't understand a thing!
That's not what we meant... Not at all.
The two had finally understood...
that they won't be forgiven, even if they groveled on their knees like dogs.
Thus ended the third day of the school trip.
The boys still haven't found the girl who was threatening them.
In the end, will Akihisa and Yuuji ever break free of their fate—
Flickering, sparkling
the lightbulb goes pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
That's the root of the problem
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go
I want to fall in love.
There'll be no boundaries to my dreams.
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway.
Flashing, sparkling,
that's the correct answer
Question 6:
Write a summary
of your second day
at the training
camp.
Himeji Mizuki's entry:
Today, I studied those parts of Physics that
I'm not very good with. Since I was with the
students of Class A, I was able to study properly
and spend my time meaningfully.
Teacher's comment:
I'm glad studying with Class A had such a positive effect on you. It'd be good if you made some friends there, since you'll probably join them after the next placement exam.
Tsuchiya Kouta's entry:
TL;DR. By then it was
night, so I went to sleep.
Teacher's comment
Please don't use "TL;DR"
in homework.
Yoshii Akihisa's entry:
...
Teacher's comment
Your lack of words
surprised me so much
that I have nothing to say either.
Question 7
Answer the following
question.
How do you physically
and mentally harm
someone to make them agree
with you?
Kirishima Shouko's answer:
Various means of torture, such as
whipping, burning, bondage,
crucifixion, hanging, etc.
Teacher's comment
Correct. Well done, Kirishima.
Nowadays, torture is prohibited because
of international laws. I think you already
know this, but please lead a hale and
hearty school life, respect the rights of
others around you, and be sure not to
engage in any such criminal activities.
Sakamoto Yuuji's answer:
I'm sorry, Shouko!
Teacher's comment
I don't even want to know.
Question 7.
How do you physically and mentally harm your opponent to make them agree with you?
I'm sorry, Shouko!
I don't even want to know.
Next time: Me, peeping, and the distant Shangri-La.
Next time: Me, peeping, and
the distant
Shangri-La!
This will be on the test.