doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
It's cold out.
I'm sleepy.
Can I really keep these?
It's probably some mistake.
Good morning, Mukae-san!
Morning!
Good morning, Kaoru-san.
Cold today, isn't it?
Good morning.
Morning, Ricchan!
Morning!
That's right.
Can't let myself get my hopes up.
I've already been rejected once.
Do you have the usual, ma'am?
There you are, the usual.
Thank you!
You're looking beautiful as always, ma'am!
Oh, it's you.
What's with the long face?
Should I guess?
You're in shock over the news that Yurika-senpai eloped?
It's all over the school!
Did you tell him about it?!
Oh, Kawabuchi-kun?
Yeah, this morning.
Hey, I don't think he's in the classroom!
I didn't expect to hear anything like this.
How must he feel about it?
Ah, that's the one that won the Prefectural Governor's Award.
We'd better take it down quick.
You take that side.
Um, what are you doing?
There's no way the school will display a painting
by a student who's involved in a scandal.
We were told to remove it.
And what's going to happen to it after you take it down?
You got me.
Wait!
This painting is important!
Please!
What's she to you anyway?
Had eyes for her, did ya?
Wha...
Let it go, Bon.
Sorry.
You can take it away.
Sen...
Hey, Sen!
Why?!
Don't you care what happens to that painting?!
Hey!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
What are you laughing at?!
Your stupidity must be contagious.
What?
Seriously, how stupid are you gonna be for somebody else's sake?
It's ridiculous.
Wait. What about the painting?
Oh, I already said my goodbye to it back there.
I feel much better now.
Sen...
Have you gotten a present from someone recently?
Like something that was knitted.
Yeah, I did.
I knitted Sentaro a sweater and used the leftover yarn to make the mittens!
That's cruel. I knew it.
This! It's called Lily-yarn or something.
I got it from Sachiko yesterday.
Anything else?
Nope. This is it.
But what am I supposed to do with this string?
Huh?
Strike!
What the heck are you...? You!
Now you're gonna get it!
Bon, wait!
Bon!
U-Um, these are really warm.
Thank you.
Ow! Dammit! What are you doing?!
Hey, I'm over here!
Nope, over here!
Come to think of it, we'll be changing classes again soon.
I guess third years are split up according to their grades,
so you probably won't be in the same class as Kaoru-san.
Bon, you're goin' for college entrance exams, right?
Y-Yeah...
I intend to go to college too.
I'm thinking about becoming an elementary school teacher.
So Rikko's gonna be a teacher?
What about it?
Rikko used to say she wanted to have a bakery or cake shop.
What? When was this?
Come on, don't you remember?
You were a glutton.
That's why you wanted a shop!
I never said that!
Kaoru-san, where do you want to go to college?
Oh, I... haven't decided yet.
As for me, never mind about college.
I might not even make it to the third year.
I see.
Wait, what did you just say?!
Listen! The next make-up exam's the showdown.
Start with these basic problems.
I'll make you some flash cards in the meantime.
You handle that.
Hey!
I'm just not cut out for studying.
What are you going to do if you fail this?!
Oh, I'll just quit school an' get a job.
What are you saying?
Joking...
It ain't a joke.
When I think about my family, I can't afford to repeat a year.
No way!
No way, no way!
I definitely won't let you flunk this test!
I'm tired. I need a break!
Wait! You're in the middle of these questions!
I can't take anymore.
If you're going to rest, it'll have to wait 'til you're done with these problems!
I can't! My head's gonna explode!
Ni-Nii-chan...
Hey, Sen...
You look really happy when you're surrounded by children.
W-Where'd that come from?
I bet you're going to have a big family of your own
with lots of kids around you.
It'll be a warm.
Chikko wet herself!
Wet herself!?
Yay, Chikko!
The bath's over there.
My ma will dry your pants, so relax for awhile.
This is an unusual setup for a bath...
Sa-chan?
You're out of soap, right?
Here...
S-Sorry...
I-I don't understand.
Isn't this Sen's family's bath?
We share the bath with Sentaro's family...
Um... I wish I had given the mittens to you earlier.
It's almost spring, so you won't need to use them for long.
Oh, that doesn't matter.
Since you knitted the mittens, Ricchan,
I'd like to wear them all year 'round.
Cold!
Condensation?
Drops often fall in there.
Sentaro lets out a yelp once in a while himself.
Say, Ricchan, why did you give me those mittens?
W-Why?
Why me and not him?
I mean... if you've liked him all this time...
Bon! How about havin' dinner here!?
Your pants aren't dry yet anyway.
I'm going home now.
Thank you for the hospitality.
Wait, your hair's soakin' wet!
You'll catch cold!
Cut it out!
Sorry.
Well, see you tomorrow.
I didn't mean to say that to Ricchan.
But I couldn't get it out of my mind.
That Ricchan probably still has feelings for him.
Sen, how did the make-up exam go?
Oh, you passed?
Yeah.
Good for you.
It's thanks to Bon.
I gotta thank 'im proper.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen Prince Bon lately.
The day before yesterday,
he passed out in class with a fever,
so he's restin' up at home.
You didn't hear?
Nope, Ritsuko didn't say a thing.
"Someday My Prince Will Come", huh?
N-No! That was just...
Rikko. Would you come with me?
Look at it. Huge, ain't it—Bon's house.
Alright, go on.
Thank Bon for me, for helpin' me study.
But...
Wait, Sentaro!
Go on by yourself.
Why?! Let's go together!
Kaoru-san, one of your classmates has come to wish you well.
E-Excuse me.
Hi, Ricchan.
Um, is your fever down?
Yeah. Sorry to make you worry.
I see. Good.
Oh, that's right.
These are for you.
Eat them if you're up to it.
Oh, thank you.
Did you go out of the way to buy them?
Um... No. I didn't buy these. Uh...
Sentaro did.
Ricchan. He came here with you, didn't he?
I saw you two out the window.
He should've come in with you.
Kaoru-san?
Never mind. I understand.
What are you talking about?
It makes sense.
You two have been together since you were little.
There's no way I could be a match for him.
Unlike me, he's strong, built,
and so handsome, he even takes my breath away once in a while.
Ricchan, you're better off with him.
Stop it already!
I know what you're saying, so don't say any more.
I'm going home now.
Kaoru-san, don't you like me anymore?
Or is it...
you just don't have any confidence, so you're trying to keep your distance?
Kaoru-san, you told me to have confidence in myself.
Those words have saved me a number of times.
But if it looks like you don't have confidence,
I have a feeling I'll lose mine too.
Huh? What the heck am I doing?
What I've wished for all this time...
Oh, you're leaving already?
Excuse me!
Oh, boy!
I bet something happened between those two!
Ricchan!
Kaoru-san!
Don't come here!
I'll go to you.
Ricchan, let me tell you how I feel about you one more time.
I love you!
I love you, Ricchan!
I love you! I love you!
K-Kaoru-san!
I love you!
P-Please!
Your relatives can hear!
Let them!
I'm not muscular and maybe I'm not as manly as I should be,
but when it comes to my feelings for you, Ricchan, I'm second to none!
You might catch my cold.
I won't mind.
Kaoru-san!
Hey! You're burning up! And you're heavy!
Excuse me! Somebody!
I just saw something amazing.
Kaoru-san! Excuse me!
I haven't made any more progress with Ricchan, and it's already summer.
Even though I was that bold when I had a fever...
What's wrong with me when my temperature is normal?!
I want to touch...
Touch what?
When did you get here?!
Just now.
Did you hear anything?
Like what?
Nothing!
Both of you! Take a look at this!
East High Newspaper
"The Olympus Has Thrown Down the Gauntlet"?
What is this?
"The Olympus is going to win at this year's festival.
It seems there are still some old-fashioned jazz musicians around,
but this is the era of rock n' roll."
They were handing this out all over school.
What are you gonna do?
I mean, you can't take this sitting down, right?!
You two are gonna perform in the festival, aren't you?!
Huh?
I've been thinking.
Me too.
We start with "Moanin'" to fire up the people that saw us last year
an' fake 'em out thinking we're gonna do the same routine.
But then we move into some other songs that we want to play.
I was thinkin' the same thing!
Alright, let's choose our next song!
Starting today, we'd better practice every day!
'Course!
How about this one?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Nii-chan!
Hey.
Welcome home!
Look, I got surprising news!
Dad says he's comin' home!
This way, the whole family can live together!
Sacchan...
What are you doing here all by yourself?
I can't say that I'm actually scared...
Scared?
See, our dad, who was working far away,
is coming home tomorrow morning.
Bon, I'm one of those that ain't got a place in the house too.
Bon-nii-chan?
I'm home.
Hey, you're back late, Sachiko.
What's Bon doin' here with you?
I see. Unlike with Kota and the other little ones,
you remember how scary Dad was when he was drunk.
But don't worry, Sachiko!
Ma told me that Dad worked really hard an' quit drinkin' over there.
Really?
Yeah. You got nothin' to worry about, Sachiko.
Now how about comin' inside, an' we can prepare together?
Yeah!
Sen...
Oh, thanks for lookin' after her.
You're the one I'm worried about, Sen.
Dope! What are you lookin' so serious for?
What?! I am serious!
Bon. Don't worry so much.
I'm fine.
Nii-chan, look!
Comin'!
Sen!
Are you coming to practice tomorrow?
Yeah.
After all, playin' with you is the most fun I have.
Nii-chan, what are you writin'?
Hmm... Nah, that's no good.
It's not comin' out right.
Ah, well. Let's get to sleep.
Bon. I'm sorry for lying to you.
I was looking forward to the festival too.
I wanted to perform.
Be good to Rikko.
Take care.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and will remain as it was back then.