Will you wear a girl's uniform if I win?
Hahaha! That's hilarious, Himeji.
Good joke.
Will you wear a girl's uniform if I win?
How... did it come to this?
A single or a couple without love, which one is...
FABULOUS?
Love!
How far do we take our chat
of my colorfully rotating future?
Pretending not to notice!
How far do we take our chat of my colorfully rotating future?
My feelings for this giant world are evergrowing
I'm loving today, too
I'm really looooo-ving it!
looooo-ving it!
My idiocy is truly more vast than the ranks of the stars
Honestly still cannot accept that
I had a dream of walking with you
Still I'm sorry
Because I did not know about love, you know.
Answer: You and the riddling me are an infinite jump!
Episode 3
Me, secrets, and a man's dignity!
Let's go back one hour.
Yuuji, wanna play Bullshit?
Look how sure you are of yourself, Akihisa.
Didst thou not learn when thou lost a burger meal in the last game?
It was delicious.
I'll have my revenge today.
Interesting. Let's empty that wallet of yours.
Okay! We're playing by the usual rules, right?
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy's Class F's rules of Bullshit.
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
Fumizuki Academy
Class F
Rules of "Bullshit"
The bunny card is laid face down.
Ace!
The other players then consider whether it's true or false.
If you think it's a lie, you call it out.
Bullshit!
False
If it really was a lie, all the played cards are returned to the current player.
True
But if it wasn't a lie,
the cards go to the player who called out.
This goes on until someone has played all their cards.
Bullshit!
False
The first person to play all their cards is the winner.
Bullshit!
True
Class F's custom rules!
A player wins if they have only two cards remaining in his hand.
Class F
Custom rules
Winner
The game ends faster this way.
'Tis important to base thy strategy around counting the cards.
The person who picks up the cards can then start from any number he likes.
If you choose a number carelessly, you'll be digging your own grave.
Well then, I'll start.
Ace.
It's my turn. 'Tis a two.
Three.
My turn, right? Fo—
Bullshit!
I didn't even finish yet!
It was bloody obvious.
'Twas written all over thy face.
You suck at this.
If I'd played my cards honestly from the start, it would get harder afterward—
There's not an honest man amongst them.
Tick.
I must be very careful here.
Three.
Four.
A four again, Akihisa?
Bullshit!
Fool! Here's a present for you!
Seriously?! You had a four all along!
The previous one was a trap!
Splendid!
I can't tell them I forgot about this card earlier.
Tock.
I'm down to six cards, huh?
Hideyoshi has... four.
This is critical.
What are they gonna play?
'Tis a six.
Voyeur, play a seven.
Seven!
I missed a chance to call bullshit!
He's good! He prompted Voyeur to play so fast that we didn't have a chance to call bullshit on his card!
Then here's a...
Oh? What are you guys doing?
Himeji! Why are you still at school?
I was helping a teacher with something.
I got these as thanks!
Shall we all have them together?
Thank you, Himeji! Can we do it after we're done with our game of Bullshit?
We have this bet...
No, I can't tell her we're gambling.
No, I mean, this is a penalty game.
A penalty game?
That's right!
The loser doth have to strip all his clothes!
Strip?
Hideyoshi.
Thou mustn't, Akihisa.
That's blasphemous!
'Tis no need to be angry, Himeji. We're all men here—
Bullshit!
Why dost thou put all the cards before me?
Even if you're all boys, it's still wrong!
Come. Let's eat these chocolates...
and chat...
All right, all right. Just one more round.
Come on. Let's get it over with.
Himeji?
Then, I play an eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Jack.
'Tis a queen.
Bullshit, Hideyoshi.
So thou wert holding the fourth one. Very well.
Since we're all boys here...
What's wrong, Hideyoshi?
Oh, my! Kinoshita, you shouldn't go to sleep in a place like this!
form
It's all right. I'll play in his place.
Hey... Himeji... what's that handkerchief?
Kinoshita must have been really tired.
But Hideyoshi was just fine a minute ago—
But what about that—
Voyeur!
It looks like Tsuchiya was very tired too.
What in the world?!
There's something wrong with Himeji!
What... could it be?
Could it be...! Wait, those are—
Goodness! Kinoshita must have been really tired to be trying to undress in front of Akihisa.
There's no doubt about it! Himeji's gone mad because of those chocolates!
Is something the matter, Akihisa?
It's just that there are only three of us now, so we can't continue.
Shall we just end here—
End?
Whatever do you mean? Aren't there four of us here?
Good luck.
Shouko! Where did you crawl in from?!
Forcibly undressing her man is one of the duties of a loyal wife.
Shit! I don't even know how many things are wrong with that!
All right then. We'll make separate teams for boys and girls, okay?
Sure. It'll be over faster that way.
What do we do, Yuuji?
Never mind. Just hurry up and lose, so it's over.
But what if they lose and have to undress?
Nah. If it goes too far, we'll stop the match.
I get it! That's fine!
Akihisa! Just one sock isn't fair!
Yuuji, that's very unmanly of you.
Himeji, shall we end this soon—
Oh, but we're just starting to get serious!
Shouko! You've had enough, right?
Commencing attack.
But undressing in front of you girls is... you know...
It's all right, Akihisa. If you don't want to get naked—
No, don't! I look terrible in women's clothing!
It's your fault for not listening to me, Akihisa.
Akihisa, I just realized something.
An urgent communication?
What?
We don't have a choice any more.
Shall we use that ?
Sorry! Let's start the next round then.
Oops!
Now's the chance!
What?!
I see you've gotten better at scheming together.
Yuuji won't make such a silly mistake during our match.
You really like to be bad boys.
Such naughty little boys.
Tick.
Seven.
It's gonna happen soon.
6 Cards
If I lose, I'm screwed.
Kubo?
She's lying!
Kubo! You're on my side?!
Thank you. I can use this!
I'll put all my feelings into this one shot!
That seven... is bullshit!
Too bad. It really is a seven.
Kubo!
Forgive me, Yoshii!
She's lying!
Not!
What the fuck are you doing, Akihisa?!
He's the one guy who'd want you to lose this match and be naked!
But why?!
Tock.
I'm having second thoughts about this game.
Himeji! It really is wrong, isn't it?
Fighting your own friends, even if it's a penalty game.
Akihisa will become an internet idol now!
Just a moment, Himeji!
I haven't allowed you to take pictures of me cross-dressing and upload them to the Internet!
Yuuji, you can close your eyes if you feel embarrassed while I'm taking your pictures.
Damn you! I'm not going to lose!
By the way, Akihisa.
What is it, Himeji?
I don't intend to let you off with just the uniform.
Shouko! You won't—
I'm wearing my best underwear today.
We're dead!
I won't undress for you!
Oh!
It's your turn to play a king, and I'm going to call bullshit on it when you play it.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Final
B-Bullshit.
Faster, Akihisa! They're right behind us!
I don't wanna be an internet idol!
Hey! No running in the—
Save us, Ironman.
Give us extra classes or something!
What are you morons doing undressed like that?
We'll explain later!
Too late, Akihisa! They're here!
Wait, Akihisa! Hurry up and wear these!
We won't let you go till you do.
Just how do they manage to get into these situations?
Question 4:
Answer the following question.
What is the chemical formula of benzene?
Himeji Mizuki's answer
C6H6
Teacher's comment:
I suppose it was too easy.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
"ben" plus "zene" equals "Benzene"
Teacher's comment:
Aren't you taking Chemistry a little too lightly?
Yoshii Akihisa's answer:
B-E-N-Z-E-N-
Teacher's comment:
Please come to my office
with Tsuchiya later.
A test run for summoned beings?!
New system
Test run for summoned beings!
Yeah. I want you guys to test it.
Why us?
Because you're just what I need.
If your marks were too good, it'd be hectic if something went wrong.
Black Book
I get it. Things did go horribly wrong last time.
I wish you hadn't reminded me of that.
But yes, that's how it is.
Could you please return to your class now, Himeji?
I wanted to help too.
Too bad.
Well, if you insist.
I'm glad that you want to assist us.
Well then, please do your best.
This is boring! I don't wanna!
It sucks enough being the Punishment Inspector.
Hmph
I seem to recall someone running in the halls in their underwear.
Well, I wouldn't expect you to do it for free.
How about I give you all meal tickets and library cards?
Fumizuki
Academy
Meal
Tickets
Today's Special
Wow!
Very well. I'll set up a summoning field covering the whole school.
Those taking part will be Tsuchiya, Kinoshita,
Shimada, Yoshii, and Sakamoto.
That's all. Thank you.
Hold up, hag. I have pretty high marks, you know.
I don't care if something happens to you.
Hey!
How'd we get stuck with this?!
I know.
It's all right!
Let's just hurry up and finish it.
Let's see. We just have to move them around, right?
That would be what it seems, aye.
Okay.
All righty then!
Summon!
So we get to wear uniforms for the test run, huh?
We don't have our weapons.
'Tis so cute!
This reminds me of our freshman year.
Huh?
The summons can talk.
The hag did say this was about improving their effectiveness.
That said, what should I have done this morning?
Eh? Hideyoshi?
Did something happen in the morning?
I did not say anything.
I didn't expect that middle-schooler from the neighborhood to confess his love.
Eh? Hideyoshi, do boys outside the school confess to you too?
Nay, 'tis false. Boys don't—
'Tis the third one this month!
It's revealing his deepest secrets.
We don't get to hear Hideyoshi's secrets that often.
Kinoshita has a good poker face.
Nay, nay, you two. I really don't—
I'm a good summon, aren't I? Hurrah!
I really am.
Hey, Voyeur!
What?
If it's about sex, I wanna listen too.
I'd love to talk about that too, but later, okay?
I'm only interested in what's inside your shorts.
He says the funniest things! So cute!
Slap
No, he isn't!
I want to see inside her shorts.
Slap
Stop hitting me.
Such a frank fellow.
Shall I have some fun too?
Do you want to know what's inside my skirt?
I have no interest in such—
Deep beneath the skirt lie a man's romance, dreams, and hopes. There's not a moment of boredom!
Tights, mini-skirts, long skirts, flare skirts, printed skirts, etc.
There are many types of skirts. Each has its own dreams to run away to.
However, I don't consider culottes as skirts!
No, I'm not interested.
They are really revealing their masters' secrets.
Why is Minami's summon sitting in my lap?
This is gonna get bloody.
Aki, hand her over.
No! I wanna stay with Aki!
It's even disobeying its master!
It's just like a child, saying everything on its mind.
I see, just like a child.
Aki huggle!
Oh no you don't! Let go of him!
No!
Now, now, Minami. It's all right.
I'm used to this.
Huh? You are?
Children really like me a lot for some reason.
It's because you're their age... mentally.
Shut up, Yuuji.
You know something, Aki?
What is it?
I'm always mean to you,
but I really love—
Stop!
Just what do you think you were going to tell him?
Are you all right, Aki?
Listen to me!
I'm sorry!
Listen up, Aki. I don't have any secre—
Actually, yesterday a girl from another class confess—
Aki, you coward! Are you trying to get some dirt on me?
It's more like you're shooting yourself in the foot.
Don't argue! Bring out your own summon and have it reveal your secrets.
I've gotta get away before my life is ruined.
But how?
So they're revealing our secrets...?
Did you say something, Himeji?
Oh, no! Nothing at all!
By the way, how do you read this?
Phosphorus monoxide
Umm... Phosphoru... sumon... oxide
Yes, that's close enough!
What? How?
Shit!
I'm sorry, Akihisa! But you have a secret I must know!
Good one, Mizuki!
Answer us, Aki! Who's the girl you love?
I have to find something to distract them!
Shit!
Damn! That idiot won't be any help.
You weren't any better!
What are you trying to say?
Listen, you two.
Hurry... Run... away!
I usually wear shorts below my skirt,
but I'm not wearing them today.
Why would we care—
Please let me under your skirt!
...about that?
That's right. You can't—
Hold it, I'm first!
...fool us that easily.
Aki, can I have a word with you?
Akihisa, we have to talk.
Yuuji!
One moment, technical difficulties
Please wait. We're experiencing technical difficulties.
You two have such dirty minds.
Reflect on your bad behavior!
I'm not wearing shorts either!
I'm sorry! I went too far!
You're horrible, Kudou!
Please be more prudent!
And you know, I woke up late today.
I didn't have time to wear a bra—
Please let us be!
You're not wearing a bra?!
Yuuji!
You've got it wrong, Shouko! This is just a man's—
Squish
What are you... Let me go!
Do you like it?
There's no way I'd—
... like this!
Good grief, he's a total pervert.
You're so lucky, Yuuji! I'm jealous! I'm jealous!
My situation is so different.
Please wait. We're experiencing technical difficulties.
One moment, technical difficulties
Right then, there are things you can and can't do.
Do you understand?
Yes.
That's right, Aki!
You can't rush. Only when both sides are sure of their feelings—
Hey, Aki, pick me up!
Akihisa...
What is it, Himeji?
I know it's sudden, but...
Do you have someone you love, Akihisa?
Why do you ask?
I've felt this before, but you sure are dumb in situations like this.
Huh? What?
I'll ask again.
Ha! I have a plan!
Who is the girl you love, Akihisa?
Her name's Salmon. She's in class G.
Salmon?
Good! Let's continue this conversation.
You're so mean, Akihisa!
You have a few things you don't want us to know too, don't you, Himeji?
I don't mind! I don't have any secrets—
Just now, when you were thinking dirty things,
I was thinking of stuff as well...
No!!
How's it going?
Oh dear! How did they end up like this?
Sparkling, honking
Lightbulbs pop
Yes!
I'm not making any progress
Someone's getting in my way
It's not enough at all!
That's the root of the problem
Do you understand what it really is, baby?
If you do, draw your answer here, baby
Neither the words nor the numbers reveal you
My heart is all tingly
with the magnetism from S and N
Congratulations! You're now my-m-my treasure!
You're special. No matter what happens,
I'll hold you tight and won't let you go
I've fallen in love
I don't want any doubts in my heart
You're special. I've met you,
but please forgive me anyway
Sparkling, glittering
The right answer is pop!
Did you need something, umm...
I'm the representative of Class E, Nakabayashi!
I called you here because my heart's been fuzzy lately.
No, not fuzzy... suffocating? Worrying?
Anyway, I'm summoning all my strength to say this.
I really want to tell you something. Are you busy?
Oh, no, I'm free. I was just confused about why you summoned me.
Please go out with me!
Why is Yoshii so handsome and charming?
His actions, his speech, his demeanor!
He's so perfect!
Woo woo.
Nakabayashi.
Yes?
Forgive me.
I don't wanna be dumped like this!
Question 5.
Question 5:
Answer the following
question.
What is the correct way
to treat a minor burn?
Himeji Mizuki's answer:
Quickly cool it down with water.
Teacher's comment:
Correct. Well done, Himeji.
If there's no running water nearby,
apply a clean towel to the burn and pour water on it.
In case of severe burns,
such as a freezeburn or a very large burn,
apply a clean towel and take the victim to the hospital immediately.
Tsuchiya Kouta's answer:
Pay consolation money.
Teacher's comment:
That's the way adults play with fire.
What is the correct way to treat a minor burn?
Pay consolation money.
That's the way adults play with fire.
Next time: Me, peeping, and the training camp!
Next
time:
Me, peeping, and the training camp!
This will be on the test.