Haruka's Room
Number 1
Haruka's Room!
Welcome to Haruka's Room!
This program will introduce the friends that appear in Kotoura-san.
I, Kotoura Haruka, will make the introductions.
Our guest for episode one
has spent the last 15 years reading other people's minds.
"Your mind is like an open book to me!"
Please welcome, Kotoura Haruka-san!
Nice to meet you. I'm Kotoura Haruka.
I recently transferred into Midorigaoka High School. I'm a first-year student.
I have the ability to read people's minds.
It's like ESP or something.
Personally, I'd rather not have this ability.
Well then, Kotoura-san, how does it feel to be able to read people's minds?
In class, there's a boy called Manabe-kun who sits next to me, and he's a sex maniac.
I get bombarded with his erotic fantasies, so it's pretty rough.
I wish he'd grow up already.
I see. It seems useful, but it has a downside too, huh?
That's right. People just don't seem to get that.
I'm beat.
The End