This land, situated in a cold region in the northernmost part of Japan, formerly known as the country of Ezo,
still has much primitive wildlife due to its complex geography and harsh natural environment that are unsuitable for living in.
All living things in the Ezo region participate in a merciless battle of life and death every day.
Cold cold cold cold!
I'll die I'll die! I'm gonna die!
This particular region, known even in Ezo to have particularly harsh snowstorms,
and which is also designated a first class disaster area — Mount Odori,
is where the strategian Togame and the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika find themselves climbing for their lives.
Dammit, piling up on my head's like this...
Annoying snow!
Ow, ouch!
It's your own fault for not dodging!
You say that...
But this really is amazing.
So this is what they call Ezo snow?
The snow is quite something, but what's really amazing is the wind.
The wind is so strong that snow only builds up to knee height.
It's like a constant avalanche.
Don't describe it like that!
You'll make me feel even colder!
We aren't even halfway up the mountain, you know.
I can't even imagine what it's going to be like at the peak.
And they live up there, right?
That "Itezora" clan, was it?
What kind of people are they anyway, Togame?
They probably look like snowmen.
Or they could be covered in thick fur and look like the abominable snowman.
Well, no doubt they're resistant to the cold, anyway.
"No doubt"... you don't actually know?
Nope. Not at all.
And while we're on the topic, I haven't heard a single thing about Soutou Kanazuchi, either.
Soutou Kanazuchi
Hammer,
The Pair
Soutou is written "pair of swords", so it could be a set of two swords.
I do know that the Itezora clan's ancestors were apparently the giants of Izumo.
Well that's useful to know...
...not.
Togame, how are you going to make any plans with such little information?
Does "Strategian" mean "someone who doesn't make plans"?
Moron! I would never make plans!
What I come up with are schemes!
By "schemes", do you mean "guessing as you go along"?
Wh-What!
Why you!
Ch-Cherirurero!
I see you get your tongue in a twist when it's cold.
If you've got the time to waste talking, hurry up and climb!
If you don't hurry up, I'm going to turn into a snowman!
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
己をはらはら花に例えて　散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsumami aguneta guren no tama wo
摘みあぐねた紅蓮の霊を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarau kare no hi areshi mune yori
さらう彼の日　荒れし胸より
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
恐るるまま命は羽搏いて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
やがて　やがて　天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
朱く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai kira no yume wo ataeta mou
すれ違い綺羅の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabite meiyo ni samayoi
待ち侘びて冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
想いがはらはら舞う故に
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sora he egaite
絆を更なる空へ描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Soutou
Kanazuchi
Owari
castle
grounds
Though I must say,
Princess
Hitei's
palace
that woman really is impossible to read, going straight from Satsuma to Ezo like that...
She must have heard about my return to power by now.
Is this a display of confidence on her part?
What do you think, Emon Zaemon?
I really couldn't say.
Boring!
What a boring man you are.
Have you forgotten who went to the effort of putting a mask over that face of yours,
darker than darkness itself, and bothered to write "unconcealed" on it?
That would be my princess—
Shut up!
I'm not looking for an answer.
I don't need an answer!
I deny it.
I deny the day I employed you!
If they're in Ezo, they'll be heading towards the frozen land designated as a first class disaster region, Mt. Odori.
That would be where the sword they seek, Soutou Kanazuchi, is held by the Itezora clan.
I thought as much.
But does that woman really think it will be easy?
What do you mean?
Do you know why Mt. Odori was designated a disaster region?
Wasn't it because it harbors the harshest snowstorms in Japan?
That unpleasant woman probably thinks the same.
It was designated as such not because of the mountain itself, but because of the inhabitants of the mountain —
the owners of Kanazuchi — the Itezora clan, who have lived there since the distant past.
This sounds like it'll get interesting.
She can go ahead and keep flirting with that Kyotouryuu until she realizes what the real situation is.
S-Shichika...
If I die...
Huh?
If I die, please make all of Japan adopt "cheerio" as a catchphrase that means a shout to fire you up...
Wha.. what are you saying?
Pull yourself together, Togame!
I can't take it anymore...
H-Hey!
This looks like the end for me...
So please, Shichika...
If nothing else, please make "cheerio"...
That's impossible!
There's no way I could make "cheerio" catch on with the wrong meaning!
You can do it...
You are the sword I chose.
Impossible!
I can't do anything without you!
What are you saying?
I've taught you everything I can already.
You don't need my schemes anymore.
What?
You still have things to do!
During this journey with you, I've realized for the first time...
Everything I've done so far is meaningless...
True happiness is finding the one you love and becoming a mother,
and then living your life out with them.
In the past, I hadn't even considered such a thing.
Isn't it a bit too early for you to be thinking about that?
I've walked this path for 20 years...
but in the mere half year since we met, you've taught me how a human should live life.
No, I really haven't done anything to change your outlook on life yet...
My body seems kind of strange...
What are you doing?!
Shichika?
Shichirin?
Hey, Shichika!
Shichika!
I thought you'd died!
What's wrong?
My limbs won't move like I want them to...
You've got frostbite, you idiot!
If you're cold, why didn't you say so?
I didn't think you were just putting up a strong face!
Well no, I'm not cold, but I'm kind of losing control of my body.
Idiot!
How dull can you get?
So this is what "cold" feels like...
No, don't go to sleep!
If you sleep, you'll die!
Shichika!
Open your eyes!
Open your—
Wake up!
Please, wake up!
Shichika...
What do I do...
What should I do?
What should I do...
Um...
Are you okay?
Here we go!
At the exact moment when the strategian Togame and Shichika were saved by Itezora Konayuki,
the 12 heads of the specialist assassins, the Maniwa Corps, were gathered in the Maniwa village.
Though, having said 12 heads, there are only 6 here.
Maniwa "Phoenix God" Houou,
Maniwa "Sea Turtle the Long-lived" Umigame,
Maniwa "Mandarin Duck the Rewind" Oshidori,
Maniwa "Otter the Investigator" Kawauso,
Maniwa "Penguin the Proliferate" Pengin,
and the shapeless Maniwa "Rabid Dog the Infectious" Kyouken.
Indeed, the Maniwa Corps have been halved in number this past half year.
The effective leader of the Maniwa Corps, Maniwa Houou, was in the middle of his report to the other 5 heads,
and was explaining how the crisis had driven him to form an alliance with the strategian Togame in Satsuma.
And thus, we must all move together as a unit from now on.
It is unavoidable, if it's true that the Insect squad really has been exterminated.
I know you were on close terms with the Insect squad's Chouchou.
I'm guessing this alliance goes against your wishes.
No, Chouchou and I merely serve the Maniwa Corps.
I would never consider acting on my own for revenge.
Right?
As far as revenge goes, personally I have a burning desire to avenge that Koumori idiot.
He was my friend...
but bearing this pain is what shinobi must do.
If we can achieve our goal at the end of it all,
it will make up for their losses a little.
To do that, we must start collecting swords as quickly as possible.
Right.
While avoiding conflict with Togame-chan too, right?
The three swords I told the strategian about are in Shireizan, Tendou, and Edo,
but for some reason they headed for Ezo.
Um... i-isn't Ezo where S-S-Soutou Kanazuchi is?
Your information gathering abilities are as impressive as ever.
With Koumori no longer with us, it's no exaggeration to say that the success of our sword collection plan rests on you.
Then we should search for the swords in locations other than those four.
Correct.
U-Um...
Um, um, um!
What is it, Pengin?
A-About that point, or rather, about the swords' locations...
Shireizan...
Shireizan?
There's n-no longer a sword in Shireizan.
Or r-rather, Shireizan itself...
I-I don't know wh-who it was, but someone laid waste to Shireizan in just half an hour and took the sword.
What on earth...
If such a monster exists, I think you'll have to move for us, Kyouken.
Kyouken?
Kawauso, how long was Kyouken here?
Give me a break...
When she moves seriously, even another member of the Beast Squad like me can't follow her movements.
Though, I had a feeling she was still around when you were talking about that Ezo stuff.
This is bad.
That means she's gone after the strategian.
That Kyouken is particularly emotional, after all.
I doubt we'll be able to stop her.
Right?
If Kyouken is on the move...
The alliance will fall apart just one month after it was formed.
Now that it's come to this, we have no choice.
Let's go, Kawauso.
As you wish.
Strategian-chan, Kyotouryuu-chan...
You are the first people to make me this angry.
I'll never forgive you!
I will avenge my friends!
Got it?
You'd better not freeze to death before I get to Mt. Odori!
You're an amazingly powerful girl.
You carried me and Togame through this blizzard, right?
And with that tiny body of yours too...
I wouldn't be able to live on this kind of  mountain otherwise!
You're pretty amazing too!
You climbed halfway up this mountain with a person on your back.
You have a lot of guts for an land dweller!
A land dweller?
Onii-chan and Onee-chan, would you tell me your names?
Oh, excuse me.
Army general director in support of critical tasks under direct control of Yanari Shogun of the Owari Shogunate, Togame the Strategian.
I'm the 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
Togame Onee-chan and Shichika Onii-chan?
I'm Itezora Konayuki, 11 years old.
Nice to meet you!
Itezora...
I see.
Meeting you here must be a fate.
We actually came all the way here because we have some business with your clan.
Really? How surprising!
I'm sorry to ask this right after you saved us, but could you guide us to the Itezora clan's village in the morning?
Um, well...
This is very hard to say, but the Itezora village was wiped out in an avalanche just last month.
Wiped out?
Yes...
I'm the only survivor.
What do we do about our sword gathering now?
Sword gathering?
What's that?
Might we have a sword which Togame Onee-chan and Shichika Onii-chan are looking for?
Yeah...
Your clan owns Soutou Kanazuchi, one of the 12 Perfected Deviant Blades which Shikizaki Kiki forged.
Have you heard of it?
Oh, Kanazuchi!
You know about it?
Not at all!
Sorry, as you can see, I'm just a child.
They didn't tell me about important matters or clan secrets.
Then was there anyone in the clan who used a sword?
Well, we don't really use swords, whether we're hunting, cooking, or building.
Oh!
Come to think of it, the mayor's eldest son...
What about him?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
More importantly, what was that about the mayor's eldest son?
I heard he used a sword when he was hunting.
But I haven't seen it, and I don't know if it's Kanazuchi...
What do you think, Shichika?
No idea.
If you're placing your hopes on my 6th sense, you're out of luck.
It's such a faint sensation that I might just be imagining it.
Then our only hope is to dig up the area around the mayor's house.
But the village was buried in an avalanche, right?
Do you even have any idea where it would have been?
Good point...
If that's the case, how I go out for a bit to fetch it?
"Go out for a bit"?
I lived in the village for 10 years, so I have a good idea where it would be.
But there's a vicious snowstorm outside...
The amount of snow falling makes no difference to us.
The snow is a part of us.
Whoops, I said "us", but I'm the only one left now.
I'll just go get it then!
Please wait here.
"Just go get it"...
Will she just give it to us if it's really Kanazuchi?
I don't know.
It's not clear what meaning Kanazuchi had to the Itezora clan, but it doesn't seem like that girl has any attachment to it.
And that means we may be able to collect this sword with only negotiations, and no battle.
I wonder if Konayuki is being kind to us because she feels lonely after losing everything...
What?
I just thought it's strange for you to recognize someone else's pain as "loneliness".
Is that meant to be a compliment?
Yes, but at the same time I'm concerned.
Concerned?
About what?
Could you fight?
Yeah, my legs and arms are fine now.
That's not what I mean.
I'm asking if you could fight Konayuki.
A child for an opponent would be easy.
I see.
That's fine, then.
But to think their village was destroyed by an avalanche after living here hundreds of years...
I guess even these things happen.
The Itezora clan's village is on the mountain peak, right?
Now that you mention it, that does seem unnatural.
Shichika, something's been bugging me since we left Satsuma.
What is it?
How did you know about that "chest" expression?
I'd just heard it from my father.
It's just that you were saying it so boldly that I thought maybe I was remembering wrong.
I see.
There isn't anything else you know about that you aren't telling me, is there?
Um...
I guess there are...
There are?!
You're such a...
Come on, tell me all of them while we're on the topic!
O-Okay...
Let's see...
I killed the previous Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Mutsue, my father, with my own hands.
I also know that you're the daughter of the mastermind behind the rebellion whom my father killed, Hida Takahito.
Who told you about my father?!
That ninja I fought on Fushou Island, Maniwa Koumori.
I see...
I dealt with him more than any of the other Maniwa corps members.
The problem is, who else has Koumori told besides you?
I think I'm the only one he told.
I think he said it to buy some time after I cornered him.
I'm sure he intended to kill me afterwards, so I don't think it was a secret he leaked to anyone else.
I suppose...
Come to think of it, he was competing with the other 12 heads to collect the swords.
I guess he withheld information from them to gain an advantage.
That's just like him to be so impudently treacherous.
W-What?
So does that mean you chose to be my sword after learning about my father?
Yeah, what about it?
You knew that, yet...
No, because of who I was, you fell for—
Togame?
Nooo!
No no no no no no!
W-What're you doing?
Sorry, I was covering up my embarrassment.
That's covering embarrassment?
I suppose there are no more doubts then.
Though it doesn't change our situation.
No, it may even have improved it.
Shichika,
I'm going to add another order.
You must never speak of these two facts to anyone besides me.
Understood.
Hey, Togame.
Assuming we collect Kanazuchi—
There's no assuming.
We're getting it.
Yeah, I guess so.
We collect Kanazuchi,
then get the remaining 6 to complete the collection of all 12 as planned.
Right.
After that, what do you plan to do?
As your sword, I intend to accompany you however your life turns, and stay by your side wherever you go.
But what about you?
Once we finish the collection, what do you intend to do with your sword?
I don't think there's been a day you've surprised me more than today.
Really?
Are you trying to ask me how I'm going to treat you as the Kyotouryuu sword?
How I'll treat someone who should be the object of my revenge?
I wonder now...
I'm not playing innocent, just so you know.
I'm really am thinking about it.
We're still in the middle of our journey.
For now, we need to focus on collecting all of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades.
I don't know if that's a valid excuse, but it's the reason why I don't want to give an answer to your question yet.
Sorry.
Shichika?
You fell asleep?!
Honestly...
Come to think of it, today is the first time you've fallen asleep before me.
Good night, Shichika.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Togame Onee-chan, Shichika Onii-chan!
This is the sword that the mayor's eldest son owned.
That?
That's not a very promising reaction...
Isn't this the sword you were looking for, Togame Onee-chan?
Unfortunately not...
That's strange...
According to the documents that were with it, this is Kanazuchi.
What?
Could you show it to me for a second?
Okay!
This is it!
This is Kanazuchi!
Wait a second!
I see...
Kanazuchi is the heaviest sword ever created.
And the Itezora clan's strength is unmatched by anyone else.
Even though you pride yourself on your strength, you can't even budge it.
You really have superhuman strength...
Oh no, I'm not strong at all.
In the strength competitions, I always came in last place.
Of course, I could never compare to the adults,
but I was also the weakest among the kids my age.
Weakest?!
Oh yeah, I forgot to mention, but according to the document, the sword can't just be given away.
What?
If any land dweller says they really want it, they have to prove they are worthy to Kanazuchi.
Are you ready, Shichika Onii-chan?
Yeah, but it's cold.
Let's start this already,
right Togame?
Yes.
Start the fight!
Here I go!
Oh? You're over there, Shichika Onii-chan!
This is kind of bothersome.
Whoop, I'm not supposed to hurt her.
I have to hold back.
I must win without injuring my opponent,
or else we can't get her to carry Kanazuchi back to Owari.
Kyotouryuu: Rose!
Kyotouryuu
Rose
I'm over here!
Now for it!
Kyotouryuu: Violet!
Kyotouryuu Violet
H-How's that?
Konayuki...
This is fun, isn't it?
Shichika Onii-chan!
I-Is it?
I'll stop thinking too much and try to finish this quickly in one move.
What should I do?
The only way I can counter Konayuki's strength is through speed, which makes Kyouka Suigetsu my only choice.
Shichika Onii-chan!
It's my turn now!
What?
She can even freely change the swing of the sword?!
Stop!
And thus in his fight with Konayuki, Yasuri Shichika suffered his first defeat on their sword collection journey.
So that's Mt. Odori?
Doesn't seem anything special.
Now then...
how should I cook up Strategian-chan and Kyotouryuu-chan?
Everyone's looking forward to it.
I'll send them to their graves in a way that suits them best.
By the way, Houou...
It's kind of sad to admit, being the leader of the Beast squad, but I still don't know much about Kyouken's ninpou.
You've known her for a long time, right?
This is a good opportunity, so tell me.
That's not quite accurate.
She is in a league by herself as far as time goes.
"Rabid Dog the Infectious"...
It would be described as something like a "resident mind".
Resident mind?
The truth is, the individual named Maniwa Kyouken died a long time ago.
Oh, I see...
She can freely jump between bodies?
That is one convenient ninpou...
Unfortunately, it seems there are limits to the ability.
Apparently she can only target women.
I didn't know that either.
Lots of secrets, that woman.
The power of Kyouken's ninpou will be beyond all description if Kanazuchi's owner turns out to be a woman.
According to Pengin-kun's information, all members of the clan are incredibly powerful.
Whatever the case, we must at least prevent the worst case where we lose both Kyouken and the alliance with the strategian.
Right.
And for that, Kawauso...
It may be necessary for you to die.
Aye sir, got it.
I've experienced many things as a ninja, but I've never died yet.
Now that it's come to this, I'm actually kind of looking forward to it.
That Koumori idiot is probably feeling lonely up there, too.
Let's hurry.
Got it.
Shichika Onii-chan, I'm really sorry!
It's fine, I said.
Don't worry about it.
I never expected Shichika Onii-chan to be so weak.
Is my handmade jerky tasty?
Yeah.
The rabbit one is particularly good.
Rabbit it is then!
Then to help Shichika Onii-chan recover faster,
I'll go hunt lots of tasty rabbits!
Stay here and rest well.
Okay, thanks.
Sorry.
What's that all of a sudden?
Well, I was thinking what happened this time was maybe my fault...
You aren't holding a grudge against me, right?
Like "a broken sword is useless",
or "it's disgraceful for my sword to lose",
or "go back to your island"?
Or are you angry at how violent I am?
I'm not angry or bearing a grudge.
It's true that I lost.
I already knew she was immensely strong, but I was underestimating her because she's a child.
Though, I don't know if I could have beaten her even if I was on guard.
You rate her abilities pretty highly even though she's just an amateur.
Frankly, that kind of opponent is the hardest to deal with.
Those ones with no sense and logic, who are simply strong.
I see.
You saved me with that swift decision.
If the battle had continued after that, I could have been killed.
You'd even thank me?
I broke the promise...
"Protect the swords, protect Togame, and protect myself."
I wasn't able to protect myself.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
I've already blamed you enough.
Or maybe too much.
I'm sorry.
Something like a fractured arm which will heal in half a month doesn't count as breaking your promise.
And I'm the one who miscalculated this time.
I don't intend to count it as disloyalty on your part.
Well, thanks.
So, what do we do?
I still can't kill Konayuki, right?
I guess we'll be having a rematch once my left arm heals, though.
About that, Shichika...
You probably won't have to fight Konayuki anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm thinking that what she said about proving we're worthy was a lie.
A lie?
Why would she lie like that?
That girl is lonely.
When she hands over Kanazuchi, we'll leave, and she'll be all alone again.
She only just lost her family to an avalanche.
As cheerful as she's acting, I'm sure she must be longing for some company right now.
So she told that lie so we'd stay here longer?
What a sweet lie...
Look!
I caught this.
I can hunt all by myself now.
I know I shouldn't lie...
But I want to play with them...
Just a little longer, okay?
After that, I'll say sorry for lying.
Everyone...
I'm so lonely with everyone gone...
Konayuki, are you okay?!
Yes...
I'm okay.
Maniwani?!
Is she someone you know?
I just reflexively...
Did this woman tell you her name?
I think she said she's one of the 12 Maniwa Ninja Corps heads, Maniwa...
Maniwa Kyouken or something.
So you're Maniwa Kyouken?
You're a heavyweight, even among the 12 heads.
I had no idea you were a woman.
Being knocked out right after showing up reminds me of Maniwa Shirasagi.
Shirasagi, Koumori, Kuizame, Chouchou, Mitsubachi, Kamakiri...
You've gone and brazenly killed my friends, Strategian-chan.
Thanks to you, the Maniwa Corps is a total mess!
So what?
I've watched over and protected my companions in the Maniwa village.
Don't take me lightly!
I will avenge them!
I'll send you to the other side with these two hands!
It's nice that you're lively, but you don't look like you're in any condition to kill me.
You've come here just to die.
What an ill-fated woman.
Don't get too depressed, I lost to that girl too.
Really? How good of you to tell me.
I was uncertain whether I'd be able to defeat you with this body,
since its only merit is speed.
Maniwa ninpou: Kyouken Hatsudou!
Note: Rabid Dog activation
Kyouken Hatsudou
What just happened?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Strategian-chan, Kyotouryuu-chan.
I am one of the 12 Maniwa corps head's, Maniwa Kyouken-chan!
Amazing!
Simply amazing!
I can feel the power flowing through my body!
This is more amazing than any other body I've taken control of before!
It's perfect!
The Itezora clan, was it?
It's such a shame I never knew about them before!
I see, so this is how she's lived for so long...
What is this, Togame?
Basically, she can jump between bodies.
She's a resident mind.
A resident mind!?
You know what that means?
Nope, not a clue.
Cheerio
Cheerio!
Togame, just making sure, but I can kill that now, right?
Will you be able to, Shichika?
It'll definitely be difficult with my left arm like this,
but I'm not sure if I could beat her even in top form anyway,
so it's kind of the same either way.
I understand, Shichika.
But it's not "you can kill her".
It's "kill her".
Cut her down.
I know!
If I go to the Itezora village and switch to an adult woman,
her body might be even more amazing!
Oh?
The Itezora clan got wiped out?
She even takes over memories?
What...
What's this memory?
What caused this devastation...
The village... the Itezora clan was wiped out!
Well, whatever.
I'll get Kawauso or Pengin to look into it later.
Hey.
Stop spouting garbage.
You came here to kill me, didn't you?
I'll play with you, Maniwa Kyouken.
That's correct, Kyotouryuu.
Shirasagi, Koumori, Kuizame, Chouchou, Mitsubachi, Kamakiri.
I'll be sending your enemies over to you soon.
Make sure you share them out when you eat them!
Are those movements...
Let me tell you something interesting, Kyotouryuu-chan.
I don't just take over memories.
I inherit them.
I've taken over more than 2000 bodies in my lifetime.
Most of them were female ninja, highly skilled in the martial arts.
I don't know how many years of experience you have, but I have several thousand times more!
All I've got is 20 years of training, and I haven't even done real battle 20 times.
Wait, if it's like this, maybe I should check to see.
What, you're trying to escape?
How pathetic. Is that how a swordsman acts?
No, I just wanted to confirm something.
What? Confirm?
Why don't you go confirm your corpse!
Stupid blockhead!
Kyotouryuu: Plum!
Kyotouryuu
Plum
It landed!
How did you do that, Shichika?
I don't know why, but ever since Konayuki was taken over, I've been able to read her movements clearly.
I see...
You couldn't read Konayuki's movements since she was a complete amateur, but Kyouken is an experienced assassin.
And on top of that, she has the combined experience of thousands of people.
It makes sense that you can read her movements now.
Shichika, this is an order.
If that woman takes over my body, kill me without hesitation.
As brutally as you can.
Understood.
Don't think for a moment that a hostage strategy would work against my sword.
Just so you know, the strength of my body is on par with sliding door paper.
I'm confident I can die just by falling over.
I'm also confident that I can lose in a fight with a rabbit.
If you still want to take over my body despite that, go ahead.
However, by that point you'll be torn into pieces.
I am one of the 12 Maniwa Ninja Corps heads, Maniwa Kyouken!
I will avenge my friends!
Now...
Eat this!
I get it now.
That's why that sword is called "pair".
There's no clear handle or tip, so you're free to hold it either way.
Soutounoinu!
Note: Twin-bladed dog
Soutounoinu
Kyotouryuu: Hikara Kuyou!
Note: Falling blossoms, scattered leaves
Kyotouryuu Hikara Kuyou
The tattoo...
Maniwa Kyouken's tattoo is vanishing!
Shichika, what did you...
I thought maybe if I only attacked the tattoo, I could defeat Kyouken without killing Konayuki.
It looks like it worked.
That's a relief.
We have to get Konayuki to carry Kanazuchi to Owari, right?
Y-Yeah...
That's right.
Well done, Shichika.
This is the first time Shichika made his own decision not to kill his opponent.
And against my orders, too.
Kyotouryuu is but a single sword,
but before that, he's also a human.
I thought I should wake up that human side in Shichika,
to make him find his resolve as a person, not as a sword.
I told myself there would be insurmountable hurdles if I didn't.
But now that it's actually happened, was I right?
Maybe everything I've done in the last two months has merely served to dull his blade.
All because, as his owner, I didn't know how to handle this sword.
Cheerio.
It seems we're too late.
I'm one of the 12 Maniwa Ninja Corps heads, Maniwa Houou.
Likewise, I'm one of the 12 Maniwa Ninja Corps heads, Maniwa Kawauso.
You have some nerve to show your faces in front of me!
Don't glare like that, Togame-chan.
We used to work together in the shadows, didn't we?
Shut up!
It would appear the worst case happened after all.
Right.
And now Strategian-dono has lost her trust in us.
I put no trust in you people from the start!
Please don't jump to conclusions.
Kawauso and I came here to stop Kyouken.
Kyouken moved of her own accord this time.
I wouldn't want you to think that the Maniwa Corps agreed to this.
However, it's entirely understandable if you wish to break up the alliance after this incident.
The alliance is already over.
Don't say that...
We were definitely in the wrong this time, so please allow us to take responsibility.
Responsibility?
Kawauso.
Alrighty.
Togame-chan, you know what my ninpou is, right?
Maniwa ninpou: Record Tracer.
Record Tracer?
Kyouken was searching through Konayuki's memories, remember?
Kawauso can do the same thing with inanimate objects.
Basically, it's a form of psychometry.
Psycho me tree?
Objects have spirits, same as people, Kyotouryuu.
Though it doesn't mean I can read absolutely anything, and conversely to Kyouken, I can't read people's memories.
I'm too shy for that.
If you can do that...
So you understand now how useful this man's ninpou is for sword gathering.
That's quite the secret weapon they kept hidden.
Right?
So, what do you mean by responsibility?
Hurry up and tell us.
Right.
Even if I offered to lend you Kawauso's ability, you wouldn't trust us.
And so I have no choice but to do this.
With this, the 12 heads of the Maniwa Corps, including myself, are down to 4.
At this point, I'm sure you agree we cannot pose any real threat to you,
so could you overlook this minor violation of our alliance?
You...
You call yourself a leader?
I told you before, you're overstating things.
The Maniwa Corps needs no leader.
Shinobi merely live and die.
How about it then?
If you still insist that we're a threat to you even without Kawauso's psychometry, then there's no choice.
I will have to fight you here.
I, too, harbor the urge to avenge my companions—
I'll let it pass!
I'll ignore this incident.
Hurry up and get out of my sight!
I don't want to see that unpleasant grin of yours any longer!
I thank you for your generous treatment.
Ah, yes...
About what I told you the last time...
Apparently the owner of Shireizan's sword changed a few days ago.
Its owner changed?
It means that there's someone besides yourselves and us gathering the swords.
It would seem that the new owner got on a boat from Roku to Shikoku.
Shikoku...
I recommend you deal with it soon.
The new owner is a monster that laid waste to Shireizan in a mere half hour.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
It's okay.
All that aside, we're counting on you.
You're the only one who can do this.
Leave it to me!
I'll be sure to take it to Owari.
Yup.
Do your best.
And don't worry about the Sanzu shrine where you'll be living from now on.
I've heard that your ancestors originally came from Izumo.
I'm sure this is fate.
Okay!
Togame Onee-chan, Shichika Onii-chan!
Thanks for playing with me!
It was really fun.
We're finally heading to Shikoku, Shichika.
We can go see the giant Sword Buddha statue that you wanted to see.
Yeah...
What's wrong?
You look down.
How to put it... I feel some regret.
What?
A change of heart?
I didn't know you had a thing for little girls!
Are you telling me you prefer that young girl over m—
No no, I said regrets, not a change of heart.
We managed to defeat Kyouken, but my defeat by Konayuki still stands.
That's why I still feel regret after beating Kyouken.
I see. I already explained that to you.
Konayuki's hit was just an amateur fluke that happened to catch you.
It's nothing to worry about.
That wouldn't normally even count as a loss.
Really?
No matter how many times you say it, I don't get it.
Are you sure you haven't had a change of heart?
Do you want me to wrap my hair around you again?
A change of heart is impossible.
I'm your sword, after all.
Well, that's fine then.
Don't make me worry like that.
Well, if you absolutely must conclude your fight with her, do it after finishing our sword collection journey.
Okay.
Understood, Togame.
Shichika's humanity was making fast progress as they reached the midpoint of their sword collection journey.
Next month's deciding battle will take place in the holiest ground for swordsmen, Mt. Sayabashiri,
inside the Seiryouingoken temple where the Buddha of swords sits.
Shichika has achieved victory without killing the owner twice in succession now with Azekura Kanara and Itezora Konayuki,
but in his next fight, he will undergo the experience of killing his own sister.
Will the sword, the heart, or both of them be broken?
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
konayuki wo koorase you ka
こなゆきを凍らせようか
I wonder if I should freeze the snow
chi ni mau mae ni
地に舞う前に
before it drifts down to the ground
haku iki hitotsu de
吐く息一つで
with a single breath
tsurara to mimagou koori no aikuchi
氷柱と見紛う　氷の匕首
The dagger of ice, mistaken for an icicle
kumo ga sakebu tabi ni
雲が叫ぶ度に
Each time a cloud yells
tsuki mo ha wo mise you
月も刃を見せよう
the moon will show the blade
nikushimi no tame ni (deau sadame mo)
憎しみの為に　(出会う運命も)
Even a fate I encounter (because of hate)
mata itoshii yue ni (ai yori aoku)
又愛しい故に (藍より青く)
Also for love (bluer than indigo)
omoi wo togeru sono hi niwa
思いを遂げる　その日には
On the day when I realize my wish
shizuke ni sora wa sumiyuki
静けに空は澄み行き
the sky will quietly be perfectly clear
tokeru darou
溶けるだろう
and fate will melt into the sky
To think that Shichika would feel regret over another woman...
I'll wrap him up with my hair so tight he won't forget me!
Now then, the owner of the sword for next episode...
To think she of all people would stand in our path...
What is Yasuri Nanami thinking?
Next time on Katanagatari: Akutou Bita.
We'll show you Shichika's new ultimate move!
Well, I'm thinking it up now...
Akutou
Bita
Poor,
the Evil
Cheerio!