SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
I gotta pee.
PHONE DUTY
WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY
"Maintenance confirmation of connection line to Headquarters...
...for the purpose of high-level emergency situations, Mission"?
Wh-What an amazing name.
It's quite an important mission.
Failure will result in disciplinary action for the whole platoon.
There are certain conditions under which a level-one alert will be announced,
and all the surrounding forces will be put into an emergency standby as well.
That's right, it's truly something of great importance.
Wh-What kind of mission is it?
It's...
Watching the phone.
What?
So you know that this phone is a hotline connected to the government center, right?
How many times has it rung before?
Not once.
That's right, thankfully.
Could it be...
Yes. It's a problem if it rings,
but it'll be even more of a problem if it doesn't ring when it should.
That's why they need to confirm that the line is working twice a year.
Which is the...
"Maintenance... um..."
Jeez, remember it already.
"Maintenance of the connection line..."
Wait...
Wrong.
"Maintenance confirmation to Headquarters..."
"Maintenance confirmation of the connection line to Headquarters...
...for the purpose of high-level emergency situations, Mission"
That.
Me! Me, me, me!
Let me carry out that mission!
I've always wanted to try talking on a phone.
Is that something to be exited about?
Its basic functions are similar to the Takemikazuchi's intercom.
The only difference is the distance.
But it's amazing.
It's so wonderful to be able to speak with someone who's far away.
Well, I guess you could say it does feel a bit weird talking to someone you can't see.
But, it's nothing special once you're used to it.
The problem is, we don't know exactly when it will ring today.
Do you still want to do it?
Of course!
Alright then, you're going to stick to the phone for the whole day.
Ring-ring-ring....
This is Helvetian Republic Army 1121st Platoon,
Private Kanata speaking.
And after the call is finished, put this back on the top.
Alright.
Fi-Fili-
My, you're so cute!
Filicia-san.
What are you doing? Jeez, I can't stand watching this.
You're gonna miss the train.
Train?
There's a document I need to deliver to Headquarters as soon as possible.
Claus-san is coming next week, right?
So I'm going to the train station.
I'm counting on you to watch the phone.
Roger!
If it rings and you're not there, the worst possible outcome is that they'll think we're under attack.
So take it seriously.
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Y-Yes ma'am!
I wasn't sleeping!
I wasn't sleeping at all!
Did you see Noel?
She wasn't in her room.
U-Um...
Maybe she's in the hangar again?
Oh well.
So, Kanata, what do you want for lunch?
Ah, I-I'll cook.
Don't worry. It's my turn.
But...
Hey, why do both you and Kureha never let me do the cooking when it's my turn?
I cooked quite a bit before the both of you came here.
That's because...
I'm pretty sure it doesn't taste bad.
Well, that's true, it doesn't taste as bad as it looks...
What?
No! I-it has a unique flavor, it's lovely!
Right?
Alright then, today I'll push my skills to the absolute limit.
Hey, anybody home?
Coming!
Senpai, it's Naomi-san.
I'm busy.
But I can't go far from the phone.
Hey! You've got a guest!
Damn, alright then.
Just a sec! I'm coming!
I don't wanna eat another sandwich full of cutting board chips.
These are...
You can drink them. It's apple cider.
These were made on the hill where we buy our apple juice from.
So that means they're related to our Calvados, doesn't it?
I see, so you knew.
Two should be enough as a gift, right?
Yeah, I suppose.
Gift?
They're holding a merchant's guild meeting in town.
They help us with accommodations, so we occasionally give them gifts in return.
Remember that.
Okay!
What a letdown. Those girls were trying so hard to hide it from you.
How did you find out?
Th-That's... Um...
I'll tell you when the time is right.
That aside, how about having lunch with us, Naomi-san?
What?
I need to attend, too?
You remember the news in this week's paper?
It seems everyone wants some kind of explanation from the Army.
News?
About the treaty conference going through trouble.
Is that true?
They still haven't reached an agreement about reparations and borders.
It's not uncommon for it to drag on.
Well, I really think those gramps from the guild just wanted to see you.
Since you played the role of the Fire Maiden in the Water Festival,
it seems your fanbase has grown.
That's a bit troublesome.
Jeez.
So that being said, it seems that I need to head out.
I'm also a maiden of the fortress in both mind and body.
I can complete the mission on my own!
Alright, I'll leave it to you.
Roger!
Kanata, I'm giving this to you.
It's my old stuff, though.
It's a trumpet book!
This is wonderful, so wonderful!
Thank you very much!
You've gotten better at the trumpet, after all.
This is a reward for your efforts.
Also, it'll probably help you stay up during the mission.
Um...
This is C.
D.
E, F, G.
A.
Summer's almost over, isn't it?
Iliya?
Maybe I drank too much?
Noel-chan, are you there?
It's raining! The laundry is getting drenched!
The courtyard is within the mission parameters.
Ka...na...ta!
Let's play!
I'm coming!
Ka...na...ta!
Let's play!
Help me!
Thanks for saving me.
Don't mention it. It's good the laundry is okay.
I really appreciate-
No wait, I-I'm so sorry for making you help me like that.
Don't worry about it.
We also apologize for showing up without prior notice.
I've come to give my regards since I'm returning to Treize tomorrow.
You're too kind.
You don't need to give your regards to a soldier.
That's not true at all, Seiya-san.
I was told that he's been quite rude to the people of this base,
so I thought we should come by to apologize, but...
Where are the others?
They all went out.
The one with black hair, Rio-san if I'm not mistaken, as well?
Yes.
I see.
I was hoping to see her-
Is this book yours?
What is it?
A trumpet book.
Rio-senpai gave it to me.
I see.
As I expected...
Ah, no. Forgive me.
I was just talking to myself.
So are you by yourself right now?
I am. Um...
I'm in the middle of the "Maintenance confirmation of connection line to Headquarters...
for the purpose of high-level emergency situations, Mission".
That's what it is.
So I would assume,
you're waiting for this to ring?
Yes, I am.
But this is the first time I'm using it, so I'm a bit nervous.
I hope I can properly handle the call.
Why don't we practice, then?
So Yumina-san is also attending the guild meeting?
Yes, she's raising donations from the people of the guild.
Here, have a drink.
It's good!
Right?
Have some too, Seiya-kun.
I'll drink it,
but this doesn't make us friends.
What are you making?
Do you both recognize this?
It's a phone!
Is this really a phone?
Yeah, it's a phone.
The kids love it, so I make it for them sometimes.
Now, Seiya-san.
Okay!
A phone, huh?
Hello.
Hello!
Awesome! It's awesome, Seiya-kun.
I can hear you!
No, you should first say, "hello" on the phone.
H-Hello!
Hello, there.
This is great! I really heard a voice!
You can use it for practice.
Right.
Um, this is...
Hello.
H-Hello.
This is Helvetian Republic Army 1121st Platoon,
Private Sorami Kanata speaking.
Yes, go ahead.
I'm honored to receive your call today.
Yes, very good.
And... Um...
Wait, birdy-san!
Mishio-san!
Don't!
Mishio-chan!
What's wrong?!
The phone!
Um... Is the priest and the-
Oh?
Oh, my dear God...
What have you done?
You were supposed to come here to apologize,
but you just played around and caused trouble.
No dinner for you tonight.
Yes, ma'am.
Does that mean me, too?
It's okay now, thank you.
But your clothes are wet.
That's okay, I have an extra-
I have a good idea!
This...
is so embarrassing.
No it's not!
Wow, you're so dazzling.
But, thanks, Yumina-san.
I'll wash these and return it to you.
Don't worry, you can have it.
It's too big for the kids,
and I can't find anyone more suitable for it than you, Kanata-san.
I'm sorry, Kanata.
Can I come and play again?
Of course.
You can come again too, Seiya-kun.
I-I'll...
I-I'll come if I don't have anything else to do.
Well then, we will excuse ourselves.
May you be blessed with great happiness.
Thank you very much.
Now then, time to clean this up...
I almost forgot.
The bathroom.
I gotta pee.
Someone, come back soon!
Come back!
Damn, those geezers...
What's wrong, Kana-
Senpai...
I beg of you, help me.
What happened, Kanata?
I... Can't...
I'm gonna wet myself!
Go already, you'll get sick!
Thank you very much!
She's been holding it the whole time?
Either she's too devoted, or overly honest.
What's wrong?!
I-I'm okay!
Kanata!
I... Can't...
I can't take another step!
She has amazingly bad timing.
Hello, this is Helvetian Republic Army 1121st Platoon,
Sergeant Rio Kazumiya speaking.
It's been a while.
I heard we need to confirm the line to your post,
so I insisted-
Are you running away?!
No, I'm not running away!
I know you haven't forgiven me yet, have you?
What do you want?
Please...
Please save this country, save Helvetia!
Good morning, Kanata.
Noel-chan...
Don't tell me... Since this morning...
Yeah, I sleep well in the bathroom.
No way!
I'm ba- My!
What a cute dress you're wearing, Kana-chan.
Or rather, what are you two doing in the hall?
Kanata fell down.
She can't stand.
Are you hurt?
No.
Then stand up.
Jeez, you're so hopeless.
What a spoiled girl.
No... Don't...
Ready, set...
Nooooo!
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
A TYPHOON PASSES - ILLUSION AND REALITY
Next episode: A Typhoon Passes - Illusion And Reality.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.