Yuu…
Haruka…?
Is your forehead still hurting?
Only a little...
Geez, you really had me worried!
Yuu!
Why didn’t you get enough sleep last night?
I’ve never seen you miss the ball before.
I stayed up late studying with my sis.
I thought I’d give you a surprise by acing the midterm test.
Please don’t overdo it!
Since you really had me worried...
...now it’s payback.
I-I think there’s someone else sleeping in the next bed!
No worries, we’ll do it softly… nice and softly.
Softly…
That wasn’t enough…
I-I’m injured here, can’t you see?!
Is that your voice, Yuu?
Scare
Stop squirming over there.
If you’re better, get back to class.
I lost a lot of sleep because of you.
Geez.
kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
while at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
We may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings run deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
If things stay like this
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
Nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
Won’t you kiss me? It’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
Can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
With our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
Mom.
Dear Friends and Family, we hope that you are enjoying the fair days that
autumn has to offer. We hope you are spending your days happily and healthily
Recently, we have decided to hold a wedding ceremony.
As such, we would like to invite you to this humble gathering,
as a sign of our gratitude for your continued support and guidance.
We know you must lead busy lives,
but we would be delighted if you are able to attend.
Sincerely,
Morita  Kouichi    Takayama Megumi
Time
December 15
11:00 AM
Place
Wedding Palace
Please inform us of your intent to attend by the 15th of November
Isn’t Megumi’s wedding sometime next week?
What do you think I should wear?
I think anything that’s not white should be fine.
Your school uniform should do.
I see…
Come to think of it, your father has a business trip that day.
Why don’t you invite one of your friends in his place?
You mean it?!
How about Yuu?
...and Shizuku, Kotone, Yuzu, and Kaede…
You might want to limit it to just one...
Then I guess I’ll see if Yuu is free...
A wedding, huh?
It won’t be long until it’s our own little Haruka’s turn.
bang
As if I’d ever let some dead-beat guy marry Haruka!
You’re being overly dramatic, honey...
They don’t mind if it’s a girl!
A Cherry-Colored Wedding
Hey there, were you asleep?
I’m wide awake...
Would you like to — wedding with me next week?
But what about the paperwork?
And did you even ask your parents yet?!
Yup, they’re all for it.
Well, if you really want to...
...I’m okay with it.
Really?! Thanks so much, Yuu!
I’ll call you again soon.
Call Ended
Mute
Haruka
Call Ended
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Call Ended
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
Haruka
Call Ended
Mute
Speaker
Hang Up
to home screen
It looks like I’m getting married to Haruka already…
Is she really okay with things going this fast?!
We’re both girls…
What do we even do for the ceremony?!
Sis—
What’s the matter, Yuu?
Big Sis
Forget about it!
Okay…
I can’t even ask her for advice!
But she’ll end up finding out eventually…
You’re rushing things, Haruka?
A-Alright.
Sis.
I knew something was up.
Well, uh… if two girls were to—
A call!
I shouldn’t have said anything!
What’s up, Haruka?
Haruka?!
Hey, listen, about the wedding…
Think it’d be fine to wear our uniforms?
We could  also go with rentals…
I didn’t know you could get married in school uniforms...
Well, this is really important to me...
I think I’d rather rent a dress.
Okay!
Mom!
Yuu said she wants a rental too.
What’s wrong with your uniforms?
Even a cheap dress would set you back ¥5,000.
It’ll come out of your allowance!
My allowance, or a party dress…
...which should I go with?
I’m picking the dress, obviously!
Are you serious?!
Sakura Trick
One week later
We haven’t done any preparations for the wedding yet…
What’s going on?
Are you feeling nervous, Yuu?
Don’t worry, Yuu. Don’t be so reserved.
I may not live up to your standards, but I’ll try my best.
That’s the spirit.
Dress Rental
Ohanaya
We’re here.
This isn’t a wedding hall...
So Haruka was just pulling a prank on me!
Dress Rental
Ohanaya
What’re we here for?
We’re gonna rent dresses for the wedding.
Haruka, I’ll go ahead and greet them first.
Wait, we’re really getting married after all?!
Yuu, did you see a ghost?
You look so cute in that!
What, this color?
It should be pure white...
Do you want to try another?
You look really good in that, though.
Ah, I know!
Have you ever put on make-up before?
Nope.
Then, here we go!
I can do it myself!
kiss
Now we’re both set.
What’s the meaning of this, Haruka?
What do you mean?
Uwaaaaah
That’s supposed to wait until after our vows!
And you just ruined it now!
Oh, come on!
You thought you  were going to be wed today?
We’re going to be celebrating another couple’s marriage.
What led you to such a misunderstanding?
You were just way too cryptic!
BANG
So what, you don’t  want to marry me?!
Just now…
Huh?
That kiss was my vow to you.
This too.
And this one too.
These are all my vows to you.
Are you two ready?
Just about!
L-Let’s get going, Yuu.
U
w
a
h
It’s so embarrassing…
I can’t look her in the eyes…
Without further ado, let us welcome the bride and groom.
Please give them a warm round of applause.
Megumi!
I think that’ll be your father too…
This isn’t a funeral...
The wedding cake will now be cut.
It’s even bigger than I had thought!
It could only be better if it were matcha-flavor!
Matcha!
W-What’s wrong, Yuu?!
It’s just so sad to see your attention stolen by food even in such a touching moment…
I’m starting to get worried.
I was touched too!
The bouquet will now be thrown.
Everyone, feel free to participate.
Think we can try too?
Let’s catch it together!
And here we go!
Yuu, it’s coming right to us!
You bet!
Haruka, I caught it!
Mom?!
My life may soon get some spice!
Sakura Trick
Our turn
Congratulations on the wedding, Megumi.
Thank you very much, Haruka.
You might be in my place next time!
throb
That might be sooner than you think.
Haruka!
My!
Please take some petals.
We’re having a flower shower…
I’ve never done this!
The bride was stunning, don’t you agree?
Yup. And so was the chicken.
I really enjoyed the cake too.
And the salad was just right.
Ooh
Geez!
Weren’t you supposed to be immersed in the mood?!
I-I was!
That reminds me…
My dad said he’s fine with me marrying anyone who’s not a dead-beat guy.
He actually didn't
Try to control yourself!
A Cherry-Colored Wedding
End
Who could that  be?
I was just finding my rhythm, too.
Hello?
Good afternoon, President Mitsuki.
tha-thump
H-Haruka?!
Would you like to come see the light show tonight?
W-Why?!
I’ll be all alone with Haruka?!
I need time to prepare myself…
Big Sis
S-Sure… I’ll go.
That’s great!
Could you invite Yuu too, if it’s not too much to ask?
Of course…
There I go getting way ahead of myself again!
I mean, I’ve never even been alone with her before!
But her calling me directly was a first…
It’s always been Yuu that’s invited me.
Sis, wanna come to the pool with me and Haruka?
Haru—
Her calling me directly must be a sign of progress!
Wait, what progress?
I wonder why she called me instead of Yuu this time…
A Cherry-Colored Christmas
Yuu.
Yeah?
I was on the phone just now…
Who was it?
It was Haruka asking if we wanted to join her at the light show tonight.
Okay then. I’ll get ready soon.
You do  have her in your contacts, right?
But you didn’t answer her call?
She’s been acting very peculiar…
If she didn’t pick up when Haruka called...
...could they be having a fight?!
I’ll go get changed.
It’s not too good to be fighting right before Christmas…
They’re really running out of time to make up…
Since she’s willing to come along, I think Yuu at least wants to do just that.
As her big sister, I’ve got to help her out!
Yuu. Hear me out for a second.
At times, you can be pretty stubborn and confusing, right?
nag
Aren’t you?
You’re just imagining things.
You can’t just keep waiting.
It’s more sincere if you’re the one to apologize first.
I’m sorry.
Know what I mean?
No, I don’t!
What’re you even talking about?!
It should be obvious!
I see the Sonoda sisters are here.
Hey there!
Did we keep you waiting long?
Not at all, no.
As I thought, Haruka’s trying to avoid Yuu.
I’ll find a way to have them make up!
Take a look at this place, it’s gorgeous!
Wow!
Now’s not the time to be enamored!
I’m gonna send you right for Haruka.
Get ready, Yuu!
You okay, Yuu?
Ah
You need to watch your step, alright?
They’re drifting apart again…
This won’t do.
It’s like they’re complete strangers.
I’ll bet they have some sort of grudge against each other.
I’d expect this from Yuu, but I guess Haruka can be stubborn too.
Looks like I found out something new about her…
Wait, what am I giggling for?!
Big Sis
I need some help!
What was that for, President Mitsuki?
Don’t Yuu and Haruka seem a bit mad at each other to you?
Think so?
It’s plain as day.
Any idea what happened?
I’ve got no clue.
But wait, what’s up?
I thought you were concerned about them being too close.
That doesn’t matter right now!
What a pain...
Mind if we check out this thrift store?
Let’s do it.
Welcome.
Wow!
Oh, Yuu would probably love this pendant.
Haruka, doesn’t this look nice?
Yuu would love that!
I’ll go fetch her!
That would look really pretty on you.
I’m flattered, but that wasn’t the right reaction!
This isn’t working.
What should I try next…?
President Mitsuki, you really like that one?
Yes, I think it looks cute.
Then why don’t you just buy it?
I went and bought presents for my little brother and sister…
...so I’m broke.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
You should try asking Santa for something!
She’s joking, right?
The place should light up in just about seven minutes.
There’s quite a crowd, huh?
We’re at the right place, right?!
Oh, relax. There’re plenty of families and close friends here.
Love can take on many forms.
I’ll go check out that thrift store a bit more!
I’ll go see what’s in the shop next to it!
They’re making it really obvious now!
Can’t they just go together? It’s the same direction…
You just  had to mention “love”...
Hold on a second, this could actually be a chance!
Alright!
We might get a better view on the other side, where there’s less people.
Why don’t we try heading over?
Okay, I’ll go get Haruka and Yuu.
No, I’ll get them, I insist!
You go on ahead.
Isn’t it natural for a student council president to be the one guiding?
Hahah
I don’t get her one bit…
We’re heading off!
Good, they left.
President Mitsuki… where’d everyone go off to?
They’re trying to find a better vantage point.
That reminds me… I wanted to try picking some flowers while we’re here.
Think you could wait here for Yuu to come back?
Sure…
Now Haruka thinks I’m actually picking flowers...
Just hang in there, Mitsuki… It’ll all pay off!
Shizuku? Kotone?
This isn’t good… I lost them.
Haruka!
Yuu…
I wonder where everyone went.
I think they found a less crowded place on the other side…
So they all went there.
They didn’t have to go so soon…
Right? They could’ve waited a bit longer…
I was just about to call one of you, but then I saw you waiting.
That sure was good timing, huh?
This doesn’t feel right.
Whenever I see her, all I can think about is that time at the wedding…
I want to be able to look her in the eyes again…
I want us to chat like we usually do…
Haruka…
Shine
The clock has struck seven.
Let the light show begin!
Whoa! The scene’s constantly changing!
Let’s take a picture, Yuu!
Why…? We were back to normal just now…
Haruka…
“At times, you can be pretty stubborn and confusing, right?”
“You can’t just keep waiting. It’s more sincere if you’re the one to apologize first.”
Haruka!
The view seems better over there. Let’s go!
T-That’s not it!
Whenever I see you… all these things just rush into my head.
It’s so much, I just get overwhelmed.
I didn’t want that to happen again…
...so I didn’t ask you directly to come tonight.
I’m just…
I was going through the exact same thing.
The same problem.
But who cares if it hurts a little?
I wanna have my heart race like it always does with you.
Something seems different about you now.
I bet your heart’s racing more than mine is right now.
I-Is not!
I have to match that, if we’re going to be together.
Where’d everyone run off to?!
A Cherry-Colored Christmas
End
Big Sis
kagayaku irumineeshon
A shining illumination
mune ga tokimeku no
makes my heart flutter
tobikiri kawaiku kigaete
I'm dressed up super-cute
dekakeyou kurisumasu
I'm all ready for Christmas
machijuu kirameku
The town's all lit up
tonari ni minna no egao
everyone around me is wearing a smile
afureru shiawase
Our abounding joy
shiroi toiki ni naru
is let out in our cloudy breath
furihajimeta sakurairo no yuki
The falling snow seems cherry-colored
kimochi tsutaetai
I want to tell you my feelings
konya dake wa ne
Tonight, for sure
kami-sama, toki wo tomete
Please God, make time stop
hira hira kagayaku
in this sparkling place
tokubetsu na shunkan
we share a special moment
anata to tsunagaru nukumori
with a warmth that connects us
nee zutto, gyutto
I'll hold you, always
sakura kurisumasu
It's a cherry Christmas
Next Episode Preview
Kotone, am I the only one you don’t have a nickname for?
bones
longevity
Happy New Year
Would you like me to make one?
That’s not really what I was getting at…
Yuzu-chan.
That sounds off.
Yuzu-chin!
That’s no better.
Yuzuriai!
That’s not even a name anymore!
Well aren’t you  picky?
How about... Mikan!
Anything but Mikan!
Next time we have, "S.B.J.K’s Year-End Debut",
S.B.J.K’s Year-End Debut
Another Plan Gone Sour?!
and "Another Plan Gone Sour?!"
See you then!
It’s Harupoppo’s debut!