"Kagami Yoshimizu Theater"
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go!
Grr!
Quit screwing around and start!
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Between sweat (whoop)
Sweat (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
It's what you call a normal girlie
Am I the only one surprised?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Take it away!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Because I have the sailor suit
← This is my conclusion
It's only Monday!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
I really prefer the summer outfits
← kya! Wah! Good! (cute!) < 3
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please ★
Do your best, be energetic
My darlin', darlin' please!
They bought me a new cell phone!
Don't put it in the laundry this time.
Yeah, I'll keep it
somewhere noticeable!
Hey, Tsukasa, help me out!
Oh, okay!
"Desires"
B-a-l-s-a-m-i-c V-i-n-e...
"Irritated"
There. ...g-a-r.
I'll type them all in for you,
so hand it to me!
You're irritating me!
That's okay. It's all right,
I'll do it myself.
I'm here to visit!
Oh, Sis. Welcome.
What are you playing?
A gal-game that came out recently.
Then I'll pick some
random manga to read.
Okay.
This is an age-restricted title...
Does she not realize it,
or is she letting it slide
without a thought?
Which is it, oh, police officer?
So, we're having Traffic Safety Week,
and so we're stepping up
on the ticketing.
We have really nit-picky checks to do,
and we have to take the time
to explain all the traffic rules.
It's really a big burden!
Sometimes, the offender gets
mad at me for doing it, too!
But, seeing you and
how you usually act...
Rules and safety hold
no persuasive powers at all.
It's really a surprise to me!
"Shikina Shima Clinic"
I hear that this year's cold
lasts for quite a long time,
so I must get better quickly...
From the reception number,
it looks like it will take a while.
I'll just read a book and wait here.
Mr. Ando? Mr. Shigeo Ando?
Miss Takara? Miss Miyuki Takara?
Is Miss Miyuki Takara not here?
Then next, Miss Mariko Nishiyama?
Huh? Huh?!
Was my name called?
What time is it?!
I must pay attention to
my surroundings a bit more...
We are approaching Kamata,
our final stop.
Where is this?
And so, I taught Tsukasa
how to send text messages.
She told me she didn't know how,
after fiddling around with it so much.
I see...
"Yay!"
And she must have been terribly happy about it,
because she texts me every day
with anything and everything
that's going on around her.
Fielding all those messages
must be a chore, too!
Well, there's no need to be
all worried about it, though.
"From: Tsukasa"
She's the type that gets all
worked up in the beginning,
but always loses wind after a while.
Yeah, there's people out there
with such childish tendencies.
Oh, I've got another one.
It's not that they get bored with it,
they just can't keep up
with themselves.
Anyway, are there that many
things to text about?
And when we're
together all the time...
Oh, and I think she's caught on
to the emoticon thing too. See?
You want to buy the soy-milk cream
buns again on our way home today?
What is all this after the sentence?
The fact that she's really
having fun gets across, but...
At this point, it's hieroglyphics.
Maybe she's gotten used to it now?
"That's true, but I like the guy
with the afro better."
"Really? But he's not really
playing that instrument, is he?"
"Yeah, maybe so."
"I see."
"Yeah."
You know...
Oh, no...
I understand how you feel,
but would it kill you to send them
to a non-relative sometime?
You guys have a moment?
What is it?
I don't really understand how to
send messages on my cell phone...
For real?!
Oh, it's easy, Dad!
Guess it can't be helped.
I'll show you!
Look at you, boasting like that
when you just learned how to do it.
Well, uh...
You just can't put that
stench into words.
Yeah, it really stinks too bad!
No kidding.
Oh, you've got quite a lot
of people entered in here.
Hey! Don't peek without asking!
Do you have messages you don't
want others to see or something?
Not really. I just felt I should say that.
A guy! It must be a guy!
I'm telling you, it's not!
She's not picking up...
I guess I'll call her house.
Hello, Kagami.
Hey, Konata? How about
answering your cell phone?
Man, I didn't realize you called
'cause the ringer is turned off.
If you can't tell you've
got a call, it's pointless!
For that matter, where is that thing?
Your cell phone really is pointless.
Anyway, about this
coming weekend...
Oh, wait, I'm being paged. Hold on.
Hey, hurry up!
Hold on for a minute more.
You're talking too long!
I can't wait anymore!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
He scolded me for talking
too long on the phone.
Oh, sorry.
I thought your house was rather
laid-back with that stuff.
But is it actually pretty strict?
No, we're in the middle
of a fighter-game match.
Mention stuff like that
earlier in the conversation!
Past and present, discount cards
have invisible magical powers...
Before you know it,
you end up buying things that
you weren't planning on buying.
You really don't plan
anything, do you?
Though I kind of understand
how you feel.
She's here...
Knowing that Ani___e and Ga___'s
are the two anime shops in this town,
she buys the same
item at both stores...
Legendary Girl A!
Legendary Girl A Shift!
All right!
Welcome!
We have Haruhi vol. 5
on DVD in stock now!
Both the limited and standard edition,
here to perfection!
Other than that, all sorts of goods
are coming in one after another!
That's right!
Inform her of what we have in stock,
as much as you possibly can.
If it's her, I'm sure she'll buy it!
Oh, I was going after the special
bookmark gift for Aquarian Age...
I'll have to go to Gamers.
No good!
Lucky Star!
Then we'll have
a sleepover this weekend,
and play all through the night!
Yeah!
When we get together to play,
it's always at my house.
Can't we go to your place, Konata?
I'd like to visit every so often.
It's not that you guys
can't come over.
It's just that Dad's usually home,
because of his job.
Oh, I see.
Right, and I don't want to be
held responsible for anything
that might happen...
Like what?!
"O-Agariyasu"
I'm kind of looking forward to
what Konata's house is like.
S'up!
Oh, welcome!
Excuse us... We'll be under
your care for the day.
Welcome. I hear about
you guys a lot!
I hear your house is a shrine,
so does that makes you shrine maidens?
--What kind of an explanation
have you been giving?!
--So do you usually wear those frilly hakama pants?
--Or rather, is that the very first thing you have to say?!
Go on in.
Wow, Kona-chan's room!
Just as I expected,
this is an amazing room.
So cute!
Oh, a door...
I'm sure this is the room
to remain unopened,
full of stuff that you can't
risk having seen, right?
No, stuff like that
I usually share with Dad,
so they're all kept in Dad's study.
I see, you share them...
Come to think of it,
your dad's an author, right?
Yeah.
So, do you get hooked
on the light novels
or the gal-games that
your dad scripts?
No, he doesn't write that kind
of stuff at all in the first place.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah.
I see... That's rather unusual.
But he likes that genre,
so doesn't he feel like
writing something like that?
Call him a strict lurker.
He said something like
he was playing a gal-game, or rather,
a nurturing game in real life,
so he didn't feel the need
to do more of it as work.
I see...
Wait, I've been overwhelmed
since I got here!
Nothing less from
the Izumi household!
The other day,
Dad was being all clingy...
Yeah?
So I told him "Dad, you're so
annoying!" as an experiment.
You know, that's being a bit rude.
When I did, Dad scolded me like,
"At least, say 'Dad, I hate you so
much!' or something like that."
Well... I'm not so sure about
that correction either.
I have a feeling that you and Dad
are thinking different things.
You already lost me anyway.
You want to take a break soon?
It's here!
You know, lately there's a lot
of 2ch-speak on TV and stuff.
Maybe so. Though I don't
know too much about it.
Come to think of it, Konata,
you're pretty hardcore,
but you don't use those
kinds of words too much.
I normally don't.
When I'm chatting online
and stuff, I talk like this.
Amazing! Is that really Japanese?
I think I've lost if people can read it.
Want me to help with anything?
Oh, then can you dish up the salad?
Sure!
Thanks for the food!
So tasty!
You're right. This is pretty good!
This much is no big deal if you
always do your household chores.
Kagami, why don't you help out
more? You might get a little better.
I don't need your advice.
Look, Konata, it's perfect...
A scene that I have only dreamt of
is in front of my eyes!
--Three high-school girls surrounding
a guy at the dinner table
--I can forget about everything else...
--Sakura... Tohsaka... Tohsaka is your older sister!
--Is an unnaturally frequent situation in gal-games, isn't it?
--Oh... So that's it...
It sure gets cold at this time of day!
Maybe I should have worn
something on top of this.
Hey, a shooting star!
Oh, I couldn't say
my wish three times.
They come so suddenly,
it's rather hard.
But someday, I'm going to succeed,
and it'll grant me a wish!
Tsukasa, you're always a dreamer.
But no matter how you think
about it, it's just impossible.
They only made that legend because
you know there's no way to do it.
And why is this end
so lacking in dreams?
You guys want some, Kagami?
Thank you!
You switched hairdos.
Yeah, just playing around.
Since we got to take baths before you.
Why is it that the image gained
from certain equipment
so different depending
on who's wearing it?
Hey, it's an album.
Can I take a look?
Oh, sure.
Wow, you're so cute, Kona-chan!
Your looks really haven't
changed at all.
Or rather, in your family,
father and child get along so well.
Oh, that's Mom.
She's a chi-- No, so young!
She looks like me, huh?
I hope it wasn't a crime!
When I look at Dad, I always think...
...what part of Dad
did Mom find attractive?
You look so much like your mother.
Then, for instance,
what kind of guy is your type?
Mine?
When you put it that way,
I really don't have one.
Really? Just say it!
Oh!
In other words, maybe Mom was
happy with just about anybody.
She said that Dad was
a childhood friend of hers too.
No, of all things, that's...
So she picked him because
she felt sorry for him.
You really show no mercy,
even to your own parents.
But, looking at Mom,
I had a thought...
Yeah.
Manga and games lately
have lots of characters
like junior high kids that
are mature for their age,
or adults who act immature.
What is that? Are you angling
for a comeback line?
It would have been nice if
Yuki-chan could come with us.
Well, she had an errand to run.
I know! I'll text Yuki-chan
so she won't feel lonely!
Miyuki is probably sensitive
about that kind of stuff,
so it's better if you don't...
Oh, she replied.
I'm glad that you are
having a fun time.
Right now, I am doing my best
to finish my homework.
Next time, I will make sure to...
I forgot that we had homework!
Kagami, do something about it!
We didn't have any in our class,
so can I go to sleep now?
Wait!
That shooting star from earlier...
Maybe I can make something of it
if I make my wish shorter?
I don't know about that...
What are you doing?
Researching how to say my wish
to a shooting star faster...
Don't go escaping from reality,
and hurry and finish up.
Hey, Yuki-chan!
I didn't understand this part
during class earlier.
Oh, that part?
Kona-chan comes from Konata,
Yuki-chan comes from Miyuki...
Then, Tsukasa, what kind of
a nickname would you give Kagami?
Kaga-chan? Gami-chan?
"Mirror (Kagami / kyou)"
I think it would be Kyou-chan.
Like, Kyou... the other way to read the kanji for "kagami."
Oh, you've got good taste there!
"Power (tsuyo-i / kyou)"
It portrays that really tough-willed personality of hers perfectly!
"Ominous (kyou)"
And, you can turn it into this kind of Kyou-chan too.
That's not what I meant, though...
I think you'd be better off not telling Sis that.
Then if you were to give yourself
a nickname, what would it be?
Tsuka-chan? Kasa-chan?
Probably Hii-chan, right?
It's hard to come up with
a nickname from my first name.
I see. It's true that you
have an image like
you're always shrieking
around like, "Hee! Hee!"
Though that's not
what I meant either...
All right.
From now on, I'll call you
Hii-chan, Tsukasa.
Eh?
What do you mean, "Eh?" Huh? Huh?
Well, don't you somehow
get a bad feeling
about a nickname that
you came up with?
Then, how about that?
That?
Anything will do, I think.
Are you going to seek
revenge, Sebastian?
It's Shiraishi!
Hey, Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chan!
Don't tell me that's
you calling for me?
I don't get it, so cut it out!
Okay, what do you
want me to call you?
Isn't Kagami good enough?
Shouldn't you have a nickname?
Like Kona-chan and Yuki-chan.
Then, how about Kagami-sama?
Hey, Kagami-sama!
Wah! She's seriously using it!
What?
No, just calling you.
Sorry to make you wait,
Kagami-sama!
--Is something wrong, Kagami-sama?
--Huh? Did she just call her Kagami-sama?
--I'm sorry, it's my fault.
So please, call me
like you normally do.
Lucky Star!
Lucky Channel!
Morning Luckies!
Now, time passes by quickly,
and Lucky Channel has surged
into its tenth episode!
I'm Akira Kogami, your navigator!
Hello! I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
her assistant!
We'll quickly move on, to
the fourth character introduction!
We're going to talk about
Kagami Hiiragi today!
The realist keeping the silliness
at bay in the main segment!
So in other words,
she's just a tsundere, right?
She's so easy to understand.
What a shallow character.
I hate to disagree, but...
I believe it's jumping
to conclusions a bit
to say that Miss Kagami is a tsundere.
Then what is she?
In other words, do we not have
a true understanding
of the term "tsundere" to begin with?
No, it is a sad fact that in this day
and age, in an inverse fashion,
as the term tsundere becomes
more and more mainstream,
the meaning gets
more and more muddled.
In the first place,
the term tsundere originated
in the year 2002 on the Internet.
At that time, its meaning was
prickly (tsun-tsun) at first,
but later fawning (dere-dere).
That's right, in other words,
it was a term that
pointed to a change of heart
as time passed!
Do you really know
the meaning of hits?
But now, it is understood
as a portrayal
of the two sides of a character's
personality, in other words,
she acts prickly on the outside,
but her true self really
fawns over things.
I will go out of my way to say it,
that it is all a clear misunderstanding!
We must bring back the
true definition of tsundere,
and ring a warning bell to
the fallen linguistic society!
Stand up, fellow citizens!
Nice going, Sebastian.
Who's that?
So, if Kagami isn't a tsundere,
what is she?
Is it me?
I really don't understand
the complicated stuff,
but if you're going to go that far,
isn't there some term
with the same meaning
as the current usage of tsundere?
Well, um, I don't think that
there is a lack of such a word...
Perhaps "cool-dere"...
No, that's not it..."Dere-tsun"?
You have absolutely no taste.
Isn't tsundere good enough?
No, that's... That's different!
Oh, I know!
Let's have our viewers
think of a new concept
that will be able to replace tsundere!
Good idea!
You're going to leave it to others?
So, all of you in front of your TVs...
yes, I mean you!
Won't you try coming up with a word
to describe a character like Miss Kagami?
And let's use that to overwrite the
Common Facts of Modern Speech!
Let's call it "The Complete
Debate of Tsundere!"
For details, please check out
the radio show or our homepage!
I'll be waiting for your
passionate input!
Wrap it up here?
Oh, well.
Lots and lots, lots and lots...
Bye-nee.
Bye-nee!
Fast forward!
Man, I really spoke
a whole bunch today.
That was the best take I've had so far!
Oh?
Akira-sama, is something wrong?
Satisfied?
Yes. Well, I spoke the most
today of all the episodes,
and I think I did a good job.
I'm going to eat with the president
of your production company,
and one of the producers...
Eh? Eh, what...
Well, you know, about what's going
to happen to you from now on...
Well, uh... Hold on just a minute...
What do you mean by that?
Well, whether or not someone
can keep going on isn't something
that they'd understand,
even if told directly to their face.
No, no, no...
You still have that part-time job
at CoCo-(ichi) for now, right?
Oh, no, that's just
during daylight hours.
It's not that I can make
a fortune out of it.
And that Korean BBQ place?
I do work at a Korean BBQ place too...
Wait, no, stuff like that
really doesn't matter!
That's, you know, too private
a matter, so please stop it...
I'm up next.
Tsukasa, how about this?
Oh, if it's this... Right, Yuki-chan?
Yes, I know of it.
Then, you guys sing it.
Thanks, Kona-chan.
Thank you very much.
Finally...
Tsukasa, you guys decided on a song?
Yeah!
♪ Lonely, showing an almost
broken self in the window ♪
This song was popular back when
we were in kindergarten, right?
I'm not really sure.
I'm sorry, I don't know either.
I remember! Our big sisters
used to sing it a lot!
Songs that your parents
or older siblings sing
are usually a generation before you,
but you learn them
so naturally through them.
♪ I always looked for something
that would keep it together ♪
♪ Why was it that I couldn't
see dreams so honestly? ♪
♪ There is no place for me to sleep
anywhere in the city ♪
♪ Love was pouring out
from all over my body ♪
Oh, she gave in.
I can't help it. It's too high.
Through the throng...
"Next Episode Preview"
Now, what's with the
next episode of Lucky Star?
Kagami here.
When you go out with friends
and eat a meal out,
it's all right to the point where
you order something with soup.
But when the soup splashes and
a little bit gets on your clothes,
doesn't it get a bit depressing?
Especially if it was
the curry roux, it's the pits!
And those times are always when
you're wearing your favorite outfit,
and you're totally blue
for the rest of the day!
And when you buy a boxed lunch
with soup at a convenience store,
you walk home being really careful
to keep the contents level
so they don't spill out and stuff...
But when you get home
and open the bag,
and the soup spilled out and
made a complete mess of things,
you really lose the will to
eat the lunch altogether!
Or like, it's nice of them
to separate the hot stuff from the
cold when they bag what you buy,
but when they put magazines in the
same bag as all your cold drinks,
the paper sucks up all the
condensation from the drinks,
and the magazine gets
all warped and stuff...
Why did they separate the bags
in the first place?! You know?
Next episode: Various Ways
to Spend Christmas Eve.
"Various Ways to Spend Christmas Eve"
Please look forward to it!