Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Kagami
Yoshimizu
Theater
Class 3-B?
Ms. Kuroi!
Yeah, yeah...
The ambiguous 3cm?
Does that mean it's plushy? Wait!
Aimai san senchi sorya punitte koto kai? Choh!
The wrapping is a uniform, argh,
it's not an act, pooh
Rappingu ga seifuku dafuritte koto nai bun
Gotta do your best, gotta just do it
Ganbacchau yacchacchau
That's time to catch 'n' release, eek
Sontokkya chanto release yo
Between sweat (whoop)
sweat (whoop)
Ase (whoop) ase (whoop)
Darlin', darlin', freeze!
No tanima ni darlin' darlin' freeze!
Kinda lethargic,
something's kinda comin' out
Nan kataru nan taberu
I love you... Oh wait,
one of those was different
Aishiteiru are ikko ga chigatte run run
Worrywarts, high metal bars
Nayamibou koutetsubou
Tasty thoughts... And that's enough!
Oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai!
The heated body of that
flying you-know-who
Tondetta aitsu no hoteru karadatte
It's what you call a normal girlie
Iwayuru futsuu na onna no ko
Am I the only one surprised?
Odoroita atashi dake?
Seconds on pork-bone broth ramen
with wire-hard noodles
Tonkotsu harigane okawari
Da da da da da
Pom-poms cheer squad
Bonbon ouendan
Let's get cherry pie
Happy fun welcoming party
Ranran kangeikai
Look up! Sensation
Yeah! Feeling of existence,
dot dot small planet
Hai! Sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Collided and it melted away,
in total awe
Butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Go all out to sing, shi-ranger!
Ooini utatte shi-ranger!
Take it away!
Motteike!
I should be the one who'll be
laughing in the end
Saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
Because I have the sailor suit
<- This is my conclusion
Serafuku dakara desu ketsuron
n n n n n n n n
It's only Monday!
Getsuyoubi nanoni!
Already in a bad mood? What to do?
Kigen warui no dou suru yo?
I really prefer the summer outfits
<- kya! wah! good! (cute!)
Natsufuku ga ii nodesu kyawaii!
Until we approach 3 pixels,
no hesitations please *
seifuku in san piece sorya matette chuucho da yan
Do your best, be energetic
Ganbatte harikitte
My darlin', darlin' please!
My darlin' darlin' please!
Konata.
Can I use your computer?
I want to type up something...
...for the meeting next week.
Sure.
Let's see...
I've been having difficulties lately...
I've been a head nurse recently,
...but I should have it finished in time...
but it's a maniac transfer,
...so I intend to speed things up...
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to cross dress more.
...but without rushing...
...while keeping the committee mood in mind...
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood (won't convert for some reason) in mind.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood (won't convert for some reason) in mind.
...and managing to work out all the details.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind, and dying to not work out the NSFW details.
I've been having difficulties lately, but I should have it finished in time,
so I intend to speed things up, but without rushing while keeping the
committee mood in mind, and dying to not work out the NSFW details.
Hey.
Can we talk about your PC for a sec?
It's hard to use other people's computers, Kagami.
A
Fine
Line
A
Fine
Line
I didn't check my inbox for two or three days...
...and now it's megas full!
You don't look like someone who'd get a lot of mail.
Cousin Yui...
Doesn't even bat an eye...
Of course I get mail.
Maybe it's 'cause I visit all the right sites...
...but over 90% of these are junk or spam.
It's hard for me to respond...
...so don't admit those things to a cop, okay?
Still, I've been thinking...
It's impressive how they can come up with all these interesting titles.
I'm Minoru
Are you free today?
Are you free tomorrow?
Are you free the day after tomorrow?
Are you free the day after tomorro...
When are you free?
Am I annoying?
You're not looking for me?
I made a deposit!
Just kidding
Are you free tomorrow?
Acknowledge me!
Ah, I want to go to Panama
My name is Yoshiko.
Please listen to my request.
That's true.
Preparing to copy files
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
2 Hours remaining
90 Minutes remaining
58 Minutes remaining
It's going pretty fast.
Maybe it'll finish sooner than expected.
Antenna Hair
Ponytail
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
41 Minutes remaining
38 Minutes remaining
Copying from "Tsundere" to "Images"
60 Minutes remaining
It happens every time...
The way it goes up and down makes it useless!
Guess I'll have a cup of ramen for a snack.
Played me like a fool...
Hello.
Welcome.
I heard Konata and Yutaka are sick?
Whew...
You okay, Yutaka?
This hasn't happened in a while.
Yo, Konata!
You ok—
Cousin Yui.
Welcome!
You don't have the strength to go to class...
...but you have enough to play games.
Well...
You know...
You should understand, Cousin Yui.
Hello!
Minami and friends.
You came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed...
...but this is the first time she's had so much energy.
I really appreciate it, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school...
Maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you.
She must be having so much fun at school.
You know how they say that sickness comes from the mind.
And it looks like people forget they're sick when they're having fun.
Hello!
Minami and friends.
You came to visit.
Thanks!
She's stuck in bed...
...but this is the first time she's had so much energy.
I really appreciate it, Minami-chan.
No.
I didn't do anything...
She had some close friends back in middle school...
Maybe you two just have good chemistry.
She's always talking about you.
She must be having so much fun at school.
Minami-chan, Tamura-san, and Patty-chan.
Welcome.
Are you okay?
Get well soon!
But...
I wonder why I'm so weak...
I don't like how I make other people worry.
Nah.
That ends up making people want to protect you.
Well, it may sound good in theory...
...but it's usually hard on the person.
You could say that...
...it's like how people who actually have little sisters...
...don't feel the charm of little sisters.
That's it!
Here it comes!
The normal folks are shunning us!
So this is the "no idea what you're talking about" aura!
It can't be helped!
We're outlaws!
Speaking of weaknesses...
...you're sensitive about how you have no breasts, Minami-chan?
Really?
U-Um, well...
They say that they get bigger if you massage them, right?
I've heard about that.
I-Is it really okay...
...Minami-chan?
You're the only one...
...I can ask to do this...
I-I'm going to touch you...
Control yourself...
Control yourself, girl!
So you're a member of that circle.
Yes.
I participated in the last Summer Comiket.
I have a few of your books.
Man...
That's very kind of you.
Really.
I want to see the manga you draw, Tamura-san.
Let me read some, Big Sister.
Sure thi—
I-I don't think that's...
Nah, Hiyorin.
Doujin works are meant to be seen.
Please have mercy!
Not to the normal people!
That's bad manners, Hiyorin.
Anyone but them!
That's incredible.
Then let's go over the answers.
Xylitol gum...
Yes.
Has the ability to reduce cavities.
That's because...
When Xylitol...
...is absorbed by bacteria...
...the bacteria's...
...ATP...
...is depleted and at the same time...
...the bacteria in the cavity...
...is broken down.
If they're so good for your teeth...
...I'll give it a try.
I was chewing gum to help my teeth...
...and a filling fell out.
Now I have to visit the dentist...
The industrious yet slightly unlucky Miyuki-san turns me on.
There, there.
And so...
...Miyuki-san was crying today.
Turned me on.
R-Really...
That's what Big Sister said.
So that's why Miyuki-san looked so down.
I feel bad for this Miyuki-san...
...but I'm going to use that material!
Well...
I haven't been able to come up with ideas...
How do you come up with ideas for manga?
There really isn't a single method to it...
...but I use a lot of stuff from personal experience.
P-Personal experience...?
You read them, didn't you?!
Um, well...
Well...
After I begged her not to show you...
S-Sorry...
Those aren't based on personal experience...
B-But there were a lot of good stories...
...that I really enjoyed.
Thanks...
I think it's called déjà vu.
I felt like I'd experienced some parts.
I would also like to read them.
Sorry!
So sorry...
That was probably the one based on you two...
Teacher, good morning.
What's wrong, Izumi?
Up all night playing games again?
Or watching late-night anime?
Man...
They sure air a lot more late-night anime these days.
Great time to be alive...
Can't you just lie and say you were studying?
Really...
I was considering splurging on a DVD recorder or something.
Nah.
Don't do it.
You'll never get around to watching it.
Like how games pile up, huh?
What are you talking about?!
Hey!
Cut that out!
That's not funny!
Just so you know...
...it's none of my business what happens!
Hello?
You didn't hang up just now, did you?
Well...
I had three bars, but I still got cut off...
Well, I guess I was a little immature there.
Sorry.
It's not like I hung up on you.
Machida Dentistry
I've returned to this place again...
Okay...
Let's see which one fell out.
We can just stick it back in.
It'll be over soon.
But you've got another cavity developing in the back...
...so let's start treating that.
What's wrong?
I just realized that...
...strawberries smell like shortcake!
Er, don't you mean shortcake smells like strawberries?
Since it has strawberries inside.
H-H-Huh?
Well...
People mix stuff up like that every now and then.
Uncle.
Big Sister.
Good morning!
Yu-chan, good morning!
Today's Bow-Wow.
So many animals!
They're doing a special on pets.
First, we have...
...a Welsh corgi, Ku-chan.
It's a corgi!
So cute!
The owner's not too bad either.
She scores high for the thigh-highs.
And she has a nicely balanced absolute territory.
She'd look good in a gothic maid outfit.
Next, we have the Siberian husky, Silviana-chan.
It's a husky!
You don't see many of them these days.
I really like them.
This girl's gotta be a tsundere!
I'd hit it.
Every girl with pigtails looks like a tsundere.
So you also play games, Kusakabe.
I like them, but I suck.
Wanna play a bit?
You're good, Hiiragi.
Wow!
Whoa, what was that?
Look!
Isn't Hiiragi amazing?
She really is.
Is this for real?!
When I see how much fun she's having...
Out of my league!
...I feel like a loser for caring so much about winning.
Total classic, right?
You go for the stink, huh?
Patricia-san.
Hello.
You've been visiting a lot recently.
Patty's a studious foreign student.
Which is why I've been teaching her about the soul of Japanese culture every day.
The stuff you teach her...
...is only a tiny fraction of Japanese culture.
Geeks are the pride of Japanese culture!
My critical mission is...
...to absorb as much as I can...
...and take it back to America!
That's right!
I admire your passion...
Say, Patricia-san...
What kind of music do you listen to?
Let's see...
Orange Ran**.
Chemis***.
Suneoha**.
Porno Graffi**.
L'Arc~en~Ci**.
*inn.
Night****.
And many others.
I'm listening to many different Japanese artists!
That's a surprise.
But you know...
They all did anime songs, right?
Man.
You're so sharp, Konata.
And you only listen to their anime songs, right?
I'd like a maid.
A maid.
A maid, huh?
You live by yourself instead of in a dorm?
Yes.
I'm so busy with cooking, cleaning, manga, and anime!
I guess it'd be hard if you're not used to it...
You'd want to hire a housekeeper.
No, no.
Not a housekeeper.
A maid.
Aren't they the same thing?
Geez!
They're totally different!
What do they teach you in this country?!
Um...
Isn't your impression of Japan a little off?
I-I can't let you have this.
It's fried.
He won't give up because he knows you're soft.
It's hopeless.
Come here, I'll give you this.
Eat slowly now.
But now I feel a little lonely.
The class thinks that she's quiet and scary...
...but she's really kind, calm, and cool!
She's really admired by Kobayakawa-san, a relative of Izumi-san.
My...
Is that so?
Minami-chan!
Circular notice!
Minami-chan is calm and cool, huh?
Which reminds me...
Izumi-san also said...
She looks all cool and flawless...
...but when you see her with
Yu-chan, you can tell she's a good person.
That's what she said.
I'm sorry.
This is on sale...
...so it's limited to one per customer.
My...
Minami-chan is cool and flawless.
Also...
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san...
Minami-chan looks like she can do everything quickly to perfection.
Minami-chan looks like...
...she could do anything.
I admire how she's so cool!
Minami-san...
...is also admired by...
...Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san.
Mom?
The item you wanted is limited to one per customer.
Oh?
Oh...
Minami-chan does everything quickly to perfection...
Yo!
Ho!
Welcome!
What'cha watching?
A mecha anime I rented.
Sure looks cool.
You still like this stuff, huh?
I'm not really interested in mecha.
You're not interested in mecha?
So why are you watching?
In order to grab a wider audience...
...recent mecha anime almost always...
...features a cute boy or girl.
Can you really call that a mecha anime?
Okay?
Hiiragi?
Got it?
It's a promise!
I'm counting on you tomorrow!
Yeah, yeah.
I'll take care of it.
Come on, Misa-chan.
Hiiragi-chan said okay.
You shouldn't keep bothering her.
But based on past experience...
People who say they'll take care of it never intend to.
Bah.
She's sharp about the oddest things...
Kagami the Great!
Let's stop by Gamers on the way home!
I don't need to buy anything...
..and I have something to do, so I'll pass.
C'mon...
Just for a bit...
No!
C'mon...
Don't play with my hair.
Besides...
You have bookstores in your town, don't you?
You know how once you've gone to a specialty store...
...a normal bookstore feels lacking in some way?
They might not have everything you want.
That's 'cause the stuff you want is too unique.
So?
What are you getting?
I'm getting this today!
You sure watch a lot of stuff...
I haven't watched the anime.
But the second I saw this cover...
...I felt a connection somehow.
It's been on my mind for a while.
I don't get it.
But you know...
I finally understand the concept of buying albums for their cover.
You know?
You choose light novels based on their cover, right?
Well, I can't deny it...
When it turns out to be good...
...you feel like you got a great deal.
And if it's not good...
...you don't regret it since you just bought it on a whim.
In other words...
...a once-in-a-lifetime encounter!
You might think that you're making sense there...
...but that's a stretch.
Let's take it easy.
Is this another once-in-a-lifetime encounter?
That was grandiose.
Cover your face.
Well...
You can't really control when you sneeze.
This is the first time I've heard
someone actually go achoo when they sneeze.
For some reason...
There's a world of difference between us after one sneeze...
No fair!
It's no fair how cute your sneeze is!
Don't tease her.
After a round, it actually smells good now.
But it's already over.
You two sure are close.
Do you guys ever fight?
Sure have!
Believe it or not...
...Ayano's really scary when she's mad.
It's true that some people are like that!
Geez...
Even Hiiragi-chan says so...
By the way...
You're always scary, Hiiragi.
So that's...
...my position in life?
Minami-chan runs the same time as you in the 100-meter dash.
Really...
But...
I bet if we actually raced...
...I'd win by the difference in our chests!
As if!
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
Smo――――oth
Fl――――at
Smooth and Flat Girls
W-Wouldn't Minami-chan win because of her height?
Flat chest...
Everyone just ignored that, huh?
Don't you agree, Hiiragi?
Isn't it fun, Hiiragi?
What do you think, Hiiragi?
Misa-chan's "don't respond to everything with a mmm..."
...and Hiiragi-chan's "don't talk to me when I'm reading..."
...are really electrifying the air.
Man...
The characters in Japanese anime and games really turn me on.
Yep.
Huh?
Isn't this image bugged?
That's okay.
This is how it's supposed to look.
But it's still pretty naughty...
What kind of game are you playing there, high schoolers?
What are you all doing?
Yu-chan doesn't need to know!
It's done.
I haven't written a long blog entry in a while.
And submit...
This page cannot be displayed
B-Back!
Back!
Warning: Page has expired
Hey there!
I'm not gonna read you the riot act...
Depressed.
It doesn't matter what's happened...
The two of you...
You know?
Worked together to build this corner up from nothing, right?
And look at this.
Why destroy it all at the end?
Disappointed.
I've done some things to make people call me dark and gloomy...
...but I've never had to mediate a pathetic fight like this!
Understand?
If we don't resolve this immediately, boys and girls...
...it's gonna make me look bad, too.
Yeah, Shiraishi?
I-I'm terribly sorry.
Gotouther-sama.
What do you think, Akira?
I'm sorry, Goto—
I'm sorry, Gotouther-sama!
In that case...
Why don't you just kiss and make up?
Okay?
One more episode.
Why don't you find your original
conviction and finish Lucky Channel?
Well?
How does that sound?
Underst—
Louder!
Understood!
Okay.
That's that.
I'll let you two handle the rest.
Do your best to survive in the anime industry.
Then I'll go home first.
I'll talk to the producer.
Call me if anything else happens.
I could lend you some help, if you want.
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
Shut up already!
Hey, people!
Can't you do a proper job on the last one?!
Are you listening?
Hey!
Forget it.
I'll do it myself!
Next time:
TBA
TBA.
Wait, what?
They didn't name it yet?!