So Ra No Wo To
...is how we'll do it.
Roger that.
We'll begin the mission-
Heading out, Kana-chan?
Good morning!
She's off to use her first paycheck.
Not all of it.
I'm sending some home, and I wanted
to send a present along with it, and...
A little present for yourself, too?
Yup!
You were a trainee for the first month,
so you didn't get paid a thing.
Must be nice, huh?
But I'm surprised.
I'd heard that we're usually paid late,
and that it's normally in scrip...
Here you go!
Thank you!
I didn't think I'd get real money.
Of course, you do.
That's why we have our other jobs-
Kanata, um, well...
There's a market in town today!
It's your first time at one, right?
It's the perfect time to use your
first day off and paycheck.
Forget about work and go enjoy yourself.
OK!
Kanata's Day Off - Hair Braiding
OK, see you later!
I told you not to tip her off!
But no one would believe
we get paid on time out here,
in the middle of nowhere!
She believed it, though...
That's part of what makes her Kana-chan.
Yeah.
Not like you two, who immediately wondered
where the money came from.
Right?
Now, then...
Let's forget about our main jobs, too.
Good stuff.
Ain't it?
But there's one problem.
I'm not lowering the price.
Um, excuse me. I was enjoying myself, and...
Looks like you're ready.
Yeah, no problems at all.
We have a problem.
And I've got a suggestion to go with it.
Want to take it?
Give us the details, would you?
This one's cute, too.
You guys are the sellers, then?
I take it you like the goods?
They aren't bad.
But there's a problem.
Oh, my. And what's that?
It'll take lots of work and connections
to sell these.
Enough so that it's not quite
worth our time...
So-
It's not my policy to give discounts.
The price is part of the taste.
No one's asking you to cut the price.
We're taking it all!
Don't even think it!
Go ahead, shoot.
'Course, before ya do,
my gun'll blow a hole straight through
that pretty head of yours.
Then...
Not too swift, are you?
That's what you get for underestimating us.
Good night, children.
I warned you.
Hey, you with them?
Mishio-chan!
Th-The car!
Boss!
Give it up!
But what about the present for the big boss?
Won't do us any good if we're dead!
Boss!
No one told me they were this crazy!
I'm never coming back to this town!
They're gone.
I see.
Then we're done, everyone.
I was scared there.
Looks like we fooled them!
Thank you for your help.
No, we wouldn't stand a chance
against the central area mafia.
You scratch our backs, we'll scratch yours.
But you'll be reimbursing us for our parts
in this little play, yes?
Oh, my. Mikhail-san, you're such a kidder.
Not at all.
I'm not kidding at all.
This is business now.
Shall I pay it?
Were you the ones who crushed their car?
It wasn't you?
What happened?
Someone smashed their car up pretty good.
Inside were all these spoils of war
they bought at the market.
I'll take them
and give you half the profits.
How's that sound?
Then we have a deal.
Indeed.
I guess that play is over.
But I was surprised.
By what?
That you were really into it.
If the military discovered we distilled this,
we'd get a lot more than a court martial.
It's a violation of the monopoly
and tax laws, too.
And at worst, treason.
That's right.
We took this job over from
the last group here.
Rio's never opposed it.
I was a bit surprised, too.
Well, at first I was shocked.
When I learned my mother's
beloved calvados was made here...
Then it may be your mother who
led you to being deployed here.
OK, see you later!
Yumina-oneechan!
I'm done.
See!
It looks wonderful, Seiya-san.
Mishio-san, it's time for their
first visit to the church.
The priest will be there, too.
So at least for today-
No!
Don't cause problems for her, Mishio!
Why not do your hair right?
No!
Never!
Why?
You always tell me to!
Shut up, Seiya!
You mustn't do that, Mishio-san.
Mishio-san!
10 yen 25 sen...
Hey girl, that's dangerous.
Um, excuse me. I was enjoying myself, and...
They're the problem.
They seem to have found
out about the deal.
Are you OK?
Yes.
But anyway, Naomi-san! What should I do?
I've never had enough money
in my wallet to buy it.
If I asked for it, I could buy it, couldn't I?
Hey. What if someone came
and tried to buy it for themselves?
Did someone say they wanted it?
No. It was just an example.
Let me see...
I'd...
I'd tell them that dolphins are very
scary animals that eat people,
so they wouldn't want it!
Ah! You're a genius!
Oh, I'll keep that dolphin
until you say you don't want it anymore,
so think about it in peace.
Then I'll buy a present for
everyone else first.
Let's see... Dad, Mom, Granny and Grandpa,
and then my Grandma and
Grandpa in Waren,
Great-Grannie, and then old
lady Nanae next door too!
Wow! Look at all the stuff they're selling!
Like this?
Sorry...
Mishio-chan?
Shopping?
She says she's looking for a box.
A box?
Did you see one like this anywhere?
Sorry.
Want me to help you look?
What are you doing, Kanata?
I'm buying presents.
I was hoping there would be
something wonderful to send
to my family back home.
But I'm not in a hurry...
No!
What's wrong with her?
I-I don't know about this...
That's a nice shirt, isn't it?
Note: Shirt says "Yoroshiku" (greeting)
written in "gangster/thug" Japanese.
This one's cute, too.
Yumina-san?
Um, Kanata-san, did you see Mishio-san?
A box?
Yes. She said it was important.
I see.
When her mother died, all her
family's property was taken.
A memento of her mother was
one of the items taken.
Every time there's a market,
she thinks she might find it.
I shouldn't have said what I did.
I got paid for the first time yesterday.
And so I told her I was getting
presents to send my family.
That's fine.
I... We are her family now, I think.
If she's still jealous, that just
means I'm not good enough.
Hey, Mom? Which is more important,
me or your box?
You!
Mom...
Mishio-chan...
Mishio-chan!
The famous Treize firecrackers!
Did you hear them pop?
Who wants some?
Onee-chan...
Yumina-oneechan...
Onee-chan!
Mishio-chan!
The car!
I'm sorry I'm not Yumina-san.
Onee-chan!
Yumina-oneechan!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now then...
Um...
O-Oh! What's wrong?
Uh, that car... Was it yours?
Was that you guys?
I'm so sorry!
There's 150 yen in here!
I'll pay you back...
Great work, guys.
You can keep it.
I've already gotten my payment.
N-Naomi-san, that box!
These ideographs mean
"beautiful rice stalk."
Carve them into her seal, and she'll live a
happy life, like a full field of rice.
My...
Miho, you're lucky to have received
such a nice name.
Did you find Mishio-san?
I've done everything I can
think of to be her family,
but I'm not good enough yet.
No, you're doing your best.
Mishio-san!
Wow, you found it!
Take good care of it.
It's an important memory of your mother-
No!
I want you to have this.
Mishio-san was taken in by the church
after she lost her family.
First her father joined the army
and didn't come back...
And her mother?
Her family lived on the Eastern
border of Vingt.
You can't mean...
Yes, the town that was attacked
by the "Invisible Reaper."
And when the two of them came to Seize,
her mother had already taken
ill, and shortly after...
Mom told me...
that she was sorry she couldn't
braid my hair anymore.
And so... And so she told me
to have it braided by the person
who would care for me most.
Braid it for me, Yumina.
Man lives on...
Even if we part with those we love
and suffer terribly because of it,
we live on.
We can live on.
That bravery is a very sad, very dear thing.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Onee-chan.
Everyone's already in there.
OK! I'll join them soon!
You're tired.
Yeah. I wanted to avoid washing my hair,
but it didn't work out that way.
Then... Then... Then I'll dry it for you!
I always wanted to touch it!
So you didn't buy the dolphin?
I thought it was your present to yourself.
Rio-sempai, do you believe in fate?
What's this, all of a sudden?
You know, something happened today
that made me believe in it.
That was enough of a reward for me.
I don't.
I hate things that are decided or
given to you from the beginning.
But yeah...
It's possible that something,
which someone did by mere coincidence,
may go round and round, and eventually
change someone's life in a big way.
If you call that fate, then maybe...
D-flat.
I guess you had a wonderful day, too.
Chirping Crickets - Spirits Down the River
Next time:
Chirping Crickets.
Spirits Down the River.
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.