Fumizuki Academy is...
a prep school that implemented
the world's first special systems.
Well then, please start.
One of them is the Summoner Test War.
It is a battle between classes using
Avatars realized using
state-of-the-art technology.
And the other is classroom equipment
based on the students' performance.
At the end of the first year,
they take a placement test.
Based on the results,
they are divided into 6 levels,
from the top, Class A,
through the bottom, Class F.
So this is the placement test.
It's difficult, as is to be expected...
but I can handle something this difficult.
Hm?
Ah!
Himeji?
Are you all right, Himeji? Hang in there!
If you leave the room during the test,
you'll receive zeroes. Understood?
Hey, Teacher!
What is it, Yoshii?
How can she help it if she's sick?!
Giving her a zero for that is cruel!
--Staying healthy is also...
--Yoshi... i...
You're late, Yoshii!
Ugh! Iron Man!
Not Iron Man! Call me Mr. Nishimura!
Here. You're the last one.
That's the result of the placement test.
You'll belong to that class from today on.
Okay!
Yoshii...
Hm?
I can tell you this now.
While watching you over the last year,
I had a suspicion... that
you might actually be an idiot.
What?
But looking at your test results,
I realized that was my mistake.
I'm sorry, Yoshii. I shouldn't
have doubted you. I was wrong.
You are, beyond any doubt,
the real deal... a genuine idiot!
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
"Episode 1" "Idiots, Classes, and the Summoner Test War"
Fumizuki Academy is...
a prep school that implemented the world's first special systems.
"Try very hard."
Why Class F?
"Akihisa Yoshii"
That's the lowest ranked class.
I was so sure I did okay in the placement test.
I answered at least one
out of every ten questions.
Hm?
Fumizuki Academy is
a prep school that takes pride
in having the latest equipment.
Whoa...
Workstations and reclining chairs...
They're provided with laptops?!
Ah! They've got free drink
fountains and all-you-can-eat snacks?!
I'm jealous of Class A!
Tatami mats? Cushions? Low tables?!
This is the Class F classroom?!
Fumizuki Academy is ruthless.
If you wish to have a better
school life, do better in school.
That is the law of this academy.
Dammit! Is this what you call a social divide?
Yoshii. Please hurry up and take your seat.
Okay.
Where's my seat?
Have a seat wherever you like.
We don't even get assigned seats?!
Teacher, my cushion
has very little cotton in it.
Please bear it.
"Whoosh"
Teacher! The draft is cold.
Please bear it.
Teacher! One of the legs
of my low table got broken.
Please bear it.
Not possible!
I was just kidding.
Yes, Fumizuki Academy is ruthless.
Well, I'm your homeroom teacher, Fukuhara.
I look forward to teaching
you this year, everyon--
I'll go get some tools, so please
study on your own until I'm back.
Seriously, this classroom is terrible.
I have to spend a year in
this place? How depressing.
If you have complaints,
you should've gotten better
scores on the placement test.
"Yuuji Sakamoto"
Yuuji! You're in Class F, too?!
Not just me.
"Minami Shimada"
Hello, hello. I'm in Class F, too.
Shimada... I see... It makes sense
that you'd be in Class F, right?
Are you trying to say I'm an idiot?
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Since you don't have breasts,
my ears are rubbing against your ribs!
It hurts so much worse than norma--
"Kouta Tsuchiya"
I-I can almost see it, but not... not...
I grew up abroad, so I can't read
the questions in Japanese. That's all!
You guys are lively, as usual...
Hideyoshi?
"Hideyoshi Kinoshita"
I'm in Class F, too. Glad to see you here.
Same here. Glad to see you here.
At any rate, just as you'd expect
from the lowest performing class.
As far as the eye can see,
I see only shabby guys.
That includes you, though.
But I'm glad... that the only girl
here is a pretty girl like you, Hideyoshi.
I'm a guy.
I'm the girl.
You don't get it, do you?
Girls are kind and graceful,
and have this soothing aura.
Just looking at them puts our hearts at ease.
Someone like you who's rough,
violent and scary with no breas--
I feel a severe pain in my spine!
Uhm... I'm sorry that I'm late.
I went to the nurse's office
and it took a while, so...
"Mizuki Himeji"
Himeji...
Ah... Yoshii!
Oh... how cute she is.
--Why is someone like her in Class F?
--I'm so glad I'm in Class F!
Yoshii...
What is it... Himeji?
Doesn't it hurt?
Ahh! My spine has never been
bent this way in my entire life!
--Ahhh! If it gets bent further, I'm gonna...
--Almost... Almost...
"Twitch, twitch, twitch..."
Muttsulini!
Hang in there!
L... L...
Don't talk! We'll call a doctor right away!
L... Light blue...
Muttsulini!
--I'm glad that there's another girl in the class.
--Muttsulini! Are you okay?! Your wound isn't deep!
--Seats are not assigned
--so we were told to sit wherever we like.
--Muttsulini! Hang in there!
--Help! Somebody, please help him!
--Okay. Thank you very much.
--Then...
--Help! Somebody, please help him!
--Doctor! Is there a doctor in the house?!
--Is that seat open?
What? Sure, go ahead.
I see. You're in Class F, too, huh?
I'm looking forward to
studying with you, Yoshii...
Are you still sick?
Yeah, a little...
The drafty classroom... Thin cushions...
Old tatami mats with
mold and dust floating about...
It's not a good environment for
someone who's still recuperating, is it?
So, what do you want?
This is what I think. Schools
are a microcosm of society, right?
There shouldn't be discriminatory
inequality among classes like this.
But no matter what we,
the lowest ranked students, say,
it's considered only the grumblings of a loser.
So we should challenge other
classes to a fight fair and square,
and obtain the power and right to
speak first. Then we should cast this issue...
In other words, you wanna improve
our classroom equipment for Himeji, huh?
I'm beating around the
bush because it's embarrassing!
Why do you have to rephrase it bluntly?!
Okay. To tell you the truth,
I was thinking about starting a war, too.
What? You too?
Yeah. I wanted to prove that
academic ability isn't all that matters in life.
And... we do stand a chance of winning.
Do you wanna try, Akihisa?
Yeah. Let's do it! Let's call
for a Summoner Test War!
Everyone, listen! As the Class F Rep,
I'd like to make a proposal.
I'm thinking of having us,
Class F, start a Summoner Test War.
What?!
A Summoner Test War...? Don't tell me...
At Fumizuki Academy,
there's a system called Summoner
Test War, also known as ST War.
With a teacher present,
a student can summon their
Avatar, whose offense power
is based on the student's
performance in that subject.
Students fight using their Avatars.
By defeating a higher-ranked
class, they can exchange
their classroom equipment with
the higher ranked class's equipment.
Everyone, aren't you unhappy
with this shabby classroom?!
Heck yeah we are!
But if we can just win in a ST War,
we can even get our hands on
that gorgeous Class A equipment!
We're the lowest ranked students!
We're at the very bottom of the academy!
We're a group of scum noticed
by no one and below everyone!
In other words, that
means we have nothing to lose!
So why don't we try?! There's no harm!
In addition, we have this guy!
Huh?
Believe it or not, this guy, Akihisa
Yoshii, is a probationary student!
He's a probationary student?!
--I didn't know we had a guy like that in this class.
--Incredible... This is my first time seeing one.
--Purify the room with salt!
--I'm in despair.
Well, I'm not all that special...
What is it, Himeji?
Is a probationary
student really that incredible?
Yeah. It's not like anyone can become one.
It's a special treatment
for a trouble student
whose school performance is bad
and who lacks a desire to learn.
It's also said to be a synonym for "idiot."
It's someone who's completely useless.
Whoa, that's really incredible.
Ah! I wanna crawl under the rug if we had one.
If we win in a ST War, we can say
goodbye to this shabby classroom!
What do you say, everyone?! Do you wanna try?!
Yeah!
Then, to start with, we'll
defeat the next rank up, Class E!
Akihisa! As an ambassador for
Class F, go declare war against Class E.
What? Me?
Normally, a lower-ranked class'
messenger who declares war
is given hell, right?
That's something that
happens in movies and novels.
There's no way they'd do rude things
to an important ambassador, is there?
But...
Akihisa. This is an important
mission that only you can do.
Please just trust me and go.
Okay.
You lied!
I figured as much.
So you expected this?!
One is unfit to be a class rep
if he can't expect that much.
At least try to sound sorry!
Now, we can't go back, Akihisa. Are you ready?
--What?
--This is what you want, right?
Yeah! Bring it on any time!
Oh? This year's Year 2 students
are trying to call for a ST War
on the first day of the first term?
How interesting. Approve it.
Understood.
Now, how will it turn out? We'll see...
"Approved"
"Hasegawa"
"Culture Club Room"
We'll use Mr. Hasegawa as
the attending teacher for the war.
We'll secure him on his
way to Class E for fifth period.
Mr. Hasegawa... Then the subject will be math?
I'm good at math.
We'll use math, the subject
Shimada's good at, as our main strength.
How are you with math, Himeji?
It's not like I'm bad at it, but...
Then, you can fight with me, right?
No, she can't.
Why?
The scores on the last test we took
become our Avatars' offense power.
The test we took last is...
The placement test...
Since I left the room in the middle
of the test, my scores are all zero.
Ah...
But once the ST War starts,
she can take a recovery test.
If she takes that test, she can
participate midway into the war.
Okay.
Do your best.
Okay!
We've secured Mr. Hasegawa!
Start the war! Everyone, start the battle!
Yeah!
Geez... For idiots, they're pretty cocky.
Everyone, time to attack!
Teach Class F a lesson!
Yeah!
Minami Shimada! I'm fighting!
Hideyoshi Kinoshita!
I'm participating in the war!
Kouta Tsuchiya! Ditto!
I approve.
I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
"Name: Minami Shimada"
"Subject: Math" "Score: 89"
Summon!
"Name: Kouta Tsuchiya"
"Subject: Math" "Score: 25"
Summon!
"Name: Hideyoshi Kinoshita"
"Subject: Math" "Score: 76"
Why am I the only one who transformed?
They're coming!
Please be careful. Real humans
can't pass through that area.
If you want to pass through
here, you have to defeat us first.
Yoshiko Mikami, I accept this challenge! Summon!
"Name: Yoshiko Mikami"
"Subject: Math" "Score: 81"
You jerk!
Here's the finishing blow!
That's my line!
Oh no...
When it comes to math,
I won't lose against Class E!
Those who died, meet me
in the remedial classroom!
That's...
Iron Man!
In accordance with the Summoner Test War Rules,
those who died with their score reduced
to zero will be given a remedial class!
Help! I don't wanna take a
remedial class taught by a demon!
If you want to pass through
here, you have to defeat us first.
I see. Then that's what we'll do.
--Summon!
Let's fight!
Humph!
"Replenish Room"
"Recovery Test"
Well then, if you're ready, please start.
What's your strategy, Yuuji?
I don't have any.
What?
It's a power game that depends on force,
so the enemy rushes into the
classroom of the overwhelmed side.
And the class whose rep gets defeated loses.
There's no way we'd be overwhelmed, right?
Trouble! We're gonna be overwhelmed!
What?!
Class E's school
performance is better than ours.
So if we fight in a straightforward way,
it's only a matter of time before we lose.
Oh no!
But they're only Class E after all.
They're not much different from Class F.
It'll take time to overwhelm us.
That time is the key to our victory.
My score is...
As it stands, you'll die.
Step back and go recover your score!
Okay!
I'll take the recovery test!
The score of this test will be your score
when you summon your Avatar next time.
If you get a lower score, your
Avatar will get weaker instead.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Which subject would you like to take?
Math, please.
I have to answer as many
as I can to get a better score!
I can't fight any more.
Muttsulini!
Let's take a strategic withdrawal!
This battle is mine!
Shoot!
Attack them!
Yeah!
Sounds like our line of defense has been broken.
--Summon!
--This is bad, Yuuji!
"Recovery Test"
If it's just numerical formulas,
it's a breeze as I don't have
to be able to read Japanese!
Ah! Kanji! I'll skip this and
move on to the next question.
"Scratch, scratch, scratch..."
"Bam!"
Those who died, meet me
in the remedial classroom!
What should we do, Yuuji?
Are you guys done already?
Looks like this is it for
you, huh? Mr. Class F Rep.
Oh? The Class E Rep herself
marches in here? How confident you are.
The first term just started
and you declared a war already?
Are you an idiot?
It's right after the placement test,
so the difference between us is the
difference between our test scores.
You think you have a chance?
Well, who knows.
Oh I see.
You're an idiot who can't figure even
that out. That's why you're in Class F.
Yuuji, without even a strategy,
there's no way we can defeat
a higher ranked class.
Oh, yeah. Come to think of it,
I did have one strategy.
What?
Don't you get why I have you here?
I see...
Don't tell me he is...
That's right. This student, Akihisa
Yoshii, is a probationary student!
Akihisa! Show them your real power!
Tsk. I guess it can't be helped, huh?
After all, in the end, I'll have
to show off my grand skills, huh?
Summon.
The probationary student's
Avatar has a special ability.
As punishment, he has to
help with the teachers' chores,
so his Avatar can actually touch objects.
And...
--Ow, ow, ow, ow... My head...!
--the Summoner receives the same pain that his Avatar receives.
See, isn't it interesting?
Is that all?
Fine. I'll take care of that small fry first.
Summon!
We won't lose so easily. Let's go!
Ahh! He hit the same spot! It hurts! It hurts!
Just as you'd expect from the
Class E Rep. You're not too bad.
He's such a useless guard.
No... He was very helpful.
Then, as the Rep,
I'll put an end to this myself.
Be prepared. Class E Rep, Hiromi
Nakabayashi! I challenge Yuuji Saka...
Please wait!
Mizuki Himeji! I accept this challenge!
I'm summoning my Avatar! Summon!
Here I come!
What's with that score?!
Her offense power is as high as Class A!
Why is such a student in Class F?!
She's finally here.
Himeji!
Mizuki Himeji...? Don't tell me you are...
Yoshii!
Shimada?
She's really amazing!
Just as you'd expect from her.
She wasn't a Class A candidate for nothing.
That's Himeji's score?!
Fumizuki Academy's tests have
an unlimited number of questions
in a limited time.
So long as you can answer,
your score doesn't have a limit.
Then the strategy you mentioned was...
Buying some time for her to take the test.
I wasn't told such a person is in Class F!
Well then, here I come! I'm sorry.
Oh no...
"Class F Win"
And thus, this Summoner Test War
ended with a victory by Class F.
All right! You're amazing, Himeji!
This is all thanks to your power, Himeji!
Well... Thank you very much.
Now we can exchange our classroom
equipment with Class E's, right?
Though it's just a little,
the environment will be better.
No, we won't exchange our equipment.
What?
We'll keep the same equipment.
Isn't that a nice proposal, Miss Class E Rep?
What...? Why?
Why, Yuuji?! We fought hard and won the war!
Is it settled?
Why are you dressed like that, Hideyoshi?
Oh, I see! You've finally
awakened to your true self, right?!
Akihisa, I'm right here.
What?! Two Hideyoshis?!
That's my older sister.
Hideyoshi is my little twin brother.
I'm Yuuko Kinoshita,
an ambassador from Year 2, Class A.
We, Class A, hereby declare war on you, Class F!
What?!
Why is Class A declaring war on us?!
We won't go easy on you just
because you're the lowest ranked class.
We'll crush you mercilessly, so be prepared.
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
The end of the school day is bliss
If I am to put it into words, "It's really angelic!"
My peace was shattered
by a sudden announcement
Talking about the make up test. "This is Hell!"
While my friends and I were
sharing funny stories, I said,
"There's no way anyone is that stupid"
But the truth is, deep down in my heart
I was shouting, "That was me!"
About that "Monthly Parking"
sign you see in the parking lot
I thought it was the name of a company...
All this time...
Sticking to your idiocy can be cool
Is our common sense nonsense?
We don't need rules in this world
It's dog eat dog food! It's social upheaval!
Look!
The sun that rose from the west is setting
Run home! It's dinner time already.
Let's go home! Let's go home!
Question 2.
Name the plant that has a subterranean
stem that sometimes is edible
and is called "lily" in English.
Yam potato! Potato! Sweet potato!
Please don't just focus on the word "edible."
Next episode! "Lilies, Roses,
and Health and Physical Education!"
This will be on the test.