Yukine-kun? Are you there?
I baked some cookies.
I'll leave them here with
some hot chocolate, okay?
Yukine-kun?
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Damn it.
Borderline!
Why am I acting so paranoid?
This is Yato's fault for using me against my will.
Stop!
Rend!
That's no different from stealing!
Damn it!
God damn it! Hiyori, too!
What the...
That kid...
Chapter
Scary Person
Not here either...
Yukine-kun's been acting really depressed since that night,
and Yato hasn't come for him.
Considering what happened,
I can't really blame him.
Oh! Hiyori-chan!
Ami-chan! Yama-chan!
I know it's a day off, but should you really be wandering around instead of studying?
What about you? You guys have to take entrance exams, too.
Yeah, but you're always asleep during class.
Usually, the whole class gets to move on to the next grade...
...but some fools do get held back, you know.
For your information,
I do study when I'm at home.
Say, have either of you
seen a boy wearing a parka?
He's about this tall.
A boy?
Yeah! He's pretty young, too.
Mrs. Iki! I'm afraid your daughter has been caught in an illicit relationship!
Operative
She's messing around in
the middle of exam season!
Operative
No! Mother! It's not like that!
It's a misunderstanding!
Operative
You seem to have a thing for ugly guys, too!
I bet he's all gross-looking!
Operative
Touno
The Ultimate Wimp!
Just look at your beloved Touno after he lost!
Operative
Touno
The Ultimate Wimp!
Operative
Stop! I was gonna watch
my recording of that tonight!
Introduce us to your boyfriend sometime!
He'd better look like Touno!
Seriously, it's not like that!
Man, that girl needs some divine intervention.
I would like to introduce them to Yato and Yukine-kun some day.
Though they'd probably
forget about them right away.
Plus...
I don't even know Yato that well myself.
Man! That was easy!
I can pretty much do whatever I want!
What the hell, man?!
Yato!
Where'd you get this?
H-Hiyori bought it for me.
Really?
Yukine-kun!
Thank goodness! So you were with Yato!
Hiyori, I hear you bought this for him.
Y-Yeah, that's right!
I bought it for him!
Man, this is why I can't stand kids.
The sky's a nice shade of crimson right now.
Twilight acts as the boundary
between day and night.
Those that inhabit this world fear the darkness and hide from it...
...while those that inhabit the other world
become one with the darkness and run wild.
As the sun sets, that boundary is blurred...
...and the shadows of evening grow ever deeper and darker.
Those that exist in the divide can
easily cross the boundary at this time.
People once said this is the time of the day when monsters come out.
Yukine.
This is now...
...the Fiends' Hour.
Ow...
Wh—
Wh-What's going on?!
Well, speak of the devil.
Looks like we're in serious trouble now.
I've found you, god of calamity.
Bishamon...
Bishamon?!
Yeah. The strongest god of war I know.
A god? Isn't she on your side, then?!
What's she attacking us for?!
I sort of got on her bad side a while back.
She's been out to kill me ever since.
Huh?!
Well then, I want no part of this! You can deal with her yourself!
I'm not sure she's just gonna let you walk away.
She wants revenge.
I'm sure she wants to take
me and my Regalia out.
No way!
It may be a grudge that drives me to slay you,
but regardless, it is my duty
to bring justice to all evil!
Come, Sekki!
Wa—
You won't escape!
B-Bishamon? As in the god
that punishes sinners?!
Revenge against Yato?
Slaying him and his Regalia?
If anything happens to me,
go straight to those two.
Track him, Kazuma.
Understood.
Target traveling northeast.
Distance: 2.1.
1.9.
There aren't many Near Shore denizens in the area, but you should still limit the scale of your attacks.
One Regalia. Abilities unknown.
Slashing is the only thing
he's decent at, anyway.
Pincer attack, Kuraha!
You got it, milady!
I will end this today!
What are you doing?! Hurry!
Before she catches us!
Oh, shut up. It's partly
your fault I'm so tired now!
Huh?!
Quit acting like such a baby.
I-I'm not acting like...
I can tell!
I've been getting pricked nonstop!
Your emotional state affects me too, you know!
Get that through your head!
But she's a god, just like you.
Are you seriously gonna fight against a god?!
She's the one attacking us.
Are you... going to use me to kill her?
Of course!
You are my Regalia!
Everything she has with her—
those weapons, clothes, and that beast—
is a Regalia.
Even that lion's a Regalia?!
Yeah.
Her navigator, Kazuma, is particularly skilled.
He coordinates the other Regalia,
and his guidance is what makes
Bishamon the mightiest god of war of all.
Hey! Where are you going?!
She's gonna spot us!
We can't escape her!
I'm going to take her out here while I still have strength left!
What?! But I don't want to!
It's her!
NORAGAMI
So powerful!
A clean hit would snap Sekki in two!
Catch him, Kinuha!
It grabbed you! It's a Regalia, too?!
Yeah!
Now keep quiet for a bit, Yukine!
Gaiki!
Locking on.
Aiming for cervical vertebrae and left humerus.
Zero point in two, one...
Fire!
Impressive.
Pardon me.
Kinuha!
How dare you!
Never again will I let you kill a Regalia!
Huh?!
You've killed a Regalia before—
I told you to shut up, Yukine!
Just leave me alone already,
you half-naked, jacket-wearing tramp!
You've been stalking me for years!
Your very name is vulgar!
I must eradicate you!
Suki!
It's been dulled?!
Hey! What are you doing, Yukine?!
Damn!
Pi
ping
Hot
Oden
Soba-Dango
Shiruko
Sweet Sake
Kofuku-san!
Oh, you need something, Hiyori-chan?
Hiyorin! Perfect timing!
Tell us, which kind of daifuku bun do you like better, the kind with—
I-It's Yato!
Bishamon attacked him!
Bishamon?
Oh my! Bisha is still after Yato-chan?
Um, she called Yato a "god of calamity."
What does that mean?
A god that causes disaster.
Huh?
I already told you that Yato-chan's
actually a scary god of war, remember?
Yato-chan killed a Regalia a long time ago.
Wait...
Does that mean it was Bishamon's Regalia that Yato killed?
This is between Yato and Bishamon.
It's none of our business.
B-But Yato told me to come to you for help!
Please, help him! Lend him your assistance!
Why are you so desperate?
Oh, do you have a thing for Yato-chan?!
Huh?! N-No, not really!
Is he blackmailing you, then?
Extortion?
Wow, no one trusts him at all!
No, it's about what's happened to my body.
Don't worry, Hiyorin! I'll help you!
Kofuku-san!
I'll take your money offering later!
Huh?
Looks like you got a deal.
Don't come crying to me later.
So, where is Yato?
I don't know.
Wait...
Maybe I do!
Whoa! She has a Cord!
She's a half-Phantom?
All the gods have a nice smell to them.
But each one smells slightly different.
That way!
Yato.
Huh?
Did you really kill that girl's Regalia?
Yeah.
Then it's only natural that she wants revenge.
Why'd you do it?
Because I wanted to.
That's all.
So it's that easy, huh?
What are you talking about?
What about me, then?
Will you kill me if I screw up?
If you don't need me more anymore?
Yeah, even without me,
Yato still has that Regalia named Nora.
You're pricking me again.
Man, will you just grow a pair already?!
Huh?
You've been acting like a real wimp!
I can barely do a thing like this, you pushover!
You hypocrite! You're scared, too!
What?!
Your hands are five times greasier than usual, you sweatbag!
Who the hell are you
calling a "sweatbag"?!
Who do you think, dipshit?!
Takes a dipshit to know a one!
You freaking dipshit!
S-Sekki!
What are you, a walking armory?
Man, you took out this Near Shore life too.
This part of the woods is as good as dead now.
I'm willing to overlook some immorality for the sake of purging evil.
I can tell this "evil" is really
bringing out the best of you.
Look at all that tolerance for immorality.
Are those your last words?
H-Hey! Don't you take that stance!
That thing'll tear right through me!
Yato-chan!
Found you!
Kofuku?!
Kofuku-dono?!
Come, Kokki!
All right, you two!
That's...
Stop! Are you crazy?!
Stop your fighting!
What just happened?!
She blasted open a Vent!
That's why I told her to stop!
Kofuku causes sudden Storms whenever she uses Kokki!
Phantoms are gushing out
from the underworld!
Bishamon-sama! I suggest we retreat!
Don't falter!
Kuraha!
Yato!
Kuraha.
Restraint.
Kinki!
Kazuma! Tend to Kuraha!
How dare you!
Bishamon-sama, we should retreat for now.
Our archenemy's standing right there!
A mere Vent won't keep me from my enemy!
Veena!
If you wish to be food for the Phantoms,
please go right ahead.
But can you really force the same upon the injured Kuraha and the others?!
What?! What is this?!
Hiyori! You sent them here?!
You told me to go to them
if anything happened to you!
Oh... I didn't mean for this to happen!
I never expected I'd run into Bishamon!
Oh, no!
Anyway, you need to hide!
Huh?
And don't call my name.
We can't risk Bishamon finding out
you're connected to me!
Right!
Out of consideration for Kofuku-dono, I'll let you go for today.
But I will kill you next time.
With my own two hands!
Don't get yourself any more blight.
Let's go, Kazuma!
Hiyori-chan!
It's dangerous here!
You need to get out of here, too!
R-Right!
You really did it this time, Kofuku!
Are you impressed?
I'm saying you screwed everything up, you dolt!
You ingrate! My lady saved your sorry ass!
Ow! That hurt, Daikoku!
Shut up!
I heard that the wind really
picked up in the city around sunset.
Some nearby woods were
completely knocked down.
How frightening.
It's no good. I can't cleanse it all.
Yukine... Is this just not
gonna work between us?
Don't look so down, Yato.
You can always use me, you know.
Nora...
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
The sky's a nice shade of crimson right now.
Hiyori. "Crimson" is—
"Crimson" originally referred to the color of a dye made from Kermes vermilio, right?
Uh, right.
On the next Noragami: "Uncertainty & Destiny."
You sure know a lot, Hiyori.
Next Episode
&
Uncertainty
Destiny
This is exam season, after all!