NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Ya...
Yato needs your help!
Yat—
Borderline!
A Borderline?!
Why?! Please let us in!
Daikoku-san! Kofuku-san!
I beg you!
Yato is...
Yato is about to die!
You're the only one allowed inside.
Kofuku, cleanse Hiyori-chan's blight for her.
Right!
This water comes directly from the spring in the garden.
Wash your body with it.
Yato needs it, too!
It's too late. This won't be
able to help Yato-chan now.
Too late? Are you saying...
If Yukki isn't punished soon, Yato will...
Name
Chapter
Kofuku, take over for a bit.
I'm gonna visit some nearby shrines.
Wh-What for? How's Yukine-kun going to be "punished"?
Ablution.
Huh?
An ablution is a ceremony
performed to expel blight.
It requires three Regalia,
so we'll need two more to help me.
You do realize what'll happen
if the ablution fails, right?
I know.
But right now, we just need to get some Regalia here, and fast.
From the looks of it, he probably won't even last the night.
Yukine.
If you move even an inch from where you are, I'll kill you.
Whatever.
It's cold!
Yato might actually die.
And I still don't know exactly how
Yukine-kun's going to be punished.
Someone, please!
Please help them both!
Actually...
Do gods and Regalia...
even have anyone to help them?
Yato-kun?!
Yes.
An ablution...
If you don't do it right,
you'll be eaten by a Phantom!
What?! By a Phantom?!
I had a friend who took part in one.
It was a pretty serious ablution, too.
What happened to her?
I don't know.
I haven't heard from her since.
If you'll allow it,
I can be of assistance.
H-Hold on! What are you saying?!
I was his Regalia, Tomo, at one point.
Thank you, uh...
Mayu.
We just need one more now!
I, Daikoku, greatly appreciate your generous assistance.
I ask that you all not be too concerned.
Worrying would only affect
Michizane-sama's health.
My Lord...
Yato has been corrupted?
What does that fool think he's doing?!
Please!
Would it be possible
to borrow just one Regalia?
I humbly beg of you!
Please!
There's no guarantee that using Regalia can save a master once corruption has set in.
What kind of Regalia stings their master that much in the first place?!
You must slay Yukine, Yato!
Daikoku!
Yeah. Yeah...
What?!
You can't find a third one?
What are we gonna do, Daikoku?!
All I can do for now is keep asking around.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah... Yeah.
I'll call you later.
The only other gods around here are...
Unless we find one...
Unless we find one soon,
Yato-chan's gonna die.
One more...
I need to find one more Regalia!
I'm sure Nora would come and help Yato.
But she'd also...
I can kill anything that
gets in your way, nice and neat.
She'd also... kill Yukine-kun.
In that case...
Bishamon
Should you cross paths with
Veena—Bishamon—again,
just keep your head in
the sand if you value your life.
This is no time to be afraid!
Kazuma-san!
Kazuma-san! Kazuma-san!
Bishamon
Anything in the northeast?
There are currently no signs of an open Vent in the area.
And the southeast?
Nothing to report!
I'll continue to remain alert!
Kazuma-niisama. Um...
There's a girl outside calling your name.
She's been there for a while now.
Is there a problem, Kazuma?
Oh, it's nothing.
Ignore her. She's clearly too ill-mannered to even come in and ask politely.
Okay.
Now, back to your reports!
Kazuma-san! Please!
I need your help!
Kazuma-san! Kazuma-san!
Ka—
You couldn't find anyone?!
You big dummy!
You just didn't look hard enough!
I looked as hard as I could!
No one wants to help the Regalia of a god they've never even heard of.
Please, pull yourself together!
Yato-san! Yato-san!
What are we going to do now?!
Hey! I told you not to move!
Whatever.
Where do you think you're going?
Kazuma?!
Who?
How is Yato?
Hold on, isn't Yato
your group's sworn enemy?
Yes, he is. But I personally owe him.
Plus...
She came begging for help.
Hiyorin?!
I suggest you lecture her later.
I warned her myself, yet she still
showed up at our front door, screaming.
Veena would've attacked her
if she had noticed.
Well, I don't know what
kind of debt you owe him,
but we have the three Regalia
we need to pull this off now.
No, from the looks of it...
We're not in the clear just yet.
Yato, can you hear me?
Revoke Yukine's name and banish him.
You're in grave condition.
At this rate, you won't survive.
Yato!
He won't listen to us.
That's why an ablution is the only option.
What did you do, Yukine?
Nothing really.
Then why did you try to leave just now?
What does it matter?
Are you feeling guilty? Is that why?
You really wanna know?!
I'm just sick and tired of you all!
I said I didn't do anything!
That so?
Then take off your shirt real quick.
Huh? Why should I?!
Just shut up and do it.
What the hell is that?!
Damn! You pricked your master that much?!
Nasty! It's talking!
Are you ready?
Yes.
Get it off! Hurry!
Get it off me!
We now cleanse this spirit
which belongs to the Yato god
and preserve the name bestowed upon it.
What?
With defilement expelled
and avarice removed,
it is a sincere, principled, just soul.
With flesh pared,
may he be cleansed.
NORAGAMI
What's going on?!
This kind of ablution involves cutting flesh.
It's a kind of beating.
One that uses Borderlines.
A beating?!
As former humans, only Regalia can judge the sins of other Regalia.
Let me out! Let me out, damn it!
And once an ablution begins,
the three Regalia mustn't stop.
Not until the Regalia has confessed
and repented every last sin it bears.
Yukine!
What sins have you committed?!
Confess them all!
Shut up! I'm gonna kill you!
But if the Regalia refuses...
Not good! He's transforming into a Phantom!
Don't look!
Stop this! This is cruel!
It's too much!
What did I do to deserve this?!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I'm not the one to blame!
This is what I get...
for wanting some pocket change?
That's right! I swiped stuff!
I stole stuff! I broke stuff!
So what?!
You guys must know how it feels!
We're dead!
But not them...
They get to have it all!
I'm having an argument with my parents.
I had my brother help me!
We're your friends!
A future...
Memories...
Family... Friends...
They get to have it all. Why don't I?
Why can't I have anything?!
Yeah.
I really am all alone.
I have nothing.
Nothing at all.
You really do have pretty eyes.
They're like the fruit of hawthorn plants, swaying in the breeze.
But...
not even birds would eat them.
They're not sweet,
bitter, or even poisonous.
They provide nothing.
They're completely
useless, empty fruit.
No one bothers to pick them,
so they're left all
alone to wilt, wither...
and die.
Poor little boy.
So what if I stole all that stuff?
So what if I broke all that stuff?
Everyone... should just be like me...
and die!
It's no use! If he keeps this up...
Daikoku! Change into
Kokki and slay him!
Quit freaking out, you dumbass!
It'll collapse if I leave now!
Besides, I'd only make
things worse as Kokki!
Try using that head
of yours, Mr. Big Shot!
His mark!
If that gets completely
consumed, it's all over!
It's too early to be calling it quits!
His name...
I need... to call his name...
before it disappears.
There's a reason
I fell for him at first sight!
Before he crosses to the other side...
I need... to call... his name.
Yukine-kun!
Hiyorin!
It's too dangerous! Get back!
Yukine-kun! Don't cross to the other side!
Don't let yourself become a Phantom!
Yato's still here for you, Yukine-kun!
Surely you heard him, too!
He might be a lousy little punk...
but I found and named him!
I'm going to reforge Sekki!
That's the kind of thing a father would say about his son!
Even when...
Even when you kept
betraying and hurting Yato,
he kept on enduring it!
But if you're still going to
betray someone like that...
then we're not friends anymore!
Fr...
Friends...
Yukine!
It's true...
that you can't... interact with
people of the Near Shore...
normally anymore.
But Yukine...
I granted you a person's name!
So...
So live as a person!
Live, Yukine!
I...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I'm the reason Yato's like that!
I stole the money, and I tried to...
f-feel up Hiyori!
I stole the skateboard,
and I broke the windows!
I told lots of lies, too!
I won't do it anymore.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry!
Rest Stop
Yep! You two are A-okay!
I thought I was gonna die back there.
You already are dead.
This is why I hate punishing anyone.
Thanks for helping this dimwit.
I really appreciate it.
I would hope so.
I never thought it'd cause you
this much trouble either, Hiyori.
Yukine, come here.
I'm sorry!
You, too!
I'm sorry, Hiyori!
If...
If she hadn't brought us here,
I probably would've died at the school.
And if she had asked Nora
to be one of the three Regalia,
the unbearable pain might've
led me to use Nora to slay Yukine.
And if she hadn't jumped in
there when she did...
If Hiyori hadn't been there...
She...
saved us!
I'm so glad!
You're both all right!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hiyori.
Thank you.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more
The stew has started to bubble.
Is it ready to eat?
I'll taste it and see for myself.
Munch, munch, munch...
Aw...
I thought for sure the Phantoms were going to gobble him up.
I guess waking you up was
the right choice after all...
Rabou.
The stew has started to bubble.
Is it ready to eat?
I'll taste it and see for myself.
It's ready.
Yato...
Is he truly the Yato,
the former god of calamity?
You can go and see
for yourself, you know.
On the next Noragami:
"Regarded with Hate."
So, it's nice to meet you.
My name is Mayu.
Oh right, we just met.
I'm Daikoku.
I'm Kazuma. Sorry,
but I must be on my way.
As must I.
S-Sure. Later.
Man, those two are surprisingly alike.
Next Episode
Regarded with Hate