That's right, Ginko committed a grave sin.
What Ginko did to her was—
I shan't...
...forgive the bears!
I will exterminate the bears!
From the very beginning, we loathed you,
and from the very beginning, we loved you.
That's why we wanted to become true friends.
We crossed that barrier...
Lily Bear!
Lily Bear Shock!
viens avec moi
Come with me
kasuka ni hibikiwataru kyoukai no chime
The faint tolling of the church bells
inori wo sasage kyou wo uragiru
are another reminder of my unanswered prayers
kurai mori no naka wo samayotte
As I wander a dark forest
danzetsu no kabe ga zangetsu ni naru no
the Severance Barrier gives way to the morning moon
toumei na arashi ni majirazu ni
Don't be swept into the Invisible Storm
amai awai hachimitsu de motto beto beto ni shitara
Flood me with your sweet, light honey and make me all sticky
onegai ii ko ni naru kara atashi wo shounin shite
Please, I'll be a good girl, so approve me
kaze ni matta ehon no page ga
The sight of the wind flipping the pages of a picture book
kage ni natta kioku wo yurasu no
uncovers memories of days long past
zutto
Until you come...
ano basho de matteru kara
I'll be waiting here for you
karappo na sekai no naka
in this empty world
subete kowarechatte mo
even if everything were to crumble around me
azayaka ni mogakinagara
No matter how painful your brilliant writhing may be
jikuu wo yugamasenagara mo
nor how torn the fabric of spacetime may become
mitsukete
make sure you find me
hanabira ga yukkuri to
The flower petals
futari wo tsutsumu yo
will cradle us gently
hoshi no yoru ni
into the starry night
nee
Hey
J'ai besoin de toi
I need you
Hey, isn't this kinda super dangerous?
Another bear appeared on campus yesterday.
But didn't they say it was killed right away?
And it was the same girl who shot it again, right? You know, the one the Invisible Storm marked.
Yeah, but this is super just between us.
I heard that bear is actually still alive.
Welcome to the Door of Friendship, my little dimwit.
Door of Friendship
LOCATION
All of the intruders have been dealt with.
Yurishiro Ginko.
She was the girl Reia gave her
star pendant to on the night of that storm.
What a foolish girl.
Without receiving love, you were plunged into the abyss.
But you only have yourself to blame.
Although you knew Yurigasaki Lulu loved you,
you pretended not to notice.
You were fully prepared to abandon her, and this is the punishment for your sin.
Can you see, Reia?
Before long, your daughter
Tsubaki Kureha will become
my bride-in-a-box.
Today, I shall...
Shock!
Bear Shock!
...eat Tsubaki Kureha. Gyarl!
I...
You're alive, at least for now.
My, you look surprised.
You... I thought you were dead, growl.
As you say, I'm dead. You're the only one who can see me right now.
I am simply the ghost of the lust that lies hidden in your breast.
Does that answer your doubts?
Where are we?
The Door of Friendship.
We're at the middle of the sky that
divides the worlds of Moon and Forest.
The place where true love is tested.
Could you tell me something?
How did you kill Izumino Sumika?
Flashback
Let's meet early in the morning to remake the flower beds.
I'll be there to help, of course.
Thank you, Yurizono-san.
How does that sound, Tsubaki-san?
Oh, sure.
Who's there?!
It was then that I realized.
That I had rivals somewhere in our school to take Tsubaki Kureha,
and that there were other bears posing as humans besides Konomi and myself.
If I didn't make my move,
another bear would get her before me.
And so I did.
Flashback
My home is in this direction.
See you tomorrow.
Izumino-san, I have a
proposition regarding tomorrow.
Why don't we set up a surprise?
A surprise?
I know a place that sells
lily seedlings close to blooming.
We should be able to acquire some today.
Really?
Yes! So why don't we meet up early
tomorrow morning before Tsubaki-san comes
and fill the flowerbed with lilies!
I don't think she would—
Wouldn't it feel simply magical? Tsubaki-san would love it!
I said it was for Tsubaki Kureha.
That said, some girl seemed to know everything.
Come now, be honest with me.
You knew that I was targeting Izumino Sumika.
Flashback
But I had realized as well.
You, too, were secretly following Izumino-san alone.
That flower... do you like it?
Aren't you the transfer student?
Sniff, sniff.
Doesn't it smell pleasant?
Do you like lily flowers too?
These flowers make me reminisce about a precious memory.
A precious memory about a friend I love.
I won't back down on love.
Nobody can take away the love I received.
I-I'm so sorry! I didn't mean
to ramble on to someone I just met.
You were envious of Izumino Sumika.
Kureha's love you so desperately desired has already been given to another girl.
The Morning of that Day
HISTORY
And yet, without even saying a word to your partner,
you approached Izumino Sumika a second time.
Was that to warn her about me?
Yes, that's why I left that morning.
What should I do? I can't believe I lost it again.
Here.
Th-Thank you! You found it!
I'm so glad. This is actually the second time someone's found my barrette.
The first time was the day of the entrance ceremony.
The person who found it was my friend I told you about yesterday.
She found it... for you.
Yeah. This barrette brought me a friend,
as well as love.
It's my precious charm.
Yurishiro-san, thank you again.
I need to leave now or I'll be late for a promise I made.
Wait...
But I was the first person she found, growl...
Yes. If only you had stopped her,
Izumino Sumika would still be alive.
Tsubaki Kureha wouldn't have had to
experience the pain of losing a precious friend.
To me...
Sumika was an intruder.
Intruders are to be excluded.
We must be honest to our desires.
I see. I...
wished for Sumika to die.
Flashback
Good morning, Izumino-san!
Shock!
Bear Shock!
What a beautiful morning.
It's making my stomach rumble with hunger!
You watched silently and let
Izumino Sumika be killed by my assault.
I could've saved her.
But you didn't.
I'm the one who ate her,
but the one who killed her...
...was me.
Yes, in that moment you became a slave to your lust.
You succumbed to your envy and committed a grave sin.
I'm a crimibear, growl.
True, but is there any soul alive who can live without sinning?
Tsubaki Kureha forgot about you as her friend and gave her love to Izumino Sumika.
Shall I teach you something nice?
In this world, it is not friends who you should place your trust in.
It is only me, your lust.
Love is a savage emotion.
It is the desire to control your lover.
It is to become one and absorb the object of your love.
Let me tell you one more thing.
There is one more bear in that school other than us.
She is a very cunning bear.
She made Kureha kill me and coerced Yurigasaki Lulu into betraying you.
Though it pains me to admit it, that she-bear had us dancing on the palm of her hand.
Right now, her eyes are set on Tsubaki Kureha.
If you don't hurry, this time
you truly will lose her forever.
Become one with me,
and put your love to the test!
Bear Dark!
I will eat that girl, growl.
These photos were found in Harishima Kaoru-san's locker after she fell victim to a bear attack.
As you can see, Yurikawa Konomi's
true identity was a bear disguised as a human.
Ooki Chouko
LILY
This is super terrifying.
Bears have masqueraded as humans and crossed the barrier,
and they've been preying on our friends in school one after the other!
Comrades, you must understand by now.
That's right! In this very classroom, there is a bear amongst us!
Bears super stand out from us!
Bears refuse to be stained our color.
Bears are evil who can't read the mood!
Can't read the mood = Evil = Bear
EXCLUSION
They've begun it once again.
Yeah, but look. Tsubaki Kureha's there too.
To think she'd be their friend at this point.
Perhaps they've given up on excluding Tsubaki Kureha.
I wouldn't be so sure.
No matter the circumstances, those girls wish for an evil they can target to exclude.
It matters not whether that target is man or bear.
Their ritual of coming together as one to exclude someone or other
is simply a means to reinforce their invisible bonds.
It won't be long until the climax is reached.
That is sexy.
Shabada—
Shall I add another coin?
Please.
Shabadadu...
Let us conduct the Ritual of Exclusion.
Ritual of Exclusion
EXCLUSION
Please select the bear that is hiding amongst us.
Let's search bear!
Invisible Storm
EXCLUSION
Anyone sheltering the bears is just as guilty!
Yurishiro Ginko
Yurigasaki Lulu
Tell me, Mom.
What should I have done that day?
Flashback
Lulu-chan?
Kurechin, I know.
I know what Ginko did to Sumika-chan.
That's right, Ginko committed a grave sin.
What Ginko did to her was...
let her die!
Is that true?
It's true, growl.
I...
killed Izumino Sumika.
Yurizono Mitsuko was the one who killed Sumika.
I already knew that for sure.
So why did Ginko say that?
What is the truth, and what is a lie?
restricted number
Hello.
Is your love true?
This is a challenge from the
Severance Barrier. Tsubaki Kureha,
if your love is true, then come to the lily garden at once.
The bears are awaiting you.
So that girl... Ginko will be there.
Entrust your body to the bears,
and your love will be approved.
I'm going to go and talk to Ginko.
This time, I'll find out the truth!
To think she would preempt us and summon Tsubaki Kureha with a false call.
Hakonaka Yuriika is unmistakably guilty.
Yeah, but don't forget that she made a contract with us for this very day.
Don't you think she's prepared? Shiny shine!
Everything is at Kumaria-sama's discretion.
That is sexy.
Shabadadu.
Ginko, just what happened to us?
I want to know the truth!
Say, Reia. Do you remember the night of that storm?
I ate you.
I stored you within the box that is myself.
And yet, that did not sate me.
I remained hollow.
It was only natural—you had already given all your love to that girl.
Thus I resolved to wait.
To wait as the girl who took your love from me matured.
Your love slowly began to open its petals inside your daughter.
I waited in my invisible world devoid of color.
I waited, and waited, and continued to wait.
But now, my wait is over.
The flower bloomed. Today, I shall eat your daughter.
I will eat Tsubaki Kureha, gyarl!
Ginko! Where are you?!
That's not her.
That bear isn't Ginko.
Reia, your girl is just like you.
Your eyes, your hair, and your scent.
Now, Tsubaki Kureha! Give me your love!
We will become one!
Accept me, Tsubaki Kureha.
Take my kiss to my bride-in-a-box.
That was super close.
Ooki-san?
The bear is escaping! After it!
That's...!
Yuriika!
Yuriika...
Yuriika! Yuriika!
Reia... you finally found me.
How I've missed you.
Ever since the night of the storm I ate you,
I could think of nothing but this day.
There is something I must return to you.
Inside the box in the very middle is The Moon Girl and The Forest Girl.
It is the ending to the tale you wrote.
The dream of our unfulfilled love.
I could not help but steal it for myself.
Forgive me.
Yes, you're right. It is the fate of those girls.
The future they must fulfill.
Please listen, Reia. I really, truly...
We'll be friends forever, won't we?
Yes, friends forever.
...loved you.
kureta tsuki to nemuru mori wo
The moon darkens over a sleepless forest
danzetsu shita kyoukai nite
At the severed boundary
kami ga shibaru okite yaburi hohoende yo
Bound by laws, you break through them and smile
muge ni naku kage ni se wo muke
You coldly turn your back on the shadows
chi ni ueta ego wo sakenda
and your ego lets out a bloodthirsty shout
kono toumei na arashi no naka de
Within this very invisible storm
afuredasu honey aa sou
Honey begins to overflow
kiba de kiru wo sakitakute
Your fangs yearn to tear through more
hate no kibou no you ni
Just like the final prayer
kimi wa kaze ni kiete shimaisou de
You seem to disappear along with the wind
watashi no naka no moujuu
There exists a beast inside me
juushin wo kamikoroshita
Who has long since devoured my gun
amaku kaoru ai no baretto de shinzou
Aim a sweetly scented love bullet at my heart
nee uchinuite
and pull the trigger
I can't believe Sensei was the bear who killed Mom.
It is the fate of those girls.
The future they must fulfill.
This is mine and Ginko's future.
No... it can't be!
Lily Bear!