Your existence...
I will erase it.
Yes?
I'm here.
Hey, wait!
Are you planning on just cold-heartedly rejecting your friend that came to visit late at night?
I have no friends, so go home!
What?
Open up!
It's the FBI.
You have the right to remain silent.
Stop it!
Okay! Okay I said!
Just give me five minutes. I have to clean my room!
You're planning to hide your perverted books, right?
That's not it!
For now, just wait outsi-
You're a manga artist?
Yeah. Currently my active profession.
I see.
So this is the reason why you keep on ditching, even though you have such integrity...
Pretty interesting.
Don't tell anyone.
Alright, but on one condition...
Condition?
I really don't have any right to talk about my feelings...
Kei?
I have something to say.
Oww~
Is it really that much fun to fool other people?
It's because you said something weird.
When I'm scouting a female lead actress, the success rate is higher this way.
What do you mean by "female lead"?
When will this get interesting?
It's been like this the whole time.
How much of this do I have to watch?
About two hours.
Don't show me things that are boring.
I don't have time for this either.
Which parts were boring?
Where, you say?
The actor is clumsy.
The story is boring.
It felt interesting at first, but...
It gets boring when you start watching it.
Then why did it feel interesting in the beginning?
That's because...
it looked nice on the surface.
The acting was clumsy, but...
It felt somewhat like it was full of energy that it was overwhelming.
You actually have a good eye.
The direction and the script were done by a senpai in the Film Club.
But I did the filming.
Good movie, right?
And so...
It seems that Kyousuke wants to film a new work...
with you as the lead.
Kei-chan...
Will you be in my movie?
The only character that will be introduced will be you, Kei-chan.
It's all right even if you only do it in your spare time.
And I will follow that with my camera.
But I'm... only a beginner when it comes to acting.
That's all right since there's no script.
Kei-chan's moments of life and feelings will be recorded as it is.
My... feelings?
Is it something like a documentary?
No, it's neither a documentary nor a drama.
This is not with any decisions made...
but instead letting it be preserved on film.
What?
Can you do that without envisioning it first?
I don't want to be held down by any preset expectations.
Chasing after ideals... will severely limit what I can do.
Even if nothing good comes out of it, there's no point if it isn't a movie I want to film.
Speaking from a professional's perspective...
creating a work isn't that easy.
Are you saying that it's not possible to make it freely?
It's harder compared to professionals who are sure to get fired.
Getting fired is what professionals fight against.
It's different from the feeling of freedom that one gets even without fighting.
The thing I want to fight against is different!
I want to film without being restricted by the viewers' expectations.
Do you draw only thinking of the readers?
I do it while drawing what I want to draw!
It's just that you have to think of the readers.
Do you film without even thinking of the viewers?
It's okay even if it's just one scene.
It's okay even if it's just one cut.
I want to film something that will touch the souls of the viewers.
And for it to be like that...
it'll be useless if it isn't a scene that touches my soul!
If you say so, then try doing it.
Sure, I'll do it!
Hold on, don't just decide this on your own.
I didn't say that I would be in the movie.
Well, just think about it.
It's useless even if you wait, so please just give up.
Well then, I will wait for a favorable response.
Listen to what other people say!
I wonder what he is planning to accomplish by filming me.
If you are thinking of making an appearance, be careful.
That guy is quick to act on girls.
Oh, so you're worrying about me.
Idiot.
Onii-chan.
Does Miyamura-senpai come over often?
Just only two or three times she has.
Really?
You know, Onii-chan...
Is it possible...
that I'm...
annoying?
Hmm?
Coming by in the morning to wake you...
and nagging you to go to school.
Onii-chan, do you think I'm annoying?
What are you saying?
Why so sudden?
It's not like that.
You don't listen even if I say the right things.
You weren't like that back then.
It's different from back then...
since I'm not a kid anymore.
Onii-chan.
You're becoming an adult too fast.
It's Chihiro.
It's about Renji-kun again...
Chihiro has a friend?
Yeah. It looks like she's been having fun recently.
Maybe... a boyfriend?
She didn't say it that way, but...
If this continues, it might turn out that way.
I see. That's good.
Hey, Onii-chan.
There's a basketball game on Sunday. Will you come and watch?
A game?
This game I'll definitely win.
I want to tell Onii-chan something important.
Something important? What is it?
For now, it's a secret.
I'll say it then.
Hey!
I'll definitely win!
Did you read it? Chihiro's novel.
Yes, it was quite amazing.
How can Chihiro have such...?
To Chihiro, writing is the same as living.
Living?
To transfer the image to a stranger...
the self of the past and the self of the future who are reading it are different people.
Chihiro is connecting the vanishing past with the future through the diary.
It's about how much you accurately transfer your image to another person.
It is same as an author.
Chihiro's ability in writing is on the same level as that of a novelist's.
Aren't those abilities supposed to be unable to improve without the ability to remember?
It might be something that was there already.
Even if she doesn't remember, her body might have possibly learned it.
With the determination prepared for death while trying to communicate...
it is a strength that appears.
Well, as this is how it is, let's hope that it will be finished.
Himura-san, just what are you?
What am I?
Work or everyday life... why are you always at the church?
Because of a person... I'm waiting for...
Waiting for?
I'm not a priest, nor am I a counselor.
But after meeting you, take this advice as a guide.
Don't get too involved with Chihiro.
The girl started to draw.
Books, instruments, paintings...
In one of those things, there were the tools that made the best humans.
But, it didn't go too well.
Many times, I got sick of it.
It didn't really matter even if I got sick of it.
When the seasons change,
you get sick of getting sick of it.
I started drawing again.
I realized that the realistic scenery was directed at myself.
To write what is there would be fine.
For something that's not there...
For humans to write about it...
might be very difficult.
Or so I thought.
Would you like to rest?
Yes.
Is there anything that isn't going well?
Yes, about the castle that the girl lives in...
I can't imagine the storage too well.
The storage?
The supply room.
The storage with the necessary articles.
Also, the book storage where the girl reads to gain knowledge.
And other things such as the scenery of the island...
or the appearance of the wild plants I don't know too well.
Materials are needed.
If there was a library or something...
I see.
One is in Otowa, and there's a library at school as well.
You want to go?
To where?
To school.
So...
What business do you have with me?
I apologize for the previously boring conversation.
Boring conversation?
What was it?
Hirono-senpai and I have known each other since childhood.
Yeah, I know.
Back then, Hirono didn't have any friends.
I couldn't just leave Senpai who was always alone.
And so, I took him to my house.
You suddenly took a boy to your house?
Kei-chan is very bold.
Is changing the subject like Miyamura-senpai's specialty?
I can't really follow serious conversations.
In my room, there were many shoujo manga.
That was the the first source of enjoyment that Hirono-senpai encountered.
Senpai read with much concentration.
But I didn't think he would become a professional.
Hirono-senpai's talent suddenly grew.
And I thought about something.
To watch someone trying their best...
and to only think it is amazing was wrong.
There's no doubt that one who tries his best doesn't acknowledge people who do nothing.
Or at least, I don't think they'll notice them...
So is that the reason why Kei-chan started playing basketball?
Miyamura-senpai said that I picked the wrong place to be honest, right?
For me, Onii-chan is...
Since long ago and even now...
For now and always...
whenever I think of him.
Because my feelings never went astray even up to now.
But even if you say that to me...
Like that.
For you to make it go astray will be fine.
I definitely won't lose to you.
I will erase you from Onii-chan's heart.
I...
from Hirono-kun's heart...
will disappear...
From there, I will start over with Onii-chan.
And with that, farewell to you.
And then, the end.
It will be the end of it.
Disappear...
Disappear again...
Hey, Mom.
Isn't there anyone with a uniform?
Like one that's not needed because they graduated.
Did it tear anywhere?
Not for me, but if there is a girl uniform left...
I'd like for you to ask around in your cooking class.
Can you?
For Chihiro-chan right?
Everyone keeps their used ones, so it shouldn't be a problem.
Really?
Now that you mention it, if it's about uniforms, Kuze-san also has them.
The ones I'm talking about are girls' uniforms.
That's right. For girls.
But why... does Kuze-san have them?
Ah, I have it.
Where did I put it?
It's okay if you don't answer, but...
Why does Kuze-san have such a thing?
You're male too.
In other words it's a memento, and right now dress when it's important and leave out only half.
Although you said it very implicitly, I get it, so it's okay now.
What are you talking about?
You're having Chihiro-chan wear it!
Please don't get any weird ideas!
Umm, so what are you talking about?
Will this size be okay?
Would you like to try it?
Size? You have more than one?
A few.
You're hopeless.
Now that I think about it...
Why does my mother know that Kuze-san had girls' uniforms?
I thought they were cute; I really wished that she would wear one.
What did you request to another person's wife?!
Umm, a moment please?
Does it not seem to be the right size?
The size seems fine, but...
Isn't it the wrong category?
Kuze-san, this is...
When you say uniform, it's without a doubt this.
You're really hopeless...
Um... I finished changing.
Otowa's school uniform, right?
Yes.
The same as Onee-chan right?
Yes, that's right.
How is it?
It fits you really well, Chihiro.
Yes.
Let's go to school tomorrow with that.
What's wrong?
Well, can't we go right now?
Chihiro...
Today, I put spirit into it.
The Miyako Special. Rice topped with barbecued eel.
The eel is wasting time?
Yeah, yeah, being free after getting promoted...
Would an eel be loitering around?!
Rice topped with barbecued eel.
Say, Hirono-kun...
Do you have work on weekends?
On Sunday, let's go somewhere to play.
During break, I need to prepare for the next deadline.
There is no time to play.
Liar.
I know... that there is a basketball game... right?
It's not a lie. It's just that I forgot about it.
Then you are going.
I really didn't promise to go and...
Really?
Then, promise with me.
On Sunday, let's go on a date.
Well, I said that on breaks...
You can't?
Well...
Lets go... together.
Kei-chan!
Don't be so disappointed.
There's still next time.
That's not it.
It's not like that.
I said that if you filmed me without my consent, that I'd use my right hand, didn't I?
Yeah, it's okay to hit me as you see fit.
There is a moment that can only be filmed now.
If you miss it, you can't turn back.
You can't get it back.
I want to film those unaffected things.
For that reason,
I take action despite the consequences.
Even if you take action, if you fail that will be the end.
It's not the end.
If you don't give up, there is no end.
Time and time again, I'll keep trying.
Where's Kei?!
Onii-chan, why...?
I called him.
Are you okay?
Some light anemia with dizziness.
And also there seemed to be a injury to the knee from the fall.
Onii-chan...
You're an idiot.
I said it's fine. It's embarrassing, so put me down!
Be quiet and stop moving around.
Seriously, doing such stupid things...
Why do you keep on saying "stupid, stupid"?
To do it to the point of collapsing is stupid.
I just took a slight fall.
It doesn't matter, so stop moving.
Don't push yourself.
I did no such thing.
You're always pushing yourself.
That's the same as Onii-chan back then.
It's okay if it's me.
How is that so?
Onii-chan... is wearing nice clothes.
You had a date with Miyamura-senpai.
I forgot about it.
Is that all right?
Idiot. There's no way that I can leave you alone.
Should I give her a call?
Aw crap, I forgot my cell phone.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Now, didn't you say that you had something to tell me after the game was over?
It's okay now.
School...
It's so nerve-racking.
It's all right. If you just walk casually, no one will notice.
How do I usually walk?
There's the scent of books.
Thank you.
Thank you, Renji-kun.
The things I want to convey are not words, but...
myself.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
I...
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?