Pardon me!
Have you seen this man?
His name is Kanata...
Pardon!
Would you happen to know this man?
Thank you very much!
Heeeeey!
Find any leads?
No luck today.
Same here.
Haruka, could we search a bit further away?
Yeah! Let's keep at it until curfew!
Kanata...
Let's go!
I-I'm sorry!
Why, if it isn't Haruka.
Mr. Nishikido!
Bonjour!
Out on a stroll?
I'm terribly sorry for what I did before!
Hm? Did what now?
A-Anyway, we're looking for someone...
Isn't that...
Have you seen him?
Welcome.
Ka...
Kanata!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Kanata, you're safe!
Brother!
I missed you...
Oh, I missed you so!
Prince Kanata!
I'm sorry, but...
who are you girls?
Do you know who I am?
Kanata...
It seems he's lost his memories.
We Finally Meet!
Kanata and His Lost Memories!
There's no doubt.
He's Prince Kanata!
It was about two weeks ago...
I happened to find him collapsed on the shore.
Are you okay?
Where am I?
Dreamy Shore.
And where did you come from?
Where? Where did I come from?
What?
Who... am I?
I still can't remember, even now.
Amnesia...
No way...
And he's been here the whole time?
Yes. I figured I ought to tend to his wounds.
Hm?
A violin?
You know what those are?
Feel free to hold it if you'd like.
He handled the violin like it was second nature.
I thought having him hold the instrument might jog his memory,
but I suppose I can rest easy
now that he's found his sister.
You're my...
Sir, could we speak to him alone for a bit?
I'm a prince?
Oui! You are Prince Hope Grand Kanata!
You're the prince of our homeland, Hope Kingdom!
And...
I'm your younger sister, Princess Hope Delight Towa.
A prince, a sister, and the legendary Precure Warriors...
Ouioui!
Sorry, this is all a bit much to believe...
I know!
Seeing the real deal might get the gears turning!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
Well? Huh?
This is a Precure?
How pretty...
Th-That wasn't the point!
Geez...
Then how about this?
The Princess Palace!
It used to be the Hope Kingdom Castle!
This was where you were born and raised!
Here?
Me?
You're just confusing the guy.
I understand that you all possess a mysterious power.
But... sorry, it's still hard to accept.
Prince Kanata!
Did you really forget everything?!
How tragic...
No luck, huh?
But he can talk to Perf without freaking out!
There may still be hope.
Yeah, totally!
Towa, you've come back through worse, right?
That's it!
Remember, Brother.
You once used this song to reawaken my own lost memories.
It sounds... somewhat familiar.
Please play it!
Sorry... I just don't know it.
It can't be!
Even this didn't work?
There has to be something else we can do.
Hmm... perhaps a visit to a place he remembers?
Easier said than done.
We can't go to Hope Kingdom.
Where else can we go?
Prince Kanata's never been to this world!
So I'm afraid...
There is one!
There is a place!
How are the seeds growing?
Just fine.
Stop and Freeze go out to gather additional despair as well.
Seeds? What seeds?
You'll see.
Shut, be quiet and follow Close's command.
Understood?
Yes!
But now that Dyspear is back,
where does that gathered despair even go?
Catch me if you can!
Wait!
It's a splendid place.
Kanata, this is where I first met you.
Huh?
I was crying at the time.
When other kids made fun of my dream to become a princess...
that's when you appeared, Kanata.
You can.
Is it your dream to become a princess?
Huh?
Yeah...
Then you can.
Really?
Dreams are powerful things.
I'm certain your dream will come true if you hold it dear.
Kanata!
Do you really not remember it?
Sorry...
That was notre last chance...
Oh...
It figures, right?
I mean, not even Towa's violin worked, right?
Sorry for dragging you all this way...
Don't sweat it!
You never know 'til you try.
Why not take a break and stop by your store on the way home?
Yeah, let's get some dorayaki!
Sure!
I'm... terribly sorry.
She's cute...
Her name's Perf.
Play with us, Mister!
Me?
Let's join them.
You look like a prince!
How?
How could this be?
I thought I finally had my chance to apologize and thank my brother...
Towa...
Haruka,
I shall not give up.
I will bring my brother back, no matter what I must do.
Yeah, but...
do you think...
we're making it harder on him?
I mean, every time we tell him something new,
he looks like he's in pain...
The usual, shall we?
The usual, we shall.
Dysdark!
That's them?
So many young dreams...
So little time.
Children, run!
Princess!
Don't!
Thank goodness...
Stop!
Freeze!
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to become a princess!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Just wait!
We shall save you!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
Dyspairvil!
Punching with rings on?
How brutish!
Dyspair...
Viiil!
How dare they exploit a child's dream!
They shan't go unpunished!
Dyspair!
Viiiil!
Over here!
Dyspairvil!
Too bad. This way!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Dyspair? Dyspair?
Up here!
Dyspair?
Dyspairviiiil!
Those are the Princess Precures!
Precure?
Dyspairviiiiil!
Girls!
Cure Flora...
Kanata...
Dyspair!
You saved me here once before...
You gave my dream support!
Dyspair...
Vil!
Kanata, it's because of you that I still aim to become a princess!
That I can protect this girl's dream!
Thank you, Kanata!
I'm so glad we met!
Dyspairviiiiil!
Dyspairvil!
Luna!
Precure!
Frozen Ripple!
Scarlet Spark!
Dyspair!
Dyspairviiil!
Lily!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Dyspairviiiiiiiil!
Do it now!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
The dream did not end.
We failed to end it.
However...
you despaired.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Huh?
Here.
Thanks!
You're just like us.
Our dreams are to become princesses, too!
Really?
Let's chase them together!
Okay!
From now on, let's be friends!
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
The legendary princesses, defenders of dreams...
Prince Kanata, did you remember something?
It's okay. You don't have to remember right away.
Wha?
B-But...
Haruka, what are you saying?!
Sorry.
I know this has been hard on you, Towa,
but even if he doesn't remember a thing,
he's still Kanata.
For now, showing him who we are is enough.
As we get to know each other...
then I'm sure the day will come.
Maybe, you know?
I-I see...
But...
But please...
Please, may I still call you my brother?
Sure.
Go ahead, Towa.
Let's start at square one.
From now on, let's be friends.
Thank you, Haruka.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Who was that woman we met by the sea?
Go! Princess Precure:
Tides of the Heart!
What Minami Fights to Protect!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!