Five mil...
They messed up my turf and stole five mil.
We can't let them get away with that, right?
Catch the man who's responsible for this and bring him to me without fail.
If push comes to shove... go ahead and kill him.
Disguise
Thanks, Reiji.
It's been my dream for a long time...
to build a mountain of hamburgers in front of me like this
and eat heartily.
Yeah...
So Cal, about what we were talking about earlier...
Did you see Judy's shooter?
I've been thinking about... how to go about it.
How?
Are you really going to avenge Judy for me? How?
They're the kind who fire away with machine guns, you know?
You can't trust me?
No... because you don't look strong.
I see, you can't trust me, huh?
But you don't have to worry. I'm not the one who'll do the job.
I'm going to ask my friend to do it.
Your friend?
Yeah.
You have a friend like that?
I may not look it but I've got lots of contacts.
Once I know the shooter's looks and clothes,
my friend will find and kill him.
So tell me about the shooter.
I want to see it to the end.
What?
I want to see your friend avenge Judy with my own eyes!
Say, Reiji, please let me see that friend of yours.
No.
Why? I'll ask your friend. Please take me with you.
Say yes.
Ordinary people like you can't set foot in that world.
But...
No means no.
I'm sorry, Cal... But...
Okay, okay. You win.
I'll ask my friend if they're okay with it.
Really?
Yeah, but...
Then I'll tell you once my meeting with your friend is decided.
But it's not like I can get in touch with people like that right away.
I'll try contacting my friend tonight.
Let's talk about it again tomorrow.
Hmm, tomorrow?
Is there a problem?
Since we were behind in our rent for months,
I got kicked out this morning. Will you let me stay with you tonight?
So how's it going, Lizzie?
Is the investigation going smoothly?
Phantom is checking up on that girl.
And I'm investigating the matter myself, too.
Well, give me a little more time.
I hope to hear good news.
Who on earth hindered our deal?
The Godo Family is absolutely vital to solidify my position in Inferno.
I can't let something like this get in my way.
Whoa... So this is your place...
It seems kinda... lonely.
This is more than enough to live.
It's empty.
Hm?
What're you doing?
I shouldn't waste the leftover hamburgers, right?
Don't tell me you'll stay here until you finish them all.
What was that?
Nothing...
The bedroom is this way.
You can use that bed.
Did you use to live with someone?
Why?
Hm... Just a hunch.
I did, a long time ago.
Your girlfriend?
No.
Oh, uhm...
May I use your shower?
So I'll just pretend to be that friend?
Yeah, would you?
Okay. Having you owe me one isn't such a bad deal.
So does she really seem to know something?
Beats me.
What? That doesn't sound very assuring.
Reiji!
Sorry! I forgot to grab a towel.
I'll bring one now.
What?
Well, I find it funny that the notorious Mr. Phantom
is taking orders from a little girl.
Just because you're letting her stay with you, don't do anything stu-
He hung up on me.
What are you doing snooping around in my backyard, Lizzie?
Really?!
Yeah. My friend said yes and will contact me tomorrow.
I'm so glad!
Say, Reiji... Do you have a family?
Family?
They're in heaven.
They are...
Yeah.
Then you're like me.
Are your parents already...
I don't know. I ran away from the worst damn excuse of a father.
And Judy took me in.
If it wasn't for her, I'd have been dead by now.
That's why you two are sisters, huh?
Right. She's the only family I got.
But Judy is dead now and...
Sorry.
That's okay.
Now that Judy's dead, what should I do?
Where should I go? What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
I didn't know... what to do, either.
What?
People die in different ways.
There are people who suffer quite a lot.
There are also those who are forgotten with no one crying for them.
At least Judy has you crying for her. She's fortunate for that.
You think so?
Yeah.
You really think so?
What should I do?
Where should I go? What should I do?
I don't know what to do.
Is the witness... in there?
What a dull pad you've got, eh, Phantom.
What brought you here?
Don't be so stiff.
I noticed that Lizzie was having some rats snoop around in town
trying to dig something up, so I got her to tell me all sorts of interesting things.
Let me talk to the girl.
I'll make her spit out everything.
Is she in there?
She doesn't know anything.
Out of my way.
An ordinary girl can't see anything in such a dark place.
She's lying about having seen the shooter.
Out of my way.
Out of my way!
Phantom!
Oh?
So you want to protect that girl even if it ends up in bloodshed?
That makes me want to see her even more.
So I was right.
You and Claudia are up to something.
You've got it wrong.
10 o'clock tomorrow.
Come to headquarters.
I'll have you explain all this in front of McGwire.
We'll find out there...
who the traitor is.
Sorry, Phantom. I couldn't keep pretending to know nothing.
Don't worry about it.
But isn't this a problem?
How are you gonna convince them tomorrow?
I'll somehow make it work.
So that girl really doesn't...?
No, she doesn't know anything.
I see.
You don't know anything... Right, Cal?
Tell me your story.
That time...
Judy?
Judy!
The rest is...
Just as I thought...
So you knew I was lying.
The man who came earlier... That's Isaac Wisemel, right?
The leader of the Bloodies.
Yeah.
Why did you protect me?
They all called you Phantom.
I know who that is. Judy's friends told me that
he goes around the country killing gangsters.
You're a real assassin then?
You're an assassin?
Phantom, the assassin.
Yeah... you are right.
Cal...
This is...!
This is the money those yakuza people had.
I counted it. There's five million dollars.
Did you... steal it?
I didn't steal it! Such dirty money!
I didn't use even one cent of it!
I was looking for someone like you...
Someone who'd help me for money.
You're Phantom, right?
Please kill them all. You can have this money.
The guy who came to that alley last night...
The guy who fired a gun there...
The guy who was supposed to receive this money...
Please kill every single one who was involved in Judy's death.
Would you do it?
I'll give you the estimate for my assassination fee.
We'll discuss this tomorrow.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
Same here.
The situation is heading in a bad direction.
We haven't found the shooter.
Only the five mil came rolling in.
If the organization finds out about this money, I can't make any excuses.
Please kill every single one who was involved in Judy's death.
What should I do?
How can I make both Cal and the organization understand?
What's going on, Reiji?
I can't explain it here.
If we talk alone, Wisemel will be suspicious of us again.
I'll explain everything in front of everyone.
Now, explain yourself, Phantom.
Yes. Then first, please let me clear up the misunderstanding.
Oh? Misunderstanding?
It's true that I'm sheltering the girl who's supposedly a witness.
But she's just a family member of the passerby who was dragged into this
and doesn't know anything.
How can you say that for sure?
I'm Phantom. I have skills to deal with that kind of stuff.
That's a stupid excuse.
It sounds like that to me, too.
If there's no evidence, it doesn't mean anything.
Did you use a truth serum on her?
No.
What about recorded data?
None.
In other words, you're telling us to trust you at your word?
Yes.
Why don't you give it up, Phantom.
Ms. McCunnen. Do you have anything to say?
You don't have anything else to say?
I have my reasons for not using a truth serum.
Oh? Is that reason serious enough that you pointed a gun at Isaac?
Yes.
I want to hear it.
It was because I didn't want to destroy her.
Ha! So now you're a humanitarian?
No.
I found a different potential in her.
I didn't want it to be destroyed.
Potential?
That's right. She's got a rare quality.
You can even call it a talent.
An intense motivation to kill...
In a hellish solitude...
A ghost who has nowhere to belong...
Talent... Someone told me a similar thing in the past.
In other words, you're saying that you want to train that girl as an assassin?
Yes.
She'll become skilled enough to become my right hand in the future.
What's the proof of this talent?
My hunch.
Stop screwing with us, you son of a bitch!
This isn't something that can be explained with words...
though it may be hard...
for someone whose sight is clouded by doubts and fears.
Phantom...!
Let me ask you one thing.
You want a new assistant that bad?
Are you saying that you have problems with your current pairing with Lizzie?
Well, it's true that we have lots of problems.
Me teaming up with Phantom is too unnatural.
Phantom is a genius and I'm mediocre.
If there's someone whom he approves as his partner,
I want her to take over my position whatever it takes.
Regarding that prostitute, whose name is Judy Devens or whatever,
who was killed along with the yakuza...
Are you certain that she had nothing to do with this incident?
Yes. She's clean. Totally clean.
I'm sure of it because we investigated thoroughly.
Hmph... What do you say, Isaac?
Are you telling me to accept it, Ray?!
If you can't produce results...
You know the rest, right?
Yes.
Then, we shall see how you do.
That was an interesting act, Reiji.
I won't be deceived. Not me...
you vixen's lap dog!
Sorry.
Don't worry about it. It was my mistake to begin with.
But...
I know...
There's no way that you want to produce more people like you.
You did it in order to protect that girl, right?
But now that you've sold her that much, you'll be held accountable.
I know.
Nothing has been resolved after all.
The shooter...
Five million dollars...
Revenge for Judy...
What should I do?
Next episode
Surveillance
That girl is probably a genius.
But is it okay to make her take the same path as mine?