One day, as the recording
of the new single approached,
Mitsuki was called out by
Dr. Wakaoji.
But this was a trap set by
a tabloid magazine.
It was devised to photograph
a scandal involving Full Moon.
Gosh! It was an important time
before the recording!
But with words of encouragement
from Dr. Wakaoji,
Mitsuki's fears disappeared and
she resonated with an incredible
singing voice at the recording!
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Excuse me...
Huh?! One right now?
Excuse me, are you going to
tell me to pose or anything?
You can do whatever you want,
if you want to move,
you can move.
If you're tired, you can rest!
Hey, is this okay?
It's going to be used
for the CD jacket.
The camera's a disposable one too.
That's probably her vision.
Huh?
Don't you think Mitsuki's natural
charm comes out more this way?
Do you think so?
I don't know.
Nice scent.
Hey, do you know?
The language of flowers for cosmos.
No.
"Young girl's sincerity."
It's perfect for you.
Hey, Takuto.
What?
Do you want to go to the
amusement park or something?
Why?
Mitsuki's photo shoot for
the second CD's jacket is over,
so that means we did good work.
Then why don't you invite her?
Gosh, you don't understand
a girl's heart at all.
A girl's heart?
Indeed, things that change are
a girl's heart and the autumn sky.
What? Is that a haiku?
– We're here.
– Hello!
Hey, I was waiting for all of you.
Come on up, come on up.
Say, guess who I saw?!
What are they doing?
It's probably a study session.
Hey, look, look.
This is so cute.
You're right.
Nice sound.
Yeah, really.
Both of you! Work over here too.
– Okay.
Hey Kumi, if I remember,
you do this one like this?
Yeah, yeah.
Huh? Kumi, don't you do it like this?
– Well, which one is it?!
– Kumi!
Oh?! What, what?
– Jeez!
Kumi, you seem to have no energy.
Do you think so?
Oww!
Sorry, sorry!
It's the usual, Kumi.
Seems like it.
Oh, I can't draw well.
In that case, it's good to
use some picture as a reference.
– How can I do this?
– Oops, a mistake!
Hey! Look at this!
Huh? What?
What? What?
Ta-da! Who is this?
Oh, who is this boy?
So cute.
Hey, the girl next to him is Mitsuki.
You're right!
– Then, this is...
– Who is this boy?
Oh! Well, that is...that is...
– Mitsuki!
Why did it happen like this?
Therefore, Eichi departed for America.
Wonderful!
So that's what happened.
It's a story you can cry about,
no matter how many times
you listen to it.
What's wrong, Takuto?
Is this something that you'd
normally talk about so frankly?!
Huh?
I mean it's not a thing to
chatter about with other people.
Those kinds of precious memories
should be stored
quietly inside your heart!
Don't you think so?
M-Maybe...
Man! I don't understand
a girl's heart!
That's incredible!
How romantic!
It's such a surprise that a girl
like that is in our class.
Oh, my dream,
reach beyond the Pacific Ocean.
Reach beyond!
Wait!
Surely, the ending will be Eichi
mounted on a white horse,
arriving to pick up Mitsuki!
Now Mitsuki, take my hand.
Yes...Eichi...
I wish I could love like that!
Now, now!
Starting today, for one week,
we will start a mini-corner with Full Moon,
who has set the release for
her second CD, "Eternal Snow."
Now, please take it away, Full Moon.
Yes, it's "Full Moon's
Eternal Correspondence!"
That's a title, left as it is.
Yeah...
Now, to the next fax-mail.
It's from radio name, "Girl Sanshiro."
"Hello, Miss Full Moon."
"I have been a big fan of
you since your debut."
Thank you very much.
"To tell you the truth,
I have somebody I like right now."
Wow.
"I was not aware of it until now."
"But recently, I saw his cool appearance
and fell in love with him."
"And I want to confess to him,
but please tell me what I should do."
Well, you know,
in this kind of circumstance...
If you believe...
your feelings will reach...him...
I think...
I'm sorry, I wasn't able
to answer very well,
but please try your best.
Now, I will give my song
as a present to Miss Girl Sanshiro.
This is Full Moon's "Eternal Snow."
Good morning, Kumi.
Oh... G-Good morning!
What's wrong, Kumi?
You've been acting weird
since last time.
Hey! Hey wait, Kumi!
We have school, school!
Please Mitsuki,
come with me a little bit!
Hey Mitsuki, what do you think
"if you believe, your feeling
will reach him" means?
What?
W-Well, Full Moon was saying something
like that on the radio yesterday.
Do you think it means waiting
until the other person realizes?
Or is there an even deeper meaning?
I don't think it has
such a deep meaning!
Huh?
Well, you know, I was also
listening to the radio show.
And that answer by Full Moon
felt like she didn't know
that much about romance.
Do you think so?
Yeah. If she were knowledgeable,
she would have given
better advice, yup!
Really?
Mitsuki, you understand because
you're an expert on romance.
What?!
Hey Mitsuki!
I want you to be my advisor,
as the master of romance!
H-Hey Kumi, you're misunderstanding
something.
I'm not an expert on romance.
Actually, I was the one
who faxed Full Moon yesterday.
What?! Then you're Girl Sanshiro?
Yeah. I've been doing judo
since I was little.
Please! Please give me advice,
I don't have anybody else!
Well, you know... If there's
something that I can do...
Oh my...
I don't know what's gonna happen.
And, who is the other person?
Machida...
So it was Machida.
Until recently...
There!
Ouch!
You dummy!
Shut up, you!
It was like that, but...
Kumi, are you really going
to jump over that?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Just watch and see.
She flew over.
That's incredible, Kumi.
Yeah!
– Kumi!
– Oh!
What do you mean,
"don't worry," dummy?
After that, I was suddenly
conscious of Machida
and I couldn't be around him
the same way anymore.
Kumi...
Yup, yup, I understand.
Hey Mitsuki, what should I do first?
Teach me! Please!
What? Th-That's...
Mitsuki!
Oh yeah! Let's first
do research on Machida!
How are we
going to do research?
Don't worry, leave it to me!
And thus, it will now become
the most suitable season
for studying and sports.
Everybody, please engage in
your interests with your best efforts.
Hey, you!
W-What?!
W-What is it?
I'm doing a program called
"The Rumored Handsome Boy in Town."
Can I interview you?
R-Right now?
Here we go. Let's do this
interview at once.
To be frank...
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have one.
What is your preferred type?
Nothing in particular.
What is your favorite food?
Umm...
It's hamburger. Can I go now?
My homeroom is about to begin.
Yeah, thanks.
See you later, Machida.
No problem... Wait!
How did you know my name?
Sh-She's gone?
Machida doesn't seem to
have a girlfriend.
He doesn't have
a particular type of girl he likes,
and his favorite food is hamburger.
You really are the master of romance.
How did you do the research?
Oh, that's a secret.
And what's next?
Next?
What should I do?
A present.
Make a hamburger-shaped cookie
with a love letter as a present.
How about making a hamburger-shaped
cookie with a love letter as a present?
Love letter?
I've never written one.
Leave it to me!
I'm not involved in this, okay?
Here comes Machida.
Y-Yeah.
Umm... Next is Literature class.
He noticed!
Y-Yeah.
He noticed the love letter!
Yeah...
He's reading it, he's reading it!
What? What happened?
I don't know.
Maybe he thinks that
it's somebody's practical joke.
What?!
What's wrong, Kumi?
But I'm embarrassed!
Don't say a thing like that.
Come on!
I wonder if Machida will come.
It's fine, I'm sure it'll go well.
Okay then, I'll leave now.
What?!
Wait, aren't you going
to stay with me?
Isn't it a problem if I stay with you?
It's not a problem.
Well, maybe it is a problem.
But I'm just uneasy being alone!
Please!
O-Okay.
Mr. Machida, although
from the shadows,
there's something I would like
to say to you.
Therefore, please come to
the back of the gymnasium today.
From a young girl who thinks of you.
It's possible. This weird sentence
would be possible for Koyama.
But if I'm wrong...
Caught you, caught you!
I'm going to be a laughing stock.
I'm going home!
Hey, hey!
Why? Let's wait a little bit longer.
But...
Little bit longer! Okay, Kumi?
Yeah...
Please Takuto!
Bring Machida over.
I know, even I...
But Kumi is serious!
I can't pretend to ignore her!
I was to support Kumi
so her love would come true!
All right, all right.
I won't say this and that anymore,
do your best in your own way.
Thank you!
Then, you'll bring Machida over?
Meroko already went to bring him here.
Wait! Please wait!
Dang it.
Why does it fly away when
there's not even a wind?!
That's because I caught it.
Wait!
Oh?
M-Machida!
Y-You were waiting for me until now.
You think that much of me?
Show your courage...now!
U-U-Umm...Machida...actually...you know...
Sorry, Koyama.
I...didn't realize...
Huh?
I get it.
You didn't have the
courage to say it alone,
so you had Saginomiya...
What?! U-Umm...
But it's wrong to have a girl say it.
As a man, I have to say it himself!
Koyama!
Y-Yes.
If you don't mind,
please go out with me!
First as friends.
W-What is happening?
I told you something like
this was gonna happen!
U-Umm... That's not it, Machida!
It's...
K-Kumi! Wait!
Kumi!
W-What in the world is happening?
Don't you understand?
You made a mistake in
the person you confessed to! Jeez!
Kumi...
Machida misunderstood.
Let's go back and clearly
explain to him, okay?
I can't. I'm not even
on Machida's mind.
That's not true.
It's true! It's so true!
It's because I'm not feminine at all!
I'm rough and my hobby
is judo of all things.
The type of girl that Machida likes
is probably somebody like you!
Sorry. I'm not actually mad at you.
Oh no, it's fine.
But you'll definitely regret it.
Because it happened to me.
When Eichi left for America
I couldn't say it.
"I like you."
I'm really regretting
why I couldn't say that one thing.
You didn't tell him
that you like him?
Didn't I tell you last time?
Oh? Sorry, I wasn't listening carefully.
But, do you now understand?
I'm...not an expert on romance.
You're right.
You don't want to regret it.
Instead of thinking later that
I should have done this at that time...
Maybe it's better to have my say.
Let's go back.
Let's go back and say it clearly.
That you like him.
Okay, it's another fax-mail from
radio name, "Girl Sanshiro,"
who sent us one earlier.
"Hello Miss Full Moon."
"I finally confessed to the boy
that I told you about last time."
That's great.
"There were all kinds of
misunderstandings,"
"but we will be going out,
first as friends."
"Please give me your support."
Of course!
"P.S. I would like to make
a request to my friend"
"who was not able to say 'I like you'"
"to somebody she liked in the past,
but is working hard today."
Okay, here's the request from
Miss Girl Sanshiro.
Here's my "Eternal Snow."
I-Izumi is...
Izumi? Impossible, not that Izumi!
He's appeared in the human world?!
That's the one!
Ordered here by the
Division Chief of Death Spirits!
He's checking up on us to see
if we're doing our job right!
Damn! At such a bad time too!
It's Mitsuki's concert for her new song!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The New Death Spirits,
Izumi and Jonathan"
– Look forward to it!