Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start.
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well, do you have anything
you're doing with all your might?
I'm always in fighting spirits,
but Miss Layla is more amazing than I am.
She is always thinking about
how she can improve herself.
Now, it's our show!
I'll make sure I complete
it by all means. I will! I will!
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
I told you, you're too slow!
Yes. Sorry.
Please, one more time.
Hurry up.
It looks tough.
I know.
All right.
Sorry. I was too early!
One, two, three... One, two, three...
Sorry.
There is less than a week until opening day.
Sora is too afraid of missing the timing.
So, she becomes nervous,
and it makes her miss the timing even more.
"The Amazing Competition Calls Up A Storm."
I don't know what Kalos is thinking.
After all, you and she
are like oil and water.
It won't work out.
He'll do anything in order to
be the topic of conversation.
Aren't you both just being used by him?
In order to make the
show somewhat presentable,
you're the one who has to adjust to her.
Whatever his intention is,
it's nothing to do with me.
Really?
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Sorry.
You fell again.
'Cause I can't adjust the timing.
But if I try to watch Miss Layla's moves,
I fall behind.
I am the one who has
to adjust the timing, but...
Sora!
Yes!
You have a guest.
What? A guest?
Yes?
Whoa...
Whoa!
Miss Layla... Excuse me...
Well, bye, Layla.
Thank you.
Thanks...
Um... I...
I'm going to stay here for a while.
What?
Um...
I asked Ken to videotape this
so I can get a feel for your timing.
I came here so I can study
your rhythms and pauses.
So, please try to learn
my moves and rhythms too.
Your moves and rhythms...
Yes.
She looks so cool.
Yes, she does.
What?
Well,
I just thought you looked cool
even just taking off your jacket.
Give up, I give up...
We eat dinner in the dining hall.
How about you, Miss Layla?
I will have it with you.
Sora!
Let's go to the dining hall!
Why...
Why is Miss Layla...?
Oh, she's going to live here a while.
What?!
Let's go.
If she is going to co-star,
she should have chosen one of us.
Like, if she chose me,
it'd be almost perfect.
Would you mind moving up?
I haven't chosen my stuff yet.
--Bowwow!
--Meow!
Even just walking, Miss Layla looks elegant.
Shall I make you coffee?
Don't worry about it.
Instead, I will borrow your shower.
She said "shower"!
Are you sure?!
Is something wrong?
Oh, well...
It's nothing!
Please take your time.
What a way to treat me!
But, I'm a little different today.
She even said "Don't worry about it"...
Negligee!
Wow!
--Oh! Miss Layla,
--Ro... Ro...
--I don't think a negligee is a good idea.
--Rope...
It's not?
--Anyway, please change.
--Rope! Rope! Rope! On the ropes!
--So, I changed.
--Rope! Rope! Gah.
--Please change into this one!
Why?
When you're in my room,
you must follow my rules, please!
All right.
Oh, Miss Layla, please use my bed.
I'll sleep on the floor.
I said, don't worry about it.
Okay...
Making Miss Layla do something like this...
If I can't adjust my timing after this...
No... I shouldn't think like this.
I have to make sure
I accomplish it by all means.
Even her sleeping face is beautiful...
Fool! When did you...
I'm a little bit different today.
The Tower...
Unexpected things may happen.
Excuse me, but isn't Miss Layla's
visit here itself something unexpected?
That's true.
Fool, please don't wake up Miss Layla.
Miss Layla's moves.
Miss Layla's pauses.
Miss Layla's rhythms.
Quickly... I have to learn it quickly.
--Step in without hesitating!
--They still can't get in
tune when they have to.
--Yes!
--It's not enough!
--They still can't get in tune when they have to.
Yes!
Too late!
Sorry... Oh!
Hey, don't you think those two are
starting to get on the same wavelength?
Sora's trying so hard...
Their timing is starting to synchronize.
I think they'll be fine in the early scenes.
But will they be able to endure
the performance at the climax?
Jump!
Oh, we're too close...
I think we'll somehow be
able to open on the first day.
However,
I think it's better if we lower
the difficulty of the climax a little.
Are you saying you want to
make the climax scene easy?
Yes.
For the time being, let's get rid
of the idea of using the diabolo.
What?!
Co-starring with a newcomer
is enough adventure in itself.
As a director,
I want to avoid any more adventures
than what we're doing right now.
But, I worked hard for--
I'm aware of that!
But we don't have time.
I will not accept it!
What?!
But, Miss Layla...
I cannot allow you to make the climax easy.
Please give us tomorrow, one more day!
Tomorrow is the Generalprobe,
the dress rehearsal.
We already postponed until
tomorrow just for the two of you!
We will use substitutes for the Generalprobe.
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
Thank you, Kalos.
Sora...
Ken...
Where is Miss Layla?
She said she had some phone calls to make.
I see.
So, what did they say?
Oh, yes...
For the time being,
we get one more day, tomorrow.
Really? That's good.
Thank you. See you...
Sure...
I'm sure you will do fine, Sora!
Yes.
Good morning. How is everything going?
Good morning, Miss Layla.
We somehow managed to do it.
Thank you.
Excuse me...
Hurry and get on the boat.
Yes!
It looks like the weather
also started cooperating.
It looks that way.
"The weather started cooperating"?
Excuse me...
We're going to start special training.
What?!
Our timing was finally beginning to match...
Will it be okay to practice
over the real sea?
Forget everything we
have done up to this point.
What?
I've also been working so hard,
just trying to adjust the timing.
But no matter how many times I repeat
the same things like I've been doing,
the final product will
be a safe and boring show.
Miss Layla...
This is a real fight between us.
A real fight with Miss Layla?
So, will you accept this challenge?
Yes.
Do you want a lifeline?
I won't need one.
It will get in my way when I move.
I won't need it either.
Really?
You're beginning to look like a real enemy.
She has such amazing spirit.
If I lose my nerve even a little,
she really is going to knock me in the sea.
If you drop your guard, you'll be shark bait.
Over the real sea, no one can
predict the movement of the waves,
not even Miss Layla...
Yeah, that's right.
They're supposed to be doing special training
in the middle of the sea around this time.
As for the rehearsal, please continue.
The show will open as planned.
Yeah.
Miss Sarah, it's not your turn yet.
I can't believe I did it. Sorry.
That's right. Keep an eye on the
space in the front and the back!
Dick! I think you should step
forward there, and let's try an ad-lib.
Okay.
Cruising?
Opening day is tomorrow.
I wonder if they'll be all right?
I assume Miss Layla has something in mind.
But I'm worried about the weather.
Amazing...
Are you reaching your limit?
No...
Really?
Stop with all the noise!
As long as you guys keep
standing there, it'll be fine!
Yes!
Really...
Can we really make tomorrow's opening date?
Miss Layla!
I think we'll be all right.
Yes!
Since the seas in the direction
of the port are still rough,
we will drop anchor here until morning.
All right.
So, tomorrow is finally a real show.
In a real show...
What?
I wonder if they could have
rain in a real performance.
You're truly amazing, Miss Layla.
You're always thinking about Kaleido Stage.
Miss Layla, why did you join Kaleido Stage?
When I was a child,
I saw Kaleido Stage with my parents.
It was so wonderful. Like a dream.
Of course, the show was wonderful,
but I thought it was strange
to see my mother and father
laughing and being
surprised as if they were kids.
Which show was it?
Alice's Adventures in Wonderland.
The show I saw with my parents was
also Alice's Adventures in Wonderland.
But, of course, it became the last
memory that I had with both my parents.
My mother, too...
She passed away.
It was my first and last time seeing my
mother surprised and laughing like that.
After my mother died,
my father devoted himself to work
to take his mind off of her.
It would be nice if your father
could see you onstage this time.
Oh... Did I say something I shouldn't have?
No...
I've never told this to anybody before.
This girl may possess a power
that can change her surroundings.
Someday, the audience
will come here just to see her.
Let's take a little rest.
Yes.
By the way, you talk a lot in your sleep.
Oh... Do I?
Talking in my sleep?
Is she talking about the
time when I was talking to Fool?
No way...
They're not coming back today?
Are they going to stay overnight?
They never told me this.
Something unexpected happened.
I have no choice.
I will wait one more night.
You guys, please come back by tomorrow.
It's me.
Hm. I see.
All right.
It's me.
We will start opening day as scheduled.
Layla and Sora are heading here directly.
They'll be here very soon.
Let's go.
Sora's coming back.
I'm glad. They made it in time.
There they are!
Sora!
Welcome back!
It's nice to have you back. Welcome back.
Jean, I want you to prepare rain for us.
Rain?
All right. I'll try.
Everyone, please come here.
Yes.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
She's faster than yesterday.
Amazing...
Oh... Five seconds before flame ignition.
Good. Ignite!
Flames ignite!
I'm coming!
Sora!
Thank you.
I've not received this kind of
pleasant applause for a long time.
Miss Layla, I'm happy.
I'm happy and I don't know what to say.
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
It's not so easy that you'll get
applause for just following the script.
And so, I alone have to
work even though it's my day off.
Moreover, she is going to appear on stage
as a guest for another theatrical company.
I'm coming with you. So, hold on!
Going through ordeals in a
completely different environment.
Out of the frying pan into
the fire. Into the fire! Into the fire!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Mysterious Amazing Circus."
My wings are my dream
and on toward the sky...