Starting tomorrow I'm a high school student, huh?
I wonder if I'll be able to make friends.
Sonoda           Yuu
Search
Should I ask Yuu-chan for advice?
No, I can't just rely on Yuu-chan!
I'll be a high school girl soon!
I'll sleep!
Sonoda          Yuu
Mobile
Yuu-chan?
Hello?
Hello, Haruka.
Did you pack your writing utensils?
Yuu-chan?
I did.
Okay.
Huh?
She hung up.
It's Yuu-chan again.
Hello?
Haruka, after you pass through the main gate tomorrow,
you'll need to find your class on the sign in front of the entrance.
Y-Yeah, I know.
I wonder.
Really!
Forget that, you better not come to
school with rice on your face, Yuu-chan!
I won't!
I'm not you, Haruka.
I wouldn't do something like that!
I'm hanging up now.
Don't show up with rice on your face tomorrow.
As I said, that's something you-
Haruka
She hung up.
What's with her?!
She woke me up!
Stupid Yuu-chan!
She called because she's worried.
Yuu-chan is always so kind.
I wonder if she'll have her usual hairstyle tomorrow.
Since Yuu-chan's so short, I'm sure her uniform will be too big for her.
I hope we'll be in the same class.
And I hope I'll get to sit in the seat behind Yuu-chan,
just like in middle school.
When the sun sets, and the sakura petals fly.
That's when...
Kiss, kiss, kiss
mou muchuu nano
もう夢chuなの
I'm already in ekisstasy
Sakura
dokidoki shichau no yo
ドキドキしちゃうのよ
My heart beats fast again
anata no soba de mata
あなたのそばでまた
When I'm close to you
takanaru kono kodou
高鳴るこの鼓動
My racing heart
tomaranai yo
止まらないよ
Just won't stop
tomodachi nandakedo
友達なんだけど
Even though we're friends
sore ijou no kimochi?!
それ以上の気持ち？！
There are even deeper feelings?!
kono mama ja watashi wa
このままじゃ私は
If it goes on like this
douka shichau
どうかしちゃう
I'll end up doing something
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
我慢では解決できないの
Holding back doesn't solve anything
darenimo mane dekinai koto ga shitai no
だれにも真似できない事がしたいの
I want to do something that not everyone can do
Won chu kiss me!
tokubetsu na futari dake no himitsu
特別な二人だけの秘密
It's a special secret between just the two of us
itsu datte doko datte
いつだってどこだって
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
私のすべてを受け止めてほしいの
I want you to accept my everything
Can I kiss you?
saikou no futari dake no jikan
最高の二人だけの時間
It's the best time for just the two of us
kuchibiru fureau no
唇触れ合うの
Our lips meet
anata to watashi no
あなたと私の
It's your and my
Kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
離れたくない
I don't want to leave you
Misato West High
Good morning.
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
62nd
Entrance
Ceremony
Sorry, Yuu-chan!
Haruka, you're late!
Yuu-chan, it's because you called me so late last night!
You shouldn't do that.
You need to make sure you have enough time to make it to school.
You're right!
I'll follow your example!
Sakura-coloured Beginning
My name is Takayama Haruka.
The first character in my name is "ta".
My best friend, Sonoda Yuu-chan, has "so".
So if we're in same class, I'll get to sit right behind Yuu-chan!
TL Note: "ta" comes right after "so" in the ordering of Japanese kana.
CLASS A
Ah, Haruka!
We're in same class!
Hooray!
So
So!
Ta
Ta!
If I were sitting behind Yuu-chan,
I could help her study.
Haruka, I don't understand this one.
Let's see.
I don't get it!
Ah, for this formula...
Thank you!
No problem.
What's this?!
Stop it!
Without Yuu-chan around,
what will I talk about?
If someone creepy sits next to me...
Ah, I'm Iizuka Yuzu.
I'll be next to you!
I'm Ikeno Kaede.
Nice to meet you!
They're here!
Wow, I let out a weird noise!
So embarrassing!
No, she's not creepy.
She's very sensitive!
Don't think that!
Entrance
ceremony
Well then, as we'll be attending the entrance ceremony next,
Entrance
Ceremony
everyone needs to start heading to the gymnasium.
Haruka!
Yuu-chan!
Let's go to the gymnasium!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's go! Let's go!
Should we do that too?
Go arm in arm?
No!
You don't like hooking arms?
You don't usually do that in high school.
Yuzu-chan is just too worried about the fact that Kaede-chan is the same gender as her!
So you think of each other as being opposite genders?
Yuu-chan, was it?
Yup, I'm Sonoda Yuu.
I'm Haruka's friend.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Yuzu!
We're in the same class!
Kotone?
This is Noda Kotone.
We're from the same middle school.
Yahoo! Let's get along!
You're all so excited!
By the way...
The class list?
Is something up with it?
Look at this name.
Minami Shizuku?
Unusual, isn't it?
Her name sounds like something straight out of a shoujo manga,
so she's got to be a total beauty!
I wonder what she's like.
*glance*
They're raising the bar.
Let's see...
It's her, isn't it?
Are you Minami Shizuku-san?
Y-Yes.
So cute!
Just like her name!
Nice to meet you!
Yeah, you too.
I'm glad that our classmates seem to be fun people.
Yeah.
It has been decided that our school will be
merged with the East High School in three years.
That means you will be the last first-year class this school has.
So I'm in high school now, huh?
Three years will surely pass in the blink of an eye.
She's sleeping?
Even then, I'd still want to be with you, Yuu-chan.
I still remember...
...the first time I met Yuu-chan.
I was alone before I met Yuu-chan.
So now it's my time to do something for her.
Club activities, cultural festivals, and athletic festivals.
Even field trips!
Let's enjoy them as much as we can!
They both fell asleep.
Yuu-chan!
Let's walk home together...
Sonoda-san!
We caught you!
Geez...
My special place!
What's wrong, Haruka?
E-Erm, spe...
Spe?
Special place...
N-Never mind!
Trouble?
Trip?
Run away?
Escape?
I ran away without thinking.
This classroom's empty?
I wonder if my relationship with Yuu-chan will become as empty as this classroom.
We used to be so close, though.
Haruka...
Yuu-chan?
Haruka!
Huh?
I should have realised it!
I'm so sorry!
Realised?
That you're a jealous, clingy woman!
Jealous
Y-You know, Yuu-chan, you don't have to stop making friends just because of me.
It's just that I thought I was your special friend, Yuu-chan...
In that case,
let's do something we'll never do with other girls.
Then we'll be special.
Are you sure?!
Sure.
I want to do fortune-telling with flowers!
Huh?
Loves me!
Loves me not!
Go ahead.
Go. Ahead.
Geez.
I was being serious.
E-Erm... What could we do...
We should do something that we would remember for the rest of our lives.
Then...
K-Kiss?
K-Kiss?!
What are you saying?!
School is for studying!
It's not a place for kissing!
Oh my!
Oh    my
The Yuu-chan who sleeps during class is actually talking about studying?
Since you can't study,
you can't kiss either?
Oh my.
I-I get it!
Let's kiss then!
Are you sure?!
Stand up!
Yes!
Yuu-chan made a noise just now.
She's so cute!
I can't stop these noises...
What if Haruka notices?
Let it out, Yuu-chan.
Once more.
I have to... hold back...
Just one more time.
So awkward!
Sakura-coloured Beginning                                 The End
Pokitz just released some more new products.
No matter what they come up with, I'll still prefer Salad's stuff.
Ah, an empty classroom.
It's locked.
The teacher said we couldn't go in.
That one's open!
All right!
Yuu
Haruka
Nobody will disturb us here!
Say something.
Yuu-chan is so cute when she tries to say something
cool but gets embarrassed when you don't play along.
Yakisoba, Balcony, and Girls
I wonder if they're going to clean here.
You mean the desks and stuff?
If possible, I'd like it to stay like this.
After all, it's the place of our memories.
Huh?
Smile!
Smile
What's that?
She's reacting like she doesn't really get it,
but thinks it'd be best to laugh anyway!
Yuu-chan!
Did you already forget what happened here?
Please return my maths notebook soon!
Huh?
I didn't borrow it.
No way!
I lent it to you this morning!
Huh?
Considering how forgetful Yuu-chan is,
it'd be possible.
...let's do something we'll never do with other girls...
So that's how much Yuu-chan values the kiss we shared.
In that case, we'll have to do it once more!
Hey, Haruka, let's go already!
I won't let you forget that we're supposed to deliver yakisoba to Yuzu-chan!
Haruka, this is bad!
The teacher's coming!
We have to hide!
Where can we hide?
A locker could be nice.
What if she finds us?
It'll be all right.
No, no.
The teacher's desk could work, too.
S-Sorry...
Let's run to the balcony!
Yuu-chan!
Yuzu, what happened with your lunch?
I asked Haruka and Yuu for some,
since they said they were going to a convenience store.
That's rare.
Those two usually bring lunch boxes with them.
I feel like eating yakisoba!
I asked them to get some for you, too.
I'll be eating yakisoba too, huh?
Even though you're expecting this,
This
they'll probably buy this.
Kaede, you don't have faith in your friends?
I believe in my friends!
No, I'm worried how you asked them.
You said more than just "yakisoba", didn't you?
Of course a high school girl wouldn't eat cup yakisoba!
Yakisoba bread is more refined!
Refined...
Stop
Don't you get it?
Huh?
Shizuku-chan, where's your lunch?
I'm not hungry.
Grumble Grumble Grumble
I have hot water!
I don't care about hot water.
Yuu-chan, are you okay-
So close!
If we're going to kiss, now's the chance!
What?
The door's wide open.
They came in!
Hiding was a good idea.
We can't make any noise.
What are you doing so suddenly?!
It's not the time to do something like this!
But...
But Yuu-chan...
You forgot that we kissed!
I thought you'd remember it if I kissed you!
Sorry!
I didn't know you disliked it that much!
I didn't realise!
That's not true!
You're being loud!
Don't hate me!
I have nobody but you!
H-Haruka, listen to what I'm saying!
Yuu-chan, marry me!
Stop fooling around!
No, Yuu-chan, don't hate me!
No!
Haruka!
Listen, Haruka!
She's quiet at last.
If you don't do it again,
I'll start yelling again!
Geez, why?
You don't want to?
Think about what will happen when the teachers find us!
It'll be fine.
Just a little.
What should I do?
It feels so good I can't stop.
Yuu-chan, I'm sorry.
Hit
You said just a little!
I'm sorry!
They're taking their time.
I'm pretty hungry.
I'm going to go buy something.
Would you like anything?
No, I'll wait for them.
Hey, Shizuku-chan want to go with me?
I'll stay here.
Should I get you some hot water, then?
I'll come.
Did the teachers leave?
I wonder why they came here.
Let's go back already.
Yeah!
Clank
Huh?
No way!
They came to lock it!
We're locked in!
Geez, if you hadn't kissed me...
You're the one that suggested coming in here!
It's my fault!
I didn't mean that!
Ah, it's Yuzu-chan's fault!
Since Yuzu-chan wanted to eat yakisoba,
it's all her fault!
What should we do?
Stupid Yuzu-chan!
Yuzu-chan, I'm sorry!
Hold on!
We should be able to get out through the balcony.
Balcony?
As expected from Haruka!
Way
My...
Long way down
We'll have to jump!
I'll go first!
You're going first?
Wait, don't leave me!
Take me with you!
Yuu-chan, what are you doing?!
Pervert!
Yuu-chan, you pervert!
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
You wouldn't normally just grab someone's chest!
I'm not a pervert!
I'm sorry!
I kissed you too, didn't I?
I'm the pervert here!
Forgive me!
I'm starving
We have to hurry!
Hang in there, Haruka.
Yeah.
Hey, Haruka.
You have C-cup, don't you?
How nice.
You noticed...
...though I'm actually D.
Haruka, watch out!
Haruka, I'll protect you!
Are you okay?
H-Hey!
Yuu-chan isn't breathing!
What should I do?
At times like this, you have to give CPR, right?
But Yuu-chan will get mad at me like she did earlier.
No, this is an emergency.
It's nece-
Ow...
I hit my head.
What's going on?
Yuzu-chan!
Kaede-chan!
This is our class's balcony!
Did something happen?
W-Well, you know...
It's a secret, so I'll have to come up with something...
Haruka has a C-cup!
Huh, what?
Well, where's my yakisoba?
Cup! Cup! Cup! Cup!
Stop the cup thing already.
We brought it here!
It was the last one.
Yakisoba flavour
Here!
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Actually, this can't be called a cup.
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba flavour
Spring Season
Limited Edition
Yakisoba, Balcony and Girls                           The End
Yay
Won't you kiss
Kiss and love
futari dake no jikan ga
二人だけの時間が
Time for just the two of us
futari dake no himitsu ga
二人だけの秘密が
A secret for just the two of us
futari dake no yakusoku
二人だけの約束
A promise between just the two of us
aru kara ne
あるからね
We have all of them
yorokobi wakachiaete kanashimi wakeaetara
喜び分かち合えて 悲しみ分け合えたら
If we share our joys and split our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
一人より幸せに なれるように
We may be able to become happier than if we were alone
ashita mo omoide wo saa fuyasou
明日も思い出をさあ増やそう
Let's make more memories tomorrow as well
ippai ni shichaou ne
一杯にしちゃおうね
Let's make a lot of them!
Love you
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
この広い世界で 逢えた奇跡
I came across a miracle in this wide world
tokubetsu na no anata janai to dame dakara
特別なの あなたじゃないとだめだから
But it's no good if you're not special to me
futari janai to dekinai koto da yo
二人じゃないとできないことだよ
It's something we can't do if we're not together
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
いますぐに 大好き kiss and love
I love you now, kiss and love
Love
Preview
I'm Minami Shizuku.
I'm Noda Kotone!
Hey, why did you tease me like that?
You're so cute, Shizuku-chan.
Why did you?
You're so cute, Shizuku-chan!
No!
Next time: Trick 2.
Another Sakura Colour
After School with Hari-chan
"Another Sakura Colour" and "After School with Hari-chan".
Look forward to it!