I think it's time to blow this scene
Get everybody and their stuff together
Okay, three, two, one let's jam
This was the most
precious of the precious.
Emergency rations
for a true emergency.
Saved for the last
of the last resorts.
All I'm asking is who ate the
food that was in this container.
Food rage... it's a scary thought.
Spike, was it you by any chance?
I wouldn't leave the empty box
lying around as evidence.
- Ed is hungry...
- Maybe you ate it,
and you're just pretending to be
mad 'cause we found the box.
What's that?
We haven't had anything
to eat in two days!
Wouldn't you call that an emergency?
I want some bell peppers and beef...
We're out of fuel. End of story.
If we can just hold out a little longer,
our inertia will carry us to Europa.
Stomach's caving in...
If only we could use that
energy to fuel ourselves.
Keep mouthing off like that, and
I'll toss you out into absolute zero.
At this point, even Ein
looks good enough to eat.
Watch it, Spike. I bet you're
looking pretty good to him too.
- Aw, man...
- That was some crash.
Hello, can you hear me
out there? Come in!
Wha--
Oh, fine. Isn't that what
they call a hit-and-run?
We're fragged! That crash
knocked us off course!
What course, Jet?!
What's going on here?!
Whoa.
Look at this, where are we?
There's nothing here.
That's the least of our troubles.
We're gonna need to
check the whole ship.
Think you could hunt
up a little food, Faye?
What's wrong?
It hurts... I got a pain...
This a joke?
Ah. These rations expired a year ago.
It's a good thing I didn't eat them.
Serves her right.
It's poetic justice.
Let's do it.
What's the plan?
Ed will help.
Gee, thanks, Ed.
Why don't you go out and
get us some food instead?
Okay!
High socks are cool!
Gotta wear them outside!
There's nothing here.
It's that hit-and-run ship!
Wait!
Hold on! Wait for Edward!
Smell food?
Ah! Food!
Gimme gimme gimme!
1,000 Woolongs each.
That includes the tax.
Cash only. No credit cards accepted.
Don't have cash.
Then you don't get no melon.
So can I have one?
1,000 Woolongs.
And it's cash only. No cards.
Hey, kid, no use staring like that.
If you want food, then go
into town and get it there.
Don't bother with the change.
But if you see this man, gimme a call.
I'll show my appreciation... cutie-pie.
Excuse me, ma'am?
We'd like to check
your baggage, please.
Is there a problem?
A mushroom dealer
running from the law.
He's on the most wanted list, and
we got word he might've come here.
What a coincidence.
I'm after the same guy
for that nice big bounty.
You're a cowboy?
We need to check your trunk.
Go ahead, feel free.
- Huh?
- What?
- All right...
- Hey!
- Freeze!
- Now, wait a minute!
- All right, stay still.
- I don't know anything about this!
- Put your hands on the ground!
- What are you doing?!
- Do exactly as I say!
- Let's go, hurry up!
- You're under arrest!
- Move it! Come on!
Foodie, food, food, food,
do you have any?
Yes you do, do, do, do.
Boy, is Ed hungry.
- Meanie!
- You crazy, boy?
Give some to Edward!
Dammit, cut that out!
Hey!
Ha! Now don't tell me that you've
forgotten who I am so soon, Domino?
- Let's see...
- Think, dammit!
I'm the youngest Shaft brother.
We bought all those
mushrooms from you!
- Uh, I don't remember you.
- No?
Do you wanna know why I drag an
empty coffin like this wherever I go?
I tell you, 'cause I'm
putting your corpse inside it!
Pieces, pieces, all gone.
What did what with who?
My older brother ate a mushroom
that he bought from you, and then...
he laughed until he twisted
his intestines to death!
Happy way to die, I'd say.
Shut up!
The whole thing was your fault!
I'd call that unjust resentment.
Edward is hungry.
Yeah? Then eat this, fool!
Hey! Get your butt back here
and fight like a man, you punk!
Food...
Hey, wait a minute, Ein!
We have to share and share alike!
Ein?
Bad mushroom?
Really?
Delicious.
Hey, well now.
This thing can't really be here, can it?
So I can't really be faulted...
for eating something that's not here.
Hey, the world really is a great place.
What?
Oh, wow, did I just say something?
Hey, mister.
This here is the stairway to heaven.
You know that, don't you?
Obnoxious little frog...
Fine, why should I care.
I warned you, though!
So that's how it is.
The secret of the universe is so simple.
Man...
By the way...
just who am I, anyway?
So these mushrooms really
aren't good for eating, right, Ein?
Hi, amigos! It's time
once again for Big Shot!
With a bunch of new and
exciting bounties this week!
Coming out the chute first today...
Is this dude, Domino Walker.
Wanted on six planets
for selling illegal mushrooms.
Hey, we saw him!
She's a cowgirl, Ein.
We'll get the reward and buy food!
Ein, you're a cow-woof-woof.
And a 1! 2! 3! 4! 5!
Here we go!
Woo-hoo!
All right, lady.
Let's start at the top.
Look, I don't know anything!
Right, so a kid and a dog
you didn't know are in your car.
Yes, what is it?
Sally, I'm busy.
What are you calling me for?
I'm in the middle
of an interrogation.
Yeah, yeah, and that's it?
No, no, I didn't mean
"that's it" in a bad way.
No, I'm not patronizing you
because you're a woman.
Yes, I love you too, hon.
Tonight at seven. All right.
Hey!
What's wrong, young'un? Why so blue?
Your woman run off with
another man or something?
Sounds familiar...
None of your business,
you old geezers.
What?
Yeah, sonny, that's what
happens when you eat too fast.
I got a home remedy
for that. Mushrooms!
You sure that works?
He's not here.
Aww...
Hmm...
Hey! It's that hit-and-run ship!
I'm sure they never dreamed
I was raising these right in here.
Mm, this one's bad.
Oh well. Landing here
was a big mistake,
- but I--
- Are you surprised?
Who the hell are you?!
- What are you doing in here?
- That's my line, kid.
- How'd you sneak into my ship, anyway?
- The door was open.
All right, hit-and-run driver,
this is a bust!
Stinky gas!
You crazy kid! I'm getting outta here!
Come back here,
you stinky cowpoke!
♪ Africa, Mexico, Sicily, Tijuana ♪
♪ India, Osaka, Indonesia ♪
You're not getting away
from me, Domino!
♪ Let's kick the beat ♪
Brotha, get outta my way!
♪ Mushroom hunting ♪
Ein, go!
Let go of that! Let go of my bag!
Let... go!
♪ Mushroom hunting ♪
Get off of me, you dumb motha--
Yah!
- I gotcha!
- Hold on!
These mushrooms are worth 100,000 each.
- Let me go, and they're all yours.
- I dunno...
Me or the shrooms,
what's worth more?
- I dunno.
- What? Are you a total airhead?
- Take the mushrooms!
- All right!
- Jeez...
- Hooray!
Thanks.
Oh, it's no problem.
Yee-haw! Dinner! Mushrooms!
100,000 each? No kidding!
Adds up to some pretty serious money.
Ed, are these real?
Excuse me.
Police officer.
Do you know a man named Domino?
He deals in illegal mushrooms.
I'm afraid we wouldn't know
anything about that, you know.
I'm sorry we can't
be of any help, officer.
Ed knows about--
The kid's a little odd.
Hey!
- She's just playing.
- She thinks it's a game.
Uh-huh...
Stand aside, please.
Mm-hmm...
All clear.
Guess you folks really
like shiitake mushrooms.
Well, sorry to bother you.
- Dinner's ready.
- What'd you make?
Shiitake stir-fry, shiitake stew,
shiitake salad...
and shiitake on ice.
Woo-hee!
Again? How many days
has it been now?
No more... I can't deal with it.
Quit complaining, and be thankful
there's something to eat.
Thankful!
aishiteta to nageku niwa
Too much time has passed by...
amarinimo toki wa sugite shimatta
...to lament that we were deeply in love.
mada kokoro no hokorobi wo
The wind keeps blowing, while my heart...
iyasenu mama kaze ga fuiteru
...cannot heal all the tears in it.
kawaita hitomi de dareka naite kure
Someone, cry for me with parched eyes.
The real folk blues.
honto no kanashimi ga shiritai dake
I only want to know what true sadness is.
doro no kawa ni tsukatta
Sitting in muddy water...
jinsei mo waruku wa nai
...isn't such a bad life...
ichido kiri de owaru nara
...if it ends after the first time...
A videotape was delivered to
the Bebop with no return address.
When we took a look at it,
things took a turn for the unexpected.
Well... actually,
the story doesn't go anywhere.
At first glance, it's pointless.
The actions are on a small scale,
and the ending is forced.
But then again, what conclusions
will you draw from it?
Next episode:
"Speak Like a Child."
At first glance, it's interesting.