May I have your attention, please?
We will now decide the order of the stage events for the cultural festival.
Club captains, please come up to the stage and draw your lots.
Go get 'em, Midori!
Any time's fine, as long as we don't fail.
Uh, there's no failure involved here.
Oh.
Okay, here I go.
All right! Break a leg!
We were the closing act last year, weren't we?
There weren't a lot of people left in the audience.
On the other hand, that meant there wasn't much pressure either.
Yeah, Kisaragi probably couldn't've handled many more.
Hey, look! It's Mochizou's club!
It's decided!
So we're starting off with a movie first thing in the morning?
Turtle, turtle!
Hey!
Sounds heavy.
The class rep looks pretty excited.
Yeah.
Next up, Baton Club.
Ah, it's Midori!
She looks ready to take on the world, doesn't she?
Here it comes!
There we go!
The 11 AM to 11:30 AM primetime slot goes to the Baton Club!
Baton Twirling Club
Whoa, she really did it!
You're amazing, Captain!
Looks like she doesn't know how to react.
A triumphant mood, with heads held high in great pomp.
This is the cultural festival where hearts flutter.
It's the time to show off the fruits of your labor.
Now, bear witness.
Tamako Market
I feel like running through
the surging crowds
As though called back,
the streets are back before me
I'm proud of the repeat customers we get
My expectation gets the better of me
and I start joking around
With a little hop I stood up
Did you have to wait long?
I saw your smile in passing and want to hug you tightly
Come here, everyone
Beginnings always
are very sudden
No party could be as radiant
as the place that we have
right here
Let's enjoy it
On that note,
I'd like call to order our meeting to decide on a program for the cultural festival.
Yay!
If you've got something you'd like to do, please feel free to suggest it.
What could we do with batons?
A New Year's firefighter show.
What the heck?
What did we do last year?
"A New Year's firefighter show," she says.
Saya!
Good morning!
I came to see how you guys were doing.
Episode 10
A Flower Blooms On Her Baton
Last year, we performed a dance to a magic show backing track.
The audience was seriously expecting to see a pigeon show up on stage...
Chose the wrong song, did you?
How about we really bring out a pigeon this year?
We've got Dela, after all.
But we're the Baton Club...
Well, there's no harm in suggesting things.
In that case... I didn't bring it up last year, but...
What is it?
A New Year's firefighter show.
So you were serious...
Not a chance.
We can't hold up a ladder that big with just the six of us.
I only brought it up because you said I should...
There, there.
Dammit. To hell with everything.
Oh yeah, are we gonna wear jackets?
Enough of that already.
Why don't we decide on a theme first?
A theme?
Anything goes.
Even stuff like "I Love Mochi!"
Or "Teen Spirit Explosion!"
How about "The Life of Mochi"?
Mochi has a life?
Yup!
First, the rice seeds get planted.
Then they grow up.
After that, they're harvested and threshed.
Ta-da! Now they're white mochi grains!
Then they're soaked in water overnight.
They'll all get down and dirty together!
Tamako's so funny.
Now that they're all softened up, they get transfered to a millstone and pounded with a mallet.
Bam!
Wham!
And finally they get eaten and live happily ever after?
Bam!
Yeah.
You've got to hold back here.
That sounds fun!
It's probably a bit too large in scale.
I see...
But I think I get it now. We've got to think along those lines, right?
Right!
I feel like I'm this close to coming up with an idea of my own!
They look like they're having fun...
So, let's go with something that lasts around five to ten minutes.
We'll show off some moves and maybe even explain a few.
The theme'll be—
Let's put the theme on hold for a while.
As our captain, you're in charge of choreography, Midori.
We expect great things.
Oh, is it okay if I select the song and stuff?
Of course.
Yup.
Oh, man!
This is gonna be off the hook!
We'll handle the costumes.
Huh? But I wanna go shopping with you guys too!
Don't worry.
We'll ask you before deciding anything.
You'd better.
Could I come with you as well?
Of course.
I wanna go too!
Me too!
Wow, this is getting exciting!
That's the cultural festival for you.
See you later.
Later!
Good work.
What style should we go with?
Mochi lovin' style!
Firefighting style.
"Cultural festival"?
Oh, yeah.
Do you wanna see some pictures from last year?
Hey! Where are yer manners?
Sorry!
Mochizou took these.
So you all swing those rods around?
That's right.
We do it while dancing along to the song.
Like the mochi pounding...
People around here really do love dancing, don't they?
Yup!
You should come watch, Choi.
I will! I love dance!
Hey, Anko! Ya lost yer manners too?
Oh, wow.
Mirror Mochi
Mallet
Millstone
Acorn Mochi
The theme will be New Year's.
New fall product
Lookin' good!
I'll show this to everyone tomorrow.
Huh?
The opening act, huh?
We won't get to build up much anticipation, but whatever.
Over.
You okay, Mochizou?
Yeah, my fever's started going down.
Good.
Have you finished shooting the movie?
Over.
There's still the scene where I fall off a clock tower.
What?! A clock tower?
It's just papier-mâché.
Phew, that scared me!
Mirror Mochi
Millstone
Acorn Mochi
The theme will be New Year's.
New fall product
I thought you were gonna jump off an actual, tall clock tower.
No way.
Oh, yeah!
You'll film this year's Baton Club performance as well, right?
Over.
Sure...
Thanks!
I'll film you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Midori's choreographing the whole thing this year.
Over.
Tokiwa is? Do you think she's up to it?
Of course she is.
She's Midori!
Ow!
Ouch!
I can't think of...
anything at all!
Hey, how do you like this?
Tamako, you're kinda... avant-garde, aren't you?
Is that a criticism?
This is great.
I like it too.
Oh, that one was my idea!
Not only is she in charge of choreography, she even handles costume design...
I came up with this stuff when I had some downtime.
Did you design it to match the choreography?
Y-Yeah...
Something like that.
You're amazing, Midori!
Uh...
Well, we've got the costumes down.
Yup.
You're so fast!
This is nothing special.
No, really! You're super-duper fast!
You're really good at this!
Lady Choi possesses great knowledge in the field of needlework.
Really?
You must be proud.
It's nothing to be proud of.
I just do this to calm myself down.
It actually calms you down?
You're not all like, "eek"?
I just stick the needle in...
and pull the thread.
Stick the needle in...
It makes me feel at ease.
That sounds like how I feel when I'm rolling up mochi!
And once I'm at ease, I can read the future Dela transmits to me.
Lady Choi's divinations are accurate 98 percent of the time!
Wow, Choi! You're amazing!
Hey, An... don't forget about me—
I can't believe how much you've done already!
You're like a professional!
But I'm still not good enough.
I've got a long way to go.
But you're so fast and skilled already!
I need to get much better.
Skilled enough to make a wedding dress fit for my prince's bride.
That's my dream.
I see.
I'm sure that'd make both the prince and his bride very happy.
What's the matter?
I've been meaning to ask you for a while now—
Sorry. Can it wait a bit?
Coming!
What's wrong, Choi?
I was just wondering how things were going.
Huh? They're going great?
Oh, Choi's helping?
Good to hear.
M-Me?!
I'm... uh...
Yeah, looking good.
I'm almost done, I guess...
Y-Yeah, bye.
God dammit!
I can't think of anything!
Ow!
Tamako Market
That's incredible!
I'm so jealous.
We can trade if you want.
Yeah, let's!
Which one?
This one or that one. Either will do.
On your way home from Tamako's place?
Nah. I didn't stop by today.
Oh, that's unusual.
Really?
So you're here today to get yourself a magic wand, I presume?
Or perhaps you're after a pocket magic mirror instead?
Or maybe some pocket mon—
I'm not here to ask you for anything!
Oh, I see.
Sheesh.
The first and most important step is to apologize.
I didn't get into a fight!
Oh, I see. Pardon me.
I'm going home.
Oh, I se—
Huh?
Idea...
Please let me come up with an idea!
I'm kinda, uh...
Sorry.
No, don't mention it.
You're mistaken if you think music is only made up of sounds.
Silence is also a part of music.
Does that mean you're telling me not to panic?
Did it sound that way to you?
Huh?
I wonder why she didn't stop by.
She seemed to be in somewhat of a rush.
Hm... I wonder what's wrong.
She sounded a bit weird over the phone as well.
This has got to be...
Stress.
Over what?
She couldn't handle the great
responsibility of being captain.
Whaaat?!
The way she's spacing out says it all.
I suppose the time to overthrow her draws near.
What are you guys doing?
It's over.
It's all over!
It's...
not over yet!
I have to...
...think of something!
Shiori...
Later.
Wow, you're pretty good.
Midori didn't answer the phone.
Oh my.
Do you think she went out?
She's takin' it easy.
Hm...
Knowing Midori...
She's probably doing great, right?
You think?
You should help out too, Kanna!
Huh?
What?
My policy is not to hold anything lighter than a hammer.
That's quite the declaration.
Excuse me!
Shiori...
Shiori!
Coming right away!
Sorry it all got so noisy.
Here, some tea.
Um, I'm here on an errand today.
Sorry! Were you in a hurry?
N-No.
Relax and have some tea, then.
Thanks.
Oh, is that the Baton Club's...
Yeah, it's for the cultural festival.
It's so pretty.
I know, right?
Midori designed it.
Wow. But she's not here?
Yeah. We couldn't get in touch with her.
What's wrong, Shiori?
In the bathroom yesterday...
Huh?
No, how can this be?!
So even Shiori goes to the bathroom...
Of course she does, Mister.
Oh my.
She didn't come today?
Have you heard anything?
Nope.
Mochi—
What? You guys haven't heard?
No, we haven't.
She's home today with a fever.
What? A fever?
Was it a cold?
That's all I know.
I'm so sorry. I should've told you right away.
Don't worry, Shiori.
I'm sure Midori'll be just fine.
I brought her some sweet bean mochi.
She can eat them even if she has a fever, right?
Indeed.
L-Let's see...
Sorry I can't offer you anything.
It's okay.
Sorry to just show up out of the blue.
Don't worry about it. Thanks.
Huh? Where's Choi?
She's watching TV back at home.
She got hooked on the talk and variety shows.
Has your fever gone down?
Yeah. I only had one early in the morning.
Have some mochi.
Oh, yeah.
Here, try some.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's this? What happened to all that energy of yours, my girl?
You seem unusually meek.
Huh?
R-Really?
Maybe I still have a bit of a fever, you know?
No, really. Is something wrong?
Does it...
have anything to do with what you were saying in the bathroom?
Kanna!
Huh?
S-Sorry.
I overheard you saying something in the bathroom.
Th-That was nothing, really.
Plus...
What...
could this be?
Oh no!
Midori?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I couldn't think of anything for the cultural festival choreography.
I couldn't think of anything. At all.
Nothing at all, really.
Everything I came up with ended up lacking in one way or another...
It all sucked.
I know...
you guys trusted me with it...
Hey! Midori!
My girl!
Huh?
What's up?
"What's up?"
You...
You're crying!
Oh, this?
It's nothing.
I'm not crying.
Your face!
Whoa!
Midori!
Sorry for not noticing.
I'm so sorry.
I can't show you such a pathetic side of me.
It's not pathetic at all!
I'm so sorry.
Midori!
Nice assist, Shiori.
Here. Blow.
Thanks.
Ridiculous.
And here I was, wondering what you were so worried about.
A dance is simply how you express to...
God...
Your friends...
And Mother Nature...
How grateful and happy you are to have them!
It's not something you "come up with."
It's what happens when you simply let your body do what comes naturally!
Behold!
This dignified dance of mine that I offer to myself!
What happened to God and the others?
S-Sorry...
Wh-What's wrong, Shiori?
That was really funny, Dela.
Wha—?!
"Funny"? How rude.
One more time, Mister.
Very well, if you insist.
That's very good.
Why do you laugh?!
Anyway, my girl.
Did that cheer you up a little?
Amazing.
Dela's dancing.
He's dancing!
Midori.
What?
We can just come up with the choreography together, right?
She's right.
A captain's supposed to work the club members hard.
Okay?
Okay.
Thanks, everyone.
Ah. Here they come again.
No, they're not.
What a crybaby.
And here they are!
Hey, that tickles!
We somehow managed to finish in time!
Yeah, thankfully.
Well done.
Yeah!
All right, I'm done!
How's this?
Oh my god, Tamako. You're so cute!
Pretty.
Really?
Hey, it's Choi.
Choi! Dela!
You came!
Who's this cute girl?
She's Choi.
Can I touch?
Captain Midori...
Do your thing.
All right, everyone!
Let's form a circle!
Yeah!
A circle?
You're part of the Baton Club already, Choi.
Me too?
Yup!
How about we all yell out the things most important to us on the count of three?!
The Darksign...
Sounds good.
Roger.
You do it too.
Here we go...
One, two...
Teddy!
Mochi!
Right angles!
Shiba dogs!
Fortunes!
The prince!
Me!
Batons!
With skies and hearts both boundless...
Now, the curtains are raised on a grand performance.
The baton girls begin dancing.
I knew it.
One, two...
There we go!
Yay!
Well then, Captain.
Congrats on a job well done!
You guys too.
Congrats on a job well done.
So it was a huge success?
How did we rate, Captain?
About 10 to 20 percent?
Harsh.
Huh? What?
I kinda feel...
really happy!
Wow.
Happy!
Ah, Choi.
Did you watch us, Choi?
How were we?
Lady Tamako.
What?
You are the prince's bride!
The record turns and turns
When it swells and breaks
the marks on it will play another music
The dryer doesn't help
Yesterday we talked too much
I took off my contacts
and the world dissolved
It won't last, but I will confirm my place in the world
Are we drifting apart?
Is what I seek always right beside me?
I knew it would be hard to find now
The record turns and turns
It swells and breaks
and a mysterious melody plays
I'll never forget it
Tamako Market
It's the season for harvesting delicious new crops of rice.
Tamako here.
I was curious about where people eat the most mochi, so I looked it up.
Turns out it's in rice-producing areas!
Makes sense, right?
Episode 11      No Way! That Girl's a Princess
What kind of mochi will I get to eat next time?