Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
When my worries keep me awake under the crescent moon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
All I can do is close my eyes and think of you
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I want to see you, I feel like crying
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I feel so romantic
romantikku na kibun
I hope my feelings reach you
todokete kono omoi
I know so very well
datte zutto shitteiru no
how hard you always work
ganbatteru koto takusan
You're the one I love
daisuki na hito ga
You're so strong, yet still I worry
tsuyokute shinpai
Only I ever see your weakness
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
I'll find you before the stars
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
Come right back home
massugu kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
nee hayaku kaette kite ne