It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
The feelings that collided before
differences were resolved
disappeared inside the bright light.
Is the path that I chose to fumble for
really the correct path?
I'm sure there will be times
when I can't decide.
But I'm sure that the footsteps
where I ran without stopping
will lead toward what
is to come for me.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin.
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
April 26, 8:27PM
Uminari City, outskirts, within the barriers
Fate!
Nanoha!
Episode 7:
Is This a Third Magician?
It's all right. You can
return, Bardiche.
Yes, sir.
Fate?!
Fate!
No! That's dangerous!
Stop...
Stop... stop...
Stop!
Fate!
Same day, 9:15pm Uminari City,
residential area, Takamachi residence
Nanoha
Raising Heart is a device
that can withstand quite a bit
of released power.
To think that one attack would
damage it this much...
Was it the clash between that girl's
and Nanoha's magical power?
No... Besides, that
doesn't explain it all.
So it was, after all, the Jewel Seed's...
Yuuno, is Raising Heart all right?
Yeabh... It sustained
extensive damage,
but I'm sure it will be all right.
It's running the auto-repair
function at full speed right now,
so I think it will be
back up by tomorrow.
And are you all right, Nanoha?
Yeah,
because Raising Heart protected me.
I'm so sorry, Raising Heart.
Same day, same time
Tohmi City, residential area
I'm sorry, Fate.
Hang in there a little longer.
I'm fine.
Thanks, Aruf.
I have to go back tomorrow
to report to Mother,
so I need to heal this quickly.
I'm sure I'll make her worry
if I returned home all torn up.
Would she actually be worried?
Mother is just a little awkward.
I know that for certain.
If it's just a report,
I can just go and do it.
Mother doesn't really listen to
what you have to say, Aruf.
But you're such a kind, good girl, Aruf.
Well... I'm sure you'll be
fine tomorrow!
In such a short time,
you found Lost Logia...
Four of those Jewel Seeds!
She might not praise you,
but I'm sure that she
won't scold you for it!
Yeah...
You're right.
April 27 6:15AM
Takamachi residence
Hm? Nanoha?
Oh, big sister.
What's wrong? You're up
really early today.
Well, I just kinda woke up, so...
I see.
Hey, where's big brother?
Yeah...
He's gone running with Dad this
morning, a little further than usual.
Um...
Your practice...
If I'm not bothering you,
can I watch?
I don't think it's very interesting.
But sure, I don't mind.
Thanks.
Nanoha?
Yuuno?
What's wrong?
It's so early in the day.
I just kinda woke up, so...
Anyway, Yuuno,
I've been thinking.
L.
That girl...
Fate is still on my mind.
She's on your mind?
She's really strong,
and she seems really cold-hearted,
but she has very pretty, gentle eyes.
And yet...
Somehow, they're very... melancholy.
I'm sure she has a reason behind it.
A reason why she's
collecting the Jewel Seeds.
That's why I...
I want to have a good talk with her.
So... To do that...
Same day, 8:17AM Tohmi City,
residential area, condominium rooftop
This should be enough for souvenirs.
An assortment of sweets?
Would she be happy with
something like this?
I don't know, but it's
the feeling that counts.
Dimensional teleport.
Dimensional coordinates 876C4419.
3312D699... 3583A1460... 779F3125.
Open, doors of luring.
To the Garden of Time, to the
master of the Testarossas!
Same day, same time
Within dimensional space
Time-Space Administration Bureau
Dimensional space flight flagship Arthra
How is everyone doing?
Is this journey going well?
We're currently cruising
at triple ship speed.
We will be arriving at the
destination dimension
in approximately 160 bexas.
Since the last small
dimensional tremor,
there hasn't been much
noticeable action,
but the danger of two seekers
clashing once again is very high.
I see.
Excuse me, Captain Lindy.
Thank you, Amy.
Admiral, Time-Space Administration Bureau
Captain of the Arthra, Lindy Harlaown
You're right.
Even if it's small, the creation
of a dimensional tremor...
..is rather troublesome.
If it gets dangerous, you must
hurry over to the site.
Right, Chrono?
Time-Space Administration Bureau
Enforcer, Chrono Harlaown
It's all right. I understand, Captain.
That is the reason I'm here.
Somewhere in high-dimensional space
Garden of Time
Only four?
This is all but horrible.
Yes...
I'm sorry... Mother.
Look here.
Fate, you are my daughter.
The sole daughter of the
great mage Precia Testarossa.
Nothing should be impossible for you.
No matter what.
That's right, you must
accomplish everything,
no matter what the cost.
Yes.
You made me wait all this time,
and you come up with so few...
There's no way I could have
welcomed you with a smile.
You understand, right, Fate?
Yes... I understand.
That is why...
That is why I want you to remember,
so that you never disappoint
your mother again.
What the hell?
What in the hell is this?!
It's too horrible!
That woman...
That woman's... Fate's
mother's abnormalities,
and her cruelty to Fate,
aren't anything new.
But this time, it's gone too far!
What the hell are they?!
Those Lost Logia... those Jewel
Seeds... are they that important?!
The Lost Logia
are absolutely necessary
in order to fulfill my dreams.
Yes, Mother.
Especially those Jewel Seeds,
which have a much higher
purity than anything else.
Because you are a kind child,
you may find yourself
hesitating at times.
But if anything is getting
in the way, crush it.
No matter what the cost!
Because you have
the power to do so...
You'll go for me, right?
My daughter...
My dear Fate.
Yes...
I'm on my way, Mother.
I'll take a nap for a while.
Next time, please make sure
to appease your mother.
Yes...
Fate!
Fate, I'm sorry...
Are you all right?
Why are you apologizing, Aruf?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
Because!
I didn't think it would end up like this.
You brought back what
she told you to bring back,
so I didn't think she'd do
something that cruel to you.
If I had known, I definitely
would have stopped you.
It's not cruel.
Mother was thinking
about my well-being.
The hell she was!
That... It's nothing more than
taking her anger out on you!
You're wrong,
because we're family.
I'm sure the Jewel Seeds are
very important to Mother.
Because she's been unfortunate
and sad all this time...
I want to find some way
to make her happy.
But... But still...
Aruf, please.
I'm sure it will be all right.
If I come home with the
Jewel Seeds in hand,
I'm sure Mother will smile at me.
She'll return to the kind Mother
that she used to be.
And I'm sure she will be
nice to you too, Aruf.
So let's go.
This time...
We can't fail.
April 27, 1:32PM  Seisho University Magnet
Elementary School, 3rd grade, classroom 1
April 27, 4:10PM
Uminari City, outskirts
How is it, Bardiche?
Recovery complete.
I see. You did your best. Good job.
You can feel it... Even I can sense it.
There is one that will
execute soon, very close by.
April 27, 5:05PM
Uminari city, residential district
Raising Heart, you're all fixed.
Thank goodness.
Condition green.
Will you do your best with me again?
All right, my master.
Thanks.
April 27, 6:24PM
Uminari city, Uminari Seaside Park
Time-sealing Barrier...
Unfold!
It's conceited enough
to put up a barrier?
It's the strongest one so far.
Besides...
That girl is here too.
Yuuno! Run!
Flier Fin.
Please fly, Raising Heart! Even higher!
All right.
Arc Saber!
Let's go, Bardiche.
Arc Saber.
Shooting Mode.
Let's go, Raising Heart!
Shoot through it!
Divine...
Buster.
Pierce it, lightning!
Thunder Smasher.
Sealing mode, set up.
Sealing form, set up.
Jewel Seed, Serial VII...
Seal!
It seems that we shouldn't
be jolting the Jewel Seeds.
Yeabh... If something like
last night happened again,
I'd feel sorry for both my
Raising Heart and your Bardiche.
But I can't give it up.
Device Form.
All I want to do is talk with you, Fate.
Device Mode.
If I win...
If you can understand that
I'm not just a spoiled child,
will you listen to my story?
Stop!
Combat here is too dangerous.
I'm an Enforcer from the
Time-Space Administration Bureau,
Chrono Harlaown.
Would you tell me the
details of this case?
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
With the emergence of Chrono,
the third mage,
and the truth finally unfolding
concerning the Jewel Seeds,
the plot takes a big step forward?!
And I find out something
that is very surprising.
Yuuno is... Yuuno is?!
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 8:
There's a Really Big Crisis?
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 8:
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Episode 8: There's a Really Big Crisis?
Episode 8:
There's a Really Big Crisis?
Lyrical, magical, I'll do my best!