Yuu-chan, are you done over there?
Yup, all finished!
Got it!
Congratulations on Graduating
Mitsuki & Rina
Oh, a speedy bunch you are.
And sent.
Send
All that's left is to hang this up.
I thought you were all done!
I already called them over.
Where are the party poppers?!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I've been entranced
Sakura Trick
dokidoki shichau no yo
My heart is racing again
anata no soba de mata
just from being next to you
takanaru kono kodou
This ringing in my chest
tomaranai yo
just won't stop
tomodachi nan dakedo
I know we're only friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but I think of you as something more
kono mama ja watashi wa
I don't think I can hold it in
douka shichau
for very much longer
gaman de wa kaiketsu dekinai no
Waiting around never solves anything
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to do something
Lies!
koto ga shitai no
no one else can imitate
Won't you kiss me tokubetsu na
Won't you kiss me?
futari dake no himitsu
This'll be our special little secret
itsu datte doko datte
Whenever it is, and wherever we go
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept everything about me
Can I kiss you? saikou no
Can I kiss you?
futari dake no jikan
Nothing can match the times when we're together
kuchibiru fureau no
and our lips meet
anata to watashi no
It belongs to us, this
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
hanaretaku nai
I don't want to let you go
Good work on your exams, Rina.
I hope I passed.
I'm sure you did fine.
So why do you think Sumi-chan called us over?
I wonder what she could need us for.
That's true.
I wonder if she has more questions about the student council.
Wait, hold on. Just where exactly are we heading?
Isn't this...
Why would Sumi-chan be in your house?
Well, I know the answer already.
I'm home...
Mitsuki-senpai! Rina-senpai!
Congratulations on graduating!
Mitsuki-san?!
hmph
"Pudding and Mitsuki's Determination"
Thanks so much, everyone.
So that's what this was all about.
Congrats!!
You're a day early though.
Are you really holding this party for me too?
That's the whole point.
Let's skip the pleasantries and get straight to the dessert we made you!
A bucket...
It's a matcha pudding bucket.
Matcha?!
It's amazing! I've never seen a pudding bucket before.
There's so much matcha to eat!
Congrats!!
What's wrong, Rina?
Nothing, I was just blown away...
Eating pudding before you study helps you concentrate better!
Wow, really?
I ate so much pudding when we were studying for the exams...
I can't tell them I've gotten sick of it.
Did you all make this yourselves?
Darn tootin'!
I'll try some right away.
H-How is it?
My! There are sweet red beans inside!
Each and every bite is a burst of flavor!
And here we've got a burst of tears.
drip
I'm so happy that it's to your liking...
Congrats!!
I don't want you to graduate!
There, there, SumiSumi.
Great, because of you, now I'm crying too!
Thank you too, Mikan-san.
Huh?
Suddenly I'm not crying anymore.
Present Time
I have some letters and presents for you two!
Wow!
Thank you!
Congrats!!
Mind if I open the letter here?
W-Wait, it's too embarrassing! Wait until you get home.
Then can I at least check out the present?
I made you handcrafted mustaches.
Aren't they adorable?
What?! You made these?!
You sure do love them.
In any case...
That thing hanging from our ceiling now...
It's a chandelier.
I knew it!
You can blame me for that.
I figured it'd be funny.
Heave-ho
I had the feeling you were behind it.
It is just a rental, right?
Not at all, it's yours now!
Wait, seriously?!
whoosh
Kaede and I will be doing our
best impressions of you two.
whoosh
I'm the Student Council President, Sonoda.
What'd you just stuff down your shirt?!
giggle
Rina's just standing there giggling!
Take care to follow school regulations.
Big Sister
Congrats!!
slide
Hey, Kaede. Why are you hiding behind me?
Geez, speak Japanese...
Excuse us for a sec.
Congrats!!
I don't think I've ever seen Kaedekko cry before.
Kaede-chan spent a lot more time
with them than we did.
Big Sister
Little Sister
Onee-chan, Haruka says she made brown sugar syrup for us.
Really?
Matcha pudding, sweet red beans, and brown sugar syrup...
Matcha pudding,
sweet red beans,
brown sugar syrup...
Matcha pudding,
Sweet red beans,
brown sugar syrup...
Haruka-san.
Yes?
Did you make anything with garlic in it?
Uuu...
Garlic?
Okay!
step
I'll whip something right up!
I'm so happy!
Rina-chan, pasta is Haruka's specialty!
Isn't that great?
Wow, now I'm getting excited!
I want to eat Haruka-san's home cooking too...
Are you sure it's all right to eat garlic the day before our graduation ceremony?
That's no concern of mine! I must eat garlic now!
R-Right...
click
Man, sorry we kept you all waiting.
Kaedekko's back to normal!
What are you talking about, exactly?
She dodged the issue.
Now from the top, we present President Mitsuki's...
You don't have to do those impressions for us.
Really, it's fine.
Huh?
Yuu-chan, we're short one spoon.
They're in the kitchen drawer.
Hey, Yuu! Don't make your guests do things for you!
Congratulations on Graduating
Mitsuki & Rina-senpai
That girl...
Wait a second!
Haruka-san's in the kitchen...
they'll be in there all by themselves!
Excuse me a moment.
Stop it! What do you two think you're doing?!
O-Oh...
I made vongole pasta.
Oh, did you?
I thought for sure you'd be in here kissing again.
It seems you're managing to keep our promise.
Why are you so quiet?
Say something already!
Th-This has nothing to do with you!
Of course it does!
In what way?!
I'm just p...
Protecting my little sister.
Not to mention that I'm in love with Haruka-san.
Big Sister
P... P...
P... P... P...
I have potatoes.
Onee-chan, you stick your nose into our business too much!
That's my job as your older sister!
Little Sister
What's with you always pulling the older sister card?
You can't even wake up on your own!
Big Sister
And what's wrong with that?
I tutor you to make up for it!
Just yesterday you ate my matcha baumkuchen!
Don't think I don't know about you wearing my culottes behind my back the other day!
scream
They're so close...
Forget her, Haruka.
Let's ignore her and do it anyway!
Huh? Do what?
Kiss!
What was that?!
Just one second, Yuu!
You can't!
Buzz off, Onee-chan!
No way!
Such bliss...
What're you getting all happy for?!
S-Sorry...
Wai—Yuu-chan...
No, stop that!
Yuu-chan, th-that's enough...
Why? You're usually the one coming on to me.
Still—Yuu-chan, sto...
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
Haruka
Little Sister
Big Sister
L-Like I said, you still haven't told Haruka-san you love her, right?
What are you trying to say?!
This is something Haruka and I decided together.
We can be like this because we're special.
We do it because we're special!
I see. You kiss because you see each other as special.
Then...
That means I still have a chance.
What do you mean?
That's right...
Haruka-san, I love... you.
Please go out with me.
"Pudding and Mitsuki's Determination"
The end
Big Sister
Little Sister
We depart today with hearts filled
and gratitude for our teachers.
Sonoda Mitsuki.
Here.
The time has come for us to leave
this garden of knowledge.
These long years and months...
Graduation Ceremony
"Sakura Trick"
Ah, there she is.
Congratulations on graduating!
Mitsuki-senpai!
Mitsuki-san.
Ah, Sakai-senpai!
Please give me your second button!
U-Um, I'm actually...
Please don't cry...
I lost her...
Man, was that heartrending or what?
Especially my singing.
Well, aren't you conceited.
I personally thought Shizuku-chan was better.
N-Not at all...
So you don't deny it?
Huh? Yuu-chan, where'd Harupoppo go?
Isn't she right...
Nowhere?!
Where'd she go?!
Just relax.
I'm gonna go look for her!
There she goes...
Is this the right place?
I probably should've told everyone I was leaving.
Yuu-chan's definitely looking for me.
After the graduation ceremony tomorrow, would you mind meeting me behind the tennis courts?
S-Sure...
And please don't tell anyone else about this.
Not even Yuu.
It's fine, nobody saw me coming here.
Ah, there she is.
What could she be doing?
Haru—
I'm sorry for calling you out like this.
No, I don't mind.
I wanted to hear your response to what I said yesterday.
Response...
I love you too, President Mitsuki.
Wait—you just... what?
Do you really love me?
But you already have Yuu...
Th-That's right! You two haven't confessed to each other or anything.
Th-Then, we can d... da-da...
D—d-da... date each other?!
Dab each other?
Dab, dab!
I said date!
What exactly does dating entail?
Well... we'd hold hands and go on walks...
Go places together,
a-and stay over at each other's houses, and even g-go on dates together.
And we'd also kiss...
That's exactly what I do with Yuu-chan!
Oh no! Now it's like I'm just pressuring her!
Huh?
Then doesn't that mean that Yuu-chan and I are...
I knew it... you didn't understand
what I meant by "love".
What? I totally do.
No, you don't!
I guess... you might be right.
Then I'll think about it together with Yuu-chan.
What your love really meant.
But if nothing else, I understand that what you told me were your true and honest feelings.
So...
Wh-What's wrong?
I understand how you really feel now.
No matter the time or place, you think of Yuu .
How you always keep my sister closest to your heart
is probably why I fell in love with you in the first place.
Isn't that strange?
But just this once...
...let me be selfish.
The petals...
This time, it wasn't an accident.
Mitsuki-san!
Where are you?
Rina.
I've been looking for you!
Sorry, I'll be right there!
Yuu?!
Oh, I was just imagining things...
...or not?!
Yuu-chan, why are you here?
I've been looking all over for you.
D-Did you see us?!
See what?
You know what I mean!
I told you I don't!
Then what were you doing there?
I was watching ants.
Little Sister
Ant
Oh, okay.
Be-
lieved
her
Be-
lieved
her
Mitsuki-san?
Right...
Haruka.
Come with me.
S-Sure.
Sh-She's running!
Mitsuki-san, you look like a weight's been lifted off your shoulders.
Who, me?
Ever since the party ended yesterday,
you've looked all lost and worried.
Big Sister
H-How could you tell?
Same way you always see through me.
You always seem to be able to tell whenever I'm feeling lost.
You weren't able to tell Haruka-san, were you?
That you applied for a university outside our prefecture.
You saw through me completely, huh.
Of course I did.
I've always been watching you.
Just kidding!
Let's keep things the way they are now when we're in university together.
Sounds good. We'll be together again come April.
We'll be saying goodbye to
this classroom in a few days.
Yeah...
Yuu-chan, you heard everything, didn't you?
When President Mitsuki and I were talking.
Yep.
I see...
Hey, Yuu-chan... did you understand what she meant?
What President Mitsuki meant by "love".
She just went a little loopy after studying too much.
Now just a second...
I wonder what the meaning
behind my love for you is.
I thought it was exactly what
President Mitsuki described,
but she said that was wrong.
We walk around holding hands, we go places together...
We even stay over at each other's houses.
We kiss, too...
doki
Right?
Haruka...
I love you.
I thought maybe we'd figure something out if we say how much we love each other while kissing...
Yuu-chan, I think I just figured something out!
Let's try it again.
I'll say it this time.
Yuu-chan...
I love you...
Haruka, I love you...
Yuu-chan, I love...
Love, love...
Love...
Wh-Wh-Why was that so embarrassing, Haruka?!
I don't know, but it really was!
Haruka.
Did you figure anything out?
I feel like I both did and didn't.
I see.
I wonder if I'll ever understand what President Mitsuki's love meant.
You will! If my sister can understand it, anyone can!
It's finally starting to get warmer.
I can't wait until we change uniforms.
Same. Oh, wanna go shopping for spring clothes?
Sure.
Morning!
Good harmony!
Hey.
Morning.
What's that?
First gag of the semester.
Not just the semester. The school year, too.
There's not much difference anyway.
It's not like there's a new year coming in.
And we're not changing classes either.
But that's a good thing, right?
Yeah.
Sure is.
Besides, heads would roll if we got split up.
Mornin'!
Good morning, everyone!
Without a doubt.
They would.
No question about it.
Definitely.
What're you all smirking for?
Who knows?
Come on, tell us!
Let's jump across together!
Sure!
Haruka.
Yuu-chan.
Ready, go!
"Sakura Trick"
The end
Love!
Won't you kiss?!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
We've spent so much time alone together
futari dake no himitsu ga
We have so many secrets no one else knows
futari dake no yakusoku aru kara ne
and so many promises we made just between the two of us
yorokobi wakachiaete
We share our joys
kanashimi wakeaetara
and divide our sorrows
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
so we can be happier together than we are apart
ashita mo omoide wo
Tomorrow, let's make more memories
saa fuyasou ippai ni shichaou ne
and pile lots and lots of them up
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki
It's a miracle we were able to meet in this wide world of ours
tokubetsu na no anata ja nai to dame dakara
I don't know what I would do without you
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
This is something you need two people to do
ima sugu ni daisuki kiss and love
Love me now! Kiss & love!