Look at him, dripping bodily fluids everywhere.
Bodily Fluids
It's sweat!
He's been standing erect this whole time.
Bodily Fluids
Erect
I'm standing up! Use the right word!
Bodily Fluids
Erect
I have some time before work,
so I thought I'd do some reading.
If you have time to read erotic novels, you should go climb a pole instead.
Hey, now. I happen to be very
particular about climbing poles.
This isn't an erotic novel.
It's a great book that Kawai lent me.
Ah, I see.
So you're waiting in this crazy heat to ambush Ricchan while wearing her favorite outfit?
Good for you. Keep releasing those fluids.
It's sweat!
Anyway, I'll be quitting my job soon,
so I thought I'd show off while I still could.
Why don't you keep working?
The pay's not half bad, right?
My Oddhand days are over.
The less oddballs I have to handle, the better.
Are you still upset about Hayashi?
It's not...
Hey, look at what your roommate's making right now.
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Too late to escape.
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
Climbing Pole Map
Laundry
(with the cute old lady)
Convenience Store
(the owner has a hot wife)
Maruta Park (but it's a bit too small)
Grade School
(risk of cops)
I didn't expect the face of despair to look so idiotic.
I'm going now.
Oh, yeah. Ricchan already left for
the book store earlier this morning.
That should've been the first thing you told me!
It's raining incessantly outside
But I don't mind since I feel at ease here
I'll turn over a new page to face
The unpredictable future lying in wait
Every morning feels incredibly bright
When I'm woken up by the hustle and bustle
And you're always right there
Standing next to me
Show me your world
And what it can be
Because look
Even your most casual of gestures
Shoots an arrow into my heart
What should we talk about tomorrow?
Let's go see how this story unfolds
The Kawai Complex Guide to Manors and Hostel Behavior
Episode Ten
Let Them Be
Should I keep working here?
Temporary summer closure on the17 th,18 th, and19 th of August.
The main restaurant will stay open as usual.
Kawahana Rd. Guesthouse ( Apprentice Cafe)
The job itself is pretty fun,
and now that I'm used to my coworkers, I've gotten pretty comfortable.
Where'd the bookshelves come from?
Anekouji!
The Madame had them sent over from England.
Let us build ourselves a place of learning!
Translation:
The owner bought them from an antique store.
Help us put the books away.
These are wonderful shelves. The ghost of an upper-class English lady dwells in them.
How could I ever get comfortable here?
This place is the express lane back to Oddhandville!
I'm quitting! I have to quit!
I've had enough of thankless work like that.
There were a lot of old books in Kawai's room, too.
She'd probably be thrilled if she saw these bookshelves.
Maybe I should casually invite her along sometime.
Owner,
that's all the books.
Oh, but there's still space.
I was hoping to fill it with old books.
Ah, if only our village elder's study hadn't burned down!
Newer ones would just look tacky.
It happened the day after I left the village...
I'd much rather have them match.
Uh, in that case...
I'm home.
Oh, perfect timing.
My friend's wondering if you
can lend her some old books.
Weren't you saying you didn't have enough room for all of yours?
She'll give us tickets for free coffee in return.
You can read at the café.
They have lots of books there.
That sounds nice.
And there's free cake in it for
anyone who helps carry them.
All right! Count me in!
Thank you! We'll be waiting!
She agreed to lend us some books.
Yes!
They're heavy, so Shiro's bringing them over in his vehicle.
What? Shiro has a car?
Kawai's on her way...
Okay, "car" might have been stretching it.
You're willing to offer us all of these books at no cost?
We'll show our eternal gratitude by reading them well and nourishing our minds!
You don't get to keep them.
And one day,
I will make it
to the capital...
And one day,
I will make it
to the capital...
Amazing.
I always had trouble reading as a child,
so I admire people who are big on books.
And I admire your ability to immediately hit on any man, no matter who he is.
She looks so happy.
She's trembling with anticipation.
Here's your tea.
Oh, she's already totally engrossed.
There's no helping this girl.
But this is...
kind of nice.
Shiro, what are you doing?
Oh, I think I'm about to get heat stroke.
You should get inside!
I love feeling like I'm on the brink!
Feel free to dry up and die, then!
Oh, it's the supernaturally-attuned Hayashi!
So you're here to see Usa?
I did some mean things to him the other day.
Yeah, they sure were. That was
some high-grade suffering, all right.
High-grade?
I want to apologize...
but I don't know how.
A few minutes ago,
I was on the brink of heatstroke, having a grand old time.
Thanks for the creeped-out reaction!
Usa was completely disgusted, too.
But he left this here.
What do you think?
Usa's Oddhand powers have evolved.
Oddhand Powers
It's impossible to not feel bad for him!
What about you?
How did Usa treat you?
Is Usa in the classroom?
I have to tell him about this scary story I found on the Internet.
Plus...
Hey, guess what?
I just saw Hayashi carrying a bag with what looked like chocolate inside.
Seriously? Who's she giving it to?
Knowing her, it'll be haunted chocolate.
It's probably for Usa.
Ugh, I feel sorry for him.
But he's the Oddball Hander, right?
He might get all emotional and date her.
No way.
Usa looks really uncomfortable
whenever he's talking to Hayashi.
And that "supernaturally-attuned" girl has no idea!
That's just pathetic.
If Usa wasn't there to put up with her, she'd be getting bullied left and right.
Oddhand sure has it rough.
Oh, let's stop at that place on the way home.
Sounds good!
Hayashi?
What are you doing?
Uh...
I wanted...
t-to tell you about a new scary story I found.
Go easy on me.
I don't handle scary stuff well.
And you shouldn't tell any of the girls.
It'd probably freak them out.
I was so embarrassed I could barely stay upright.
I didn't want to remember it.
But...
What I did to Usa was...
Shiro! That's enough already!
Hayashi?
Wait, Hayashi?
I-I...
I...
What?
Why's she here?
What does she want now?
Thank you!
Thank you, Usa,
for not ignoring me!
For looking out for me
and putting up with me.
Thank you!
I'm sorry I took advantage of you!
I'm really sorry about the mean things I said!
I'm sorry!
I get it. It's okay.
Your face is a mess.
Isn't this supposed to be waterproof?!
Wh-Where's the restroom?!
Usa, you dumbass.
You're too nice.
She should have messed up her mascara on purpose.
You're too easy. Isn't he, Ricchan?
Typical Kawai. Nothing can tear her away.
Hayashi, why don't you come inside the café?
You're a bigger masochist than Shiro.
Usa...
You're too nice.
How can you forgive me so easily?
Well, I had people to support me.
Though I'd be lying if I said I didn't harbor any ill feelings.
If Kawai hadn't shown up when she did...
So I wasn't hurt that badly.
...I probably wouldn't have forgiven her.
So you should thank them too.
Well, just a thought.
I'll be sure to thank Kawai later, too.
You know...
Seeing her after she's been rejected makes me want to cheer her up.
But I came here to make fun of her.
Aren't kindred spirits great?
Shut up!
I wasn't rejected.
Uh, but...
I was never the type to fall in love if I knew it wouldn't work out.
I only aim for guys I have a good chance with.
Whoa, whoa...
After all...
I'm a lot cuter now! I don't want to let that go to waste!
You're not as cute as you think.
Just because you two were born with better looks...
Nah, just one of us.
Women's Washroom
Oh, there you are.
This is yours, right?
Th-Thank you.
You have such a wonderful guardian spirit.
You shouldn't do stupid things that upset it.
It left you on your way back from that mixer.
That "thank you" was commendable, though.
Take good care of your guardian spirit, okay?
Ba-dump
What?!
I don't get what turns you on!
And I don't want to know!
It was a waste of time cheering her up in the first place!
Has a lot of issues with that statement,
like how she wasn't cheering her
up to begin with
Oh, welcome home.
How was it?
The café has a pleasant atmosphere, so you must've done a lot of reading.
Not really.
Oh, was the book you picked not so good?
Huh? Where's Kawai?
She was here reading until just now.
I don't think she even noticed you.
She left?
Without the slightest glance.
Could you cut out the whispered jabs?
Kawai.
Do you have a moment?
That part was hilarious!
I liked how the twist ended up being something stupid.
Yeah, it was so elaborate for no reason!
How do you pronounce this?
"Insouciance."
What's it mean?
A light-hearted lack of regard.
Sounds like a pretty advanced word.
Maybe I'll use it.
Huh?
What are you writing, Usa?
Your fantasies are so out of control that
you're writing your own erotic novels now?
That's the kind of self-sufficient life I want.
Usa's first novel, titled My First Time.
Firsts all round!
It's a book review!
I'm reviewing a book that I borrowed
from Kawai for my summer homework.
Oh,
so the mere use of the phrase "first time" was enough to turn you on?
If you were a car, you'd get incredible gas mileage.
It's like talking to a brick wall.
Wait, if I get caught up in this conversation, Kawai will go...
And?
nowhere.
Any book-related conversation
is enough to hook her, it seems.
And?
The customers at the café love the books you lent them.
The place itself is a little strange, but
a lot of the customers are big readers.
She looks happy.
Even Hayashi was excited about the original editions.
Huh?
Hayashi's still visiting the café?
Apparently she likes the atmosphere, so she's been there a lot.
She was a big reader in junior high, you know.
Are you serious?!
Is your inner Oddhand kicking in again?
There's no such thing!
I'll be quitting that job soon anyway.
Whoa, I need to get going!
Bye!
Is it just me, or is Usa getting nicer and nicer?
I didn't win, huh?
He'll never be able to quit that job at this rate.
They need his Oddhand powers to manage that bunch of weirdos.
Maybe masochism is infectious when living in close quarters.
What?
Does that mean Usa's going to infect me, bringing me to a whole new level?
Why don't you just leave this room and never come back?
Shiro!
Chinatsu?
Haven't seen you in a while.
What's up?
I figured you'd be lonely since I haven't been spending any time with you.
So I was going to let you do my summer project for me.
Thank you for the request!
And you can do my drills, too.
And there's yet another request!
Shiro's gas mileage is good enough to revolutionize energy as we know it.
Problem is, I have no materials or time.
Mud?
Oh, is that your lunch?
Oh yeah, Mayumi.
Could you bring me some worn-out pantyhose you don't need?
Is that your dinner?
Shiny mud balls?
Shiny Mud Balls
Those were all the rage at one point.
The key is to polish the mud with pantyhose.
I wanna try it!
Ricchan likes this kind of stuff more than you'd expect.
Well, it can't hurt to go back
to being a child now and then.
Being surrounded by shiny things can only be good.
Like marrying into money.
No child thinks that.
I'll make the shiniest ball of all!
Well, you are the oldest one here.
Shut up!
First, squeeze the water out of the mud, and then form it into a ball.
What? Damn.
I can't get it nice and round.
Once it's balled up, pour dry dirt on it,
and rub gently to get rid of the excess dirt.
Damn, I pressed too hard.
Sounds like what you do whenever you fall in love.
When you find a good target, you press too hard and leave a mess.
Just kidding.
This is weird.
A lot of people have told me I'm good at rolling balls.
Lots of people praised me at my school's ball rolling event, too.
It was a huge ball!
Nighttime exercise usually involves smaller balls.
I'm also good at getting the balls into the basket.
Nah, the balls don't fit.
When Usa isn't here, everyone gets out of control.
Once the balls are nice and round,
wrap them up and let them sit for a while.
Mayumi
Ritsu
Chinatsu
Shiro
Thanks for the food!
Is Sumiko out?
She said she was going out to see a friend.
What about Usa and Sayaka?
Usa's working.
Sayaka went back home, I think?
She probably found a man.
A date with her boyfriend? That sounds great!
Loves talking about love
No, she doesn't have a boyfriend.
She just goes from one man to the next.
So she's really popular!
No, I'm more popular.
Mayumi, your ball cracked.
Sob
Rub fine sand over the surface, and they're almost done!
You can have one of the ones Shiro made for me.
Huh? That's news to me!
Next, the moment you've been waiting for:
polishing them with pantyhose until they shine!
If you don't have pantyhose, you can use
tracksuits or reusable grocery bags instead!
It's incredibly disgusting how you refuse to call them "stockings" or "hose."
Ooh, it's getting shiny!
A date, huh...
Glance.
What a nice ball.
Ms. Loner, aren't you dating Usa?
Dating?! Wh-Why do you think that?
Aren't you a couple?
Hey, why'd I get skipped?
No.
Even though you live together?
Why'd you skip me?
Don't put it that way.
In TV shows, couples get together
just by watching fireworks together.
We haven't watched any fireworks.
That's not my point.
Neither of us is interested in a relationship!
Really? That can't be true for Usa.
I'm positive that he likes you.
He's been stuck on you all this time.
I'm really sharp when it comes to that stuff.
Sh-She said it!
Just like that!
Even Sayaka never went as far as saying it out loud!
Sadistic grade school girls are scary!
You're wrong.
Usa is just, well...
He's used to taking care of
people who are a little strange.
He could let them be, but he doesn't.
He gets stuck on them, and he ends up taking care of them.
That's just what Usa always does, since he's so nice.
That's why he's called the Oddball Handler, you see.
I'm not special to him or anything.
Ricchan...
You're such a pain!
Just accept that he likes you!
He's so obvious about it, too!
Sayaka was right! She's living in her own world!
She worries too much about other people's feelings.
Is it because she's big on reading?
What? Are you sure?
I guess I wouldn't know the details.
I'm sure.
He's taking care of a girl from his junior high at work.
Oh, so you're just jealous.
Wh-What?!
In other words, you're mad because he's just as nice to other girls.
I never said anything of the sort.
So what would you do if Usa and I started dating?
Call the police on Usa.
Then what if he started dating Mayumi?
Call the police on Mayumi.
Jeez, you're so stubborn.
Hey, cut it out.
Think about how other people feel.
If you push it hard enough that this gets weird for her
and the whole thing turns into a sappy teen rom-com, I won't be laughing!
So give it a break!
Ah, so you want her to think about how you feel!
You're outta here!
Thanks!
Hey, hey.
Hey, come on.
I'm home.
Huh? Chinatsu?
Long time no see.
The sadist girl seems awfully quiet.
Usa, was Hayashi there today?
Yep.
She must be bored lately.
What about it?
Well, you see, Ricchan...
Is something bothering you, Kawai?
Not at all.
Kawai?
What? Why?!
What happened?
Oh, there was some ball rubbing and pantyhose ripping going on.
Seriously, what happened here?!
Too bad for you, Usa.
If you had come back an hour earlier, you could've enjoyed the fruits of your youth with a blushing Ricchan.
Once you grow up, you forget a lot of things.
This was a good reminder.
Girls in grade school get so blindly excited about love that it's beyond annoying!
You like that
boy, right?
We can
tell.
He's
here!
It makes you so mad you even get
sick of the guy the rumor was about.
Talk to him!
Hey!
I pushed her too hard. Tee-hee.
I never knew it felt so good to watch someone else have their youth ruined without getting my own hands dirty!
I'm home.
Oh, long time no see.
You smell good, Sumiko!
Right. Take a look at this!
My friend taught me how to bake decorative bread.
She said it'll last about a year.
It's so cute!
She gave me the leftover dough, so would you like to make one?
It's fun, like playing with clay.
And it doesn't take long.
I wanna try!
This can be my summer project!
Now that I think about it, shiny
mud balls are a thing of the past.
They're not cute at all.
I accept your cut-and-run with pleasure!
Broken
Hey, what happened?!
I barely got to show up in the second half, and everyone's leaving me in the dark! That's cold!
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can hold our heads high and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
I have to disagree
I may be alone, but I'm not lonely
Only a special man can lay claim to this beauty
I feel bad that you fell for it, but we're just getting started here
Be it in order or chaos
We need only be ourselves
I don't care
But I can't stop thinking about it
There's a little pity in the air
I poke my nose where it doesn't belong
And applaud your eccentricity
We offer a tired mind some respite
And a lonely heart some warmth
There's always trouble brewing
And never a moment of peace
But that's the kind of place we call home
We'll all stay pitiful tomorrow
But we can smile at each other and say that's all right
When we're here
Surrounded by happiness every day
We live our lives as we please
Preview
Sayaka's friend is coming to visit Kawai Complex?
She was just one of my junior high classmates, actually.
I didn't think Sayaka had any female friends.
Really?
Don't play coy. You've won the Woman-Other-Women-Hate Award ten years running.
I'm gonna grope you later.
Now that I think about it, I haven't
heard any of you talk about friends.
A single man's best friend is his right
hand and the amazing technique of—
You're going to get this show pulled off the air if you don't stop!
Well, friends would just be a pain, so I don't need any.
Episode Eleven
I Don't Have Any Friends
You shouldn't make fun of Kawai for being a loner, then.
I may be alone, but I'm not a loner.
That's right!