HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Our Hearts Unite as One!
I am the Strongest Precure!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
The HeartCatch Orchestra...
...didn't work!
A valiant attempt, Precure.
But not nearly enough to defeat me.
My hatred will never be stopped.
It will grow without end until it has torn all of existence apart.
It's time you saw...
that your love is powerless before the force of my hate!
What's happening?!
Over here, girls!
Here he comes.
Who'dda thunk it?
These 14-year-old beauties
having to face off against Dune.
"Beauties" is debatable.
Let's go save our planet!
Yeah!
Erika, you forgot. Yuri's seventeen.
Oh man, I did!
I'm sorry, Yuri!
Go on.
Okay!
Moonlight!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said all those things before.
You were the one suffering, and I...
Your kindness and concern taught me something incredibly precious.
We had best join them.
We'll be back soon, Grandma!
Dune.
If we can't bring an end to your sadness,
that just means we aren't strong enough.
If your hatred can't be stopped, then that means our love isn't strong enough.
So...
So we'll...
So we'll just have to combine our powers.
I'll help too!
Don't forget me!
Or me!
We'll all combine our powers!
Infinite possibilities are blooming before us.
The grand flower, filling the cosmos!
With infinite power and infinite love...
The Precure with star-filled eyes...
HeartCatch Precure: Infinite Silhouette!
Your hatred will only bring you pain.
Feel this love!
Precure Fist Punch!
Sorry, sorry!
Erika!
Hey, Tsubomi!
Don't "Hey, Tsubomi" me!
I know Futaba's cute, but stop poking her all the time!
It's hard enough to resist doing it without you there.
Sorry, couldn't help it.
I'll be back later, okay, Futaba?
See you later, Mom!
Bye bye, Futaba!
Must be nice having a little sister.
It really is.
I mean, I am the little sister, so I could never really tell...
But it's nice.
It feels weird thinking of you as the big sis, though!
Hey, Sis, lend me some pocket money?
Jeez, Erika!
Hey, Itsuki! It's time for school!
Morning, you two!
Good morning!
Good morning to you too, Satsuki!
Morning.
I've just gotta get ready, so give me a sec!
Whoa!
Kumo...
jacky?!
Itsuki, Itsuki! Who is he?!
Oh, I haven't introduced you yet.
He joined the Myoudouin School yesterday.
His name's Kumamoto.
Kuma?
Kumo?
That was such a shock!
It's too early for a surprise like that!
When this Kumojacky lookalike just showed up and asked to join... Well, I screamed in shock!
They must've returned back to normal!
He'd been comatose in the hospital and had no memory of the last few years.
Then somewhere out there...
there's a Sasorina lookalike,
and a Kobraja lookalike running around!
I bet there is!
There has to be!
What about the Snackies, then?
Them too!
I bet they're all back to normal!
We've done the impossible!
This world shines so bright, and it's all thanks to us!
These 14-year-old beauties have saved the world!
I'm getting so tired of this that I'm nearly up to here with it.
I'm amazed you can give the
same speech every single day.
I think Erika still can't quite believe we all became the Infinite Precure together,
and she's been riding the high ever since.
"Infinite power" this, "infinite love" that.
I don't think Erika was ready for it all.
Quit treating me like a kid!
You two were the same!
We've done the impossible!
You were right there with me giving that speech!
Don't deny it!
You did it too!
Infinite power! Infinite love!
And we saved the world with it!
How can anything in my life compete with that?!
Woe is me!
Erika.
Are you still going on about that?
Living in the past isn't going to get you anywhere.
Sorry.
She's right!
You're gloating over what's been and gone, Erika!
Life flows like the wind! It doesn't look back! It cannot look back!
Ichuki! It'sh been sho long!
And you're looking shuper lovely as ever, Ichuki!
Thanks, Potpourri.
Chypre, how's the Great Heart Tree doing?
Good!
Everyone's Heart Seeds are helping it to grow!
It'll be fine with us watching over it!
I'm helping too!
The Great Heart Tree has watched over us all for so long.
And now, it's time for our hearts to help nurture and protect it.
We can't keep longing for
infinite power and infinite love.
We need to live our own lives.
Yeah!
Live our lives, sure... but what's that mean, exactly?
Well, doing your best to realize your dreams is a good start.
Erika, you still wanna be a pro fashion designer, right?
I'll do whatever I can to help your dream come true!
Let me help too!
And me!
And you, Yuri?
What's your dream?
My dream?
I suppose I'll have to think about what to do with my life.
Our lives...
Well, as for me...
I wanna keep training with the Myoudouin School, while trying to broaden my horizons.
Doing what?
That's a secret!
You could at least tell me.
What about you?
I'd like to go up into space again.
But this time, by my own power!
You wanna be an astronaut?!
That's my best friend for you! She dreams big!
You're wrong.
We're not best friends.
We're the bestest of friends!
If I can...
If I can make it up there,
I want to help flowers bloom
across the empty void of space.
At least then, maybe he...
The four of us Precure who defeated the Desert Apostles and saved the world
will fade into legend one day, and eventually be forgotten.
But the year we spent becoming Precure together and chasing our dreams is something I'll never forget.
Because they helped me grow,
and helped me see a brighter future.
This year has been a treasure beyond compare.
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself in the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!