Why?!
Why did Anchan have to die
because of a pathetic addict like you?!
Ishihara!
AnimeFansFTW Presents:
Sunlight was the only thing that felt right
Before I came here
But inside it feels like it keeps raining
And every drop is like the tears we can drop
Cause inside we were all alone but this place gave us something
And somehow we are strong
There’s a place inside this world where rules and dreams are not yet lost
Timing:
Durzegon
Typesetting:
Ryuga
We’ll stand and climb against these walls
Karaoke:
Durzegon
Encoding:
Ryuga
We fight this fight forever more
Editing:
xxxTristxxx
QC:
Ryuga
There’s a place inside this world where we must go back to once more
Until the day we find out fast we’re not alone
Sasaki was off to a great start
for the upcoming mayoral election
when suddenly the boys of Block 2, Cell 6 appeared.
"Hospital Director"
Doctor!  Dr. Sasaki!
What's gotten into him?
This isn't good.
He still has courtesy calls to make, too...
I'm worrying too much.
Nothing's going to happen.
Nothing's going to happen...
No, what can those brats possibly do anyway?!
Yeah! Nothing's going to happen!
I wont let anyone get in my way...
O-Oh, it's you...!
Perfect timing.
I was getting in a foul mood.
Yes, wait at the usual place.
I'll be right over.
Oh Dr.Sasaki.
I'm heading out for a bit.
I'll be back in the morning.
Doctor! You still have courtesy calls to make...!
I'm sorry, but tell them
something urgent came up.
I appreciate your help.
D-Doctor!
Ugh.  If only he didn't have that side to him...
"Komurasaki Inn"
That's a nice boy.
You waited for me in bed.
I can't wait any longer, either!
Let me see your face!
Oh, I see you haven't changed a bit, Dr. Sasaki.
You were planning to have
a lot of fun tonight, weren't you?
In that case...
...why not come with me
for old times' sake, Dr. Sasaki?
Wh-Why are you here?
What do you mean? I already told you.
I want to help you run for mayor.
You, help me? Cut the crap!
Come on now, Dr. Sasaki!
Just for a little while. Okay?
Anchan...
This is how it should be, right?
Well, we're here, Dr. Sasaki.
Hey, guys!  Sorry for the wait!
The leading man's here!
We've been expecting you, Dr. Sasaki!
That was another brilliant plan, Scam.
He gladly went to that inn
after I threatened his boy-toy into calling him.
Sorry about getting your hopes up, Dr. Sasaki.
So, are we ready?
Yep, all set.
Yeah, check it out!
It's the perfect front-row seat!
Go on, Dr. Sasaki!
Cabbage worked hard to dig it just for you.
M-Money?
You want money, right?
How much?!
How much do you want?!
I'll pay you whatever you want!
Just don't kill me!
We just want to see you enjoying yourself.
That's all.
W-wait! Wait!
All right, Cabbage! Fill it in!
Right!
Stop!
There! All done!
Now that's a sight!
Almost looks like an octopus in the sand!
Now then, Dr. Sasaki!
The tides get pretty intense on this beach.
It's quiet now, but in half an hour it'll be at full tide.
And then you and your noggin'll be
completely underwater!
Oh, here it comes!
Oh. Full tide might come sooner than I thought.
P-Please... Don't kill me...
I'll do whatever you want...
Forgive me!
Just give yourself up!
This is what you deserve, after everything you've done.
Or maybe you can have forgiveness
if you confess to every bad thing that you've done.
Maybe that'll keep the waves away?
F-Fuck you!
Hey, Turtle. That's enough fun.
We should be going now.
Yeah, you're right!
Bye, Dr. Sasaki.
Have fun being dinner for the crabs.
Hey! Wait!  This is just a joke, right?!
Hey!  Are you listening to me?! Hey!
I-I don't want to die...
I'll talk! I'll say whatever you want!
Don't go! Save me!
With his face pointed out to sea,
he couldn't see behind him.
"Are you guys still there?
I don't want to die. I'm afraid..."
Filled with the fear of death, Sasaki screamed.
Help me!
"Komurasaki Inn"
I'm coming in.
Oh, you're still in bed?
Your friend left early this morning.
"The waves of the tide coming at my face...
Not being able to move my hands and feet.
Was it all a nightmare?
No, it wasn't..."
That unfathomably deep sense
of foreboding made Sasaki turn pale and tremble.
"Setsuko Koike"
Sorry I don't have any clothes for you to wear.
No, I'm the one who should apologize,
being a burden like this...
I didn't know you were living on your own, though.
Yeah, I changed hospitals,
and things got tough at home for various reasons...
I see.
So... did you go to Numazu?
Yeah...
Ishiara!
Why?
Why won't you kill me, Sakuragi?
You had so many chances to kill me!
Why didn't you?!
You did the same thing then, too!
You gave me Hagino's suicide note
and then turned your back to me!
Where are you going, Sakuragi?!
Where were you about to go, leaving me behind?!
Cut the crap about not messing
with your friends and face me!
Kill me now, Sakuragi!
Get lost, Ishihara!
Never show your face around us again.
You're not even worth killing.
S-Sakuragi...
"Ishihara's nothing but filthy, shitty garbage.
He's not human.
He's not worth taking responsibility for.
Even Anchan would disapprove of me if I did it.
Rokurota Sakuragi had saved Mario
from a lengthy imprisonment.
I realized it.
I realized where Anchan was going
after he turned his back to Ishihara.
He wanted to see the rest of my fight.
Is it weird to think that?
That's amazing.
Ishihara even stabbed him in the gut.
But he didn't care about that.
He just kept walking towards the gate...
Amazing... He really was amazing...
Ishihara and Sasaki didn't beat him at all.
Anchan... Anchan! Won!
Isn't that obvious, though.
Sakuragi would never lose.
Yeah.
Thank you, Sakuragi, for stopping Mario...
"Municipal Hall"
Our next candidate is Gisuske Sasaki.
It's okay. Nothing to worry about.
Nothing's going to happen.
Begin when you're ready.
If I can just get through this, I'll be major tomorrow.
And then those brats won't be able to mess with me!
Wh-When I'm elected m-mayor...
We're just getting started, Dr. Sasaki...
"Broadcast Room"
Here comes the real fun, Dr. Sasaki...
Hey, what's wrong with him?
He's not saying anything...
Okay! Let's get started!
Right.
I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Help me! I'll confess everything!
That's... his voice...
Yeah...
That's right! I was constantly
raping boys at the reformatory!
I paid that guard Ishihara
to let me have my favorite boys!
No! This isn't what you think!
It's some sort of mistake!
The incident with Eiichi Hagino was entirely my fault!
I used him as a plaything
and drove him to suicide!
And then I covered it up
as an accident so no one would find out!
I was behind Rokurota Sakuragi's death too!
He knew everything about the Hagino incident!
Forgive me! I'm sick!
--I'm a perverted old man who rapes underage boys!
--N-No... No...
No!
"Sasaki drops out of race"
Good thing that creep dropped out.
Yeah. I almost voted for him too...
He even mortgaged his hospital
to run in the election.
He's done for.
Thank god he didn't get elected mayor.
Summer's coming to an end, Sakuragi.
I think the boys from Block 2, Cell 6
can move forward on their own now.
"Sakuragi"
So, I've decided to move forward, too...
Bye, Sakuragi.
Yo.
I saw the papers. You really went all-out.
That's just like you, of course.
Mario...
Did you... Ishihara...
These were taken from Anchan's body.
Setsuko wants us to each keep one.
I didn't need to.
Anchan put an end to him long ago.
Everything was already settled.
You guys might not be satisfied,
but I'm content with it this way.
Good job, Mario!
What are you guys gonna do now?
I'm gonna be an SDF officer.
That's all I want.
I'm gonna stick with the black market for a while.
The money's good!
Plus I can't let Lilly get too lonely.
I'm gonna head back home for now.
My old lady's probably worried about me.
I'm gonna get my chance to be a singer someday!
I'll do anything, as long as it means good food!
That's all you ever care about, Cabbage!
What about you, Mario?
Dunno. Good question.
You never change.
Right now, I don't know where I'll go or what I'll do.
But, someday...
Someday, I'll be like you and...
Sasaki had lost his hospital, his wealth, and his honor
and Ishihara had become the shell of a man.
The battle was finally over.
But the six boys of Block 2, Cell 6
didn't regard it as the end of Ishiara and Sasaki.
"This is no different from spitting out chewed gum."
The six boys etched into their minds,
"We can fly freely now,
Love, money, success, and satisfaction
will finally be ours!"
What could I keep watching over
same ta manazashi
with these empty eyes of mine?
nani o mi tsuzukeru no ka
I can even sacrifice
mamoru beki mono
my life for those
whom I must protect.
kono mi sae oshiku wa nai
even if I rot away
just keep on running
so far away but I never give it up
Our unbreakable bond
ima toke nai kuzuna ga
has begun to entwine with fate,
unmei to koosaku shi te yuku
guiding us to the endless future
kagiri nai mirai e
laid out before us.
tsuzui te yuku
and I will get over it now
a far off distance
Held back feelings, Mario explodes.
I don't want to give her to anyone.