Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, what's your father like?
Is he nice, or is he scary?
Miss Layla's father is a workaholic
and he has no clue about her feelings.
Even on her special birthday, he's working.
Oh! If he keeps acting that way,
I feel sorry for Miss Layla!
I do! I do!
Yaritai koto wa nani
Sou kikareru tabi
Aoi sora miageta
Kotae wa only my heart
Honto ni daiji na kotoba
wa kantan ni wa iwanai
Hikari ga yubisasu
basho e to hashiridasu yo
Dakishimetai mono nara
nakitai hodo mune ni aru
Egakitsuzukete yuku kitto take it someday
Shiroi kumo ga nagareru
chiheisen no mukou ni
Naranderu mirai wa itsumo soba ni aru kara
Can I do a grieving
chimpanzee pose at the end today?
No.
Oh, sorry.
My chance!
I should say something to make them laugh!
As you may expect from roses!
Roses...
Oh! Darn it!
I wish I could be better at ad-libbing.
That look is perfect!
Anyway, that's a big bouquet.
I know. It's for Miss Layla.
Her father, Mr. Hamilton, is here.
Oh? Does he come here often?
Well, he's very busy, so he's rarely here.
He's the owner of Hamilton Hotels.
Hamilton Hotels?
I think we have some in Japan too.
They're all over the world.
Wow...
Oh, I need to deliver this quick.
He sounds great.
"An Amazing Star Even In Tough Times."
It seems like "Cinderella"
will be one of Layla's best works.
How is the box-office record?
The audience numbers
are the best in history.
Who are these three fairy godmothers?
They're newcomers who
passed the audition this year.
I see.
Father.
Ah, Layla.
Congratulations on
the successful production.
Thank you.
And thank you for the beautiful flowers too.
There is no flower that
exceeds your beauty, Layla.
I really would like you
to see my show this time.
I don't have the time.
By the way, we're having a party
with top business leaders tonight.
Make sure you come to
the party after your show.
I will.
Kalos, please be her escort.
Yes, I will.
And let's invite those
three fairy godmothers, too.
Those three?
It's important to provide
them with publicity.
We need to have the next
generation of stars after you leave.
Well then, I will see you tonight, Layla.
He's such a busy person.
Yes. So busy that he has never
seen one of my shows to the end.
We did it perfectly again today.
The audience seemed like they were
waiting for the transformation scene,
so it's really worth doing, you know?
Why don't we stumble off the
stage when we exit next time?
No way.
I agree.
That's what I figured.
Don't give an unfocused performance
just because you're a little popular now!
We're sorry.
But we were perfect today.
Our top star is in a bad mood.
Maybe she's more uptight than usual
because her father's
here to see her performance.
But I think he left
without watching the show.
What?
I didn't know.
All of you,
go to the costume department.
A party?!
It's kind of awkward.
I wonder if I should say something?
It was too bad that your father
couldn't stay for your show today.
That's nothing new.
Oh, really?
This is awkward.
So beautiful.
It's Layla Hamilton.
She is stunning.
You look beautiful, Layla.
Thank you, Father.
Hey, Sora.
What's wrong?
Somehow, I feel like I don't belong here.
No, I'll be all right.
Hello...
It's definitely more nerve-racking
than performing on stage.
That's true.
It seems like they're drawing attention.
Yes.
By the way, do you know that man?
He looks familiar.
If I remember correctly,
he's a movie producer.
That's right. He's looking for
a heroine for his next movie.
Audition for the role.
Miss Layla is going to audition for a movie?
This is a great opportunity.
To advance your career from
being Kaleido Stage's top star
to becoming a worldwide top star.
You have that much commercial value.
I understand.
Miss Layla.
Miss Layla!
I saw you in the newspaper.
Aren't you that fairy godmother?
You're so cute.
Hey, how do you do that Triple Illusion?
Do something for us.
Yes! Please show us.
What should we do?
You want to do something?
Let's put on a little show.
What?
Sora, let's do it.
Yeah!
Here!
There, there, there, there, there, there!
Tada!
It's them.
Here, Sora!
Here!
Tada!
Well, well, not bad.
If you would come to the
actual stage, you could...
Thank you, thank you.
Please come see Kaleido Stage.
Now, for a little party joke.
Ladies.
Oh, Miss Layla's father.
I have a favor to ask.
Yes?
To tell you the truth,
tomorrow is Layla's birthday.
We're having a party at
our house in the afternoon.
Won't you three come to the party too?
Really?
Definitely!
Oh, I know!
If you have the day off tomorrow,
please come and watch
our show after the party.
I have to work tomorrow.
I will make sure you get paid for your work.
So please be there.
Please, wait.
What?
We don't need to be paid.
We'll still go even if we're not paid.
You certainly are generous.
You will never be successful like that.
He's awful.
That's nothing new.
I wonder if Miss Layla is lonely?
So, I think we should brighten
up the mood at the party tomorrow.
Oh...
That's what I'm thinking...
Oh!
What?
Oh, nothing...
What?!
Cancelled?
Yes, it was cancelled.
What's going on?
Can we at least give her a present?
What are you all doing?
Well, Miss Layla...
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My father asked you to come, didn't he?
Yes.
Excuse me,
but why was it suddenly cancelled?
It wasn't sudden.
Every year, my father invites
guests to the party by paying them.
But a party like that is meaningless.
I suppose so.
That's why I cancel it every year.
It sounds like your father doesn't
understand your feelings at all.
That's how things work here.
But even so, he cares
about me in his own way.
That's enough for me.
Well, haven't you heard enough?
Please go home.
Okay.
I have to practice now.
Practice?
At home?
Wow...
Amazing.
I can't believe there's a
practice room inside the house.
How often do you practice here, Miss Layla?
Unless I have practice for
a new production, every day.
And on the days when my
performance was unsatisfactory on stage.
That often?
It's your birthday today and you're still...
Someday, I want my father
to acknowledge Kaleido Stage.
And for that, my performance
has to be the best at all times.
Miss Layla...
The movie audition, maybe you're actually...
I will audition for the movie.
I'll make sure to live
up to his expectations.
Because I don't want to disappoint him.
Aren't you satisfied now?
Please leave.
Okay, thank you.
All right, I've decided!
Decided what?
Then after the curtain drops,
the curtain call will become
Miss Layla's birthday party!
Doesn't it sound like magic?
Now that we've decided
to do this, let's hurry!
Mia is the director.
Ken and Jean are in charge of the stage sets.
And Anna and Miss Sarah,
please make the costumes.
Oh, Marion, you need to help us, too.
Since we don't have much
time left before the evening show,
let's get started now.
Huh?
What are you all doing?
Hurry, hurry!
Once she makes up her mind,
she's the type that runs with it.
That's one of her good traits.
I couldn't agree more.
Is there any sort of trick to this?
Just do an adequate job, I guess.
Oh...
What is this? It's fun!
Marion!
Ready?
Yes.
I wonder how she'll react?
I can't wait.
Are you up to something again?
Oh, we're going to celebrate
Miss Layla's birthday.
But please keep it a secret.
I hope everything turns out well.
Yes! Thank you.
Okay?
Jonathan, you're going to hand the
cake to Miss Layla at the end.
All right.
Now, everything is all set to go.
No, not yet.
Without this, it won't be magic.
Are you serious?
Of course.
Even if you want it, that's impossible.
You can't contact him?
Well, I can contact him, but...
You can't?
I guess we can't do it after all.
Oh, fine!
It's time to sink or swim!
Oh, then...
Yeah, I'll try to contact him.
Thank you!
Yes. Mr. Hamilton please. Yes.
She needs to talk to him
concerning Miss Layla.
Her name is Sora Naegino, from Kaleido Stage.
Oh, well, she's still new.
I'm not suspicious or anything.
I am a fairy godmother!
What?!
That sounds plenty suspicious.
No way!
Mr. Hamilton, you have a phone call.
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
But...
It's from someone called "fairy godmother."
Shall I contact the police?
No, I'll take it.
I'm sorry to call you at work.
So, what business does a
fairy godmother have with me?
Do you want to get
paid for the party after all?
The party was cancelled.
What?
It has been cancelled every year.
Miss Layla was practicing by herself.
That's ridiculous.
We're having a birthday
party for her at Kaleido Stage.
And we would very much
like you to attend the party.
That's impossible.
Even if it's impossible, please!
Actually, I want you to
see Miss Layla's show, but...
It takes four hours from here
to Cape Mary even by private jet.
I won't make it in time
for the start of the show.
Then at least, can you make it
to the end of the show? Please!
Thank you for letting me know.
Thanks to you, I now know how Layla feels.
Looks like she wasn't happy
with a party that I bought for her.
You still don't get it.
What?
You don't understand how Miss Layla feels.
It doesn't matter how many people are there.
If the person she wants
most to be there doesn't come,
she'll just feel even more alone.
She feels lonely and sad.
I think that's why she cancels the
parties and just practices by herself.
She needs her father.
So, please.
Please come.
Inviting Miss Layla's father?
Yes. It seems Sora is calling him right now.
That's impossible.
You never know, because it's Sora.
Come in.
Excuse us.
What is it?
Miss Layla, your father's like,
coming to see your show.
My father? There is no way.
But today's your birthday, so...
What's going on?
Happy birthday, Layla!
Happy birthday, Miss Layla!
Sora...
This is from all of us.
A small...
present.
That's impossible.
All right!
Yeah! It was a big success!
We did it, Sora!
Yeah, I'm so glad.
Miss Layla seemed happy with...
What is the meaning of this?
Did you come up with this?!
Yes.
Stop doing things like this!
I've never appeared so dumbstruck
in front of an audience before.
Oh... I'm sorry.
Please don't do anything like this again.
Excuse me, Miss Layla.
What?
You still have something to say?
At the very least, please take this cake.
Well, the cake isn't really that important,
but there's a message.
I got this message personally
from your father.
What?
That's all right.
I thought everything turned out fine.
Don't be discouraged, Sora.
It's not your fault.
It's your fault.
I knew it. It was like,
unnecessary after all.
I got this message personally
from your father.
Please don't do anything like this again.
Why am I so irritated?
Happy birthday, Miss Layla.
It's because I pushed for the birthday party.
No, we were all in on it.
I guess Miss Layla doesn't
like that sort of thing.
In the end, I ignored Miss Layla's feelings
just like her father did.
What should we do with that cake?
You want to eat it?
Well, we did take the time to make it.
Yeah.
I'm going to at least
deliver the message to her.
Sora.
She may get mad at you again.
Well, I'm already used to
someone being mad at me.
Sora, I'm coming in!
Please do!
Oh, here it is! Here it is.
I'm so glad.
What is it?
Miss Layla's maid just
came to pick up the cake.
What?
She said she'll at least accept the
cake since you took the time to make it.
Really! Layla can be so
pretentious sometimes.
Then, I will leave the cake here.
Excuse me.
Fax?
Happy birthday, Layla.
You're always sparkling in my heart.
My Kaleido Star.
It's so difficult somehow.
I guess even real families worry
about their opinions of each other.
I wonder if that's the way everyone acts?
I think that it is.
I see.
Won't you worry about my
opinions once in a while too?
No, I will not.
Wha...
Happy birthday, Miss Layla.
When you sabishii toki doushitemasuka
Never say sonna no wakannai
Nemuru asobu magazine mekuru
Sabishii toki wa sabishii yo
Mienai denpa ga kyou mo
tulututu machi ni tobikau
Anyway kokoro no bekutoru
so many reason hanashiteru
Jiyuu ni sora o tobitai keredo
Hane o hirogeru basho ga nai
Demo shinjiteru
Katachi no nai mirai ga aru yo
Katachi ni shitai watashi ga iru
Kanashikutemo machigai demo
Omou mama fly to the free
"Next Kaleido Star"
Don't you have any stars other than Layla?
And so, for the heroine of the
upcoming production, "The Little Mermaid,"
I end up auditioning in front of an
important person without a rehearsal!
But Sora makes a mistake.
She becomes afraid and unable to jump.
Don't worry, Sora. Trust me.
What's gonna happen to me? What? What?
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"My Amazing Challenge For the Lead Role."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...