Everyone, Kaleido Star is about to start!
When watching Kaleido Star,
please keep the room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
I'm Sora Naegino.
I came to America all by myself
with aspirations of joining Kaleido Stage.
Everything is new to me,
but I'm doing my best in the spirit
of "try it rather than think about it."
There's nothing I can't do if I try,
and if I can do it without
trying, that'll be super lucky.
And if I'm gonna do it, I just
gotta do it! Gotta! Gotta! That's me.
Well, well, well, do you
know anyone who's difficult?
Rosetta seems to be just that kind of person.
She's a talented diabolo performer,
but I end up performing with her on stage.
But wait, I've never
worked with diabolo before.
Oh boy, what should I do? What? What?
What is it that you want to do?
Every time I was asked that
I looked up at the blue sky
The answer is only in my heart
I don't easily say the
words that are really important
I start running towards
the place the light points to
There's so much in my heart
that I want to embrace, I could cry
I'll keep painting my way,
I promise, take it someday
Beyond the horizon,
where the white clouds drift
The future is lined up and
it'll always be there by my side
Jonathan, this way!
So this is Jonathan's pool?
This is how it turned out
after I followed Kalos's request.
I'm glad that Jonathan seems to like it.
It's great, it's great!
It's so big.
He looks happy.
Jonathan, over here!
Jonathan!
He's ignoring us.
Ungrateful.
I guess I won't be able to be
with him all the time anymore.
Marion, Vince is back from the market.
Your meal is here, Jonathan.
Vince, Jonathan says he's tired of waiting!
That girl...
"The Amazing Girl Who Doesn't Smile"
Okay, Rosetta.
Your provisional contract lasts one week.
After you finish tonight's performance,
we'll do a formal contract including
an extension of your time here.
I hope you understand these arrangements.
Rosetta?
The French diabolo prodigy
performer is finally here.
That's right.
She's really a genius!
I'm a fan of hers, so I couldn't help it.
Sora.
What are you doing?
We're just passing by.
We weren't eavesdropping or anything.
He's not going to buy it.
Sora, come in for a second.
Yes?
Boss wants to ask you to
be a guide for the guest.
Really?
This is Sora Naegino.
She will take you to your room.
You should rest a little.
I'm Sora Naegino, nice to meet you.
See you later then.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Um, well, I'm your fan...
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mia.
I'm Anna.
Nice to meet you.
Where is Layla Hamilton?
She's not in yet.
I see.
Your baggage has already
been delivered to the dormitory.
I'll take you there.
Let's go, Rosetta.
Oh, Boss.
Thank you for building
a big pool for Jonathan.
This is your room, Rosetta!
The sea breeze is nice, so
I'll keep the windows open, okay?
Sora?
Huh? What?
So Kalos only arranged a regular
room for me like the ones you have?
Huh?
I was the youngest winner in
the world diabolo competition,
and I won for the next four years straight.
That's right, I remember watching you on TV
when you were the youngest
to win the competition.
You were answering TV interviewers
so actively despite being so young.
That's why I remember it so well.
Traveling around the world from
one circus to another all by herself,
a French born genius child
performer of diabolo!
That's Belgium.
I was born in Belgium and studied in France.
You're supposed to be my guide,
but you don't know
anything about me, do you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
How was it, Sora?
It's finally come to Kaleido Stage,
the super diabolo performed
by world champion Rosetta!
If you want to be a world champion yourself,
you can get your own diabolo
at our gift shop starting at $30.
Miss Rosetta!
Excuse us.
We want you to like, teach us diabolo.
My agreement with my agent does not allow me
to display my diabolo
performance except on stage.
Please shut the door.
I can't concentrate.
I'm sorry.
How rude!
It's like, poor little me.
--That girl is amazing.
--She's a genius.
She's amazing.
But I wonder why?
It's not that fun to watch.
She's like a well-oiled diabolo machine.
Mom, I'm bored.
A clown's coming on stage after this, okay?
It's time for an intermission now. Oh!
Welcome to Kaleido Stage.
Miss Layla, how was my performance?
It was perfect.
There were no mistakes.
Thank you.
I'll enjoy your show for the week.
I'm sure I can be with you longer than that.
It sounds like you're quite confident.
Oh, yes.
Rosetta, I need to talk to you.
Can you spare a minute?
About the contract extension, right?
No. Today is your last performance.
What?
Maybe I should have picked something
more suited for a younger audience?
As for the pay, I will pay you one
week's worth as agreed in the contract.
But you don't need to
appear on stage anymore.
Well, everyone, it's almost time to start!
I demand a satisfactory explanation
from you in the dressing room!
I'm going just for a while.
Sora, it's almost our turn!
Rosetta, your diabolo is wonderful.
That's why I invited you.
However, the audience at Kaleido
Stage did not enjoy your diabolo.
I realized that when I
watched your show today.
Then I'll rearrange the diabolo combinations.
Rosetta, I'm sorry, but...
I didn't make any mistakes!
It was a perfect performance.
They don't enjoy my diabolo
because the audience at Kaleido
Stage isn't sophisticated enough!
So you are saying that
it's the audience's fault?
You believe you're right and
you can stay the way you are?
I'm a world champion.
The world recognizes my diabolo skills.
Kaleido Stage exists to
entertain the audience.
And the audience was not
enjoying your performance.
Why can't they enjoy my performance?
Kaleido Stage is not an athletic
event to show off your skills.
Oh, excuse me.
I will talk to your agent.
Ken, when you have time, take
Rosetta and show her around Marine Park.
But, Boss...
Don't treat me like I'm stupid!
Rosetta!
What?
How should I know?
What's going on?
What's wrong with her?
She runs fast too.
Boss, you're really not
going to allow her on stage?
Of course.
That was not a show.
But it's only after one show...
Watching it once was enough.
You don't know that.
She may be able to change.
I wouldn't mind bringing
Rosetta back on stage, but...
Oh, really?
You have to be with her.
What?
Excuse me?
The contract is for six more days.
During that period, you do what
you can to get her back on the stage.
Well, that is to say...
See you later.
--Oh, wait.
Act two of Cinderella
will be starting shortly!
--Oh, no! Let's hurry, Sora!
--I've never done diabolo before.
It's a crucial time for you right now.
My performance is always perfect.
When you were little, that was enough
for you to get plenty of attention,
but the number of jobs
has decreased recently.
You have to change a little.
Hang in there for a little longer.
All right?
But I'm performing flawlessly...
Are you all right, Sora?
Not at all.
Why don't you just tell
him that you can't do it?
Yeah, why don't you?
Oh, but I'll still give it a try.
Of course you will.
Oh!
Oh! Miss Sarah! Miss Sarah!
We have a problem!
What's wrong?
Rosetta's not here!
Oh, my, that is a problem.
I wonder if she left for home?
At this time?
Rosetta! Rosetta!
Rosetta!
Oh, really! Where did you go?!
--Rosetta! Rosetta!
--Oh, Sora, she's right here!
What?!
I'm so glad.
Why does Kalos want me to pair up with you?
Do you really think you can do it?
I'm planning on trying first,
rather than thinking about it.
You know, if you start thinking,
you only worry about things,
like, "What if I make a mistake?"
I don't think it makes for a fun show.
We should always expect
ourselves to perform flawlessly.
It's better not to do it
than to make mistakes.
There's no way I can perform like you do.
So I want them to at least enjoy it.
Or rather, maybe it's more about
trying hard than being perfect.
Working hard?
Ken!
I got these for you.
I thought they could be useful.
Look.
Wow! Where did you get these?
We stocked too many.
I was wondering what to do with all these.
It's my fault, isn't it?
Sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
The audience didn't enjoy my show.
That's all.
Sorry, Rosetta. Sorry...
In the end, maybe I can't...
I don't think it's your fault.
What?
She was nine years old when
she won the world championship,
but if I remember correctly,
she started diabolo when she was five.
At that age, I just loved Kaleido
Stage and enjoyed watching it
without thinking about anything else.
Me too.
She may never have had a chance to
enjoy the show as part of the audience.
Ken, I'm going to give it a try.
To the airport.
She's gone.
Okay.
Oh, Ken?
A show that's not perfect,
but still entertaining? What is that?
Miss, do you know the people on that bike?
They've been following us the whole way.
What's wrong?
Sora wants you to see her show.
Why do I have to?
You have to see it.
Go, Jonathan!
Catch! What is this?!
It's a fish.
It's a saurel! Saurel!
You're doing good, Jonathan!
Give it back to me!
Give it back, Jonathan!
Rosetta! Here, hurry!
I'm just going to take a quick look. Oh!
Sora, jump in!
I did it!
Sora, you're awful!
Jonathan's better than you!
Jonathan!
Wait!
Hey, Jonathan! Hold it right there!
You're doing good, Jonathan!
Sora, go!
You! There! I did it!
Look!
You're awesome!
You did great!
Sora, go for it!
Sora!
Isn't it strange?
Huh?
When I'm watching Sora's
show, it makes me nervous,
because I'm worried she's
going to make a mistake.
Here!
She does, in fact, make mistakes,
--but once in a while, she
can be incredibly wonderful.
--Oh, where are you, Jonathan?
Unbelievable, like magic.
Please watch Sora's performance today.
Sora's performance?
Here!
Yeah!
Amazing...
It's completely different from my show.
Sora...
Sora.
Rosetta! You came to see the show!
I want to see what our diabolo
performance might look like together.
Me too.
Okay.
You'll do it perfectly,
while I try really hard at it.
Don't you think that'll be interesting?
That's a good idea.
But to do that, Sora's diabolo
needs to improve a little more.
Instead of thinking, I'll just try it!
Wrong!
Okay!
Do it as if you're going toward the diabolo!
Don't actually collide with it.
Okay.
The upright Devil.
--It means that she needs
to make extreme efforts.
--Again!
--Okay.
Not good. One more time!
Okay.
Reading Tarot cards by
myself only makes me feel empty.
This... this... this is really tough!
Only one more day left until the time limit.
We don't have time to goof off!
Looks like they've
managed to make the deadline.
Building a new set in such a hurry was tough.
Sorry.
Well, I think it's an interesting idea.
Did you say it was their idea?
Yeah.
They make a good team.
Now, at last, it's time for the
first diabolo battle in history!
In this corner, the world diabolo champion,
Rosetta!
In the other corner, with
five days of diabolo experience,
Sora!
Now, let's see the long-awaited
outcome of this battle!
Ready?
Start!
Okay!
Doing good! Go, Sora!
Rosetta, don't lose!
Here!
Go!
Not so fast!
Ouch! Shoot!
Rosetta made a mistake!
I can't believe this!
Winner, Rosetta!
Champion!
They did it.
You're amazing, Sora.
Awesome!
Bravo! Bravo!
You changed Rosetta, Sora.
Sora, I remember back
when I was nine years old
and competing in the world championship.
Everyone was smiling behind the interviewers.
Everyone was saying,
"It was fun," or "It was interesting."
Everyone was happy.
Back then, I really felt
glad I was doing diabolo.
I completely forgot how
happy I was during that time.
The time when I loved diabolo so much.
I remembered it today.
Thanks to Kaleido Stage,
and thanks to you, Sora.
Wait a sec, Rosetta.
Wow... Wow...
What? What?
I owe it to you, Sora.
What?
Thanks to your magic, Sora.
Wow...
So you're going home after all?
Yes. Thank you, Sora.
Yesterday's show was
successful because of your talent.
It was very captivating.
Oh...
No, I owe it all to Kaleido Stage.
I really would have
liked to extend the contract.
I can't.
Is this your revenge for
what happened a week ago?
I want to go home and develop
my own diabolo over again.
Boss, you look like your
girlfriend just broke up with you.
Yeah, that's what I feel like.
See you again, Rosetta!
Merci, Sora.
When you're lonely, what do you do?
Never say you don't get any of that
Sleep, play, flip through a magazine
When you're lonely, you're lonely
Like always, invisible vibes fly
around the city today, tulututu
Anyway, the vector of my heart
is talking about so many reasons
I want to be free and fly the skies
But I don't have space to spread my wings
But I have faith
There is a future yet to be shaped
And there's a me that I want to shape
Even if I'm sad, even if it's a mistake
I'll do what I want and
fly towards the freedom
"Next Kaleido Star"
You have that much commercial value.
And so, Miss Layla's father
came to Kaleido Stage,
but he left without seeing her show.
It seems he sees his daughter as
nothing more than a business tool.
Even on her birthday, he tried to get
away with it by just spending money.
So we'll just have to make her
birthday party a success all by ourselves!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"An Amazing Star Even In Tough Times."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...