Boss...
What's going to happen to us?
Don't worry.
If we keep believing in the Precure, we'll be fine.
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
For the Earth, and For Our Dreams!
The Precure's Final Transformation!
Father!
Yuri...
I have no right to hold you in my arms.
All of this was because of the weakness in my heart.
The Great Heart Tree, protector of all lives and hearts...
I believed that by studying it...
I could bring happiness to the world.
As if by magic.
I convinced myself it was possible to just make people happy,
and refused to accept the truth.
Happiness is something we all find for ourselves, slowly but surely.
But to complete my research,
I allied myself with Dune, and
allowed him to rob me of my heart.
And I became Sabark: his minion,
hell-bent on destroying the world.
Yuri, I'm so...
Cure Moonlight!
Get away from Professor Sabark!
Father?
I'm sorry, Yuri.
I ended up creating Dark Precure for the sole purpose of bringing you misery.
She existed purely to destroy Cure Moonlight—
a doll without a heart.
But it's okay now, Dark Precure.
It's all over.
Yuri.
I created Dark Precure using the fruits of my research into the Great Heart Tree
and cells from your own body.
She is your sister.
I forced my daughters to fight each other.
Dark Precure...
You are my daughter.
Father.
Such a heart-wrenching tale.
I did so enjoy it.
You never cease to amuse me, Professor Tsukikage.
Dune!
Don't you go blaming me, Professor Tsukikage!
It was you who wanted to make use of my power.
When you were conducting research in France,
you chose to become one of us.
And your research proved most helpful in
breaching the Great Heart Tree's defenses.
Thank you, Professor Tsukikage.
I couldn't have desiccated this planet without you.
And now your last hope, the Precure,
will learn unyielding despair at my hands!
I suppose you hate me too?
Bravo!
You're far too weak!
The weak are but prey for the strong.
Is that not the natural order?
Father!
Yuri.
Look after your mother.
Father!
Father...
Dune!
Am I to have a taste of your hatred next?
Let me go.
I won't!
You can't fight just to vent your anger and hatred.
But I...
I do hate him!
It's his fault...
that my father and Cologne were taken from me!
If that hatred gives me strength... then I'll use it!
Don't say such awful things!
The Yuri I admire would never say things like that!
Please.
If you fight with hatred in your heart, you won't win!
We have to find the strength to move on,
and not get dragged down by sadness and hate!
Why is it we've fought as Precure this whole time?
What was it your father and Cologne wanted you to do?
But I...
I can't...
Tsukikage Yuri!
The Cure Moonlight I always respected...
What is it you want to do?
What is it you need to do?
And what are you fighting for?
You have to remember!
We'll fight not with hatred, but with love.
Tsubomi, let's transform.
Right!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
The feelings that got me here all seemed so half-hearted
But there's no turning back now
I just have to trust in all my hard work, and take the first step
Now's the time to take the plunge, ready, go!
So no matter how afraid we feel
We'll never give up, cause even though you can't see it
We've found a treasure more precious than any other
In the sunny skies of my heart
I soar into a higher octave
My heart goes on, and when it resounds with all of my friends
Those distant dreams can one day become reality
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, sparkling in the Moon's light!
Cure Moonlight!
Our limits are just an illusion we make because we're afraid
I've come to understand that now
You've always believed in me, been there to support me
You've given me such courage
You saw the way out of the dark
So I know your eyes will be able to see
The true light within that no one else can find
In the boundless skies of my heart
This melody takes flight
My heart goes on, and I won't let a moment go to waste
And though my tears fall, slowly the seed shall bloom into a beautiful flower
In the sunny skies of my heart
I soar into a higher octave
My heart goes on, and when it resounds with all of my friends
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Those distant dreams can one day become reality
By love's gentle touch, and the light of the stars, we're all shining here together
Heart Catch!
Let's do this, with all our heart and soul!
HeartCatch Mirage!
Everyone, let's finish this!
Mirror, o mirror, grant we Precure your power!
The shining flowers illuminating the world.
HeartCatch Precure: Super Silhouettes!
Flowers, bloom tall!
Precure HeartCatch Orchestra!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself in the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
With our friendship...
...our courage...
...and all our hope!
Infinite possibilities shall bloom!
The grand flower, filling the cosmos!
HeartCatch Precure: Infinite Silhouette!
Taste this punch of love!
HeartCatch Precure:
Our Hearts Unite as One!
I am the Strongest Precure!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!