kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
For now, practice using the mouthpiece only.
Ehhh?
Dissatisfied?
No...
Well, it's just that... I really want to play as well as Rio-senpai as soon as I can...
I'm very Spartan, you know.
Got it! I look forward to learning from you!
Now go eat breakfast first.
The dining hall is over there. I'm going on ahead.
Yes, ma'am!
It's rough and ragged.
Let's do our best from today onwards!
Good morning!
You really suck!
First Battle
The Story of a Chair
All of this was originally prepared to welcome you last night.
And we put our hearts into making this.
I'm very thankful!
Oh, that reminds me, Rio.
Did you bring in everything that was being dried up there?
No.
I don't know anything about it.
That's odd...
Get it together, Noël!
If you're going to sleep, at least do it after you eat.
I'm giving it... my all...
This isn't your all!
Trying...
That's...
Rio-senpai's...
Hurry it up. The food is getting cold.
Now then, allow me to properly introduce the members of 1121st Platoon.
First is our Commander.
2nd Lieutenant Filicia Heideman. I'm a tank commander.
Let's have fun together!
Nice to meet you!
This is...
Hey, Noël...
Kannagi... Noël.
Corporal Kannagi. She's a pilot.
She's also a mechanic.
Nice to meet you!
And the last one is...
Private Second Class Suminoya Kureha. I'm a gunner.
Listen.
Although I'm younger than you, I came here first.
So you should listen to every—
She ran out of strength, huh?
Thanks for your hard work, Noël-chan.
Well, let's eat.
Eh?
But...
Geez, it's fine!
Well then, let's eat.
Let's eat.
I'm so happy.
I personally made the bacon. Give it a try.
Okay!
Being a soldier and playing the bugle requires a strong body.
So eat up and grow stronger!
I'll do my best.
Kureha.
Yes, ma'am?
After we're done...
...show her around the base.
Roger.
Attention!
I'm actually very busy, but I don't really have a choice.
Since this was an order, I have to show you around.
Y–Yes! I hope we can work well together, Kureha-san!
Don't be so informal with me, Private Sorami!
I'm sorry!
Um... Private Suminoya.
Good.
First, face the national and platoon flags...
Salute!
The 1121st Platoon currently only has five members.
A 2nd Lieutenant, a Sergeant Major, a Corporal, and two Privates.
And thus, five in total.
Yes, Private Suminoya.
That is the smallest size a platoon can be.
In other words...
...we're all elites.
I understand.
Our platoon is equipped with...
One tank, one heavy machine gun, two light machine guns,
four rifles, and five handguns...
Using these weapons, our mission is to ensure that the region around the Seize border remains safe.
Excuse me...
P-Private Suminoya! I have a question!
Very well. You are permitted to speak, Private Sorami.
I...
If I remember correctly, beyond Seize is...
It is true that the area beyond is Nomansland.
But this is where the border of Helvetia extends to.
This is the national border! The front lines!
A very important base!
We cannot fail to keep our vigil.
At night, it'll be divided up between the five of us.
It's only for two years, so cheer up!
And then there's this.
It's the only hotline in the town.
In other words...
If a call comes, it must be something serious.
And then, everyone will be woken up,
and we'll immediately be placed on Level-One Alert status.
Understood?
Yes, Private Suminoya!
The second floor is the Commander's quarters as well as the battle strategy room.
Under normal conditions, entry is...
...freely permitted for now.
But be sure to knock first!
This is the bath.
Boiling water and cleaning are a part of regular duties.
And then there's...
Bathing is done in order of rank, right?
Actually, no.
Don't you think it's more enjoyable to bathe together?
Commander!
What are you doing?
Cleaning the bath.
Isn't it Noël-chan's turn?
But she seemed pretty worn out.
Commander, you're setting a bad example for the new recruit!
I'll do it when we're done here.
The Commander should act like one!
Please leave here immediately!
Now, take a good look.
This is the main tank that the 1121st Platoon is equipped with.
Vector 0-Series Automated Walker Tank, Takemikazuchi.
This is much larger than what we trained with.
This is one of the zero-generation tanks.
There are less than ten of these antediluvian relics left in the nation.
I've heard of them.
They really are amazing tanks.
But its legs...
They are still under repair.
We just don't have enough parts.
Well, to be honest, we don't have any manuals either...
and we can't even find the parts...
But!
Noël will think of something, so it's not a problem!
And don't you dare call it an accessory!
I'm sure... some day... for sure...
Don't make fun of us.
I know we're laid back.
We really are quite leisurely.
People say we're the Burden Platoon of Seize — that we're just a formality!
Even though we're a pink squad, we don't even have a single functioning tank!
But...!
Kureha-chan.
The tour is now over! Dismissed!
It seems like they're getting along well.
Does it really?
It's just like when we first met.
You're right.
But it is a little troublesome.
Last night, after you sent Kana-chan to bed...
Commander! Why is she our communications person?
Didn't we say that new members would be ammunition-loaders or pilots?
It can't be helped. Command sent her over.
What you want and what you get are often different.
But...!
There, there. It's all right.
Rio will surely still adore you, just like she always has.
And of course I will too.
Despite the way she acts, she's a really bright child.
Perhaps she's noticed something...
Is that so?
I guess we'll have to think of something.
It's here.
What is?
A ghost?!
Yes.
That's ridiculous. Weren't you just half-asleep, Noël?
So it was...
What do you mean by that?!
I saw it too — the ghost.
Near the barracks, right?
Yeah.
Hey, why are you agreeing with her?!
But isn't that normal? Having ghosts—
Like I said, stop talking already!
You too, Noël!
Since you're a technician, you should have done some proper scientific investigation before reporting it!
No way.
Why not?
Because I'm scared.
What are you talking about?! Ghosts don't exist!
No way. No way. No way! They definitely don't exist!
I'm with you on this.
Aren't I right?
Of course. Ghosts don't exist.
They don't!
They definitely aren't real!
Most certainly not!
All right!
Go conduct a proper investigation.
If you encounter something, just blow your bugle.
We'll send reinforcements immediately.
Why...?
Um... Private...
What is it, Kana... Private!
This feels... very exciting!
The thunder sounds like a marching song.
This is a mission! Not play time!
Got it Kana... Private Sorami?!
You take the point. I'll back you up!
Yes, ma'am!
Well then, forward!
This place has been this way even before the fort was built.
What was it before?
How would I know something like that?!
Just hurry and move on.
Okay.
Modern Lit.
Ideograms. I wonder what they say.
If you can't read it, don't sit there fixated on it.
It'd be great if we could read it.
It's probably just useless junk from long ago.
Let's get going.
Aren't you scared?
Nope.
Why not?
Because... aren't ghosts here to protect us?
Well, we celebrated ghosts at the village where I was born,
and held a festival every year to show our gratitude.
What kind of village are you from?
These so-called ghosts possess people,
drink their blood, and control dead bodies.
They are very devious things.
That was a close call, wasn't it?
Rats usually carry lots of deadly diseases.
What, you scared?
They're gone.
Looks like it.
Hey, Private Kureha.
This is just what I think, but could this place possibly have been a school before?
Huh? Even the capital doesn't have a school this large.
But weren't there more people a long time ago?
So this place must have been filled with lots of kids like us back then.
And they all studied together.
Oh!
What? What is it? What?!
This must have been where they taught music.
Outside of the army?
I mean, look at this...
Nothing has changed.
I can't read this, but...
D-sharp.
Sounds... never change.
What are you just standing there for?
What?
Hey, Kureha-chan! Isn't it wonderful?
What is?
Everything!
The town of Seize. The buildings inside the fort.
Everyone in our platoon. Everything!
We're just a small useless unit stationed way out in the countryside.
Our tank doesn't even work, and they forget to send supplies.
Missions have always been just talk.
And we're really laid back...
But you love it, right?
No! No!
What? What? What?
I-It's here!
Wait! Kureha!
Kanata!
Amazing...
Of course.
In this wonderful 1121st Platoon that I'm a part of and love,
I'm the gunner, after all!
So this is our ghost... huh?
What part of this looks like a ghost?
Hey, you sure look like the thief from yesterday.
Why you... I'm going to eat you!
You can't, Rio!
You shouldn't scare wounded animals!
But...
I'm thinking that it probably has nowhere else to go.
Plus, remember what our platoon's emblem is.
If you roast it, it'll be bad luck.
Right, Shuko-chan?
You even gave it a name...
But I think it's great.
You almost died yesterday because of this guy!
But it's also the reason that I got to go on a great adventure.
Right, Kureha-chan?
What are you talking about? That wasn't fit to be called an adventure.
My, my. I guess we'll decide by voting.
No. By Commander's orders.
But next time you steal food, you'll be punished.
Got it?
So that was Rio this morning, huh?
If Kanata did it every day, we'd start getting complaints.
I'm sorry.
That is your seat.
Kureha-chan!
I just happened to find the exact same chair!
I didn't do it especially for you or anything.
Thank you!
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
That's dangerous. Seriously!
The food...
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
A Day in the Troop
Rio Runs
Next Time: A Day in the Troop · Rio Runs