Why...
Why didn't you tell us?!
When did you get to know that from Keigo-san?
Since after the summer festival.
This isn't the first time.
Last time, when I was still young.
He rejected a really nice opportunity.
I understand, but...
I don't get it!
I thought we were friends!
Shiraishi!
To think that I was the only one who thought we were friends.
Haruka...
I don't want to hear it!
Calm down.
Haruka-cha-
I won't...
I won't consider you as my friend any more!
With this...
The Underwear Society is history!
N-No way...
I have two bad news today.
Due to her brother's work, our class representative Hayama Nayu, is transferring to another school.
Because this is happening so suddenly, she won't be able to attend classes anymore.
Why don't we write her a card or something once we've calmed down?
The other bad news is about the fire last night.
Unfortunately, Mizuno-sensei's apartment was completely burned down.
Please be careful with fire.
Things have really become interesting.
But it's almost winter.
No way!
That's rough.
Cheer up, Mizuno-sensei.
You can come talk to me any time.
Thanks guys.
Since Hayama will be transferring now, we'll have to select a new class representative, so let's start voting...
What are we doing about the society today?
I-I...
What's going to happen?
I-I don't know.
But...
Hey, can we visit the Underwear Society some time?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Oh, right. Hayama-san is leaving, isn't she?
But you'll keep running it, right?
T-That's...
But... now that Nayu-chan is...
Your bra is cute, Shiraishi-san.
Did you make it yourself?
I just made some changes to something I bought.
As expected of an Underwear Society member.
Shouldn't you be wearing bras one size larger now, Terumi?
How do you you?
I'm a regular at the fittings.
Maybe I'll go attend one as well next time.
I'm getting late!
Why's everyone getting so emotional?
Even after showing them up.
It seems the Society will be off today.
There won't be any point in having it when Mizuno-sensei is in that state.
Besides, Hayama-san isn't here either.
The society didn't even last a year.
Well, I've got a photo shoot to attend.
Seems like she's busy working for magazines these days.
I'm going home as well. I've got to get ready for an upcoming match.
What the hell? Compared to someone whose home burned down, transferring isn't anything big!
It's finally quiet enough to study in peace.
Can we really not do anything without Hayama around?
H-Huh?
I see... so the Underwear Society has become inactive, huh?
When things were finally starting to get interesting.
Apparently Hayama-san's too busy moving to come to school.
Really?
Are you going to confess your feelings to that Senpai of yours?
It's too early to cry.
But before that, have you thought about where you are going to live?
Well you can stay at my place for a while.
Wait, Haruka.
What are we going to do today?
That has nothing to do with underwear!
I guess now's not the time for that.
How long is Haruka planning to sit there?
I'll go get her.
Why did I say something like that?
What am I supposed to say now, Nayu-chan?
What can I do for these girls?
I have seen this scene before somewhere.
Komachi-kun...
Come to think of it, you didn't know my name at the time.
Are you waiting for Keigo-san?
Yeah.
Where's your umbrella?
Well, it was sunny this afternoon...
You know, Shiraishi now just keeps staring at the field after school these days.
She runs away when that forehead freak tries to talk to her.
I've tried mailing her, but I haven't gotten a reply yet.
I thought I had finally made some friends, but I'm all alone again.
You're not alone.
Komachi-kun-
You can borrow it.
I did it! I finally got you, Yako!
Just as you started wearing a sports bra, I'm not the same as I used to be either!
Haven't you gotten a bit shorter?
You're not acting like yourself. What's wrong?
We all change slowly over time.
We can't just stay in the same place forever.
I can't let things go like this.
I can't let Haruka and Nayu part without making up.
Go for all or nothing, else you are not a true warrior!
How long are you going to keep sitting there, Haruka?
Looks at this. These are the leftovers from Mizuno-sensei's swimsuit.
From the overnighter. Do you think she'd be happy to have them back?
Yeah, she said she doesn't have anything left from that accident.
You guys should focus on moving your hands, not your mouths.
Thanks for your help, everyone.
You're welcome.
If you find anything you can use, you can have it.
T-Thank you very much!
Why do I have to help as well?
Don't be like that.
Once we're done, let's go eat something.
Amahara's been doing nothing but complain.
If she really didn't want to do it, she wouldn't have come prepared.
What's wrong?
The textbooks I packed after so much effort!
I'm sorry, Amahara-san.
Oh, my.
Sensei, please go help out with cleaning or something!
What? But...
Besides, why isn't Shiraishi-san here when I am helping out as well?
I'm sure Haruka-chan must be busy with something.
Help her move?
Just leave me alone already!
Are you really OK with it, Haruka?
Okay, why don't we take a break?
I'll go prepare some tea, so you go buy some snacks for everyone, Nayu.
Okay.
Come to think of it, I had some good coffee around. I wonder if we already packed it away?
Don't worry about it.
Why'd you have to say that?
Did you even invite Shiraishi-san?
Of course I did.
But... I came back empty handed.
Are they're still fighting?
Why don't you just force them to meet?
Yes?
Sorry to call you so late at night.
It's ok.
Come tomorrow.
You've got to come tomorrow.
But... I...
She's leaving in two days. Tomorrow's your last chance to talk things out with her.
Last chance...
Do you remember the first time I wore a bra?
You sprayed water all over me, and I wore the bra Nayu made.
I'm sad as well.
But if Nayu has decided to go with Keigo-san, I'd like her to go off with a smile on her face.
That's what friends do.
You should do it, too.
Yako-chan...
Once Halloween is over, we'll be getting ready for winter.
What will we be doing this time next year?
I brought her with me.
Haruka-chan...
Shall we get in the boat?
Is it alright to leave those two alone together?
Probably.
They both actually want to apologize to each other.
Things are just too awkward, so they can't do it.
They just have to take that step.
I don't think either of them have the courage to do it.
Is that what you think? I think they'll be fine.
They'll be fine. They both care about each other.
Sorry I didn't help you move.
Don't worry. I'm just glad I got to see you.
I was happy to get your texts.
But I did something so horrible to you...
I kept thinking all the time about how to reply you back.
No way.
I knew how you felt, but I was so sad you'd be leaving, I just couldn't help myself.
I made this.
Would you like to eat it together?
It's delicious.
I was scared.
I thought everyone would leave me if I told the truth.
I'm sorry! I did something terrible to all of you!
I'm sorry as well.
Women's friendship is difficult, isn't it?
Haruka-chan...
Hey, you two!
Did you make up?
Yeah.
Even if we aren't together, we'll be able to run the Underwear Society.
We have text messages, phones and stuff.
During summer vacation, we can visit each other.
She might be a troublemaker, but she's not so bad after all.
You had me worried for a while.
Sorry.
You're right. It's just like you said, Haruka-chan.
I should have told you two right away about the transfer.
Nayu-chan...
I didn't realize not telling you would hurt you so much, Haruka-chan...
I was hurt, too! Where are my eggs?
Take it easy, Yako-chan!
I'm going over there, too!
Yako-chan!
Hayama?!
Wasn't this how we became friends?
You were sticking your butt way out, though.
I'll definitely keep mailing you!
Even if you're far away, we'll always be together.
What a bunch of idiots.
Don't go looking up people's skirts over there.
What's with the dissatisfied expression?!
Nayu, looks like you've got a mail.
That's amazing! Amahara-san is a magazine model!
That's impressive.
She may have been suited to becoming a model.
I'll meet you there.
Amahara-san...
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
Actually, I got these for everyone.
Komachi-kun, could you give one to Amahara-san?
Why me?!
Thank you. I'll treasure this.
I'll treasure the memories we've had these past six months.
Haruka-chan...
This isn't the end, Nayu.
Yako-chan...
Hayama, I...
I...
Thanks for everything, guys.
I won't forget the time we've spent together here.
Nayu!
Nayu-chan!
Hayama!
E-Excuse me...
Could I go to the next Underwear Society meeting?
Of course. Take this as well.
Thank you.
TL Note: The girl used a masculine first person pronoun earlier. Which is usually only used by men.
What did she just say?
E-Excuse me...
Do you think I could join your club?
Keigo-san said he would come back on weekends.
Mizuno-sensei's going to stop by and check on me once in a while.
Do you think we could work together again?
Do whatever you want!
Nayu-chan!
I'm back.
What are you laughing about?
Don't ever leave us again.
Haruka-chan, Yako-chan.