I saw Mom in town at sunset.
She was wearing her usual priestess clothes.
She slowly walked in the dusk, like she was drifting.
When I saw her, I didn't find it suspicious that she was there.
Instead, I was so happy to see her again that I just had to open my big mouth and get her attention.
But Mom didn't even turn around.
Mom
She just kept walking, step by step.
I hurried after her,
but when I turned the corner,
no one was there.
I must've mistaken someone for her. Yeah, must've.
Why would Mom be there anyway?
Mom
Mom... already...
Then the street lights started turning on, one after another.
I could see the back of Mom's figure
standing in the pale light of the fluorescent street lamp.
Mom
I could hear the sound of her staff,
and smell the faint scent of herbs and incense.
Mom always smelled like that.
Mom
Mom's figure started flickering on and off,
in sync with the street lamp.
Mom
I tried to catch up to her and get her attention,
but Mom started drifting further and further away in the sea of lights.
Mom
No matter how fast I ran, I couldn't catch up.
Mom was walking slowly under the flickering lights
to a place far beyond my reach.
I was so afraid I would never see her again
that I yelled her name at the top of my lungs.
After that, she started to turn around.
Mom
And when she did, the area was filled with a bright light.
The streetlights all burnt out, having exhausted the last of their filament.
Just like that, Mom vanished into the darkness.
Mom
I couldn't even begin to comprehend what I just saw.
I stood there like I was rooted in place.
I love her, I miss her, and I want to see her again.
But I'll never be able to see her again.
Mom
I just saw her with my own two eyes, but...
But I know that's not possible.
Because Mom...
has already...
Because Mom has already-
Kamisama no yubisaki de
In the blink of an eye,
Dekiagaru watashi no kisetsu tachi
the myriad gods change the seasons of my life
Hoshizora yori mo haruka ni nagai
I thought I could sleep long after the stars faded from the sky,
Nemuri o yusaburu uta
but I was awoken by a song
Sasami@Unmotivated
Mimi o fusaide hito ni magireru to
I try to mind my own business and blend in with the crowd
Watashi ga kieta mitai datta
but that makes me feel like I don't even exist
Kokoro o enjiru ni wa
I wish I could follow my heart,
Zatsuon o eraberu hodo otona ja nai
but I'm not experienced enough to filter out the static
Deatta kouya no hana
I come across a diorama of flowers blooming in the wild
Kowakute yasashikute
They look gentle, eerily so
Fureta shunkan ni   Jiorama datte hontou ni naru
The moment I touch the flowers, everything in the diorama becomes real
- al
ter
a
tion -
Kamisama no itazura de egakareta
My future has already been mapped out
Watashi no miraichizu
thanks to the whims of the myriad gods
Ikusen no neiro ga hibiku kara
But the echoes of the countless sounds around me
Oikakete kuru ashita mo kowasu
are strong enough to shatter the bleak future that haunts me so
Hoshizora no shita de yorisou kizuna
With the stars watching us, we grow even closer
Nukumori ga mieta yo
Close enough that I can see your warmth
Kizutsukete tsukuridasu kizuna
Our relationship might be one of take without give,
Mamoritai no wa sonna kizuna
but that's the kind of relationship I want to treasure
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Sasami@Unmotivated
Episode 6
Only Parents Give Us Problems
Hey, Kagami! Kagami!
What?
It's vital that I get my morning sleep.
Do not disturb me.
Kagami, listen!
You should try listening to other people every now and then.
I saw my mom yesterday!
Please give me a break.
I saw...
my Mom...
Are you being stupid or having a stroke?
You don't have to literally break.
Either way, I don't have time for your delusions.
Do not disturb my sleep.
Oh, I know! Kagami, you should come shopping with me after school!
What does that have to do with anything?
Well, I wanna get a bike, but I don't know what kind should I get.
You are being incoherent.
You keep saying whatever comes to mind.
My brother has been taking me to school every day, but we got yelled at for riding a bike together.
I just said—
Help me pick one, Kagami!
Sadly, I must take Meat to the vet today.
Meat?
Yes! A lovely, white, soft and fluffy little creature!
I need to keep her company, or she'll die of loneliness.
That applies to me too!
No means no.
Sometimes the best adventure is the one experienced alone.
Kagami's so heartless...
I'm no better than a rabbit?
Give me a break.
Mom?
On my way home from school, I saw Mom.
What are you doing, Sasami? Shopping?
Yes...
What are you shopping for?
Uh... Well, a bike.
I see.
If you are going to ride it to and from school,
then one with a basket, like that one, might be the best choice.
No way! That one isn't cute!
A Tsukuyomi priestess doesn't need to be cute.
Seeking help and relief from others
would become one of your weaknesses.
Likes and dislikes only serve to interfere with your ability to direct the world down the correct path.
I don't have very many memories of Mom,
but the few I have, I remember very clearly.
She taught me spells and I practiced them with her.
When I was young, I was always by her side.
Is something wrong, Sasami?
Nothing...
What is this noisy object?
Oh, this?
You can use these controls to move the crane.
You can get the dolls inside using that.
Wanna give it a try?
Dolls are wicked.
Locking souls in figures that resemble living creatures is but a trivial task.
Therefore, there is a great risk these dolls are cursed and being used by our enemies—
Here we go.
Listen to your mother!
Damn, this is hard.
Allow me.
You can't do that!
A Tsukuyomi priestess should always take the shortest path.
That's against the rules!
Now the clerks are staring at us!
Then I shall use a spell to move the doll itself.
It fell in.
Are you sure about this?
I personally approved of it.
And if a Tsukuyomi priestess gives their approval, that is—
The clerks are coming!
Let's go, Mom!
Do not run! My body cannot handle this!
Mom
Mom has been frail since birth, so she was sick a lot.
I often stayed by her side, nursing her.
They'll catch us if we're careless.
A Tsukuyomi priestess is... beyond the public authorities...
I shall take a rest now.
Being less fit than I am is pretty impressive.
I merely do not see the point in being physically fit.
Wait a sec.
Here.
I sense a suspicious chill. What is that?
Ice cream. It's a cold sweet.
It is wicked to indulge in luxuries.
Pleasures are the source of preferences towa—
Whatever!
It's cold!
You sounded so cute!
I am always cute.
My, this is actually...
Notebooks by brand
Do you have a computer, Mom?
They're really convenient.
A Tsukuyomi priestess sees not the point of convenience.
Buy this for me, Mom!
No. Material desire is wicked.
Brother would buy it for me...
That is beside the point.
Do not rely on him or your soul shall rot.
Mom, I'll pick out some clothes for you.
It must be boring having to wear that priestess garb all the time.
I am a priestess, therefore it is natural that I wear priestess garb.
I need no garments from this vulgar world.
That was fun!
Do you still have time? We could eat dinner together.
Such proud words coming from the mouth of a helpless chick.
Is there anything you'd like to eat?
That is unnecessary.
In any case, Sasami, I have something to disc—
Oh, how about Italian?
You've never had any before, have you?
Wait, Sasami!
Wait, I said!
Every now and then, I think back to my last memory of her.
I think back to my last memory of her.
Looky, looky! There's a lot of pets here!
So many soft and fluffy creatures!
Is this heaven?
Welcome to the vet, Meat!
Behave yourself! There's nothing to be afraid of!
Aww, you know how to look after a bunny! I'm so proud of you, Sis!
You're being obnoxious. Please kill yourself.
This soft and fluffy creature is wearing clothes!
Bunny
clothes
I-Is this... a sign from the heavens telling me to get all lovey-dovey with Meat?
I doubt that.
Okay Meat, how about this one?
This is gonna take a while...
Sasami.
Yes?
Who will feed us now?
Normally it'd be Brother...
It's okay! It's easy! Just watch!
Like this...
Put that aside for now, Sasami. We have something to discuss.
What is it?
I saw Mom in town at sunset.
Earlier you said that you had fun.
That is something your mother is glad to hear.
We never have spent time together like a normal mother and daughter who talk and go shopping.
I was not a good mother.
I am sorry, Sasami.
No...
Don't apologize, Mom...
I'm happy.
I've always dreamed of spending time with you, like a normal mother and daughter.
I saw Mom in town at sunset.
She was wearing her usual priestess clothes. She slowly walked
in the dusk, like she was drifting.
You must have been lonely.
I don't mind!
You had your duties to take care of, but I know that you still tried to raise me to be a great successor.
Sasami...
The streetlights all burnt out, having exhausted the last of their filament.
Just like that, Mom vanished into the darkness.
I couldn't even begin to comprehend what I just saw.
I stood there like I was rooted in place.
I love her, I miss her, and I want to see her again.
But I'll never be able to see her again.
I just saw her with my own two eyes, but...
Thank you. I'm really grateful.
I love you!
The streetlights all burnt out, having exhausted the last of their filament.
Just like that, Mom vanished into the darkness.
I couldn't even begin to comprehend what I just saw.
I stood there like I was rooted in place.
I love her, I miss her, and I want to see her again.
But I'll never be able to see her again.
I just saw her with my own two eyes, but... But I know that's not possible.
But... because of that... there's something I need to tell you.
What is it?
Because Mom has already-
Because Mom, you've already... passed away.
passed away.
I... passed away?
Sasami, did you think I did not notice?
Of course I am dead.
Mom... then why...
My appearance has been preserved by an alteration.
This body is a corpse too.
It is rotting away slowly. These
people around us cannot sense that.
This is how I really look.
Every human dies.
The souls of the dead descend the slope of Yomi to the underworld.
There is no reincarnation, therefore no one gets reborn.
That is how the world works.
But there is a way out.
Before I ate the food of Yomi and
became a resident in the land of the dead,
I negotiated with the king of the underworld.
We have a common interest.
Thus, he has allowed me to return to the mortal world until my body rots away completely.
But why?!
Revival is an abominable thing that not
even the gods of creation could achieve!
Why, you ask, Sasami?
Normally, I would have moved on satisfied.
However...
I saw.
I saw you leave the Tsukuyomi Shrine, abandon your duties, and do nothing with your life!
I could not stay dead.
I told you to take care of the world.
And you nodded and said,
"Leave it to me, Mom."
Yet you broke your promise.
For that I shall not condemn you.
You are not the only one who has sinned.
I too committed a great sin.
I passed away before the effort you put into your training could bear fruit and you came of age to become a priestess.
Return to the shrine, Sasami.
You are to undergo training again.
The shrine's gone!
I know.
Buildings matter not.
All you need is a place far from the vulgarities of the world where you can train in peace.
We are going.
No!
I'm not going back!
Why do I have to give my sweat, tears and blood to make the world more convenient to mankind?!
I'm not a Tsukuyomi priestess anymore!
Do not misunderstand me, Sasami.
No one asked for your opinion.
It is for the sake of mankind.
Do you believe your happiness, freedom, or pleasures to be worth more than the future of mankind?
You have far more on your shoulders than your own weight!
This is not about life!
This is about something much greater!
Your selfishness matters not!
But...
You are a spoiled, foolish child!
When are you going to grow up?!
Your existence has no meaning if you are not living it as a Tsukuyomi priestess.
It is a sin for you to live without a care, abandon your duties, and waste away!
Why can you not understand?!
The blame lies with me for spoiling you so.
What a useless child you turned out to be!
Hey.
Take a chill pill, mother dearest.
Is it time for our parent-teacher conference?
Well, Mom?
Tsurugi...
I heard the rumors, but this is the first time I've seen someone return from the underworld by themselves.
Do not speak like a human, you evil god.
Was it your smile and pleasant words that lead Sasami astray?
I'm no evil god. Those are some big words coming from a walking corpse though.
Not even gods, humans the least, are allowed to return.
That's what our parents decided.
You only live once, so live your life without regrets.
Sure I might be some slacker who
abandoned my duty to watch over this world,
but that doesn't mean I can ignore
such a severe violation of the rules.
I'll amend this!
No one led Sasami astray! She chose this herself!
Don't come back from the dead and pretend like you're a responsible mother after all this time!
Hop on board the bullet train and get your ass back to the underworld!
You make light of me.
As the Tsukuyomi priestess, I stood atop the Tsukuyomi shrine and exterminated any and all anomalies.
Disposing of evil gods is a trivial matter.
I'm no evil god!
Just as the legends say, you cannot fight to save your life, Sun God.
Tsurugi!
Sister!
Get outta here! She's strong enough to beat the crap out of you two!
Stop running off without us!
You're an empty shell who can't use her full powers!
Shut up!
How can I face my students if I
can't even stop a violent parent?!
What a laughable bunch.
The gods of this land only seek pleasure.
I cannot leave this land in your hands.
This world only advances and propers because we guide humanity.
All is done for the world and mankind.
My last duty is to train Sasami and make her fulfill her role as a Tsukuyomi priestess.
I harbor no ill feelings for you, but should you get in the way,
you shall die.
I'm not going to the underworld!
There's someone I really hate there!
What?!
That is indeed the divine sword, Ame-no-Murakumo.
It is powerful, but it is for protection.
A grass-cutting blade used for self-
protection lacks the spite to kill another.
Huh, is that...
This is the sword that defeated
Yamata-no-Orochi, dulled due to a curse,
and was then reforged in the underworld.
The sword of misfortune, Ame-no-Habakiri.
The king of the underworld presented me with this sword capable of slaying gods.
The king of the underworld had Ame-no-Habakiri?
Now I see what's going on!
I knew you were too strong for a human, and now I know why!
That motherfucker's gone too far this time!
Sister!
How dare you!
No way!
I have protection from the king of the
underworld and I hold the defiled divine sword.
Your likes can not even lay a finger on me.
Kagami!
Damn you!
You are too weak.
Having returned from the underworld,
I can easily open a pathway there.
Those who fall down the slope of Yomi can not return easily, not even gods.
Your age is long gone, Sun God.
Sink and hand the world over to the Moon.
Now then.
Out of the way, you nobody.
You lot must enjoy pretending to be super
heroes by protecting my selfish daughter,
but that itself is devoid of all meaning and value.
For the sake of the world and mankind, Sasami must become a great Tsukuyomi priestess,
and lead this land in the right direction.
I don't get it! I'm stupid!
But why are you so mean?!
We were all so happy!
Tsurugi was having fun!
Kagami finally started smiling!
And Mamarin made that all possible!
Nothing you say makes sense to me!
Nothing!
Then I shall put it in a way that even you can understand.
Get out of my way.
Stop!
Stop, I'll go with you!
I'll go back to the shrine and become a Tsukuyomi priestess! Stop already!
Please...
Welcome back to the human world.
Sasami@Unmotivated
Here we go again! It's time for the ending song!
This time, Sasami's beautiful singing will be heard in living rooms around the country!
At least I thought so, but the situation apparently won't allow that.
Will I have to work hard by myself again?
Oh!
What?
Great timing, Mom!
Come here for a moment!
What is it?!
Take the microphone! Are you ready?
Please, do sing!
Wait a moment! I do not understand this situation.
I will not sing a song.
A Tsukuyomi priestess needs no songs.
No problem. This episode's story was so serious
that they wanted to cut the ending to let it linger.
This recording probably won't be used anyway.
But please, sing, just in case!
Take a big breath and...
...and on like a... sy-sy-symphony
...down like... love
You can not trick me!
Why sould I do something like this?!
Sit up straight, Kamiomi!
I shall behead you right now!
Ouch! Mom, don't beat me with the microphone!
We have to use that same mic for every episode!
Uh, oh, next time!
Unmotivated@Warmup
It's time for the Unmotivated Warmup!
First, a deep breath!
Try to fill your lungs with the scent of Sasami!
One-two!
Two-two!
Now open your arms wide, like you're hugging Sasami!
One-two, Sasami!
Two-two, I love you!
Let's do our best for another day!
Next time: episode 7, "I forgot how to speak".
Next Time
Episode Seven
I forgot how to speak