Yoshimizu
Kagami
Theatre
Well, let's get going.
Let's go!
Stop messing around and start!
aimai san senchi sorya puni tte koto kai?
曖昧３センチ　そりゃぷにってコトかい？
About 3cm? You call that squishy?
choh!
ちょっ！
Geez!
rappingu ga seifuku...daa furi tte kotanai
らっぴんぐが制服・・・だぁぁ不利ってこたない
My wrapping is a uniform... Can't hurt!
pu.
ぷ
Psh.
ganbaccha♥yacchaccha
がんばっちゃ♥やっちゃっちゃ
I'll try my best ♥ I'll get it done
son to kyaacchi & release
そんときゃーっち& Release
When it's like this, I'll just catch and release!
gyoh
ぐョッ
Gyo!
ase ase no tanima ni darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
汗々の谷間に Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
In cleavage of sweat, Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
fuu
nanka daruu nanka deruu
なんかダるー　なんかデるー
Feeling kinda lazy. What's going on?
aishiteruu aree ikko ga chigatteru n ruu
あいしてるー　あれー個が違ってるんるー
I love you! Huh, one of those is wrong!
nayaminbouu koutetsubouu
なやみン坊ー　高鉄棒ー
Worry wart, high steel bar,
oishinboo iikagen ni shi nasai
おいしん簿ー　いーかげんにシナサイ
Glutton, Cut it out!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
The girl that just flew off blushing...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
所謂ふつーのおにゃのコ
is just another normal girl
odoroita atashi dake? tonkotsu harigane o-kawari da da da da da da
驚いたあたしだけ？　豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだだだだ
Am I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu? Seconds, p-p-please!
Guess what?
My glasses...
Where are my glasses?
But I've been playing the same fighting games lately.
If I don't have my glasses...
BON-BON ooendan
BON-BON おーえん団
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
let's get! cherii pai
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeekai
RAN-RAN かんげー会
RAN-RAN Welcome party
look up! senseeshon
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
hai!
はい！
Yeah!
sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
存在感・・小惑星
The presence... of asteroids!
butsukatte tokemashita boozen
ぶつかって溶けましたぼーぜん
As they confoundedly collide and melt...
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Sing loudly! Like a Sirenger
motte ike!
もっていけ！
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
I'll be the one with the last laugh
seeraa fuku da kara desu ←ketsuron
セーラーふくだからです←結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor uniform ←And that's that
getsuyoubi na no ni!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm feeling horrible. What should I do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? Wa! Iiv
夏服がいいのです←キャ？　ワ！　イイv
The summer clothes are so much better! ←Oh, so cute!
sekkin san pikuto suru made tte chuucho da
接近３ピクト　すれまでってちゅーちょだ
It's getting close to 3 picts. Yet, I'm still hesitating.
yan☆
やん☆
ganbatte harikitte my darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
がんばって　はりきって　My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
Try your best! Get your spirits up! My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
yay☆
Oh, yeah...
We switch to summer uniforms today.
Someone like Konata will probably show up in her winter uniform.
At least one person in our class will forget.
Good morning, Sis.
There's one in this house.
All Kinds
of People
Rats!
I forgot to sign up for the TV drawing.
Bah.
I kinda wanted the prize.
An apron from Apron of Love.
Not enough love.
You forgot because you don't have enough love.
Not really.
More like I've been busy with student council stuff and tests.
Nope, nope.
Those are just excuses.
I've never forgotten.
Don't put me on the same level as
someone who only ever thinks about having fun!
And the way you put it really pisses me off!
How do you win a drawing?
To put it simply...
Love!
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just a loveless woman.
Well...
If you jot down the usual stuff...
...you're not going to win.
What do you put on yours?
Stuff that'll help me win.
How?
Good handwriting is a fundamental must.
You have to design a postcard that just begs to be drawn.
Like what?
Like...
Use a fluorescent marker to draw a border around the postcard.
That'll stand out.
Then you add a picture related to the prize.
A picture, huh?
I can't draw very well though.
In that case...
...just send in as many entries as you can.
I can probably handle that.
But...
No matter how many you send...
...write each one out without using a printer.
And send out a hundred each time.
A hundred?!
Isn't that normal?
Wouldn't that cost a lot?
You're fighting for something you want.
That calls for passion and guts!
But wouldn't it be cheaper just to buy it then?
Some things in this world can't be bought with money.
Can you fit a hundred postcards in a mailbox?
You don't send them all at once...
...but a few here and a few there.
And over the course of a few days.
Depending on who's running the drawing...
...you might get caught.
Well, sometimes you're better off without the tricky stuff.
And sometimes it's the exact opposite.
So what do we do?
Like I said...
Love!
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, if you want to win...
...glance through free newspapers and flyers...
...and look for drawings that
probably aren't going to attract many people.
You'll have a high chance of winning.
I'll give it a try!
Where's the love in that?
You know, for twins...
...you don't look anything like each other.
That's 'cause we're fraternal twins.
So it's more like comparing sisters.
Identical twins look exactly the same...
...but fraternal twins can be...
...pretty different in appearance and personality.
I see.
Tsukasa is laid-back...
...but Kagami is pretty crazy.
What was that?!
If you had the same hairstyles with the same ribbons...
...you might end up looking the same.
Kona-chan!
No good.
Kagami could never be the cutesy type.
Zip it!
Don't insult me with your weird fantasies!
Can you use telepathy?
You know.
With twins...
Even when they're raised separately...
...they end up having similar lifestyles and significant others.
And sometimes they end up marrying another pair of twins.
And when one of them is in danger...
...the other one can sense it from a completely different place.
There are all kinds of mysterious phenomena.
So can't you use telepathy?
Give it a spin.
Abracadabra!
You read way too much manga.
Same with ManaKana...
ManaKana?
I heard that they have a few differences.
By the way, Mana is the careful one...
...and Kana is the optimistic one.
And apparently they sound a little different when they sing.
That reminds me...
ManaKana thought they were fraternal twins for a long time...
...but they recently learned that
they were actually identical twins.
Seriously?!
Is it really that surprising?
The definitions for identical and fraternal twins...
...have changed recently.
Which means that you two could be identical twins.
Your identical traits would be...
You both like sweets, right?
Love 'em.
I guess.
You're both left-handed.
That's right.
What's your favorite color?
White maybe.
Black.
The same colors as your souls.
What was that?!
All this talk about eggs and black
and white cookies has made me hungry.
Nobody was talking about food.
It's suffocating in here.
We just got on and I've already broken a sweat.
It's that time of year.
Hot...
They haven't turned on the air conditioning yet.
H-Hey!
Hot...
Soujiro Izumi
Konata
After a long courtship,
we, Kiyotaka Narumi
and Yui Kobayakawa,
will be tying the knot
on June **.
Ladybug Samba, punk version.
One of my cousins is getting married this month.
So she'll be a June bride.
Sounds wonderful.
How does this...
...wet and gloomy season supposedly signify happiness?
Why does getting married in June make you happy?
The name June...
...is generally said to be...
...derived from the name of the Roman goddess, Juno.
In Greek mythology...
...Juno is known as Hera...
...the goddess of marriage and fertility.
Which is why those who get married
in Hera's month, the month of June...
...are said to receive her protection and blessing.
But wasn't Hera Zeus's wife?
Yes, that's right.
I have this image of Hera being extremely jealous...
...so I'm not feeling this happy thing.
What?
Would you rather wear a dress or a kimono for your wedding?
I would wear a dress.
It's been my dream since I was a child.
I'd also go with a dress.
But a kimono would also be nice...
I wanna wear both!
They have miniskirts and really colorful dresses these days.
A miniskirt wedding dress?
It'd look really cute with lots of frills on them.
Lots of dreams!
Lots of frills!
Right?
You're Angel Salvia.
Wait.
Your hair makes you look more like Daisy.
So a yellow top and miniskirt it is.
Tsukasa-san.
You'd probably look good in a miniskirt.
Really?
Your dress is important...
...but the person you're getting married to is also important.
A childhood friend?
Or a rich lady?
Tough choice to make.
One has lots of money...
...and the ability to cast Beho*mi and l***zun.
But as far as feelings are concerned...
Bianca hands down!
Oh, Kagami.
You're the true love type, huh?
I thought you'd go for the money.
No comeback, huh?
Yo, Konata.
I've got a question about a game I borrowed the other day.
Oh.
Hold it right there, Kagaminya.
Isn't it more fun when you figure it out yourself?
You have a point.
Yep, yep.
Since you understand that you should do things yourself...
...you'll do your own homework from now on, right?
Don't the detectives in manga and TV shows...
...run into an awful lot of murders?
Like in Conan or Kindaichi.
There wouldn't be a story otherwise.
Really?
Couldn't they just solve normal cases?
Normal?
Like travel around Japan in search of missing persons.
Tailing people would translate well into a game.
With plenty of thrill and suspense.
I guess.
You could also conduct investigations into unfaithful wives.
Or look for pets that ran away?
Yep, yep!
But would that be fun to watch?
Probably no fun at all.
Right?
Also...
Cases in real life...
...don't really use any brilliant tricks...
...like the ones you find in manga and TV shows.
I guess not.
Fabricated fingerprints that can't be
detected through a luminol reaction.
Stuff that's a step ahead of forensic labs.
Well...
Anything too good might lead to copycats.
Or be too sensitive for broadcast.
Ah, or that...
The really hard cases end without
anyone realizing they happened or go...
...unsolved.
That'd be wrong in so many ways!
Don't you hate how it's been
constantly raining the past few days?
You're right...
And I used to like rain...
You get soaked...
...and you can't hang clothes out to dry...
...so I've never really liked it.
Why did you like rain, Kona-chan?
Because baseball games would be
cancelled and I'd get to watch anime.
I see.
Sounds just like something you would say.
They have a lot more dome stadiums now.
Is something wrong?
You often see idiots and geniuses
going to the same school in anime...
Cease that immediately.
Bite me!
Get lost, neener-neener!
Isn't that actually kinda strange?
If you put it that way...
...in some recent anime...
...the teacher looks the same age as the students.
Or even younger.
Teach.
YOUTH
HI
IT'S
BACKWARDS
BACKWARDS IS
THE GREATEST ECSTASY
LUCKY STAR DASH!
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS
WHAT'S INSIDE
AGE MEANS NOTHING
IN THE FACE OF LOVE
WRYYYYY~
Yes, Ta*****na-san?
The world's always been interested in watching...
...the gap between physical age and mental age.
Don't get it.
You shouldn't question it.
In fact, wouldn't a student who's
really different from everyone else...
...be the real mystery?
Yeah.
I agree one hundred percent.
I shouldn't be saying this...
...but I don't know how you got into this school, Konata.
You're good at putting stuff off till the night before...
...so you didn't study until the night before, right?
What?
You mean she really did?
Nah.
Well, I couldn't have pulled it off in one night.
That gave me a scare.
But I'm impressed that you actually kept studying.
Did a quiz game come out for DS or something?
My dad set some conditions.
A D-rank would mean a Pippin.
A C-rank would mean a 3DO.
A B-rank would mean a PS2.
Papa Izumi.
You really know how to deal with your daughter, huh?
I've been wondering...
Isn't the real mystery how Tsukasa's in the same school as us?
She said it without even blinking!
Woo-hoo!
Come back in ten years!
I won again!
Damn it!
I can't beat her at fighting games.
She's spent way more time on them than I have.
Challenge to me a different game if you want.
Sure about that?
Then next is...
A quiz game!
N-No way...
I lost to Konata in a game of knowledge?
Unbelievable...
Don't tell me...
...she memorized the question order?
Humiliated.
Her memory's incredible when it comes to gaming.
What should we play next?
Don't be in such a hurry.
Huh? That's weird.
Didn't you have a really easy party game?
How do you know all the games I have?
You could probably beat me at that one.
It just stunk!
You've barely eaten any snacks, Kagami.
Usually, you wolf them down.
There's no real reason for it.
I know.
Dieting for summer?
It's not like that.
Not like you have anyone to show your swimsuit off to.
Shut it!
It's none of your business!
Oh, yeah.
Weren't you guys born on Tanabata?
Isn't your birthday soon?
What about it?
You remembered our birthday.
Seventeen, huh?
Seventeen's right before the big one.
What does that mean?
In the year before a critical year...
...unlucky things begin to happen.
As our birthday approaches...
...I'm getting worried...
...so I bought a bunch of wards...
...and power stones.
That sounds like fun.
Sure is!
I couldn't stop buying them.
And like...
We have wards against rage at our place.
Er, no.
All-purpose ward.
Wards against rage, hah.
Like...
We ensure safe pregnancy and protect
you from traffic accidents at the same time!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Did you know that your birthday is Ponytail Day?
I had no idea.
But why July 7th?
Because Vega from the Tanabata legend had a ponytail.
Sounds like a stretch.
There's a Japan Ponytail Society...
...and they give an award every year to a
celebrity who they think would look good with a ponytail.
Really...
But I have a feeling that anyone would look good with a ponytail.
Sure about that?
My hair's the shortest...
...so it's barely a ponytail.
But a little ponytail's pretty cute.
Yours also looks good, Kona-chan.
You could go with that on an everyday basis.
Think so?
Sure.
S-Sis also...
Kagami's is...
Fine!
I get the idea!
I'll undo it!
All manly like a warrior.
Sorry about that!
Don't drunks often wear ties around their heads?
Is that supposed to mean something?
Oh, that?
Isn't that just when the guy loosens the tie...
...and tries to pull it off over his head...
...but it gets stuck?
In that case...
...it's a lot weirder that they're always carrying a takeout box.
Takeout box?
The thing Kato-chan from the Drifters carries.
I'm not getting it...
Drunks these days...
...pretty much always have a tie around
their head and a takeout box in their hand.
Right?
I hope Vega and Altair meet this year.
Shine. Shine. Shine.
Hope those rage wards of yours can deliver a miracle.
Mind your own business.
They're giving away all varieties of QUO cards at Comp Festival.
Oh, yeah...
You're always collecting QUO cards...
...but do you ever use them?
I don't.
Then why spend the effort?
Isn't it natural to want any item...
...related to a series you like?
As a fan. As a collector.
Not really...
...if you're never gonna use them...
You can't use them!
You have to take good care of them!
It really pisses me off when I see someone use one.
You're not supposed to use these things!
Much less auction them off or sell them.
Using them makes you a surefire failure...
...as a fan and as a collector!
I really can't say anything when you're so worked up.
In my case, I need at least three.
One for preservation.
I keep it in a special case.
Then one to take out occasionally to look at.
What's the last one for?
An extra.
What's that?
Don't you always want two or three of something you like?
Yeah, yeah.
You don't.
I'm just a geek.
A weirdo.
No.
I kind of understand what you're saying.
You'd expect Tsukasa to be popular with guys...
...but I've never heard anything like that.
Tsukasa's a little plain and doesn't really stand out.
Isn't it because she's got a scary sister guarding her like a hawk?
Did you say something?
I'm not sure if I'm really plain...
...or if it's more that Kona-chan and Yuki-chan are really unique.
Miyuki knows all kinds of things.
And she's pretty.
Has a good figure.
Wears glasses.
Hates the dentist.
Clumsy.
Naturally clueless.
Hey now.
Isn't this getting a little weird?
But it's true that I haven't heard anything about Miyuki.
Maybe it's because she's so pretty...
...that everyone's afraid to approach her?
I doubt that.
She's kind...
...and really good at helping others.
That's true.
Maybe a lot of guys ask her out.
But she turns them down?
Turns them down, huh...
Nah.
Maybe she doesn't realize that they're asking her out.
That's possible.
Yuki-chan can be a little clueless...
...so an indirect approach might not work.
Man, the guys in your class are hopeless.
Doesn't a single one of them have the guts...
...to confess his passionate feelings to Miyuki?
Guess not...
We don't have enough maniacs in our class.
Miyuki-san's type is usually a bigger hit with maniacs.
Maniacs, huh?
Right?
Oh.
It's already this late.
I'll need to excuse myself.
Really?
Please continue to enjoy yourselves.
Then I'll excuse myself.
See you later!
Buh-bye.
Anyway...
Going on with the story...
...that person was actually...
O-Oh?
I-I'm terribly sorry!
Yay!
I-I'm sorry.
Man, oh, man...
Doesn't that always happen?
I did it the other day.
So did I.
Everybody does it at least once.
Right, Konata?
I haven't.
That was definitely an element of moe!
Miyuki-san.
Good job!
Good lucky!
Okay!
Today's another whoo-whoo happy episode of Lucky Channel!
I'm your navigator, Akira Kogami.
And...
Uh.
I'm Akira-sama's assistant, Minoru Shiraishi.
It's a pleasure.
Okay, okay.
The two of us have now done this show...
Ta-da!
Three times after today!
How do you feel about it, Shiraishi-san?
Have you gotten used to it?
Well...
Not yet...
So sorry.
It feels like Shiraishi-san hasn't opened up to me yet.
And it looks like we're sitting further apart than usual.
Is this what they mean by emotional distance?
Sob.
Th-Th-That's not true!
Shuffle.
Okay!
Let's get rollin'!
Um...
We've got something the fans will love today!
Guess what?
We'll be doing our first
introduction for a member of the regular cast!
Da! Da-da-dum!
Okay, uh...
We'll be introducing Miyuki Takara-san today.
Let's see...
The class representative, well-mannered, kn—
Knowledgeable.
Knowledgeable...
...in both literary and culinary arts. A perfect person.
Shiraishi-san.
You know Miyuki-san, right?
But of course!
She's so wonderful, yeah?
First, there's her glasses!
And then she's pretty as a button.
With those looks...
...you'd expect her to be hard to approach...
...but she's actually a friendly person...
I wish you'd talk that much on the radio show...
You can't stop talking when it's about Miyuki-san.
No!
That's not it...
Well, yeah.
Miyuki Takara-san, is it?
A pretty face.
With large breasts.
And other various elements of moe.
Isn't she so lucky to be a pretty character?
Akira-sama, that's a little...
The maniacs love her.
Uh, maniacs is a little...
But you know...
If it's maniacs you want, I'm a huge hit with those lolicons...
Too bad!
It's time to say goodbye!
And so...
Send us any questions or comments about the show, please!
Please look forward to next time.
See ya!
So what's she really like?
Exactly the same.
No way!
Doesn't she like smoke a pack at a time backstage?
No worry of that. She isn't you.
That was fun!
A unique song.
I'd like to hear a song that normal people can enjoy already.
You know the next one, Kagami.
Guess it from the intro!
It's not another weird song, is it?
What was this song again?
Don't know...
Kagami.
The answer is...
It's from FMP. FMP.
And it's Kagami's favorite...
Fumoffu!
Really...
I-I just read the novels...
...and got a little hooked.
Say a day were to come when tears begin to fall...
You're really good, Kona-chan!
You can also sound like an adult.
Isn't she just doing an imitation?
...I would want your back for comfort.
So?
What are you two going to sing?
I wonder if there's anything I can sing...
I don't know very many songs...
Kindness can be very cruel at times...
Anything works.
Look at Konata.
Just sing what you want to!
Um...
Then I'll have a look.
I'm not very confident about my singing...
The more we try, the more we lose sight of the answer.
It's fine.
We're the only ones who'll hear you.
Just take it easy.
Really?
In that case...
If you can see rainbows in our town after the rain has just passed...
Then let's set out now.
Something's about to begin...
Next Episode
Well, next time on Lucky Star:
I'm Tsukasa.
Guess what?
I laughed so hard the other day that I couldn't breathe.
Then at school one morning...
I'm already out of time?
Next time:
「Motivation Issues」
Motivation Issues.
Look forward to next time!