It seems our final showdown with the Precure is at hand.
Yes.
Not having last-minute doubts, I trust?
The Precure and I... we shall fight until one side can fight no longer.
This is the moment I have been waiting for.
Even at this climactic moment, still all you care about is doing battle?
Well, I can't say I have much admiration for your blunt-headed nature.
But I do find great beauty in watching you fight.
Where's this coming from? You're creeping me out.
I'm merely speaking my mind. Don't read anything into it.
You're so haughty it infuriates me.
But I respect your strength!
Your validation means nothing to me, you realize?
Neither does yours.
You shall go no further, Precure!
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
I'm afraid this...
is where you die!
You always have to spoil the moment.
Leave them to me.
You can't handle both of them alone.
Allow me to help as well.
I'll stay here and help Sunshine.
Blossom, Moonlight, you two go rescue your grandma.
Don't worry. We'll catch up.
Or do you think we can't handle it?
Of course not!
I don't think so!
Kumojacky! Kobraja!
We Will Never Forget You!
That was quite the move.
That's not even gonna slow them down!
Split up like this, you're no match for us.
Cure Sunshine.
You are worthy of being my opponent.
Come, let us do battle on a more fitting stage for the occasion.
Bring it on!
What's so funny?
Is turning the world into a desert really that amusing to you?!
I don't care about your planet.
Reaching the zenith of my strength, and doing battle with the strong...
That is all I desire!
Your beauty and mine, pitted against each other in a graceful battle!
Truly, a performance befitting the end of the world.
There's no beauty to be found in
making the world suffer like this!
Alas, I have no empathy for that which has no beauty.
Especially your pathetic human hearts.
You stupid...
I hope you put up a good fight, Cure Marine!
Do you realize how many Flowers you've stolen from people's Hearts for your stupid "desire"?!
I'll never accept your twisted thinking!
Marine and Sunshine are risking
their lives to allow us to proceed.
We mustn't let that be in vain.
Just try to stop me, Precure.
Futile!
Your attacks are futile!
You cannot even compare to the strength I desire!
Marine!
Without an opponent like you...
I would not be able to stage a battle of such utmost beauty.
Do try to live up to my expectations, Cure Sunshine!
Now, let us make this battle even more beautiful.
Yes... let us create a work of unparalleled art!
Sunshine!
What is this?
Look!
Dark... Precure!
Blossom, go on ahead.
Moonlight?
I have to bring this to an end.
I have to defeat Dark Precure, and the person I once was.
The person you were?
The one who rejected friendship and allowed her fairy to die.
The one who lost to Dark Precure.
If I can defeat Dark Precure, that will
prove I'm not that foolish child anymore.
Moonlight...
Sabark.
If it wasn't for you and Dark Precure...
Dark Precure... She told us she was an artificial Precure.
It was you that created her, wasn't it?
Why did you make Dark Precure in Moonlight's image?
In her image?
Yes. Don't tell me you hadn't noticed?
If Moonlight represents the light,
then Dark Precure is its shadow.
They're two sides of the same coin.
This is the end.
I won't let you!
Coffret!
What are you doing?!
Are you trying to get hurt?!
I don't mind what happens to me if I can save you!
A powerless little fairy dares to strike the mighty Kumojacky?!
So, you still have some power left.
Now this is getting interesting!
Cure Marine, fight me with everything you've got!
Let's go, Coffret!
Right!
What is this power?
Cure Marine!
What's made you this strong?!
You keep going on about strength, but you don't have the first clue what it means!
What?!
You called Coffret a powerless little fairy.
But he still tried to fight you!
He risked his life to try to save me!
He might not be able to fight like we can, but he's billions of times stronger than you'll ever be!
Yeah!
The desire to protect others—true strength is that strength of heart!
How pathetic, Cure Sunshine.
I just can't bear to see you
rendered so unseemly like this.
I shall give you the beautiful end you
deserve with my own beautiful hands.
You're sho not beautiful, Kobraja!
What?
Potpourri!
As if a fairy would even be capable of appreciating my beauty!
You're heartless!
What?
No matter what happens, Sunshine has
the shtrength of heart to protect people.
That'sh more beautiful than you'll ever be!
Potpourri...
Thank you!
I told you before!
The heart is useless!
I don't care how pathetic or unseemly you think I am.
I want to protect the world... and its smiles, radiant as the Sun itself!
It's always bothered me.
If you'd ordered Dark Precure to finish her then and there,
you could have defeated Moonlight for good.
But you didn't.
No, you couldn't.
Something deep inside you couldn't allow it.
What are you rambling about?
You saved Moonlight... You saved Yuri.
Snackies! Guard the prisoner!
Sabark, why?
Kumojacky, you are really strong.
But what do you want to do with that strength?
What do I want to do?
Yeah.
I want to be a Precure and protect the world!
I want to live with Blossom and my friends, and for us to be happy together!
And I'll become as strong as it takes to do that!
I'll never give in!
But all you care about is being strong.
That's just so sad.
You may very well be right.
But even so...
I can't allow myself to be swayed!
You've toyed with so many hearts just because you want to be stronger.
You've made our world a desert!
My heart may be vaster than the sea, but this is as much as it can take!
Gather, Floral Power!
Marine Tact!
Making new friends, and growing closer together
Flowers, glitter bright!
I've changed enough to face whatever the future brings
Precure Blue Forte Wave!
I want us to protect this whole wide world
There's nothing to fear when we stand hand in hand
Rather than shining on those who are already loved
I want my gentle light
To shine on those who've never known love
I'll keep looking forward, running toward the sunlight
Such beauty.
You act without hesitation to leap to the aid of total strangers,
I want to realize this dream not for myself
yet still fight to the last to protect your world.
But for everyone around me
Is this the beauty you find in the heart?!
Once the world makes it through the winter
Oh, had I only learned of this sooner.
And our future starts to bloom again
I'll bring it light with my sunshine!
But it's far too late now!
Sunflower Aegis!
Sunshine Impact!
There's still time, Kobraja!
The darkness in your heart shall be illuminated by my light!
Like the Sun in the sky, I want to shine on everyone
And bring a smile to the faces of people trapped by fear
Gather, Floral Power!
The energy of the Sun exists for everyone
Shiny Tambourine!
And the joy of protecting the people I love
Will become the power of sunshine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
You've bested me, Cure Marine.
It seems your world had a lot left to teach me about what strength is.
So beautiful.
A fitting end for me, don't you think?
I'm glad it could be at your hands, Cure Sunshine.
Adieu!
In the language of flowers, a rugosa rose represents "beauty in sadness."
Beauty in sadness...
All because he was too busy looking for outer beauty.
It's sho sad.
In the language of flowers, an
Achillea alpina represents "battle."
He really did love to fight, didn't he?
Grandma!
Tsubomi?!
Lord Coupe!
Thank you, Tsubomi.
Cure Flower! How can we repair the Great Heart Tree?!
With the Heart Pot.
By using the Heart Seeds, with all the feelings they represent,
we can bring back the Great Heart Tree.
But first, we need to defeat Dune and put a stop to his tremendous power.
Moonlight!
I've got to help her!
Lord Coupe, look after Grandma!
Tsubomi!
Please.
Don't let Moonlight fight Sabark.
Now, the light shall be enveloped by shadow!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself in the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
In the midsts of the battle with Dark Precure,
Professor Sabark's tragic identity is revealed...
It can't be...
This can't be happening!
I can't take this in...
Moonlight, you mustn't give in!
You can't let this sadness continue!
HeartCatch Precure:
Please, Say It's Not True!
Professor Sabark's True Identity!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!