Aisaka?
Kitamura-kun.
Happy New Year.
H-Happy New Year.
Takasu isn't with you?
No...
He was hospitalized after catching
the flu at the end of the year,
and he's been home in bed
ever since he got discharged.
Really? That sounds serious!
We should go check up on him.
Kitamura-kun.
U-Uh...
Aisaka?
(My Silky Love)
Every time I think of you
MY SILKY LOVE nijuu yojikan zutto
(My Silky Love)
for 24 hours straight,
MY SILKY LOVE kimino koto omoutabi
(My Silky Love)
It only makes me feel
MY SILKY LOVE modokashii kono kimochi
(My Silky Love)
that much more impatient.
MY SILKY LOVE tada afure kaetteku
It's so simple just to say I love you.
But when you come close to me,
sukito ieba kantan nanoni
kimiga maeni kichauto
my own emotions go awry
and get in my way.
kyaraga sobie watashino
koto wo jamashiteru
I can bring myself to do anything.
That's who I'm supposed to be.
itsumonaraba tsuyoki de ikeru
sonna seikakunanoni
But I just can't break this
wall down no matter what.
donna ganbatte mitemo kabewa kuzusenai
Please understand these feelings for you.
sasshite hoshii kono kimoch iwo
That's why these gazes of mine,
dakara watashi wa itsumo kimini
they tell my love for you.
daisuki dayoto okuru shisen
Now gather up my courage!
saidaino yuukide
A fragile heart made of silk,
yabure souna shirukuno haato
I realized that by meeting you,
kimini atte kizuita yatto
I was so clumsy when it comes to love.
ainiwa bukiyou dattan datte
A forgotten scar left in my heart,
wasure kaketa koino kizuato
and I suddenly felt it sting deep inside.
kyuuni uzuki dashitano kyunto
I have to say that I love you someday...
itsukawa watashi rashiku sukito iwanakya
Or it'll keep making me weaker.
imayori yowaku nacchauyo
Stay Like This Forever
I ended up bedridden all winter break...
How am I supposed to face her?
I was...
shot down, right?
Rather definitively.
Ta-Taiga!
Wh-Why are you ignoring me!?
Show yourself!
Hey, Tai—
Jeez, what is it?
Keep it down, boy.
My noodles are going to get soggy.
Eating that junk again...
So annoying. Maybe I'll eat it in front of you.
It's ready now.
I've still been cooking
your share every day,
so why haven't you come
over since New Year's?
Listen, I know you're upset about Minorin rejecting you,
but don't take it out on me.
I'm not...
I'm just mad.
I'm not asking for your pity.
But you could at least act normal around me.
This is for you and Minorin.
I was so stupid.
I said I'd help you with her,
but I spent all my time at your place.
No wonder she got the wrong idea.
And you think that's why she shot me down?
Uh-huh.
Pretty sure she just isn't attracted to me—
No, I'm positive Minorin likes you.
But she believes that I need you.
Do you honestly think Minorin
doesn't like you?
W-Well...
I guess I sorta had this feeling that
she was kinda interested in me.
Then don't avoid her.
I won't go over to your place anymore.
I don't need you to make me food.
And you don't have to wake
me up in the morning.
If I learn to survive on my own,
and your feelings for Minorin don't change,
I'm sure she'll respond differently.
So...
So!
You should do what you need to!
Don't run away!
Find out how Minorin truly feels!
Got it.
But try not to burn the place down.
Don't worry, I promise to never use the stove.
I swear to eat out for the rest of my life!
Man...
How long are you going to last?
Forever...
Bye.
Good night.
R-Right...
Don't run away, huh?
I'm off.
Ryu-chan, you forgot something!
Jeez, I signed it for you and everything...
Signed what?
The Okinawa thing.
Consent Form
Oh!
Close one.
I totally forgot.
You're going to Okinawa for your class trip?
That's so wonderful! How fancy!
I wanna go too!
Kinda got bigger issues on my
mind right now, though...
Nothing. I'm off.
When I see Kushieda, I'll go up and say hi.
I'll start from there!
Oh, Takasu-kun!
I wanted to return this as soon as possible.
It looked really expensive.
Oh, this is...
You're that costume guy!
Yep, yep.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
It's fine, really.
Anyway...
This was in the pocket the whole time.
Oh, no worries.
I didn't actually need it that night.
Beach! Sun! Okinawa!
Pit vipers! Biscuits! Okinawa!
Six days and five nights in Okinawa!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, Tiger! Happy New Year and all that!
You're by yourself?
That's unusual. Where's Taka-chan?
Beats me.
Oh...!
Tiger! Tiger!
Right here! Read this!
Souvenirs from Okinawa:
Biscuit
Bi-Bigstick.
You guys hear that!?
Too late for this...
- Whoa! Hey!
- Hold it right there!
Taka-chan! Save me!
Tiger kicked me!
Because you kept moaning about biscuits!
What'd you do?
Come on...
What's that?
Th-This is...
What's it called...?
Something I no longer need.
Yoink!
Well? How's it look?
Give that back!
What? What!?
That still belongs to Ryuji!
- You're gonna make me bald... Ow!
- Give it back to him right now!
Hey now...
Good to see everyone's excited
for the new semester!
Morning, people!
'Sup?
Good morning, Minorin!
Uh...
G—
G...Go—
Gotta go buy juice!
Class is about to start!
That idiot...
Why did I run away?
I'm such a dumbass!
I wish everything would burn to the ground...
It burned to the ground!
But nothing will be canceled.
So everything's okay.
All will go as planned.
Teach, we have no idea what
you're talking about!
The hotel we were going to stay at
in Okinawa burned down in a fire.
And so, we'll be having a three-day,
two-night ski trip in the mountains!
Yay! Isn't that great?
What!?
That sucks!
Don't blame me! I didn't burn it!
I strongly object!
This is nonsense!
Damn it!
Why does Ami-chan have to
be late when we need her!?
Yeah, she could do something about this!
Kawashima-san is working in Hawaii.
Due to flight issues, she
won't make it back today.
And since she's spent plenty
of time on tropical islands,
she might actually prefer a
winter mountain excursion.
Hell no!
This is torture!
- My first plane ride! My first Okinawa trip!
- Who goes to the mountains during winter!?
You single...thirty-something!
Life doesn't always go your way!
Takasu?
Heading home?
Kitamura...
Where's Aisaka?
She isn't with you?
No...
She said she had something to do.
If I learn to survive on my own,
and your feelings for Minorin don't change...
She's living on cup noodles
to help me, and I'm...
Takasu?
Hey...
Did you see that girl?
She was gorgeous!
Maybe she's a model?
Kawashima.
I thought you were working in Hawaii.
Why are you here?
Piss off.
Why're you picking a fight
when we haven't seen each other since before break?
Because I hate you.
You're an idiot.
She called you an idiot...
Taiga!
- Why are you—?
- You're late!
We were supposed to meet ten minutes ago!
Don't be so anal, Dumb-chi!
Here.
As requested.
It's perfect!
You two are close enough to
buy gifts for each other now?
This isn't a gift.
I'm going to pay for it.
Too bad I don't need it anymore.
Oh, well. It'll have its uses.
Aren't you taking it to Okinawa?
You haven't heard?
It's been changed to a
three-day, two-night ski trip.
What!?
Our hotel in Okinawa burned down.
You've gotta be kidding!
S-Sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
Well...
Oh, that's right.
I have something to tell you before we leave.
Listen up.
Don't hang around Ryuji on the trip.
Excuse me?
He's the one always hanging around me.
You see...
Minorin shot Ryuji down on Christmas Eve.
For real?
More like, she implied that I shouldn't tell her
my feelings before I even got the chance to!
Oh...
So somebody finally got hurt.
But you see...
Minorin's actually attracted to Ryuji.
It's just not working out for various reasons.
When we're seniors,
we'll have college exams,
not to mention we might end
up in different classes...
So this trip is our last chance to
find out how Minorin truly feels.
Got it, Dumb-chi?
If that's what you really want.
Man, what a waste of time.
I'm out of here.
Oh, me too.
It's a shame that you're not
the only one who got hurt.
C-Come again?
Guess you're too stupid to understand.
What was that about?
Hey! Why are you following me!?
W-Well, I happen to be headed this way...
You know...
I didn't realize you were so serious
about Kushieda and me.
Thanks, I guess.
Uh, well...
I'll do what I can on the trip.
Even if there's no point in finding
out how Kushieda feels, I—
Idiot.
Your feelings are mutual.
Trust me. It'll be fine.
Hey...
Why are you so confident?
Really wanna know?
Because I have good reason
to believe that it's true.
What I'm saying is, I believe in you.
I believe that you're worthy of Minorin's love.
Anyway, I need to drop by the station.
A new shop opened
that sells boxed lunches.
O-Okay...
Oh, wait. What was up with
your attitude today?
You better not avoid her again tomorrow.
R-Right...
Taiga believes in me.
If I don't take the next step,
it's like I'm disappointing her.
G-Good morning!
Yo, Yoyo Ma!
Uh...
S-Sorry about yesterday...
You know...
Hmm? Whatcha talking about?
Didn't bother me one bit.
Oh.
Guess I'll go, then.
Grab him!
Ain't no thang!
Nice, Minorin!
Tai—
You were caught, so you get to carry my stuff.
What's with her?
- Stupid Taiga, stupid Taiga, stupid Taiga...
- Kushieda...?
Um, this is no big deal!
No problem at all.
Okay, give me a handle.
So, um...
Your hair looks a little different.
Oh, you noticed?
I got a little trim.
I actually wanted to cut it super short.
Like a guy's.
I had a buzz cut back in grade school.
I'd sit next to my little brother at the barber's,
and they'd just zip my hair
off with the clippers.
My nickname was Mr. Lady.
Still, I'm surprised you noticed.
Yeah, well...
I spend a lot of time looking at you.
Wow, now there's a shocking confession.
Right?
Yeah, I have to take the next step.
That reminds me.
Your brother plays high
school baseball, right?
His school regularly makes it to nationals.
Wow, you must be proud of him.
Uh-huh. But to be honest,
I'm jealous of him, too.
Yeah?
Oh, Amin-senpai!
First time I've seen you this year!
Why, good morning, Minori-chan.
Have you seen Taiga?
Nope, sure haven't.
What can I say...?
This makes me sigh.
Why would it?
Who knows?
That's a good question.
Whyever would that be?
Okay!
These will be the groups for the trip!
Hold on!
Don't you think they're a little weird?
You, Ami, and Kashii.
Aisaka and Kushieda.
Takasu and Noto.
Haruta and me.
A mixed group of nine boys and girls.
Since our class has more girls than boys,
this arrangement seems perfect to me.
B-But this means you and Tiger...
Never mind!
But this means...
What is it?
Join another group if you've got a problem.
You're a pain in the ass, Noto!
What was that!?
I said you're being a pain in the ass!
- Any thoughts, Takasu?
- You're a pain!
Wh-Why not?
Wait! Takasu-kun agrees!?
- If you have a problem, join a different grou—
- I said that's not it!
Come on, Professor Kitamura agrees.
You can stop talking, Noto!
Why are you being so mean!?
Huh? We have to make a guide?
Yeah.
Each team has to write one up
and turn it in by next week.
Why do we have to waste our time on that?
Why don't we all meet up someplace
to work on it together?
But where?
How about my place on Sunday?
You sure?
Uh-huh, it's pretty big.
Ooh...
Th-This place is unbelievable.
I wonder how much the rent is.
You and Takasu are neighbors, right?
What? Takasu-kun lives in this building too?
No, I'm in the place next door.
Okay!
Let's get started!
I borrowed some examples from
previous trips to use as reference.
There should be some guides in here.
Way to go, Professor!
Good job!
I'll go make some tea.
I brought madeleines.
Aisaka, where can I find an outlet
to plug in my computer?
Behind the TV.
Oh, thanks.
You can act normal around Kitamura now.
More or less.
Forget about that. Go help Minorin.
O-Okay...
Kushieda.
Let me give you a hand.
Hey, Golgo.
I'm not Golgo...
Then I'm Golgo.
Don't stand behind me.
Uh, I'm standing behind you, but...
Excellent.
It feels so weird to see clean
dishes at Taiga's place.
I haven't been here in a year.
Everything looks totally different.
And it's all thanks to you.
No, I haven't done anything lately.
Taiga's been doing this by herself.
But you're still the reason she can do it at all.
Hot!
- Ouch, burning...
- You haven't visited in a year?
Right.
After the stuff with her dad...
I thought if I stopped coming over and gave us some space,
I wouldn't mess up again.
In other words...
You did a good job, Takasu-kun.
You stepped in here and didn't let yourself
get worked up about screwing up.
Kushieda...
Hey, you think anybody will notice
if we copy the whole thing?
Why would we copy a guide to Okinawa
when we're headed for snowy mountains?
Are you an idiot?
What is it?
Oh?
We can't let Yusaku see this.
- Hey, Ami-chan!
- What is it?
You're better off not knowing.
That only makes me more curious.
Ooh...
Must be a shock, right?
It's only a picture, but after
that grand rejection—
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Stupid Dumb-chi!
What?
- It's his fault for being so sensitive!
- Here you go! Tea's ready!
- What was that!?
- Man, could you two get along?
To be honest, I'm kinda looking
forward to the class trip.
Because it's the last time 2-C
will get to do something together.
This class has been so much fun...
I'm going to miss it...
If only we could stay like this forever.
Yeah, you're right.
If only we could stay like this forever...
Can Kushieda and I...and everyone else...
stay like this?
She sorted her trash...
No...
We can't stay like this forever.
I have to use this trip to find
out how Kushieda truly feels.
Bus #3
Ohashi High School
S-S-S-Sour grapes!
S-S-S-Silver oxide battery.
Yucky scab.
Belly button lint from a maid.
Dark chocolate.
Takasu, we're on "E."
Every effort counts!
For what?
You can only use things that are bitter.
Well, you could say that
wasted effort is a bitter thing.
You've got a point there.
Then we're on to "T."
T...
T-T-T...
Ta-ta-ta-ta...
- As in, Bobby Bitter singing scat.
- Yeah...
- Who the hell is that!?
- Every little effort counts.
So I'll try one more time to express the
feelings she denied on Christmas Eve.
In those sleepless nights,
nemurenai yoruni wa
I lay there sighing all alone.
hitoride tameiki
What about everyone else?
minna wa dounano
It just feels so lonely.
nandaka samishii
A tiny little seed in this huge Earth.
hiroi daichini hitotsubu no tane
Stretch out those roots,
nekko nobashite
and bear a fruit that's still unripe.
mada aoi miwo tsuketa
The fruit that wants to hurry and turn orange.
orenji ironi hayaku naritai kajitsu
Showering in your light
kimino hikari wo abite
only nurtures bigger ideals and dreams.
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
Why won't you notice?
kizuiteyo nee
I ate the orange today but cried
because it was still too sour.
orenji kyoumo tabete mitakedo
mada suppakute naita
It reminded too much of me,
watashi mitaide nokosenai kara
so I finished the whole thing.
zenbu tabeta
I love you. It makes me cry.
sukidayo nakeruyo
I love you. I love you.
sukidayo sukidayo
Can't Help Myself
I'm going to redo my
Christmas Eve confession.
Not just for me, but for Taiga and
all the support she's given me.
I'm useless.
All talk.
I can't take this anymore.