Akihisa Yoshii is a young man
who is very particular about everything he does.
Time to eat!
When I have salt water as a side
dish and sugar water as the main,
the meal seems a little extravagant, doesn't it?
The degree to which he is particular
about things gets lower every day.
Coming!
Long time no see, Aki.
S...
Sis...?
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
"Episode 9" "Kisses, Breasts, and Ponytails"
Akira Yoshii. 23 years old. E cup.
She is Akihisa's older sister who lives abroad.
Sis! You came here dressed like that?!
Why're you raising your voice
all of a sudden? That's absurd.
Says someone who walks
around in her bathrobe...!
You should let people finish their stories.
I have a reason for being dressed like this.
Sorry, Sis. What happened?
"A Day in the Life of Akira, Story of an Elegant Day, Episode 1"
I walked quite a ways from the airport
in the heat with heavy luggage.
Uh-huh.
When I got on the train, I saw
myself all sweaty in the window.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Although I was going to see my brother,
I should pay attention to my appearance.
I didn't want to show myself all sweaty.
Uh-huh.
So, in order to deal with the sweat,
I changed into a bathrobe
since it's highly absorbent.
Stop right there! That's messed up!
Thus, I was able to reunite with
my little brother while maintaining
the dignified appearance
his older sister should have.
And that's even more messed up!
I'm glad that the train was rather empty.
"A Day in the Life of Akira, Story of an Elegant Day, Episode 2"
If it was crowded, I would've had problems changing.
Hold on a sec. Where'd you change?
"Omitted (024 - 1)"
"Omitted (024 - 2)"
Aki, I came here today because
I have to attend to important affairs.
What?
I'll start my investigation
now on how you're living
and decide if it's okay to
let you continue to live alone.
What?!
When you started living alone,
I gave you two conditions to follow.
I'm sure you haven't forgotten them, have you?
If I say I did, will you get upset?
No, I won't.
Good! Well, I completely--
Instead of getting upset, I'll give you a kiss.
...completely remember them!
Moreover, I'll give you an incredible kiss,
then marriage will no longer be possible.
What're you planning to
do to your own little brother?
Relax. It's me who won't be able to get married.
I can't relax!
You'll live the rest of your life
feeling guilty towards your sister
since she won't be able to get married.
I remember them well, so please spare me!
Then, tell me what they are.
Uhm...
Aki. Close your eyes.
Ah! First, I can play video
games for 30 minutes a day!
Second, illicit sexual
relationships are forbidden!
Sorry.
Are they wrong?!
When they're correct, I can't kiss you.
Is that something you should be sorry about?
It's tidier than I thought.
You thought it'd be messier?
You're at that age, too, so...
I thought that your room would be
buried in two thousand dirty books.
I don't have money to buy two thousand of them.
In other words, you have at least one book?
Ah!
As a semi-illicit sexual
relationship, that's minus 20 points.
What's that score?
It's an assessment used to determine
if it's okay for you to continue living alone.
I'll compare it with your next periodical
test and reconsider the approval.
In other words, that means that if
I get 20 more points in the next midterm,
it'll cancel out that 20 points, huh?
Let me ask you, just in case...
You're not in any other illicit
sexual relationships, are you?
Doing what gives me how many negative points?
If you hold hands with a
girl, that's minus 100 points.
What?!
If you go out with girls to
see movies or have crepes,
or if girls make you lunch or waffles,
you'll get minus 50,000 points.
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
You're a healthy young man.
I understand very well that you don't
know what to do with your young body.
I didn't say that.
So I'll concede as much as I can as well.
Although I forbid illicit
sexual relationships with girls...
I think I can accept your illicit
sexual relationships with guys.
What happened?!
What happened to your sense
of values while living abroad?!
The stars look... pretty.
These scores are...
more terrible than I expected.
Be that as it may, I tried hard in my own way.
Trying hard is only a means to an end.
No matter how invaluable
the act of trying hard is,
if you become proud of the effort itself,
you're mistaking the means for the end.
You don't have to say that.
If you don't want me to say that to you,
please overcome the subjects
you're bad at. Even one subject is fine.
Tsk. You do have a subject
you're bad at too, you know.
What is that?
Cooking.
That has nothing to do with academics.
But it's necessary for living.
--Well, all you're good at is academics. As for the rest...
--If you say more, I'll kiss you to shut you up.
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
Yuuji... I want you to show me your cell.
Why?
They said on a TV show
last night that the traces
of your partner's infidelity can be
found on their cell. Show it to me.
I refuse.
My eyes... My eyes hurt like they're burning!
If you resist, I'll take it by force.
Hey! Don't take my pants, too!
I heard that guys like
seeing a shirt on a naked body.
It's not that we like to
see ourselves like that!
I wanna see it, too.
Ah! Okay! I'll give it
to you! I'll give it to you!
You will...?
Don't be so openly disappointed!
Geez... Here.
You get more e-mail from Yoshii than me.
So what?
That means that you're
having a love affair with Yoshii.
Are you kidding me?!
Can I stay overnight at your place?
I kinda don't want to... go home tonight.
Hey, wait... Shouko! Sto--!
I'm all set now.
Good morning, Akihisa.
Hm?
What happened, Akihisa?
You look healthier than usual.
Yeah. I had a decent
breakfast this morning, so...
Akihisa sold his manga books and
video games to a second-hand shop
and got money for food.
Even if it's just during Sis's stay,
I'd better pretend that I live a healthy life.
Or I'll get negative points.
Cool Biz?
Who'd follow Cool Biz just below their waist?!
This is all because you sent me a weird e-mail!
There was nothing weird about it, was there?
Then read it out loud.
"Sent Box" "001 Yuuji" Let me stay over" "002 Yuuji: Love"
"003 Yuuji: Don't let go" "004 Yuuji: Together"
"Can I stay overnight at your place?
I kinda don't want to... go home tonight."
I don't get your true feelings!
You should wait to do something
like that until you are older!
That's obscene, Yoshii!
Baka Test
Uhm... Yoshii.
Go to the nurse's office.
You think something's wrong if I'm studying?!
Did something happen, Aki?
To see you suddenly studying...
Hm?
You're acting strange today.
Nothing... really.
Oh? You've got quite a well-made lunch today.
Yeah, for a change...
Amazing... Who made it?
Me.
Liar.
That's a lie.
I'm not lying!
This is by someone very skilled.
Is it either Sakamoto or Tsuchiya?
Be honest and spit it out.
Who made it for you?
I'll leave it to your imagination now.
You don't wanna go home today, right?
You're that dirty, Aki?!
I don't want to believe it!
I hate you, Yoshii!
What were you imagining?!
And hey, why is Kubo here too?!
By the way, Akihisa...
why do you wanna stay over at my place?
--What? I-It's because I suddenly realized studying is important.
--Don't lie.
Hey, I didn't even finish!
Well, midterms are coming up soon.
The idea of a study group isn't too bad.
Really?
But... at your place.
N-N-N-No! Not my place! Today isn't... good!
What're you hiding?
Shall we go check it out?
A house search...
In any case, today isn't
good! It's really messy!
I'll help you tidy up.
Well... but...
Oh yeah, if the mess is from something
that girls don't like to touch, then...
I've got two thousand dirty
books scattered all over, so...!
I'll tidy them up!
I'll ditch them all!
Leave it to us!
Dammit! That backfired big time!
Idiot Test
Are you really coming to my place?
What on earth are you hiding, Akihisa?
Considering that you brought
a lunch that someone made...
In all probability, it's a girlfriend.
What's that mean, Aki?! Explain it!
Uhm, I didn't say anything.
Don't worry. There's no way that Yoshii
would date someone behind our back.
Isn't that right, Yoshii?
Your eyes are serious.
Well, once we go inside,
it'll probably be all clear.
Unlock the door, Akihisa.
I... I don't want to!
Do you wanna experience the
agony of wearing nothing but a shirt?
I'd appreciate it if you
look upward with watery eyes.
Are you gonna sell it? Are
you gonna sell my pure heart?!
Tsuchiya, have him unhook
the top two buttons of his shirt.
Himeji, your request is too detailed!
Okay, okay! I'll open it!
You'll be happy if I open it, right?
Your buttons?
No, the door!
Ahhhhh!
There's already something that
I can't come up with an excuse for!
This physical evidence is
about as good as it gets.
I'm so jealous that I wanna kill him.
This isn't good, Yoshii.
Huh?
The size of this bra... doesn't fit you.
She's not gonna admit it.
Ah! Th-That's...
That's a cotton puff for makeup.
No, that's a fish cake.
A fish cake?
Ah! This is...
Hm?
A healthy lunch for a woman...
What's the matter, Himeji?!
I can't keep on denying any more.
Why are underwear and
cosmetics okay but a lunch isn't?!
Oh, you brought friends?
Ah! An older pretty woman...
A nice body with big breasts...
You're cruel, Yoshii!
Give me back my pure heart!
I don't understand what
you're saying anymore...
Okay. I'll be honest and tell you.
She's my older sister.
Older sister?!
My name is Akira Yoshii.
Thank you very much, everyone, for
being friends with my stupid brother.
I hope you'll continue to be friends with him.
This is surprising! She looks like
an ordinary older sister in every way.
Thanks, Sis!
I'm Yuuji Sakamoto.
I'm Kouta Tsuchiya.
I'm Hideyoshi Kinoshita.
People often make a mistake,
but I'm not a girl. I'm...
A boy, right?
You're the only one who
recognized me as a guy at a glance!
Sure, since there's no way that
my stupid, ugly, good-for-nothing
little brother can get female friends.
So these two are boys as well, right?
What's with the sudden rude
remarks?! You were acting so nicely.
These three are all girls, okay?!
No, she's right about me being a guy.
Girls?
Since when have you started bringing girls home?
Ugh!
"Akihisa's
allotted points"
You'll get minus 200 points for the act
of illicit sexual relationships with girls!
Nooooo!
Akihisa... You've been
having hardships too, huh?
Yuuji...
I'll allow illicit sexual
relationships with boys.
It's not like that!
I'll give you 10 points for that.
That doesn't make me happy or anything!
Oh, Akihisa, since we suddenly came uninvited,
we'll at least help you make dinner.
Okay. Thanks.
Me, too.
I'll help, too.
We'll be fine by ourselves!
You girls take it easy here.
What? But...
Sis, keep them company.
Okay. If you like, I can show you photo albums.
What? Is that okay?
Well then, I'll show you embarrassing pictures.
Anything but those!
That was a narrow escape.
So, what's on the menu?
With these, we can make paella. I like paella.
In any case, did she know we were coming?
No way. Since she doesn't know how
to cook, she bought too much by mistake.
--Yeah, put it over there.
--This one is really good, too.
Here you go.
These are pictures of Aki taking
a bath when he was two years old.
H-He's really cute!
These are pictures of Aki taking
a bath when he was four years old.
Oh, Aki's fallen asleep.
These are pictures of Aki taking
a bath when he was seven years old.
So this was when he was
in elementary school, huh?
These are pictures of Aki taking
a bath when he was ten years old.
Hold on a sec! Why are they
all pictures of me taking a bath?!
These are pictures of Aki taking a
bath when he was thirteen years old.
Hey... Why are you all suddenly quiet?
And these are pictures of
Aki taking a bath yesterday.
When'd you take them?!
--Don't look at them! Don't look!
--Hey, don't leave the pot unattended.
--Don't look at my private parts!
Noooooooo!
They made delicious-looking food.
Oh? You made paella?
Huh? Didn't you buy those foods for that?
Th-That looks good, Aki.
S-So you really can cook, huh?
--Ahhh! You must've seen them! You all must've seen them!
--Seriously, Aki is restless. Negative 10 points.
It's your fault, Sis!
You keep trying to annoy me!
You hate me, don't you, Sis?!
No. I do like you, Aki...
What?
...as a woman.
This is terrible!
There's a Japanese saying that goes like this:
"The stupider the child is,
the more darling he is."
Give up, Akihisa. She loves you
more than anyone in the world.
Does that mean that she thinks
I'm the stupidest in the world?
I think you're the stupidest in the world, too!
I, too, am convinced that there's no
one else who's stupider than you are.
--Stop it! Don't hurt my glass heart, everyone!
--You really are stupid, aren't you?
Well... now that we're full,
shall we start studying?
If you like, I can help you study.
Is that okay?
I got a degree in education
over there, so I think I can help you.
Over there?
Boston, in America.
Could it... possibly be... Harvard University?!
What?!
I see...
Leftover genes, huh...?
What do you mean by that?!
"Dirty Book"
Well then, here are the reference books.
I found six of them under the bed.
My top secret!
Aki, I'll give you minus 60 points for this.
Does that mean 10 negative points per book?
No. That's because you didn't have
books with a focus on older sisters.
That's too unfair!
Well then, please use them as
Health and Physical Education references.
Stop it. My hobby is gonna
be exposed to the light of day!
Looks like Aki tends to study by focusing
on the topic of girls with
big breasts and a ponytail.
Ah!
W-Well, let's start studying, shall we?
Why are you tying your hair up, Mizuki?!
I thought it'd be in the
way while I'm studying, so...
I'll do it for you!
You're mean, Minami!
Why? That way, it won't be
in the way while studying, right?
Aki, you get minus 100 points.
What?!
Why?!
Learn the reason on
your own in your future life.
What's the matter, Muttsulini?
Where are the other 1,994 books?
So you took it seriously...
--G-Good morning, Yoshii.
--Good morning, Aki.
Hm?
Good morning, you two.
You changed your hairstyle, Himeji?
Y-Yes, to change my mood.
You changed your breast style, Minami?
No! They were bigger when I woke up!
Are you serious?
Since I'm still growing,
something like this can happen!
I won't allow you to profane
secondary sex characteristics.
Tsk.
Yesterday was fun, wasn't it?
We made progress in our studies, too.
But it looks like I'll be
forbidden to live alone.
I wish Sis would go back to America.
You shouldn't talk about your family like that.
She's a nice sister.
She isn't nice. She tries to kiss
me and gives me negative points.
She enjoys teasing me.
That's not true.
Your sister loves you.
Does that mean she really thinks I'm stupid?!
She watches you and your surroundings very well.
I think that means she really cares about you.
I wonder if that's how it is.
What shall I make tonight?
She came all the way back to Japan.
Maybe Japanese dishes would be good.
I'm home!
Oh, welcome home, Aki.
Well then, I'll go get food for dinner, okay?
Dinner? Wait, Aki.
What is it, Sis?
Your midterms are coming up soon.
Can you afford to spare
your time for cooking right now?
I can't, but... you came all the way back, so...
You're mistaking the means for the end.
Huh?
I came to check on your life, Aki.
What's the point in you using your time for me?
I won't know what to do if you use it as
an excuse when the results aren't good.
You don't have to cook for me.
You focus on studying. I'll cook fo--
What's with you?
All you care about is the test results, right?!
I'll go study as you wish!
Stupid Sis!
I'll definitely get good
scores and show her I can do it!
Good morning, Yoshii.
Good morning, Aki.
D-Don't talk to me.
The stuff I memorized and
crammed into my head might come out.
R-Really?
Then, we'll leave you alone.
Okay then, we'll start the test. Start now!
"Q. Answer the following questions."
I can do this!
Question 1. 334 BC! The last king of
the Achaemenid Empire of Persia was
Alexander the Great! Next!
He must be taking the test right now.
Well then, I guess I'll start, too.
All right. I did my best.
I'll have another look at
them in the remaining time.
Okay. Put your pencils down.
Those in the back, collect the answer sheets.
Ah!
"Name: Alexander the Great"
Goodbye, my life of living alone.
Geez, you stupid Alexander the Great...
You put the first answer in
where you needed to put your name,
so the rest of the answers
became off by one, huh?
Please...! Call me by my real name.
Darius III.
Ahh! Don't humiliate me any more than you have!
I could've gotten a decent
score if I didn't blunder.
Do you think you'll be forgiven
if you make the same mistake
in a real college entrance exam?
I tried very hard in my own way.
I thought I told you that trying
hard is only a means to an end.
Yes ma'am.
Sis is ruthless.
Geez... What a mess.
Hey, she doesn't cook, though.
"Half-cooked" "Forgot to put in saffron"
"The heat was too high"
"Detergent got mixed in"
"Sticky" "Too much salt"
"Terrible taste"
Are these... failed attempts at paella?
Could it be that... she wanted to
make my favorite food so she practiced?
Trying hard is only a means to an end.
If you become proud of the effort itself,
you're mistaking the means for the end.
Really... she's such a dummy.
I'd have to say the first kiss
tastes like strawberry milk
As it turns to evening,
I'm pushing my bike home
So which is it, a delusion,
a simulation, or a dream?
After stumbling seven times,
I stumble an eighth time, wahahaha
Each day is different and
every day is an anniversary
Let's connect them together to that sky
My future is bright. Do I see
myself becoming someone big?
Tomorrow too, for sure...
it'll be sunny, with occasional smiles
Say, Sis...
Yes?
Thanks for everything. I like you a lot.
What're you...
Of course, as family.
Even if you say such a nice thing,
I won't overlook the test score.
That's a shame.
One of these days...
What?
One of these days, if I feel like it,
maybe I'll make dinner for you.
Really?
That is only if I feel like it.
I look forward to it.
Sis...
What is it?
Do you know what the best spice is?
The best spice?
Since I don't cook, I don't know. What is it?
Yeah, I wonder what it is!
Question 10. Name the Japanese novelist
who introduced the "Adolescent Detective Gang"
and the "Mystery Man of
Twenty Faces" to the world.
The thief is among us!
It's not me.
Next Episode! "Prep Tests,
Mysterious Thieves, and Love Letters."
This will be on the test.
"Please join us again next week!"
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"