History Club
Boys Basketball Club
Ballroom Dancing Club
Hocus-Pocus Club
Club Application
Classic Literature
Faculty Office
Earth Science Prep Room
Oreki
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away the
awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
The Return of the
Time-Honored Classic Lit Club
Jumonji Family, Sarusuberi Family,
Chitanda Family, Manninbashi Family
Unlocked
Locked
Seimei ('The Clearing')
When all of nature is bright and clear,
and we see what grasses have sprouted
Hyouka
When all of nature is bright and clear,
and we see what grasses have sprouted
Diligent application and
unswerving determination
Rosy
Baseball Club now seeking members
Joro Spider Society
filling two vacancies
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The Prestigious Classic Lit Club's Activities