High school life, they say, is rosy.
And rosy, they say, is high school life.
High school life is always
treated as being rosy,
so much so, that being told
as much is commonplace.
And yet, I don't think that all
high-schoolers want it to be rosy.
History Club
Take studying,
Boys Basketball Club
and sports,
Ballroom Dancing Club
and romantic affairs... there are
people who show no interest in any of them, aren't there?
Hocus-Pocus Club
There are students who prefer things
"gray," as it were, aren't there?
Well, I guess that might be
a pretty empty life, though.
Hotaro, I never knew you had
a masochistic streak.
Masochistic?
Taking a negative view of studying,
sports, and romance...
The perennially gray person.
That's who you are, Hotaro, right?
It's not that I have a
negative view of them.
Not in your opinion.
Energy-conserving...
That's what you are, right, Hotaro?
You're simply not interested in anything
you consider to be a hassle or frivolous.
Which brings us to your motto...
"If I don't have to do
something, I don't do it.
If I have to do something,
I do it quickly."
Yep. But you know, Hotaro,
you, having not joined
any of the clubs offered
in this shrine of various clubs
known as Kamiyama High School,
you've ended up being
the color gray itself.
That "empty life," as you call it,
is nothing other than masochism.
You sure do like to run your mouth.
Now you're telling me? You've known
me since middle school, right?
Hmph, whatever. You can leave without me.
Without you? What's going on?
Is that...? No, it couldn't be!
Club Application
A club application?!
Hotaro, you're joining a club?!
Classic Literature
And the Classic Lit Club, at that!
You're familiar with it?
Of course I am! But, Hotaro,
what possessed you to get into classic lit?
That's... a letter from your sister, right?
She mailed it from India.
Vanarasi, or someplace.
Let's see...
I see the problem now. It was
a request from your sister.
Apparently, it's on the verge of
being shut down for lack of members.
She wants me to join so it can keep going.
If I remember, your sister's thing was...
Aikido and takedown moves. If she wants
to hurt you, she can really hurt you.
You can't turn this down, then.
Well, when she writes that there's
nothing I really want to do, she's right.
They don't have any members
in the club, right?
Yeah.
Then you have the Classic Lit Club's
room to yourself, don't you?
Having your own private space
inside the school is a pretty nice thing.
Private space?
Kami High!
I salute those who live an
energy-consuming lifestyle.
Faculty Office
People often get the wrong idea,
but it's not as if I hold energy
conservation to be superior.
I don't look down on those
who are more active.
I'm just faithful to my own motto.
"If I don't have to do
something, I don't do it.
If I have to do something,
I do it quickly."
Earth Science Prep Room
Oreki
Here, look!
Jeez!
Earth Science Prep Room
Fourth floor of the auxiliary building.
That's as remote as it gets.
I scowled at the wind blowing
at my window of boredom
so I could turn away the
awkwardness I was feeling
Hyouka
I nod noncommittally at today
as I hold it in my hand
projecting myself a little exaggeratedly
I get the feeling that
something is about to change
It's all because of you
calling out to my heart
Peeking up at cloudy skies,
I sense what's coming
Let's reach out our hands
with courage stronger than ever
Light and shadow are both still far off
but even so, we want to know
the reason for this kindness
Let's go look now, beyond the brilliance
that goes by nobody's name
before it all becomes a thing of the past
Hello.
You're in the Classic Lit Club, too, Oreki-san?
The Return of the Time-Honored Classic Lit Club
Who are you?
You don't know?
Chitanda. Chitanda Eru.
Sorry, I have no idea who you are.
You're Oreki Hotaro-san, right?
From Class 1-B?
Yeah.
I'm in Class 1-A.
You know, that doesn't really help much...
Class A? Then one of the elective classes?
You wouldn't happen to be
in my music class, would you?
Yes.
We've only had that class once so far.
What kind of memory does she have?
Uh, so, Chitanda-san...
What are you doing in this room?
Oh, right.
I've joined the Classic Lit Club too,
so I came to pay my respects.
I've joined the Classic Lit Club...
The Classic Lit Club? Why would you?
I have some personal reasons.
What about you, Oreki-san?
Oh, as long as there are
other members, that's terrific.
Rejoice, Sis. The Classic
Lit Club lives on.
Well, I'll be going now.
You're leaving already?
Yeah. Good luck. And
could you lock up, too?
Huh?
I can't lock up.
Why not?
I don't have a key.
Oh.
Here.
Why do you have one, Oreki-san?
Why? You can't get into a locked
classroom without a key, right?
Come to think of it, how the
hell did... Oh, excuse me...
Chitanda-san, how did you
get into the room?
The door wasn't locked.
When I got here, it was closed, and...
It was closed? You mean, the door?
Yeah, I do.
So then, are you saying that
I was locked inside here?
You're the one who locked it,
right? From the inside?
No, I didn't!
But I'm the one with the key.
Who else but you could have locked it?
By the way, is that a friend of yours?
Huh?
Satoshi!
Hey, sorry, sorry! I wasn't
intending to eavesdrop.
You weren't intending to, you were.
Be that as it may,
when I see my hard-boiled Hotaro at a classroom
window alone with a girl, with evening closing in,
it's only natural that
I'd be a little curious.
I didn't mean to interrupt your
little after-school rendezvous,
and I've never been a Peeping Tom
before, so... U-Um... Um, I...
Are you serious?
Of course not. I'm joking.
Is that so?
Sorry about that. That's just
the sort of guy he is.
"Nothing beats an impromptu joke.
It creates a breeding ground for lies."
That's my motto.
Oh. Oreki-san, who is this?
This is Fukube Satoshi,
would-be sophisticate.
Would-be?
Smooth! Nice introduction, Hotaro!
Nice to meet you, uh...
Chitanda Eru.
Ch-Chitanda-san?! By Chitanda-san,
do you mean, the Chitanda-san?
Is something the matter?
Hotaro, haven't you ever heard
of the Chitanda family?!
There are more than a few pedigreed,
prestigious families in Kamiyama,
but if you mention the "Four Higher
Power Families," they're notable.
There's the Jumonji family of Arekusu Shrine,
Jumonji Family, Sarusuberi Family, Chitanda Family, Manninbashi
Family
the bookstore tycoon Sasusuberi family,
the wealthy farmers of the Chitanda family,
and the Manninbashi family,
who own the mountain timberlands.
Each family name is one power
of ten greater than the last,
which is why people call them the
"Four Higher Power Families."
Really?
I don't know if we're a
"prestigious" family,
but that's the first time
I've heard us be called that.
You made that up, huh?
Sometimes, I'd like to be
the one who coins terms.
But they really do go
in orders of ten, huh?
Don't act impressed; you'll swell his head.
What's more, the oldest Chitanda girl is
known for her high marks and fair features,
and for being a well-refined beauty.
In middle school, she got high grades
in the prefectural practice exams,
and I've seen her name around a lot.
O-ho, you're all that?
It's a fluke. I just have
a knack for taking tests.
Well, I beg your pardon.
By the way, I heard all
about it. Truly fascinating.
What is?
The way Chitanda-san got
locked inside this room.
Oh, that's right!
When I came here, the door
to the room was unlocked.
Unlocked
But when Oreki-san arrived afterward,
he said the door was locked.
It's a mystery.
Locked
How do you figure? You just
forgot that you locked it, right?
Nope. Kami High's doors are set up
so that you can only lock them
with a key, both inside or outside.
Meaning that it is impossible for
Chitanda-san to have locked it from inside.
Look at that!
As big a know-it-all as ever, I see.
I'd prefer you call me a database.
Hmph. Well, the lock business
must have been some kind of mistake.
I'm out of here.
Please wait, Oreki-san!
What?
I am curious.
How did I get locked in?
And if it happens that I wasn't locked in,
how was it that I was able to
get inside this classroom?
Supposing that it was some kind of mistake,
whose mistake was it,
and how was it made?
Please, Oreki-san, you think about it, too!
Oreki-san...
I am curious.
Yeah... Okay. That is interesting.
Let me think about it for a bit.
Thank you very much!
Oreki-san, do you have any thoughts?
Chitanda-san, give him a minute.
I'm just a database, so I can't
come up with any conclusions,
but not Hotaro.
Once he starts thinking,
his reasoning is sound, in its own way.
Put a sock in it.
Now then...
Hmm... When did you enter the room?
I think it was about three
minutes before you got here.
Hmm. Did you notice anything else?
Now that you mention it,
something has been rattling around
underfoot for a little while.
Huh? I don't hear anything.
You can hear it. Listen.
Chitanda-san, you have sharp ears.
Hmm...
Figured anything out yet, Hotaro?
Maybe. It's probably playing out
again on the floor just below us.
There. All right...
Aha. Chitanda-san must have gone
in the Earth Science prep room
while that work was being done,
and was unlucky enough
to be locked inside.
I have the circulating key.
There are also the master keys,
but students aren't allowed to use those.
That's how you knew it was the janitor.
Still, way to realize something like that!
Not really. So, Chitanda-san,
what I don't understand is,
why you didn't notice the sound of the lock
while you were inside the room?
Ah, in that case...
I was looking at that building.
It's old, huh?
Yes.
Is it?
Yeah, exceptionally so.
Hmm...
By the way, I still haven't
paid my respects yet.
Your respects?
Yes.
We are going to be together
in the Classic Lit Club, after all.
Together?
Fukube-san, what do you say
about the Classic Lit Club?
Why not? Today has been interesting.
I'll have to juggle it with Executive
Committee and Handicrafts Club, though.
Mm-hm, I'll join.
And so will Hotaro.
He's already filled out the application.
You have?
Huh? Yeah, well, the thing is...
Here.
Huh?
Okay, I've got it. I'm looking
forward to this with you.
As am I. You, too, Hotaro.
Hmph.
You know, we have to choose a
club president. What should we do?
Good question. Hotaro isn't cut out
for that sort of thing at all.
Sis, are you satisfied now?
The time-honored Classic Lit Club is back.
And farewell to my days of peace
and energy conservation.
No! I'm not saying goodbye yet.
I'm not giving up on my peace.
I will devote all of my efforts
toward conserving energy.
The problem is...
and such a sharp mind, doesn't he?
This little lady.
Seimei ('The Clearing')
When all of nature is bright and clear,
and we see what grasses have sprouted
Hyouka
It happened yesterday after school.
A 1st-year girl went to the
fourth floor of the auxiliary building.
As she did, she heard the beautiful melody of
"Moonlight Sonata" coming from the music room.
The setting sun bathed the
school building in crimson.
The beautiful tones of...
Objection. It was raining yesterday,
and you couldn't see the setting sun.
Yes, it was in the dampness
of the falling rain,
and evening's gloom was drawing near.
A sense of discomfort clung at her skin,
accompanied by the noise of the rain.
That's so not what happened.
Lured by the tones,
she entered the music room,
when immediately, things fell silent.
The lid of the piano was up,
but there was no pianist.
The curtains were drawn closed,
and the room was dark.
That's when she saw her!
A girl student with long,
unkempt hair hanging over her face,
whose body was limp and slumped over,
and whose eyes were a fiery bloodshot red,
was staring at her from off to the side!
Yes, once, here at Kamiyama High School,
there was a Piano Club member who met a bitter
accidental death just before a national competition!
Was there?
Huh? Who can say? Maybe there
was one, but I don't know.
That's what I thought.
I have to admit, I didn't expect this.
I mean, you, forgetting your
homework and having to stay after?
I did do it, yesterday.
I just forgot to bring it.
And now, I have to sit here
writing the same essay
while listening to all your blather.
So that's it.
By the way, I hear there really
was a disheveled-hair ghost.
It was the talk of Class A
during lunch break today.
The important question is how
this story is going to spread now.
This is one of the Seven Wonders of
Kamiyama High School... number two!
I'm waiting to see how many days
it takes to reach my own Class D.
Hmm? Hold on a second.
When, where, and from whom
did you hear this story?
Earlier, in the club
room, from Chitanda-san.
If this is the second of the Seven Wonders,
there's a first, too, right?
Would you tell me what that is?
So here is where the two of you are.
I wrote it up, Fukube-san.
Ah, thank you. Sorry about that.
As an Executive Committee member,
I have to ask for these kinds of
tedious procedures to be done.
Not at all. I have taken on
the club presidency, after all.
Oreki-san!
You came just at the right time.
I just heard an odd tale from Satoshi.
Ah, about that! At lunch today...
It was a story about the
"Secret Club Recruitment Note."
Do you know it?
Secret club?
Satoshi, fill her in.
Huh? Mm-hm...
Well, would you like to hear
the tale of the "Secret Club"?
Yes.
It's a story I heard during
Executive Committee.
As you know, Kamiyama
High School has many clubs.
So naturally, there are a lot of
recruitment posters for them,
and the bulletin boards around the
school get buried under these posters.
When the Executive Committee finds
an unauthorized poster or note,
they take them down.
However...
Every year, apparently, there's one
recruitment note that turns up
for a club that nobody
knows anything about.
Last year, there was a meeting
place and time written down
on what looked like a scrap
of notebook paper.
It seems that there's a secret club
that not even the Committee knows about,
and they are secretly recruiting members.
Diligent application and unswerving determination
The club's objectives and membership is unknown,
but they do actually exist.
Their name is...
Their name is...?
The Joro Spider Society.
Joro Spider...?
Last year, Executive Committee
Chair Tanabe-senpai
tried to contact the Joro Spider Society
using the note they found.
But it didn't go very well.
He said he ended up concluding that it was
a just a hoax that was using the name.
However...
However...?
On graduation day, one of the
graduates said to Tanabe-senpai...
"I was the president of
the Joro Spider Society.
Give my regards to next
year's president for me.
That is, if you can ever find them."
I'm sure they're recruiting
somewhere for this year, too.
We still haven't discovered
where, as of yet, though.
A single note...
The Joro Spider Society...
I am curious!
Yes!
I thought you might say that.
That's why I said you came
at just the right time.
What do you mean?
We're going to go looking,
of course, for that note.
Okay!
There are 30 bulletin boards in all.
That many? Are we going
to search them all?
Of course not.
It's quicker to think about
where it most likely might be.
That makes sense.
What sort of place
do you think it would be?
If it were me,
I think I would post it on one of
the school's corner bulletin boards,
where it would attract as
little attention as possible.
That's where you're wrong.
I'm wrong?
Supposing that it's a recruitment note,
it would be the 1st-floor
entrance bulletin board.
Huh? But that's where it would
stick out the most, isn't it?
Now, now, Chitanda-san,
Hotaro apparently has something in mind.
Whoa, looking at it like this,
Kamiyama High School is incredible.
You're right. An Ink Painting
Club, a Manga Research Club,
Rosy
a Go Club, a Basketball
Club, a Track Club...
You can barely see the
bulletin board itself.
Oreki-san, is something the matter?
No, I'm just being swamped
by the deluge of activity.
It must be an unfathomable world
to our energy-conserving Hotaro.
What's more, this is the first
bulletin board that new students see.
Which means it's a battleground area.
Battleground area? Oh, I get it.
With this many things posted here,
an unauthorized bulletin wouldn't
draw much attention, huh?
That's true, as well.
As well? Is there some another reason?
Well, yeah. Let's just start looking.
Right!
There's the Global Action
Club, the Debate Club,
and even a Hundred Poets Card Game Club.
The Fortunetelling Club!
I have a friend who joined this one.
Oh, yeah?
The Koto Music Club,
the Ping Pong Club, the Art Club...
Hmm... There doesn't seem to be
a note from the Joro Spider Society.
I don't know.
I'm not sure you'd be able to tell
what it is by looking at it.
Huh? What do you mean?!
In order to avoid the
Executive Committee's eyes,
Baseball Club now seeking members
there might be some kind of trick to it.
A trick, you say?
Well, if it is here, we'll find it in time.
Found it.
Huh?
Joro Spider Society filling two vacancies
There it is, all right.
I thought it would be hidden
someplace less crowded.
This is a 1st-year mindset.
They're as unpracticed as they are
trying to be different.
If this secret club had any sense,
they'd be smarter than this.
That's true. Still, it's strange.
Now that you say it, it seems
like it should be so obvious,
and for some reason,
I don't feel surprised.
No approval stamp from
the Executive Committee.
Time to do my job.
Well, I'm going to turn my
essay in to the faculty room,
and then head on home.
Yeah, okay. I think I'll head home, too.
All right. Well then,
I guess this is goodbye.
"As unpracticed as they are
trying to be different."
I'll remember that.
Your "fight mystery with mystery"
plan was a real hit.
Thanks for your help. For some reason,
I had a feeling she was coming.
Mm-hm. So that's why you got
that note and thumbtack ready.
Well, turns out you were
right on the money.
Then again, Hotaro, why did you
set up that elaborate stunt
just to change the subject
off of that piano mystery?
Don't tell me it was because
you weren't up to that one.
The music room was too far away.
That's all?
That's all. I just wanted to go
straight to the entrance,
turn in my essay at the faculty room
next to it, and then leave.
Okay, I get it.
That's you all right, Hotaro.
I am curious!
If I have to do something, I do it quickly.
Hotaro, that won't do.
If you're going to announce your motto,
you should do it proudly,
with your head held high.
It sounded to me just now like you
were simply offering an excuse.
Intercepting a mystery
with another mystery.
Mm-hm, I like it. Nice curveball.
But you know what, Hotaro?
It wasn't your speed.
When Chitanda-san showed up,
why didn't you just say "I don't know"?
That was the fundamental mistake
that you made today.
In fact, that's the way
you've always been, isn't it?
Maybe you're right.
"As unpracticed as you are
trying to be different."
That's exactly the way you were today.
You aren't at all used to
having Chitanda-san around.
That's why you took such
a roundabout detour.
You might have been trying
to foil Chitanda-san today,
but you know...
I wasn't trying to foil her.
Of course not.
That was just you putting the
current state of affairs on hold.
On hold?
That's it. On hold.
By the way, what do you think
the whole music room deal is about?
Oh...
The "ghost" is supposed to have
messed-up hair and bloodshot eyes, right?
Like someone just waking up?
Oh, right.
The Piano Club member was tired,
so she went to sleep.
To make sure she woke up before
the school gates closed at 6:00,
she put "Moonlight Sonata"
in her CD player, and set the timer.
That would have done it.
That makes sense. I'm sure if
you'd gone there, you could tell.
The timer setting on the player
is probably still there.
The music room is too far away.
Yeah, I get it. But you know, Hotaro...
Hmm?
I have a hunch that going to the music room
will end up having been the
energy-conserving route, going forward.
Today's problems might end up
costing you surprisingly dearly.
Uh-oh!
Hotaro! I don't plan to hold
today's events over you! Bye!
On hold, huh?
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
The heat of your budding warmth troubles me
Don't you understand how I feel yet?
There isn't supposed to be
any significance in your glance
I mean, it's the same one
you give all your friends
The tiny wishing star fading
into the morning light
and the magic it works during the night
(I wish you would notice)
Tonight it turns to love
Meet me in a pleasant dream
Make sure that you find me, okay?
Our snooze-time date
Next time, "The Prestigious
Classic Lit Club's Activities."
The Prestigious Classic Lit Club's Activities