oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to have it again and again
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
jounai manjou
The theater's full
nazotoki dokidoki shinan
Mysteries are fun
shikake ga ariari desu
Tricks are fun as well
joshiteki onayami wa sugoroku sai wo futte
We can solve girly problems by throwing dice
(hai hai)
(really?)
ichi de mo roku de mo nain
It's not one nor six, but nine
(sou kai)
(really?)
ichi kake bachi ka de sain
The stakes are high, but you can get a sign
(sou kai)
(really?)
hanashi no tsunagari ga miemasen ne
I don't really see how that's related
oya omoshiroku narisou na yokan wa
See, this looks like it's gonna be fun
(oya oya desu)
(see, see?)
me no sakkaku desu ka
Or am I just seeing things?
iya soredemo kamawanai
I don't even care
hai minna
Come on, everyone
mawatte
Let's spin!
omote mo ura uragaeshite
Front and back, let's just turn it around
dondengaeshi mo yoshiyoshi
You can turn the story upside down too
osaki ni ikou saa douzo
Let's go on, ladies first
osaki mo mae mo yoroshiku ne
I hope to see you around again and again
ura butai ga hare butai de
The backstage is the main stage
muda uchibanashi mo yokayoka
That's where we can chat idly
oato ga mata yoroshikute
Thank you kindly for your attention
osaki mo shiroki gokuraku da
I hope it was a good comedy
gokuraku da gokuraku da
A comedy, a comedy
arayotto gokuraku joudo ringu
A comedy from the comedy heaven
chin-ton chin-ton-shan
Twing-twang twing-twang-twong
A
Happy New Year!
"Teddy, that was so mean of you!
"I was waiting at the cornerstone decoration all this time!"
"What are you talking about? I said I'd be by the corner... stoned."
That was the cornerstone of that age.
Thank you kindly for your attention.
We hope that
you will have
a happy
new year
too.
Doing it over and over again doesn't make it any funnier.
Could you just stop doing that?
Okay.
I'll have your head if you dare do this for Valentine's.
A
The Dreamer
Strikes Back
We wish you a happy new year!
So, girls, what was the first dream
you experienced during the new year?
Don't ask stupi-
Don't be so mean!
That was the first chance I've had in ages to say it...
How was that mean?
I haven't seen mine yet!
I haven't been able to sleep since New Year's Eve,
so I haven't seen my first dream yet!
Huh? Really?
I'm sure you'll all love talking about your first dreams,
but I won't be part of the discussion!
I hope you all had wonderful first dreams!
Was she always so jaundiced?
She's just tired.
Then how about you sleep here?
Come on, close your eyes.
We'll sing you a lullaby!
Sleep, sleep...
I feel like you're cursing me...
Sorry, we'll stop with the lullaby.
How about this? "One sheep, two sheep..."
But that only works in English...
"Sleep" and "sheep" sound similar, so
it's like hypnotizing yourself to sleep.
Then are they saying "sheep one, sheep two"?
Shouldn't it be plural?
What's the plural for "sheep"?
You add an "s" to form the plural of nouns.
The plural of "sheep" is "sheep".
What?!
Sheep are treated as a flock, so it's a collective noun.
Can't a sheep be alone?
You're so loud I can't sleep.
Th-Then we'll keep quiet, whatever happens!
I said I can't sleep...
Isn't it just great that you're all having fun!
S-Sorry!
You've all become dreamers so early in the new year!
You can have all the noisy fun you want!
But all I see is the harsh reality!
After New Year's, that stray cat I always saw stopped coming by.
My father decided to get an antique dealer license,
and hopes to revitalize his company.
My grandmother started putting on more and more makeup.
She goes out often and it's quite
typical for her return in the morning.
Not to mention this Republican western man who claims to have been my mother's acquaintance
keeps inviting us to live in Oregon.
All I see this early in the year is a dreadful, harsh reality!
I wish I could be dreaming instead!
That series of misfortune could fit in some bad cell phone novel.
That reminds me, why aren't there cell phone novels anymore?
It's okay!
Even if you're insomniac, you'll eventually fall asleep!
Really?
Some people say they haven't slept for five days,
but they actually fall asleep for
short periods of time without noticing!
That's true. When I can't sleep, I space out more and more,
and after a while I can't even tell if I've started dreaming...
I wish all that about the cat, my father, my gran, and Oregon was just a dream!
Hey, this is getting stupid.
All of this might be a dream.
Us being in the dressing room and getting an anime adaptation might all be a dream.
Now that you mention it, there was some unrealistically huge new year's decoration breaking in the room...
Right?
No! This is the real world! Not just some fantasy!
If you keep saying stuff like that, it'll just get even more complicat-
I have a good idea.
We should give Kukuru her first dream!
Wait, is this a dream?
Kukuru can't tell the difference
between dreams and reality now.
Let's give her a nice first dream!
This must be a dream!
What a nice opportunity!
We're gonna perform a dream.
This is the dressing room.
A dressing room in the dressing room?
It's like a dream within a dream!
Let's perform a nice first dream, and cheer up Kukuru!
What would be a nice dream?
They say the luckiest things to see in your dreams are one, Mt. Fuji; two, a hawk; and three, an eggplant.
Isn't this lucky?
H-How terrifying!
I've never seen such a scary dream before!
Scary? But it's so lucky!
It has Mt. Fuji, a hawk, and an eggplant.
But...
Seeing Mt. Fuji, a hawk, and an eggplant all at once is too surreal even for a dream!
That's
true.
Curtains closing for a moment!
What now? No one would believe they dreamed about the top three lucky charms at once!
But I've never seen any of those in my first dreams!
I doubt anyone has.
Well, if there are only three lucky charms, then you could go your whole life without ever having a lucky dream.
So what do we do?
Are there more? I'd want to see at least something from the top ten!
Then what's below an eggplant?
It's an eggplant for crying out loud!
Well, if you want something below eggplants...
Time for the second act!
Continuing from the eggplant...
Four, green pepper!
Five, carrot!
Six, broccoli!
Why are we listing the veggies you hate?!
Are you like 10 years old?!
That reminds me they say "four, fan; five, tobacco; six, blind man"...
They do?
The fan spreads out, spreading your luck,
and tobacco smoke rises, lifting your spirits.
And why the blind man?
He's blind, so you won't see any bad luck.
Oh.
What should we do next?
Well, we moved on to plants from animals,
so we should do something below that next.
What are you doing?
Lend me your belt!
Hey!
Continuing from the broccoli...
Seven, chloroplast!
Eight, mitochondrion!
Nine, cell nucleus!
Ten, Golgi bodies!
You'll be lucky...
This is so scary!
I feel like I'm going to be sick!
Then what would be okay?
Well, if we were to go below the cellular level...
11, vanadium!
12, calcium!
13, potassium!
Wow, this sounds nice and healthy.
14, cesium!
15, strontium!
16, plutonium!
Want to see it past 17?
I'll pass...
What are you doing, Marii?
What do you mean?
Don't hesitate! Go through Almond's door!
I don't want to go somewhere this pink!
What are you talking about?
Almond is a staple in Roppongi!
Their mission is planting a pink flower in a gray city!
That's why it's so pink!
R-Really?
I guess.
They were the first to give guests wet towels!
Yeah, it's a jewel of Japanese cuisine,
the birthplace of the wet towel!
Amen.
Just go in already.
Sorry it took us.
The gang's here. Let's go in.
I'd just worked up the courage to go in myself!
A
Gotta
What's this?
It's huge!
Yeah, it's over ten meters.
Is it a spider?
It has a name too.
It does?
It's called Maman.
Maman?
Go right under it.
It has lots of eggs on its belly.
But isn't this where people often meet?
Like the Hachiko statue in Shibuya!
"Let's meet under the Maman holding her eggs!"
That's so hard to say!
This is too creepy! I couldn't wait here!
It feels like her eggs would hatch if I waited here for an hour!
What are you talking about?! This is art!
Couldn't it be something prettier?
This's huge too!
This one's five meters.
A rose... right?
It's the symbol of love and beauty on 66 Plaza.
It's more gaudy than beautiful.
Those thorns look dangerous...
It'd fit in the Little Shop of Horrors!
Feed me!
I'm telling you, it's art!
Couldn't it be some more humane art?
At least it shouldn't be scary...
This is the Counter Void.
Ah, these are just numbers. There's nothing scary about it.
Four for fe4r!
Sicks time too!
It's scary after all!
Didn't 4 stand for fourtune?
The Hills are such a dreadful spot!
It's quite infamous, really.
It felt like horrible things take place every day there.
No, the area has a proper protector.
A mushroom?
Isn't it some fruit?
A big head with a long face!
It's called the Protector Stone.
Protector Stone?
It's the guard that protects the Hills.
I'm not feeling protected at all.
How could this protect the Hills at all?
No, it's thanks to the Protector Stone
that TV Asahi managed to get top audience ratings in all four major airtime blocks!
What does this stone have to do with that?
Finally a place to catch my breath!
Look, medaka!
Those are aliens.
What are you talking about? Those are just medaka!
Yeah, but they're medaka from space!
Huh?
These are descendants of the medaka born on the
Colombia space shuttle in Mukai Chiaki's experiments.
Medaka born in space?!
Yeah, I think those were the first vertebrates born in space.
Yeah. Mouri's astronaut team brought them back to this pond.
So cute!
Look, there are spot-billed ducks too.
Such a heartwarming sight...
But these ducks eat the space medaka.
That's why the number of the fish has plummeted.
The spot-billed ducks eat the space medaka...
But the duck has to raise its chicks too!
Which get eaten by crows in turn.
They live by the law of the jungle...
It's so scary! The Hills are scary after all!
Though metropolitan regulations seem to prey on crows.
So on top of the food chain are laws?!
That's so scary! Laws are scary!
But you know, now that we have the Hills
and Midtown,
it feels like Roppongi's changed completely.
The velfarre used to be here,
but now it's called the nicofarre.
Whoa! Roppongi Hills might turn into Nico Hills one day!
They could open a theater called Nicohirotei here too.
By the way, I heard that velfarre
stood for Versace, Ferrari and Armani.
Ah, the economic bubble...
I wonder what it was like.
I bet you'd have loved it during the bubble if you were in your twenties back then.
Probably! I'd love to live through a bubbly age...
I see. "Take me back to the bubble age!", huh?
Very well.
What's this?!
A time machine!
Hoichoi Productions claims you can go back in time with this!
Put on this swimsuit and jump in!
Who am I, Hirosue Ryouko?!
Have fun, Marii!
Be sure to come back!
Good luck!
Go to the bubble age!
I'm gonna go bald!
Ouch...
Is this really the bubble age?!
They're all having so much fun!
If you're stupid anyway, at least dance-dance!
This is Giroppon for you!
Bring me more Pink Don'!
And if you want me to stay for the night, we've gotta sleep at the Akasaka Prince, you know!
It's like... bubbles...
Stop spacing out, Marii!
Where am I?
We've come to Roppongi, remember?
It's not the Roppongi of back then?
What's this? Some other piece of art?
Yeah. This is a piece of public art called the Day Tripper.
The Day Tripper...
I see... It showed me a dream like froth.
But bubbles burst and vanish quickly.
Boris Vian, who wrote Froth on the Daydream, once said:
"There are only two things that should exist:
love and happiness together with pretty girls
and the music of New Orleans or Duke Ellington.
Everything else ought to go,
because everything else is ugly."
Now how about a pilgrimage to the sacred spots before going home?
It'll be a bit of a walk though.
What pilgrimage?
You know, E**zou!
Oh, that tower!
Let's go drink tequila from ashtrays!
We could become human national treasures too!
That ninja uniform looks quite hot...
A
We're dressing in
accordance with the
Cool Biz initiative
for saving electricity.
And then, you see, I told those Iga ninja!
What did you tell them?
However hot you Iga ninja feel,
you should be throwing shuriken instead of shriekin'!
Thank you kindly for your attention.
A
Blacks
You call this Cool Biz? We look like ninja!
Yeah! In fact, we're already playing ninja in the dressing room!
I'm quite all right.
It's too hot to move around like that!
Stop playing ninja!
Hey.
I said stop it!
Are those the famous metal rings used by female ninja?!
But our true weapon is—
Hey, are you okay?
Our true weapon is our femininity!
D-Damn, I let my guard down...
Wait, no! I said to stop this crap!
But...
It's impossible not to play ninja
when we've gotta dress like this for Cool Biz!
Who'd think we were just rakugo
performers trying to dress light?
If we asked 100 guys at Shinbashi, all 100 would say we were ninja!
A
Cool Biz
Ninja
We may be saving electricity and complying with Cool Biz,
but having to wear this in the dressing room is just weird.
Not to mention, we're professional storytellers.
We can make people shiver with our stories!
Ah!
Ghost stories!
Yeah.
Let's make our guests feel cooler
with stories that chill the blood.
Ghost stories... Hmm...
But can we still scare people with ghost stories?
I'm scared of ghosts!
Of course. Everyone is.
But in this day and age, reality is even scarier.
First, look at this.
It's the sea!
I'd love to go!
What's that?
Yeah! There's a white, man-shaped spot on the picture!
It's a ghost!
Creepy...
Yeah, it'd be scary if it were a ghost.
But look at it closely.
It's just a man wearing white clothes.
Ah...
So it's just a person...
That's even scarier!
I know, right?
A guy in white clothes accidentally being in the photo
is way scarier than a white ghost!
Yeah! Invisible radiation is a lot scarier than a visible ghost!
But ghosts are scary too!
You know that red-roofed house in the third street?
Yeah, the one that nobody would move into.
There's a ghost!
No matter how many exorcists they call,
that earthbound ghost keeps sitting there!
Isn't that scary?
Yeah, earthbound ghosts are scary,
but take a look at this picture.
An earthbound ghost in an old mansion?
Now look more closely.
It looks like a monster from the Cthulhu Mythos...
Look closer.
It's a politician who's been called a loach many times.
What, a politician?
How dare he do all that crap?!
And by the way, that's no mansion. It's the Diet.
Aren't politicians who raise taxes with
reckless abandon scarier than any ghost?
They are! A lot more!
Not to mention that unlike earthbound ghosts, they harm all of Japan at once.
But ghosts are scary too!
Did something happen?
A while ago, I was walking down the corridor to the dressing room,
then suddenly I heard an otherworldly, dreadful rapping!
That isn't scary at all.
What's that?
No matter how dreadful, an otherworldly
rapping you hear somewhere isn't nearly as scary
as the outlandish pop music you hear everywhere all the time!
But that country's pop music is really popular.
Have any of you bought the CD, then?
Not me.
Nope.
Me neither.
I haven't.
That's freaky as hell!
If no one bought it, how can it be "popular"?!
Next, let's go for the visuals!
If we paint the walls blue, we might feel cooler!
Let's test it in the dressing room,
and paint the theater too if it works.
I'll help too!
Me too!
Hey, is it really okay for us to do that?
The eyes of the dragonfly are blue as the sky...
Ah, Mariiemon!
An Osprey!
More like a Blue Man!
The Blue Men are a trio!
We'd get way more people coming to see this!
Maybe.
Yeah, it does feel a bit cooler.
But once you get used to it...
It feels just as hot as it did before.
Let's get more blue things!
First, dye your hair blue!
This isn't an '80s anime...
I'm not Konata!
I'm not Ayanami.
I'm not Lord Aoshi!
I'm not Soldier Blue!
I'm feeling a bit of a generation gap here...
Well, there are remakes and re-airs.
Anyway, let's give it a try!
Having this much blue hair really
cools the atmosphere, doesn't it?
It's a lot more effective than I thought it'd be.
They should stop re-airing Touch during summer break,
and just broadcast shows with blue-haired characters instead!
But...
Once you get used to it, it feels just as hot as it did before.
We should try wearing blue clothes too.
Yeah! Let's wear blue!
This works quite well too.
Right?
Hey, I just had another new idea!
Miura Toshihiro
Born in 1970. Graduate of M University. Famously shrewd producer.
Ghosts!
What's he talking about?
His wife's scarier than any ghost...
But this'll just feel hot again once we get used to it.
Is there anything else? Anything blue?
Ah, there is!
So cool...
Now it really feels like summer.
Your Mongolian spot's so blue, Marii!
I'm the coolest one here, you know!
A
jugemu jugemu gokou no surikire
Live long, live long and prosper
A
kaijari suigyo no suigyou matsu
May great wealth await you wherever you go
A
unrai matsu fuurai matsu
Even in different lands and under different skies
A
kuuneru tokoro ni sumu tokoro
May you always have your daily bread
A
yaburakouji no burakouji
And always be brimming full of life
A
paipo paipo paipo no shuuringan
Like the long-lived king Shuringan
A
shuuringan no guurindai
And his dear wife Gurindai
A
guurindai no ponpokopi no ponpokona no
And their children Ponpokopi and Ponpokona
A
choukyuumei chousuke
Live a long and blessed life
A
choi to jikan itadakimasu
Let me have a bit of your time
goseichou kudasai
Please listen closely
A
totonoimashita
We're ready
A
warau koto to kakemashite
You write it "laughing"
A
omatsuri yarou zo tokemasu
You read it "let's party"
A
sono kokoro wa sono kokoro wa
And the point of it is, the point of it is...
A
dochira mo happi ni naru deshou
That everyone will be happy!
A
oato ga yoroshii you de
Thank you kindly for your attention
waraou waraou sa waraimashou
Laugh, laugh, hey, let's laugh
konna jidai koso waraimashou
Life may be hard, but let's laugh
waraou (soiya soiya)
Laugh (yeah yeah)
naitara make da
If you cry, you lose
yakekuso waraimashou
So just laugh until your sides ache
haranbanjou sui mo amai mo
Life may have its ups and downs,
norikoeta appare nipponjin
But great Japanese can get over it
waraou donna toki de mo
Laugh, whatever time may bring
nanikuso waraimashou
Laugh until you run out of breath
kuuki nante yomazu ni warattoke
Who cares where you are? Just laugh
egao (egao) egao (egao)
Smile (smile), smile (smile)
warau kado ni wa fuku kitaru
Smile and the world will smile back at you
I'm Tetora.
A
Preview
I'm Kukuru.
I'm Gankyou.
I'm Kigurumi.
I'm Marii.
The final, thirteenth performance of Joshiraku
consists of Character Guts,
Mighty Akiba,
and we'll perform Extra Lectures
too.
Wait, why am I stuck with just the "too" again?!
A
Character Guts
Mighty Akiba
Extra Lectures
Thank you kindly for your attention!