kono sora no kagayaki kimi no mune ni todoiteru
The luminance of the sky has reached your heart.
yumemiteta shirabe wa shizukesa no youni
The melody I dreamed of was like silence.
kimi no te ga mada yume ni tookutemo
Even if your hand is still far away in my dreams,
omoidashiteyou yasashii koe wo
I’ll still remember your kind voice
dareka ga kimi no tame utatta shiawase no koto
and the happiness that was sung for you.
sora no woto hibike takaku kanashimi wo koete
Let the sound of the sky ring high over your sadness.
kimi no me ni utsuru mono wa subete hontou no sekai
Everything reflected in your eyes is that of the real world.
namida sae kimi wo koko ni todomete okenai
Even tears won’t be able to stop you here.
furisosogu hikari no naka ashita wo kanadete
Amidst the descending lights, you’ll play the song of tomorrow.
It's a sound that could even wake the dead.
A Day in the Troop
Rio Runs
I'm digging in!
How is it?
It tastes pretty good.
Yup. It's delicious.
I-It's okay...
That's a relief.
This is a local dish from my village.
Is this what they call "miso"?
It's made using the same method as soy sauce?
Yes.
I brought some of Mom's miso here.
There's still a lot of it.
So have as much as you want!
To Treize?
Yes. A message from the supply corps finally arrived.
Kureha-chan and I will go get it.
We're low on ammunition, medicine, and everyday supplies, right?
We'll be fine now.
And you, Noël?
Going to Carl-san's workshop, right?
Yup.
Got it.
Kanata.
I'm going to train you fiercely this afternoon!
Eh? Really?!
Time to eat.
Where are your manners?
If your father saw this, he'd probably cry.
Who cares about him?
Here, have some snacks.
Fortune cookies?
You still don't like them, huh?
The kids at the church didn't do anything wrong.
Using useless superstition to make money. It's the same all over.
But that's not quite true.
The ones here are quite delicious.
Oh?
Great Luck
But it seems like Kana-chan is getting used to this place.
She sure is cute, working hard everyday.
Is she?
I do agree that she's enthusiastic and diligent.
But if one thinks that those qualities alone will suffice, they're too naïve.
What's with that look?
Se~cr~et.
What? How annoying.
Great Misfortune
We'll be leaving now.
It'll probably be late when we return.
Okay. Take care.
Don't give Rio-senpai any trouble!
I won't.
Proceeding with departure.
Have a nice trip!
Although I don't expect you to do it at this level,
using the mouthpiece to control sound is a fundamental skill.
Try it.
Yes, ma'am.
How are you finding life here?
It's great!
It's just like you to say something like that.
I'm a little jealous of that sanguine personality of yours.
Oh right. Why did you want to join the army?
That's because... well...
I heard that you could learn an instrument for free.
But... um... p-protecting the country is also important!
I don't care about that. I won't judge whether it's for money or other reasons.
Those who have a clear goal persevere longer than those who don't.
Um... Thank you.
Then, Rio-senpai, why did you join?
I...
Oh right. I guess it's because of the exact opposite reason.
Nevertheless, these sure are rare nowadays.
Especially brass instruments. You don't hear them outside the army anymore.
A long time ago, I heard one.
Just like yours.
Kanata?
The sound... of... the sky.
What is it? Get ahold of yourself.
Get ahold of yourself, Kanata!
Answer me!
No...
Please, stop moving so much.
It's hot...
It's hot... Mom.
It's hot? I see.
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
M-Mom...
What's wrong, Kanata?
Kanata!
I want to eat... snow.
I got it. Wait a moment!
Snow... Snow... Snow...
Why would we even have that?!
Calm down. Calm down.
Medicine!
No... That's only as a last resort.
Medicine... Medicine...
Found it!
We're low on various things.
Damn those idiots in the supply corps!
Damn it...
What...
...should I do?
Damn it!
U-Um...
Is something wrong?
Did the children do something again?
I sincerely apologize for my past behavior.
So... um...
Please help me.
Drink this.
Just like that.
Although her temperature is still quite high,
she should be fine now.
It's not some severe sickness, right?
I believe it's probably tertian malaria.
Tertian malaria?!
Don't only children get that?
Adults can get it as well if they happen to be severely exhausted.
The new kids that are brought to us often get it too.
They seem fine at first, but then suddenly they have a high fever.
She must have endured it for a while. I'm sure of it.
Th-Then, will Kanata recover?
She won't stay this way...
I think she will be just fine.
Thank goodness.
Thank you...
Uh...
My name is Yumina.
Here. Although these are just medicinal herbs...
Wait a little while, and then have her drink this.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Don't mention it.
To be able to serve this city is our joy and also our duty.
Then, may you be blessed.
Thanks for your aid.
Ow...
I-I'm sorry!
You all right?
Sorry.
I'm just like miso.
The stuff from the morning?
No.
Miso dregs.
When you make miso soup, you strain out the miso.
The beans and such that are left over are the dregs.
The stuff that is extra or useless. Like that.
I've been like that since I was little.
That's why I wanted to try hard this time.
I didn't want to drag everyone down.
But...
You sure are a lot more fragile than you look.
And you're also stubborn and like to be spoiled.
Did I... say... something?
You said a lot.
Oh, right. Senpai?
Wh-What?
The song that you were humming earlier...
Wh-What are you talking about?
This song...
Impressive. You've only heard it once.
Not once.
I heard it a long time ago.
If only I could play that piece as well.
That's why I...
...want to sing a song that seems to resound from the sky.
But it seems that miso is... miso no matter what, eh?
Kanata.
We can't be indebted to the Church.
The Takemikazuchi is a product from a long time ago.
And within this guy sleeps various things.
Various?
Yup.
Ask Noël for specifics later.
All right, this is it.
I'm starting!
This piece!
This is probably what the complete song sounds like.
There are various instruments playing, and their sounds harmonize together.
They become a single unit.
It's just like tank crews.
Commander, gunner, driver, and communications.
Everyone works together; that's how a tank is able to move.
There's nothing unnecessary.
There are no notes that are not needed.
Don't look at me like that. It was something I was told.
The one I admired and respected the most.
If I use her words...
Kanata.
Why do you think senpai and superiors exist?
It's so that their juniors can trouble them.
It's fine if you aren't able to do it now.
Just remember how it felt being frustrated and powerless,
as well as the happiness of someone caring for you.
That way, some day, when you need to protect others...
...you'll definitely be able to.
That's why, cause as much trouble as you want.
I also did that.
Of course, you'll get scolded and punished.
But... if it's difficult, then say so.
Understand?
Understood!
From now on, I'll give you lots and lots of trouble!
That's...
Go easy on me, okay?
Geez, I knew I should have stayed.
Actually getting cared for by Rio-senpai.
That damn Kanata.
What? It was nothing. She was just too tired.
She'll be fine after some sleep.
Takemikazuchi's lights...
Ah. Sorry, I used it for a bit.
Is there something wrong?
You listened to that song, didn't you?
Didn't you say you wouldn't listen to it anymore?
It just happened.
And then?
It's a secret.
Let's remember our love and friendship
aijou yuujou omoikasanete
and play out their importance.
taisetsu wo kanadeyou
We were so happy that we cried.
ureshikute naita
It hurt so much that we laughed.
itakute waratta
But these are all proof that we are alive.
dakedo sonna zenbu ga ikiteru akashi nan desu
Let's move forward one step at a time.
yukkuri aruite yukou
Everybody singing
Let me hear the words of your heart.
hitosashi no honne kikasete
You're just my friend!
Even if our love and friendship sometimes waver,
aijou yuujou toki ni yuretemo
I know, you know, a little happy
let's make it echo forever and ever.
zutto zutto hibiki aitai
Can you hear my precious note?
Words are hardly enough to describe it.
arifureteru kotoba de wa tsutaekirenai
This is our harmony.
watashitachi no harmony
Can you hear it? Our harmony!
kikoeru our harmony
The Rainy Season Sky
The Glass Rainbow
Next time: The Rainy Season Sky · The Glass Rainbow