We came to the ocean
for a summer training camp.
At night, baths,
fireworks, and pillow fights!
A lot of fun things!
Right, Najimi-san?
There's no time!
The sales exhibition is in two days!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Pushing?
Pulling?
Strategy! What to do?
Oh, what a night! (It won't get done.)
It won't stop.
Dream and delusion rampage battle!
The dazzling world.
That's a life encounter.
I can't? But I want to see.
But more and more
heart throbbing, heart throbbing...
...heart throbbing, heart throbbing
is what you get, right?
Why not! Why not! Why not! Why not!
Friendship that'll last a lifetime!
It's not like a hero,
but you feel something.
You, me, who? This, that?
Him, anyone's okay!
Anywhere it is!
If you're with everyone, it's the best!
Chance to get up!
Just decide.
Chance to get dream!
Dojin Work
Trains are good once in a while.
You can tell what
society is interested in.
They're the fresh voices that you
can't hear through number data.
Boys, you want to know the
continuation of that manga right now, right?
The manuscript of
next month's issue is...
...inside this editor's bag
which belongs to me.
It's gone!
Why...
Why isn't the manuscript here?
Don't scratch the car.
I know.
You didn't forget anything?
Nope.
All right, Brother, I'm off!
Inside the car!
I was the one that forgot something!
10th Edition
This is what it's come to.
So, yeah...
With all that, I came
chasing after it all the way here.
Really...
Brother, you work at a publisher?
Hey!
Ah, you didn't know?
I thought you were a male escort...
I mean, your hair is so weird...
Hey, regardless of how
you see it, it's cool, right?
By the way, where are
Najimi and Nido-san?
I got them to walk
and go grocery shopping.
This late with just two girls...
I'm worried...
Najimi-san!
Look! A big fish!
We're not buying that! Put it back!
You'll save money with this rice!
We don't need 10 kg right now!
Then, just the badminton set!
No!
Folk art section
Najimi-san! Souvenirs!
No, listen to me...
Hey, where did you come from?
You really saved us!
It's all right, we were bored anyway.
Are you guys like that?
Buddy-buddy sister type?
Does it seem that way?
What?
Yeah, the t-shirts
are totally the same too.
Damn it!
I was the one that chose them!
Did you come here to swim?
Um...
Right! We came to train.
Training?
Riding the waves or something?
No, um...
It's drawing training!
Ah, like art students?
W-Well, it's different, but...
Drawing male bodies is really hard.
Hey!
Really? You draw stuff like that too?
You want us to be your models?
No, um...
Please!
W-What!
T-This is kind of disgusting...
I-I can't help it! I don't want to either.
Could you bring your face closer?
I want to go home...
L-Like this?
More!
I can't do this anymore!
Don't breathe on me!
Don't move!
No!
What kind of drawing is this anyway?
The beautiful shape of love!
Beautiful?
Shape of love?
More than that...
Let's make the normal
shape of love instead...
What is going to happen to us?
A ghostly flame?
It's coming closer.
Huh?
A ghostly flame in this day and age?
Right?
You're kidding, right?
There's no way...
W-What is it?
It's a person.
Justice.
Justice-san...
I'm sorry my companions
have troubled you.
Who the hell are you?
They are having fun with us!
Having fun...
Really?
Then why don't I...
...get you guys to mix me in too!
I-It's appeared!
By the way, the writer
that you have your eyes on...
...what kind of person was he?
Najimi-san is making
a really good book.
Wait a second!
Najimi-san?
It's a girl. So it was a girl!
Okay!
Okay, continue.
First off, read this.
Ah, it's Najimi's book.
This is good paper...
How is it, Brother!
No, this is horrible...
No it isn't!
Brother, you don't understand the
feelings that were put into this book!
More than the feelings
that were put into it...
...it's just the feelings you
have for the girl that drew this.
You hit the nail on the head.
It's not like that!
Brother, you just don't understand!
Forget it, just leave!
This is me and Sora's room.
Brother, you blockhead!
I'll just leave!
Ah, that's...
...a closet...
But I should try not to follow guys
that I don't know from now on.
Somehow, I finished the
story and the frame work!
I need to thank Justice-san.
So, want to go to bed soon?
Let's do that.
It's like a school trip.
Hey, let's have a pillow fight!
No...
W-What? It's fun though...
Okay!
How is it? Tell me the bad parts!
Everything.
Specifically...
All the drawings.
Please tell me the bad parts!
First of all, as an adult...
What?
I think it's the drawings!
Okay, I'll do my best!
It's done!
It's finally done.
Congratulations!
Well, it's on copy paper,
but somehow it's done.
It's amazing, Najimi-san!
I was moved!
Yeah, seriously!
What? You're still here?
I moved my luggage.
I'm about to leave.
But it was seriously a good harvest.
I think I understood your
meaning a little more.
Ah, my book?
More like, who's he?
We didn't introduce him.
He's Hoshi-kun's older brother.
Really...
Nice to meet you. I'm Najimi Osana.
Ah, yeah, yeah...
She held my hand!
Ah, hello, thank you for taking
care of my brother all the time.
No, he's been taking
care of me more.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Okay, so now both
of them are together.
Brother, what's up?
That girl named Najimi,
she's coming on to me.
What?
Well, I just met her,
and she went to hold my hand.
What am I to do?
If you say that, when I
met her for the first time...
...she intensely hugged me!
W-What...
She definitely likes me more!
What a loose girl...
Najimi-san isn't that kind of person!
I'm going to put mine on this side.
What? Yeah...
Oh, little brother!
Brother!
Hold off...
Nido-san?
Yes?
Nose bleed...
No, this isn't!
It's the sweat of my heart!
Now I'm going to sell away!
Me too!
Huh?
Things like this happen, huh?
I thought it would turn out this way.
But with this, everything
you did went to waste.
Well, but it wasn't all a waste.
It was the first time
I drew that intently.
Right?
Excuse me...
How much is this?
It's 100 yen!
Here.
T-Thank you very much.
There was something
like this for 100 yen?
Really?
Dude, it's bad!
Can I get a copy too?
Yes!
Can I get a copy of that one?
Ah, yes!
Please line up single file.
Can I get you anything to drink?
The emotions are conveyed, huh?
Should I head home now?
No! The manuscript!
A breathtaking manuscript.
Mysterious.
Before one knows...
If you take your first step...
Completely, totally unexpectedly...
...you start liking things
that you don't like.
My true self wakes up?
Mu, fu, fu, maybe it's a charm.
Run through life in one line.
The sky is pink.
Bloomers just fly by.
Area of no experience.
Let's move on!
Happy smiling!
The dreaming maiden is sui sui chao!
Even the steep places breaststroke.
Let tomorrow be
the polka-dot pattern.
So let's do our best!
Here, it's the final leg of the race.
Let Najimi hear your cheering.
11th Edition, Najimi's going to fly.
Let me hear your idiosyncrasies.