You'll make any wish come true, right?
Don't fret. I can grant yours without a doubt.
So, you're ready?
Yeah. Do it.
Now take hold of it.
That is your fate.
kawashita yakusoku wasurenai yo
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made.
me wo toji tashikameru
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll close my eyes and make sure of it.
oshiyoseta yami furiharatte susumu yo
押し寄せた闇　振り払って進むよ
Shaking off the darkness that closed in on me, I continue to move on.
itsu ni nattara nakushita mirai wo
いつになったらなくした未来を
When can I see once more the future that I lost?
watashi koko de mata miru koto dekiru no
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
Again and again, I'll tear apart...
afuredashita fuan no kage wo
溢れ出した不安の影を
...the shadow of distress that spilled out...
nando demo saite kono sekai ayundekou
何度でも裂いて この世界歩んでこう
...and walk on in this world.
tomedonaku kizamareta
とめどなく刻まれた
The time that ticked away...
toki wa ima hajimari tsuge
時は今始まり告げ
...ceaselessly now announces the beginning.
kawaranai omoi wo nose
変わらない思いをのせ
Putting my unchanging feelings into it,
tozasareta tobira akeyou
閉ざされた扉開けよう
I'll open the closed door.
mezameta kokoro wa hashiridashita mirai wo egaku tame
目覚めた心は走りだした未来を描くため
My heart awoke to draw the future where I'd start running.
muzukashii michi de tachidomattemo sora wa
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
Even if I come to a standstill on a difficult road,
kirei na aosa de itsumo mattetekureru dakara kowakunai
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる だから怖くない
the sky is always waiting for me in a beautiful blue, so I'm not scared.
mou nani ga atte mo kujikenai
もう何があっても挫けない
By now, no matter what happens, I won't get broken.
Episode 5     There's no way I regret anything
Excuse me.
That wasn't very ladylike of me.
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Not enough sleep?
Yes. I was at the hospital and had to deal with the police until late.
What? Did something happen?
I guess I was sleepwalking or something...
There were a lot of people with the same symptoms,
and when I came to, they were all lying around me.
Huh? What's up with that?
The doctors said it was called a collective hallucination or something.
I have to have a complete physical after school today, too.
What a bother...
You shouldn't have come to school, then!
No, I couldn't do that! Then it'd be like I was actually sick.
People at home would get even more worried about me.
I guess honour students are like that!
You're pretty tough!
It's been a while since I've felt this great.
I feel wonderful!
Sayaka-chan, aren't you scared?
Hmm? Well, yeah, I am a bit scared.
But I took care of that witch from yesterday pretty easily.
When I think about the fact that I might have lost two of my friends, you and Hitomi,
I find that it's much scarier.
So it's kinda like I have more self-confidence...
I feel more at ease...
It's like I want to congratulate myself for everything so far.
I guess I'm flying high.
Magical Girl Sayaka-chan will do everything she can to protect Mitakihara City!
So you don't regret anything at all?
I guess if I had to pick something,
it'd be the fact that I hesitated to begin with.
If I was going to become a magical girl anyway, I should have decided sooner.
If Mami and I had fought that witch together, she might not have died.
I...
You're thinking of something weird, aren't you?
I... I should have...
I can say all of that because I'm already a magical girl.
The idea is that I became a magical girl anyway, so why shouldn't I have done it sooner?
It's like I was destined to become a magical girl from the start.
Sayaka-chan...
I found my wish.
I had something worth risking my life for this whole time.
I'm just a little frustrated it took me so long to realise that.
That's why you shouldn't feel inferior to me for not becoming a magical girl.
That's all.
Yeah...
Anyway, I have to get going.
Huh? Do you have something to do?
Yeah, just a little something.
I see. So you're not getting released yet.
I still haven't completed the rehabilitation for my legs yet.
I need to be able to walk completely first.
They say they don't know why my hand healed all of a sudden,
so they need to look at it more thoroughly.
How are you feeling, though?
Is there anything strange with your body?
No. There's so much that isn't wrong, it's scary.
It's even starting to make me think being in the accident was all just a bad dream,
like I'm not even sure why I'm in this bed any more.
This is a miracle, just like you said.
What's wrong?
I said a lot of mean things to you.
It doesn't matter how depressed I was. I...
Don't worry yourself thinking about anything weird that happened.
You should be really happy right now!
Don't make that face.
Right.
All of this just doesn't feel real.
Well, that makes sense.
I guess it's about time.
Kyousuke, let's get a breath of fresh air.
Why are we going to the roof?
It'll be fine.
Everybody!
The real celebration will be when you get out of the hospital,
but since your hand healed faster than your legs...
I-Is that...
You told me to get rid of it, but I just couldn't.
I...
Now try it. Don't be afraid.
Mami-san,
my wish came true.
There's no way I regret anything.
I'm the happiest I could possibly be right now!
That's the new magical girl in this town, huh?
Do you really want to start fighting with her?
I mean, it looks too easy.
I'd kill someone like her in an instant.
Or what?
You got a problem with all of this?
It may not be as easy as you think.
There's another magical girl in this city, after all.
What's she like?
I don't know either, really.
Huh?
What's that supposed to mean?
She became a magical girl after forming a contract with you, right?
You could say that, and you also could not.
She's an extremely rare irregularity.
Even I can't predict what move she'll make.
Sounds good to me.
Being bored all day isn't good, after all.
I need to have some excitement.
What did you want to talk about?
Um, about Sayaka-chan...
It's easy for her to believe what she wants to, and she gets really stubborn.
She's quick to fight,
but she's a really nice person!
She's kind and courageous,
and she'll go to any length to help someone.
That's fatal for a magical girl.
Really?
Excessive kindness leads to weakness.
Reckless courage becomes inattention to detail.
And there's no reward for dedication of any kind.
You can't be a magical girl unless you understand that.
That's why Tomoe Mami lost her life.
Stop talking like that!
Sayaka-chan might be saying she's fine,
but when I think of something happening to her like what happened to Mami-san,
I don't know what to do.
You're worried about Miki Sayaka, aren't you?
I can't do anything for her any more,
so I want to ask you.
Could you be friends with Sayaka-chan?
Don't fight her like you did with Mami-san.
It should be much safer if you all fight together to kill the witches, right?
I don't want to lie,
and I don't want to make any promises I can't keep.
So give up on Miki Sayaka.
Why?
She shouldn't have made a contract.
Honestly, it's my fault, as well.
I should have watched her actions properly, not just yours.
Then you...
But now that I've taken responsibility, I must tell you that it's a mistake I cannot do anything about.
It'd be like trying to bring someone back from the grave.
She's become a magical girl already.
There's no hope for salvation.
That contract forces you to give up on everything in exchange for a single desire.
So you've given up, too?
You've given up on yourself and the other girls? On everything?
That's right.
I won't make excuses and say I'll try to atone.
I must continue my fight, no matter what sin I must commit to do so.
It seems I wasted your time.
I'm sorry.
Are you nervous?
Well, yeah.
One mistake and I'll be dead.
Madoka.
Sayaka-chan, are you going to...
That's right. I'm going on patrol to search for bad witches!
It's part of the job when you fight for justice.
Will you be fine by yourself?
I will!
Mami-san did this, too.
I should be able to do this since we learned under her.
I can't do anything,
and I know I'll just get in the way,
but could you take me with you, at least until it would cause a problem?
Aren't you trying too hard?
I'm sorry...
I shouldn't. I know I'd get in your way.
No, I'm really happy.
Hey, can't you tell?
My hands started shaking, and they haven't stopped.
Pathetic, huh?
I'm a magical girl now, but I kinda feel helpless by myself.
Sayaka-chan...
You're not a nuisance. I'm really happy.
I feel a lot better just because someone would stay with me,
like that alone gives me the power of one hundred people.
I...
I'll protect you.
So relax and just follow behind me.
Let's go get those witches together like we always have.
Right!
You know it's dangerous, right?
I'm stupid, so if I'm by myself, I might do something reckless.
If I keep in mind that Madoka is here with me, I think I can be careful.
I see.
Well, it's fine as long as you have a plan.
Kyubey...
You have a plan, too, right, Madoka?
I know how you want to protect Sayaka.
Just by staying with her, you're able to keep an ace up your sleeve if the worst happens.
I...
You don't have to say anything right now.
I'm sure Sayaka will be against it, too.
But if there comes a time when you have to make up your mind, I'll be ready.
Okay...
It's here.
This barrier is probably a familiar's, not a witch's.
The easier the better.
I don't have a lot of experience.
You can't let your guard down.
I know.
Is that...
It's going to get away!
Leave it to me!
Wait a minute. What are you two doing?
It's going to get away!
Can't you tell? That's not a witch; it's a familiar.
It's not going to have a Grief Seed.
If you just leave it be, someone's going to get killed!
You just have to wait until it eats around four or five people and becomes a witch.
That way it'll form a Grief Seed.
Why are you trying to strangle a chicken before it lays eggs?
Are you saying that we should let the witch kill everyone it attacks?
You're thinking about this wrong.
You know about the food chain, right?
I'm sure you learned about it in school.
The witches eat the weak humans,
and we eat those witches.
That's the way stuff works, right?
The stronger you are, the higher up you are.
That's...
You...
I hope I'm wrong here, but you didn't form a contract with him...
...just to make people watch you play out some ridiculous joke,
like pretending to be a superhero and wanting to rescue people, or something else that stupid, right?
And what if I did?!
Could you, like, stop?
It really pisses me off when someone messes with my work just because it seems kinda fun.
Sayaka-chan!
Hmph. Stupid rookie.
Cool your head a bit.
That's weird.
I should have hurt you enough to put you in the hospital for three months.
Sayaka-chan's okay?
That's because she became a magical girl using a wish for healing.
Her ability to heal damage is far greater than anyone else's.
Who'd lose to you?
It's because people like you are around that Mami-san...
You're annoying.
So freaking annoying!
Actually, you shouldn't even be talking to me that way.
I've been doing this far longer than you.
Shut up!
Stop moving around. You freaking slowass.
Sayaka-chan!
Madoka, it's too dangerous to get closer!
If you're so dumb that you don't get it when I try to tell you,
and you don't get it when I beat you down,
I'll just have to kill you!
I won't lose...
I won't lose!
Why...
Why... do two people on the same side have to fight when a witch isn't even here?
It's hopeless.
Neither of them feels like backing down.
Please, Kyubey, make them stop!
This shouldn't be happening!
I can't do anything.
But if you want to stop them by force,
it's not like there aren't any options on the table.
Only another magical girl can come between their fighting.
But you have the capacity to do that, if that's what you really wish.
That's right...
If I form a contract, too...
It's over!
I...
There's no need for that.
itsuka kimi ga hitomi ni tomosu ai no hikari ga
The light of love you lit in your eyes one day...
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
toki o koete
...transcends time,
時を超えて
horobiisogu sekai no yume o
and surely destroy one dream...
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
tashika ni hitotsu kowasu darou
...of this world and hurries to its ruin.
確かに一つ壊すだろう
tamerai o nomihoshite
Swallow down your hesitation.
躊躇いを飲み干して
kimi ga nozomu mono wa nani
What is it that you wish for?
君が望むモノは何？
konna yokubukai akogare no yukue ni
On the path of yearning as greedy as this,
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に
hakanai ashita wa aru no
will there be a good future?
儚い明日はあるの？
kodomo no koro yume ni miteta
Like ancient magic...
子供の頃夢に見てた
inishie no mahou no you ni
...that I dreamed of when I was young,
古の魔法のように
yami sae kudaku chikara de
with the power to slash the darkness,
闇さえ砕く力で
hohoemu kimi ni aitai
I want to meet the smiling you.
微笑む君に会いたい
obieru kono te no naka ni wa
In these frightened hands of mine,
怯えるこの手の中には
taorareta hana no yuuki
I have the courage of hand-picked flowers.
手折られた花の勇気
omoi dake ga tayoru subete
My feelings alone are all that I rely upon,
想いだけが頼る全て
hikari o yobisamasu
a wish that awaken...
光を呼び覚ます
negai
...the light.
願い
Yuupon (nitro+)
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch; she's a magical girl like you!
Episode 6     There's definitely something wrong with this
There's definitely something wrong with this.