I use this hand to kill...
and I use this hand to eat.
Both are the same thing.
That's how I live my life.
That's how it is, right?
Hey.
What a tragedy, Stone-head.
Gant, you son of a bitch!
Why do you show up like this?!
That's quite a look in your eyes, Tony.
What are you talking about, old man Gant?
Don't deny it.
I've known you guys since you were kids.
So I can tell...
that the look in your eyes means you'll cause a bloodshed.
Don't do anything stupid, okay?
I'll always be watching you.
Are we going to do it, Tony?
Yeah. We'll annihilate Inferno.
It's not for revenge.
We'll do it to protect our town.
Gant is watching us, though.
We can't be careless.
I have an idea.
We can have them meet their end and wash our hands of it.
Inferno members fight among themselves and disregard orders.
These fifteen honchos among the organizations on the West Coast...
are those who would gain from joining Inferno.
Richard Harrington.
Carlo Mendoza.
Are these big shots really teaming up in secret?
If we get evidence of that and make it public, they are finished.
Any organization would take care of treacherous members.
Those who spit on the code of honour...
will see hell through their own foolishness.
Amazing...
That's looking like the best way to play the game.
Anton, I'll leave the matter to you.
Keep them under surveillance and find out their true nature.
But... be careful.
Good morning, Miss McCunnen.
I see you're as radiant as usual today.
Why are you here?
I asked him to come.
His opinions based on his unique competence...
are quite profitable to us.
I'd like to have him attend future executive meetings as a regular.
Do you have any objections?
No, sir.
I called this emergency meeting
to notify you of Tony Stone's latest endeavors.
Tony? Is that stonehead still at large?
I have intelligence that he sent spies out.
I got the feeling that annoying flies have been buzzing around me lately...
So they were Tony's instigation, huh?
Apparently the message we sent him had the opposite effect.
It would have been very convenient had they blindly attacked us.
But I didn't expect that he'd try to separate us.
I suppose we should kill him now after all.
But our aim from the start was...
to get the Stone Family's turf without wreaking havoc.
Do you have a plan?
I think that Tony Stone's foolhardy actions...
...are a rare opportunity.
Oh? Interesting.
Let us hear it.
Ein is late...
That's crazy.
Such a bold plan is-
With Phantom it's possible.
Her ability is beyond doubt.
True.
Even though it's on a larger scale, it's not much more brash than her past missions.
It's not impossible.
We'd like your decision, Mr. McGwire.
You know the right timing to present your abilities.
That's too kind of you.
Very well.
If you have such confidence, why don't we give you a chance, Scythe Master.
Good, Ein. Wonderful.
You're the best work piece after all.
My will shall transform this meaningless and chaotic world.
A new order... A new balance... I will create it all.
The audience of this display is god himself, watching from the gallery of heaven!
You have the lead role...
Ein.
My adorable prima donna.
Did the meeting drag on?
These are our orders for the next operation.
Read them later.
This time, it's a series of missions.
Our targets are...
twelve people.
Twelve?
In one night?
Each of our tasks aren't that hard.
We have to plan our timing carefully and focus on perfect cooperation.
These are all executive members of Inferno's rivals.
If we succeed, it will change the power balance on the entire West Coast.
Is that okay?
Isn't it a bit hasty?
That's not for you to worry about.
Isn't it normal to consider the long-term goal of our missions?
Who told you that?
You shouldn't think on it too much.
It's not appropriate for our way of existence.
What is our way of existence?
As a tool, or as mere equipment...
We only have to perform our function.
Don't think about unimportant matters.
How can you say it so harshly?
Is thinking bad for us?
We'd be finished...
Both me...
and you.
I see all preparations are taken care of.
Don't give me that coy smile, you snake.
Your plan isn't even an operation.
It's acrobatics.
It's the same as walking a tightrope or jumping through a flaming hoop.
It's laid out like this because I have confidence in you people and your abilities.
Why are you allowed to do whatever you want on this one anyway?
Where's Clau?
She said she couldn't come because she had to take care of something else.
What a bother.
On Clau's orders I would cross any bridge, no matter how dangerous.
But I ain't gonna risk my life for you.
We will have more of these kinds of operations.
You may have to reconsider your plans for the future,
Ms. Garland.
Lizzie. It's time.
Don't get absent-minded! We're leaving!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Well then, excuse me.
Phase one complete.
Roger.
Starting phase two.
To the back! He escaped to the back!
Search over there!
I got him! This way.
Who is he?
I've seen him somewhere.
Wasn't he working as a bouncer for Tony?
Stone Family?!
Why did they come to kill the old man?
Those bastards!
Carlo isn't doing anything unusual tonight.
He's dining at one of his usual restaurants right now.
What a conceited bastard.
Yes... Correct.
Well then, until the next routine call.
What's going on?!
Regarding Ahlen Construction's bid,
rumor has it that local mafia was involved.
Therefore it's likely this is a gang war.
I see.
Ah, yes.
We have just received information that
there was a gunfight and subsequent car accident on the Pacific Coast Highway.
We have a live feed from the scene.
They're overreacting.
The night has only started.
Are you saying that this commotion isn't it?
Tonight's bloodshed is only the beginning.
From now on, it will truly be an era in which only the fittest survive.
A world where you can realize any dream if you have power.
That world...
Mr. Godo,
does it fascinate you?
Anton, what the hell is going on?!
Abel, Bark... No one's reporting...
Even though things have become this bad!
They'd all be dead by now.
Like a bullet, they left their mark.
I'm sure they're satisfied.
Wh-What do you mean?
Did Bark and the others do all that?
Did they kill Don Ronny and Hugo?!
That's what everyone will think...
since no one will go interview them in their graves.
Anton... Why...?
Don't you know? You probably don't...
since you're such a stone-head.
Well done, kid.
Yeah.
I can kiss this filthy town goodbye now.
It took me twenty-five years to get out of this dump.
I'm sick of it.
You're calling it quits so early?
I got enough money from Inferno.
I'll buy a cottage or something on a Caribbean beach.
What's your cut?
My first promotion in fifteen years.
I'm the man of merit who put an end to the mafia war, after all.
Looks like we will both live a long life.
An era came to an end yesterday.
The six crime lords who had long been in control of the underworld on the West Coast...
have died.
Tony Stone was thought to have pulled the strings...
but was brought to justice by the law.
All the now leaderless organizations,
will be lead into the new era by our brotherhood...
...Inferno.
Splendid.
Another miracle brought about by your Phantom.
Thank you very much.
Regarding the mafia war that shook the entire city,
Lieutenant Cyrus Gant who was instrumental in resolving the case has received a decoration from the mayor.
Tony Stone, a renowned gang leader and the boss of Melanie Square,
Will people accept the news like that, I wonder.
simultaneously attacked six West-Coast-based criminal organizations and succeeded in full.
No one cares about the truth.
His ambitions were thwarted by Lieutenant Gant's heroic conduct, however.
The spotlight won't last long.
Who will pray for the people who died that day, I wonder.
Who will atone for the sin...
Neither prayer nor atonement matters.
Death is the end of everything.
No matter what you do now...
there's no point.
There's nothing...
Dreams are just a mirage.
They will only become a hindrance for reality.