Street Number 3
Cat Boy
Eyes.
Eyes turn.
Eye colors change.
Eyes look.
Eyes focus.
While being a passive sensory organ that acquires visual information,
eyes sometimes give away someone's will
or feelings in their own language.
It can also be an active organ.
The eyes can say as much as the mouth can.
This much is true.
Eyes accurately reveal one's true nature.
That man has definitely been here before.
Yeah. He's our homeroom teacher.
I wonder what he's here for today.
Did Hotori do something again?
Um, teacher,
can I ask something?
What is it, Arashiyama?
Going out of your way to come meet me like this after school...
You've fallen for me, haven't ya?
Wha?
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
七色の黄昏おりてきて
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
風はなんだか涼しげ
The wind is kinda refreshing
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Saturday night is lively
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
Minna ukiuki
みんなウキウキ
Everyone can't wait
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait.
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
Let's go downtown
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
Ukiuki
ウキウキ
Can't wait!
http://FurukawaPan.net
#FurukawaPan@irc.rizon.net
Encoder: Xarda
Edit + QC:
Liasion
lalala
Xarda
Translation: crazybob
Timing: SiegN
sportsrmyname
[Eye]  From Volume 1 Story 4
"Wha?"
"Wha?" is too direct!
My dream is dying.
Checking vitals... no heartbeat... no respiration... no blood pressure... all zero!
Is that right, teacher? You're single?
She did it right in front of you too... what a shame!
So you make your own boxed lunch.
How sad.
It's all the same once you put it in your stomach.
Hey, shoo. Don't take my customer like that.
What are you saying?
The customer is everyone's customer.
Arashiyama!
I called dibs first!
Toilet paper!
You didn't have a chance anyway.
Well then,
what did you come here for?
I'll have to say no if it's about a boring extracurricular class.
After sorting out the things my grandfather left behind,
I found a mysterious thing.
Was my approach too direct?
Hm?
It was this thing.
A painting?
So it's a painting.
It's just an ordinary looking portrait.
What's mysterious about this?
Huh.
That's a pretty weird painting.
Wha?
Why did you say that? Everyone else said it looks normal.
This smartass is just trying to get his attention by saying what he wants to hear.
No I'm not! I mean, you're only 20% right...
Oh really?
Just look!
This canvas is square!
Aren't paintings normally taller or wider?
Certainly.
Now that you mention it...
I see.
This painting does have an aspect ratio of 1:1.
In other words, a perfect square. Good job, Arashiyama.
I knew you would be able to spot unusual things, so I brought this painting here.
Your existence is something special to me!
I-I'm not that special... and I'm still a high school student...
You're conveniently misinterpreting things again.
My grandfather created this painting.
He was the youngest of three in his family and wasn't able to sell any paintings during his life.
As a gambler,
my grandfather didn't leave much of an estate,
but he did leave many of his paintings.
As a memento after his death, his family and his brother's family
were to each receive a third of the paintings.
Now,
the real problem is with this second painting...
What's that?!
Four eyes?!
Disgusting!
According to the label on the back
these are my grandfather's paintings
and the names of both paintings are the same - "Eye".
Eye?!
Why would my grandfather make such a strange painting?
It's been bothering me ever since
I discovered this painting.
I can't stop feeling perplexed!
As you know, I'm a math teacher.
My job is to think things through logically.
What was the painter thinking when he made this painting?
Augh!
Nonsense!
How can I stand not knowing
even when the artist is dead?!
He's lost it!
However,
through correct conjectures,
we should be able to hypothesize what the answer should be.
You like mystery novels, right?
Yup! I love them!
I'd like you to find out why that
painting was made.
Me?
By all means,
please find me the answer.
I'll come again tomorrow.
He's such a troubled man.
Or rather, it's because of that personality
that he isn't married. But you got an eye on him, right Hotori?
Stop talking about the teacher and let me think.
Oh? You're still thinking?
I already figured it out.
I've also unraveled the mystery.
Grandma too?
Shall I tell you my theory?
Do you know the creator of that painting?
And this is?
It's from the post impressionist painter
Vincent van Gogh.
To Gogh, this unusual coloring
is how he perceived reality. Or so it's been said.
And just like Gogh, if you take this painting as
how the old man viewed reality, it all makes sense.
My theory: The teacher's grandfather was astigmatic.
Oh? That's quite the deduction!
But then, why did he only draw one mouth and one nose?
Head maid, this girl is getting on my nerves!
I mean
there's also the painting that's normal.
Adding or removing eyes is just weird.
How naive, Hotori.
What if you thought about it as normal?
Your teacher said that his grandfather left a ton of paintings
and that he thought that this painting was strange.
That means the other paintings weren't strange.
Amongst the paintings of things like scenery and still life...
there was only one strange painting.
Yeah, sounds about right.
In other words,
this man always painted everyday things.
If that's true,
why does this painting have to be special?
If you think of this painting as just another ordinary painting it all makes sense!
My theory: The teacher's grandfather was an extraterrestrial with four eyes!
When this painting was drawn, the upper set of eyes were closed!
Oh? That's incredible.
Breaking news, huh?
What an annoying brat! Really.
Head maid, what are we going to do about her?
Hm?
Wait. If we assume the opposite and think of this as an ordinary painting...
I see!
Hahaha
Waahahaha
Waaaahahahahahahaha
What is it?
Are you ok?
Did you think too hard and break your head?
When a detective laughs like that
obviously it means that the mystery's solved!
Well then, let's hear your answer.
Alright teach. There are six cards.
How would you split them amongst three people?
Are you making fun of me?
Obviously, each person gets two cards!
You got it!
Ok then how would you split a sponge cake amongst three people?
Only thing to do is to cut it into thirds.
Correct! Oh no! I don't have a piece!
So what does it matter?!
That was a hint.
I hate sluggish explanations in mystery novels and Clippy in MS Office!
Stop giving me hints and just give me a straight answer!
Those were the only hints.
You can unravel the mystery if you use these hints.
Think about it, teach.
Could it be that you still don't get it?
Why don't you get it?
There's nothing to do than to
use the formula and solve it!
Why don't you get it?!
So this is what it feels like!
Wahahaha!
Feels good!
Teach is always feeling like this when he looks down on me.
Arashiyama... Arashiyama...
You'd better tell him what it is or Mr. Moriaki won't last much longer.
How could there be something that Arashiyama understands that I don't?
This... this can't
This is what I was thinking.
C'mon, look -
What... is that?
This is the true form of the artwork.
It's a dice.
I put in the missing sides.
The title "eye" isn't about his own eyes, but about the pips of the dice.
Note: Eyes also refer to the pips on dice in Japanese.
There are paintings with one eye all the way to six eyes. The six paintings make up this artwork.
Your grandpa was a gambler, so he made a fitting self portrait.
But, in order to split the cube into three parts,
the work had to lose its meaning. The pieces you received
were just two pieces of the whole.
This is the truth.
Is my client satisfied?
Arashiyama is showing signs of intelligence!
It's a miracle!
No matter how much vinegar you drink, it won't make your body more flexible, poko~
The eyes can say as much as the mouth can.
Eyes normally tell the truth, but
whether those words can be understood is uncertain.
It depends on whether the viewer's eyes can spot the truth.
I asked my relatives and it was as you said.
I found the remaining four paintings.
The artwork has been restored to its original form which
I'm now giving to you as thanks.
Get it out!
What are we gonna do if you make this place any worse?!
You're gonna scare the customers if you put that there!
Stop it! It's a gift from Mr. Moriaki!
Then why don't you decorate your own room with it?!
Ahh... that's a bit too much.
"Poko" means "a little" in Italian, poko~
[Cat Boy] From Volume 1 Story 11
Onions.
Amongst the constituents of an onion, the alkyl compounds oxidize the hemoglobin in blood,
and cause hemolytic anemia when consumed by non-humans.
It may be deadly for animals, but onions improve blood circulation in humans.
However there is still insufficient medical data to say whether onions have an effect on our well-being.
When an onion is cut, the alkyl sulfide vaporizes, stings the eyes, and causes tearing.
If the onion is chilled before cutting,
the vaporization of alkyl sulfide is suppressed and less tearing should occur.
It's common sense to housewives.
You're not going to ask why I'm crying?
Onions.
Oh.
Mr. Carrot Onions, yes!
Mr. Carrot Onions...
I'm not a kid anymore. I can go shopping properly at least.
But you can't.
Your permanent record says you've screwed up before.
Here. It's Onirot Man.
If you forget what you're doing along the way
this will help jog your memories.
I'm gettin' really pissed!
Can't believe they're taking me for such a fool.
Carrots and onions! Who'd screw that up?
Wha?
Onirot man, meaning.. uh...
So it's a combination of a round part and a narrow part.
Was the round part a potato?
Huh? What was it... Jeez.
Having this reminder is making even more confused.
Coban!
Coban! Coban!
Coban! Coban Coban!
No good.
Wow. A pretty boy.
Eye. Cross-eyed. Teary eyed. Prejudiced eyes. Misfortune comes in pairs.
Eyes reflect a person's heart.
On top of that, when eyes meet, hearts understand each other.
What are you looking at?
Your ass, of course.
Judging from his attempt to hide his voice changing,
he's a 12-13 year old kid.
At that age, the blonde hair is a sign of rebellion...
Oh, you're Hotori, aren't ya?
I saw you hit the policeman with a kickball the other day.
"You?" Shouldn't you be calling me Ms. Hotori or Onee-chan?
This street is hard on kids who don't follow the rules.
What are you doing anyway?
You're so suspicious. What kind of ritual is this?
Take a look.
Oh, a cat.
Cat eyes.
It's an expression to describe something whimsical.
The dilation and contraction of the pupils
that changes moment to moment is the basis for the expression.
But one can also argue that this expression is used because cats are simply spontaneous.
Due to the whimsical nature of cats rubbing off on their owners,
cat eyes also have another meaning associated with people who have magic powers.
My cat isn't coming out of there.
Oh so Coban is the cat's name.
Yeah.
Why did you name it Coban...
Oh.. giving Koban to cats?
Note: Koban is a gold coin. This is the Japanese equivalent of "cast pearls before swine".
You're so smart!
Thank you.
Oh yeah. I have a onirot.
You mean onion.
Want it?
No, I don't want it!
I don't mean you. I mean for the cat, to get it out.
Seriously, I'm saying that cats don't eat onions.
Or rather, they shouldn't eat onions.
Oh I see.
Was it that if a cat eats an onion, it'll get sick?
Note: Ika (squid) and Ikan (no good) sound the same.
You mean squid.
That's no good.
That's... no good...
It's cold! Go home! It's snowing!
Sorry! I don't know why I'm here saying these things.
Coban!
She won't tell weird jokes anymore so come out!
It's my fault?
Cats don't do too well in the cold so stop scaring Coban!
Coban!
It's alright. It'll come out of there.
Cats are spontaneous animals.
But Coban is a good kitty.
Owners always say that.
It's gonna be annoying if I let Coban catch a cold.
You're kinder than you look.
Wh-What?
Hey! What are you doing?!
Yo-You freaking punched me!
Because you were strangling me! Why did you do it?!
Ahh, well, I was wondering if it'd come out if its owner were in trouble.
It isn't a dog!
If I had a dog at home.
It'd come running if I were in trouble.
Probably.
I'm... telling... you... it's not a dog!
Oh brother. I'll have to put my back into this one and make a plan.
Alright, enough. Just go somewhere...
He's out!
See? An onion was the right answer!
Hotori! Catch it!
Alright! Leave it to your big sis!
Got ya!
I call this the "Maid Cage".
"Maid Cage" sounds like some sort of name for a porno.
Cheeky kid.
You got me so worried there.
Isn't this great, Coban?
Grea... huh?
No way! Did I step on the cat?!
Did anything tail-like fall around here?
Are you looking for a tail?
No, I mean, not mine...
Well, it could be mine... there was an accident...
but it definitely wasn't on purpose!
This cat never had a tail to begin with.
Cymrics are a breed without tails.
It's been said that long long ago, when this cat ancestor boarded Noah's Ark,
the door closed on the cat's tail and cut it off.
Really. I'd think that would piss off PETA.
It's a romantic legend, isn't it?
But don't you think it's weird?
Coban's ancestors were different cats.
Even if a father gets injured, the child doesn't inherit his injury.
Whatever. Stop quibbling over the details.
Well, I guess I should say thanks!
See ya.
You guess?
You just keep being a smart ass.
Oh yeah, what's your name?
Huh?
Well, Cat Boy then.
Maybe I should've taught her the "don't loiter on your way" song.
And maybe I should've given her a map instead.
Ho... to... ri!
Oh, yesterday's
Cat... Girl?!
Sorry! I thought you were a younger boy.
I guess some of what I said didn't make much sense, huh.
So you go to my school...
I knew that.
What class?
Class A.
Hold on, I'm in class A too but...
was she in the class? She isn't...
I mean, at the very least I remember the faces of my classmates!
Crap... I always thought I'd meet a ghost one day
but I didn't think she'd be a ghost.
Now that I think about it, she suddenly disappeared yesterday.
If I look away she might just disappear...
wait, she has appeared at school too... she's got me completely...
Kon-Senpai, sup!
Senpai?
Hey Haribara, we're having a tournament at the club today, right?
I just replaced the rubber on my paddle, so the death god is going to have your head today.
Say that after you win.
So you're an upperclassman, senpai.
You just looked so young, you know...
So sorry for all the misunderstandings...
Hey hey, don't worry about it, onee-chan.
Can you cut me a break?
Rap isn't just hip hop, poko~
Maids.
Today in Japan, maids wear the outfits of English homemakers...
and appear in maid cafés, maid bars maid reflexology centers, and maid mahjong parlors.
The maid industry has gone beyond household service and back.
This power which knows no limits has arrived.
And now, we have two maids locked in battle.
How did you defeat me?
Would you like to know? Fine. I'll tell you before you die...
Hi,
1,
ひ、
Fu,
2,
ふ、
Hi, fu, mi, yo
1, 2, 3, 4
ひ、ふ、み、よ
Taikutsu ya
Living alone is boring,
退屈や
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
My pufferfish cheeks
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
Pulls the town into chaos.
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
I didn't confess to him today.
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
I play the drums to train
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
My body for ping pong.
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
But this band isn't a fake!
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
The members aren't playing rock!
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
We're not trying to lead the song!
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
We're not looking for Nirvana!
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
We're maids! Yea!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
メイド姿で参上！参上！
acho-!
アチョー！
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
They're maids! Yea!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
acha~
アチャ～
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
kanchoooO!
enemaaA!
かんちょぉぉお！
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
There's a contagious curse that curses one person after another
What the heck? That's scary.
After a minute, the curse curses another person.
What an unusually contagious curse.
If we start with one cursed student every student in school will be cursed in 10 minutes.
Given that, if you start with two cursed students...
how long will it take for every student to be cursed?
It's twice as many, so...
half the time. 5 minutes.
Wrong.
Street 4  [The Curse Equation]
Next time: Street number 4: "The Curse Equation"
We were all over the place yesterday, poko~