kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
while at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
We may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings run deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
If things stay like this
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
Nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
Won’t you kiss me? It’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
Can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
With our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
“In every respect, the small things in life are particularly beautiful.”
It’s so cold.
Hey…
Isn’t it way too cold today?
Haruka, didn’t you check the forecast?
It’s snowing?!
A Snow Day, Memories, and a Big Shock
It doesn’t usually snow around here, right?!
This is so rare! Think it’ll pile up?
Nah, I’m sure it’ll stop soon enough.
I wonder if Yuu’s still sleeping...
Yuu, it’s snowing out there!
She’s awake! That’s pretty rare too!
I take that back… she was just about to give in.
Misato West High School
Yuu, it’s lunch time!
And it’s actually snowing today!
Take a look!
poke
C’mon, you can sleep later. Look out there.
She’s sucking on it?!
What’re you being so loud for?
You’re such a child sometimes, Haruka.
Yuu, it’s snowing pretty hard out there.
Why would I be excited for snow?
She’s acting pretty mature for a change.
Now we can’t have gym outside!
I should’ve known…
I really like it though.
Same here!
It’s almost magical, huh?
Got that right! You’ve got good taste, Shizuku!
I have an idea!
Let’s take this chance to have lunch outside and enjoy it!
Are you in your right mind, Harupoppo?
Try playing it out in your head.
I-I’m in!
Shizuku!
See? What about the rest of you?
No way! It’s freezing out there.
No thanks!
So that leaves…
glance
Kaede, please pick a side!
The student council’s having a passing-the-torch meeting of sorts, so I’ll pass.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Aw man…
Three against two… seems like the indoors side won.
See?
Then we’ll just go alone, right Shizuku?
S-Sure.
They’re really  set on this, huh?
Whoa… no switching sides, now.
It’s pretty cold, but you gotta love the snow!
Are you okay?
It isn’t worth catching a cold over.
I’m just fine!
I’ve got a hand warmer.
Let’s see if it helps.
It’s so warm…
I-I’m too cold to eat…
R-Right?
Haruka… I’m starting to think we should quit while we’re ahead…
You have a p-point…
Let’s get inside.
But...
Misato West High School
We might not get to see this next year, or the year after…
If we never get to see this view again, I’d like to etch it into my mind.
I think we really ought to head inside!
You get kinda like Kotone sometimes.
Like just now?
It’s like she's made a promise to herself.
She said… “Three years’ll fly right by, so I want to make them count.”
She said something similar to me as well.
“If you let this chance go, Yuu might never have her cheer squad.”
I see…
I think I’m starting to get why she’s so hung up on that thought now.
That’s right… Kotone’s already betrothed…
Not too long from now, she’ll hardly get to see Shizuku…
so that’s why she asked to live with her even if her parents were opposed…
Wait right here.
There she goes...
Her living with me won’t last long…
Once we graduate, we’ll walk separate paths…
I… I don’t want this to end so soon…
I want to see her even after we graduate…
I want to be with her always…
C’mon Shizuku… let’s play.
Let’s make some memories.
So then we can look back on them and laugh when we’re adults.
It’s bone-chilling out here!
I told you I didn’t wanna come!
You’ll get used to it!
Are you five or what?
Last time I checked, we’re in high school alread—
Yay! The dunce walked right into it!
Yuu!
angry
You took it a bit too far, Yuzu!
She’s  the one who called me a dunce!
I hit you two dead-on!
Yuu… c’mon.
No!
You got my scrunchie all soaked!
Didn’t think she’d  make such a fuss…
I don’t even feel a thing.
Well then… let the battle begin!
Here it comes!
Yuu!
That was uncalled for, Kotone!
Looks like Yuu was the dunce after al—
Now you’ve done it!
Think fast, Yuzu!
It’s actually super fun when we’re all playing together!
I know, right?
Not quite everyone  is here…
Student Council Room
That is all.
The matter of student council inheritance is dealt with.
Next year, there will only be two grades, so be prepared for that.
Sumi, we’ll be counting on you, okay?
Not to worry!
Cast aside your doubts and trust in me!
Big Sis
Well now, thank you for everything this past year.
Thank you too.
President Mitsuki!
Oh, Kaede. Thanks for everything.
I guess it wouldn’t be President  Mitsuki now, huh?
Former  President Mitsuki!
Just stick with what you're used to...
Um… I’ve been thinking about this for a while…
I wanna see if you get the same feeling.
I know it’s kind of a touchy subject, but…
I won’t be phased if you told me.
I’m sure Yuzu would be shocked, but…
I’m of the same idea… I think.
What exactly are you getting at here?
Aren't Haruka and Yuu dating?
A Snow Day, Memories, and a Big Shock
End
Misato West High School
Huh? No way, get that outta here.
I wonder what we’ll do for gym today.
No idea.
I think the teacher mentioned skipping rope or something.
What?! I wanna play volleyball!
Yuu, aren’t you cold in just shorts?
I’m fine!
They do  say kids are one with nature.
I am not  a kid!
One with nature…
Let’s get going, Kaede!
Sorry, I was just spacing out.
Kaede, your skirt!
Man, I was almost about to wrinkle my skirt.
C’mon, we’ll be late for gym.
Huh
Did you seriously forget to take ‘em off?
Yeah.
We’re talking about you  here…
so I thought you’d done that on purpose,
and were just waiting for someone to make a jab at you.
We’ll go with that, then.
What You’d Expect in a Gym Equipment Room
What’s with you lately?
You’ve been a little off all day.
Some stuff’s been on my mind.
Is  Kaede acting weird? I can’t really tell.
She’s pretty much the same as always, huh?
Did you notice anything, Kotone?
You’ve known her since middle school, right?
I’ve already got my hands full with you, though.
W-What’s that  supposed to mean?!
Oh my, oh my.
You’re such a cutie, Shizuku!
I know, right?
Help me, Yuu!
Oh Shizuku.
It’s really hard to tell if she’s actually acting strange.
She’s got such a pokerface.
Maybe she’s got some worries…
She’s always  strange!
Who walks around town with a mouse toy?
I bet all she worries over is who she’ll prank next time.
There’s no use in paying it any attention.
plop
Oh, my bad.
I carelessly tossed you my spider.
And here I was worrying for you!
I’m fairly sure that was just Shizuku.
Where’d you even buy this?!
I wouldn’t even get one if you paid me!
But think, Haruka… it’s a plush toy.
Put that down, Yuu!
C’mon, get it out of you.
You’re gonna have her throw up…?
Peek.
I’ll make sure to curse the rope she skips with…
Cut her some slack, Haruka.
But that’s exactly what she preys on!
This is why you’ll always remain an SBJK.
How am I jealous of her?!
Super Unforgiving High Schooler.
Super
Unforgiving
High
Schooler
There's a difference.
Super
Unforgiving
High
Schooler
I’ve got another label now!
Sakura Trick
Are we all set with the skipping ropes?
Yes.
Today you’ll split into groups and compete to do the most skips.
If you mess up, it’s back to zero.
So good luck, everyone!
This sucks.
I just know I’ll fail.
No way I’m gonna lose to you, Kaede!
Grrr
Okay, get ready… and go!
Here we go!
One…
C’mon, Haruka!
Four… five…
Here we go again.
One…
I’m sorry…
Let’s try it again.
One…
Ouch!
Don’t sweat it.
One…
Haruka!
Are you even jumping, Haruka?!
I really am!
Looks like you’ve attained another SBJK skill!
But this isn’t jealousy or  unforgivingness!
Unbelievably
Unbelievably Clumsy High Schooler…
Clumsy
High
Schooler
Unbelievably
Clumsy
High
Schooler
is what I meant.
What’s gotten you like this?!
I have no excuses…
Harupoppo, you’re jumping right when we swing the rope,
but you should wait until the rope’s close to the ground.
Just pick yourself up and try again!
Okay.
Okay, we got it this time.
One…
I did it!
I jumped!
Sorry… it was me this time.
I’ll let this one slide, Shizuku.
Oh Yuu!
998…
999…
1,000!
Alright, pack it in.
You guys were astounding.
And so…
Defeated
The last place group will tidy up.
Hmph
You just had  to hold us back!
I know, I’m sorry.
I’ll tidy the ropes up alone, so forgive me, please.
You’re the best, Harupoppo!
Sure you don’t want some help?
No, I’m fine.
It’s just packing away some skipping ropes.
No worries.
I didn’t think there’d be this  many…
M-Maybe I could use—
empty
S-So they already left, huh?
Yuu… what’s up?
Don’t mind me!
Let’s wait up for Haruka then.
She’s got a huge grin…
So easy to read.
They finished already?
That sure was fast.
There we go…
Great! That’s the last of ‘em.
bang
I’ve been locked in!
Hey! Come back!
I’m still in here!
Open this door, someone!
My phone!
…I left it with my uniform…
Yuu… I’ve been trapped in here…
I've been through this before, come to think of it.
Like when we sneaked into that empty classroom.
Though I wasn’t scared, being with Yuu.
Oh, Yuu!
She’s sure taking her time…
I feel like we should’ve helped her instead.
What’re you still doing here?
I was wondering why you weren’t in class yet.
Yuzu, Kaede… you see—
You guys sure tidied up fast.
I’m impressed.
Our teacher…?
We haven’t seen Haruka yet!
I hope she didn’t get locked inside the equipment room...
W-Wait up, Teach!
I’ll try to see if I can get a look from outside!
Can you guys try from the inside?
Okay.
I see she’s worried sick for her after all.
Her?
Wait a sec… who would be the girlfriend in this case…?
Hey, Haruka! You in there?!
Maybe she’s not even in there after all.
Perhaps she just took a different path.
Haruka!
Her hand!
So she’ll respond to Yuu’s  voice…
She actually does seem pretty trapped, huh?
I hope she’s alright in there…
What if she’s pinned under something…?
If she can manage that, I’m sure she’s fine.
That’s very true.
But I can’t help but worry!
Why don’t we get a peek inside?
Yuzu… thanks for the help!
You’d better not be trying to get on my shoulders...
I’ve got a ladder right here.
Thanks so much, Kaede!
Haruka!
Yuu!
You okay?
Oh Yuu… I can’t get out of here…
grab
Thanks for coming.
Haruka! I’m gonna fall!
Before you got here, all I could think about was you.
I’m kinda in the mood now…
Hold on…
Yuzu and Kaede are right down there.
That’s right… I should control myself…
Maybe just for a sec…
They won’t know, right?
Don’t worry about it.
It looks like Yuu’s… trying to pull  her out…
No way that’ll happen.
Hey, watch out there!
Yuu!
Haruka!
Yuu?
I wasn’t sure what would happen to me…
You’re such a klutz.
Man, you really caused a commotion.
Sorry we had you do it all.
Sure you’re okay?
I’m fine, don’t worry.
It really does seem like they’re dating…
Despite what Mitsuki thinks…
What do you mean they’re dating?!
Um…
Do Mikan and the others know of this?!
She’s gotta be doing it on purpose by now…
Uh, no. It’s not like I asked them directly.
It was just me speculating.
Oh, I see now.
We still don’t know if that’s the case or not.
I mean, they’re both girls… take that into account.
You do have a point.
The only thing is Haruka’s a bit too clingy with her…
right
Big Sis
She’s just such a hard worker, and can’t help but give Yuu her support.
Thinking back, Mitsuki couldn’t stop talking about Haruka…
What You’d Expect in a Gym Equipment Room
End
Keep Smiling, Rina
Hey Rina!
Good morning to you!
Excuse me, Rina!
Is now a good time?
Thanks so much for that.
And now we have an announcement from Vice President Sakai Rina.
We thank you so kindly for that!
Hey, Kaede! What the hell’s going on?!
I mean, all Rina did was smile—
Yuzu!
Just… let it be.
But, Kaede…
Oh, um… I didn’t say anything.
Extra
Keep Smiling, Rina
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
Won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
The time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we keep
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
If we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
and split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
Memories to come… let’s make them now
ippai ni shichaou ne
We’ll make lots and lots
love you!
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
The miracle that we met in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
It had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
It’s something we can’t do unless we’re together
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
Right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
Oh my, what with all these mikans?
Mom brought some home!
Ah
They look delicious!
But they’re pretty sour.
But they’re much sweeter than lemons, right?
Oh, right. I made friends with someone named Yuzu!
Oh, I see.
C’mon Sis, stop hogging all the mikans!
There’s more where that came from.
So what’s this Mikan girl like again?
Well Mikan just loves yakisoba.
Next time on Trick 11:
Now the President’s SumiSumi
The Cherry-Colored Truth
“Now the President’s SumiSumi!”
and “The Cherry-Colored Truth”.
See you next time!
Hold on...