Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
Did you...
Did you hate me that much?
Origin Bullet.
It causes the victim's mana to go out of control, instantly ripping apart his entire body.
What?!
Time Alter: Double Accel!
The Origin Bullet didn't work.
No...
I see.
He's using Command Spells as his mana source.
By the time the bullet's effects manifested, the Command
Spell—his mana source—had already vanished from his arm.
Since he isn't using his own Magic Circuits, the Origin Bullet's magic won't work.
But if I can land a shot...
...it'll at least be powerful enough to kill him.
Don't expect to get away next time.
Now that I know you're moving at double speed, I'll simply adjust my timing to compensate.
He's fast!
Is your overwhelming madness...
...also my fault?
My...
Time Alter: Double Accel!
His advantage at close range is enormous.
I've lost my Calico.
The Contender needs reloading.
However...
Avalon...
He recovers quickly enough to
instantly regenerate a demolished heart.
I'll have to destroy the brain, then.
But...
My right arm has been disabled.
Avalon's healing powers also
work on self-inflicted wounds.
I have a knife and two grenades left.
I have twelve Black Keys and eight spare Command Spells.
Time Alter: Triple Accel!
Time Alter: Square Accel!
Even so, I will win the Holy Grail.
If I don't, there will be nothing I can offer to you as recompense.
Even after all that, you would still
take up your sword for such a reason?
How helpless you are...
This place...
I knew you'd come.
I had faith you would reach this place.
Iri.
This is where your wish will be granted.
We're inside the Grail you've been seeking.
That's the Grail.
It has yet to take form, but the
vessel is more than full enough.
You just need to give your prayer now.
Only then will it be able to go outside.
Now, please...
Hurry up and give it form.
Kiritsugu, you alone are worthy of defining it.
Who are you?
I am Irisviel.
No.
If preparations for the Grail are complete, then she's already...
Answer me.
Indeed.
I won't deny that this is a mask.
Unless I use a pre-existing personality as
a shell, I cannot communicate with others.
However, the personality of Irisviel that
I've recorded is unmistakably the real thing.
And so, I've inherited her last wish.
Are you the will of the Holy Grail?
Yes.
That interpretation is correct.
I have a will, a wish.
The will to be born into the world.
Impossible.
In that case, how does the Grail intend to grant my wish?
Well, Kiritsugu...
Isn't that something you
should know better than anyone?
What?
You learned how to save the world a long time ago.
So I will do as you did, take over
from you, and answer your prayer.
What are you talking about?
I suppose there's no avoiding it.
The only way is to have you ask yourself from within.
This place...
Three hundred on one ship.
Two hundred on another.
What?
Five hundred total passengers
and crew, plus Emiya Kiritsugu.
Let's posit that these five hundred and
one people are humanity's last survivors.
Giant holes have opened up at the bottoms of both ships.
Kiritsugu alone has the ability to repair a ship.
Now then, which ship would you repair?
The one with three hundred people, obviously.
After making that decision, you are captured by the two hundred people on the other ship.
They demand that you repair their ship first.
What would you do?
I would...
...kill all two hundred people.
Correct.
That is what Emiya Kiritsugu would do.
Next, the surviving three hundred abandon their damaged ship,
split themselves between two new ships, and continue their journey.
This time, we have two hundred on one ship,
and one hundred on the other.
However, holes have opened up at
the bottoms of both ships once again.
Wait.
You are kidnapped by the hundred in the smaller ship.
They demand that you repair their ship first.
Now, what will you do?
You already know.
But...
Yes, you made the right decision.
Ridiculous...
That's ridiculous!
How is that the right decision?!
Two hundred survived, but three hundred died for their sake!
The scales are tipped the wrong way!
No, your calculations were correct.
You chose to save the majority at the cost of the minority.
Isn't that right, Emiya Kiritsugu?
You've always killed the minority on the lighter side of the scales.
Even if it meant leaving a long trail of bodies behind you,
you believed that if lives were saved,
then those lives were worth it.
Is this what you wanted to show me?!
Yes.
This is your truth.
The answer that lies within Emiya Kiritsugu.
The course of action the Grail should take as a wish-granting device, in other words.
No!
This isn't what I wished for!
I wanted some other way.
That's why a miracle was my only hope!
Your wish could never include a
method you yourself are not aware of.
If you wish to save the world, it must be
done in a way that you can comprehend.
To hell with that!
How on Earth can you call that a miracle?!
It is a miracle.
The deed that you tried and failed to do on your own can
be accomplished at a scale beyond the power of any man.
If that's not a miracle, then what is?
Dad...
Natalia...
Emiya Kiritsugu.
You truly are Angra Mainyu.
The one worthy of bearing all the world's evil.
Now, the last question.
Three remain.
Will you save two?
Or choose one?
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
You're finally back!
You understand, don't you?
This is the Grail's realization of your prayer.
All you need to do now is wish for it.
To bring back your wife.
To take back your daughter.
I won't be able to go looking for walnut buds with you anymore.
It's okay.
I'm happy, as long as you and Mommy are with me.
Thank you.
Daddy loves you too, Illya.
If nothing else, I swear that to be true.
Goodbye, Illya.
Illya!
Illya, Illya, Illya...
Illya, Illya...
Why?!
Why did you do that?!
My love, you killed our Illya!
My love...
Why?
Why do you refuse the Grail?
Why do you refuse us?
Six billion people...
I curse you...
Emiya... Kiritsugu!
...against two members of my family...
Angra Mainyu curses you...
I...
Suffer...
Lament until the day you die...
I'll kill you and...
I won't...
...save the world.
...forgive y—
What a stupid conclusion.
Why did you refuse it?
You saw it too?
I thought you sacrificed
everything you had to make it this far.
How could you simply cast away
what you worked so hard to obtain?
It's too foolish for me to understand.
Its cost is greater than any benefit it offers.
That's all.
That thing is no omnipotent wish-granting device.
Then give it to me!
You may not need it, but I do!
If it...
If that thing is born, it can answer my every doubt.
It longs for its own life, its own birth!
Please don't kill it!
It...
And you...
You're too foolish for me to understand.
Irisviel...
You're late, Saber.
I know you were frolicking
around with your rabid dog of old,
but making me wait like this wasn't very prudent of you.
Archer...
Look at your face.
It's the face of a ravenous wild dog.
Get out... of the way...
The Holy Grail... belongs to me!
Saber.
Even when you're delusional and flat on the ground,
you're still a beautiful woman.
Lay down your sword and be my wife.
A Grail that grants miracles?
Why obsess over something so dubious?
Abandon your foolish ideals and vows.
From now on, seek only me
and be stained only in my color.
If you do, as king of all the world, I shall give you every pleasure there is to feel.
You'd take the Holy Grail from me...
...for such nonsense?!
I wasn't asking for your opinion.
It's what I've decided!
Now, give me your response.
I refuse! I'd never—
Are you too embarrassed to accept?
That's fine.
You may give the wrong
answer as many times as you like.
In order to learn the joy of serving me,
you must first learn pain.
Kiritsugu.
So you've finally made your decision.
By the name of Emiya Kiritsugu,
I order you with my Command Spell.
Give me the Holy Grail.
Saber, use your Noble Phantasm...
...to destroy the Grail.
Wha—
Impossible...
What are you doing, Saber?!
I'm not!
By my third Command Spell, I order you again.
Why, Kiritsugu?!
You, of all people...
Why?!
Bastard...
You dare disturb my wedding ceremony, mongrel?!
Saber, destroy...
No!
...the Grail.
Episode 24
The Last Command Spell
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
I remember that face.
A man with tears in his eyes,
happy from the bottom of his heart.
The man was grateful for something.
"Thank you", he said.
Next Episode