SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
There...
Autumn's here.
A TYPHOON PASSES
ILLUSION AND REALITY
So your father was a tanker, Kureha-chan?
Yep.
With just six Type-2 Millipads,
he led more than a thousand citizens and soldiers...
...out from the completely surrounded Wardenburk.
He was the hero of the legendary "Strategy of Retrieval".
Incredible.
Right?
And when he got wounded during that mission,
he met my mother who was a medic where he was hospitalized.
And the baby born from them...
...was you?
That's right!
No! I'm not a potato!
My, what a splendid potato.
This is thanks to your care, Kana-chan.
We probably have enough to share some with the townspeople.
And Claus-san should be coming by.
Let's give some to him as gift.
He's coming?
You really like him, don't you Kureha-chan?
R-Rather than like, I look up to him.
Poke.
Rio-senpai...
So she can do that too?
That's Rio-senpai for you.
Yeah.
The wind is getting stronger.
It looks like the weather's getting worse, so let's finish up and get inside.
Roger!
Roger.
You too, Noel-chan.
Okay.
What?
Like I said, Rio-senpai seemed weird, didn't she?
For example?
Like that trumpet playing.
That was wonderful and cool, wasn't it?
She didn't seem to be in high spirits.
Doesn't she usually avoid small talk?
But...
Ah, the dinner!
The tempura was delicious, wasn't it?
Yeah, the potato was so soft.
Not that!
Here, Rio. While it's still warm.
Yeah. Thanks.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Really? Glad to hear it.
The green pepper!
She chewed it like it was nothing!
What? The Rio-senpai?
Yeah!
The Rio-senpai that would always pick them out no matter how finely chopped and set them aside.
That... is pretty serious.
Poke.
Hm?
Is this Claus-san?
Yeah! It's my treasure!
The Desert Wolf, Miracle Claus!
He has the 481st Platoon's symbol of unity and glory, a wolf's head,
tattooed on his left chest.
It's so cool, right?
You can't have it.
I don't think we need to worry too much.
We worried too much about the Captain the other day, too.
After all, it's Rio-senpai we're talking about.
She's so cool, striking and beautiful.
Right. She must have conquered her hate of green peppers, and now she can eat them.
You really like Rio-senpai, don't you Kureha-chan?
She's the person I look up to, after all.
Well, me too, but...
Hey, what do you think, Noel-chan?
Poke...
Watch out!
Noel-chan's already sleeping.
She's so hopeless.
I'll give her half of my bed.
Kanata, grab that side.
Okay.
The fire in the bath...
You forgot to put it out.
Sorry, I was careless.
The way you seem to always be sharp but actually careless at times is one of your charm points,
but you've been overdoing it lately.
I'm sorry.
Do you regret hanging up on your father?
Well, no worries.
I'll do something about your mistakes.
At least, act the cool senior in front of those kids.
Was it the wind?
I don't think so.
Sorry to intrude so late,
but it's of top priority.
Who is it for?
1121st Platoon, Sergeant Kazumiya Rio.
Please accept it.
Major, please come in.
You won't be able to travel in this weather.
Even as the Desert Wolf.
I told you to stop calling me that.
I'm sorry.
How about hot tea and a warm bath as an apology?
Thanks for carrying out your mission, even in the middle of a typhoon.
Um, I apologize that these are leftovers from last night, but please have some!
You should have woken me up if Claus-san was coming.
This is well made. It's good even though it's cold.
The green peppers were grown with great care, too.
Really?
I was the one who picked and fried it.
Looks like you'll be a good wife, Kureha.
Is that a new newspaper?
Yes, the Major brought it with him.
What about the peace treaty?
The talks are still encountering problems.
They still haven't reached an agreement.
If only Princess Iliya were still alive, things might have turned out differently.
Princess... Iliya?
You seriously don't know her?
She was the hero of Vingt.
The first Princess of Archduke Arkadia.
Our Helvetian army's goddess of victory.
She was a tanker goddess along with Claus-san, the Desert wolf.
Kureha, about that...
Is everyone here?
We have an emergency!
Rio! Rio!
What's the ruckus?
A kid from Yumina's place has been missing since this morning.
Please lend us a hand.
What?!
Yumina-san, who's missing?
It's Seiya-san.
The river's level has risen quite a bit.
They haven't harvested the fields downstream yet.
If the dam doesn't hold, it'll be ruined.
I don't know my way around town.
I'm counting on you, Kureha.
Roger!
I'm truly sorry!
Just as I took my eyes off him...
Search and rescue is one of the army's responsibilities.
Leave it to us.
Let's go!
Roger!
Seiya!
Seiya-kun!
Wow...
The current's so strong.
If he fell in there...
Seiya!
Seiya-kun!
Wh-What was that?
You!
You know something, don't you?
You came out here because you know where he might be, right?
Spill it!
Where's Seiya?
The field.
The field?
Eggplants.
It's Yumina onee-chan's favorite.
That's why we gathered up our allowance...
I'm sure Seiya...
Where is it?
Wai- Lemme-
What are you doing?!
Why did you come here in this typhoon?
I'm protecting the eggplants!
What are you saying?
Don't be stupid!
We're risking our lives because of you!
No one asked you to do that!
I never asked you to save me!
What did you say?!
Enough already!
Listen, kids without parents need to be stronger than the other kids.
Everyone will look down on you if you cause trouble.
Not only you, but Yumina...
They'll look down on her, too.
Kureha...
Okay.
I know, because I'm an orphan too.
Come on, let's get back.
But...
You're still complaining?
Now, calm down.
Something you grow with all your heart is as valuable as your life.
These are big enough to eat.
When pickled, they're absolutely delicious.
Thank you, mister!
Major...
Seiya-kun is climbing up.
Major, please go first!
Sure...
No, you go first.
I'll watch your back.
Roger!
Both of them seem to be okay.
But...
They lost their means back up.
This is the worst-case scenario.
Thank you very much.
D-Don't mention it.
Our situation has worsened,
but I'm with you, Major.
I believe you'll be able to do something.
You got it wrong...
What? Did you say something?
Nothing.
Listen now, don't be afraid.
You're with "Miracle Claus" now.
I won't!
The ground won't hold!
It's eroding away.
Dammit, this is why I hate kids!
A kid that won't do what he's told should just be locked inside!
Rio!
What's the point of getting worked up?
Those kids have always been looking up to you.
I'm sorry, I said too much.
B-But I'm sure they can do something.
They say Claus-san brings miracles, after all.
That's not true.
He is neither the Desert Wolf nor Miracle Claus.
He just happened to have a similar name and stature.
Kureha got too exited and decided it by herself the first time they met.
Since Claus doesn't speak much,
he always missed his chance to clear up the misunderstanding.
That's...
Anyway, right now we need to think of a way for the courier who only has a long record of service,
and the motivated yet inexperienced soldier, to get out of there.
Give them rope.
There's no foothold above them.
The distance is too far if we were to throw it from here.
If it's about throwing a rope from here,
there's a way.
The first time I met you, I thought that if my father were still alive, he'd look just like you.
I always talk to everyone as if I know my father well,
but the truth is I just heard about him from others,
so I don't really know everything.
By the time I was old enough to understand, he was already gone.
Kureha...
"Pay attention to your left."
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
The Takemikazuchi!
Halt!
How is it, Noel-chan?
The Linear Anchor Coil is functional.
Targeting System, partially functional from B7 to F5.
Begin targeting.
It's possible.
Prepare to fire the wire-anchor!
Kanata, do it!
Roger!
It's coming!
I'll protect you in your deceased father's stead!
Roger.
Major.
Ready!
Fire!
Come on!
Kureha!
Major!
Kureha-chan!
Retract the anchor!
Hurry!
Hey, Kureha...
I'm gonna say this since we managed to survive.
I'm...
You really are...
...the man I looked up to, after all.
A clear blue sky right after a typhoon, huh?
So you pulled it off, after all.
I was honestly surprised.
I didn't expect you to be able to do that.
When I saw those eyes that believed in me, I was more afraid of crushing Kureha's dreams than of dying.
That's why I could pull it off.
In the end, I'm just a coward.
That's not true!
You were wonderful, Claus-san.
Listen up, girly.
What you see on the surface and what the person truly feels...
are very different.
The glasses called "admiration" are always blurry.
You'll understand how hard it is someday, when you're looked at through those glasses.
Could you at least stay until Kureha wakes up?
Can you pass this on to Kureha?
This is the best scar of honor in my entire life!
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
DEPARTURE - THE FIRST SNOW
Next episode: Departure - The First Snow.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.