When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Hayate left the mansion?
Looks like I'll have to find a replacement quickly, then.
Hey!
Klaus-san.
He said he's quitting.
It'd be a different story if he had asked for advice.
Maria, what should I do?
It's because...
...I acted so awkwardly towards him...
Nagi...
Hayate-kun, where did you disappear to?
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
The second part of the preview to the final episode is starting.
Um, is this the only place we get to speak?
Merry Christmas!
Say, Onee-chan, don't tell me you've been drinking since Christmas Eve?
Yes!
Screw a white Christmas!
I'll have it all red instead.
Hina~
Believe it or not, people have given thousands of obl*te to me before!
Assy, Messy, and Nessy!
All the things college girls do!
But I'm not a college girl anymore.
I'm a teacher!
What age did you live in?
If you're lonely, you should have come home.
Me? Lonely?
Onee-chan!
A white Christmas, eh?
Hayate-kun?
What are you doing here?
Nothing. Just came to get things I left in the classroom.
But you look empty-handed to me.
You're a sore loser, Ayasaki-kun.
You were bidding farewell to Sanzenin-kun by visiting the classroom.
Am I right?
Farewell?
Have you made up your mind?
I will answer the superintendent personally.
What is this about? What is the superintendent planning?
Well, um...
There was a rumor going through the butler association this fall.
Shion-san!
The rumor says, anyone who defeats the butler
Ayasaki Hayate gains the Sanzenin's huge estate.
I thought it was bogus,
but I might have to think twice on that.
Give me that, Hayate-kun!
Show it to me!
Hey, that's-
Looks like you had a horrible Christmas.
Yes, you could say that.
Could this be...
This is blackmail!
Um, Hinagiku-san.
You make it sound as though we're the villains.
Give me the data.
It's cheating to pick at others' weak points.
Really?
Please stop. Hinagiku-san has nothing to do with this.
What are you saying, Hayate-kun?
Take me away now, will you?
Wait, Hayate-kun!
Please do not mention this to Milady.
Hayate-kun!
This can't be happening.
Welcome, Ayasaki.
Have you decided to become my vassal?
If I become your butler, you will give up on the Sanzenin estate?
I will promise you.
But why are you saying that after taking my powers as a butler away?
You will be gaining more butler powers than before.
And you will be reborn as a perfect butler that swears his body and soul to me.
Hayate...
Yes, this is the Sanzenin estate.
Oh, Hinagiku-san?
What? Hayate-kun is?
Hey, it's me!
What?
He asked me not to tell you, but I couldn't pretend I didn't see anything.
Plus, he looked like he was getting blackmailed over the Sanzenin estate.
Hayate left in order to protect me and the Sanzenin family.
Nagi...
Hayate took everything upon himself!
Butler and master are whole only when they're together.
They must face all hardships and crises together!
Then there's only one thing for you to do as Hayate-kun's master.
Yes.
I leave the house in your care, Maria.
Shion, bring the item.
Yes, Kuzuha-sama.
Th-That's!
The treasure among the butlers,
passed down since ancient times.
What could the butler treasure be?
Continues to part B.
Ramipasu Ramipasu Rerererere!
Rerere no re. Genki desuka?
Rerere no re. Genki desuka? = Rerere no re. Are you doing well?
This treasure is something I found when I went to the Amazon.
Amazon?
The reason I went there was to get
a hold of the legendary vanilla beans.
The cave we found by luck was a ruin of the ancient butler civilization.
Um, what is an ancient butler civilization?
But, we did not fear it and marched deeper.
She ignored me.
At the deepest part of the cave, the giant snake, Jormungandr, our Jor-kun, was protecting the ancient treasure.
We were enchanted by him
and became guardians of the treasure.
As a result, I gained the power to control white snake magic!
And I gained the power to turn into a man from Jor-kun,
so that we can protect the treasure together.
S-So you're being used by the snake?
They really are  being manipulated.
You should be honored, Ayasaki Hayate.
I will let you see the ancient butler civilization's treasure, too!
This ancient butler robe is still in its slumber.
Shion and I have used countless butlers to test the robe,
but no matter how talented the butler we bring, for some reason the robe rejects them,
and they can't even put their arms through the sleeves.
Hey, that's not a butler uniform.
But I'm sure you can wear this robe.
Come. Become a butler who serves us with your body and soul.
I said that's not a butler-
So you know, you can't take this robe off once you wear it.
And, if you get rejected by the robe,
you'll turn into a white snake as part of the curse.
We'll now start the ceremony.
Elohim Essaim, Elohim Essaim.
I desire and here I moe.
O ancient robe! Awaken!
The ultimate butler uniform is awakening!
Milady!
Look!
Hayate must be there!
Yes ma'am.
She's here.
Hey, over here!
So it's begun?
Hayate, are you all right?
We're here to save-
Is it sweet, my Master?
Yes, it's exquisite.
I'm so happy ~nyan.
Hayate! What's with the outfit?
Oh, we have guests.
I'll prepare some tea right away.
Hayate, do you not recognize...
He's now completely my butler.
Look at the design.
Can't expect better from an ancient civilization's artifact.
Those clothes still count as butler attire?
Anyways, I'm taking Hayate back.
Hey, Hayate!
We'll get him out of those clothes, first of all.
Y-Yeah.
Stay out of the way.
I haff been waifing for 30000 yearf for this snack time.
I see. Your speech totally gives it away.
Exactly.
This snake is manipulating eferyone.
Hey, out of my way!
If you get in my way-!
We don't need two mafters for Ayafaki Fayate!
Protect our Lady!
Fho are you?
Himegami!
My name is Princess God.
I was born in darkness, and in darkness I live.
I don't really care.
Take care of him!
Hey, Hayate! Take this chance and get yourself out of those ridiculous clothes.
What?
Fine, I'll resort to force.
What are you doing to me?
Just strip him, Nagi.
Yup, I will.
Please stop.
She seems to be enjoying it.
But it's still too early for this.
That robe has yet to fully awaken.
What are you planning?
Hinagiku! Himegami!
Nagi!
Hayate is my butler!
I will not give him to anyone!
I don't need my mansion!
I don't need my estate!
Hayate...
I'm happy as long as you're with me!
Even if you've lost your powers as a butler...
So...
So please! Wake up!
Hayate!
Hayate, you...
I'm sorry, Milady. I'm...
I'm!
Hayate...
I'll have to punish you later.
Yes, Milady!
Hayate!
It has begun.
That smart aleck!
Your opponent is me!
S-She's so manfy.
Hayate! Get out of there! Hey!
Don't worry, Milady.
But you've lost your powers as a butler.
It'll be fine. Even if I didn't have anything of the sort,
as long as Milady trusts me, I'm...
I'll be a butler!
Hayate!
What is going on?
"To awaken the holy butler uniform, he must..."
Eh... how do I read this character?
Give it to me!
Let's see... "he must lose once the powers of a butler."
"The treasure sleeps in the form of girls' clothes to test if the individual truly holds the soul of a butler."
"But, when it accepts him truly,
the treasure shall awaken and show its true form."
S-So that's how it worked.
I'd lofe to own this wafkthrough.
Besides, there are too many myfteries that you can nefer solve wifout reading wafkthrough these days.
So where did you buy this book?
From Ya*** ***tion.
Oh, it's here, it's really here.
The ultimate butler uniform is finally awakening!
Um... I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm the butler who protects Lady Sanzenin Nagi.
So that's the legendary butler uniform...
What horrible taste.
I've been protecting this for 30000 years?
It's shining brilliantly!
It's cool!
You're super cool, Hayate!
Thank you very much, Milady.
Hey! Are you guys blind or something?!
How abominable.
I'll go afean and deftroy that ifem.
I will gain freedom!
Hayate!
Come to me, my original butler ultimate attack!
Here I go!
Hayate.
Milady.
It's dangerous here. Let's go outside!
There goes one of the school's facilities...
Himegami-san!
Thanks to you, I got a hold of this fully awakened item.
Himegami-san...
Take care of Nagi.
Did you use Hayate to get a hold of that?
I didn't want to wear it even if it meant dispelling my curse.
Besides, what exactly are those golden clothes, Himegami?
I'm not Himegami.
I'm Princess God.
I will save this world one day.
Enough of that!
I only need three more to get the legendary God Butler Dragon.
Gosh. What's wrong with him?
But, if it hadn't been for Himegami-san,
I might not have been able to come back.
Yeah, maybe, but...
Wh-Where am I?
What have I been doing all this time?
K-Kuzuha-sama!
Thank goodness!
Looks like the curse wore off of both of them.
So that means...
Hakuou Academy will now become peaceful.
Shion, you're not bad at all when you're small.
Kuzuha-sama.
I don't see much of a change in them.
Oh yeah, what happened to that picture?
It's inside here!
The memory card must be broken to pieces by now!
I see. Then be careful on your way back.
I'll be waiting, Nagi.
They must be coming back soon.
Have a wonderful Christmas, both of you.
Hina, you were still here?
Huh?
Wow! What the hell is this?
A lot happened.
What are you doing out here at this hour, Onee-chan?
I was out to go buy some chasers.
I thought I'd start drinking again.
Do you want me to come with you?
Oh, but of course, I'll be drinking juice.
Yeah!
Thank you very much, Milady.
It was nothing, really.
Hey, Hayate.
Don't let it bother you so much. Thank you, too.
Oh no. I feel too embarrassed all of a sudden to face him.
But this is Christmas, so...
Let's make a stop before we go home!
Merry Christmas.
Everyone, please buy a cake.
Hold on, if these don't sell, do I get to keep them?
Um, Milady, why are we here?
You do remember this, right?
Yes, of course.
I've learned a lot in this one year, too.
Look, I can now buy the warm, too.
Hayate, this is for you.
Just take it.
See? The warm that we couldn't buy that day is now within our grasp.
This is the year that we spent together.
Thank you for the warm every day.
Milady...
Merry Christmas, Hayate.
Merry Christmas to you, too, Milady.
Milady?
What's the matter?
Could it be that you're sleepy?
Ow!
What was that for, Milady?
Damn you, Hayate!
P-Please wait! Milady!
Nagi and Hayate-sama are late.
Yeah, really. So much for setting aside time for them.
Let's just start eating.
You can't, Sir.
Welcome home!
All those watching Hayate no Gotoku.
Thank you for your long support.
Next week starts the fourth season.
Nagi and,
Hayate's
Butler Network!
I'm the creation's dream, Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
Hayate no Gotoku the animation has finally faced its final episode.
Thank you everyone for your support.
Please look forward to the succeeding show.
It's not over yet, Milady.
Just like the famous Hermit said, "It will continue a little longer."
Oh, it will?
What a pain!
The fourth season starts from next week on.
I will continue to give my all so I can be your best butler.
Y-Yeah, I'm counting on you, Hayate.
Bye-yaya.
Hayate!
What's the matter, Milady?
Let's go see the first sunrise of the year at a beautiful beach.
Just the two of us!
What's the point of going to watch a sunrise?
It's really cold out.
Shut up, you idiot!
Stop talking and get ready!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Osechi is Also Good, but Enjoy Hayate, Too.
Osechi = Traditional New Year's food.
Did you know? In Vietnam, they eat
watermelon on New Year's for good luck,
and in Hong Kong, they give
New Year's allowances even to adults.