Everything is proceeding according to plan.
You continue to waste my time
with your trifles, Tokiomi.
I beg your forgiveness, king of kings...
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh.
My intention this evening
was to demonstrate the power
the King of Heroes wields,
discern which of the lions
we should hunt first,
and thus herald your march
onto the battlefield.
Please have patience.
Very well.
Perhaps I shall distract myself
for now with a little stroll.
I find this era quite interesting.
You've taken a liking to this time period?
It disgusts me beyond words.
Still, I cannot help but be fascinated.
All that matters is
if I can find treasures worthy of
addition to my collection.
Should I find that this world offers
no object of value...
Wasting my time with such a useless summoning
would be a grave offense,
Tokiomi.
Worry not.
Without doubt, the Holy Grail will suit
the tastes of the King of Heroes.
I shall be the judge of that.  Regardless...
For now, I shall do as you suggest.
All the treasures of this world belong to me.
The Holy Grail's true value matters not.
I shall not stand by while a group of mongrel curs
fights over it without my permission.
Tokiomi, I leave the details to you.
Dear me.
Really...
For Gilgamesh, of all Servants,
to be summoned into
the Archer class, which boasts the highest
potential for independent action...
Well, for now, I can leave
everything to Kirei.
All is moving forward as planned.
Assassin's been killed?
Hey, Rider!  Big news!
One already down!
Hey...
Did you hear what I said?
Assassin's been defeated!
Come on, that means the
Holy Grail War's begun.
I've been out scouting and researching,
and all you've done is watch TV and pig out, day after day after day!
You're more useless than a familiar...
Than a rat!
And I told you to dematerialize
when I don't need you.
I'm providing the mana
you need to do it, too.
Look, who gives a damn
about some hired killer?
A cowardly assassin,
whose only strength is in sneaking
in the shadows, is no match for me anyway.
Regardless, boy, here's the good stuff!
See?  Like this huge, black B-2 thing.
It's spectacular!
I'd like to order ten.  What do you think?
With that kind of money, you could
just buy a country outright.
Ah, I see.
So the problem is a lack of funds.
If there were just a huge city around,
loaded with treasure like Persepolis,
we could plunder all
the wealth we require.
At any rate, it appears this man, Clinton,
will be a formidable opponent.
Likely to put up a better fight
than King Darius.
A-Anyway, we're damned lucky Assassin
was the first to go.
You're the type who favors a
full-frontal assault, right?
So it benefits us to be rid of
the guy who prefers
tripping people up with clever traps.
I could use some of these
Tomahawk contraptions, too.
We can scratch Saber, Lancer, and Archer,
the three Knight classes,
and Berserker, who's only good for
mindless destruction, off the list.
Given your Noble Phantasm, none of them
should pose the slightest bit of trouble!
The problematic one is Caster.
If we could just figure out his identity, we...
How did Assassin fall?
Which Servant defeated him?
Did you not see it happen?
It was Tohsaka's Servant, I think.
His outfit, his attacks...
Everything about him was
bright, shiny, and gold.
It was over in an instant.  I couldn't―
Fool!
When I fight, I intend to emerge victorious!
How can I accomplish this
if you cannot attend to details?
At any rate...
Did you notice anything else
besides his flashy appearance?
T-That's easy for you to ask.
It was pitch dark, and the fight
only lasted a second...
So, Rider, Servants normally only have
one Noble Phantasm, right?
In theory.
But there's no point in trying to understand
a Noble Phantasm with numbers.
I'm sure you know, but Noble Phantasms
are items that have come to
personify the Heroic Spirit,
either through legend or historical anecdote.
That includes weapons with a particular
ability or a unique attack.
Then could there be a Noble Phantasm
that allows the wielder
to throw ten or twenty swords at the opponent?
A sword that can split into
infinite copies of itself?
It is possible.
That could be the
Noble Phantasm's special ability.
But the weapons looked too different
to all be copies of the same one.
Either way, I'll know the enemy's
true identity once I engage him.
Y-You think that's a good idea?
Yeah!  That is what excites me!
Food and sex, sleep and battle...
Whatever you do in life,
you must be certain to derive
all you can from it.
That is the only way to live!
So what do you say to going out for some fun?
Prepare yourself, boy!
We make for the front lines.
A-And where, exactly, are we headed?
Irrelevant.  Somewhere, anywhere.
That's ridiculous!
You cannot be the only one
watching Tohsaka.
The rest must also know about Assassin.
And that means they'll be on the move.
We'll hunt them, one by one.
Hunt them?  It isn't that simple.
I am Rider.
I guarantee that no Servant is faster than I.
Wait, wait, wait!  Not here!
You'll blow up the whole house!
My Servant has been eliminated,
leaving me, his Master, defeated
and unable to continue in the Holy Grail War.
As per the rules,
I, Kotomine Kirei, seek asylum
from the Holy Church.
Accepted.
Without violating my role as mediator,
I, Kotomine Risei, will guarantee your safety.
Please enter.
Father, is anyone spying on this church?
No.  This is a neutral zone.  I assure you,
no one would dare attempt infiltration.
If any of the Masters try to interfere,
the Church will remonstrate with them.
Then the peace here will remain undisturbed.
Still, I feel it wise to stay vigilant.
I want a guard posted here at all times.
Understood, sir.
Was anyone else observing the battle?
I detected four
distinct magical presences.
I have confirmed that the final Servant,
Caster, was summoned the
day before yesterday.
All seven Servants for this Holy Grail War
should now be in our world, but...
Someone wasn't watching.
I had intended for all of the Masters to see that.
At this stage of the game, I would say that
is a obvious step for every Master.
If they don't take even that basic precaution,
they would constitute such a minor threat that
we Assassins would hardly
notice their presence.
When the other Masters lower their guard,
upon hearing the news of Assassin's defeat...
We, the Heroic Spirits of shadow,
shall appear from behind,
and we shall become true darkness.
And thus the battle commences.
The fourth Holy Grail War has begun.
It seems like this old man will
witness a miracle, at last.
This is Kiritsugu's home country.
What did you think of air travel, Saber?
Nothing in particular.
Far less interesting than I'd expected.
Perhaps flying through the air
seems mundane after being
summoned as a Heroic Spirit?
It's not that.
When Servants are summoned,
we are given knowledge of the era
into which we appear.
If worse came to worst,
I expect I could pilot this aircraft.
You can fly a plane?
One of my core skills is the ability
to ride anything, be it mortal or divine.
Once I mount it and
grab hold of the reins,
I can more or less feel my way through.
Mount it and grab the reins...
Did I say something amusing?
No...
It's so lively here.
Kiritsugu should have arrived before us, yes?
Yes, about twelve hours ago.
But he'll find us, so there's nothing to worry about.
Until he says otherwise,
we'll tread carefully,
keeping an eye on the situation, as it evolves.
We've come all the way to Japan.
We should enjoy ourselves a bit
before the fighting starts.
That would be quite reckless.
We should be establish a fortified position,
rendezvous with Kiritsugu,
and plan our strategy.
You're probably right, honestly...
But it's such a waste!
We've traveled so long
to this far-off country.
And...
I've never before been out.
Hmm?
Before today, I'd never set foot
in the outside world...
You've spent your entire life in that castle?
I was just a puppet, crafted to fight
in the Holy Grail War.
It isn't as if I'm totally ignorant of the world.
Kiritsugu has shown me pictures and movies,
and has taught me many things about the
places and current events of the world.
But this is the very first time I'm
seeing it with my own eyes.
That's why...
I'm sorry.  I'm rambling!
Stop.
This will be my first time walking
around this town, as well.
A knight is duty-bound to escort her charge.
I shall do what little I can for you.
Come.
All of your equipment has arrived.
Madam and Saber have arrived in Fuyuki
and are working their way through the city.
That should be sufficient to convince
the other six that she is Saber's Master.
Good.
Last night, there was movement
at the Tohsaka mansion.
This is what was recorded.
What is your interpretation?
It is too good to be true.
There was very little time
between the start of Assassin's
infiltration and
the appearance of Tohsaka's Servant.
Taking Assassin's skill at stealth into account,
I cannot believe he was registered that quickly.
They must have expected an
invader well in advance.
Keeping your Servant's true identity
a secret is an absolute must in this war.
Why would Tohsaka
risk sending his Servant into the open like that?
Perhaps it was deliberate?
Maiya, what happened to Assassin's Master?
We have word that he sought
asylum from the Church,
and was taken into protective custody
by the observer last night.
Assassin's Master was Kotomine Kirei.
Maiya, send a familiar to Fuyuki Church.
Are you certain that's wise?
Masters are supposed to be forbidden
from impinging upon
the Church's neutral zone.
Just get it as close as possible without
attracting the Father's notice.
Understood, sir.
And the one I left with you?
Right here.
Two seconds...  I'm rusty.
Yes.
Ilya still weighs less than that Walther,
even though she's about to turn eight...
Try to focus only on the task
that lies before you.
Push everything else from your mind.
It's beautiful.  Like a giant mirror,
pointed toward the night sky.
Walking through a new town
with a gentleman friend
is such a wonderful feeling.
Was I enough of a gentleman for you?
You were absolutely perfect.
A knight in shining armor, I would say.
It was my honor, princess.
Saber, do you like the ocean?
I don't quite know how to answer.
In my era, in my kingdom, the ocean
was flooded with invaders
from faraway countries.
I had no love for the ocean.  I cursed it.
I'm sorry.  Even though we're both women,
your life as King Arthur never permitted you
the freedom to wander about,
as we did today.
And you, Irisviel, would have preferred to
walk the town with Kiritsugu, correct?
I couldn't...
It would be a painful memory for him.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy
spending time with you?
Happiness only seems to cause him pain.
An enemy Servant?
Yes.
I sense something lurking in the shadows,
about one hundred meters from us.
It seems they are challenging us.
How chivalrous.
They want us to decide the field of battle.
Shall we accept their invitation?
Gladly.
Rider, I want to go down.
I'm too...  Hurry!
Why are you complaining?
This spot is ideal for observing the enemy.
Let's go down!  No, take me down now!
I-I can't take this...
You act like a child.
The waiting game is merely
another kind of battle.
I wanna go home... Back to England.
Again, do not be so hasty.
Look!  Things are finally about to begin.
Now I'm getting pumped!
You did well to make it here.
While you paraded around town today,
everyone else stayed within,
fortifying their defenses.
Only you had the valor to
answer my challenge.
Such a pure fighting spirit...
Am I right to assume that you are Saber?
None other.
And you must be Lancer.
Here we are, about to fight to the death,
but we cannot even exchange names,
as is traditional...
It dampens my enthusiasm.
Saber, be careful.
I can support you with healing magic,
but no more than that.
I can handle Lancer.
But I dislike that his Master has yet to appear.
There may be more to their plan
than is apparent.
Please stay alert.
I'm trusting you to watch my back, Irisviel.
I will, Saber.
Secure the victory!
I shall.
Episode 3
Fuyuki City
Now my little King of Knights,
let's see what you're capable of.
The Saber Class's attack magic is impressive.
He's good.
Enough playing around, Lancer.
What's going on here?
I'll go!
Next time: Spearhead
Take me with you!