[ED GASPS]
[AL] Brother...
We've almost reached
the Dublith station.
Were you having a dream?
Yeah... I was
dreaming about him.
[ED] Well, Al...
We're finally here.
[AL] Yeah.
[ED SIGHS]
[ED] It'd be nice if
Teacher wasn't home.
[AL] Uh-huh.
[LOUD THUDS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[ED AND AL YELL]
Hmm...?!
Um... hello Sig.
Long time no see.
Good to see you...
You've grown up
a little huh?
He's... squishing me.
[AL] You probably
don't recognize me,
but it's Alphonse.
Sorry we've been
away so long.
Looks like you've grown up
more than a little!
[AL] No one's patted
my head like this
since back before
I lost my body.
Izumi...
The Elric shrimps
have come for a visit.
Do you think
you can see them?
[IZUMI]
I'll be right there...
I'm feeling a little
better today.
[AL] Lying down?
That's not a good sign.
I guess she hasn't gotten
any better since last time.
Huh...?
[ED YELLS]
[CRASH]
[AL GASPS]
Hello, my stupid pupil...
I hear you've become one
of the military's dogs!
[DOOR CREAKS]
[AL GASPS]
Uh, Teacher... you see...
it's because... um...
Al...?! Look at you!
You've gotten so big!
[AL EXHALES]
[AL] Teacher...!
It's really good to see yo--
[AL YELLS]
[AL GROANS]
Your skills are rusty.
[AL] You've got
lots of energy
for someone who's
not feeling well.
Not feeling well...?!
What're you talking about?
I'm perfectly--
[ED AND AL SCREAM]
You shouldn't exert yourself.
How sweet of you
to worry, dear!
Thank you!
[IZUMI]
The Philosopher's Stone?
No, I don't know
much about it...
It holds no interest for me.
[ED] I see. Okay.
[SIG] There was
that one alchemist...
I thought that
one man from Central
knew a good amount
about the Stone...
[ED GASPS]
So who was this guy?
Let me think...
what's his name?
Ah... Hohenheim.
What is it?
Then he's alive.
Someone you know?
[AL]
He's our father.
The one who ran out on
you when you were little?
Yeah, that's the one!
It's all because of that bastard
that our mother's dead...
and... if it wasn't for him...
Oh! You boys are up early...
What're you doing out of bed?
[ED YAWNS]
Al said that
he had to go potty.
[TRICIA] And of course his
big brother took care of him.
Thanks a lot,
little man.
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
Hey... why isn't Dad here?
Your dad left.
When's he coming back, Mom?
[TRICIA LAUGHS]
I'm gonna getcha!
[AL AND TRICIA LAUGH]
You silly boy...!
He'll be back
before you know it, Al!
Now, finish your dinner, boys.
[ED] Mom...
Mom...
Mom!
[AL] Um... did our
dad say anything
about the
Philosopher's Stone?
Something about a life-long
dream coming true...
He seemed very happy
when he said it.
[ED YELLS]
Now we're going to eat!
Okay!
[DOG BARKS]
[SIG] You aren't
eating, Al?
Oh, no, I'm fine!
I had a big meal
on the train ride here.
Hey, Al...
You should tell her
about Rush Valley...
about the baby
being delivered.
Oh, yeah!
We helped deliver a baby!
There was this big storm
and we couldn't get
the mother to a doctor!
[ED] I don't know.
It's pretty generous to
call what we did 'helping.'
Heh... Yeah,
it was mostly Winry.
And the whole family
pitched in, too!
The mother was so brave!
Everyone's blessed when
a baby's born, huh?
Yes, that's right...
That same miracle brings
us all into this world...
Always take pride in
the lives that were given you.
[ED AND AL LAUGH]
[AL] Hey, Ed...
Teacher hasn't
changed, has she?
Nope...
She hasn't changed one
bit in all this time.
[RAIN POURS]
[MAN A]
Stack 'em up tight!
[MAN B]
We need more!
[MAN A]
It's collapsing!
[MEN GRUNTING]
[MAN B]
The levee's breaking!
Head for higher ground!
Brother... look.
[MEN YELL]
Well, that oughta hold
the water back for awhile.
Lady, who are you?
Just a housewife
who was passing by.
Uhh...
Hey, old lady!
Could you be our teacher?
[ED AND AL YELL]
[ED AND AL]
Pretty please, old lady?
I'm a little hard of
hearing, you see,
so I didn't
quite catch that...
Maybe you'd like
to repeat yourselves?
[ED] Uhh...
Uh...
We'll try again!
Please, please teach
us... pretty lady!
No way!
[ED] Why not?
Because I don't
take on students...
and besides I'm in
the middle of a trip!
[ED] But please!
[AL] Please teach us!
You brats...!
What about your parents?
[MAN B]
Um, ma'am...
These little ones
don't have any parents.
Ah...
How am I supposed
to say no to that?
[ANIMAL SOUNDS]
[ED AND AL]
Huh...?
[IZUMI]
You two are on your own.
Huh...?
[IZUMI] This is your
introductory training...
If you do well, we'll move
on to the main training phase...
During this first stage, the use
of alchemy is totally forbidden.
Huh...?
"One is all...
and all is one."
You have one month to
figure out what that means.
You'd better find the
answer in the allotted time...
If not, you're headed
back to Risembool!
[ED AND AL YELL]
Bye.
[ED AND AL SCREAM]
[ED AND AL]
What do we do now?!
[ED]
I'm so hungry.
[AL]
I wanna sleep in a real bed.
[FROG CROAKS]
How is a camping trip
considered alchemy training?!
[STOMACH GROWLS]
[ED]
I'm so hungry.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[SIG] I wonder if they're
doing all right out there.
You know
what they say:
no better teacher
than experience...
This is the best
way for them
to learn the essentials
of alchemy...
I'm teaching them the
same way that I was taught.
[IZUMI]
If they don't learn
anything from this...
It means their talent as
alchemists will be limited...
and I'll have to give up
on them as pupils.
It's not their education
I'm worried about...
Their lives could be
in danger out there.
They're not doing
anything that I haven't...
My training began
with a whole month
in the Briggs
Mountains in winter!
You know you shouldn't compare
yourself to normal people.
[IZUMI] That island has
plenty of things to eat.
They're not going to die.
[ED AND AL]
Got one!
[AL]
How are we supposed to eat it?
We kill it.
Kill it?
Uhh...
No way...!
You take care
of it, Brother.
Catching them
is more my area.
You always make me
do the dirty work!
Huh...?
Ah...!
Hey...! Come back here!
[ED AND AL BREATHE HEAVILY]
Fox cubs, look...
Maybe we should
just switch to fish.
[ED] Great! How're we
supposed to catch a fish?!
We don't have any rods or line
or hooks or bait or anything!
[AL] Here we are... no food...
no fire... no nothing!
Don't remind me!
[RAIN FALLS]
[ED GASPS]
[AL] Hey!
What are you
trying to do to me?!
Huh...?
Uh, Brother?!
[ED YELLS]
So gross!
Al... I'm still alive...
I'm alive because
I ate the ants.
I consumed life.
I'm still alive...
We're not
going to die!
[ED AND AL YELL]
I'm sorry.
[WATER SPLASHES]
Just keep going
a little longer.
[ED YELLS]
[AL GASPS]
[ED AND AL LAUGH]
[ED]
Tomorrow will be one month.
[AL] Hey, Brother...
Have you figured out...
what Teacher meant by
"One is all, and all is one"?
I've been thinking about
it this whole time...
but I still only have
a few vague ideas.
I'm not really
sure about this...
but... do you remember when
I was weak from hunger...
and I ate those ants?
[AL] You ate
a lot of 'em.
Heh... I sure did.
And boy did they taste nasty.
But then that
got me thinking...
If I hadn't eaten them,
I might've died...
then I would've
been eaten by them.
I'd go into the earth
and become grass...
and then the rabbits
would eat that.
[AL] You're talking about
the food chain, right?
Yeah but...
it's not just that, either.
A long time ago,
this whole island was
probably at the
bottom of the sea...
and tens of thousands
of years from now...
it could be the peak of
a mountain for all we know.
[AL] All things are connected.
Is that what you're saying?
Everything we see...
everyone we meet...
is caught up in a great,
unseen flow.
But it's bigger than that...
It's the entire world...
the entire universe, even.
And compared to something
as big as that, Al...
you and I are tiny,
not even the size of ants.
We're only one small part
within the much greater flow...
Nothing more than
a fraction of the whole.
But by putting all
those 'ones' together,
you get one great 'all'
just like Teacher said...
The flow of this universe
follows laws of such magnitude,
that you and I can't
even imagine them.
[IZUMI]
Today is the day...
Let's hear what
you've learned about
"One is all, and all is one."
"All" is the world!
And "one" is me!
[IZUMI LAUGHS]
Very well...
now the real training starts.
[AL LAUGHS]
- [AL] Oh yeah!!
- [ED] Yeah!!
The basis of transmutation...
is the power of the circle.
Which denotes
the circulation of power.
In order to call upon
and harness this power,
one must draw a structural
matrix over the circle.
[ED YELLS]
[AL YELLS]
This is also
the circulation of power.
It's best if you
experience it for yourself.
[ED YELLS]
[IZUMI]
Enough of that.
Keep reviewing the morning's
lessons until lunch is ready.
Let's see... the circle denotes
the circulation of power...
in order to call upon
and harness this power,
one must draw a structural
matrix over the circle.
But Teacher, you just
put your palms together
to perform transmutations,
don't you?
You can do it without
drawing the structural matrix?
If you think about
it a certain way,
I myself am the matrix.
How do you do it?
Tell us teacher!
[IZUMI] Perhaps it's
something you learn
when you see the truth.
[ED GASPS]
Our Teacher has
seen the truth too.
[IZUMI] So... what is it
you wanted to ask me?
Uh... well...
[ED GRUNTS]
[ED YELLS]
As I suspected, you can
transmute without a matrix.
[ED GASPS]
On top of which,
Al is now a suit of armor...
and two of your limbs
are made from automail!
Teacher, how
did you know?
Please! I could tell
from sparring with you!
You saw it...
didn't you, Edward?
[ED GASPS]
You saw it!
[ED] Y-Yes!
[IZUMI] It seems both
of us are beyond help.
[ED] Teacher... you saw it
too... could you tell me...
[IZUMI GASPS]
[IZUMI SCREAMS]
[IZUMI YELLS]
[SIG GRUNTS]
For awhile it seemed
we were barren...
We wanted a child
but couldn't conceive.
When we were finally
able to conceive...
I ended up falling gravely ill.
And our child as well...
He was not able to take a
living breath in this world...
and so...
I committed the taboo.
As a result, I lost
parts of my inner organs.
What an idiot I was.
Now I realize I should
have told you sooner.
It must have been awful.
Nah...! I did it to
myself, after all.
It hasn't been that
big a deal, actually.
[AL] Besides, now I've got
this long list of things
I get to look forward to eating
when I have my body back.
[AL]
Right... Brother?
Yeah!
It's nothing!
[IZUMI]
You darling little idiots.
It's okay to hurt.
[ED] Forgive us...
[AL]
We're so sorry, Teacher.
[ED] Please forgive us.
[AL] We're so sorry.
- [ED] Please forgive us.
- [AL] We're so sorry.
[ED] The flow of this universe
follows laws of such magnitude,
that you and I can't
even imagine them.
You have to
understand that flow...
deconstruct it,
and then reconstruct it.
[AL] That's what
alchemy is, Brother.
[ED] You're right...
but it's also what living is.
So the basis
of alchemy...
deconstruction and
then reconstruction...
is just like the food
chain then, isn't it?
Like when you
eat a rabbit
and your body breaks
down its flesh...
then it's restructured
as a part of yourself...
And even before that...
the rabbit restructured
the grass it ate
into a part of its own body.
Alchemy is part of that flow...
and the flow is life itself.
[NARRATOR]
His name is Greed,
and he revels in his
own sinister desires,
running everything in his
path with cruel cunning.
Now he stands before Ed and Al,
an intimidating figure
in all his grotesque glory,
as if he were made for battle.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode 13... Beasts of Dublith.
This mighty beast is not
to be to looked upon
by the faint of heart.