Yasuri Shichika, the seventh generation master of the Kyotou style,
and strategist Togame, War Campaign Overseer under the direct authority of Shogun Yanari of the Owari shogunate...
set out on their quest for Shikizaki Kiki's twelve perfected swords.
Of the twelve swords that are said to hold the might to conquer the world,
the two retrieved Kanna, the Obstinate, from Maniwa Komori and stopped by at Kyoto...
to prepare for their journey.
Are you awed by the unfamiliar scenery?
Yeah.
There are people everywhere.
I can't tell them apart like this.
You don't need to.
I don't?
Nope.
If you paid attention to every person that walked by, you'd go crazy.
I think I'm already starting to go crazy, Togame.
Hey!
I'm over here!
It's even harder to distinguish people with similar heights.
You're beyond terrible.
Um...
Yes?
Aren't you cold?
No.
Oh, don't mind him.
Think of him as a bear or something like that.
Is there something strange about me?
Well, to answer that question,
I'd have to say you're a compilation of everything strange.
But I do need to do something about your clothes...
I'm not wearing any of these!
You sure know how to thank someone.
Besides, I don't need these.
They'd only slow me down.
Well, without clothes, people on the street will look at you, like that girl did.
It doesn't bother me.
It bothers me, though.
What would people think of a woman who keeps a young man by her side, stripped naked in this cold winter?
What would they think?
They'll see me as a master with an abnormal fetish, persecute me, and throw rocks at me everywhere I go.
That would be a problem.
Then wear a kimono.
Being on the mainland seems to be quite a pain.
Everyone lives their life weighed down by these shackles.
Have you come to a decision?
Yes.
I'd like to buy this, that, that, that, and that.
Wow, so many!
I don't need so many.
They're for me!
Don't you already wear plenty of clothes?
A maiden needs to be fashionable.
I don't understand you...
That should be my line!
Look at you!
I'm not naked, so don't I pass?
Well, it's quite unique,
and could be taken as the most challenging fashion style this winter,
but I don't quite like it.
Like and dislike...
Now that's something I don't understand.
Who are they?
You'll come across them from time to time.
What should I do?
Protect me.
Very well.
I will protect you.
Nice clothes you got there.
You know what to do to save yourself, don't you?
I don't intend to give you anything.
Moreover, if you want to live, don't pull out your swords.
What the fuck are you-
I thought I warned you...
You!
If you were better at using your swords, you'd be dead.
Kyotou style technique...
Wait, wait!
Don't just kill anyone you see!
I can't kill them?
You can't.
Is that another rule on the mainland?
It's more or less common sense.
You can't just go around killing everyone who acts out of malice.
Consider yourselves lucky.
Seriously, you wouldn't be alive now if I hadn't stopped him.
What a pain...
A man who knows no man and a woman who's lost her heart...
With many difficulties, their journey has begun.
A month has passed since their quest for Shikizaki Kiki's perfected swords began.
Searching for the second sword, Togame and Shichika made their way to Inaba.
Don't do it so hard.
I don't know my strength.
Hey...
How much longer do we have to continue this?
Until you can clearly distinguish me from everyone else.
I can't have you remain a weirdo who can't tell people apart.
You're right.
I also wouldn't like to be killed for being mistaken as an assassin when I try to pull a joke on you.
I can't agree with you more.
That's why I'm trying to remember your colors and scent.
Hey, no biting now.
It hurts when you bite.
Can I lick you?
You can.
Actually, lick me and remember my taste.
But don't move around too much.
It hurts when my hair gets pulled.
I bet it does.
Taming can be quite humorous.
In any case, we'll be in Inaba tomorrow.
Right.
Inaba's... what was it again?
Gekoku Castle.
We're going there for Namakura, the Slayer.
Doesn't sound very strong.
That's the irony Shikizaki intended it to have.
Namakura's main characteristic is its unmatched sharpness.
No matter what it's cutting, it'll slice right through it like butter.
Or so I've heard.
So what would happen if someone tried to cut Kanna with that sword?
I can't say without seeing it for myself,
but I assume the less perfect sword will break.
Namakura was forged later, so perhaps Kanna may end up sliced.
There's a reason I chose Namakura to be our second sword.
We're up against a swordsman this time.
Swordsmen will be easier to fight than ninjas.
I guess Uneri Ginkaku would be considered a ronin.
Or perhaps he's considered a castle lord.
The owner of the sword back when the former Shogun ordered the sword hunt,
was Uneri Kinkaku, a samurai who served under the owner of the Tottori Domain.
Kinkaku refused to surrender his sword, committing an unacceptable act as a samurai.
He stated that the sword was by all means his.
The total number of soldiers that died to retrieve it amounts to over ten thousand.
Ten thousand?
I hear that the current holder, Uneri Ginkaku, is his tenth generation descendant.
Door front the through entrance grand a making be to ninja a for embarrassment an of bit a it's.
In way other any have didn't I guess I but.
Shirasagi Maniwa I'm. Myself introduce I'll.
Ninjas Maniwa the of heads twelve the of one.
"Reverse-Speak the, Shirasagi" as known also.
Anything through slice to ability its for known is that Slayer the, Namakura have I may?
Here loner some like hanging me leave and me ignore don't, man hey.
Problem a be could this.
Anyone to just around show to thing cheap a exactly isn't technique Seeker Reverse-Scale Shirasagi's Maniwa.
It see to want you do or?
By any chance...
Is your Reverse-Scale Seeker a technique where you can keep talking even after you've been split in two?
W-When did I-
G-Ginkaku!
Secret Move: Null Flash.
The tatami's stained with blood...
My dad actually told me about Inaba, so I've been looking forward to this.
Oh, the stories of Inaba you've heard from your father are already outdated.
The Inaba Desert has been rapidly expanding in the last five years.
It's covered the entire Tottori Domain.
Inaba isn't a habitable land anymore.
So what in the world is Uneri Ginkaku doing here?
I already told you.
He's the castle lord.
That's what I don't get.
What's the point of being the lord of a barren land?
Well, the shogunate had the same idea and sent him many messengers for a negotiation,
but not one man returned.
Refusal through killing, huh?
He might be affected by the poison of Shikizaki's sword,
or perhaps he has another reason.
So you don't know anything?
Didn't you specialize in using your brain?
It's all part of my strategy.
No need to ask.
Oh, I almost forgot.
We need to come up with a catchphrase.
A catchphrase?
Yep.
For whom?
For you.
You see...
I wrote a bit about your fight last month.
Oh, a report or something, right?
Yeah, so I finished that ninja guy off with style, just like you asked.
Yes, about that...
I didn't exactly see how you defeated the ninja, so I couldn't write about it.
What? After I went through the trouble of doing what you asked me to do?
Don't blame me.
I can't write what I didn't see.
But that's not really a big deal.
I'm sure we'll have more chances later.
But you see, Shichika...
When I was putting the retrieval of Kanna into words, I noticed something extremely important.
What did you notice?
Your character is weak.
I thought I'd act surprised to go with the flow.
What's wrong with that?
You're so naive.
Were you born yesterday?
You could say I know everything except sword skills.
Your self-centered way of going about things is also a problem.
When I was writing the report, I couldn't help but make Maniwa Komori stand out more.
I revised it over and over again, but he still stood out more than you.
Ultimately, I couldn't give you more spotlight than Komori.
Hey, wait a minute.
When I read over the finalized copy in the end,
I could only get the impression of you as a half-naked idiot.
Hey, just wait a minute, Togame.
I can't win in individuality against a guy who can take out a sword from his body.
I already won in battle, so isn't that good enough?
Well, losing in battle is out of the question, but I also can't have you lose as a person.
Your human nature simply lacks appeal.
Is being considerate a foreign idea to you?
I can't write a bewitching report by being considerate.
What in the world is she fighting against?
For instance, there are other ninjas with stronger individuality.
Out of the ones I know...
There's a ninja called Shirasagi the Reverse-Speak who always speaks in reverse.
What's the point of doing that?
He's doing the best he can to be unique.
Is that what it takes to be a ninja?
Those Maniwani.
Maniwani?
Oh, you shortened it.
"Maniwa ninja clan" is a tongue twister.
I'd bite my tongue saying it.
Maniwani, huh?
Is that weird?
No, I like it!
It's cute. Let's use it.
All right.
Good work.
You said something smart for the first time.
This brings the readers more intimately into the world of the report.
It must be tough to write those reports.
Now you understand?
The Maniwani are like a hotspot of individuality though,
so having them as your goal or telling you to ultimately achieve their level is also quite unfair.
But Shichika, I'd still like you to put in some effort.
That's how it is, so I'd like for us to think of a catchphrase for you.
Is it really necessary to do that?
Yeah.
It's like saying "this guy's something special" and leaves a stronger impression on the readers.
I don't really mind being normal...
Well, I do.
What if the reader gets bored and stops reading midway?
Do reports really need to be interesting?
Oh, I just remembered!
Sabi Hakuhei, the prodigy swordsman, also has a pretty cool catchphrase.
Even though it doesn't feel right to compliment the guy who betrayed me,
what should be recognized should be recognized.
Well, I'll hear it for reference.
"I shall have you fall for me."
I'd cry if I had to say something like that.
Oh, wait.
There's a phrase I say pretty often.
Well, that "what a pain" kind of thing.
Cheerio!
Have you no brain?
Why would you want to use such a dull phrase to describe yourself?
And put yourself in the shoes of the one who has to write about such a boring character.
What if I can't get motivated enough to finish the report?
Right...
Besides, if I depict the image of you collecting the swords while constantly repeating "what a pain,"
it's like you're being backward about doing this.
So you want me to do this enthusiastically?
That's exactly right.
Anyway, I just can't have people thinking that I'm forcing you to help me retrieve the swords.
And you said I'm self-centered?
Still, I can't just think of one on the spot.
Not to worry.
I thought you'd say that, so I came up with some beforehand.
Though I'm sure you have a preference, so you have the right to pick one out of the candidates.
That's a rather pushy right.
I will if I find one I like.
Of course, but don't worry.
I've found you the coolest remarks to use.
"Since you know, God loves me most."
Since...
Wait, wasn't your excuse for your lack of strength something about being intelligent?
What do you mean?
I thought of this catchphrase precisely because I am intelligent.
True, it's a pretty devilish idea.
It's basically something you'd say to provoke your opponent.
It shows that you're out of their league, or rather it signifies your absolute confidence.
By stating this, it doesn't just show your omnipotence but also sounds like you won with ease.
I think that just makes me a jerk.
I'd actually have it easier if you were a bit of a jerk.
People's opinions of me would increase if I held the reins to someone wild and cocky.
In that sense, you're much too nice.
This girl...
"It looks to me like you want to be banished for good."
Why would I want to say something like that with pride,
when I myself was banished for twenty years?
Are you dumb?
That's exactly why it's convincing and works.
I don't want to be convincing about that.
You're such a picky man.
Is this unproductive conversation going to last the entire walk?
The rest are...
Well they're not that interesting, but...
"Though by then, you'll already be shredded to pieces."
I think that's it.
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
Let's go with that.
I like that one.
"Though by then, you'll already be shredded to pieces."
Yeah, it sounds really good.
Oh, is that fine?
That was unexpected.
It wasn't exactly what I would've recommended out of the candidates,
but I guess it was still one of my proud works.
Yeah, I'm really surprised.
It fits me too well.
Oh, is that so?
I got the idea from your super ultimate move, Shichika Hachiretsu.
R-Really...
Yep. Feel free to thank me.
Thank you, oh so very much.
I see, I see.
It's certainly great that you like it.
But thanks to your pickiness, the conversation lasted much longer than I expected.
Though we aren't in any rush yet.
I'm sure we'll get there by sunset at our current pace.
Yeah, though by then, you'll already be shredded to pieces.
Cheerio!
Don't you use your brain at all?
This is kinda hard.
Yeah.
And about the "cheerio" I've been saying.
It's my catchphrase.
I-I see.
I didn't even notice.
"Cheerio" is a word that's popular in the Satsuma Domain of Kyushu, and it's a shout that gives you a little energy.
It's more of a culture thing than a dialect thing.
It's not that I have any deep connection with Kyushu,
but don't you think it's rather cute to say "cheerio" to increase your vigor?
It has a sort of synergy with my outer appearance, so I think it's a promising idea.
Once I turn in the report...
As we all know, the actual word used in the Satsuma Domain to increase vigor is "chest,"
and the "cheerio" Togame refers to is a foreign word that signifies farewell.
The moment she realizes this fact and gets into some embarrassing chaos...
is a story not to be told until many months have passed.
Hakuhei!
That sword will be mine!
So you are yet another wanderer, possessed by this sword's power.
Here I come!
I shall have you fall for me.
You're... so cool.
Hold on for a minute.
You're walking too fast.
Oh, sorry.
I'm not used to walking with people.
Your legs are probably heavy because you're wearing so much.
Quiet!
Don't call a woman heavy so casually.
No, you're really light.
But isn't it difficult to move like that?
Quiet again, you!
Girls have different muscles for fashion.
Girls have an organ for fashion?
It's a delicate organ men would never understand.
Well, I don't care about fashion,
but I think clothes just weigh you down.
I've already given up on putting some clothes on your upper-body,
but don't go naked with your lower-body as well.
I wouldn't want to travel with a freak.
Don't worry.
I actually like these clothes you bought me.
They're easy to move in, and easy to fight in.
Are those two things different?
Yeah, more or less.
So where is this Gekoku Castle?
It's going to be night soon.
Wouldn't that only be more trouble for you?
You're right.
Sleeping out in the desert would ruin my fashion.
Is that the problem?
Who the hell left something here?
He's a Maniwani...
Maniwa Shirasagi!
Wait, a castle?
How?
It's a camouflage caused by the air's mirage.
We couldn't see the castle until we got this close.
That's the Gekoku Castle of the Inaba Desert.
Difficult to attack and easy to defend.
Many people don't know about this, but it's a rather famous fact among some.
It really blew my mind.
Forgive me.
I thought I'd blow your mind.
Seeing how this guy was abandoned out here...
If I recall correctly, Komori said there's a competition among the twelve heads of Maniwani.
A competition to retrieve the twelve perfected swords of Shikizaki Kiki.
What probably happened was Shirasagi discovered that Uneri Ginkaku of Gekoku Castle possessed Namakura, the Slayer,
and came to seek him out.
He ended up getting killed instead.
What an unbelievable end for a Maniwani head.
I also defeated a Maniwani head.
In your case, you got lucky.
Well... I'll try to stay optimistic.
The Maniwani who got here before us failed to retrieve the sword.
This isn't exactly a bad thing, from a certain point of view.
If Shirasagi had successfully retrieved Namakura, our trip here would've been in vain.
I see, that's optimistic.
But since this guy failed at his attempt, the castle owner's probably on alert now.
He may have already left in the worst case scenario.
That's unlikely.
Uneri Ginkaku never moved away from this land despite the entirety of Inaba becoming a desert.
Besides, seeing what happened to Shirasagi, Uneri has absolute confidence in his skill.
He wouldn't make an escape when the act signifies unpreparedness as a swordsman.
It sounds like he's a tougher opponent than I had imagined.
Maybe we can come back another time.
Impossible.
As the Maniwa ninjas have begun to move rather quickly, I have no time to be loitering around.
Shichika, I'm actually relieved right now.
Since Maniwa Shirasagi did us a favor by being the appetizer,
the report I write will have a bit of a flare.
The Maniwa ninja clan betrayed us,
but we retrieved a sword from the swordsman who slew one of the betrayers.
Doesn't that sound thrilling?
Moreover, now I won't have to write about a rather annoying ninja who talks in reverse.
Besides, Shichika...
surely you're not telling me to write about a cowardly act of backing out when the stage is perfectly set, are you?
I see.
That's optimistic.
That's why I fell in love with you.
It isn't safe to walk in front of me.
I'm doing the fighting, right?
Or do you plan to fight Uneri Ginkaku first?
Are you dumb?
You very well know my fighting ability.
Defeating me makes poking a hole through a paper wall a great feat.
You don't have to boast about it...
Okay.
It looks like you seem to have misunderstood a little, so I'll tell you just in case.
We're not really trying to steal anything.
The point of this isn't to enter the territory swinging our swords, then retrieve it.
We need to follow procedures and try to negotiate.
So...
Is this kind of like following government procedures?
That's an acceptable understanding for this case.
If that's what you're doing, what am I here for?
Anyone who chooses to take in Shikizaki's swords' poison is bound to be a madman.
So you don't expect anything to be negotiable at all, right?
Even so, it's still possible.
For instance, if the holder of the sword was a good person,
what would you do?
You're allowed to kill anyone with the shogunate at your back,
but that doesn't mean we can cut anyone as we please.
Now, let's keep moving.
Well, this looks undoubtedly suspicious.
It means something's here, right?
Hey, wait!
Don't open it so carelessly!
Hey!
You're Uneri Ginkaku, correct?
I am Togame, a strategist and the War Campaign Overseer under the direct authority of Shogun Yanari of the Owari Shogunate,
I believe that sword you have is Namakura, the Slayer.
Am I wrong?
Shut up.
Yes, I am Uneri Ginkaku, but don't speak so loudly.
Well, my apologies.
So what does such a person from the shogunate want with me?
Would you kindly surrender that sword to us?
Of course, we'll give you a reward.
We'll do as much as we can as the shogunate.
A little while ago,
some fake ninja guy came and told me almost the same thing.
What's with him?
Is he your friend?
He's no friend of ours.
We aren't at all like that filthy ninja.
We seek a formal trade.
Of course, we believe to understand the value of that single sword you hold.
It's completely irreplaceable, regardless of circumstances.
However, Uneri.
Couldn't you make an exception for the shogunate, for the world and the nation?
Anyone who can say something like "for the world and the nation" isn't even half decent.
Even you must not be planning to spend the rest of your life in this castle.
If you have an ambition, I believe I can help.
Both in the open, and in the shadows.
Are you saying you'll take a ronin like me under your wing?
It's a welcoming idea,
but I've heard that there's a bounty on my head.
Of course.
I can also free you from that shackle.
I'll make your wildest dreams come true.
Hey, Uneri!
You weren't loud enough, and I couldn't hear you very well.
Could you come a little closer?
Besides, isn't it rude to talk to a swordsman across a threshold?
I don't know how important you are,
but it certainly doesn't look like you're asking for a favor.
You're certainly right.
Forgive my rudeness.
Kyotou style: Lily.
Ow...
What was that for?
Calm down.
How can I be calm after receiving a kick out of the blue, you dummy?!
I thought I was being abducted by aliens because I was being pulled by some invisible force!
That's quite the imagination...
The art of drawing?
I-If I weren't wearing as many layers, I would've split in two...
No, I think he would've missed your clothes completely.
What a surprise.
That's the first time someone evaded my Null Flash using this sword.
I'm the one who's surprised.
I've heard that sword drawing techniques are the ultimate form of kenjutsu,
but I didn't think they were that fast.
Well then, your surprise and my surprise make us even.
Uneri!
Do you know what you just tried to do?
Well, what about you?
You brought your strong elder brother with you.
You were ultimately planning to take my sword by force, weren't you?
"Elder brother"?!
Do I look like his little sister to you?!
What part of me says anything about that?
My ancestors opposed the lord of this land, and even the former shoguns, to keep this sword from leaving their hands.
If I gave it to you just like that, they'll take me for a clown right from their graves.
Are you afraid of losing that sword?
That "Null Flash" move...
You can't get that speed with any other sword, can you?
Are you afraid of losing that sword?
What if I am?
Nothing.
I just thought that's the limit to swordsmen who use swords.
Aren't you a swordsman yourself?
I am.
Without a doubt.
Really.
Then words aren't necessary between swordsmen.
If you want this sword, come and get it without a word.
I, on the other hand, will simply resist without a word.
Is that stubbornness?
It's pride.
You're probably in a good mood from protecting that woman,
but that last move there wasn't at full power.
The speed of Null Flash at its peak...
surpasses even light.
Wanna go?
Togame.
I have something I want to confirm.
Is that okay?
Hey...
Just a little strategy meeting.
We'll be right back, so just take a nap or something.
I hope to see it when we get back.
Your fastest Null Flash.
Close the door when you go.
Oh, one more thing.
You haven't told me your name yet.
What is it?
I'm Yasuri Shichika, the seventh generation master of the Kyotou style.
I bit my tongue...
Don't look so grumpy.
You'd be in two if I hadn't done that.
Me don't look grumpy!
"Me"?
I-I don't look grumpy!
You say childish things sometimes. How old are you, exactly?
You're older than me, right?
Why does that matter?
Anyway Shichika, what was it that you wanted to confirm?
I didn't see any reason to stop the fight at that point.
I wanted to know whether he'd accept my request.
Whether he'd accept it?
Basically, whether he'd come after us as we left the building.
But he didn't.
Well, I guess so.
The moment you crossed the threshold and entered the room,
he swung his sword.
In other words, so long as we stay out of that room, he won't come attacking us.
That room, which extends a certain distance, is convenient for attacking the enemy.
I see.
Even Maniwa Shirasagi had no choice but to go in from the front.
That room is completely Uneri Ginkaku's territory.
Then we must simply draw him out of that room.
Do you have an idea?
First, you enter that room.
Okay, I go in.
Then you become the target of Null Flash and get split in two.
He wouldn't leave a corpse right there.
So he'd come outside to throw you away like he did with Maniwa Shirasagi.
Then what?
That's where I get him.
Cheerio!
That means I'll be split in two!
Yeah, so I don't think we can really follow that plan.
That's a given!
So I'll give up on drawing him out, but I still have a plan, Togame.
I hope I stay intact in your other plan.
If it's a man who must be fought fair and square, then fight him fair and square.
Shichika, if that's your conclusion, I'm going to get mad.
Wait, you've been mad from the very beginning.
Don't start!
So, in order to continue winning after today, I can't simply win.
I can't win by luck like I did against Komori.
I never thought I'd hear you say something serious.
"Protect the swords."
And "protect you," right?
W-Well if you understand that, don't come up with a plan where I'd die in the first place!
So, I'd like you to stay behind me.
For safety, just in case.
I hope you understand that I don't have any strategy to protect your back.
That's not why.
Shichika...
Well...
I can't really say it well, but...
I'd like you to do that.
Basically, I'm saying those with something to protect are strong.
Kyotou style, huh?
A martial art based on kenjutsu.
There's nothing to gain for a swordsman who abandons his sword.
What a wicked style...
Oh well.
It's nothing to worry about.
I simply protect this castle and this sword.
That's all.
Everyone ran away from this desert.
They all abandoned their home.
Perhaps if I weren't the last one here, I also could have left Inaba...
No.
I never had that choice.
Wandering wasn't an option.
Perhaps it's obstinacy toward this land and this sword...
And it may also be a delusional conviction.
Swordsmen need something to protect.
Without that, they cannot fight.
Hey.
Did you wait long?
Yeah.
So, did you come up with a way to counter my Null Flash?
That's a little iffy.
Oh.
Does Kyotou style have a counter for sword drawing techniques?
Well, with your level of sword mastery, I think it'll work.
The success rate for this technique goes up as the speed of my opponent's sword goes up.
Kyotou style, seventh stance: Iris.
What's with that stance that clearly shows you're charging in?
That's your counter plan?
I seem to be taken as a joke.
Kyotou style...
An unworthy opponent...
You idiot!
He's belittling you!
Oh, whatever.
Well, now...
On your mark, get set, go!
Three steps until range.
One...
Two...
Three! Null Flash!
Kyotou style: Rose!
Did you do it?
No, it was too shallow.
I'll recognize your diversion with the footsteps.
I was slicing through an illusion that wasn't even there.
But...
What the hell was with that weak-ass blow?!
What does he mean?
Rose worked...
But I landed it halfheartedly.
I lost a bit to his sword pressure.
Shoot.
This happened because of his lack of experience.
Shichika-
Don't move!
Don't get out of my back.
You fool!
I can't do that now that your plan failed!
What a surprise...
Luck doesn't happen twice in a row.
I'm wide awake now, Mr. Kyotou style.
I haven't felt this good since the moment I was born.
Then you're welcome, and good morning.
And good night, maybe?
I know very well that it was something incredible.
But don't start thinking the same trick will work twice.
Injuring him was a bad idea.
Null Flash Alteration: Quintet.
Five strikes...
Now it won't matter whether you slow down or speed up a little.
It'll overcome such a minor timing error.
Is that your secret move?
This?
No, no, not at all.
What happened?
He cut himself.
What for?
This is the secret to Uneri Kinkaku's Ten Thousand Slayer, Kyotou style master.
Look.
By filling the scabbard with blood and covering the blade with it,
I can increase the speed in which I unsheathe.
By significantly dropping the friction between the blade and the scabbard,
Null Flash reaches super speed.
That is the ultimate secret move limited to Namakura, the Slayer!
The more I cut, the faster it becomes.
I got an idea!
Shichika, this is when we should strategically fall back!
He'll die from blood loss after some time.
Denied.
It's a way to win!
That isn't winning at all.
Didn't I tell you that we can't win by coincidence?
I gotta say, you're really cool.
Seeing you makes me embarrassed for hiding my ultimate move.
I'm done hiding things now.
I'll show you the entirety of Kyotou style.
Let's go.
Oh, by the way...
I'm a little curious about something, so I'd like to ask, miss.
You said you would've granted my wish if I had given you this sword, right?
Y-Yeah...
Then...
Would you have been able to restore Inaba in return for giving you this sword?
No, that's impossible.
Tottori Domain is already a forsaken land to the shogunate.
Even if it weren't, there's no way to restore an area that has become a desert.
I see.
Then I wasn't wrong in swinging at you.
That's a relief.
So...
Why do you do this?
I don't know.
Is it pride, like you said earlier?
I don't know about that either.
That's just something I randomly spouted.
Don't take it seriously.
I think...
I just wanted to protect something.
I wanted to, but these were the only things I could protect.
I see.
Then here I go.
Yeah.
Null Flash is ready to go, no matter what moment.
I'll show you a Null Flash that surpasses the speed of light.
And if you really do have an ultimate move,
show me what you've been hiding.
Yeah, I will.
Though by then, you'll already be shredded to pieces.
On your mark, get set, go!
Null Flash Alteration: Dectet!
Gyafun!
Everything in here reaches your Null Flash?
I don't think so!
You can't pull it off on a guy right above you, can you?
Fuck you, Kyotou style master!
Kyotou style, seventh technique: Flower Storm!
Hey, where are we going next?
Hey...
Hey, Togame.
Don't ignore me.
You've been ignoring me since yesterday.
Did you get hurt when I kicked you?
Shut up!
Don't talk to me so casually when I'm mad!
Goodness, I never thought you asked me to stand behind you to be used as a wall to kick off of!
Oh, that's what you're mad about.
No, I'm not!
If my first combination of Iris and Rose had worked, it would've been over.
You were really just for safety.
You could've told me so in the beginning!
Instead of saying things like "those with something to protect are strong" as if you were saying you cared for me.
Sorry.
That was just me saying random things.
Random things?!
Those with something to protect are strong.
Through this battle, Shichika learned something.
That the saying wasn't just a reason to live,
but that some people need something to protect in order to live.
Katanagatari.
The excitement in store for this month ends here with a curtain fall.
Now that I remember, you haven't seen the blade of Namakura, right?
Here.
No, that's all right.
In the end, I couldn't follow Ginkaku's Null Flash with my eyes.
So, I think that's all there is to it.
I see.
Hey, what's going to happen to Inaba now?
And the Gekoku Castle?
Nothing.
That area isn't even under shogunate jurisdiction.
It'll simply rot away.
Though it'll definitely remain for much longer than you and I, perhaps even a thousand years.
But, it is no longer a castle.
I see.
Perhaps it signifies that no swordsman or sword can overcome nature.
I guess that's what it is in the end.
I guess so.
But you know, Togame.
Uneri's final words were pretty cool.
They weren't simply cool, but they also really portrayed his character.
Would you also call that a catchphrase?
That's a little different.
That's what you'd say as you fall.
What you'd say as you die.
What you'd say in your final moments.
Perhaps we could refer to it as a will.
Unlike catchphrases, you're only allowed to say it once in your life, before you depart to the underworld.
I see.
Does it bother you?
The words you say in your final moments will indeed be something much more effective than a catchphrase.
Precisely because it's something you'd only say once.
However, Shichika.
You're not given the right to that one time.
So don't even think about what to say for those words.
Finally, I can rest in peace.
Though by then, you'll already be shredded to pieces.
It isn't one of the better ideas, in my opinion,
but since Shichika likes it, that's the one we'll go with.
Now Shichika will stand out a little more, despite his dullness.
Oh, I think I'll also give that reverse-speak a try.
Of authority direct the under Overseer Campaign War and strategist the, Togame...
I can't do it!
Next time, on Katanagatari: Tsurugi, the Thousand Blades
Cheerio!