Wrong!
That ain't even close!
What are you talking about?!
I played it exactly right!
There wasn't any swing !
If you play it without feelin', it ain't jazz to me!
Ricchan, do you know the name of the tune he was playing on the piano?
Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers' "Moanin'."
doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
My aunt's gone grocery shopping for dinner.
I've got one hour to make it or break it.
Dissonant chords...
Syncopation and a unique accent...
I thought I understood the distinctive features of jazz in my head,
but reproducing them is proving to be extremely difficult.
This guy doesn't get jazz at all!
And he's got no sense for it.
Dammit!
No matter what it takes, I'm gonna show him up!
I want to master this as soon as possible
and then perform it in front of him and Ricchan!
Y-You win...
Kaoru-san, that was wonderful...
As if...
Well, well. Nishimi-kun...
You sure look like you're in a good mood.
Where ya goin'?
Don't make a fuss.
That's not true!
Ricchan?
What's wrong?
Cut it out! Let me go!
What did I ever do to you?
It's my neck, is all.
These days, I've got a crick in my neck that just won't quit,
an' it's puttin' me in the worst mood.
So I thought havin' a little fun like this would brighten my day.
Other than that...
...you've kind of been gettin' on my nerves lately.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
He's in the kendo club, so you'd better not resist.
Sentaro!
There's trouble! Come quick!
Let's see...
How can we entertain ourselves?
How about splitting a watermelon?
D-Don't...
We can do better than that.
What do you say we pants 'im?!
Now there's a good idea.
D-Don't...
Don't move.
Keep nice an' quiet.
Students from the girls' school come home this way too,
so this'll give them a good show.
Too much momentum...
Hey! You still alive?
Hey, when this jerk wakes up,
tell 'im that no real man gangs up on a weakling...
Wait, it's you, Bon?!
W-Well, sorry about that!
A-Are you okay, Yamaoka-kun?
Y-Your front tooth is...
Why are you guys just standing there?
I don't care how you do it.
I just want you to kill that guy!
Oh, what's this?
We're gonna play a game like "monkey in the middle"?
Oh, no... At this rate...
R-Ricchan! What are you...
Sentaro will take care of them,
so get away!
Huh? Clearly, you boys ain't used to scrappin'!
I look pathetic.
Ricchan literally caught me with my pants down.
And on top of that, she rescued me.
Ricchan, would you hold on to my glasses for me?
Take this!
I think I'll pay you back for knocking out my front tooth!
What the hell?
Is he dead?
You little twerp!
Get 'im!
Alright!
Now it's startin' to get interesting!
Ow!
Well? You up for some more?
I-I'm gonna see to it that everyone in class gives you the cold shoulder!
Huh?
You an' me are in the same class?
Can't remember seein' this guy...
B-Be prepared!
Huh? My neck feels better.
Kaoru-san, your forehead is bleeding.
Are you okay?
Don't worry 'bout his forehead.
Are your... fingers okay?
Huh? He's actually looking out for me?
I'm home.
Oh, you took another pounding, huh?
Somebody's waiting for you.
Go on downstairs.
Could it be Jun-nii?!
Come on!
Why is the squirt beat up too?
He was in a fight.
Jun-nii!
Hey!
Sen-bou, you've been gettin' rowdy again?
Yeah, well, today wasn't much of a fight.
Well, it's good to see you're in fighting form.
So, who's this guy?
He's my buddy.
Huh. Cool.
An odd couple, huh?
Yeah!
Actually, we're not friends...
Ah, well...
Say, is he your brother, Ricchan?
No, Jun-nii-chan is our neighbor.
He's going to a university in Tokyo...
Ritsuko...
Mind the store for just one tune.
Dad, you always say "just one tune",
but then you don't come up for two hours!
It's not every day that Junichi comes back to town, right?
Ricchan, I'm asking you too.
Next time, I'll treat you to a cream soda at our shop.
Throw in a choux à la crème?
Sure.
Alright! We've got us a deal!
Let's get started!
Wh-What?
A live session...
Bon, get over there!
Me?
I can't!
Just make some noise, that's all!
What are you so jittery for?!
Don't sweat the details. Just jump in!
Huh? So you've only been playing jazz for two weeks?
That's amazing.
It was all over the place,
but you got the mood.
You've played piano for a while?
Y-Yeah, kind of...
How about coming over here from now on to practice?
He'll come every day even without being told, right?
Well, I have to get to work.
Thank you, Ricchan.
Oh, that's right, Jun-nii.
What's the name of that record you were tellin' me about?
Oh, the Elvin Jones one?
Yeah, that's it. "Tommy" something...
"Flanagan."
Maybe it's upstairs.
The two of us are alone.
Um, say...
Ricchan, what do you usually do on your days off?
Oh, you mean with summer vacation coming up?
Yeah, right.
I was thinking maybe
we could do our homework together.
Sure!
I bet I could make real progress working on it with you, Kaoru-san.
How's next Sunday?
Would 11 work?
Sure, of course!
I know! Let's meet up behind the church.
Hold on. I'll draw you a map.
That's right.
Summer vacation...
Up until now, I've spent my summer vacations alone in my room
with far too much time on my hands.
What should I do?
I have so many things to look forward to
that I can't wrap my head around it.
Looks like I'm a little early.
Oh, church on Sunday morning...
Ricchan...
...is a Christian?
No way.
Him too?
Kaoru-san!
Sorry to make you wait!
That's okay. Well, should we...
Let's go!
Huh?
Wait a second!
This is how we're going to the library?
Or rather, why is he with us?
Kashimae Pier
BUS STOP
Um... What about the library?
It's so hot today.
Doesn't it feel much better at the ocean?
Sentaro agreed this was the way to go too!
Ricchan... I meant for this to be a date.
Hey!
I rented a boat!
Hop in!
How did it come to this?
Why'd it end up being the three of us?
Bon, give me a bite of that, would ya?
What's with the face?
Doesn't the rower get any kind of reward for his services?
Sentaro, you can finish this.
No, he can't!
Why not?
Well, uh... Fine!
Here, eat it!
One bite, right?
Ricchan, do you always have a cross on too?
Nope. I have a rosary,
but it's not something you're supposed to wear around your neck.
Our priest says Sentaro is special, though...
Rikko...
You don't have to tell him all that.
For just a second there, the tension was thick enough to cut with a knife.
Or was it just my imagination?
Wahoo!
Kaoru-san, aren't you going to swim?
We came all this way, so let's take a dip!
The thing is, I didn't bring along a bathing suit.
Neither did Sentaro. He's just wearing his undies.
Let's swim, Kaoru-san!
Yeah. Okay!
Hey! Rikko, hurry up and dive in!
R-Right...
What are you bein' bashful about?
You're flat as a washboard!
Last time we went swimmin', you had nothin' but your slip on!
Oh, for goodness' sake! That was when we were in elementary school!
Don't say weird things like that in front of Kaoru-san!
Enough, Sentaro!
Ricchan...
Could it be you...
Rikko, pinch your nose!
Hey!
Alley-oop!
Ricchan!
You too, Bon!
Geez! You're such a meanie, Sentaro!
It feels good, doesn't it?!
He really is a jerk, isn't he?
Say, Kaoru-san...
Why do you keep swimming in circles?
This is the only way I know how to swim with my head out of the water.
Kaoru-san, you're a funny guy!
She laughed.
Why do I feel so happy when she smiles?
Oh... I feel like I could do anything for that smile.
Hey, you two look like you're havin' fun.
Let me join in!
Forget it!
Ricchan, let's get away!
Kaoru-san, wait for me!
Hey, what gives?!
Why are you swimmin' away?!
Oh, I only wish that we could keep going...
That I could take you away from here...
Let's trade places.
I'll take over the rowing.
It's pretty hard, y'know. And on top of that...
Just let me do it!
Dammit...
Wanna switch, Bon?
No, it's not about strength. It's about technique!
And I think I'm getting the hang of it!
Not that I'm complainin'...
...but you've been takin' us in circles.
Cool.
You took us to a completely different beach.
It's fine.
The sun is already setting anyway,
so if we tell the boat rental guy what happened,
he'll come by and pick it up.
Come on, miss, have a little fun with us.
Don't be so stuck-up.
No! Leave me alone!
We ain't gonna hurt ya!
Let go of me!
We got a car, so let us take you for a ride!
Come on!
Hey. The lady ain't willin'.
So how about gettin' your mitts off her?
What's that?! Who the hell are you?
Actin' so tough...
What, are you tryin' to be a hero?!
Hey, that guy is East High's Kawabuchi!
East High... You're...
Kawabuchi?!
Th-This time, I'll let you off the hook.
You saved me.
Thank you.
It happened in an instant.
I didn't realize what had just taken place.
But when it comes to falling in love, you don't need a reason or time.
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and remained as it was back then.