Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
along with my food!
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
but sorry for finding out!
gomennasai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
Getting lost in silly conversations
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Chatting about love and relationships
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Say, why can't you make friends?
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
You came right out and asked?!
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You two never quit!
iitai houdai ne
The three leaves are on a rampage,
mitsuba ga daibousou
and there's nobody who can stop them!
dare ni mo tomerarenai
It's the day to chow down
on chicken and cake!
You're acting strangely...
Huh?
Both of you.
You're wonderful, Miss Youko.
Cat paws are amazing!
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
issei no mae mitekou
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
mae mae miteru
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
Three heads are better than one!
sannin yoreba monju no chie
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
Everything's going my way,
hora going my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
susumesou my way
Let's go full steam ahead
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
I'm living the best days of my life,
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Futaba
Lady Youko
Teru
I'm sure that this is a
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
That's a pretty Christmas tree!
It is!
It's finally the season, huh?
It certainly is.
The season of
expensive heating bills!
That's not what I meant...
It sure has gotten cold.
I couldn't get
out of bed this morning.
That's it!
Huh?
I can just wrap myself
in blankets when I'm at home.
That way,
I'll save money on heating!
I see...
Miss Youko!
I'll buy a heater for you!
Excuse me...
Oh, apologies. Here you go.
Miss Youko!
Huh?
Anyway, my point was that
the Christmas season is here!
Oh, I see.
Christmas is an important day!
It's the day to chow down
on chicken and cake!
That's not what Christmas is about.
Then what else is it for,
here in Japan?
I guess it has become a day
for chicken and cake here.
Hey, let's have a party!
How about it?
My, what a wonderful idea.
All right!
I'm gonna chow down
on chicken and cake!
I told you, that's not
what Christmas is about...
A party sounds like fun!
A Day to Chow Down
on Chicken and Cake
Miss Youko!
Oh, Futaba.
Morning!
Is Hayama at school already?
Yup, she had
some class rep duties.
She sounds busy.
Such a model student.
The teachers think she's an angel.
Oh yeah, about the Christmas party,
I'll be baking the cake too.
My, how wonderful.
You'll host the party,
Hayama will bring snacks, and...
Were you making
Christmas plans just now?
Yeah, the three of us
are having a party.
I have some information
that might be of interest.
Huh?
Christmas also happens to be...
...Teru's birthday!
Wha...?
What?!
What's up with you two?
N-Nothing! Right, Miss Youko?
Q-Quite right, Futaba!
Hayama's birthday is on Christmas.
That means...
A devil was born on a holy night?
I never could've imagined!
It's fine if you're a fallen angel—
I mean, it doesn't matter
when you were born!
Quite right!
All part of God's plan—
I mean, the Devil's plan?
What are you talking about?
You're acting strangely...
Huh?
Both of you.
Oh yeah!
Miss Youko said she had
something for my ears only.
What? I said no such thing.
Come on!
Wait, F-Futaba!
I'm thinking about it too much,
and it's got me nervous.
Me too.
What should we do on Christmas?
Hmm...
I know!
Let's make our Christmas party
a birthday party for Hayama.
Hmm? What do you mean?
We'll tell her it's a Christmas party,
and she'll be surprised
when it's actually for her birthday!
Oh! She'll fall right into our trap!
It's not supposed to be a trap...
Anyway, let's keep it a secret
from Hayama.
Understood.
What are you doing, Sonobe?
Passing out
Christmas cake flyers.
I already told you
to stop doing that here.
That's too bad.
If our sales went up,
I might be able to give you a raise.
What?!
N-No!
Go home this instant!
Bakeries must be busy
at this time of year.
That's right.
Cake orders have been coming in,
and we're making stollen.
I've been helping.
What?! You're making cakes too?
I help out with measuring
and sprinkling things on top.
Yes, it takes longer with more people,
but it's helpful at this time of year.
Of course I'm helpful.
Who do you think I am?
You're wonderful, Miss Youko!
Man, what's with this conversation?
So does that mean
you'll be working on Christmas?
You may have that day off.
What?
You've finally made friends.
For the sake of Hayama's birthday party,
I'm willing to work my fingers to the bone.
Sonobe...
Well, she's more useful
than a cat's paw.
Of course I am!
Seriously, what's with
this conversation?
Wait just a minute!
Cat paws are amazing!
H-Hayama!
What are...?
I'm curious.
What do you two have to say
that I can't hear?
I'm sorry.
We've been hiding
something from you.
Sonobe!
Actually,
I'm planning on making cakes
shaped like bears and cats.
What?!
Wow!
I was keeping it a secret
because I wanted to surprise you.
You can keep as many
secrets like that as you want!
We're off the hook somehow.
Sonobe got us out of this one.
I love Christmas.
The streets are abuzz
with excitement.
And picking out presents is fun!
Which one is better?
Pink?
The red one's good too.
It took an hour to decide,
and I ended up with both.
I splurged and finished off
all of this month's allowance.
Yeah, that's the plan
for the big day.
This is my first time
throwing a birthday party for a friend.
Anyway, let's have a great Christmas,
since it is Hayama's birthday.
What?!
Hey, wait!
Nishiyama?
What did you say?
What was that
about Hayama's birthday?
Oh, you overheard?
Hayama's birthday
is on Christmas.
What?!
We're throwing her a surprise party,
so keep it a secret.
I'll buy you a little something.
Please do.
Yay!
I've been wanting
the new card game!
I... I can't believe it.
Are you excited?
Yeah!
Nishiyama?
What's wrong, Nishiyama?
Christmas...
Huh?
Christmas is...
Oh, you do like Christmas.
This year—
I don't care...
What?
There's nothing
to celebrate anyway.
Hmm? What's gotten into you?
You love Christmas.
Let's have a Christmas party.
No.
Maybe I'll just
eat curry on Christmas.
No way!
You're having
a Christmas party with me!
Come on, get up!
Let's go buy a cake.
for the holiday
Come back again tomorrow
I'm heading out.
Oh, wait, Teru!
Bring this along.
I made it for you.
I stewed it overnight!
Have fun at the party!
Hayama
Um, where should I put this?
Hurry, hurry!
Hayama's coming soon!
She's here!
Hello.
Hayama!
Happy birthd—
Oh, you scared me!
I thought you were going to shoot me.
Shoot you?!
You had a pretty intense expression
on your face just now!
Happy
Birthday
Teru
My sister told you, huh?
I didn't want you to feel like you had
to celebrate with me, so I didn't say anything.
That's why you didn't tell us?
I'm pretty much used to my birthday
being secondary to Christmas celebrations anyway.
That's so sad.
Thanks, though.
It's been years since
I've celebrated with friends.
All right then,
let's have some cake.
Thanks!
I helped too!
I measured and
sprinkled things on top.
Thanks, Miss Youko!
Oh, I brought something too...
...from my sister.
I'll have some!
Whoa!
Don't force yourself.
M-Miss Youko?
You can do it!
Miss Youko?
A-Amazing.
I-I feel like I could
run a whole marathon.
Miss Youko!
That was probably a mistake, huh?
Probably.
Cheer up already!
I can't stand knowing that Christmas
is defiled by Hayama's birthday.
Were you able
to enjoy your Christmas?
Hayama?!
It's also the day
I was brought into this world!
Apologize! Apologize to Christmas!
Why would I do that?
The masses abound
with joy at my nativity!
Apologize! Apologize already!
Hayama...
Apologize to Christmas!
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
It's the first snow of the winter...
...and it's already piled up so much.
Unusual weather.
But the snow
is really exhilarating!
We can't open unless
we clear the path, though.
That's right.
It's so cold!
And my back aches.
How can you...
How can you make
Miss Youko shovel snow?!
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
Sonobe, this snow
must be your doing!
You're the first
to accuse me of that.
It's still coming down.
That it is.
I wonder, though.
Will the snow
stop people from coming in?
Not necessarily.
Blizzards and typhoons exhilarate people
and make them want to go out.
Is that what happens?
I'll have some!
See?
Futaba.
You're having cake
on this cold and snowy day?
Yup. When I saw the snow,
it gave me a craving for it.
Ahh, one with
white whipped cream?
Tiramisu, chocolate ganache,
and opera cake, please!
Has all the snow melted by you?
Teru!
There's so much snow!
Let's go out!
No way.
What?!
The city's blanketed in white.
We've gotta enjoy it!
I just want to stay warm inside
on cold days like this.
Oh, come on!
Just for a little.
It's so great out!
Whoa, hey!
Ta-dah!
I made an igloo!
What?!
You made this by yourself?
I didn't know that was possible!
Isn't it amazing?
It's warm inside.
Here, take a look.
I'll bring something
for us to drink inside!
It really is warm in here.
How strange.
The snow is cold,
but the air isn't.
Teru?!
1 New Message
Kou Hayama
Teru's in trouble~~
Help!!
Received Mail
Oh, no!
Hayama got caught
in an avalanche in the garden!
The garden?!
I knew I should've stayed inside.
Teru!
Let's play.
Let's pl—
I told you...
I got a text saying
that you're in trouble.
...use the doorbell.
The snow's still coming down.
Yeah, it might keep snowing
for the rest of the year.
Miss Youko, what are you doing
for New Year's?
I have no plans.
Will you be on your own?
Yes.
That won't do!
You can't spend it alone!
I have nobody to spend it with.
Why don't the three of you
do something together?
Huh?
That is, of course, if Hayama
and Futaba agree to it.
Sounds good to me.
Me too.
It's lonely spending
New Year's by yourself.
Thank you both!
If that's the case,
you should have a pajama party.
Paja... what?
It's natural for girls
to have pajama parties.
At a recent conference,
it was shown that
more than eighty percent
have a pajama party by graduation.
What conference was that?
You'll remain
in the other twenty percent...
What? I'm the daughter
of the Nishikawa family!
I will host
a splendid pajama party.
Does that sound good?
Huh?
Well, sure.
In that case, we'll cook and have cake,
just like at our Christmas party—
Oh, pajama parties
are a little different.
We just lay around in our pajamas
talking about things.
What?
That counts as a party?
Do you have enough blankets
for us at your place?
Well, er...
So, what are we supposed to do?
Girls usually
talk about love, don't they?
Then let us begin.
I love rice!
I could eat it forever,
paired with fried cod roe!
I love cats! And dogs!
I can't decide between them!
Pajama... party...
Ah, I forgot; I made some snacks.
Oh, then I'll make some tea.
Miss Youko!
Are you oka—?
This is all wrong.
A real pajama party
has more squeals and giggles.
What are you
trying to do, Sonobe?
I'm not trying to do anything.
I just want Miss Youko
to live a normal high school girl's life.
What's that camcorder for?
To capture the memories.
Unbelievable.
My, my.
Well, I'm at least glad she's not
spending her New Year's alone.
Good morning, Hayama.
You mean...
...Happy New Year.
Oh. Happy New Year.
We got worked up
and fell asleep without realizing.
Yes, we did.
Food's almost ready!
Mom!
Dearest Mother!
There, there. We'll eat soon.
All right! Let's pound some mochi.
Pound mochi?!
Er...
What's this?
Oh, it's a mochi-pounding machine.
What?
Off
Steam
Pound
You said "pound mochi," so I thought
we'd be using a mortar and pestle.
As did I...
I asked for it for my birthday!
Wow!
Time to eat!
After a pajama party,
the high school girls eat mochi.
What a rare event.
Why do you have the camcorder out again?!
Uh-oh.
Yum, so good!
It's so fresh.
It really is delicious!
Yeah!
Soy bean flour, spicy, pan-fried with soy sauce,
edamame paste, fermented soybean, or walnut!
How many should we each have?
What?
How many each?
Mochi is a must-have on New Year's!
Eat as much as you want!
What?
We're not doing
an eating challenge!
H-Hey!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if it's turned black inside
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if I can't be extravagant
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
ryou ga ookutemo
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
sannin dakara tabechaou
I'm not wasting electricity at night
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Things that make me smile?
egao ni nareru mono
Food! Money! And things I can't say
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
Let's have fun and make silly memories
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
Will continue forever in just the same way
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
If you want to know the answer to one times three
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
Then come on over here
nee koko ni oide
An event in February?
That must be...
Festival of Broken Needles!
An event held in memorial
of broken needles.
Mainly in the Kanto region
It's an event
geared toward women.
Valenti—
Or the Bean-Throwing Festival!
Next
Time:
A Day to Chow Down
on Chocolate
Next
Time:
A Day to Chow Down
on Chocolate
Next
Time:
A Day to Chow Down
on Chocolate