Ryuu-chan...
Ryuu-chan!
H-Hey...
W-What?
You're okay?
Not hurt?
In-suke.
Yasuko...
You...
Raised Ryuuji-kun to be a big, fine boy.
Yeah...
I rai...
I raised him!
I...
"Had been in a terrible accident."
Well, Yacchan...
Ryuuji was...
After being completely tricked by the lie Taiga left on her answering machine...
Yasuko cried a lot.
Then Grandpa yelled at her a lot.
But...
It was like...
It's like...
Yacchan's a little kid.
A family is amazing.
Even though they haven't met for years...
They're still...
Mom, thanks!
It's because you keep spoiling her like that, that Yasuko—
Now, now... Don't be a meanie.
No, but you...
Yasuko must be tired too—
We're family, right?
Family...
Ryuuji-kun...
Take your bath before the water gets cold.
Yes, ma'am.
So you weren't married?
You heard?
Your papa went somewhere with another woman when I was pregnant with you.
Everyone told me to abort you.
But Yacchan really wanted to protect you.
No matter what.
But...
In the end, I couldn't protect you, and a lot of things fell apart...
Nothing's fallen apart.
Didn't Grandma say so?
"You raised him into a big, fine boy."
See?
I'm way bigger than you.
Be proud.
It was big.
When you were running, your back was really big.
So big, it was like you weren't the Ryuu-chan I knew.
I was scared.
But I was also a little happy.
Even so...
I was so afraid that you'd never come back that I...
So you decided to leave first?
Dummy.
I can't really talk about others...
But you can't get anything by running away.
Ryuu-chan.
I will become an adult.
Not in some place you can't see.
I'll do it right in front of you.
So...
Watch me.
Always...
Quit crying!
But...
Wh—
What's this?
Grandma said since we're going to get married anyway, why not be in the same room?
It was probably that kind of fuzzy logic that invited Yasuko's situation...
Yacchan laughed!
Yeah.
Hey, turn off the lights.
Why?
Just do it.
What is it?
So many stars.
Actually...
I was worried.
I thought, there's no way that running...
And getting married would work out.
But...
Just for a little while...
I wanted to dream that it would.
I felt like if I hadn't done something right then, everything would fall apart again.
Both you and Yasuko...
Nothing's fallen apart, right?
We can just start from here instead.
We don't have to run away to get married, we can do it right.
It's better to get everyone's blessing, right?
"Everyone" as in?
Grandpa, Grandma...
And your parents.
That might take some time...
It doesn't matter how long it takes.
We're going to be happy anyway, why not be happy with everyone?
That would be better.
For now...
Let's try it a little.
Look.
A veil.
Taiga...
I, Takasu Ryuuji, will...
How does it go?
Whatever, just make something up.
I can't just make up whatever!
Will take Aisaka Taiga as my wife—
Nevermind, I don't need a promise.
What?!
You're the one that said it!
Do you remember what you said a long time ago?
You said, "We're the tiger and dragon."
"Since a long time ago, we've always been thought of as equals."
That's why we'll always be by each other's side, without any kind of promises, right?
Tai—
Your eyes are bloodshot.
You're breathing hard.
Shut up.
Your lips are peeling.
It looks like it'd hurt if we kissed.
Like we're ever going to...
If we kissed...
I'm sure...
It'd hurt.
How was it?
Just as I imagined.
It was really rough, like a starving barren wasteland.
And...
It was really hot.
Hey, it's cold, so one more time...
Once more...
Somehow...
It feels weird.
Going, it was just the two of us.
But coming home, it's three people plus one.
Ryuuji, you were confident...
That Yacchan would come flying if we told a lie like that.
Then make up with Grandma and Grandpa.
It's not like I was confident.
I didn't think it would absolutely be okay, but I didn't think it would definitely be bad either.
I wonder why?
Maybe that's just how it is.
Maybe that's just how a family is.
I'm hungry!
Taiga-chan...
You're eating dinner at our place, right?
I...
Don't be shy.
We're a family of three.
Right?
I-In...
I forgot about you, Inko-chan...
Taiga?
Go ahead.
I'm going to change my clothes first.
But your parents will be in your apartment—
I'm going with you, too.
I got it.
Hurry up.
Tonight's your favorite, pork cutlets.
Mom?
Taiga, what are you think—
Do you really understand what's going to hap—
Quit foo—
Taiga...
Do you really hate me that mu—
I give up!
I don't care what you do or where you go!
I'm going home, so do whatever you want!
Bye!
What's with that? She's a kid too.
Ryuji...
I always, always thought that someone like me would never be loved by someone...
Smells good!
It's not just pork cutlets.
Grandma taught me how to make some great meat stew.
Yay!
Thank you, Ryuu-chan.
...but maybe that was just me running away.
I can't see any stars...
So small.
It's awkward and unreliable...
Just like me.
I blamed my lack of confidence on my parents and everyone around me.
But you love me just as I am.
That's why...
I won't run away anymore.
I will change.
I will accept everything.
Because I want to love you with my head held high.
That night, Taiga didn't come over for the pork cutlets.
Takasu...
We won't get it if you don't tell us.
What happened?
Why did Taiga—
Come on, everyone, get in your seats.
I have some bad news for you.
Aisaka-san is withdrawing for family reasons.
I've just heard from her mother.
Aisaka-san will be going back to her mother's—
Wai—
This is a lie, right? It's a complete lie, right? They made her, right?!
She didn't tell us any—
From here on out...
You will all come to a lot of different crossroads.
Whether you want to stop there or turn back...
You will have to choose something.
Aisaka-san's choice...
May lead to leaving all of you.
But I'm sure it's a choice she thought very hard about.
Let's support her.
Okay?
How scary kids these days are!
You're all calling Aisaka-san at once?
Texting her?
I can't believe you guys!
How about a little more time to reflect?
Takasu?
I can't connect if we all call at the same time!
Everyone, get in your seats!
Takasu-kun!
Kushie—
Wait.
Could you grit your teeth for a sec?
Why were you the only one who came back?
Why is Taiga transferring?
I don't get it!
Hey, Takas—
Wait, Kushieda!
Kitamura-kun.
I...
I didn't want to let her go either.
Even now.
If I could, I would drag her back here.
Why'd you decide on everything by yourself?
But...
She believes in me.
That's why...
The only thing I can do now is accept it.
Takasu...
Now she decides to clean up.
What's this?
A sock without its pair!
Unforgivable!
Where's your partner?
I'll definitely find him...!
Wait...
That dummy...
Isn't this stuff she was supposed to take?
You're really a dummy, aren't you?
Really?
When I fell into the river...
Oh, crap!
In the middle...
I even said it to Kawashima...
Yeah...
I'm really dumb too.
Tomiya-kun, are you free today?
There's somewhere I want to go on the way home, can you come with me?
Hey, this is...
Ami-chan...
Taiga...
"I'm sorry for yesterday."
Is what I'm not thinking.
If you're not thinking it, then don't bother telling me.
But I think I get what you said, just a little bit.
Hey, hey, Taiga's text message.
It came, it came!
I got it too!
This one, right?
That one!
Seems like it came to everyone who texted Taiga yesterday.
But why is it just a picture?
I don't get it.
Yeah, what is it actually?
Seaweed?
It's the night sky.
Kushieda?
She's right.
Is that small shining thing a star?
Really?
I don't know about that.
It's definitely a star.
But why the night sky?
"I will be watching over you all from a far-off sky."
That's bad luck! She's not dead!
"I'm going to try hard."
I think is what she's trying to say.
Even in a sky that is so dark you can't see anything...
There will definitely be stars somewhere there.
Shining...
If I shine even more brightly than I am now...
I'm sure people will be able to see me better.
I think she's being...
Pretty selfish.
But even so...
The sky is all connected.
As long as each of us can shine...
No matter how far apart we are...
We can see how each other is trying really hard.
That was so badly done, I can't stand it.
Chills went down my back.
W-What?!
But I kind of like it.
Feels like youth, don'cha think?
Me too!
I'd like it if she was right!
Speaking of stars...
Someone at some time had a lot of trouble with a certain star once...
Oh, that!
I think she'd be happy...
If we replied to her picture.
Be careful!
It's not here...
Where did we put it?
I remember putting it away afterwards with Ami-chan's tree...
Thanks.
Thinking of ways to make other people happy...
How should I put it...
You're a genius.
Naturally.
After all, my existence itself is amazing.
You know, I used to think Taiga was exactly as she seemed.
Running head-strong into everyone, but even so, loved as she was.
I was jealous.
But...
It wasn't like that.
Even though she has a big attitude, her heart is as cowardly as her small body.
Even though she's always trying to figure out what everyone's thinking...
She won't ever let anyone see her real self.
She's just the same as a certain someone.
Yup.
She was seen through by a certain someone from the beginning.
You said I was a kid, right?
I hate the me that pretends to be an adult.
That's why I was anxious to have others accept me for who I am.
But watching Taiga, I thought...
As long as there's one person who understands me...
I'll be okay.
Even if that...
Isn't love...
Kawashima...
Treasure ahoy!
I just have to press here, right?
Sensei!
Please hurry up while I still have my god powers!
Come on, Takasu-kun, smile.
Smile...
I am!
Amin.
Okay.
Here I go!
I'm a dragon.
You're a tiger.
Since a long time ago, tigers and dragons have stood together as equals.
Even...
If you're not here right now...
You're always by my side.
Transcending time and space.
These feelings...
Will never change.
Hey, Inko-chan...
Is this color a bit too flashy?
Yacchan's a mother, after all.
Maybe I should use a nude lip gloss or something...
But I don't have anything like that!
Inko-chan!
I-Inko-chan said his name!
It'll be lonely once the third years leave.
There were a lot of really interesting people...
Did you know?
The student council president, Kitamura-senpai, will be studying in America after graduation.
The cultural and sports festival were amazing when he and the third years organized it!
Yeah!
But I heard that the cultural festival from the year before was even more amazing.
Oh, I heard about that!
The one where the legendary class, 2-C, won everything, right?
Yeah, yeah!
Something about how somebody by the name of Tenori something had a huge role...
Tenori something?
You mean Tenori Taiga?
The one who brings you happiness, that one?
That was a real person?
Yeah, yeah, Tenori Taiga!
Apparently she was at this school last year.
That, and...
She's Takasu-senpai's girlfriend!
There's something that not a single person in this world has seen.
It's gentle, and very sweet.
Probably, if they ever had the chance to see it...
Anyone would want it.
That's why...
No one has ever seen it.
That's why the world hid it.
So that you couldn't get it easily.
But...
Someday someone will find it.
That one person who should have it...
Will be able to find it.
What?
I was going to scare you...
Did you grow?
I haven't shrunk nor grown a single millimeter.
So sorry to disappoint.
Hey...
I love you.
Tai—
W-Why are you saying something so embarrassing in broad daylight?!
Things like that n-need a certain mood or...
That's how it's made.