Man, it's hot...
Even though it's September starting today,
why is it so hot in the morning like this?
Let's finish yesterday's leftover curry soon...
Ah...
Good morning, Minorin!
Ya ya, how goes it you two?
H-Hey, how are you doing Kushie-
Osu~ everyone! Have you done your summer homework yet?
Have you brushed your teeth? Taken a shower?
What's with you, Haruta?
Suddenly acting so cheerful...
Ha-hum...
Hast something good happened to you during thy summer vacation, good sir?
Summer vacation is a thing of the past!
It's now the second semester!
Let's march onto our life's next prime stage, the Cultural Festival!
Something else new will...
Hm... that's good isn't it...
an eventful summer vacation...
Yuri-chan-sensei.
But then again,
it's perfectly normal for something to happen during your summer vacation.
It's your 17th summer after all.
Of course, it's entirely different for a single woman in her thirties...
Ah... what a cruel world...
As for Yuri-chan-sensei, I guess nothing good happened, huh?
PRE PRE PARADE tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Pre Pre-parade, although I'm not strong
PRE PRE PARADE itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
Pre Pre-parade, I will capture you one day
Aero Subs Presents
ra
do
!
yudan shitara sono yubi chikuchiku ATTACK kakugo shite
Be prepared for the prickling attack when your guards are down
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitai na anata
I'll grasp you like a flea although I'm small
hoshii no wa PLASTIC no HEART
What I want is a plastic heart
PLUS PLUS dakedo MINUS
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soredakeja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita monogachi
But just that it's boring for those who realize they are the winners
koi wa amakute nigai mono
Love is a sweet and bitter thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
It's plain and simple, yet complicated and mysterious
doudemo ii koto bakari ki ni shitari suru no
Worrying continuously about the trivial things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it like, it's like that
onkou tokujitsu ECCENTRIC na anata
You, who's gentle and sincere, yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
Opposing with the attitude of tough pretence with the body
sunao na dake dato shigeki ga tsuyokute kurakura
Just being honest is too stimulating and it makes me dizzy
kizutsuichau no kizutsukechau no
I get hurt, I hurt you
junjou PURE PARAATO
A naive preparation
atama no naka wa junjou PURE PAREEDO
In my mind, I'm always alone on the naive pre-parade
itsumo hitori no
Oobashi Highschool Culture Festival - Part 1
So, in the end, there will only be one day for the exhibition this year as well,
which means everything will have to be crammed into one day.
Even with the President's power...
It's not like we're in this alone.
This is business.
The negotiations with the teaching administration begin here.
Indeed.
If things go according to our plans,
as long as we keep fighting for a settlement of two days, we still have a chance to win.
This year's cultural festival,
will be exciting no matter the cost.
After all, this is truly my last big event.
Takasu-kun, let's look for UFO's next time.
Whoa, stupid Chihuahua.
What are you doing, you trash!?
That's why I told you,
my nails are too long, and I can't touch the ball right now.
They'll break.
You stupid Chihuahua!
What a cute smile...
I knew Ami-chan was an angel...
I'm leaning more towards the "Palmtop Tiger" though.
Then, mine will be Kashirai.
Kihara is uber-good too, no?
Whoa, Taiga is riding Ami-chan like a horse!
Ah, I want to be ridden like that too.
Ladies and Gentlemen!
What's with the monologue?
There are no "ladies" here.
By the way, what's 'gentle'?
Everyone...
have you ever wanted to see the girls in their cute daily attire?
Are you all right?
Did you get bitten by something weird during summer vacation?
Just listen till I finish.
The Cultural Festival is almost here.
During tomorrow's long homeroom,
we will talk about what we, Class 2-C, are going to do for the Cultural Festival.
In addition, I am a member of the executive committee.
And, so what?
A-n-d s-o...
For example:
Let's say we do a maid cafe, then we'll see the girls in maid costumes.
If all the guys vote for the same thing, then no one can complain.
So how about that!?
That's a good idea...
Even though it's coming from Haruta...
Wait a minute.
In that case, rather than maid costumes...
I want to see the girls in Chinese dresses!
Whoa!
That could work too...
Takasu thinks so too, right?
Y-Yeah, that's true...
If it's maid clothes, I could use part-time uniforms as a reference...
but a Chinese dress fits the body line perfectly, so...
No! That won't work!
If the clothes have to fit the body line, then I'll have to make another Ginyu-Pad...
What are you talking about?
No, nothing!
As for me, rather than a Chinese dress,
what about lolita?
Takasu...
You're a genius!
Eh?
Then mine would be a nurse!
A stewardess is good too!
You fool! Call them "hostesses"!
A priestess works too!
Wait a moment everyone, let's slow down just a second!
Ah, I don't know what we're talking about anymore...
In other words, a cosplay cafe.
If we do it that way, that would cover everything right?
That's it!
Taiga, I'll go on ahead.
Okay.
Ryuuji!
Eh?
Look at this.
What's this all of a sudden?
Whoa, this is horrible.
It was ripped by that stupid Chihuahua.
Just wait a minute.
Could you stop trashing other people when they're not here?
Didn't you just step on it, fall and then rip it yourself?
Didn't it all start because the stupid Chihuahua was evading the ball!?
That's why I told you that my nails...
Stop it, I say.
I'll fix the ripped part.
There you go, enchanted by her as usual...
Make sure it's fixed before next week.
Hey! Don't just leave after blaming someone for things they never did!
Hey!
Those guys are spirited aren't they?
Kushieda.
Well then, shall we return to the classroom?
Y-Yeah, that's right...
By the way, about that UFO talk...
My, as a Diet Warrior, I knew that instant noodles were the enemy.
Huh?
Oooh, scary, scary...
This can't be fixed without adding some new cloth.
Maybe I'll just take something from some of Yasuko's old clothes.
It's ringing, Taiga.
It's fine, just leave it.
Damn, that rotten old man.
Rotten old man?
What's that?
I don't care what it is, but that's bugging me, the phone...
Shut up!
What's with you all of a sudden?
I told you to leave it alone.
He remarried and made me out to be a hindrance,
kicking me out of the house and leaving me by myself in a mansion, that's how he is.
He abandoned me, that cold-hearted man.
Your dad!?
It's rotten old man!
No matter what kind of a man he is, a father is still a father.
Calling him a rotten old man is a bit...
A family, you see, no matter how far they're separated, deep down in the heart,
is something like...
I told you he's a rotten old man didn't I?!
Rot... t-ten... o-old... m-man...
Ah! Don't remember words like that!
He-Hemorrhoids.
Ah, Inko-chan, again...
Hemorrhoids.
Hemo.
He-He. He-He...
What? Ryuu-chan, are you talking about Papa again?
Hemo.
He-Hemorrhoids.
Hemorrhoids.
We're not talking about my old man here!
It...
He was a wonderful man!
It hurts. It hurts.
No matter how many times he was stabbed, he'd just say "It's fine".
The left side hurts.
Not this again!
Hemorrhoids.
Hemorrhoids hurt.
That is NOT wonderful, and stop talking about things like that in front of others!
Have it.
I have it.
Hemorrhoids.
But your father...
Hemorrhoids hurt.
That being said,
our class representative for the beauty contest has been decided!
Topic of
Discussion
Cultural
Festival
Culture Festival
Executive Committee Member
Haruta Kouji
The beauty contest representative will be Ami-chan. I'm sure there's no objection.
Now the only problem left is wha-
The same: Kawashima Ami
I'm sorry, that's not possible.
I appreciate your feelings, but I was elected chairman of the beauty contest.
So, I can't participate even if everybody chooses me.
That's why I think...
Aisaka-san should do it in my place!
Since after all,
Aisaka is REALLY small, cute, and infamous throughout the whole school.
What the hell kind of nonsense are you spouting, stupid Chihuahua?!
Why do I have to do this?
Ah, but that might not be bad.
Well, it's true that Taiga is famous.
It actually might turn out pretty well.
Tch, you guys...
Now, now...
You can't do that, Taiga-chan.
You can't back out now, after being chosen by the class for such an event.
Hey, stupid Chihuahua! If words don't work, then I'll just crash the Cultural Festival-
Now, now.
Hold it, hold it.
If it's Aisaka, who knows? You might turn out to be a real winner, okay?
O~kay. Then our class representative for the beauty contest is Taiga.
Now moving on, any ideas on what our class should do for the Cultural Festival...
Yes!
Okay, Noto-kun!
How about a cosplay cafe!?
Eh!?
Doesn't that just reek of otaku?
The other classes will probably do something like that I think...
I absolutely don't want to do that...
Ah...
Uh-Uhm... Y-You see, I-I got this idea, you see...
Well, it's not like I want to do it anyway...
I hate it, but if this would make everyone happy then,
Uh-Uhm... T-That's... a-a-a haun-
I got a bloody nose...
D-Don't mis-s-s-understand...
I-I wasn't a-about to say anything weird...
I-I was a-about to s-say a-a-a ha-a-unted house there...
Kushieda, why don't you stop about there?
Your body won't hold up you know.
Won't allow...
I will not allow it, I say...
Y-Yuri-chan?
A cafe? No way! Form a band and do a live show? Ah, that's the worst thing in Japan right now!
That kind of excitement for a day, it's an illusion after all.
It's still far from Christmas anyway, so no way!
Did something happen to her over summer vacation?
Anyway! We're not going anywhere at this rate!
Since it has come to this, we'll decide it this way!
Everyone, write out what you want to do right away!
No matter what the girls write, it's just a wasted effort.
They're no match against the men's alliance.
Okay, has everyone finished writing? Then, let's do this.
Shake! And... get!
What! You're picking at random!?
Then, I'll announce it right away!
This year, for the Cultural Festival,
our class will be doing a "Pro-wrestling show"?
PRO WR
ESTLING
(CLASH!)
Huh, a "Pro-wrestling show" of all things?
By the way...
why didn't you decide this with a majority vote?
That stupid Chihuahua,
before she reaches the next cycle of reincarnation,
I'll make sure she sees plenty of hell!
Just give up and enjoy class events sometimes.
You have a small heart.
What? You just want an excuse to get excited.
Excited? Me?
Since coming back from the trip, always.
Huh? That's weird.
What's wrong?
Strange, I can't withdraw any money.
It keeps showing me the number zero.
It can't be helped then, let me...
Impossible...
It's because I always ignored the phone...
So this is how you do it...
Unbelievable.
Phone? You mean like the last time?
Until recently, I just hung up on him,
but because it was annoying, I started ignoring it completely.
And now, he suddenly takes away my living expenses.
That rotten old man...
I really want to kill him.
You can't say things like that about your parent.
This is a threat isn't it? What he's doing.
Just answer it for now.
If you don't talk, nothing is gonna happen after all.
And then, you'll have problems without money right?
Well, it's good if you want to talk, but...
...why do I have to be the one that meets him?
I see...
I get it.
At any rate, that means my daughter won't be coming right?
Yeah, I apologize.
I wanted to see Taiga no matter what.
But I guess she hates me even more now, huh?
Well, sorry to bother you,
Um, Takasu-kun was it?
Then, just order anything you want.
No it's fine, it's about dinner time anyway.
W-Well, then I'll order some...
An egg bagel.
Ah, is that so?
Excuse me, can we place an order?
This guy here will have an egg bagel.
And then, I guess I'll have a salmon bagel.
I'd like it with a lot of cheese please, and put it in between.
Ah, that's right, before I forget,
here, money.
Ah..
I wanted to see her no matter what...
I have something important to talk about you see...
Something important?
And then... so uh... what kind of relationship do you have with Taiga?
Are you dating her?
No, that's not it!
I'm just her friend. We're not dating or anything like that.
She's just my neighbour. And we happen to get along pretty well.
I see, then you must have heard a lot of things about our family situation from her.
My new wife is very young.
That's why Taiga won't live with her no matter what.
And that, coupled with several misunderstandings...
My current wife, Yuu, is her name.
Taiga was put in a situation where either Yuu or her would have to leave and so... Taiga...
I want to live together with Taiga again.
Together again.
Today, that's what I was gonna talk about with her.
There absolutely won't be any mistakes this time.
I want to start over again with just the two of us.
I'm considering separating from Yuu in the near future.
And I'll live together with Taiga,
because we're a family.
Because I love her.
This is bad...
Your old man, he's coming to see you.
Ah, what are you doing?! You have to rub it more than 5 seconds...
Ah, shut up.
Don't lend a hand.
In exchange for you meeting with him, I promised you I'd do the dishes.
Then, do it properly!
Just go over there and don't bother me.
How do I say this...
Your father is kinda strange isn't he?
He doesn't act like a normal adult...
I told you, "Just go away!"
Just boil some water and make tea or something!
Your father, you see, he seems concerned about you...
That's why he wanted to try to live with you agai-
Isn't that stupid?
I'm trying to be serious here.
Your dad said to me: "I want us to live together!"
He asked me to tell you...
Stop, that's enough!
Don't interfere in other people's family affairs!
Huh? This is happening because you made me go there, right?
You're just going to accept the money and that's it!?
That's right, that's why I'm washing the dishes.
That's why it's finished with this.
I don't want to see that man again!
Hey, stop it with this...
Shut up!
Don't act overfamiliar and touch me!
Your dad, he was depressed because you ignored him!
How awful that is for him!
It's more pitiful for me!
Tai... ga...
All right.
Has everyone got one yet?
I feel responsible for this so I made it,
the scripts for the "Pro-Wrestling Show".
Hey, why don't we just call it quits?
Here.
Everyone...
Please show some enthusiasm here!
There's no turning back now!
Yuri-chan has already put her seal of approval on it after all!
Hey, this might be interesting after all...
Everyone has a role in here.
Haruta-kun is unexpectedly good...
So I play the role of an MC here...
I feel a bit happy about it.
Ami-chan...
Hey, it's true...
It actually looks pretty decent...
Haruta-kun, let's do our best!
Okay, how about we start practicing right away!
The time is in the future.
With Ami-chan as their leader, everyone in 2-C was leading a peaceful life.
However!
There's someone who disagrees with that peace!
And that someone is...
the evil incarnate, "Palmtop Tiger", and her henchman, "Yanki Takasu Ryuuji"!
Just wait a minute,
why am I her henchman, and a yanki on top of that?
Why am I the evil incarnate?
Well, just listen 'til the end, okay?
The "Palmtop Tiger" keeps attacking everyone in 2-C,
and one by one they fall victim to brainwashing.
But then! With Ami-chan desperately convincing them, the brainwash is overturned.
In the end, everyone combines their powers and successfully drive off the "Palmtop Tiger" and "Yanki Takasu Ryuuji".
And with that: "All's well that ends well" Happy End!
How about that!?
So that's what you meant by listening to the end...
It's simple, yet dramatic.
It might actually turn out to be a good show after all.
No way!
There's no way I'm doing that!
Geez, Aisaka-san is so selfish.
Hey! Not only about the beauty contest...
why do you keep pestering me to do strange things!?
"If hitting me will make you content, then hit me as many times as you want."
Of course, I'll do it!
"But there will be nothing born from it!"
Huh?
Whoa, it looks like the "Palmtop Tiger" is really into it.
Eh?
Jumping into practice immediately, huh?
What a strong intensity!
Okay! At that point, Taiga.
Your brainwashing line.
Eh?
Next line you know, next. Here.
Taiga is screaming something...
Ami has changed a lot recently hasn't she?
Yeah.
Seems that way.
You, what the hell is with your looks!?
I dunno, Haruta-kun said this is for a special role.
Everyone, please listen for a moment, a school announcement has been issued.
For this year's Cultural Festival, there will be a competition between classes.
The best class will get special prizes!
Huh...
On that note, the prizes will be...
For one thing, "The class will have a refrigerator installed inside the class!"
A cold juice, wouldn't that be refreshing?
Next: "Starting next year, the class will get priority for the installment of the newest AC unit that can control dampness!"
Dampness, don't you want it?
"The current ban on electrical usage in the washroom will be lifted!"
The schoolyard, don't you want it to change?
And then, "A discount at Kanoya Supermarket!"
A discount, don't you want one?
Wait... huh?
Hey guys, keep it together!
Y-Yeah...
Hey, what do you want for dinner?
Buri...
Buri? And how should it be prepared?
Teri...
So you want it grilled?
Sorry, I was waiting for you here.
All this time, um...
This damn stalker!
Taiga!
Stop being so stubborn!
Let me go, stupid dog!
Are you taking his side?
How cruel, I thought you were my only ally!
I'm saying this because I AM your ally.
It's for your sake!
Who do you think that was!?
That's your father isn't it!?
He came to see you!
At least hear him out!
You're wrong! That guy is a stalker! I don't need him!
Stop being stupid!
Hey, wait just a...
You were crying because you were abandoned, right?
Just be honest!
Just be honest! The truth is you want to go home, right!?
Someone like you, what do you know about me?
I no longer need that guy.
It wasn't me that was abandoned.
I abandoned him! Because he is trash, that's why!
You bastard, that person right over there, does he really look like trash to you!?
No matter how much I want him to, my father won't be coming back!
It wasn't for Taiga's sake, I...
I'm sorry Taiga, I...
That's enough, if you're going to put it that way...
So stop it with that pained look.
Tai...
A good thing?
I'll start to think of it that way.
I don't know if I can do it, but...
because it's you who said it...
I'll try to think that way.
That's good.
Definitely...
Right?
BANIRA SORUTO de BANIRA
Vanilla salt, and vanilla
amai dakenara
If it's only sweetness
SORUTO kakemashou
Then add some salt
dareyorimo motto motto watashi wo
I want you to understand me more than anyone else
shitte hoshiikara sarake dashitai
so I want to disclose
demo dekinai no
But it cannot be done
keike NOTHING modokashi sugiru
Because I have no experience, and it's rather irritating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
But a love that's only sweet is a little
watashi ga moto meteiru mono to wa chigau
Different from what I wish for
shiro to iwaretara
If I'm told it's white
kuro datteicchau
I will say it's black
sunao ni narenai amanojyaku
Unable to be honest, I'm just rebellious
suki to iwaretara daikiraidatte
If you say you like me, I will say I hate you
ureshii no ni nani ittendarou
I'm obviously happy, but what am I saying
amai BANIRA ni SORUTO kakeru youni
Just like adding salt to the sweet vanilla
Oobashi High School Festival- Part 2
Koigakubo Yuri, turned thirty this summer.
Everyone, give me presents please...
Better yet, someone marry me...