Your Highness, I brought your tea.
You're looking at that again?
I got it from Mother, so...
Why not look at it?
The legend of the Silver Princess and the Blue Knight...
dare no koto o kangaeteru no
Who is it that you're thinking of?
haato no supeesu soudatsusen
It's a game for a space in your heart!
senkyouteki ni isshin ittai de
It's an advancing and retreating invasion
yudan naranai na
I still can't let my guard down
a
no
ano ne ima no koto
ne
You see, right now,
honno suu paasento shika
I only have a few percent
aitsu no kokoro ni
tsu
of the space
ibasho ga nainda
in his heart
true
intentions
peek
out
seifuku no poketto
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
My
true
intentions
peek
out
true
intentions
out
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
My
true
intentions
out
My
true
intentions
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
My
intentions
peek
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
My
out
intentions
peek
out
My
from
my
uniform's
pocket
honne o shinobasete
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
pocket
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
pocket
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
uniform's
from
my
I
calmly fix
my collar
sotto eri o tadasu
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
I
calmly fix
my collar
my c
calmly fix
Simply revealing all the tricks up my sleeve
sonna kantan ni wa
te no uchi akasenai
would be no good
So I guess I'll just have to wait and see
akumade mada yousumi no dankai
dakedo hontou wa ne
But you see, the truth is
miyabutte hoshii no
I want you to realize it
awai kitai ni mune tokimekashite
My heart throbs from this bubbly expectation
chirachira to miteru
I shyly take a glance at you
onna no ko no daiji na mono
What girls value as important
i
ijiwaru de
a bit mean
ji
wa
ru
de
otoko no ko no daiji na koto
and what guys value as important
mukatsuku
mu
and annoying
ka
tsu
ku
hiku ni hikenai sorezore no jijou
tug back and forth with each other
hoka ni nani mo kangaerannai
My mind stutters, I can't think at all
ma
massugu de
so direct
s
su
gu
de
isshun datte yosomi dekinai
I can't take my eyes off you for a second
ni
nibui ne
yet so dull
bu
i
ne
juujitsukan afureru hodo ni
I'll fill you up with this sense of contentment
mitashite ageru yo
until you can't receive it anymore
jo
u
jouken chiratsukase
ken
Add requirements
yousu ukagatte miteru
See how things go
otagai win-win na
ga
I think we can both win here
i
win-
win
na
to
ri
torihiki shiyou yo
hi
so let's make a deal
ki
shi
yo
u
Cultural Festivals and Beetles!?
What!?
We have to write a script for the theater club!?
Cultural Festivals and Beetles!?
That's right!
The cultural festival is almost here.
My best friend, Matsudaira Kenji,
is in the theater club,
and they still don't know what they're doing this year!
I would like to help my friend!
To that end, I need your help!
So, Sanae, where's this act coming from?
Four Eyes told him that he has no talent for this sort of thing,
so he's not expecting any help,
and I guess Koutarou didn't like that.
How idiotic.
If everyone writes one,
the probability of ours getting used goes up significantly!
Theater Club Shouharu Festival Play Script
Application Guidelines
The deadline is the end of this month?
Theater Club Shouharu Festival Play Script
Application Guidelines
There's not much time.
I can't do this.
I'm not asking you to do this for free.
Corona Apartments #106 Territory Allocation
No-man's land
If you help me write, I'll give you 5 points.
points
And if any of yours gets picked, I'll give you 20 points!
20 points
No-man's land
You're giving away 20 points if no one's is picked, or 40 if someone's is picked.
That's very generous, Koutarou.
Corona Apartments #106 Territory Allocation
Big!
Yes, it is!
Corona Apartments #106 Territory Allocation
You're really dumb, aren't you?
Is it that important to show him up?
Your Highness, Theiamillis.
Y-Yes?
Sometimes men must duke it out.
I-I see.
Anyway, I, Satomi Koutarou,
would like to request your help!
Help me get back at my enemy, Makkenji!
I'll do it!
I'll participate!
If mine gets picked, I'll get 25 points,
and even if it doesn't, I'll get 5 points!
Even if it just helps me out a little...
Yeah!
Work hard so they pick yours!
Very well, Neanderthal.
If a subordinate requests help,
it's a master's job to fulfill that request.
I'll do it too!
We have a truce right now anyway,
so I don't think it'd be that bad to help out.
Well, then.
I guess I'll have to participate as well.
I may have the most points,
but I'm not so nice
that I would allow Theia-dono to overtake my three point lead.
A prudent course of action.
But to be honest,
I think it'd be fun to give it a go.
That sounds just like you.
Yup.
I appreciate all of your help!
Just you wait, Makkenji!
Honestly though, I'm not sure what to write.
Left! Left!
Your Highness, I have to analyze some data,
so I'll be heading back to the Blue Knight.
Okay, I'll be back soon.
I've already decided what to write.
What!?
Are you serious, Tulip!?
We're just not on the same level, Neanderthal.
This girl...
I'll get everything ready for writing, then.
Satomi-san, I'd like to ask you something.
Yeah? What is it?
Well, the vice president from the Cosplay Society wants me
to take care of her pet while she's moving.
Pet? What kind of pet?
Well...
What!? You already brought it here!?
Here it is.
Show me!
What is it?
Are you stupid, Yurika!?
Why did you bring that thing into this room!?
Do you understand what you've done!?
I'm sorry.
Why did you decide to take this thing!?
Wasn't there something else you could do!?
Not really.
Huh? Is this bug really that dangerous?
The thing is, Theia-dono,
this is a rhinoceros beetle.
Do you really like beetles
that much more than me!?
W-What should we do, Neanderthal!?
If Ruth sees this, it'll be a big problem!
That's why I'm worried!
How long do you have to keep him?
Their family just came into a lot of money, so they have a bunch of stuff.
I think it'll be a while.
One or two months...
One month
Two Months
People go crazy when they get a lot of money.
Yeah, but Ruth always acts on a schedule,
so I don't think it'll be hard to—
This is bad, Tulip!
Sorry, I forgot something.
Huh?
Were you all doing something?
Oh, nothing at all.
Y-Yeah, we're not doing anything.
We definitely don't have a be—
No, it's really nothing.
Right, Tulip?
The Neanderthal is right.
You said this is nonfiction, right?
Did your parents elope or something?
Yeah, my mom's family was rich,
so they wanted her to get married for the family, you know?
She ran off to my dad's place.
I see.
Want to take a break, Koutarou?
I've been borrowing your body to write, so...
I'm fine.
I haven't even figured out what I'm going to write yet.
It's a little weird being a literal ghostwriter,
but it's fun.
Well, then,
after this I'll massage your
shoulders and help you out.
Sure, thanks.
You've got pretty handwriting, Sanae.
I know, right?
Just try remembering how your hand's moving to make those letters.
Sure, why not?
Keep telling me how awesome I am!
You're awesome.
Help me, Satomi-san!
W-What's wrong, Yurika!?
Hercules-chan keeps moving around and I can't sleep.
Why should I care?
Yeah, but when he moves around,
he sounds exactly like a cockroach.
Please do something, Satomi-san.
Yeah, but...
You can't just get rid of him?
No! The vice president really loves this little guy.
Oh, fine. I have a good idea.
Really?
Yeah, you can keep Hercules in the closet.
And then you—
Can get out.
Sanae, I understand how you feel,
but you're not helping.
Just relax a little.
Right.
You put Hercules in the closet,
and Yurika, you...
can live in the room for a while.
Huh?
A-Are you sure?
Thank you so much.
Aren't you happy, Hercules-chan?
Now you don't have to leave.
I'll make sure you get back to your owner.
Are you not tired, Your Highness?
I've got the Thought-to-Text interface ready.
No, it's important that I keep myself on the same level as this planet.
Also, I need to play on the same field as the Neanderthal and Kiriha.
A space-time quake.
Coordinates 125, 88, 493.
Size 181.
Right next to this planet.
Could it be...
One month later
Thank you for coming here,
savior of the Theater Club!
Congratulations on winning the scenario competition,
Theiamillis Gre Fortorthe-dono.
It was no problem at all.
Winner!
Shouharu
Festival
Playwright
The Silver
Princess and
The Blue
Knight
It was a wonderful script,
"The Silver Princess and The Blue Knight."
I'm just glad that this planet understands true art.
Yeah, right.
Why did the Tulip get chosen,
while the rest of us didn't?
Right, Yurika?
Seriously.
Do you think you plebeians can
really understand what we wrote?
Exactly.
Those two get along really well.
Yeah, almost too well.
I guess they've grown closer after writing together every night.
You losers can go lick each others wounds.
Don't get all high and mighty, you stupid princess.
Shouharu       Festival
The play that the princess wrote,
"The Silver Princess and the Blue Knight,"
is based on a legend that everyone in the Fortorthen Empire knows.
The Fortorthen princess,
Alaia-sama, caught up in a coup,
was defended by Reios-sama, the Blue Knight,
while traveling to visit their old friend in the Land of Pardomshiha.
I see.
Sounds like a story the
club president would like.
All Forthorthen girls adore the Blue Knight.
Her Highness really likes the story herself.
So she was really enthusiastic, then?
If she didn't have her script
chosen after working so hard,
I'm sure she would have
been extremely dejected.
Please do whatever you can, as this
shows her feelings for the Blue Knight.
I understand, Ruth-san.
That's why I'm helping out here.
I'm the one who asked her in the first place.
Thank you.
You're quite nice, Satomi-sama.
No, well...
No!
You aren't all bad, but... I don't know.
You're not the Silver Princess!
You need to be more fragile-looking—
Demure, but with a burning passion within you.
Oh, you understand, don't you?
Me! Me!
I'll be the princess!
I don't wanna be the horse. Give me a role where they can see my face!
Yeah, we do have a limit on the people we have.
Since whoever we have be the Blue Knight will be a far cry from the real thing,
I don't really mind if Matsudaira does it.
But I don't want to compromise the Silver Princess.
Why are you ignoring me?
Calm yourself, Comrade Yurika!
Satomi-san!
Tulip, I've heard your concerns.
I know someone perfect for the role of the Silver Princess.
What?
Are you serious?
Tell us!
No problem.
In exchange, I'd like you to
give my comrade, Yurika,
a role where her face is shown.
Satomi-san...
Oh, fine.
Is there anything available?
Well, if she can't play the back of the horse any longer...
There's the evil Bandit A that she can play.
I-I can do the bandit!
I'll do my best to be evil.
evil
Hey there, drop your money and get out of here.
You want that role?
So, Neanderth—
Koutarou.
Who's the person that's perfect for the role?
Hold on.
I'll bring her now—
Excuse me.
Oh, Satomi-kun.
Could I help with something?
Oh, Senpai!
Good timing!
Sakuraba Harumi, huh?
R-Reios-sama, you can't fight all on your own!
You've already fought so hard for me.
Please forget about us, and run...
That was good.
I was worried that you didn't
want to actually take the role,
but I think you'll be fine.
While I think it's a wonderful story,
I don't understand
Princess Alaia's feelings.
I see.
Maybe it's hard because you don't have a partner to practice with.
If you want, I could help you.
Y-You will, Satomi-kun?
Sure!
Soldier A doesn't really get much screen time.
Princess Alaia, it seems this is as far as I'll be able to accompany you.
Reios-sama?
Your Highness,
please flee with your sister.
I see.
The princess...
Alaia is drawn to this guy.
The Forthorthen Empire, and the Knitting Club...
They're both in danger and
could disappear any moment,
but the Blue Knight, Satomi-kun, saved me from that.
That's right. The Silver Princess and I...
Our feelings are the same.
No, Reios-sama.
No, it was because of you, Princess. All of your subjects adore you.
That is why for all the people, I...
I understand.
I understand how she feels.
The Silver Princess...
The reason why I didn't fold
was because you were there.
You've already fought enough.
Please forget us and run.
You should be able to escape on your own!
I want you to live!
Bravo, bravo, Sakuraba-san!
President?
I knew it was the right choice to make you the lead.
I'm looking forward to the play.
I'll be counting on you too, Satomi-kun.
Right!
Satomi Koutarou will back up
Princess Alaia with everything he has!
S-Satomi-kun...
So there really aren't any clues
left after that space-time quake.
Yes, we're not even picking up a faint signal.
There's only one answer, huh?
We'll stay alert.
Hopefully it's just a warning.
One day left for the festival
Work, work.
Excavating stuff!
I need to go help out with the play after I'm done.
What are you doing, Tulip?
Neanderthal, don't just
stand there. Help me up.
You seem like you're just fine.
What are you doing?
You think a Fortorthen princess would intentionally bring shame to herself?
Talk to you later, Tulip.
Wait, Neanderthal!
I guess it'd be better to tell you than some random passerby.
They're props.
Huh?
I have a bunch of props to use for the play in here!
I tried to ask someone to help me carry them,
but I tripped.
That's all!
Just laugh already.
Neanderthal?
Don't you want to laugh at me?
I changed my mind.
I thought you were trying to do something crazy again,
but you were actually helping everyone out.
There's nothing funny about that.
Are you hurt, Princess?
No.
I'm sorry for my rudeness, Princess Theiamillis.
The Blue Knight...
What's wrong, Tulip?
Did you hit your head or something?
I'm fine!
Totally fine!
This isn't going to work!
The Blue Knight is fine,
but what about the princess!?
Koutarou and the theater club president both said you were the best!
That's weird.
It was so perfect earlier.
Sakuraba-san, are you not feeling well?
N-No, that's not it.
We don't have time for this!
Stop it, Tulip!
Satomi-kun...
Sakuraba-senpai is just tired from her first full rehearsal.
She's nervous because she got paired up with Makkenji all of a sudden.
What should we do, then!?
We do this one step at a time.
Makkenji, switch with me.
First, we'll rehearse with me,
then she should be able to
perform like she did before.
After that, we can ease
Makkenji in so it works out.
Do whatever you want.
We can't make do with her acting as it is now.
Sakuraba-senpai's got a lot more in her than you think, Tulip.
Right.
Princess Alaia, it seems this is as far as I'll be able to accompany you.
Reios-sama?
Your Highness,
please flee with your sister.
I'll draw as many of them away as I can.
Get as far away as you can in that time.
No, I can't leave you behind, Reios-sama.
I was able to come this far because of you.
If you're to thank someone,
it should be the people of this land.
If they didn't help us...
Reios-sama!
How was that, Tulip!?
That's Sakuraba-senpai's true acting ability!
Y-Yeah...
Her acting just now was completely different.
Sakuraba Harumi is pretty good...
but why do I feel more than ever that the Neanderthal
is a lot like the real Blue Knight?
Okay, Sakuraba-san, how about we have you do the same with Matsudaira-kun—
But from what I can see,
it seems that Sakuraba-senpai can only perform like this
when she's with Satomi-kun.
Huh?
I have a suggestion, in that case.
How about we have Satomi-kun be the Blue Knight?
You want me to be the Blue Knight?
Yes, rather than having Sakuraba-senpai try acting with Matsudaira-kun,
why not just have you do it, Satomi-kun? It's faster.
I see.
That's fine with me.
It's not that I'd like to give up the part,
but unfortunately, I can't get
Sakuraba-senpai to act like that.
Makkenji...
You're the only one who can play this role.
Oh well.
I'm a little reluctant, but I'll let Koutarou be the Blue Knight.
W-Wait!
Soldier A was hard enough,
but now I have to be the Blue Knight!?
There's nothing to worry about!
Huh?
I know more about the
Blue Knight than anyone.
I'll make sure you're the perfect Blue Knight before the play.
Seriously?
It's pretty silly to have a play about the Blue Knight here.
But this works out very well for me.
Theiamillis-san, your play won't be getting a happily ever after.
akogarete iru no you
I always wanted
anata to sukyandaru
to have a scandal with you
itomenai no kokoro
My heart wants to win you over
ano koyori mo hayaku
before that other girl does
hito wa
Why do people
nande nande
Why, oh, why?
nando
Even though each and every time
kizutsuitemo
I end up feeling hurt
koi ni
It's love
koi ni ochiru
I fall helplessly in love
ikimono nano
Ah, but such is life
marude marude mirukutii
Just like a milk tea
betsubetsu no tokoro de umareta futari
Our hearts lie in separate places
amai amai no mirukutii
Just like this sweet, sweet milk tea
atsu atsu yo ima sugu kyun to nomihoshite
It's steaming hot, so I want you to drink it up in one go
marude marude mirukutii
Just like milk tea
zetsumyou na kaken ga wakaranai no ne
I can't make sense of this breathtaking feeling
torotorokeru mirukutii
It's liquid velvet, just like milk tea
saigo dake chotto dake horori tii tongai
Even though it tastes slightly bitter at the end
The color of the flowers
have already faded away, while in idle thoughts.
My life passes vainly by,
Hey, what game is this?
as I watch the long rains fall.
I don't understand what she's saying.
Yeah, I don't think the people here are going to be able to do this.
Next Episode
My Knight