It was a small incident that happened
to me, Nanoha Takamachi,
a girl who was supposed to be
an ordinary third-grader.
I accepted the heart of courage,
and I gained magical powers.
We've seen each other, and
came into contact many times,
yet we still know nothing
about each other.
I want to hear the answer...
I want to share...
That is why I decided
to face her straight on.
Getting rid of all doubts,
believing only in the magic
that dwells in my heart.
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha
is about to begin.
Cradling my knees in
a corner of my room
I always shivered from uncertainty
I was scared of learning the truth,
so I closed the door
I found my own place within a kind lie
and I fled inside my dreams
I dye a sea of loneliness that
nobody knows of into a deep blue
An intense feeling to
hide the loneliness
Is continually injuring your heart
The secret hidden deep
within the eyes
To the truth behind the smile
that draws me in
I will deliver a love so soft
Right now, a warmth that might
break upon touching it
Parts itself from the past,
and overflows
I'll be by your side forever
Do not be lured into
the somber shadows
All three of you, come back.
Roger.
Now...
Nanoha and Yuuno,
you'll both receive a very stern
lecture directly from me.
Everybody's Separate Heart-felt Vows
Following all instructions and
orders is a necessary rule
to protect an organization,
not just individuals.
Selfish decisions and actions
may have put not only you,
but everyone else around you
in danger as well.
You understand that, right?
Yes, ma'am...
Normally I would put a very
heavy punishment on you.
But as a result of what you did,
we have gained a little as well.
So, for this one time,
I will let it pass by.
However...
There will be no next time.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
We're very sorry.
Now, the problem is
what goes on from here.
Chrono, do you have any ideas
on the cause of all this?
Yes.
Amy, bring it up on the monitors!
Gotcha!
Oh...
That's right.
A mage from Midchilda,
just like us. Precia Testarossa.
Her specialty was development of
energy for interdimensional travel.
She was a grand mage, yet was exiled
due to causing an accident
through illegal research.
The wavelength of the magical attack
just now matches the data on file.
And that girl Fate is, most likely...
Fate...
Back then, she said "Mother"...
Mother?
Parent and child, huh...
Um...
She didn't look like she was
surprised so much as scared.
Amy!
Can you give me a bit more
detailed data on Lady Precia?
Where she went in exile,
her family makeup,
anything that you can find.
Aye aye. I'll look for them right away.
This is Fate's mother...
You had such a great chance
in front of you,
yet all you did was
stand there in a daze.
I'm sorry...
How horrible, Fate.
Do you really want to make
your mother that sad?
I want to be friends.
Precia Testarossa...
According to Mid history,
she was head of Sector 3
of the Central Technology
Development Office 26 years ago.
However, at the time,
she was developing
a dimension travel energy motor
called the Hudra,
where she conducted an experiment
using illegal materials, and failed.
Because it resulted in
a mid-size dimensional tremor,
she was forced to leave Central,
and was relocated to a rural branch.
There seems to have been
much debate about it.
She argued that only
the result was a failure,
and that there were no illegalities
in the experimental materials.
After being relocated to the outskirts,
she was involved in tech research
for several years.
After a while, she ended up missing...
And nothing ever since.
What about her family, and her
activities when she went missing?
All data concerning those questions
has been completely erased.
We're contacting headquarters now
to have them looked over.
How much time will it take?
I believe it will be in
the next day or two.
Neither Lady Precia
nor Fate should be able
to move around too much after
emitting so much magical power.
We have to use that time to
strengthen the Arthra's shields, too.
It's best that you two rest for a while.
Oh, but...
Especially you, Nanoha.
It's not good for you to be absent
from school for too long.
I will allow you to go home
for the time being.
It's better for you to
put in an appearance,
for both your family
and your schoolmates.
Yes, ma'am.
Fate! Fate!
Fate... Fate...
Only nine...
I can cause a dimensional
tremor with this many,
but I can't reach Alhazard.
I don't have much time left.
Neither for me, nor for Alicia...
You're her mother, and that girl
is your daughter, right?!
She's doing her best right now,
she's honestly trying so hard...
How can you be so cruel to her?!
She's terrible at making
a good familiar.
Too many excessive emotions...
Fate... Your daughter wants you
to smile so much,
wants you to be a kind person again,
and does so much...
You're in my way.
Begone!
It doesn't matter where.
I have to teleport!
I'm sorry, Fate...
Just for a little while, wait for me!
Fate...
Wake up, Fate.
Yes, Mother.
The number of Jewel Seeds
you have brought is nine.
This isn't enough.
I need at least five more.
If possible, even more than that.
Hurry and get them for your mother.
Yes...
Aruf?
Oh...
That girl ran away.
She said she was scared,
and had had enough.
If you need one, I'll get you
a better familiar.
Don't forget that your one
true ally is your mother.
Got that, Fate?
Yes, Mother.
And that's how it's been
for the past ten days.
Oh, I see!
Mrs. Lindy...
It's either a really great cover-up,
or a complete lie...
Amazing.
I can't tell them the truth.
Please say that it's me caring
enough to not worry your family.
However, Miss Nanoha
is an excellent child.
I really would like my child
to be more like her.
Oh, my... That's going too far!
My Chrono isn't good at
being kind to others.
Nanoha...
You can stay home for at least
the next day or two, right?
Yeah.
Arisa and Suzuka have been worried
too. Have you contacted them yet?
Yeah, I sent them e-mail a while ago.
And... send!
Miss Arisa, did you receive
some good news?
Not really. Just an ordinary e-mail.
Samejima, stop the car for a second!
It really was a big dog.
It's hunrt, as well.
The wounds look severe.
But it's still alive.
Samejima!
Understood.
Fate...
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha.
Oh, are you awake now?
This girl... I've seen her somewhere.
You're built really tough.
You were hurt so bad, but they said
your life wasn't in danger.
I'll take care of you until your
wounds are all healed up.
So rest easy.
It's that girl's friend.
Here. It's soft dog food.
Can you eat it?
There's nothing to worry about
if you have that much appetite.
After you eat, take your time,
rest, and get better soon.
Nanoha!
I'm so glad you're doing well!
Yeah! Thanks, Suzuka.
I'm sorry to you too, Arisa.
I made you worry.
Well, I'm glad you're doing okay.
I see... You have to go again.
Yeah...
That must be tough.
But it's all right!
What about after school? Will you
be able to play with us a little?
Yeah, it's okay.
Then, wanna come to my place?
I bought a few new games.
Oh, really?
That's right... Last night, I picked up
a dog that was hurt.
A dog?
Yeah. It's really big, with orange fur,
and on its forehead is
a red stone, like this.
Just as I thought...
It's you, Miss Aruf.
Is that you?
Those wounds...
What happened to you?
And what about Fate?
Oh, no, it's lost its energy.
What's wrong?
Are you doing all right?
Maybe its wounds hurt.
Maybe we should leave it alone?
Yeah.
Yuuno!
Hey, that's dangerous.
It's okay. Yuuno will be all right.
Nanoha...
I'll hear what she has to say.
Nanoha, you go with
Arisa and Suzuka.
Okay.
Then how about some tea?
I have a couple really
tasty tea snacks.
Yeah!
I'm looking forward to that!
What in the world happened?
Something happened
between you two?
The fact that you're here means that
the guys from the Bureau
are watching us now, right?
Yes.
Chrono Harlaown of the Time-Space
Administration Bureau here.
It seems like the situation
is very complex.
If you speak honestly, I will make
sure it doesn't work against you.
About you, and about your
master, Fate Testarossa.
I'll tell you everything.
But you have to promise me
that you will save Fate!
She hasn't done anything wrong!
I promise.
Amy, the recorder.
Already recording.
Fate's mother, Precia Testarossa,
is the cause of it all.
Hero takes 28 points of damage.
What you got a few minutes ago...
Correct. Here!
Which one?
Nanoha, did you hear that?
Yeah. I heard it all.
The conditions that you
have described to us...
And examining her familiar
Aruf's testimony,
as well as her current
physical condition...
It looks like there are no lies
or contradictions in her story.
What's going to happen now?
We're going to capture
Precia Testarossa.
Just the fact that she
attacked the Arthra
is more than enough reason
for us to arrest her.
So, as soon as we get orders
from the Captain,
we will be forced to change our
mission to the arrest of Precia.
What will you do then,
Nanoha Takamachi?
L.
I want to save Fate.
Miss Aruf's feelings, and my own will.
A sad look on Fate's face
somehow makes me sad as well.
That's why I want to save her,
from all the sad things.
Besides, I told her that I wanted
to be friends with her.
I haven't heard her answer yet.
I understand.
We're also thankful to have your
magical powers on our side.
We'll leave everything concerning
Fate Testarossa up to you, Nanoha.
Is that all right?
Nanoha... was it?
I don't have the right to
ask you, but please...
Save Fate!
She really is all alone right now.
Yeah. It'll be all right. Leave it to me!
You're late, Nanoha!
Come on, we've been waiting for you
to enter the new dungeon!
Sorry, sorry!
Wow, this looks so cool!
As planned, our return to the Arthra
is set for tomorrow morning.
In the event that you
encounter Fate before then...
Yeah... It'll be all right.
I got really into that one!
After all, it's more fun when
you're with us, Nanoha.
Thanks.
I'm sure everything
will be over very soon.
And then everything will be all right.
Nanoha...
Hey, did you get over it, just a little?
Um, well... I don't know...
I was worried.
Actually, the reason why I was mad
wasn't because you were
hiding something from me,
or because you were always
thinking about something.
It was because you looked
troubled and confused.
And every so often...
You looked like you were
going to go somewhere,
and never come back
to see us ever again.
I won't be going anywhere.
You're my friends.
I wouldn't go anywhere!
I see.
Right.
I won't go anywhere.
I'lll make sure to
come back right here.
It's just that for a short time,
I'm going to spend my time
differently than usual.
So that in the future, I can live
a straightforward life as myself.
A small journey so that
I won't regret anything.
You're looking better now.
Are your worries gone now?
Dad?
You knew that I was
worried about something?
Of course I did.
I am your father, after all.
You're going to take off early
in the morning tomorrow, right?
Yeah. I'm sorry to trouble you.
Well, you're a strong girl, Nanoha.
I'm not all that worried.
Make sure to do your best!
Yeah!
Uminari city, residential district
Takamachi residence, 5:27AM
Nanoha!
Uminari Seaside Park, 5:55AM
It's all right if it's here, right?
Please come out, Fate!
Scythe Form.
Fate, let's stop all this now.
You shouldn't listen to what
that woman tells you!
Fate, you'll end up more and more
miserable if you keep going.
So please, Fate!
But still...
I'm still her daughter.
It's not good enough
to just throw it away.
And it's even worse if
I were to run away.
I'm sure it all started
with the Jewel Seeds.
So, both of us should risk every
Jewel Seed that we have!
Put out.
That's where it starts.
Where it all starts.
Nothing between us has even started.
So to start our true selves...
Let's begin...
Our first and last serious battle!
Make a little wish
Even though at times
I'll trip or get lost
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
Ah, going over the sea of cellophane
and over the forests
Passing through the silver wind
I was looking for something
neither of us had
Ah, I was just crying inside
a diorama of a city
Until I met that warm hand that
reached out to me that day
Among the swaying days,
I felt a strong gaze
Hey, I finally, finally
found the secret key
Make a little wish
Collecting the lemon-colored
drops from the moon
I want to keep a light shining
on the road that you travel down
Make a little wish
I wonder if there is something
I can do even though I'm so little
Because you're with me, I can
continue to smile and be energetic
The duel with Fate that
I decided I would have,
and the two individual's past and
present that it pieces together.
The Garden of Time begins to move.
What is the Alhazard that
Precia is longing for?
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 11:
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
On the next episode of
Magical Girl Lyrical Nanoha:
Episode 11:
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
Episode 11: Memories
That Lie Beyond Time
Episode 11:
Memories That Lie Beyond Time
Lyrical, magical, full power, all-out!