Finally...
You're finally mine, my sweet Marble Doughnut!
You've been swamped with work lately, huh?
Yeah! So, bon a—
Excuse me!
You're Amanogawa Kirara, right?
Oh, yeah.
Can we get your autograph?
Sure, why not?
They're fast!
Here.
Thank you so much!
You're quite the star.
Um, good luck with your work!
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
I'm beat...
You've sure got a lot of fans!
Everyone seems to adore you!
Kirara!
Pres?
The deal's finally done!
Which one?
The Japan Collection!
And you'll be one of the main models!
The Japan Collection? Me?
For real?
Yeah. You did it, Kirara.
That's great!
What is this "Japan Collection"?
It's a show featuring a hand-picked
selection of the most popular models!
It's the highest profile fashion show in the world!
And a middle schooler passing the selection is almost unheard of!
Goodness, that sounds wonderful!
This year's show is being held in New York.
Wow!
If you can pull this show off, you'll have a huge foothold in the overseas industry!
An overseas foothold...
It's finally here!
This is my big chance to make my dream a reality!
Dreams or the Precures?!
The Dazzling Kirara's Decision!
Is that the Castle of Stars?
That light...
Is this castle attempting to awaken like the Castle of Flames did?
Oh, let me introduce you, Kirara.
She's a rookie model who our agency has just started training.
I-I'm Akeboshi Karin.
It's nice to meet you! I'll work as hard as I can!
She'll be your assistant until the Japan Collection show.
Glad to have ya!
Th-Thanks! I'm glad to be here!
Good luck!
I heard the good news!
The Japan Collection?
Seems like you're finally in with the top models.
Why, thank you!
Good work!
Help yourself!
Thanks.
Next up, I need one more outfit for another shoot...
Want a shoulder rub?
I'm fine, really.
Anyway, Rinrin...
Rinrin?
If you wanna be a model,
you gotta watch and learn how it's done!
You don't have to wait on me hand and foot, 'kay?
Right!
Sorry, Kirara...
Don't sweat it!
Shine, O stars!
Precure!
Twinkle Humming!
Adieu.
Open!
The door to your dream!
See ya! I gotta get to work!
She's out quick!
Should you not rest?
Don't sweat it!
Take care of the rest!
Kirara sure seems busy.
Make your skin shine!
Take it from Kirara!
She did say she's been getting more TV work lately!
Kirara's so amazing!
Indeed.
Let's go.
Okay!
Kirara's shooting straight for her dream...
Huh? Minami!
My inspiration for modeling is definitely my mom, Stella.
I still remember the first time I saw her model on stage.
She lit up the theater the moment she stepped on the runway.
I was spellbound!
That's when I knew I wanted to be a model.
So you must look up to Stella a lot, huh?
Hate to admit it, but maybe.
With the Japan Collection under your belt,
you're finally among the top idols, so what's next?
To be a world famous top model!
That's been my dream since I was a little girl!
Good work!
Whoah, that's huge!
I tried making a doughnut...
but it came out a little oversized...
It's handmade? Wow!
But it's still too big...
Okay, let's split it!
Sure!
Bon appétit!
Wow, it's great!
Thanks!
So, seeing Stella made you want to become a model, right?
Yeah!
I can't imagine what it's like to have a supermodel as a mom.
What about you?
What made you want to be a model?
Oh, me?
Well, I...
I didn't have a dream.
Really?
I tried at school, sports, and art,
but I was never any good at them.
I wondered if there was anything I could do right.
When I was really down in the dumps,
a magazine cover happened to catch my eye... and I was hooked!
The model on that cover shone like a star!
The longer I looked, the more I cheered up,
and soon, I wanted to try fashion too!
I'd read magazines, look up cute clothes and hairstyles, practice poses, and before I knew it...
I started to want to become a model.
Well, your dream came true!
No, I still have a long way to go!
Besides, my dream is... I mean, I want to be a model, but not just any model...
Not just any model?
You mean like one who sings and dances, too?
Or are you shooting for Top Model just like me?
No! I mean...
My dream...
is a secret.
Don't leave me hanging!
Spill it already!
Not a chance.
Geez, now I'm dying to know!
What a despicable rainbow.
It's the power of the Precures...
Stop.
Right.
Freeze.
Here.
Crush the Precures.
Ensure they can never restore another rainbow again.
Such an undertaking is naught but beyond those two.
This task calls for naught but I, Shu—
You stay here.
Fine.
Crush the Precures.
Yes, crush them.
Are you nervous?
The whole world has its eyes on this show, so I can't mess up.
Kirara...
But part of me is just so excited to get on that runway that I can't sleep!
You're quite the powerful girl.
You spare no effort in anything you do,
be it modeling or Precures.
Modeling and Precures are what give me power.
That's why I can pursue them nonstop.
Right now, I'm shining brighter than ever before!
The world, my dream...
they're all waiting for me!
It's flying!
Is Kirara's plane going to be that big?
Yeah, I'm sure it will!
It's almost time to depart, Kirara.
Yeah!
Kirara, you'll be a superstar by the time you come back!
Then perhaps we should request an autograph while we still can?
Perhaps!
C'mon, girls...
I want an autograph too!
Huh?
Oh, not you too!
Precures spotted.
I spot a strong dream.
What perfect timing.
It will do perfectly.
Stop!
Freeze!
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
Rinrin?
My dream is to be a model...
A model who can turn those who see her into dreamers...
A model just like Kirara!
Rinrin...
The model on that cover...
shone like a star!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Rinrin!
Kirara!
You need to get to the airport!
We'll handle this ourselves!
We'll protect her dream!
You mustn't let your chance to stand on a global stage slip away!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
Dyspairvil.
Dyspair—
vil.
It didn't work?!
Dys!
Pair!
Get to the airport!
It's almost time for takeoff!
You've gotta hurry!
Go, Kirara!
Dys!
What are you waiting for?
If you don't leave now, your dream will escape you!
The Japan Collection is the start line I've worked so hard to reach...
The dream I've had since I was a little girl...
My dream is to become a world famous top model...
That's my dream...
Dream...
My dream...
is a secret.
Sorry, Rinrin...
but your secret's out.
Your dream was inspired by looking at me, right?
Huh?
Kirara!
Why?
I have to do it!
It's Rinrin's dream...
I want to protect it by my own hands!
Protecting dreams is a Princess Precure's duty!
And darn it, I'm a Princess Precure!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Dys! Pair! Vil!
Dyspair!
Vil!
Dyspaaaairvil!
Bzzzzzz!
Twinkle!
Girls!
Right!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Bubble Ripple!
Precure!
Scarlet Flame!
Dyspair...vil!
I won't... give up!
Dys! Dys!
Viiiiiil!
Dyspaaaair!
Give Rinrin...
Give Rinrin's dream...
baaaack!
Galaxy!
Sharanla, O Galaxy!
Precure!
Galaxy Chorus!
Dyspair!
Girls!
Right!
Mode Elegant!
Royal!
Dress Up Royal!
Let it ring across the lands!
Precure!
Grand Printemps!
Dreaming...
Blooming...
Adieu.
Is that all?
That is all.
Open!
The door to your dream!
Go get 'em, Kirara...
Thanks, Rinrin.
We can't apologize enough.
Thank you for your time.
Pres...
I know you, so I know you must have had your reasons.
But this has done some major damage to your career.
Forget going global, you'll have trouble finding local work for now.
Let's hope it's only for now.
I'm sorry...
Hello?
Yes, I'm terribly sorry...
It's finally time for the Japan Collection!
Man, these big-name shows sure pull out all the stops!
Kirara!
You don't need to worry about me.
But...
Back then, I just wanted to protect Rinrin's dream myself.
I don't regret it.
If I could do it all over, I'd still save her.
You could ask me a million times and my answer wouldn't change.
So I'm fine!
Kirara...
Well, I'll be in my room!
Don't sweat it!
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Flora!
Let the flower of yearning bloom
and fix your heart upon the land beyond the bounds
Never give in and never run away
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Kirara, you're retiring from modeling?!
Are you sure you want to abandon your lifelong dream?
I know! Listen up...
Oh!
We're in!
I don't know what you're planning, but I've made up my mind to quit.
It's all effort or none!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Shooting Star, Kirara!
To the Stage Sparkling with Dreams!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Hokkaido - Saki (Age 6)
Wakayama Prefecture - Tefu (Age 6)