How long are you gonna sleep for?
Get up already!
I'm still sleepy, Neppy.
No can do! We need to go on patrol again today.
Hey! No going back to sleep!
Anyway, just get up now.
Morning, Nepgear.
We leave in half an hour, okay?
O-Okay. Got it, Sis.
Ow. Neppy's super tiring to be around these days.
Yes, you're right.
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#09 The Challenge (Rebellion) Of Eden
What? So neither Nepgear
nor Neptune are around?
No. They've been going out on all-day patrols recently.
Patrol? Neptune?!
My thoughts exactly.
By the way, why are you in Lowee?
I came here to help Rom and Ram out.
As it turns out...
We found it using satellite imagery!
We found where Peashy is.
What?
Nothing out of the ordinary so far.
Yeah, Sis.
Neppy, we only just came here three days ago.
That's enough time for things to change.
It's a pack of wolves!
They weren't here the last time.
Let's get rid of them.
Huh? But there's pretty much no danger of them making it all the way to town.
Monsters are monsters.
Kill first, think later!
Wait, Sis!
Here they come.
Here we are!
Sorry for making you do this.
Don't be.
We want to see Peashy too.
Where's Peashy's place?
Well, going by the satellite image you sent us, probably that one.
Hey there!
Looks like this one's empty too.
That means...
She's gotta be on the top floor!
Was this really the right thing to do?
We came here by ourselves.
Nepgear and Neptune have been wanting to see Peashy too, haven't they?
Yeah, of course.
We just need to take Peashy with us to the Basilicom.
Once they get back home, they'll get a big surprise!
Yeah, a surprise!
That's right.
So, is this Peashy's home?
Hello!
Peashy!
What's with this place?
Where's Peashy?
Say no to CPUs!
We don't need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from
our dependence on them!
"Say no to CPUs"?
How rude!
This looks familiar.
Didn't we get one back then in town?
We should live our lives not under the CPUs, but under the right rules and regulations.
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
Say no to CPUs!
We don't
need goddesses!
Let's free ourselves from our
dependence on them!
So the person who was handing out the flyers back then is Peashy's mother?
I wonder about that.
Either way, it doesn't look like anyone's home.
Peashy...
I hate CPUs.
CPUs should all just disappear!
So why do I have to take part in this?
Not very good at giving up now, are we, Rei?
You forced me into this!
I'm just a social activist!
Why did you pick me?
I didn't have a choice.
My client for this job ordered me to drag you into it.
Who is this client?
No idea. I've only ever spoken to them over the phone.
But they pay well, and that's what matters.
I'm leaving.
That won't do, my dear.
You're an accomplice now.
You were the one who kidnapped her, weren't you?
Get it? Time you stopped rotting away over there and did your job.
She'll be ready soon as well.
Give us a hand, Plutia.
Don't wanna. I feel sorry for them.
What are you talking about? We're doing this for you too, you know.
You need to detect any major upheavals as soon as possible, right?
This was barely a change at all.
Besides...
Plutia transformed!
People who say they're doing something for others when they're actually doing it for themselves...
seriously piss me off.
Are you talking about me?
I don't believe there was anyone else here acting like a total pain in the ass.
I-I just wanted to patrol and look for upheavals—
Don't get the wrong idea.
I love you, Neppy.
But when I see people lying to themselves,
it makes me want to bully them to hell!
Stop it, Plutia.
I don't want to fight you!
Well, isn't that something? I feel the same.
Let me have my way with you.
Then there'll be no need for us to fight!
Oh no...
What am I to do?
What's wrong, Neppy?
Come at me!
Is this all you've got?
Stop it, Plutia!
Stop.
Please, just stop!
I'm telling you to stop!
Way to go.
I expected no less from you.
Stay my friend, Plutia.
I'd do anything for you.
I can't believe you're still lying to yourself.
Don't you have someone else you'd do anything for?
P-ko...
I should've spent more time with her!
I should've let her have more of my pudding.
If only I'd told her I wanted her to stay longer...
That's more like it.
If you can't do anything about your feelings,
just spit them out.
That's the Neppy we know and love.
Hello?
Hey, Plutia.
What, Neppy?
This felt better when you were in your HDD form.
Is that so?
Guess I'll transform just for you.
Just kidding!
This isn't half-bad either! It's like scrubbing my heart on a washboard!
Really?
Yay!
Sis! Plutia!
Huh? You wanna be scrubbed too, Nepgear?
Oh, come on.
I just got word from Histoire.
She said a new nation's been formed!
Say what?!
A new nation? What do you mean, Lady Histoire?
I'm not completely certain yet.
I just suddenly received word that a new nation has been formed on R-18 Island.
Anyway, it seems Neptune and Nepgear will go check it out along with the other CPUs.
What's going on?
Like I said, they're going to—
Why is Nepgear the only one who always gets to go to R-18 Island?!
No fair!
We're goddesses too, you know.
Take us along!
Why are you yelling at me about this?
This sucks!
We wanna go!
R-18 Island.
I knew that place was fishy.
Guess there was a point to that artillery after all.
We completely missed the signs.
Plutia.
Is that great power you're
looking for also over there?
Dunno, but it might be.
Watch out!
Hi, my lovely goddesses!
Don't tell me...
My humble greetings.
Welcome to the brand-new state, Eden!
Why, hello there, Noire.
How are you here?!
I confirmed that you were in prison just three days ago!
I know.
You came to visit me while I was serving my time, did you not?
Or to be more precise, you visited my body double.
You think you can mock me?
I'll get you now!
Oh, but you can't.
This is an independent nation.
I'm afraid that not even you have the jurisdiction to do that, Noire.
Dummy.
Who in their right mind would recognize a nation founded by a criminal?
You don't even have a CPU!
Give it up!
Noire!
Ouchies.
Flying is hard!
Are you...
...a CPU?
Yep, yep!
And my name is, um...
Oh, that's right!
I'm Yellow Heart!
Nice to meetcha.
How ridiculously massive!
There goes your unique identity, Vert.
What are you saying?!
Size doesn't matter! Shape does!
That's the same thing I've been hearing from the losers all along!
Can't sympathize with you there, I'm afraid.
Hey, you!
Ohmigosh! A person came out of my bum-bum!
I didn't come out of anything!
Just get off of me already!
I'm gonna catch that guy!
Huh? Catch?
Over my dead body!
A-Amazing strength!
That's a good girl, Yellow Heart.
These terrifying ladies are trying to catch me!
Not if I can help it!
If it's a fight you want,
you'd best be prepared!
Time for you to go out of production!
Not such a big deal, eh?
She's just a rookie.
This is fun!
Let's play more!
She's not hurt at all.
This is just part of the process.
The real objective is—
Hey!
Wh-What?
Do you know anything about that huge cannon?
N-Not a thing!
Anything's okay, no matter how small, so please tell me.
I have nothing to do with it.
But I saw you taking a walk near the cannon.
I was just passing by!
You simply reek of lies.
What fun!
Bring it on!
Hey!
What's with her?
L-Listen to me, please.
I was just tricked into helping out with this, you see.
I'm a victim.
Oh?
I hate people who play the victim.
Eek!
Please don't hurt me!
No bullying!
I also hate people who interrupt me when the going gets good!
Plutia!
Are you okay?
Yeah, she only grazed me.
Neppy, you can't.
I didn't want to pick a fight with the CPU of a new nation.
But you were the aggressor here.
We're not gonna go easy on you anymore.
Huh? You don't wanna play anymore?
Don't think you can just get away with anything by making them bounce!
Calm down, Vert.
About time for the climax, I suppose?
This is me going all-out.
Tricolor Order!
Ein Schlag!
Darjeeling Rotation!
Dual Edge!
Did we get her?
That's a "we didn't get her" flag if I've ever seen one.
My bad.
That hurt!
My transformation reverted.
P-ko?
Papa! Mama!
Where are you?
Right here.
You did well, Peashy.
Go on. You praise her too.
Atta girl.
Thanks.
Hold me!
Sure thing.
How cute.
P-ko! Why are you here?
Don't tell me you're...
No way, huh?
Go away.
I hate people who hurt my papa and mama.
I hate you!
P-ko?
What have you done to that girl?!
Me? Do something? I wouldn't dream of it.
I am but a consul.
I serve this lady here.
It's a little late for this, but let me introduce you.
This is our goddess! Eden's CPU!
Yellow Heart, also known as Lady Peashy!
Neppy.
Oh, also, Rei will be making an important announcement now.
Read it out, Rei.
Huh? O-Okay.
The CPU Yellow Heart-governed—
I can't hear you!
Eden hereby demands permission to export the adult goods manufactured in this country
to all other nations in unlimited quantities!
Failure to comply will be considered a declaration of war!
You wanna go?
You just formed this nation.
Your Share reserves are paltry!
Do you really think you can beat us?
You can say that again. It certainly is reckless.
But isn't this just the most exciting thing?
Does this mean...
we'll have to go to war with Peashy?
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
Rei will be making an important announcement now.
Read it out, Rei.
O-Okay.
Th-The passion...
I can't hear you!
The passion running through this body cannot be contained!
The Battlefront (Conflict) of Oblivion
Who the hell asked you to read erotica out loud?!