Meet Mitsuki Koyama,
12 years old.
Her debut song, "Myself" is
a big hit and
she wanted Dr. Wakaoji's opinion
of the song
but he said he didn't listen
to music anymore.
We all went after him in an attempt
to get him to listen to the song,
and we finally found him at
Mitsuki's parents' grave.
His true feelings toward music, revealed
at their grave, touched Mitsuki.
So, I wonder what's going to
happen today...
Got that?
Yes.
Oh, here it is! It's this person!
- Huh?
- What's going on?
I'm going to be on TV together
with this person tomorrow.
No kidding. "Fuyuko Komaki"?
Is she a geisha?
Idiot! Is everyone who wears
a kimono a geisha?
- She's an enka singer.
- An enka singer?
Why are you going to perform with
such a person?
You're an idol, aren't you?
Yeah. It seems this Miss Komaki
is going to do a music show
where she'll have
newcomer idols as guests.
And it turns out I'm going to
be on that show.
What's this, "From here on, I'd like
to sternly educate the next generation..."?
I see.
It's the gateway to idol success.
Gateway to success? What's that?
Well, I guess it's a path that you
must pass through in order to succeed.
Then say so in the first place.
"Gateway to success," he says.
You're sounding like an old man, Takuto!
Oh, I see. Meroko, you didn't know what
gateway to success meant, right?
Of course I did!
In the first place,
I'm older than you, Takuto!
Then if I'm an old man,
you're a really old lady, Meroko.
Whaaat?!
Hey! Takuto!
- What?! How mean!
- Oww! Cut it out!
- How could you say I'm an old lady?!
- Hey! Cut it out, Meroko! You're tickling me!
- I'm just a little older, you know!
- No, not there!
This will be my first trial.
Eichi. I'll do my best.
Wow! A television studio's
really big, isn't it?
Uh-huh...
Oh!
It's the weather girl I like!
Ahhh, to think I could
meet her here.
Oh! I've seen that person before
in a magazine!
Aww, I should've brought
my autograph book.
S-Stop that, Mitsuki.
Huh?
You're also one of them now.
Oh...I'm sorry.
More importantly, be sure to greet
Miss Komaki when you see her.
She's really picky about stuff
like that, so...
Okay.
And the greeting in
show business isn't "Hello," but...
- Good morning!
Good morning!
Good morning! We look forward to
working with you today.
Good morning.
Oh! Oh no!
Huh? "Good morning"?
Even though it's afternoon?
Good morning, Miss Komaki.
We will have the pleasure of
working with you today.
This is Full Moon, and
I am her manager, Masami Oshige.
Oh, hello.
So where's this "Full Moon"?
What?
Huh?! Mitsuki?!
Let's go, Tadokoro.
What?! Oh, umm!
Okay, see you later.
It's Miss Komaki,
so be sure to greet her!
Oh... H-Hello...
Hey, wasn't that Komaki,
just now?
What? That was Miss Komaki?
Th-That's right...
Ohh, I messed up.
Why didn't you come with me?
Huh?
You didn't know that was
Miss Komaki just now?
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
She wasn't wearing a kimono, so...
Enka singers wear jeans, too,
you know!
More importantly,
were you sure to greet her?
Huh? Yeah...
Kind of...
Hmm, I'm kind of worried...
MISS FUYUKO KOMAKI'S
DRESSING ROOM
Listen up.
This time, be sure to greet by saying,
"Good morning."
Okay.
Here we go!
May we come in?
It's Masami Oshige.
I'm sorry about before.
Once again, we will have the pleasure
of working with you today.
This is Full Moon, and
I am her manager, Masami Oshige.
Good morning. I'm Full Moon.
I'm looking forward to
working with you today.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Fuyuko Komaki.
Glad to have you here today.
She's new, so I'm sure she will
cause some inconvenience, but...
Oh!
Wow!
H-Hey, Mitsuki!
Wow! Kimonos sure
are beautiful, aren't they?
Miss Komaki, it's just like
the Shichigosan Festival!
Oh...
- Huh?
- Oh...
Aww, I messed up.
Miss Oshige seemed very depressed.
What should I do?
It's my fault.
Even so, that Komaki is really
an obnoxious old lady, isn't she?
Are you sure you should be
saying those things?
Shut up!
Jeez. That Komaki is really
an obnoxious old lady, isn't she?
And that balding guy who's
always by her side is creepy, too!
Oh, Tadokoro, right?
He's creepy, isn't he?
He's always kissing butt.
That being said, you were bowing
to Komaki, too.
Well, in order to survive in
show business, it can't be helped.
It's almost time for rehearsal,
so let's go.
Okay.
What was up with that?
How obnoxious.
How can you say that?
Oh, that's dangerous.
They should be sure to
put out their cigarettes.
You!
What're you doing smoking?!
You're a minor, right?!
Huh? Oh...
Really! Entertainers lately get
full of themselves so quickly!
Oh, no...
The people who were here earlier
didn't put out their cigarettes, so I...
My! To talk back after being admonished!
Jeez, kids today!
Unthinkable in the old days!
What?
Oh... Umm...
But it wasn't like that...
She's really an aggravating
old lady, isn't she?!
There's no way this girl would smoke.
I'm sooo annoyed!
H-Hey, Meroko.
Where are you going?!
Huh? Hey, you two!
Mitsuki.
It's almost time for rehearsal.
This time, let's pull it together so
we don't get scolded by Miss Komaki!
Okay.
Test, test.
Mic check... Mic check...
Wow!
There's a lot of staff here.
That's right.
Everyone's working hard
to broadcast your song.
Okay, Miss Full Moon.
Please stand by.
Go on. Do your best.
I-I will.
Okay. Then let's give it a go.
Okay, here we go.
Five seconds to go.
Four! Three!
Why do I like you so much?
My tears are falling...
Cut!
What's she doing?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It was so sudden,
I got startled.
I see. I'll be shooting the same way
during the actual show, too.
So please don't be alarmed.
All right...
Okay, let's go once more.
Five seconds to go. Four, three...
Why do I like you so much...
The lasers go off in the intro! Okay, go!
Cut!
Does that girl think something's
going to happen to her
if she gets hit by the lasers?
We can leave her on the back burner.
Let's do Miss Komaki's part first.
Okay.
Okay, we're changing the lights.
Please stand by.
We're going to take a break.
So in the meantime, talk to Miss Full Moon.
I understand. I'll calm her down.
All right, thank you.
We're taking a break.
Oh?
So by leaving her and
bolting out on your own,
what're you going to do?
- Oh!
- Huh?
There he is.
Huh?
Look, that guy!
The band guy who was in the magazine...
that girl was reading last night!
I'm going to be on TV together
with this person tomorrow.
Yaaaaah! How handsome!
Say! You're not looking for Komaki?!
Jeez, you're annoying.
It should be okay if
I stop off for a bit, right?!
Or could it be that you're jealous?
Huh?! Why would I be jealous?
Could this be my first "date"
in awhile?
Well, I feel bad for leaving
that girl alone, but...
I'm a heartless little devil, Meroko.
But you're a Death Spirit.
I know it's work,
but Fuyuko Komaki, huh...
- Huh?
I've started getting nervous, Takeda.
You have your cute points, too, eh, Ono.
Please stop kidding around.
Hey, Meroko.
Isn't that guy the "Myojo" reporter?
Huh?! That guy who was doing
the interview before?
Don't get so serious, Ono.
Although she may not look it,
Komaki's a pretty good person.
But I've heard
unpleasant stories about her.
Like she's temperamental,
she kicks around newcomers...
all kinds of stories.
Well, it's certain that she's stern
to the extent that she's misunderstood.
But that's her style of affection.
She just doesn't want them to fall in
to the same trap she fell.
Oh...
That thing a long time ago about her
being forced to become an idol?
Yeah. At the time of her debut,
she was forced to sing songs
she didn't want to sing.
Giving in to despair, smoking and
drinking and wasting her precious voice...
Memories from the past might
unintentionally come out with strong words.
I get it.
But, was her voice that good?
Yeah... How can I describe it?
It was like it'd slowly sink
into your heart.
There haven't been
any singers like that, lately...
Is that so?
I see. So that's why
she got angry like that...
She might be a good person.
Umm, and so...
There was a sudden change
in plans.
Now, your recording will be
done first, Miss Komaki.
I said that was no good,
but the director insisted.
I understand.
R-Really? Well, thank you.
But jeez, what is
that new girl thinking?
Saying rude things to you,
and now messing up your schedule!
She is truly a rude person!
Right, Miss Komaki?
Miss Komaki!
So the story goes.
I see... That was it...
I keep doing more and more
bad things to Miss Komaki.
Okay! I'll have to be sure
to apologize to her later!
Right.
Yeah.
Miss Komaki is coming in.
- Huh?
- Oh!
Here I go.
I'm sorry, Miss Komaki.
Huh?
Okay. Enough with the act.
Just get on out of here.
Oh, uh, well...
Huh?!
What's the meaning of this?!
What? What does this mean?
Miss Komaki will be recording from now.
I can't have you
do anything more
that would interfere
with her singing!
Why'd that guy throw Mitsuki out?
I bet Komaki told him to.
Oh! See?
She was a disagreeable person!
Jeez, what an outrageous newcomer.
I know. Let's get rid of
that Full Moon's song
and use that part for an advertisement
for Miss Komaki's new song.
Uh-huh...
Hey, what's he talking about?!
Takuto, we have to let her know!
Yeah!
What? They won't let me sing?!
It seems so.
I knew she was a bad person!
That's harsh.
Hey, what's the meaning of this?!
Why no song recording
for our Full Moon?!
But it can't be helped, can it?
She's done nothing
but rude things to Miss Komaki.
To even have
her schedule messed up...
Miss Komaki doesn't have
time to spare like you guys!
- Oh?!
- Hey!
But that's just too harsh!
- Mitsuki!
- Huh?
Miss Komaki!
Miss Komaki! Is it true that
I won't be allowed to sing?!
What're you talking about?
But, Mr. Tadokoro said...
He did something again, huh?
I did many rude things
to you, Miss Komaki.
But not being allowed to sing
is just too much.
It's my first TV appearance.
I must sing and then quickly...
Quickly what?
You want to quickly get famous, sell,
and get lots of attention or something?
No!
Then, what is it?
If it's not that, why did you think
to become a singer?
A promise...
I made a promise...
with someone special...
Someone special?
Yes. I don't know where
that person is right now.
But we made a promise!
We promised to reach for
our respective dreams and do our best...
So I'll keep singing and...
Think again.
What?
You've got your head up
in the clouds!
You'll give your all to singing and
eventually forget about some silly promise!
You'll just be singing for work!
No way!
Then...
Then, you're just singing
because it's your job, Miss Komaki?
Yes...I am a professional.
I don't think so...
I don't think so!
I want to sing, cherishing
such feelings!
If I can't, then I don't care
if I'm not a professional!
All I want to do is sing songs
that resonates in the hearts of people!
All right, Miss Full Moon.
If you would!
What? But I thought I couldn't sing.
It's okay.
What?
That whole thing was all
that balding guy's idea.
So you don't need to worry.
You can sing!
Right!
Okay, let's go once again.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Why do I like you so much?
My tears are falling
Mitsuki, promise me. That we'll be closer
to our dreams when we meet next.
Yes.
Because in the past there were
a lot of things I lost
And I couldn't sing
Okay, so we'll sell her as an idol.
That's it then.
Wait please!
I want to sing traditional songs!
was where I belonged
I found a loneliness...
Wait please!
in your eyes that day...
I don't think so!
I want to sing, cherishing
such feelings!
If I can't, then I don't care
if I'm not a professional.
All I want to do is sing songs that
reverberate in the hearts of people!
Why do I like you so much?
Your voice echoes and
it sounds almost sad...
Yes. That's nice!
This rivals the old Fuyuko Komaki.
I realize, now that I'm far away
What was supporting me
Miss Komaki...
Why do you do such selfish things?!
As of tomorrow,
you don't have to come anymore!
Miss Komaki!
Hey, look at this.
Oh, Miss Komaki.
Huh? Mr. Takeda, too?
Miss Komaki is recently putting
much effort into the fostering of newcomers.
So, how are the kids, these days?
Let me see.
Today, there was this one kid
who didn't greet me,
looked at a person's kimono and
said it was like shichigosan.
And to top it off, this kid made error
after error during rehearsal,
disrupted my schedule and
really gave me a hard time.
That must have been rough.
But...
this girl was a bit different from
the newcomers until now.
She was able to express
legitimate opinions to me.
Really?
It's embarrassing to talk about,
but I feel like
she got me to remember
what is most important as a singer.
It was like remembering why
I started this in the first place.
Then, this will have
an affect on your future?
Yes. That girl might have
woken me up.
So...
Until the day we meet again,
do your best. Okay, Miss Newcomer?
I will!
This is bad, Takuto!
Mitsuki's being targeted
by a tabloid photographer!
If this keeps going on,
her secret will be found out!
Damn! Her true identity
must not be revealed!
Hold on, Mitsuki. I'll save you!
Hey! You're not ready to handle this on
your own. You're still a rookie!
Shut up! I'll protect her,
no matter what!
Next time on Full Moon:
"The Dangerous Lens."
- Don't miss it!