This will probably be my will.
Things have calmed down a bit.
I can't say I'm happy with how things turned out,
but I've got a little bit of time,
so I figured it was a good time to write this.
My name is Megumi Sakura.
I was a Japanese teacher at Megurigaoka High.
No... I still am...
...even if this school is not the same place it was before.
The first time I realized it was when
I stood on the roof on that fateful day.
No, it was earlier than that.
I'd felt the signs that it was coming some time before.
School Living Club
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
When you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
Let's do it together! (Yeah!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
You know what you have to do after school
Come on, now, get together!
Don't sneak off to go home! (Hey!)
How about club? Let's get something done!
Don't go playing around!
That girl says "I'm back" (Welcome back!)
We'll be fine as long as we're together (Club!)
Everybody say: let's all be friends
Cause you wanna do it, if you wanna do it
when you wanna do it, you wanna do it!
I love you so much! (Yeah!)
We are enjoying our lives
We're having fun 24 hours a day
The red sun shines bright on the roof
I tried shouting out to it (We're doing great!)
We are right here
We have dreams here, too
If you're talking about buddies,
you're talking about your friends! (That's right!)
I tried saying "I love you!" (I love you so much!)
I love
Megu-nee
Back Then
Message Inbox
From: Mom
Good morning!
Good night.
From: Mom
Take care of yourself, okay?
Sender: Mom
To: Megumi
Subj: Good morning!
Good morning, Megumi.
Are you doing a good job as a teacher?
I'm a little worried about you.
You were always quiet as a child,
not that that's a bad thing,
but taking care of your students
Ribbon, ribbon...
Oh, no!
Mom again?
I'm driving!
I know you're worried.
I know you said I wasn't suited to be a teacher, Mom.
You said it when I started my education track,
and when I got my teaching license.
I wonder what's going on?
There are so many sirens this morning.
Teacher's Office
I wouldn't say you're not suited to be a teacher,
but you must maintain distance
between you and your students.
Saying you're on friendly terms
with students may sound nice,
but teachers are not on the same level as students.
I'm not suited to be a teacher, huh...
Alright?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
The vice principal says that to all the young teachers.
Right...
We're going to cut to a camera on the scene.
An alarming amount of accidents have occurred.
What's going on?
While the reason behind them is still unknown,
That's crazy.
Dozens of car accidents reported in Megurigaoka
citizens are hoping for a swift response to prevent more.
Alright, I'm going to pass back last week's tests.
Ishizuka.
Coming.
Shoujouji.
Here.
Sera.
Right here.
Takeya.
Yuki Takeya?
Here.
Look at her hat...
I'd like you to retake it after class.
You're so mean, Megu-nee.
Don't call me Megu-nee. It's Sakura-sensei.
On friendly terms with the students...
Is that what this is?
Bye, Sensei!
Goodbye!
Man, I feel bad for Megu-nee.
What is it?
Is it hard to concentrate with me right next to you?
I don't like tests.
But I don't dislike being with you, Megu-nee.
Then let's try our best, together.
Yuki-chan, I'm going to step out for just a minute.
I'll be right in the hall, so call me if you need me.
I'm hungry. I wanna eat some snacks.
Once you're done with your test, okay?
What's wrong, Ebisuzawa-san?
Don't you have club right now?
Umm...
Umm, sorry to bother you during a retake...
But you're the only person
I can ask for advice, Megu-nee.
Don't call me Megu-nee. It's Sakura-sensei.
I dunno, I just don't know anymore.
I don't know why I'm feeling like this.
Whenever I'm with him...
I see, your senpai, right?
I get it.
I think I get it.
You like him and want advice, right?
Wha... No, I...
Maybe, I dunno...
But...
maybe, I guess.
So there's nothing to worry about, then.
Yeah.
I feel better now that we talked.
I dunno why, but I can't say this stuff to anyone else.
But I can when I'm with you, Megu-nee.
Thanks for everything.
Maybe I'm not suited to be a teacher.
Still...
Okay!
You were gone so long!
Sorry.
I finished the test a long time ago!
Good work.
It's finally over!
I'm so tired, Megu-nee!
I told you, don't call me Megu-nee...
Maybe I'll get ice cream, maybe I will!
Don't buy any on your way home, okay?
Message Inbox
From: Mom
Emergency
Evacuate now!!
From: Mom
Please reply
...sending you this video.
...on the news
Huge traffic accidents in Megurigaoka
Huh?
That's really close to here!
Chaos at Local Shopping Mall
Train lines shutting down one by one
Suspension of service
Hey, Megu-nee?
Hmm?
Megu-nee, are you listening?
What're you looking at?
Hey now, don't look at other people's phones!
Darn!
I'm going home!
Takeya-san!
It looks like the trains aren't running.
Maybe you should wait here a little while?
Oh, they aren't?
Aww, but I'm hungry!
Oh, that's right!
Let's go up to the roof!
They're growing baby tomatoes up there, right?
Yes, but we can't eat those.
And students aren't allowed up there on their own.
Oh, then we can say we're
observing the Gardening Club!
It's okay then, right?
All right.
The door's unlocked.
Oh, sorry!
I forgot to lock it again!
Could you please lock it for me?
Wow!
Oh, are you in the Gardening Club?
As you can see.
Are you here to observe?
Yeah!
Wow, those tomatoes look really yummy!
Would you like to eat one?
Can I?
Sure, if you're going to help.
Yeah!
Yuri-san, do you always do all this work alone?
Oh, no.
For some reason, nobody else came today.
Why isn't Mom picking up?
Call Ended
Home
Incoming Call
Kamiyama-sensei
Hel-
Are you okay?!
Sakura-san, where are you right now?!
Who's that?
Maybe another club member who's on duty.
The roof? Lock the door,
and don't let anyone up there!
The teacher's office is al-
Wait a sec, I'm coming!
Wait!
Megu-nee?
I have to open the door for them.
Please!
Please, open the door!
Ebisuzawa-san?
Hurry, lock it!
He's hurt!
What happened?!
Sensei, we have to get him to the infirmary!
You can't go down there!
You can't anymore!
What's happening?
Everyone just...
Turned into those things,
and then the Track Club was surrounded...
Then, Senpai...
Senpai?!
We have to go out and call an ambulance!
No, I've been calling for one,
but my phone won't connect!
I don't get it...
Why?
Why is this happening?
Dammit, they're here!
We can use the Gardening Club's locker!
Wakasa-san?
Takeya-san, push the washing machine over here!
Senpai...?
Ebisuzawa-san!
Ebisuzawa-san, run!
You dummy.
Why are you crying?
And what's wrong with you?
Wearing that weird hat...
Sensei, what should we do?
With school, and outside as it is...
Sensei?
Sensei!
A lot of people lost their lives.
Students and teachers.
Those girls are the only ones left here.
I believe someone will come to save us.
As long as I'm alive, I'll protect them.
After all,
I'm their teacher.
School Living Club
Let's eat!
It's so dry.
I can't say I dislike hardtack,
but it's hard eating it for a meal.
I agree.
The power's out at school today, so we can't cook.
But I like blackouts!
They're kinda exciting!
Our water heater's electric, you know.
What?!
So we don't have any hot water.
Nooo, my bath...
You okay?
I hope it rains.
Why?
Then I could take a shower!
What are you, a dog?
That's true.
Not even Taromaru would do that.
Let's go camping!
Huh?
I said camping!
Camping?
C'mon, you know other clubs have
field trips and go camping, right?
Well, we're the School Living Club,
so we should camp out at school!
Oh, that sounds great!
You're going to pitch a tent in the classroom?
I get it, there's no electricity when you're camping.
We should have a tent in our room.
It should fit four people.
Then it'll fit all of us!
Hey, what about me?!
I-it's okay, we can fit you in
if we squish together, Megu-nee!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
Oh, sorry, Megu-nee.
No, I'm kidding. We need a lookout, after all.
Oh.
Megu-nee...
thanks for working so hard all the time.
What's this, all of a sudden?
Good work.
Yeah, thanks, Megu-nee.
Good, uh, work.
Goodness, don't call me Megu-nee.
It's Sakura-sensei.
Right!
It really feels like camping!
You're right. Now's the time when
we tell scary stories, right?
It feels like camping, sure, but...
No way!
Did you know that on a dark night like tonight...
Chop!
Owie!
Do you have any stories that aren't scary?
No, not really.
Really?
You've gotta have something!
C'mon!
Please stop touching me so much.
Aww, why?
Pssshhh
Huh? Mii-kun, you're bright red!
C'mon, let her go.
Ooh, then let's talk about romance!
Like guys we like and stuff!
Sure, but do you even have
any of those stories, Yuki-senpai?
I sure do!
Wait, maybe not.
C'mon now.
What about you, Kurumi-chan?
Ah, she avoided the question.
You love your shovel, don't you, Kurumi-chan?
I don't think that falls under "romance."
Before, when I lost my crush,
you comforted me, didn't you, Yuki?
I did?
You're good at that, Yuki-senpai.
Ah, nope, I might be wrong.
Yeah.
Whaaa...?!
You guys are so mean!
I hear Megu-nee!
Shoot, really?!
Whoa, that was fast!
Now, nobody's being a bad girl
and staying up late, are they?
It's very late, so get some sleep, okay?
Okay, we're good!
Megu-nee's keeping a lookout for us, huh.
Man, that scared me.
Were you scared?
I'm not scared of Megu-nee!
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
Hey, you know, we're going to
graduate sooner or later, right?
Uh-huh.
But Megu-nee's always going to be at our school.
Thinking about that makes me kinda sad.
I know how you feel. She's a great teacher.
Yeah, without her, we wouldn't be a club.
You're right.
Yeah, she's so nice.
She gives a lot of homework, though.
And sometimes her spelling's off.
Uh-huh!
But she's so nice!
Though she gives a lot of homework.
Wait, we're going in circles!
Sensei must...
Megu-nee must be someone you really love.
Yup, I love Megu-nee!
Talking on our way home
Telling each other our secrets
Even when the 5-o'clock chime rings out
I wonder why I feel we still haven't talked enough
A tiny four-leaf clover
Sways in the gentle breeze
Hey, I'm sure that yes, I'm sure
I hope tomorrow will be sunny, too
We walked the road together
Always saying we'd meet at the usual place
Ah, the fluffy clouds above
Seem like they'll be burned, they're shining so bright
Even if, one day, these days
Are but a faded memory
I want to give you
A lot of smiles right now
Next Time!
Hey Megu-nee, why did you become a teacher?
Oh, you want to know?
Eh, maybe not.
What?!
'Cause you'll always be Megu-nee!
Field Trip
Next time on School-Live, episode 4:
"Field Trip"