Hurry and wake up!
I bet you stayed up all night again.
I saw your light on until at least 2:30!
Ryuji... from inside my ears... the rice... the rice... shiny, shiny...
If it's about breakfast, I brought it.
I'll heat it up for you, so go wash your face!
Breakfast?
Alright!
Next, dishes and laundry.
This is such an empty room.
A box?
What is this?
An album?
This...
What the hell are you looking at?
Taiga! This is-
Yes, it is! It's a collection of Kitamura-kun's pictures. You got something to say?
Because even if you do, I'm not listening!
This...
is Kitamura?
What do you want from me!? I don't know why, but they're always blurry!
Whenever I try to take Kitamura-kun's picture, something...
Want me to take some for you?
Pictures.
Me.
I'm not that great, but I'm at least better than...
Wait just a sec!
H-How many can I have?
What kind of picture would be good?
His profile? Softball practice?
When he's eating lunch, that would be great too!
I'm telling you, I'll take as many as you want!
Even so, there are certain ones I want!
Take lots and lots for me.
Good morning!
You're later than usual.
Yeah,
I went to the student council room first.
O-HA!
That's old. That's way too old, Taiga.
Ah! I take it back... umm...
Aisaka!
O-ha!
I'm going ahead.
O-ha?
Hey, did you take it?
What?
The "O-ha!" of course!
It was too sudden!
How the hell was I supposed to take it?
You useless dog...
Now, wait a minute.
Hey, Maruo, look at this.
The model featured here looks just like you.
You guys, it's almost time for the morning assembly.
Stop chatting and go to the yard.
Maruo, you're cold!
Even if he is the vice president of the student council, he's way too serious.
I wanted at least some kind of reaction.
Me, too!
Kitamura is actually pretty popular with the girls.
What is that, "Maruo"?
Maybe I should roll you up instead!
Everyone, line up!
Hey, you bastards.
It seems there are some idiots who forget their student notebook and still come to school.
We've got proof.
According to the disciplinary committee's report from last week's bag check...
How many was it...
59 people.
In the whole school, 56 people didn't have their student notebook...
Sorry, it's 59 people.
I don't give a damn about the exact number,
but forgetting to bring your student notebook is the same thing as forgetting about the pride of Ohashi High School!
You got it, you bastards!?
Yes!
Good.
Can you really talk about other people?
You've forgotten something too!
A-Aisaka...
Hey, you, shorty. Did you say something?
You've forgotten the "At ease!"
AT. EASE.
My bad.
Everyone, at ease!
Why the hell do we have to line up like this even in high school?
Lining up like idiots, listening to this useless crap on and on.
Is it really that bad?
You're just putting your hands on your waist.
What did you say!?
Wait, Aisaka!
This is great. You're starting out the day with all this energy.
President, you need to calm down too!
What the hell do you know!?
The feeling of having to put your hands on your waist even if you have no back or labor pain...
Aisaka!
Aisaka,
just hold it in for now.
I'm sorry, President.
Please continue the morning assembly.
O-Okay...
What, what's going on?
They said the Tenori Taiga bit into the president.
That girl...
And the good does.
She's obviously depressed...
Or is she actually happy?
Okay, okay, that's enough, Haruta-kun.
Um, next is...
Aisaka-san?
You look pretty happy today.
Let's have you read it then.
Um... Or not.
Haruta-kun?
No way!
Give it your best shot!
Please, listen!
Here's your lunch.
I don't want it. I'm not hungry.
I fought with the student council president.
I bothered Kitamura-kun.
But...
I was lifted by my arms.
Happy, happy, so happy.
Taiga?
But I want to apologize!
Don't worry about it!
The president isn't the type to care about that kind of thing.
You brought your lunch? Can I eat with you?
That sounds great! Let me join you for this meal!
Doing stuff like this from time to time is great.
Yeah!
I'm hungry!
Thanks for the food.
What's in my lunch today, what's in my lunch?
How did it end up like this?
Fried chicken!
Taiga! You're over-reacting!
Taiga's lunch has lots of different kinds of food!
Dammit, I forgot, our lunches are...
Aisaka, you've been bringing your lunch lately, right?
Are you making it yourself?
T-This...
Takasu?
It's not what you think.
Remember?
Kushieda was doing it too, right? Working part time to decorate cell phones.
I've been trying to earn some pocket money by making lunches...
Really?
I'd like to try one of Takasu's lunches.
Me too! I bet that lunch would be brown-colored and really cool!
I'm excited!
T-Then I'll make some for everyone next time.
Kitamura-senpai, Kushieda-senpai.
Um... it's about time...
It's the softball club manager.
A meeting?
Sorry, you two go ahead and eat.
Okay.
That was bad.
Really bad.
Taiga?
Hey,
do you really want Kitamura to know that I'm making your lunch?
Just when they finally believe that there's nothing going on between us...
What do we do? What do we do? WHAT DO WE DO?!
Calm down!
Geez.
Why do you always get like this whenever Kitamura is involved?
You have to be more careful from now on, got it?
What? If you got something you want to say, swallow first, then say it.
Hey,
there's no meat in today's lunch.
If you want meat all the time, get adopted by a family who always does so!
Public facilities' mildew is fascinating. The roots are deep.
But you were really unlucky to be found by me!
Taka-chan! Let's finish up!
I'm going to finish up the rest. You can go ahead.
Lucky!
I'll leave it to you.
You damned black demons. What, giving up already?
I'll finish you off with one of my 48 Takasu Ryuji housework secret techniques: Takasu Style Mildew Buster!
Ryuji!
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Hurry up and come! You dog!
Wha- Taiga!
This is the boy's bathroom...!
Never mind! Hurry up!
Hey!
What is it, Taiga?
What are you do-
That's it?
Kitamura?
Hurry! Hurry and take it!
This girl...
Now, now! Hurry!
I got it.
Um, if I remember right, the shutter...
Now, that one!
Wait a sec, I'm figuring out the settings.
Enough! Gimme!
I get it.
That's how she got all those blurry pictures.
Amazing. Kitamura-kun, there, there!
Goooo!
Hey!
Hey, he's waving really hard.
Shut up.
Klutz.
Welcome to Sudoh-Bucks!
Chef, there's an order for American coffee and Neapolitan spaghetti.
One Neapolitan coming up!
I can't believe they haven't been sued yet.
And over here...
You didn't have to print all of them out.
Hey, you're drooling!
There are many, many Kitamura-kuns. Kitamura Carnival.
What are you doing!?
They say young people snap easily, but that's going way too far!
I'm going to help, you useless dog.
Since... you took pictures and all.
You don't have to.
I'd like to be able to clean the futon tomorrow...
If you keep saying crap like that, I'll slice you up.
Slice? Hey...
And...
Next time, you're going to make lunches, right?
For Minorin and...
K-Kitamura-kun.
Alright. Can you peel potatoes?
Don't make fun of me! Of course I can... I just peel these right?
Geez.
Homemade food for Kitamura-kun?
That's true.
Since Kushieda's also going to eat the lunch I make, I must put some effort into it.
What are you doing!?
What? I got all the skin off, see?
AND, if I do it like this, I won't ever cut my hands!
Um... well...
Rice balls for dinner? It's like a picnic.
This rice ball is small and cute too!
I made that!
No way!
Taiga-chan, you're a genius?
If it's these, you won't hurt yourself no matter how much you practice.
You don't have to peel anything, either.
I told you: eat, then talk.
It's yummy!
I can taste Taiga-chan's hands!
Here, I made some tea.
They'll get messed up if you don't put them in an album!
Shut up. Annoying mother-in-law.
What, just when I was thinking of laminating the ones you liked.
You can do that?
Yup.
Wait a minute.
Um...
If you laminate them, it doesn't matter if you fall down or get them wet, they're still safe.
Taiga...
Something wrong?
N-Nothing!
It doesn't have to be just one picture.
Two or three...
Shut up! Just wait a minute!
I'm picking them now!
What's with you, all of a sudden?
I...
I'm going home.
What, all of a sudden?
I can't calm down and pick them out here. I'm going home to pick them.
Hey, Taiga! Wait!
What's with her?
I want a picture too...
Of Kushieda.
Look, look at this!
T-This is... a light yellow dead squid?
Or... a slime?
It's amazing, isn't it? I made pudding in a bucket!
T-This is?
How should I call it? A 'psychological browser crasher'...
Pudding in a bucket!
It's every girl's desire!
But it's so big, it didn't go too well.
The part that's supposed to be jiggly and the part that's supposed to be smooth got mixed together and that was...
You ladies over there! Look at my bucket play I did with all my might!
This is..
Kushieda's picture.
The part that's supposed to be jiggly and the part that's supposed to be smooth...
Got all mixed together and that was... somehow weird but harmoniously beautiful...
It's a little different from what I wanted, but...
Well, this is okay too.
Huh?
What are you doing?
What? It's just Ryuji.
You're still picking them?
Shut up.
What's with that?
You went home so suddenly yesterday.
I told you, if you can't decide, I'll do as many as you want.
What are you doing!?
If you're going to comment so much, you pick them out!
I'll leave it to you.
How can I pick out something like this?
That Taiga...
Is that Aisaka's?
Yeah...
That's a picture of me.
Um, this is... uh, how do you say it...
That reminds me. I had totally forgotten.
I had just left it inside.
This brings back memories.
Y-You... Why do you have this picture?
The photography club used to sell pictures...
And this was one of those...
Not that!
Why do you have Taiga's picture?
I liked Aisaka, so I put it in.
That's it.
Then she turned me down flat in one second after I confessed.
I said it out loud!
Please keep this quiet.
W-Wha-
Takasu, what's wrong?
What the hell's that?!
What a waste.
What did you expect me to do?
When he told me, "I like you," I was surprised, and turned him down...
But then, after that...
I started noticing him, then, somehow... Somehow, I fell in love with him!
It was... right here.
Aisaka!
Your straight-forward personality, the way you don't bother to hide your anger, it's great!
I've fallen in love with you!
Kitamura...
It's a weird confession, isn't it?
Was he praising me or picking a fight?
But I was happy.
Since I thought I was alright.
As there was someone out there...
Who needed me just how I was.
What is this...
Why was it that the room Taiga lives in somehow flashed through my mind?
There were so many pictures...
But one wasn’t there.
I want that face.
The moment that Kitamura-kun confessed to me.
One more time...
W-What embarrassing things are you making me say, you useless dog!
It's my fault!?
Who else could it be!?
To be needed by someone.
What does that mean to Taiga?
She's such a clumsy girl.
If she's going to fall in love later, she shouldn't have turned him down so quickly.
Right, Inko-chan?
And Kitamura is Kitamura!
If he's going to follow through, then he should take responsibility and follow through!
You think so too, Inko-chan?
You tell 'em, Inko-chan!
Isn't it okay?
Kawashima Ami, that natural beauty, has suddenly appeared.
The only thing I can say is: women are scary!
What's that? Ami-chan doesn't understand!