The Sexual Harassment Trial is Popular
Street Number 2
Maruko Town Shopping District
Otani High School
To rest quietly at the end of the week
requires working diligently on the other six days of the week.
Not even the God in Genesis is exempt from this law.
- Kirk H. Hill
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
七色の黄昏おりてきて
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
The rainbow colored twilight is falling
The wind is kinda refreshing
風はなんだか涼しげ
Kaze ha nandaka suzushige
Saturday night is lively
土曜日の夜はにぎやか
Doyoubi no yoru ha nigiyaka
The only thing that'll brighten soon are your dark emotions
暗い気持さえすぐに晴れて
Kurai kimochi sae sugu ni harete
Everyone can't wait
みんなウキウキ
Minna ukiuki
Can't wait.
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Let's go downtown
DOWN TOWNへくりだそう
DOWN TOWN he kuridasou
Can't wait!
ウキウキ
Ukiuki
[Sexual Harassment Case] From Volume 1 Story 3
Arashiyama,
you have many good things that you can't lose in against Tatsuno.
Trust me, I know.
No good!
My head just decided on its own to remember Mr. Moriaki!
And it also manipulated the memory rather conveniently!
It's my well earned Sunday!
I shouldn't think about school or teachers.
I'll concentrate on this novel today and finish reading it!
Stop right there!
Take a good look.
What you're holding is a chikuwa stuffed with mustard.
You wouldn't normally confuse that sort of thing with dynamite.
You're the only one who could be the perpetrator!
No!
Why did the main character have to have the teacher's face?
Why...
Ow.
Sis! Let's play!
Sis is occupied.
Lies. You were just zoning out.
Adults also treat zoning out as work.
Alright. You're a good girl so
play with your brother, ok?
Takeru, play with Yukiko.
Whaa.
C'mon, there's something you can play together, right?
Something that beeps and bloops.
Do it please.
Aaah!
What... are you doing?!
I didn't get to save!
That hurts!
It's your fault!
Ow!
Mom!
Sis is...
Hotori! What are you doing?!
Augh, enough, enough!
Isn't today your day off?
Why did you go out of your way to come here?
Something terrible happened to me at home.
Sanada might visit, so I came here.
Sanada?
So Tatsuno is at that age...
Compared to her, Hotori is so...
Anyways Tatsuno, hear me out -
Recently, when I think about the teacher,
this part of me feels funny.
Oh really, Hotori too?
I know. Whenever I think about math tests, my stomach hurts.
Ah no, I don't mean my stomach.
I mean, things like differentials and integrals are beyond reason, aren't they?
... 7-11?
Differentials and integrals!
You can talk about difficult things, but I won't understand!
When I was in elementary school, I stumbled on dividing fractions.
If I flip the top and bottom... will that work?
It still makes me uneasy.
And you've managed to make it this far.
Tatsuno isn't very good at listening.
Though it's very Hotori like to not realize
the topic switched from love to math.
It's said that people who handle dividing fractions easily
will also handle their lives easily.
Oh!
I've also seen that movie.
Even if you can't follow logic,
if you're the type that can make conversation
then your life will move forward smoothly.
There are formulas for life, huh.
And now we've moved to theories of life.
Leaving logic aside, if you can make conversation well, you'll be OK.
You can figure out the perpetrator in anime detective shows
if you follow a formula, even if you can't reason it out.
Really?! How?
The character voiced by the best paid voice actor is the perpetrator.
Augh. Now I'll always know who the perp is.
I shouldn't have asked.
Hotori, if you're free, why don't you go to the grocery store and buy some potatoes and onions?
But... I'm a customer today.
Then pay for your meal and go home.
Tsk. I'll go then.
Lend me that thing
that goes vroom vroom.
♬〜Potatoes and onions, potatoes and onions
♬〜Potatoes...
HEY!
Potatoes!
Onio...
Hey, that was dangerous!
What is it, jeez?
What? You stopped me for nothing?
Seeing dangerous people like that make me think it's Spring.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S DANGEROUS!
I didn't hit you that hard!
Women don't understand the seriousness of things.
It's your fault for suddenly standing in front of me!
It's your fault!
I told you before to not ride on the streets, didn't I?!
If you don't knock it off I'm going to report this incident!
Don't ride on the streets?! Are you saying I should ride it in the house?!
My mom will get pissed off!
This kid...
So you're putting the law below your mom...
That's why you're a minor!
Listen, ok? You have no license. You have no license plate!
You have no headlights! You have no turn signals!
Due to the above reasons, you're not prepared to ride on the street.
It's the same as a burger without the patty, cheese, lettuce, or pickles!
It's a depressing burger.
Can I just eat the buns?
I can't stand this anymore.
Hmph.
Fine fine, I'll stop riding.
Huh. She's obedient today.
Cuz I've arrived already.
Milk is best with bean jam bun, poko~
Running errands for the hag?
You got a problem with grandma, punk?
We have good carrots today! They've just been picked! Carrots! Freshly unearthed!
There's still mud stuck to them. Come get 'em!
Be quiet! I'll forget what I came here to buy!
Uhh... I feel like they were ingredients for curry...
Ah yeah, one of them was definitely potatoes and...
Potatoes and...
Carrots please!
Sure, thanks for your business!
Oh yeah, Hotori,
take this with you.
The expiration date is tomorrow so drink it all.
Thank you.
If she drinks milk she might get a bit bigger.
Haha, ain't that right.
What did you say will get bigger?
We might have a sexual harassment case depending on your answer!
Cop!
Try not to laugh with him.
Yes!
I want to laugh, poko~
Perverted old men. I'll remember this.
Don't ride it. Push it home,
please.
Headlights and license plate, eh?
And turn signal and license!
Don't simplify the problem. I'll confiscate your scooter!
You can't handle this if I floor it.
Wha?
Let's go, Tetsuo!
Tetsuno isn't... wait, I told you not to ride it!
Jeez.
She'll go far away as a bride someday.
And then it'll be as if the town has lost its fire.
But right now, it seems like she's starting fires.
I'm back.
Sanada really came.
Huh?
She's already back.
You mean she's late, right?
The cop said he was going to arrest me or something.
What did you do?
Depressing burger.
Wha?
Good job. Have some coffee?
I'll just have a cup please. I'm having milk.
Oh, so you'd like to get bigger?
It's too late for drinking milk to help now. You've already past your growth spurt.
Even if you were to get a little smaller
it would be nothing to worry about.
That's just who you are.
Arashiyama is Arashiyama.
You bastard! You and everyone else! Just ignore my face and talk about my boobs, huh!
I'm going to have a sexual harassment trial.
No! Objection!
I-I was talking about your height.
Yeah! Sanada isn't that kind of person!
Members of the audience may not speak without permission.
I'll be Sanada's attorney. Objection!
Objection denied.
Like I was saying, height, not boobs.
I said potatoes and onions...
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used as evidence against you.
That's not a court, that's an arrest!
Forget the boobs, do something about her brains.
The popular name is "Sore Machi", poko~
The world affairs are...
[The Sign Girl is Popular] From Volume 1 Story 8
Maid!
What's that?
[The Sign Girl is Popular] From Volume 1 Story 8
It's the maid greeting.
Why does "maid" get a Vulcan sign?
Wrong.
The Vulcan one is like this
Maid is like this, turning into an M.
If we make this our shop's greeting, we'll get more customers.
Nonsense!
What makes you say we'll get more?
Mai... huh?
I can't do it.
Either way, forget it.
Wha?
But if we aren't distinctive, customers won't come.
Meeting in session. No one may enter.
Head maid! I found this...
Customers don't come cuz you're an idiot.
The world reflects one's own heart.
When the heart is peaceful, the world is filled with affection, but
when the heart is in pain,
the angry waves of adversity start to swirl.
Again.
There's also an arrow here.
Here too.
Yo. Aren't you the dry cleaning guy?
What's going on with you two?
For some reason there are arrows posted around town.
Oh. I was actually walking around and following them.
Is this some sort of scheme?
Hey, look.
That's grandma's place, isn't it?
Yo.
Oh my. Some bad characters again.
Welcome hom...
Maid!
An inconsistent shop, eh?
Grandma, what's with those arrows?
Are you doing something?
What, arrows? Don't know about them.
Nyahaha.
I shall explain.
I spent two days around town putting up arrows
so customers would come following them.
Sometimes ninja-like.
Sometimes shinobi-like.
They're both the same.
Hahaha, like that would make customers come.
Didn't you?
We did.
Might as well stay.
Let's have a meeting about the festival.
Yeah. We've already come this far.
Three cold waters.
Yes,
three cold waters.
three coffees please!
Three katsu curries. Alright, got it.
You're right here, don't play telephone!
Excuse me...
Welcome.
Welcome hom...
Maid!
These arrows...
Neheheh!
Another person fell into my trap!
Let's rename this place "Café Antlion!"
No.
So it was you after all.
What did you peel them off for, you four eyed officer
Megapoli!
You can't just go and put these up.
There were 30 of them.
I worked so hard putting them up!
Why do you have to be my foe?
I didn't mean to do that.
Whenever I take action for the sake of the town
I always run into you first.
You're always getting in the way of my life!
I can say the same to you.
Sorry,
our maid is an idiot. Here, have a cold one.
Chew on the ice and return to your den! Leave! Leave!
I can't stand this anymore.
Didn't we tell you not to be
rude to the customer?!
Alright?
Next time I don't know what'll happen.
I'll shoot.
What a stupid fool.
Whoa, trying to imitate Beat Takeshi.
Bad impression.
What? Try saying that again!
Wait! Tell me your names!
Oh? So you spent over 30 minutes chasing middle schoolers?
Head maid, what should we do with her?
There are no special considerations.
I'm cutting thirty minutes of pay.
Why? I did it very seriously.
If you seriously chase middle schoolers, catch them.
I mean before that! The original greeting and the arrows.
That was for the sake of getting new customers,
look at these never changing faces.
What? Do you have a complaint about your customers?
Aren't we helping you out by eating katsu curry at such a weird hour?
I won't be able to eat dinner now.
Why are you giving this to me? I like eating with my family.
Men with families are so...
But I kinda understand what Arashiyama is saying.
We've been numbed to it recently but
the maid café's usual customers are all from the shopping district.
I'd like more guys to come who enjoy maids.
Why do the customers have to be pleasant to the staff?
But Arashiyama's battle plan completely missed the mark.
That greeting is especially terrible.
Wha? Well at least we should make this place stand out more.
That's true. The sign looks like an impromptu thing.
How about putting in an order for a new sign?
Agreed!
Hotori was a crybaby, as cute as a grandchild.
But now she can talk about my management...
Oh? What's the matter, Hotori?
I see, I see.
C'mon, have some curry.
I couldn't give him the chocolate after all.
I'm such a wimp...
I see, I see.
C'mon, have some curry.
I'm crying cuz I lost my wallet.
I see, I see.
C'mon, have some curry.
Grandma?! What's with that outfit?!
What revolution is this?
Maid cafés seem profitable.
C'mon, have some curry.
Ate it, didn't ya Hotori. You ate it.
I have something to discuss.
Since you've eaten curry free for the past 10 years
you'll have to work here to pay it off your debt.
What?!
Hotori was a crybaby, as cute as a grandchild...
I agree that we should do something about the sign
to make our shop stand out.
Why don't we try something?
Really?
But what are we going to do?
Well, there's a giant piece of cloth on the second floor, so
can you make me a showy banner?
Things have gotten interesting!
You better take it seriously.
It's over here.
And there's also paint.
What are we gonna write?
I'll write "Maid Café Seaside" really big!
Do you even know how to write the characters for café?
I do!
Ok!
You talk big... but the results taper off like a tail.
The characters are like you.
Give me some paint. I'll write "Popular" in the empty space.
(JARO - Japan Advertisement Review Organization)
Won't JARO complain?
It'll be fine. We'll be popular after the sign goes up.
Ok!
Yes!
Note: She just thought of a nickname for Tatsuno when she spoke.
Nice Tatsun!
Sauce katsudon in milk, poko~.
A bit over there. Pin it down.
Finished!
Grandma, come look!
We worked hard on it
I see. Looking forward to it.
Note: The ない next to the sign turns popular into immature.
Immature...
That bastard dentist Naitou!
Seems like no matter what I do today, the world gets in my way.
Damn world!
The world reflects one's own heart.
When the heart is peaceful, the world is filled with affection, but
when the heart is in pain, the angry waves of adversity start to swirl.
I'll take this down!
I'll cut this down and defeat the world!
Arashiyama, please do that sort of thing at night.
This is what you need to be ninja and shinobi like for.
What do you mean, ninja like?
What are you doing to my sign?
Sorry.
I did a very immature thing...
If you guys were to put on shows every day
you might get more customers, eh?
In other words, when you returned to the shop
the victim was already collapsed here, right?
Suspect A: The beautiful owner of a boutique.
Suspect B: The taxi driver that drove her.
Suspect C: The president of an IT company who invested in the boutique.
The voice of the boutique owner is kinda cute and probably popular.
The poor looking taxi driver's voice actor has an austere voice.
The president definitely has a relationship with the boutique owner.
Err I mean, that voice seems popular too... it's a handsome voice.
Who's voiced by the best paid voice actor?
You couldn't possibly be suspecting Sachiko?
He's the perp!
Wha? How did you know?
He only played dead.
But he hasn't said anything yet. How do you know?
This is a rerun.
Mom! Sis is...
Hotori! What are you doing?!
Augh, enough, enough!
ひ、
1,
Hi,
ふ、
2,
Fu,
ひ、ふ、み、よ
1, 2, 3, 4
Hi, fu, mi, yo
退屈や
Living alone is boring,
Taikutsu ya
ロック魂携えて 一人暮らしの 爆音人生
Listening to explosive music with my rock soul.
Rokku tamashii tazusaete hitori gurashi no bakuon jinsei
天然の 提灯河豚のほっぺたで
My pufferfish cheeks
Tennen no chouchin fugu no hoppeta de
町をカオスに 今日も巻き込む
Pulls the town into chaos.
Machi wo kaosu ni kyou mo makikomu
ツンデレは インテリジェンスの証しなり
As a sign of the tsundere's intelligence
Tsundere ha interijensu no akashi nari
今日も彼氏に なぜか告れず
I didn't confess to him today.
Kyou mo kare ni nazeka kokurezu
卓球に 命を捧げ足腰を
I play the drums to train
Takkyuu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
鍛える為に ドラム叩こう
My body for ping pong.
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatakou
こんなバンドでもヤラセじゃねぇ
But this band isn't a fake!
Konna bando demo yarase ja nee
こんなメンバーロックじゃねぇ
The members aren't playing rock!
Konna memba- rokku ja nee
目指してるのは音頭じゃねぇ
We're not trying to lead the song!
Mezashiteruno ha ondou ja nee
たどり着くのは涅槃じゃねぇ！
We're not looking for Nirvana!
Tadoritsuku no ha nehan ja nee!
我らはメイドっ！（イエー！）
We're maids! Yea!
Warera ha meido! (Yea!)
メイド姿で参上！参上！
Visiting in maid outfits! Visiting!
Meido sugata de sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチョー！
acho-!
ここらはメイド！（イエー！）
They're maids! Yea!
Kokora ha meido! Yea!
事件現場は惨状！惨状！
Visiting the scene of the crime! Visiting!
Jiken genjyou ha sanjyou! Sanjyou!
アチャ～
acha~
無敵のメイド！（イエー！）
Unrivaled maids! Yea!
Muteki no meido! (Yea!)
便秘は難産 かんちょー！かんちょー！
Constipation is like a hard delivery! Enema! Enema!
Benpi ha nanzan kancho-! Kancho-!
かんちょぉぉお！
enemaaA!
kanchoooO!
清く･正しく･潔く　シーサイドは （絶賛！）
The pure, right, and open hearted seaside is (Amazing!)
Kiyoku - Tadashiku - Isagiyoku Shi-saido ha (zessan!)
営業中！（めいど！ありがとうございまーす！）
Now open! (Maid! Thank you!)
Eigyouchuu! (Meido! Arigatou gozaima-su!)
Now that I think about it, there's no year of the cat in the Chinese Zodiac.
There's also no cat constellation in the sky.
Why not? It's such a familiar animal.
Though there are cat mounds and cat promontories.
(Tatsu = dragon)
We have Tatsuno even though there are no dragons!
Did you forget that I'm here right now?
This smells like a conspiracy.
There must be a hidden truth behind why there's no cat year!
Street 3  [Cat Boy]
Next time: Street number 3, Cat boy.
We'll be all over the place tomorrow, poko~
Street 3  [Cat Boy]