Hi Setsu, how are you?
It's been a week since I came to Meirocho.
There are so many things I don't know about living here.
They're so surprising, and hard, too.
But every day is fun with everyone!
Just like I promised you, Setsu, I'm looking forward
with a smile and walking ahead.
But I still...
Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
Kanaetai yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora hikari ga mieru docchi? Acchi!
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Docchi ni ikou? Nayande kimaranai
Yume no michi wa itsumo kyodai meiro
Migi ka? Hidari ka?
Seikai wa docchi? (Docchi?)
Docchi o erandemo
Nakama to ireba tanoshii kara
Daiseikai!
Kanaeta yume ga aru dakara kyou mo ganbaru
Michi ni mayotta toki wa kamisama chikara o kashite
Hora mirai ga mieru issho ni arukidasou
Hora egao ga mieru docchi? (Kocchi!)
Shinjite susume
Hi fu mi yo itsu mu jan-jan
Natsumeya
Hey, Chiya!
Don't shirk on helping with breakfast!
Where are you going?!
I'm sorry!
No!
We don't show our stomachs when we apologize, right?
That tickles, Koume!
Why are you girls such harlots?!
Ow!
That hurt!
Why is a guard here at Natsumeya?!
She always comes here to have breakfast
after the night shift is over.
Right, Saku?
Yeah.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here you are.
Thank you.
You're Tatsumiya...
...Kon, right?
That's right!
She only remembers Kon's name?!
That's no fair! What are our names?!
Harlot and Little Monkey?
Chiya and Koume!
Hey, Chiya-chan, where did you go just now?
You've been going somewhere every morning.
Oh, actually, I've been looking for my mom.
I thought I could find her right away
just by coming to Meirocho,
but there are so many people here,
I just don't know who she is.
But there aren't a lot of people out at sunrise,
so I thought it'd be easier to find her.
C'mon, the only ones wandering around at sunrise
are suspicious people and scary people.
Hey!
You're looking for your mother?
I'll do what I can to help you.
Really?!
It's my job to help those in need.
Yay!
So, first off, what's your mother's name?
I dunno.
How old is she?
Any defining physical features?
I dunno!
Do you know anything else that could help?
Nope!
Ahh... Nina, your miso soup really is the best.
Saku-chan!
Chiya, you really don't know?
Nope!
There's no way you can find someone
if you don't know her name or what she looks like!
C-calm down, Koume!
How is she supposed to know?
She grew up in the mountains.
She probably thought she could find her
by following her tracks or her scent!
Right, Chiya?
No matter what you might think,
I don't think humans can find something like that.
Are you feeling alright, Kon?
I... I was trying to help you!
Now, now, now!
I've got it!
Times like this call for a diviner!
There, there... There, there...
Let's have Nina-sensei find out where Chiya's mother is!
She's a Rank 5 Urara, after all!
There, there...
Huh?! Can you do that, Nina-sensei?
Huh?
I-I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, I don't think it's possible.
Huh?!
Trying to find something when you don't
have any idea what or where it is
would be difficult for even a Rank 1 Urara.
The only person who could do that...
would be the legendary Rank 1 Urara.
The legendary Rank 1 Urara?
Saku-chan, do you know her?
Yeah.
Huh?!
What kind of fortune-telling does she do?!
I've never seen or met her.
But the rumors say there's nothing she can't find out
through her fortune-telling.
Apparently, she can see things
you can't see with the eye.
Even the gods of Meirocho that the Urara believe in.
That's... that's kinda like...
Like someone who lives up above the clouds.
Okay! We'll go to Bloque 1 and ask
that awesome Rank 1 Urara to help me,
and then I can see my mom!
Huh?
You can't do that.
WE ARE HERE.
Urara can only go to the bloques
that are the same number as their card, or lower.
Huh? Really?!
WE ARE HERE.
That's the most important rule here in Meirocho.
And I've heard that having your fortune told
by a Rank 1 Urara is really expensive.
What?!
I heard they only take customers
on really rare occasions.
What?!
I hope Chiya-chan's okay.
She was spacing out all through class.
The talk this morning must've been a real shock.
Is there anything we can do to help her?
Hmm... Like asking around?
Oh, I'm good at drawing face sketches!
MISSING
Her face probably looks like Chiya's!
White, and fluffy, with red eyes...
Got it!
Got what?
N-n-n-nothing!
MISSING
Woof!
We were imagining what
your mom might look like, Chiya-chan.
When I was little, I imagined what she looked like
a lot before I fell asleep.
She was strong like a bear,
and fast like a bunny,
and cool like a wolf,
and pretty like a pheasant,
and she could fly high like a hawk!
So, a demon.
Sounds like a demon.
A demon...
Oh, no, she's a human!
How did you and your mom
get separated in the first place?
You lived with someone in the mountains, right?
Um... It's a long story...
I was raised by Setsu.
Setsu was my mom's friend, and she watched over me
from when I was born until I turned fifteen,
just like she asked.
That's the end of the story?!
Yeah.
That's all Setsu knows.
That's not enough!
I was alone with Setsu in the mountains,
but every day was really fun!
Setsu was like a teacher, and a friend, and my mom!
Maybe it's kinda selfish of me
to want to meet my own mom.
Of course not!
It's not selfish at all!
There goes Matsuko-san!
What's wrong, Nono?
U-umm...
I don't really know what my mom looks like either.
Huh?
She died when I was little.
I didn't know that...
Oh, but I wasn't alone long at all!
My big sister raised me, and Saku-chan
was there for me, too, but...
I'd like to see her again, just once.
Matsuko-san is a doll my mother
bought me when I was born.
She bought her in hopes that
I would grow up healthy, strong, and kind.
That's why she's always been with me since I was little.
I always felt like my mom was watching over me.
Now that I think of it,
whenever I can't sleep,
all of a sudden she's standing there by my pillow...
She's always watching over me!
Scary, scary, scary!
That's frickin' scary, Nono!
Huh? It's not scary at all!
That's right, Matsuko is very kind!
Her face is scary, dangit!
Trying to find something when you don't
have any idea what or where it is
would be difficult for even a Rank 1 Urara.
The only person who could do that...
would be the legendary Rank 1 Urara.
NINE
Checkpoint
Wait!
Where are you going this late at night?
I know you're probably trying to sneak into Bloque 1
after what we talked about this morning,
but a Rank 10 Urara like you doesn't have
the right to pass through this gate.
No matter what.
I'll walk you back to Natsumeya, so please come quietly.
You don't have to let me through.
I can jump over it!
Wait, wait, wait!
Chiya!
If you go past that gate,
I really will expel you from this town!
That is the law of Meirocho.
The Urara in this town take great pride
in their work and their cards.
That's why you have to put your effort
into your studies every day.
So that one day, you can pass through
this gate on your own merit.
I won't let you stomp all over our laws with your dirty feet!
So what should I do to see my mom again?
Setsu told me that my mom is here in Meirocho!
That's why I came here!
But...
I don't care if it's the legendary Rank 1 Urara or a god!
I'll go anywhere if I can find my mom!
Even if it means getting expelled from the city.
If I can't see my mom,
then there's no point in being here!
Then you should become a Rank 1 Urara.
Huh?
When you do, you can enter Bloque 1 freely
and meet with the legendary Rank 1 Urara.
You can make ridiculous
amounts of money and get really rich.
And...
...I'll let you through without arresting you.
I... I get it!
Captain Saku! You're so smart!
So, I'll become a Rank 1 Urara!
It's not going to be easy, of course.
I know, but I'll work hard!
Is that so?
Then it's a promise.
If you keep your promise, I'll help you.
Captain Saku!
H-hey, you're too close!
I've been wanting to ask for a while now...
...but why do you always show so much skin?
I know Meirocho is a town of women,
but male customers come by in the afternoons,
s-s-so you should dress a little more discreetly!
When you jump around like you were earlier, uh,
y-your underwear shows, and...
"Underwear"?
Huh?
WHAT?!
No, no, no, there's no way you don't wear any, right?
Today, everyone is going to try
their hand at fortune-telling!
Th-this is the first time we've actually done it!
That's right.
We're going to be doing shooting star fortune-telling,
where you tell if your customer's wish will come true
by looking at the stars.
Today's finally the day!
Ever since I was little, I've wanted to try an Urara's art!
Ple-
Please teach us, Nina-sensei!
My, Chiya-chan, you sure are excited to do it.
M-me too!
I-I beseech you for your guidance and tutelage, Sen-
Oh my...
Spin, spin, spin...
What is she doing over there?
SPIN,
SPIN...
Spin?
Are you all ready to begin?
We're going to ask the stars above
if your wishes will come true.
Okay!
SHOOTING
STAR
FORTUNE
TELLING
First, you'll need to prepare a black paper lantern,
incense, and a candle.
Use black curtains to put the room into total darkness.
Next, focus your will while you tell
the paper lantern your wish.
Close your eyes and use the incense stick
to burn twelve holes in the lantern.
You can make the holes anywhere you like.
There, all ready!
Wow, it's so pretty!
It's like stars!
Then, stay quiet, and turn the lantern
holding your wish onto its side...
...and burn it.
You're burning it?!
That's right.
Count slowly from one to twelve,
then cover it with a cloth to put out the fire.
If there are still stars left on the lantern
afterwards, it means "yes."
Your wish will come true!
Then if there are no stars left,
it means your wish will not come true?
That means you just have to go like this...
Little girls who cheat won't make it anywhere.
Because you're all going to do some fortune-telling,
let me talk to you about something serious.
There is one rule that an Urara must never, ever break.
That is...
...you must never try and divine the fortune
of the gods of Meirocho.
We are all borrowing the gods' power to tell fortunes.
If you try to expose the gods' true forms,
you'll lose the ability to divine fortunes forever.
I've heard a lot about them, but do the gods really exist?
My, you don't believe in them?
There are countless thousands of gods in Meirocho,
as many as the stars in the sky,
and while we may not be able to see or hear them,
they're always watching over us.
Always?!
Even when we're eating?
And sleeping?
And in the bath?!
We now wrap the darkness in all directions.
Forty-eight wishing stars.
Tell us if they are to be granted or not.
We cross through the darkness to beseech you.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
The air has changed.
What is this mystical feeling?
Five, six, seven, eight...
Chiya?
Chiya...
Chiya!
What's that smell?
Chiya, your hair, your hair!
Huh?
Ch-Chiya, stop, Chiya!
Oh, no! Fire! Fire!
Move, Sis!
Chiya-chan, close your eyes!
My...
We can't tell our fortunes now...
I-I'm sorry!
Failing right from the start...
Can we really become diviners like this?
There's nothing we can do, it's already in the past!
Let's go eat something sweet and
go all-out to turn our moods around!
Four red bean
jams, please!
Welcome!!
Look at this!
The Koume Special: candied plums,
red bean jam, and dango!
You're going more all-out than any of us, Koume.
Who cares?
It'll make us feel better!
My, Captain Saku!
How many today?
Hello, just me and-
The guards of the Meirocho 10th Bloque Patrol Unit!
Oshima!
And Shiozawa!
That makes a table for three, please!
K-keep it down!
Captain Saku!
She's practically glued to Captain Saku!
When we can't even get that close yet!
But that uneasy look on
Captain Saku's face looks so cool!
CAPTAIN IS
LIFE!!
Did you come to go all-out too, Captain Saku?
All-out?
Here you are.
Your usual spicy-hot curry rice!
They serve curry in a sweets shop?!
You're so cool!
What's that? Is it yummy?
D-do you want a bite?
Yeah!
OUT OF...
...HER SPOON!
Stop it! Get off of me, Chiya!
Captain Saku, it's sho good!
Do you want some, too?
Yes, Ma'am!
We'd be honored!
We'd be very grateful!
Eating out of Captain Saku's spoon...
Near her smooth cheeks!
Really? I didn't know you wanted it so badly.
Sorry I didn't realize sooner.
Captain...
Excuse me, two more orders of curry rice!
Coming right up!
I thought you had more of a sweet tooth.
Sorry about that.
OSHIMA:
CAN'T
HANDLE
SPICY
FOODS
No, uh, Captain Saku, we...
SHIOZAWA:
CAN'T
HANDLE
SPICY
FOODS
We want YOUR curry rice...
Wait! Don't say another word.
I was negligent with you two.
I should have been more considerate of your feelings.
Captain!
Oh, sorry.
Please change those orders to be extra hot!
C-Captain!
Wow. You love spicy food so much, you're crying.
Captain Saku is such a caring person.
Yes. Saku-chan might not like sweet things,
but she's very sweet and kind herself.
She spoiled me a lot when I was young.
Maybe I was too naïve today.
I thought everything would go great
because my sister was with us.
Nono?
But it was a total failure.
Maybe I'll never be an adult who can handle everything.
It's okay!
You'll be an adult!
Why are you so confident, Chiya?
'Cause I'm gonna be a Rank 1 Urara!
A Rank 1 Urara?
How can you, of all people,
say such an outrageous thing?!
There's tons of curry around your mouth!
Wipe your face, Chiya-chan!
My hands! My hands!
Koume-chan, here's a hand towel!
When I was a child, I asked my mother...
"Mother, what are the gods like?"
Now, Kon, you shouldn't want to know that.
But when a god chooses an Urara,
she can see their true form and hear their voice.
Do you want to be an Urara like that?
Hey, when we were telling fortunes today,
what happened?
I felt like I heard something.
Like someone was calling my name.
Chiya, you might've been hearing the voice of a god.
Huh? No way!
I couldn't understand anything it was saying.
Maybe I just imagined it!
Chiya.
I want to be a Rank 1 Urara, too!
Let's be Rank 1 Urara. Let's do it together!
It's our secret for now, okay?
Yeah!
Oh, but the gods might've heard us.
That's right!
Okay! Let's make a wish on the stars!
That we'll be Rank 1 Urara someday!
Y-yeah, especially after we messed up earlier today.
Okay, c'mon, shooting star!
Any time now!
Magari kado turn shitara yume ni tadori tsukeru kana
Mayoi mayotte mawari mawatte
Fuwari deaetara suteki
Ichi kara juu made nattenai hi mo aru
Nee dochira e susumeba happy end?
Migi kara hidari e suki kara daisuki e
Otto koi ni koishite atafuta
Akogareru no nukedasenai
Watashi wa sagashiteimasu
Anata o sagashiteimasu
Mada minu sugata ni tokimeku kuusou Kiss me
Deai gashira de shoutotsu
Chotto kojirete unmei
Moshika moshikashite anata mo mayotteru no
Goal wa mienai
Romance de hajimaru meiro
Mitsukete kuremasu ka?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Our Friends and Colleagues are Sometimes Rivals"!
We'll use shoe fortune-telling
to see what kind of episode it'll be!
Chiya, throw off your shoe!
Hup!
"Our Friends and Colleagues
are Sometimes Rivals"
It flew into Bloque 9...