Serpentine
Academy
Serpentine Academy.
Serpentine
Academy
Embracing the philosophy that evil is more magnanimous than good,
this school secretly trains those with a propensity for evil.
In other words, the dark ninjas.
Assemble at once, she says.
I wonder if she wants us to go meddle with those girls at Hanzo Academy again.
Who knows?
That kind of half-baked work really isn't my thing, you know?
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry! Please forgive me!
It's tough being a rookie.
Keep at it.
O-Okay.
At this rate, she won't even make it as a rookie.
How unusual of you to offer such kind words to a stranger, Mirai.
Don't you think her desperation will be that much greater after she's been given some hope?
Man, you're just as unbearable as—
Serpentine Academy, rule number 48.
"A reverse social order shall be observed on campus,
whereby a senior is obligated to answer the challenge of a rookie at any time."
I will acknowledge your spirit, but really...
You should've known better.
I am quite upset.
Yomi, what's the matter?
The price of vegetables has been constantly rising of late.
You have a point.
I don't have any complaints about it being more expensive for the rich.
But they raised the prices of the commoners' cheap sprouts!
What is the big idea?
Beats me.
Hey, are you actually listening to me?
Yeah, you bet.
I'm not so sure.
It's just about time.
If you'll excuse me...
Oh,
is it that late already?
Hey, Hikage!
I'm not done talking about sprouts!
I'm more concerned about the earful we'll get if we're late than I am about sprouts.
Hey, Hikage! Hey!
Sprouts!
Oh, what is the use?
I have summoned all of you for one reason.
You have new orders.
New orders?
Destroy these eternal chains
Senran Kagura
In my heart ravaged by doubt I was hiding
a dented and rusted sword
Now I blindly lift it to the heavens
When you allow no weakness, you can't be strong
Once I realized that, a burning passion was lit in me
Like a spiral, this red trap coils around us
Burn reality into your mind
and scatter the ashes far away
In the distant sky
I see light for an instant
Dress yourself in the rampant shadows
and blast them into the stratosphere
I swore that I would
cut a path for myself with these very hands
so that my invisible chains would crack
You don't need to grieve anymore
Who can read the future? Know thyself
Ready now! Discern truth or false
Break your world
Eye your target.
Can I have a break, Yagyu?
How can you be worn out after just that?
It's because I'm scared! What if we're attacked by those people again?
Don't worry.
I will protect you, Hibari.
You!
Don't stop! Constant vigilance!
Your enemy won't sit around and wait in a real fight!
R-Right!
They claimed to be students from Serpentine Academy...
Why would they repeatedly take provocative action without killing anyone?
We still don't know what their objective is, but there is one thing we can be certain of—
we must be powerful enough to resist them as soon as possible.
Katsu... you sure are... fired up... aren't you?
There's no telling when they'll strike again.
I have to get stronger! A megaton stronger!
Huh? I think you're plenty strong already—
Aren't you a weak one?
I won't be beaten!
I swear... I swear, I'll get stronger!
I'll definitely get stronger!
Sneak Attack! Hanzo Academy
They have everything in the world,
and yet they constantly whine, their good fortune taken for granted.
These students are all so privileged, it makes me sick.
They'll all make wonderful marionettes.
It's a shame I can't do anything to them.
First, we have to locate our targets' classroom.
Why would they put a ninja training center
in the middle of a regular college-prep high school?
Could anything be more annoying?
Hide a tree in a forest; hide a student in a school, I guess.
These ninjas do seem to enjoy doing things the roundabout way.
Hmph. That's fine, as long it's not so long and twisted that you end up trapped in a maze.
The five have successfully infilitrated Hanzo Academy.
They are the cream of the Academy's crop.
Infiltration should be simple for them. The question is...
Yes, the hidden school within Hanzo Academy,
as well as the top-secret ninja art scroll which lies within it.
You are certain that they are
keeping it concealed in there?
There can be no mistake.
It is not that I doubt you. In fact, it's because you told me that I am convinced.
Yes, sir.
However, the existence of the dark ninjas is shrouded in obscurity,
and to act so openly means exposing the shroud.
That is something the girls understand well enough.
Hmm...
I expect good news, Suzune.
Yes, sir.
Ninja arts have always been skills of the mind; the body is nothing more than an adjunct.
Thus, a strong mind is essential for the body to manifest these skills.
In other words, it is by standing with both feet on the ground
that the firmness of the earth
becomes your strength... Hey!
Ah! Sorry!
Katsuragi!
Huh? Is it lunchtime already?
Katsu...
Unacceptable! Out to the hall!
We've looked everywhere else.
This is all that's left.
It certainly is an old building.
It's no longer in use, and appears to still be here for the sake of cultural heritage.
"Off-limits to unauthorized personnel."
Hmm. I smell something, and it reeks.
It smells suspiciously like our quarry.
Tch, he didn't have to send me out to the hall for napping, did he?
At least the weather is nice.
On a day like this, I'd love to be running around outside.
Yes, as much as I liked, like I did back then...
Come on, Choco!
Mom? Dad?
Katsuragi's parents, having failed an important mission,
were ordered to atone for their failure with their lives, in accordance with ninja laws.
However, the two of them chose to live on as fugitive ninjas, rather than take their own lives.
They left young Katsuragi behind, so that she would have no part in their crimes.
Katsuragi believed that if she became a great ninja,
her parents would be forgiven.
I'll save Mom and Dad someday...
I just have to be strong...
Stronger than anyone else...
Not again.
I went and remembered them again, didn't I?
Sheesh...
We're going in anyway, so let's get a move on.
If this is their headquarters, I doubt it will be so easy to enter.
Then, what shall we do?
First, we'll eliminate the biggest obstacle.
Hey, now. I'm not here to run around in circles.
It's all right. They'll be stripped bare soon enough.
Intruders
Huh?! What is it?!
Hibari!
It's the intruder alarm.
Intruder?
Who is it?
Hmm. They appear to be ordinary students.
Ordinary students?
Ah, is that all?
So it's just some ordinary students
playin' hooky again, Teach?
It appears so.
Katsuragi, that's enough.
Back to the classroom.
Right.
Hee hee hee. I dunno who you are,
but thanks for lettin' me off the hook.
What are you two up to?
You know this area is off-limits, right?
Are you ditching classes here?
How about saying something?
There's really no helping you guys.
Your classes and names.
If you don't tell me, I'll march you straight to the faculty office.
Marionettes?! It can't be—
Hey, isn't this...
What? What's going on?
A battle sphere!
Why?
Yagyu!
Yagyu! Yagyu!
Let's go!
The old school house... no, the whole academy has been enveloped in a battle sphere.
Don't be ridiculous.
Who could create a sphere this huge?
I don't think one person could do it alone,
but it's possible that multiple ninjas could create one huge battle sphere together.
Can that really be done?
I've read that there are ninjas who possess such an ability.
For example...
puppeteers.
Puppeteers?
You mean like, the one who attacked us?
Then, could we be under attack by Serpentine Academy?
Those intruders earlier are probably here...
to eliminate Mr. Kiriya!
An ambush!
This is a dark ninja ambush!
Senran Kagura
There must be ninjas somewhere merging multiple battle spheres.
We have to defeat them and break up the sphere that surrounds the whole school.
A little beat-em-up, huh? Fine by me!
Yagyu...
It's all right. I will protect you, Hibari.
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Ninja Morph!
Ninja Morph.
Where are you?!
Come on out already!
Katsuragi!
What?
We're inside the enemy sphere.
It's dangerous to move about carelessly.
No point standin' around though, right?!
First, we have to see what the enemy is doing.
It's showtime.
There they are!
Stay back!
Huh? Where'd everyone go?
The sphere?
What's going on?
Yagyu? Yagyu!
Hibari... Hibari!
I should've been more alert.
These marionettes were decoys to lure us into splitting up.
This is why I can't stand well-bred girls.
So this was your doing after all.
How do you do, little missy?
Quite a bold move, using that uniform to infiltrate the academy.
How fitting for a rich kids' school to have such a finely made uniform.
Answer me! What is the purpose of this attack?
I do not appreciate your holier-than-thou attitude.
But that doesn't mean that I will not tell you.
After you have beaten me, that is.
Ninja Morph.
What power! I won't be able to take all of this!
Does fighting make you too sweaty for your liking?
Always the elegant young lady!
Where is Hibari?
Where are you, Hibari?!
I'm going all-out today!
Ninja Morph!
Don't you ignore me!
Hibari! Where are you?!
Stop ignoring me!
Stop sneaking around and get the hell out here!
Fight me out in the open!
I'm right here.
It's you...
Aren't you a weak one?
The one from before!
I got my orders, so that's why I'm takin' you on.
I'm glad I got you for an opponent.
Hmm?
I didn't think I'd be able to pay you back for earlier so soon!
Why, you!
I just don't getcha.
Huh?!
Why're you gettin' so hot and bothered?
If I don't get hot and bothered...
how am I gonna win the fight?!
The fight is won... by skill, right?
How did you—?!
I really don't get what you meant.
Wh-Where is everyone?
Aren't you looking well?
Thanks for helping me out back there.
It really is you, Homura. Then...
Don't look so taken aback.
You're a ninja, aren't you?
B-But... why?
I got close to you just to ascertain your capabilities.
Who, me?
The capabilities of the legendary ninja's granddaughter.
Ninja Morph.
I am Homura. One of Serpentine Academy's Clandestine Five.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, again.
How can you be a dark ninja?
Back then, you weren't even worth drawing my sword for.
But today...
I'm here on business.
What tremendous bloodthirst!
Are you trembling?
How pathetic! You're the legendary ninja's granddaughter!
At least show me a glimpse of your worth!
Th-That's right. I am...
You won't get away!
...Grandpa's granddaughter!
Say your prayers!
I won't be beaten here!
Oh? You'd go all-out from the very start?
I like that. I want to see if you were really worth drawing my sword for.
Homura, I thought you were such a nice girl.
I thought we might become friends.
Homura!
Just how naïve are you?!
I'd kill my parents and friends in cold blood if I was ordered to!
That's what it means to be a ninja!
I don't believe that!
I...
I did it!
Looks like I don't have to hold back now.
This sensation... I've felt it before...
Welcome.
Wh-Who are you?
You really are a cutie, huh?
It's like I caught a little bunny.
I remember her from before!
Is she the puppeteer?
You don't have to be afraid.
Come on over here, little bunny.
I-I have to beat this girl... Yagyu!
Ninja Morph.
I knew it. Hibari's in a separate sphere.
You've got fast legs, huh?
I've finally caught up to you!
If I defeat her, I might be able to move into other spheres.
Stop ignoring me!
It looks like you're ready to fight me at last.
I'm in a hurry.
Let me beat you quickly.
Wh-What a thing to say, after how you've been ignoring me!
I won't take it anymore!
Secret Ninja Art!
Walküre!
I'll make sure you pay!
You mean, this mission is not to steal their top-secret ninja art scroll?
Please understand, this is just to lay the groundwork for that.
I personally taught those five their skills.
There is no reason for concern.
This top-secret dark ninja art scroll, Yin...
and the other scroll, Yang...
It is said that originally, these two were one.
Putting Yin and Yang together is a long awaited destiny for us.
I understand.
Such pretentious preachings, while he himself is blinded by simple desire.
The vulgar snob.
When the love you devoted to others vanishes, girl,
your heart will turn to ice
When the wishes you believed in have rotted away, girl,
you will come to know only strife
Once I was deemed innocent,
but now those days are gone forever,
and I wander aimlessly and all alone
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
The fragrant flower                           in your heart
blooms undaunted                               under this sky
You, evil beings of the night,
are full of grace and pride
There is a red flower in your heart
Let it bloom and scatter its petals before it is picked
Next Episode Preview
Homura, you're with the enemy?
Surprised?
Yeah!
I have a bigger surprise.
I go to a tanning salon every day and tan my skin.
R-Really?
No, I'm lying.
Next time, Interlocking Battle Spheres.
Interlocking Battle Spheres
Come get it like your life depended on it.