pure purepara-to
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
Even though I'm not strong
pure purepare-do
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
I'll catch you someday
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
When your guard is down, be prepared for an attack
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
Even though I'm small, I'll grasp you like a water flea
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na ha-to
I want a plastic heart
purasu purasu dakedo mainasu
Plus, plus, but it's a minus
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
But from that point I've noticed that and I've won
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
Love is a bittersweet thing
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
Something amazing that's simple, but complicated
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
But I worry continuously over confusing things
donna kanji sonna kanji
What is it? It feels like a loss
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
You, who's sincere and eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
While I pretend to be tough and practicing full-body swings
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
Being honest is too stimulating and makes me dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou purepara-to
I get hurt, I hurt you, it's a naive preparation
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou purepare-do
In my mind, I'll always be alone on the naive Pre-Parade