O, my friend!
This is a victory for us!
Our fame starts here!
O, my friend!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
"I died for naught"
I won't let it end like that for you
until I am the last one standing
The enemy is cruel
We will kill
The enemy is huge
We will jump
In our hands we hold blades of glory
We sing of victory
On our backs we have wings of freedom
We put our iron determination into our hearts
We slash apart the circle of idiocy
We fly through the endless blue
on wings of freedom
the eotena onslaught
What Should Be Done
The Night Before the Counterattack ( 3 )
When did you last change your shafts?
Six days ago, sir.
After we finished combat operations.
That matches our records.
Okay, next.
You are?
Krista Lenz, Squad 42.
Check for wear.
Guess you can be punished for killing Eotenas.
I know it seems weird, but they were valuable test subjects.
But why would they think the culprit is one of the trainees?
Good point. We just finished cleaning up the Eotena's mess today.
We're all exhausted.
Whoever did it must've really hated the Eotenas.
Yeah.
But in reality, they've wound up doing the Eotenum a favor.
They may have achieved their own personal vengeance,
but they foolishly betrayed Mankind in the process.
As a fellow fool, I think I get why they did it.
Before I actually saw an Eoten,
I was totally sure I wanted to join the Legion.
But now I never wanna see another.
And this is the day I have to decide which force to join.
Even Jean's seriously...
Everyone's thinking the same thing.
"If I'd known it'd be this unbearable,
I'd never've become a soldier."
Now I'm so exhausted I can't think anything else.
Hey, Marco...
I can't even tell which bones are yours anymore.
If I hadn't've become a soldier,
I wouldn't have to wonder who we'll be throwing on that pyre next.
Are we just going to abandon our hard-won tactical progress,
and let the Eotenas eat us?!
I know. I know we have to fight.
But not everyone's like you, Mr. Death Drive.
Stay cool and hear me out.
You're not strong, Jean.
You can understand the feelings of the weak.
That, and you're excellent at analyzing the situation at hand.
I mean, you can clearly see what should be done right now, can't you?
What should be done...
Hey, guys.
Have you decided which force you're joining?
I've made my choice.
I...
I'm joining the Reconnaissance Legion!
Damn it.
Hey, Annie, what d'you think?
Even Jean's planning to join the Legion.
Huh? Jean is?
Doesn't affect me.
You're joining the Gendarmerie, right?
Maybe I will too.
If I jumped off a cliff, would you?
What the hell? No way.
Then why not make up your own mind?
Armin, what about you?
I...
I think there are times and places in which
people are morally obligated to lay down their lives.
Not that I want to die.
I see. So you've made your choice.
I have.
I've been thinking about it for a very long time.
Seriously, Armin? You too?
You're puny, but you've got guts.
Th-Thank you.
Annie, you're actually pretty nice, aren't you?
I mean, it seems you don't want us joining the Legion.
But is there a reason you want to join the Gendarmerie?
Not really.
It's just...
I want to survive.
Looks like they couldn't find any Maneuver Gear that was used without permission.
Then who did it?
No idea...
Right now I'm more worried about the induction ceremony.
How many of the new troops will actually be crazy enough to join us?
Hey, Eren.
Anyone in your class you think'll join us?
A few people.
No, they were going to join.
I'm not so sure now.
Attention!
Mount up.
We're going out on patrol.
Yes, sir!
Good morning, Captain Levi!
Listen up, Eren.
Never get more than two horse lengths away from me.
Don't forget that the only reason you're not chained up is that I'm watching you.
Yes, sir!
Let's move.
Get up!
Jean!
You're really joining the Reconnaissance Legion?
Yeah.
Why the sudden decision?
I mean...
Aren't you scared?
Ya stupid?
'Course I don't wanna join the Legion.
Th-Then why...?
It's not that the Eotenas don't scare me anymore.
And I'm not gonna give you any recruitment bullshit.
"The Legion's best for the best!" or something.
Unlike some dumbfucks, I got no death drive.
You're talking about Eren?
But he's already joined the Legion.
Trainees, form up!
Form up in front of the stage!
I'm not risking my life for anyone else's rationales.
It's a job you can't do unless you make your own choice.
I am the commander of the Reconnaissance Legion, Erwin Smith.
Tonight, you will choose a branch of the military.
Frankly speaking, I'm here to persuade you into joining the Legion.
During their recent onslaught,
you learned just how terrifying the Eotenas can be,
and just how limited is your own strength.
However,
that battle brought Mankind closer to victory than it's ever been before.
Eren Jaeger was the key.
By risking his own life, he proved himself
to be Mankind's strongest and most faithfull ally.
With his help, not only did we halt the Eotena's onslaught,
but we found a way to uncover their true nature!
We believe that in the basement of Jaeger's abandoned Shiganshina home
lie all the answers about the Eotenas he himself doesn't know.
If we can reach that basement,
we will find the key to closing the door on a century of Eotena domination!
In a basement?
We've already advanced that far?
If we learn what They are, we can end this!
No matter how desperate he is for recruits,
it's madness to make this information public.
Or does he have some hidden motive?
What is he trying to discern?
Branch Selection ( 1 )
After their three years of training, a ceremony
is held in which recent graduates choose the
Garrison, Gendarmerie, or Reconnaissance Legion.
Branch Selection ( 1 )
After their three years of training, a ceremony
is held in which recent graduates choose the
Garrison, Gendarmerie, or Reconnaissance Legion.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
Branch Selection ( 2 )
However, only the top ten students in each class may enter the Gendarmerie,
so for most the choice is between the Reconnaissance Legion and the Garrison.
The Garrison is overwhelmingly preferred.
Branch Selection ( 2 )
However, only the top ten students in each class may enter the Gendarmerie,
so for most the choice is between the Reconnaissance Legion and the Garrison.
The Garrison is overwhelmingly preferred.
Information available for public disclosure
the eotena onslaught
We will reach that basement in Shiganshina.
However, this requires us to retake Wall Maria.
In short, our primary objective remains the same.
But with the Trost gate permanently sealed,
we'll have to take the long way around from Karanes in the east.
It seems the four years we spent preparing a route for an invasion force
have gone to waste.
In those four years, more than sixty percent of the Legion's forces lost their lives.
Sixty percent in four years.
An insane figure.
Any trainees who join us will participate in next month's sortie beyond the walls.
We expect thirty percent will not return.
In four years, most new recruits will be dead.
But those who make it through that Hell
will become superior soldiers, capable of surviving anything.
Now you have the cold, hard facts.
Any still willing to risk their lives, remain here.
Ask yourselves,
"Am I willing to offer up my beating heart for Mankind?"
That is all.
All those wishing to join another branch are dismissed.
Commander.
Aren't you being somewhat overly forceful?
All of them will leave!
Fuckshit!
Come on, you pussy! You've made your choice!
Don't force me to hate myself more than I already do!
If I don't walk away now, I'll have to face Them again.
I left the village to join the Gendarmerie.
My mom would be delighted.
If I joined the Gendarmerie, the whole village would think better of me.
We all know...
We've all seen it...
The way the Eotenas...
...devour human beings!
Are you all willing to die if ordered to?
I don't want to die!
I see.
I like the looks on your faces.
I hereby welcome you all to the Reconnaissance Legion!
This is a true salute!
Offer up your hearts!
You all...
This is terrible.
The Reconnaissance Legion.
I'm scared!
I wanna go home!
I don't even care.
Don't do shit you know is gonna make you cry!
You have done well to overcome your mortal fear.
You are brave soldiers.
You have my heartfelt respect.
Salute!
I'm Squad Leader Ness.
And this is my horse Shallot.
She loves munching on your hair,
so be careful if you wanna keep them flowing locks!
Nice to meetchya all!
Hey! S-Stop it, Shallot!
Someone stop her!
Our training began the next day.
In lieu of practical training, we spent most of our time
memorizing the long-range recon formation Commander Erwin had devised.
Strangely, although the formation was laid out in exacting detail,
Eren Jaeger's position was nowhere to be found.
You new recruits'll be here,
between the recon support team
and the escort for the supply wagons.
You'll be wrangling the spare horses and relaying messages.
The Special Operations Squad will be here,
standing by in the center of the reserves.
We're pretty far back.
It's the safest place in the formation.
We're even more heavily protected than the supply wagons.
Well, this is just a there-and-back-again practice run.
The real purpose of this expedition
is simply to gain experience for your journey to Shiganshina.
Um...
I still don't know what my power will be used for.
Did you understand what the Commander's question meant?
What do you think the enemy is?
Did any of you understand it?
Nope.
I can't claim to understand it perfectly.
But I think—
This mission may have a secret objective,
but the Commander has judged it best not to publicize that objective.
So let's focus solely on getting there and back.
Just believe in the Commander.
Right.
That's all for today's training.
Prepare to return to base.
Th-That's—!
Sir, may I go talk with my classmates?
If you must.
Hey, Mikasa! Armin!
Eren!
It seems like it's been so long!
Eren, did they do anything bad to you?
Touch you in strange places?
Try to make you do things you didn't want to do?
Of course not.
That fucking pygmy went too far.
Someday I'll make his ass pay.
Surely you don't mean Captain Levi, do you?
Hey, Eren.
It's been so long!
What? You're all here?
But if you're here, then—
This doesn't mean you all joined the Legion, does it?
And why else would we be here?
So only Jean, Annie, and Marco joined the Gendarmerie?
No way. Not you, too!
Marco's dead.
What did you just say?
Did I hear you say Marco's dead?
Seems not everyone gets their blaze of glory.
I don't even know how it happened.
He died without witnesses and without help.
Marco.
Hey, new kids, come on over!
Your uniforms are here!
Are you really...
Yes, we'll all be participating in the mission.
Hey, Eren.
I've heard that when you turned into an Eoten, you tried to kill Mikasa.
What would you do that for?
No. Eren was just trying to swat a fly—
I wasn't asking you.
Mikasa, that scar on your cheek seems pretty deep.
When did you get that?
They tell me it's true.
In my Eotenes form, I tried to kill Mikasa.
So you're saying you don't remember it, right?
In short, at first you had no idea you even had this power,
and now you don't possess the means to control it.
Yes, that's right.
You all hear that?
That's how it is.
Mankind's existence, our existence, depends on him.
But I bet we'll die just like Marco did,
without Eren's or anyone's witness.
Jean, what's the point questioning Eren about this now?
Listen, Mikasa.
Not everyone's like you,
willing to die for Eren's sake and no higher purpose.
We need to know what we're dying for.
Otherwise, we'll hesitate when the time comes.
We want something from Eren in return for our deaths.
So let's see what he has to offer us.
And whether it's worth our lives.
So, Eren.
We're really depending on you!
Right.
Sir, preparations are complete.
We've driven all the Eotenas from this area!
Thirty seconds until we open the gate!
It's the Legion!
That emblem on their capes is the Wings of Freedom!
Awesome!
It's time!
It's time for Mankind to take another step forward!
Show me what you can do!
Open the gate!
Move out!
We will now begin the 57th sortie beyond the walls!
Onward!
If we assume that I am not truly who I think I am,
then how can you claim that you are yourself?
A castle of sand guarded your heart, and it fell apart
Can you gather the pieces and repair yourself?
The voices of others calling you
are just a ringing in your ear now
It's like time has stopped
Now, wake up
I want to escape the darkness
I want to flee like a raging storm
We lived like corpses, as though already dead
Let us meet again
outside the walls
where maps reach terra incognita
Assuming its long-range scouting formation,
the Reconnaissance Legion advances beyond the walls.
However, they suddenly face the assault
of a mysteriously intelligent Eoten.
Eotenes Fatale
57th Sortie Beyond the Walls ( 1 )