Izumo
Since Togame the strategian and the Kyotouryuu head Yasuri Shichika departed,
almost 3 months have passed on their journey to collect the remaining 10 of Shikizaki Kiki's 12 Deviant Blades.
In the autonomous region of Izumo, long believed to be the land where the gods gather,
awaits Tsuruga Meisai, head of the Sanzu shrine and the owner of Sentou Tsurugi —
Note: Sentou Tsurugi = Blade, the Thousand
the sword that Togame and Shichika are aiming for next.
onore wo harahara hana ni tatoete chirinuru wo
}己をはらはら花に例えて　散りぬるを
As though I were the fluttering flowers scattering
tsumami aguneta guren no tama wo
}摘みあぐねた紅蓮の霊を
The ending of a crimson jewel
sarau kare no hi areshi mune yori
}さらう彼の日　荒れし胸より
taken by a fire in the evening storm
osoruru mama mikoto wa habataite
}恐るるまま命は羽搏いて
Still fearing, life takes flight
yagate yagate ten no hate ni
}やがて　やがて　天の果てに
finally, finally to the ends of the heavens
akaku somare
}朱く染まれ
Become dyed in red
sure chigai kira no yume wo ataeta mou
}すれ違い綺羅の夢を与えたもう
Missing one another, the princess' dream granted
machiwabite meiyo ni samayoi
}待ち侘びて冥夜にさまよい
Wandering in the long awaited dark night
tomo ni moeyou ka
}共に燃えようか
Shall we burn together?
omoi ga harahara mau yue ni
}想いがはらはら舞う故に
Because our fluttering thoughts dance
watashi wa mayoi wo kinjite
}私は迷いを禁じて
I will forbid my doubts
mugen no kairou yori umareta
}無限の回廊より生まれた
I was born from endless halls
kizuna wo saranaru sora he egaite
}絆を更なる空へ描いて
Our bonds are drawn further into the sky
hana no chiranu uchi ni
}花の散らぬうちに
Before the flowers fall
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
Sentou
Tsurugi
This the famous 1000-step stairway.
It's almost like a fort.
Let's go, Shichika.
Meisai is at the summit.
You're going to walk yourself?
I did cross that hellish Inaba desert on my own feet you know.
Something like this is nothing in comparison.
Wait Shichika...
I'm tired...
Give me a hand.
Tired?
You've been traveling with me for three months already.
Haven't you figured out how weak I am by now?
Figured out?
A gust of wind would blow me over, and drizzles of rain put me to sleep!
I pushed this weak body all the way up here on my own!
I'd say that's worthy of praise!
Sorry...
Um...
Do you want me to carry you then?
You think I could subject myself to something so disgraceful?
Disgraceful?
I-I'd be clinging onto a man from behind...
So what?
"So what"?!
Our b-bodies would be in close contact!
So what?
How about a piggyback then?
Cheerio!
A piggyback would be way too embarrassing!
That's not something a grown man and woman would do!
But back on the island, Nee-chan and I often—
"Often"?
Ah... nothing.
So what do you want to do then?
Idiot, I'm a strategian.
Of course I have a plan for something like this.
Well?
Isn't this good?
This way it won't be embarrassing even if someone sees us.
Ah, Togame...
What?
This Sentou Tsurugi sword... are there really a thousand of them?
Yes.
The main focus of Tsurugi is overwhelming numbers.
Hence, a thousand swords in one.
Don't talk about them like they're carrots or something.
Ow!
The final gate is in view now.
I figured it'd already be dusk when we arrived, given how slowly you walk.
Well sorry.
Tsuruga
Meisai
Good day.
Orders from the Shogunate?
I'll believe you.
After all, that'll make it more interesting.
Right? Miss Strategian.
Are you really Tsuruga Meisai?
You don't look like a former mountain bandit to me.
My time as a bandit ended seven years ago.
I've since washed my hands of the business and haven't met my compatriots since.
Also, Tsuruga Meisai was the name of the previous priest here,
and I merely took up that name for the sake of convenience.
Thus it's hard to answer if I'm "really" Tsuruga Meisai.
My old name?
I've forgotten it.
I don't think I had one to start with.
Bandits don't need a name, you see.
It's called a shrine, but that's just how it looks.
There's no one but shrine maidens here now.
It's kind of like what Buddhists would call a convent.
You've seen our shrine maidens, haven't you?
Yeah, the ones down below right?
Not just below. They're here in the main shrine too, about 50 of them.
This is officially an armed shrine after all.
We have 1000 shrine maidens, so if we don't spread them around, this area would overflow with them.
So, since you're here on orders from the Shogunate, you must have some urgent business.
About that, Meisai-dono, can I speak with you privately?
Of course.
Togame...
Don't worry about it.
Go play outside for a while.
I'll hear you out in the main shrine then.
The 50 shrine maidens in this area all very unsettled, you see.
Some killed their parents, some killed their families, some wiped out their entire clan...
They are all devoid of inner peace.
Please don't mind them.
As a side note, you have quite interesting hair, young lady.
I'm not young enough to be called "young lady" by you.
From my perspective you're a young lady.
Though, it does seem that you're not as young as you look.
Meisai-dono...
Now now, no need to rush.
Drink up.
As you can see, it's not poisoned.
You drink well!
Happy now?
Yes.
Now we're friends.
Well, to tell you the truth, I'm pretty sure I know what you're here for.
It's about Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades, right?
The higher-ups have only ever meddled in our affairs once before, after all.
It goes without saying, but I mean General Kyuu's sword-hunt decree.
Furthermore, you say you're the army general director.
So in all likelihood, you're here about Sentou Tsurugi.
As you have guessed, my duty is to collect Shikizaki Kiki's perfected Deviant Blades.
To what end?
To maintain public peace and order, of course.
We've already obtained two of the swords.
Zettou Kanna and Zantou Namakura.
As the owner of Sentou Tsurugi, you must at least know their names.
Yes, I know them.
So you've already managed to collect two of the swords that General Kyuu could not.
That's quite impressive.
And your Sentou Tsurugi will be the third.
Sign: Tsurugi
The only swords which Shikizaki considered disposable, the ultimate and absolute 1000 blades —
Sentou Tsurugi, the swords you have your 1000 shrine maidens armed with.
I'm from the Shogunate, so I'm well aware of the situation that Izumo is in,
including the circumstances of the Sanzu shrine.
If you were to hand Sentou over, the Shogunate would be happy to take care of those "circumstances".
I don't believe this is a bad deal.
Indeed.
I do think it's a good offer.
By the way,
there's one thing I'd like to ask.
Yo!
Did I do something wrong?
Is that boy there your man?
That's my sword.
Your sword...
It doesn't look like he's carrying one.
Is he hiding it somewhere?
Something like that.
Its name is Yasuri Shichika.
The 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, Yasuri Shichika.
The 7th generation Kyotouryuu head, huh...
I see, that's why you called him your sword.
He can be a little too sharp sometimes though.
Did you kill the previous owners of Kanna and Namakura with that sword?
Yes.
The hero of the rebellion, Kyotouryuu.
Swordsmen who use no swords...
Very interesting.
No... it's exciting!
If my Sentouryuu were to be pitted against that boy's Kyotouryuu, which would win?
Note: Sentouryuu - Thousand Blade Style
Sentouryuu?
Okay, I've decided, young lady—
No... Togame the strategian.
This is my decision as the head of the Sanzu shrine of Daisen, Izumo.
I am willing to hand over Sentou Tsurugi,
as long as you accept some minor conditions.
How did it go?
Unfortunately,
it turned out for the worst.
We have to find the first blade of Sentou Tsurugi?
That's right, Tsurugi is 1000 identical swords.
Meisai says that an original, the first sword, exists amongst them.
And you have to find it?
Without your help, too.
If I find the first sword and you win in a one-on-one fight with Meisai, she'll give us Tsurugi.
And if we lose?
We give her Kanna and Namakura.
What's up with that?
What do you mean?
It's not fair!
Even if we win we only get one sword, but if shes wins she gets two.
Yes...
Actually, I wanted to avoid fighting this time around.
Shichika, you can let go of my hair now—
Get off me!
Even if you say that...
Would this be that "disgrace" thing you were talking about?
Cheerio!
Hey, don't dodge me!
I'm not really dodging you...
I don't want to hear your excuses!
It appears that Togame-dono has accepted your conditions.
Those two aren't just master and servant.
Of course, they aren't just a couple either.
They are most likely tied together by fate.
That's quite possible.
Did you see that hair?
Hair doesn't get like that unless something significant happens.
And the way she acts...
It seems that no matter what cruelties one suffers through, one's true self cannot simply be discarded.
No...
It may be an inherent desire to protect oneself.
Meisai-sama...
Why would she wear such brightly colored clothing?
So she does not forget herself.
I'm guessing that Strategian is the daughter of some feudal lord.
If things had turned out better, she might have been the princess of her own country.
Neither a world of war nor a world of peace can sooth our pain.
What do you think, Shichika?
Does it suit me?
How does it strike you?
I shouldn't have bothered asking you.
From now on, if I ask you "Does this suit me?" you must reply "It suits you well."
Unfortunately, Shichika didn't have what we call "Miko moe" today.
Togame, where are you going today?
First I'm going to inspect those black shrine maidens' swords.
After that I'll be down below.
When I'm ready to come back tonight, I'll light a torch.
Come down to meet me when you see it.
Hey, is that the only role I have in this?
There is one more thing.
What?
Don't wander around.
How boring.
Poison of the sword, huh...
Hey little lady, wanna play with us?
You're in my way.
Move.
The one in the way is you!
Now you've done it!
We'll kill your ass!
Woah, I've never seen a sword like that...
I can see a path to the heavens opening up!
A sword is not for display.
It is for killing.
I'll have you fall for me!
S-So cool!
These are the remaining Sentou within the shrine grounds.
Meisai-dono!
Meisai-sama!
Get them out of here.
But—
Don't worry about me.
Meisai-dono!
Go!
It's alright now.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
More importantly, get your wounds tended to!
I'm fine.
Put the swords back on the table when you're done inspecting them.
Meisai-dono!
Thank you.
When I find the original sword,
Meisai will be...
It's possible that Maniwa Koumori and Maniwa Shirasagi failed to obtain Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades and met their fate...
Koumori already had Kanna though... I wonder what could have happened.
It bothers me, it bothers me, it bothers me.
Don't you agree?
Oh, there it is.
M-Master, w-we've arrived...
When people put so much faith in me, I have to live up to those expectations!
Please forgive us!
Ninpou: Uzugatana!
Note: Uzugatana - Whirlpool Blade
This is why they call me Kuizame of Sabaku — written 'chain' and 'bind'.
Ninpou Uzugatana
I should have made an appearance last month?
You people say some funny things!
Cutting down people like you is the best!
This is fun, I'm happy I was able to answer their expectations.
Now then, time to get to work and collect Sentou Tsurugi.
It was located at the Sanzu shrine, wasn't it?
I'm looking forward to it, I'm looking forward to it.
Shichika-dono.
Thank you.
It's fine, I was free anyway.
This is the first time those maidens have had contact with anyone besides myself and Meisai-sama.
Did Meisai bring them here?
No, most of them were serving here under the previous priest.
Though, there are some who heard the rumors of Meisai-sama and struggled to get here.
Rumors of Meisai?
That she had swords which sooth the soul.
Would that be Tsurugi?
What's wrong?
I don't feel that aura that Shikizaki swords have from your swords.
Well, I could be wrong though.
I'm gonna go take a break.
They don't feel like Shikizaki swords to him?
He says some interesting things.
I must have a talk with that boy.
Togame sure is taking her time...
Kyotouryuu boy...
Want some?
I heard you helped our maidens out.
You have my thanks.
It's nothing...
More importantly, what kind of shrine is this?
The maidens run away as soon as they see me.
I have no idea what's going on.
So the young lady hasn't told you anything about the Sanzu shrine.
Basically,
this shrine is something like a refuge temple.
A refuge temple?
It's sometimes called the shrine of separation.
I don't really get either of those.
What exactly are those black shrine maidens?
Why do you give them swords without wearing one yourself?
Because those swords are necessary for those girls.
No, more like a necessary evil.
They're all victims.
Their mental health was destroyed after long term abuse by men.
Mental health... destroyed?
Not just mentally.
Both their souls and bodies have been abused to their limits.
No, they've been abused beyond their limits,
then simply thrown away, just like that.
This shrine's maidens are those abandoned girls who have been picked up.
You should understand why they fear you now.
To them, that's all men are — something to be feared and avoided.
Fear and avoidance between men and women...
I don't really get it.
I see.
Well, it is a different world from that of a swordsman.
But I do know why Togame asked me not to wander about now.
A very feminine consideration.
And now, you should have picked up on another thing —
The reason I give the shrine maidens Tsurugi.
It's to use the poison of Shikizaki Kiki's swords as medicine.
As medicine?
Taking too much medicine becomes poisonous, and poison can be used as medicine.
The swords should serve to help restore their broken minds.
Of course, that's only if the Deviant Blades actually do have power beyond human understanding.
You're probably the first person to use Shikizaki's swords like that.
Probably.
No one would try to restore life with a killing tool like Tsurugi.
But it appears to work to a degree.
I can say that after watching over them for seven years.
Even if you take away the poison, by obtaining the strength a sword provides, a woman can become equal with men.
Is that talisman on their faces the same kind of thing?
No, that's simply for coverup.
There are many among them who've been branded as criminals.
Is that so...
It's those "circumstances" the little lady talked about before.
It helps make the shrine seem threatening.
I see.
The talismans are just a mask.
All that's really needed is the sword.
They can't sleep well due to their emotional damage,
but even with that, carrying Tsurugi with them allows them to retain their sense of self.
For them, Sentou Tsurugi is their heart and soul.
That's why I cannot afford to give up Tsurugi.
I have to save as many women as possible.
If I can beat you and obtain your two Deviant Blades, I'll have saved another two people.
That is why I cannot lose to you.
That's the way it should be.
I will fight to my utmost, and you'll fight to your utmost.
This will be a worthy battle.
Sympathy tactic, failure.
Drink.
I have something important to say.
Okay.
What's with this bitter drink?
Don't tell me you're a lightweight, boy?
Oh, it was sake?
I've never had it before.
It's good sake.
Though contrary to how you look, you can say some pretty harsh things.
You're not much fun.
It's because I'm a sword.
My body and soul don't move for anyone but Togame.
Are you okay with robbing Tsurugi, even though the hearts of these women will break once more?
Good or bad, I can't help it.
If Togame says she wants Tsurugi, then that's absolute for me.
I can do nothing but make you give it up.
Don't you have any doubts about it?
Once you've decided, that's it?
Aren't you just being too lazy to worry about it?
Too scared to make a decision yourself?
Always just "a hassle"?
I won't deny I find it a hassle.
How many people have you killed so far?
Two.
Two huh...
That's not many for a person like yourself.
I'm just a monkey who grew up on an uninhabited island.
My first real fight was about two months ago.
So, two people for two Deviant Blades.
Yeah, that's about it.
Will you kill me too?
Probably.
Same for you,
how many have you killed?
Too many to count.
I can only say for certain,
at least 43.
43?
What kind of number is that?
It's the number of my compatriots I killed when I left the bandits.
Those are the only kills I'll never forget.
And conversely, those 43 people are the only ones I remember.
People must say I'm a cold-blooded barbarian.
But even a person like me needs the resolution to kill.
Something you're prepared to throw away.
It seems like you don't have that.
Yeah, probably not.
Then what on earth do you fight for?
I told you earlier — for Togame.
I fell for her.
Do I need any other reason?
Throwing-off-balance tactic also failed.
My, my.
Actually, that's not right...
What isn't?
It's not two people, it's three.
There was actually one more person.
I slew my father.
Oh, you noticed me?
That was faster than I expected.
I would have liked to have heard just a little more of your interesting discussion.
Oh well, thanks to you I've got a good grasp of the circumstances.
Thank you.
I suppose thanking someone after bowing one's head just comes naturally.
Then allow me to introduce myself from a higher position.
Ah, that's good.
Announcing myself in the open is good, good!
I am one of the 12 heads of the Maniwa corps, Maniwa Kuizame.
Be sure to remember me.
Ah, a Maniwani...
"Maniwani"?
Good heavens, that is incredibly sublime!
To bestow such a lovely name upon a band of ninja assassins such as us,
you truly are a benevolent man!
Someone you know?
No, I don't know this particular one, but his group is after the swords.
Exactly!
I have traveled here in order to procure the swords you two hold.
That's good, good!
The air of hostility is good!
Ninpou Uzugatana!
Ninpou Uzugatana
This is why they call me Sabaku Izame, written 'curse' and 'chain'!
Oh?
You're not going to tell me I should have arrived last month?
Well, I guess now's not the time to be saying that.
Boy.
As the head of this shrine that protects Izumo,
I have a duty to repel this ninja.
Also, I know about Kyotouryuu, but you've never seen Sentouryuu.
That's unfair right?
What are you talking about?
Here I go then.
Good, good, this is exciting!
Speaking of which, you just asked didn't you, Tsuruga Meisai-san.
"What on earth do you fight for?"
If I were to answer, I'd have to say "for money".
I'm quite proud of the fact that I have never fought for any other reason.
However...
You shouldn't bother fighting if you have to ask that every time.
"Why do you fight"?
"For what reason"?
I don't want to hear such sloppy questions!
That's nonsense!
Kyotouryuu boy,
could you help me deal with this body?
Slow, slow, slow!!
I've been all over this huge shrine — from west to east, south to north,
tiring myself running everywhere!
You have some nerve to leisurely nap through it!
A Maniwani appeared.
We don't know when another will show up,
so from tomorrow onwards, I'm staying by your side.
You don't need to worry about that.
But—
This is the original sword.
In the end it came down to how scratched the sheaths were.
Of course, I can't guarantee it for sure,
but the scars on this sheath are the oldest.
Thus, this sword's most likely the one.
I see.
I'd overlooked the sheath.
Thank you, that helps.
Are you okay with this?
Yes.
If you say it's the original sword then it must be.
See you tomorrow then.
At noon exactly.
How about a cup to raise our spirits?
Sounds good.
Kyotouryuu boy,
how about we get this over and done with?
You're pretty easy going right before a fight with your life on the line.
That sort of thing's supposed to be my territory.
How about we allow surrender as an option then?
If you feel you can't win, just say you give up.
I see.
Show me your Kyotouryuu.
Yeah, and you can show me that Sentouryuu you're so proud of.
Proud?
I'm not at all proud of Sentouryuu.
This thing is merely a sword.
Let's go then.
Indeed.
Nothing will start if we continue this pointless chatter.
Ready...
Begin!
Wai—
What?!
Ittou: Ichimonji Kiri!
Ittou: Ichimonji Kiri
Where did she pull that out from anyway?
So the hunt for the original was just an excuse to bide time for this...
So this is Sentouryuu.
That's right, Kyotouryuu boy.
It isn't just the use of your opponent's swords.
It's about making all swords on the battlefield your own, hence "Sentouryuu".
With Sentouryuu and Sentou Tsurugi together...
Chikeikouka: Sentou Meguri!
Note: Chikeikouka = use of the land
Where did those two go?
How am I supposed to write my report if I don't see the battle?
Kyotouryuu is no match for this Sentou Meguri.
What now?
We did agree surrender is an option.
I am prepared to let you live if you say you give up.
You believe that much in your Sentouryuu?
Believe?
Yes, I believed in it, from the bottom of my heart.
It was everything to me, until that rebellion.
Rebellion?
20 years ago, the rebellion led by Hida Takahito, the lord of Oshuu.
My father was the commander of the 2nd squad, 3rd regiment of Izumo's defense corps,
as well as the master of the Kendo dojo handed down from my ancestors.
He taught me Sentouryuu.
I was the daughter who was to inherit it.
That's why, from a young age,
I never doubted that Sentouryuu was the ultimate art of defense.
However, in the midst of battle it was as though Sentouryuu was useless.
Father died,
along with every one of his disciples.
I was the only survivor, as I had never joined the battle.
I lost everything in that rebellion.
My house, my family, even my beliefs...
Before I realized it, I was using Sentouryuu as a tool for murder.
Not long after, I joined the largest bandit gang in Izumo.
Its chief at the time held Sentou Tsurugi.
Sentouryuu is an art of absolute self-defense in which you don't arm yourself.
It's founded upon the idea that swords are dispensable.
Tsurugi follows the same principle.
It was no accident that brought Tsurugi to my ownership.
It was fate.
Before I knew it, I'd become the bandit chief.
My life after that isn't even worth talking about.
I just fought and killed every day.
Why did I fight?
I didn't have the luxury of thinking about it.
I first considered that question when I met Tsuruga Meisai, the priest at the time.
I'd known about the Sanzu shrine from before,
that it was a sanctuary for weak girls.
In that case, why didn't they save me?
Aren't gods called gods because they help anyone?
Forgive me please
for not being
able to save you
Forgive me please
Forgive me please.
The previous Tsuruga Meisai said to me,
"Please, forgive those girls."
"They've done no wrong."
Those were his last words.
It was the first time I had heard such words from a dying man.
It made me think...
"Why do I fight?"
"Why do I live?"
After returning to the bandit stronghold, I killed my companions.
I didn't leave a single one of the 43 alive.
Afterwards, I inherited Tsuruga Meisai's dying wish.
And I've been fighting for those girls ever since.
That is why I cannot lose!
It's for their sakes!
And for my own sake too.
That's the end of my story.
What now?
Don't continue this useless resistance.
Admit your defeat.
Kyotouryuu cannot match up to Sentouryuu.
That's the simple truth.
I eat the meat of animals.
What about it?
It's not strange for martial artists to eat meat.
There's no simple way to catch animals quickly.
When you really want to eat them, you have to set a trap.
But I'm an idiot, so I laid one right next to the house, and accidentally caught Nee-chan.
I got in big trouble for that.
I learned that traps are to catch your prey,
so you shouldn't set them around your house.
What on earth are you talking about?
If you're not surrendering, then—
One thing comes to mind.
I've been thinking about it the whole time —
a way to get out of Sentou Meguri.
There's no such thing.
Sentou Meguri is invincible.
Sentouryuu is the art of absolute defense.
How about we test out whether Kyotouryuu is really inferior to Sentouryuu!
No way!
As I thought, no traps over here.
Besides me, you had to look out for Togame too.
Even if you did manage to take Sentou, have you even thought of a way to transport it back to Owari?
If I lose this fight, the shrine maidens could help you get back to Owari.
What are you talking about?
And in exchange for that,
I'd like to request that you obtain a guarantee from the Shogunate of the future of those girls and the Sanzu shrine.
Hey, what do you think you're...
You know who my successor is, right?
It's just that she hasn't completely recovered yet.
Please get the Shogunate to send someone who's kind and knows their way around people's hearts to take care of them.
Even amidst the demons of the Shogunate, there must be one who fits that profile.
Are you acknowledging your defeat?
No.
I told you, I can't afford to lose.
I have to protect those girls.
I'm just being contradictory here, but I figure it's fine if I lose this fight.
I was wrong to think I could save those girls with the poison of the swords.
I've always thought that.
I used the sword as a cure, but if they become unable to part with it,
in the end it'll be more poison than cure.
That's why I've been waiting,
waiting for people like you two to come and smash my pointless hopes.
Of course, I'm not admitting defeat.
That's the original Sentou Tsurugi.
How do you know?
Togame told me the swords house souls.
The swords choose their masters.
However, they don't choose who to slay.
Sentou Tsurugi chose you, just like I chose Togame.
Indeed.
I am the Kyotouryuu 7th generation head, Yasuri Shichika.
Come!
And I am Izumo Daisen Sanzu's...
No...
The Sentouryuu 12th generation head, Tsuruga Meisai.
Here I come!
I will show you the thousand secrets of Sentouryuu!
Sure.
However, by that point you'll be torn into pieces.
Kuuchuu Ittou: Okumoji Kiri!
Kuuchuu Ittou: Okumoji Kiri
Kyotouryuu: Kyouka Suigetsu!
Kyouka Suigetsu
Togame! I won.
As you can see, it was a clear victory.
Yeah...
Shichika, you didn't have to...
What's wrong?
Good job.
I thought it would come to this.
I will definitely obtain a guarantee of safety for this shrine and its thousand maidens from the Shogunate.
Thank you.
What's going to happen to this shrine now?
There's no more swords so they're unarmed now.
True...
However, it just means things returned to how they were before the sword got involved.
Meisai should have just done that from the start.
Meisai bore one of the Deviant Blades.
She would have been consumed by the poison of Shikizaki's sword.
I doubt she'd have been able to let go of it unless it was forcefully taken.
What about you?
If I had lost, would you have handed over Kanna and Namakura as agreed?
Mumble mumble.
Mumble mumble?
Well...
I never once thought you could lose!
That's why...
Yeah, yeah.
We have to say goodbye to these steps too...
I'm going to miss them.
You'll miss the steps rather than the shrine?
Weird guy.
No, I just doubt I'll get the chance to embrace you like this again.
Cheerio!
At that time, they never dreamed that Japan's strongest swordsman and the owner of Hakutou Hari —
Sabi Hakuhei — awaited them at their destination.
How will the duel between Sabi Hakuhei and Yasuri Shichika turn out?
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
adokenasa wa doujo no temari ni kometa aisatsu
あどけなさは童女の 手毬に込めた挨拶
Innocence is a greeting trapped in a little girl's temari ball
kin wa nan demo
金は何でも
Even given gold
iza kagayakeru kana
いざ輝けるかな
Now it is shining
hitotsu hito wo ayame
一つ　人を殺め
First, you kill a person
miai yamai
みあいやまい
You can't stop the fight
arashi no gotoku kurueru mune
嵐のごとく　狂える胸
My crazy heart like a storm
mada tooki nao tooki
まだ遠き　なお遠き
Still far, far away
eien wa tokoshieni todokanai basho
永遠はとこしえに　届かない場所
Infinity is an eternally unreachable place
asura sura no sumu yokaze tachi kinu shunkan no
阿修羅修羅の住む　夜風立ち来ぬ瞬間の
At the moment when the night breeze where Asuras and Suras live blows,
hana tamukeru chi no kage ni
花手向ける　血の影に
in the shadow of blood where flowers are offered,
sen no bohyou
千の墓標
a thousand gravestones lie.
The strongest swordsman in Japan — Sabi Hakuhei.
However powerful Shichika's Kyotouryuu is,
we can't let our guard down this time.
No, this is isn't even a question of letting down our guard or not.
We leave to collect our 4th sword.
The most dangerous moment for Yasuri Shichika!
The most daring scheme for Togame!
History will be made on the holy island of Ganryuujima!
...I hope.
Next on Katanagatari: Hakutou Hari
Hakutou
Hari
Cheerio!