Wh... Wh...
What the hell is this?!
Hi!! Question: Alone or together,
which one is wonderful?
My future starts spinning colorfully
How much should I tell him?
Should I pretend I didn't see?
I see, this vast world
grows based on my mood
I love you today, I really love you
I'm so stupid... My stupidity is greater
than the number of the stars in the sky
I couldn't admit my feelings for you,
but I had a dream of walking with you
I'm sorry... It's just,
I didn't know it was love
The answer is, you and mystery
plus me equals infinite jump!!
"BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts 2-"
"Episode 12
Idiots, Clownery, and Requiem!"
A strange phenomenon
struck out of the blue.
"Hello"
That is some real fancy-pants
armor for Akihisa's Avatar.
His height is about life-size, too.
Wait, guys! There's something else
that should catch your attention, right?!
All right, all right already.
I got it, so put that other face away.
I can't even ask you to
do chores like this, huh?
Please be more concerned
about the real problem here!
--Good morning!
--Good morning.
Go... od morning, you two.
"Random hitting"
I'm sorry. I didn't
know what was going on.
No, I'm sorry for scaring you like that.
Th-That's right! It was
your fault for scaring us!
I wonder if everyone else's
Avatars have changed, too.
Shall we try and see?
Yep, yep.
Summon!
Th... This is...
Looks like they transform into monsters
that show their summoners' true nature.
I see... Then my Avatar was
affected by my chivalrous spirit...
Akihisa, don't turn
your eyes away from reality.
Or maybe it's that I'm so
manly that I look good in armor...
Or that I'm so strong that
I can swing a big sword...
It's probably just that no head means idiot.
You went and said it! The plain truth
that I was turning my eyes away from!
The truth is cruel at times.
Yuuji's Avatar isn't much
different from Yuuji himself.
A doppelganger?
What're you guys saying?
This is the monster "Yuuji Sakamoto"!
With hideous looks and a nasty personality...
Aim for the Olympics!
Nadeshiko Japan!
You kicked it, Yuuji! You kicked my
Avatar's head as if it was a soccer ball!
Don't be so upset, Akihisa.
They often say "My friend is a ball," right?
Shouldn't it be "The ball is my friend"?!
What the...
A werewolf...
B-But there isn't even a
full moon. Why did he transform?
Did he see something round?
So it really is a ball, huh?
Aren't you two summoning your Avatars?
I suppose... then...
I'm summoning my Avatar... Summon!
Ahh! P-Please don't look!
At any rate, your true
nature is easy to figure out.
N-No! It's true that I'm fat,
but they're not so big that
they can be my calling card!
Stop it, Himeji. If you say more than
that, a certain someone will get hurt...
It hurts! My wrist is twisted! Ahhh!
--If there's something you wanna say, I'll listen, Aki.
--Ahhhh! There's nothing!
Geez...
Mizuki, it's your fault for
having such a naughty figure.
That's so harsh, Minami.
For that matter, I don't have to worry at all.
I bet a super cute one
will come out, so just watch.
Summon!
I can't laugh. If I laugh now, I'm a goner.
Say, Aki.
Wh-What is it, Minami?
I wonder what this Avatar
is trying to tell me, huh?
Y-Yeah, I wonder...
Dammit!
Now that it's come to this, I'll mention
a characteristic other than "totally flat."
Oh, that's right!
You and Nurikabe both
have the trait of being hard.
Whose what is hard, you said?!
--It's hard!
--The truth really is cruel.
Get away from my honey, you pig jerk!
M-Miharu...
You're a pig jerk! Receiving a hug
from my honey is a very serious crime!
--Ahhhhh! Ow, ow, ow, ow...
--Go to hell!
Pipe it down, you bastards!
You guys are...!
Who are you again?
Are you mocking us?!
We're Tsunemura and
Natsukawa from Year 3 Class A!
Oh, the Toko-Natsu Duo.
Toko-Natsu upperclassmen?
I feel like I've heard that somewhere.
Don't put our names together on your own!
During the school festival, this
Toko-Natsu Duo blah, blah, blah...
We can hear your racket all the way from
the Year 3 classroom and we can't study!
That's an outrageous false accusation.
What?!
We're on the third floor.
On top of that, this is Class F.
Year 3 Class A is in a different
building and on a different floor.
Indeed, it's hard to think that
our voices would reach there.
You were just probably wandering
about since you got bored of studying
when you heard Akihisa's stupid, silly voice.
Then you just started wanting
to take it out on us, right?
Didn't you just casually
lay the blame on me?
Shut up! The fact still remains
that you guys are an annoyance!
You guys all got suspended for
causing a peeking racket not long ago!
What're you gonna do if that causes
our academy's reputation to go down
and affects our college entrance exams?!
So he says, Yuuji. Why don't you apologize?
Now, Akihisa, hurry up and apologize.
We're talking about the two of you!
No way.
Stop messing around!
We're gonna put some backbone
into that foolish nature of yours!
Math, huh? Just what we want!
Summon!
"Math"
Go to hell!
"Idiot"
What?!
I'll be the first one to punish
the pig jerk! Please don't interfere!
If you're going to attack Yoshii,
I don't care if you're our upperclassmen!
I'll take up the fight!
Shimizu?! And, why Kubo?!
They look the same.
Lost gods... Monsters who
are lost on the humans' path
and try to get you to become one of them...
Perfect description.
Dammit!
Let's finish this now, shall we?
Stop right there!
--Principal?!
--Old hag?!
I want you to use your remaining scores
in the event that we're gonna start now.
Event?
Shouldn't you work to turn
our Avatars back to normal first?
As it stands, the entire school
will become a haunted house.
Oh? You've got a good intuition for an idiot.
Huh?
We're holding an inter-grade
courage contest using Avatars!
Inter-Grade Courage contest?!
You guys just screwed up
the system tune-up again, right?
Oh, this is good. Maybe I'll
have you guys manage the event.
Ack!
Well, Year 2 and Year 3, which
should play the ghosts and goblins?
Of course, we, the Year 3
students, will do the scaring.
We have to teach them a lesson, so...
Then, the Year 3 students
will be ghosts and goblins
and the Year 2 students will be
those to brave the haunted house.
Rules for the Inter-Grade Courage Contest.
Wooooo, badump, badump, badump...
Challengers will group up in
pairs and brave the haunted house.
When the challengers make
noises louder than a set sound volume
in the haunted house, they'll
become disqualified on the spot.
"Challenger"
Challengers will fight Avatar battles
with goblins at the four checkpoints.
If they win, they'll clear the checkpoint
and proceed to the next checkpoint.
If they clear all four
checkpoints, the challengers win.
On the contrary, if all the
challengers get defeated, the goblins win.
Humph! Just competing isn't fun.
Let's decide on the penalty
game for when you guys lose.
Hold on a sec! Don't add rules
on your own for an academy event!
What? But... that's the least...
Don't be so disappointed, upperclassmen!
Hm?
As long as you're at
one of the checkpoints,
you'll eventually be able to
fight us individually... Right?
Interesting!
We'll beat you up with
everything we've got!
What...? Me?
Idiot Test!
So, we enter the haunted house
in pairs. This is a rare occasion,
so I'm thinking of having guys
and girls pair up as much as possible.
But if the girl screams,
the guy will be disqualified, too.
That shouldn't be a problem. In this
kind of event, this is more exciting.
So, decide on pairs on your own.
So... what's this really about?
Since Shouko threatened me, I thought
I'd involve everyone to spread the pain.
If you don't pair up with me...
we'll get married immediately.
What's the matter Mizuki?
Well... uhm...
Himeji?
I've always hated ghosts and stuff...
So I might scream before anyone
and cause you guys problems.
Himeji, if you're so scared,
you don't have to push too hard.
Th-That's right. Y-You don't have to push.
Everyone has...
something they don't like... so...
We'll try hard so that you don't
have to go into the haunted house, okay?
Okay.
How dare you, Akihisa Yoshii!
I'll make sure to banish you to hell!
Shimizu...
Whoa!
Wh-What?
Would you like to... join hands with me?
Let me hear what you have to say.
And thus, the Inter-Grade
Courage Contest began.
This is quite elaborate.
Th-These are just fake, right?
I bet they'll try to scare
us with some pretty lame...
Ahhhhh!
Disqualified.
The Year 3 students are quite serious.
They might be tougher than I thought.
Dammit... Why do
I have to pair up with a guy?
It's your own fault that you
aren't popular among girls.
What'd you say?
You, too, asked out over 20 girls
and got rejected by all of them.
That's not true. It's not that they
rejected me. It was all just bad timing.
I had bad timing too, that's all. It's never
the case that I'm unpopular among girls.
It's not that I'm not popular, either!
Me, neither!
No, me, neither! Me, neither! Me, neither!
Disqualified.
This is good, Natsukawa.
You'll walk all over them like this.
I see...
Well, I'm gonna go give
them even more to be scared of.
Ah...
M-Mikami!
Are you okay?
Thank... you.
--Tsk!
--Tsk...! Tsk...! Tsk...!
Hey, didn't something strange
appear on the screen just now?
What? Something strange?
Tsk!
It's okay. I'll protect you.
To think that they'd use
an obvious trick like this...
Ahhhhh!
H-How dare he...! That damn bastard!
Dirty! Their way of doing things is
dirty, and so is that face on the screen!
That's scarier than ghosts!
I may not be able to sleep tonight.
Ahhhhh!
Someone, help!
"Disqualified" "Disqualified" "Disqualified"
The first strike units... have been annihilated.
Dammit... Everyone!
What're we gonna do?! There's no
way to defeat such a frightening enemy.
Leave it to me.
Muttsulini!
I'll come with you, Muttsulini.
I'm gonna teach that
baldie what true terror is.
More victims are here.
Here I come.
Yahoo!
"Yeah!"
How dare you show
me something like that!
There, there, upperclassman. Smile!
We'll upload these pictures to the net.
Hell no! Just you wait and see!
Bye-bye!
"Checkpoint 2"
You're finally here, huh?
Let's get started already!
Summon!
"Health and Physical Education"
Muttsulini, their Avatars look strong.
They do, but...
Summon!
"Smack!"
They're no match for us.
"Health and Physical Education"
"Challengers Aiko & Muttsulini Passed"
Whoa!
All right!
They're both amazing!
What just happened, Yuuji?
I didn't get a clear look,
but the faceless one
became naked in a heartbeat,
beat up her opponents,
and put her clothes back on.
Why did she have to
take off her clothes?
Within that moment, Muttsulini
bled, stopped the bleeding and
completed the blood transfusion.
That's our Muttsulini!
At this rate, can't those
two clear all the checkpoints?
Well, the Year 3 guys will
probably step up their game as well.
The next checkpoint is
coming up soon, isn't it?
Yeah. Hm?
What's the matter?
Welcome.
I'm Aoi Kogure, a tea ceremony
club member from Year 3 Class A.
Are you okay, Muttsulini?
This is nothing.
How cute... But I'm
wearing another uniform, too.
Another uniform?!
To tell you the truth...
...I also belong to...
...the rhythmic gymnastics club, too.
Muttsulini!
The...bleeding...
The bleeding isn't stopping!
We're coming to save you, Tsuchiya!
Rhythmic gymnastics! Rhythmic
gymnastics! Rhythmic gymnastics!
This is terrible, Yuuji! We'd better
take a camera and hurry there too!
Sorry, Akihisa... I'm not
quite sure what happened.
That's too much excitement for Yuuji.
--But I got the gist of the situation.
--What a feast to the eyes!
I've got a plan, too!
Oh man. I'm not good at this kind of stuff.
Oh? A pair of girls?
It's true that using her feminine
charms won't work on those two.
Yeah, on top of that, the
older sister is a Class A student.
I don't like the rough stuff.
Well then... I'll leave the rest to you.
Got it. Summon!
"Chemistry"
Setting aside how it looks...
that score wouldn't be...
--Summon!
Why are you a cat-girl
and I'm just a plain old cat?!
You're always playing coy, so...
What... did you say?
I found an opening!
Sis!
I'm not so weak that you
need to worry about me.
Besides...
"Meow, meow, meow"
"Chemistry"
I hate bugs!
A piece of cake. Let's go.
Got it.
Wait... Hideyoshi Kinoshita...
I wonder what he wants.
Hideyoshi Kinoshita,
I was waiting for you to come.
I don't know what's going on,
but ask him to make it quick, Hideyoshi.
I'll just get straight to the point.
What on earth is this about?
Hideyoshi Kinoshita...
I...
I'm, well...
I'm in love with you!
That day...
...for the first time in my life...
...I heard Hideyoshi scream.
Flash! Shine! Light bulb, shiny flash!
I'm not making progress.
Someone's interfering... No, no!
The issue is, I don't have
enough common multiples
Okay, I basically get it.
What is the truth... Baby?
If you see this, draw a
diagram and explain it, Baby!
No word or number can describe you
My heart is being shocked by
the magnetic force between S and N
(S! S! Super! Sticking together,
Number! I say No.1 boy!)
Congratulations! From here on
out you're My, ma-my "treasure"
You're special to me,
no matter what happens
I'll hold you ever so
tight and never let you go
I want to be in love, in a
dream you can forget about limits
It's special, right? After all,
we came to know each other
Forgive me for being like this
Flashed! Shined! Right answer, perfect match!
Everyone's song!
"Sun and Sunflower."
Whenever I notice, my
eyes are always following you.
--I will bloom into a big flower.
--Come to think of it, I'm always seeking your smile.
--I don't know the words to describe my feelings,
but I still want to tell you.
I love you, Kinoshita.
I'm seriously...
...madly in love with you.
I-I'm sorry... To think that
I screamed shamefully like that...
Don't worry about it, Hideyoshi.
That's right, Hideyoshi.
It's rather impossible not to
scream under that circumstance.
I never thought... that he'd start
reading a poem he himself wrote!
"Everyone's song"
"Quite a creepy job!"
I fell unconscious, too.
Yep, yep.
At any rate, we have to take action soon.
Hey! Are you watching, you losers?!
Ahhhhh!
Those bastards...
If you're feeling frustrated,
why don't you hurry up and get here?
Hey, Tsunemura, you say something, too!
Kinoshita! I...
Hey, Yoshii! Sakamoto!
You're listening, right?!
How long are you gonna
make us wait?! Get here already!
Come here so we can have lots of fun!
Darn poet!
Those bastards! Fine by me!
Question 13.
Calm yourself down to
check your answers so far,
and indicate how satisfied
you are with your answers.
I wrote my name correctly for sure!
It's harder to make a
mistake than write it correctly.
Next episode!
"BAKA and TEST – Summon The Beasts!"
This will be on the test.