Crystal Fortunes
ASTROLOGY
Kokkuri
DANCE
FORTUNES
TEAR READING
DREAM FORTUNES
Sometimes, people lose their way
to their fate, or the crossroads of life,
as they wander through the maze of their everyday lives.
In those times,
a diviner can present you with an arrow
pointing to the right choice.
The magical power that points the way
is sometimes panacea, sometimes poison.
To possess that power, one must be a girl
who has passed her fifteenth birthday.
The girls in this fortune-telling town
are sometimes goddesses, sometimes witches.
Urara!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see a light! Which way? (That way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
Which way should I go? I can't decide!
The path to our dreams is always a big labyrinth
To the left? To the right?
Which way is right? (Which way?)
No matter which way I go
It'll be fun because my friends are there!
That's the right answer!
I want to make my dreams come true
So I'll give it my all again today!
When I get lost, I'll ask the gods to help me
See, you can see the future! Let's walk together!
See, you can see a smile! Which way? (This way!)
Believe in yourself and march on!
One, two, three, four, five, six! Jan-jan!
As you all know, Meirocho houses hundreds
of thousands of gods, as numerous as the stars,
and they are always watching over Urara.
That is because the gods
are looking for an Urara to wed.
Realizing this, the Urara competed to be the most
beautiful brides and assembled before the palace.
The gods, greatly amused by this sight,
merrily went about choosing their brides.
That is the origin of today's White Kimono Festival.
Oh, so it's basically a matchmaking meet for the gods.
What are your hobbies?
Suddenly this seems a lot less serious.
Well, it's just an old Urara legend.
The White Kimono Festival is still
an important yearly ritual, even now.
And Meirocho looks so elegant
with so many Uraras dressed as brides.
The festival sounds fun, but I don't like wearing this!
It's real hard to move.
Don't be selfish, now! We all have to participate!
Taking part in the ceremony
is another important part of an Urara's work!
It's our responsibility to see that Meirocho's traditions
are carried on in the correct manner.
By the way...
...it's also tradition for us to arrest rude men
who hit on women at the White Kimono Festival.
So don't do anything improper.
Y-yes, Ma'am.
YOU'RE
ARREST!
UNDER
There, Chiya-chan, you're all done.
Wow, she looks so pretty!
She's almost like a different person.
She looks like she'd make a perfect bride!
Are we finished?! Can I take it off?!
No! You just put it on!
Aww!
Chiya-chan takes her clothes off all the time.
EXPOSED!
I'll need all of you to keep a close eye on her today!
Umm...
I don't know if we can.
Now... next up is Koume-chan.
Ta-dah! What do you think? Do I look good?
Koume, you look like a princess!
Yes, she's really beautiful, but...
It's too short! We're starting over!
What?! You're so strict, Nina-sensei!
I won't let you leave the house showing those legs!
Make sure you fix it!
Now, it's your turn, Nono.
Nono? What's wrong? You look upset.
I-it's just...
I'm too plain-looking,
and I'll probably never be anyone's bride.
That's not true.
You look really pretty today, Nono.
Yeah!
Besides, girls like you who say that kind of stuff
are usually the first to get married.
That's right, Nono, you're very pretty!
Marry me!
Oh, my!
Matsuko-san...!
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
So pretty...
I can see why girls always want to wear this.
One day I want to get married in this white kimono,
thinking back on all the times with my friends...
No! I can never get married now!
It's alright, Kon-chan!
You're not getting married today!
That's right! And everyone said
your belly looks really good!
They're not supposed to see it!
There, there, Kon-chan!
Now that you're all finished getting dressed,
visit the shrine, then enjoy the festival.
That's your homework for today.
Hooray!
Yay!
Honestly...! You really can't flip up my skirt today!
Pull
Flip
Over
up
Everyone's in the same outfit!
The town's in all white.
Can the gods really pick one bride
out of all the girls here?
I'm sure it's a hard decision for them, too.
If that's the case,
why don't they just take multiple wives?
Though it kinda feels like you should yell
"Just pick one already!"
So many! Which one do you want?
Which one? Which one?
I might not be able to decide myself.
Wouldn't suddenly being told
you gotta marry a god be super off-putting?
We don't know anything about them!
You make a good point.
What would a god be like?
A god would stay distant but always
watch over us, protecting us, and helping us.
Oh, and be smart, and good at making tea,
and make delicious miso soup...
Right, right... You're talking about Nina-sensei.
The gods, huh...?
Always watching over us
and protecting us from a distance...
He's gotta be big, cool, and have a ton of eyes!
That's cool to you, Chiya?
Really cool!
What do you think they're like, Koume?
Hmm... Let's see...
Stop it, you three!
Nina-sensei taught us that Urara are not allowed
to divine the true nature of the gods!
But...
When I asked my mother about it, she said...
"An Urara can only see a god's true form
if the god has chosen her."
Perhaps only someone chosen to be
a god's bride can see them?
What're you doing, Kon?
ARINSU
Hurry, hurry!
Stop it, you three!
You're going to eat more after all you ate before?!
No, no, we're not gonna eat. Look!
SACRED
SAKE:
FREE
ARI
NSU
Sake?
Purified sacred sake!
They're giving it away for the festival!
Really...?
I've never had sake before!
It's so neat and mature.
That's right. Only adults are allowed to drink.
We're just allowed to smell it.
Hey, Chiya?!
Is that just from the smell?!
I feel kinda warm an' weird.
Chiya looks really mature!
Sake is so lewd!
Animals came out of nowhere!
They're drawn to her more than usual!
Did the sake trigger Chiya's
feral pheromones to go wild?
Then that means even humans will...
Nono, Koume! Be careful, that sake...
You smell really good!
Let's snuggle in close!
Too late!
What's that?!
Whoa!
Look at me, Kon!
Festivals are so much fun!
Oh no, I can't stop Chiya, I can't stop her!
Pon poko!
Let's play!
...or these two, either!
Captain Saku!
We've got trouble!
What is it? Another pervert going after Urara?!
No, Ma'am, it's...
It's a group of wild animals and a girl in a bride's outfit!
Wild animals... girl...
Hey!
Cap'n Saku!
Wha-?!
Captain Saku!
What a way to push her down to the ground!
Are you alright?!
She looks so cool lying there!
I knew it had to be you, Chi-
Hyan!
Wha-?!
Wh-wh-wh-wha...
You shameless harlot!
She said "Hyan!"
Hyan...
That was so much fun!
It feels like I'm back in the mountains again!
I haven't run around like that in a while.
Makes me feel nostalgic.
No, that's not true.
I don't miss those days, just...
Every day in Meirocho has been so much more fun.
Before I knew it, I just fell in love with it.
The wind feels so good.
I'm feeling really sleepy.
I wonder if my kimono will get dirty.
Nina-sensei will get mad at me.
Huh? When did you...?
Black ears, red eyes, a big...
It's not a rabbit or a fox.
Hey, why are you all alone here?
You don't wanna go to the festival?
I was at the festival just now. With my friends!
A festival is where the town's all festive
and there are lots of yummy things to eat!
It's really fun!
Hey, what's your name?
I'm Chiya!
My name is Chiya!
Huh?
What did you say just now?
Who are you?
Chiya!
You guys...
Huh? What happened to me?
You got drunk at the White Kimono Festival yesterday.
After you ran amok, Captain Saku found you
sleeping in an open field.
You've been asleep for a whole day.
I'm glad you're okay.
Kon...
Are you okay? Do you hurt anywhere?
No...
Ow! It hurts! My cheeks hurt!
We were really, really worried about you!
Chiya, you moron!
Stop it!
Saku!
I'm sorry they cause you so much trouble.
I must take responsibility for her actions,
as head of Natsumeya...
So, my belly...
Now, wait, don't show me your belly! You're not Chiya!
Show you? No, I would slice it open.
Huh?!
I'm sorry!
My, Saku, did you think I'd do something like that?
No, uh...
What were you doing out in that field
in the first place, Chiya?
Huh? Uh...
I met a weird monster in the field.
It was big and black, and had really long ears,
and when I tried to talk to it, it disappeared.
Could that be...
...an angry Captain Saku!
Instead of ears, she had horns, I bet!
Hey. Who the hell are you calling a monster?
Punishment in Progress
Nooooo!
But I really saw it.
Most likely you were just drunk and dreamt it.
Forget that, Chiya, you should be
deeply reflecting on what you did yesterday!
You caused a lot of trouble for a lot of people!
Especially when... when you...
When I... what?
Hyan!
N-nothing! Just no more sake for you!
I'm sorry.
Huh? You're not gonna show your belly today?
She's acting really meek.
Why the sudden change?
I dunno why, but I'm feeling really cold,
and my head hurts, and I have no energy.
She's got a cold!
A cold?!
What's a cold? Is it awesome?
Why are you getting excited?
It's my first cold!
Huh?!
My, my! We've got to have red rice to celebrate!
Note: Red rice is customary to celebrate special occasions,
such as birthdays, weddings, and the like
Uh, I think she'd be better off with some rice porridge.
My
first
cold!
Congratulations!
Rice porridge? Is it yummy?
It's got a very gentle taste.
You've got to eat things that are
good for your digestion when you're sick.
Really...?
Be careful, it's hot.
Here, say ahhh.
Ahhhh!
Wh-what?
Is this what having a mom feels like?
N-no, I...
Hey, Chiya. That thing you were just talking about-
Look at you two, getting all
lovey-dovey in here all by yourselves.
W-we weren't doing anything like that!
You don't have to hide it!
W-well, then...
Here!
There!
What are we doing?
I... I thought it'd be better if we all did it.
RICE PORRIDGE
RELAY!
I'm so full.
Is there anything else you want us to do for you?
Huh?
It feels really weird for you to be acting all calm like this.
Hurry up and get better.
Koume!
Okay, then...
Belly pillow!
So squishy and soft!
No way!
Aww!
Ch..Chiya-chan!
If you want, I can lend you this!
Matsuko-san?
Yeah.
Are you sure, Nono?
Just for today!
I got sick a lot when I was little,
but Matsuko-san would always sleep next to me, so...
M..Matsuko-san, I hope you won't forget about me
after sleeping with Chiya-chan!
Of course I won't, Nono!
N-Nono, you don't have to,
just the thought is enough, okay?
C'mon, Chiya, you've gotta stay warm.
Pull the futon up to your shoulders.
Everyone's being really nice to me.
Having a cold is really great!
Alright, it's time for us to get to class.
Call us if you need anything!
I'll come, too!
Having a cold is really lonely!
Sorry, did I wake you up?
No, I'm okay! I slept a lot.
I brought you some ginger tea.
Ginger?
It's yummy. It has honey in it, too.
Here.
I feel so warm!
Ginger tea warms up your body.
Kon, you're so amazing, you know everything!
I didn't even know what a cold was until today.
That's not true.
Yes it is!
You know a lot about fortune-telling and divining tools,
and you even get perfect scores on tests!
Well that's because...
I studied really hard before I came to Natsumeya.
I stayed in the library all by myself every day,
studying so I could be a really good Urara one day.
But...
Chiya, that "monster" you saw yesterday...
Never mind! Sorry to bother you about it
when you're not feeling well.
The monster Chiya saw...
I thought it could be one of Meirocho's gods.
Kon-chan!
Nina-sensei!
I thought you'd be here.
Huh? Why?
My...! I am an Urara, after all.
I should know where my cute students are.
I also knew you came here looking for something.
I see.
You came here to see if you could confirm
what Chiya-chan saw.
Mm.
It's a strange thing to speculate...
...but maybe Chiya has the ability to see gods?
You think so too, Nina-sensei?
I always studied by myself, so I never realized...
how much I hate to lose.
When I came to Natsumeya,
I was so happy to meet so many people
with the same dream as mine for the first time.
Let's be Rank 1 Urara!
Let's do it together!
But I didn't want to lose.
I thought to myself, if Chiya saw a god,
then I want to see one, too.
Kon-chan, that feeling is very important.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
We're Urara, after all.
All Urara treasure one another as colleagues,
but they are also treasured rivals.
They study hard to practice their craft.
If what Chiya-chan saw truly was a god,
then I'd like to see one, too.
If I could be chosen, I want to be chosen.
But Kon-chan, we don't know
what will happen in the future!
You might not have seen one today,
but maybe tomorrow you will see one!
That's why we work hard and have fun!
You'll always have times when you'll doubt yourself,
but when those times come,
come to me a little more often.
I am your teacher, after all!
Nina-sensei...
Th-though I may not be able to help
even if you do come to me...
Especially after all that trouble yesterday...
and sometimes you seem more like the teacher than I do.
Why can't I be more like a teacher?!
At this rate I'll really have to slit my belly!
Kon-chan?
Thank you, Nina-sensei.
I'll work hard from now on, with everyone,
so I won't lose to them!
That's the spirit, Kon-chan!
Of course, I won't lose to you either, Nina-sensei!
Huh?
Oh, Kon-chan!
Sorry!
If I turn the corner, I wonder if I'll reach my dream
Getting lost and wandering in circles
It'd be great if I could just run into you!
There are some days when I don't have it altogether 1 to 10
Which way should I go to get a happy ending?
From right to left, from like to love
Uh-oh, I'm in love with love! I'm in such a hurry!
I want it badly, I can't get out of it!
I'm looking
I'm looking for you!
I haven't seen what you look like, but my heart's beating fast
Kiss me in my imagination!
The moment we meet is a crash
It gets a little complicated, that's fate
Maybe, maybe you're lost too?
We can't see the end
The maze that starts with romance
Will you find me in there?
Next time on Urara Meirocho,
"Love and Pursuit Sometimes Go 'Good Girl, Good Girl'"!
What kind of episode do you think it'll be, Matsuko-san?
Nono and the girls go topsy-turvy and get lovey-dovey!
"Love and Pursuit Sometimes Go 'Good Girl, Good Girl'"
L..lovey-dovey?