Well, I think that wraps up homeroom for the day.
Be careful on your way home, everyone.
Are you still here, Boss?
He's already gone home, I'm afraid.
I had something for him to deliver to his mother too...
Well, why don't Erika and I deliver it for you, then?
What?!
That'd be great, thanks.
I'm counting on you two, okay?
Tsubomi, haven't you heard the stories about Boss?!
Stories?
You see, he's better known as...
The Legendary Gang Boss!
The Legendary Gang Boss?!
Um...
What's that, exactly?
What?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
You really don't know?
I've never heard the term either.
I know it!
It's this!
That's a banjo!
Thank you very much!
That was a great act!
Well, think of them as like, the toughest
person in a school or a college or something.
They're the ones who always beat up the bullies.
That sounds really cool!
You really think so, huh?
Let me tell you about Boss... the Gang Boss Legend!
Legend of the Strongest Boss!
It's a Pleasure Meeting You!
Legend
Gang Boss
On the edge of town,
there's this park where all the gang bosses
gathered and caused problems for everyone.
Boss of Samurai!
Legend
Boss of Ramen!
Gang Boss
Legend
Boss of Regency!
Gang Boss
Legend
Boss of Computers!
Then Boss happened to be passing by, and...
Hrm?
Huh?
Isn't that a good thing?
If that was all that happened, maybe.
But the very next day...
The leaders of all the bosses, Big Boss, barged his way into the school...
Big Boss!
Please spare us!
And that's why he's legendary?
He sounds so cool!
He seems very serious at school, but not exactly frightening...
Well, we had music practice together today.
Gang Boss
Legend
He'd fallen asleep, so I just...
Hrm?
Hey, Boss.
He really is scary.
This is his house?
Is his family rich or something?
Oh my...
That uniform means you must be from Ken's school, am I right?
Ken?
Oh!
We're Ken's classmates.
Oh deary me, whatever should I do?
Ken is friends with such cute young ladies, and two of them at that!
Um...
Whatever should I do?
Ken's still not back from school, I'm afraid.
Huh? But...
He left before we did—
Shhh!
I've got some lovely tea if you want to wait for him.
Oh, I should get some cakes!
Boss!
What?
Ma'am, he's right...
Um, we'll come some other
time, so if you'll just excuse us!
Oh my...
He glared at me! He glared at me! Like, right at me!
Boss!
Why is he chasing me?!
Why is this happening to me?!
Now just hold on a second!
Just stop it alrea—
E-Erika!
I-If you l-let g-go of m-my hand so s-suddenly, I-I...
Tsubomi!
Move it!
Tsubomi, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right, thanks to him.
Let me help!
It's fine. I can handle it.
You can't reach your own back, silly!
Huh?
Oh, here. Ms. Tsurusaki asked us to give you this.
So that's why...
Thank you.
You're very welcome!
He seems kinda different than how I imagined.
Really?
Hey, why were you shushing us earlier?
If my mom found out I wasn't coming straight home, she'd worry about me.
Huh?
Not coming straight home?
So that's why we got to your house before you.
So what've you been getting up to, huh?
Th-That's got nothing to do with you!
Besides, I need to get my bag!
Whoa!
I'll go get it for you!
Oh no, everything's fallen out!
Wait!
Huh?
Don't read it!
Is this... a comic?
And isn't this...
...Precure?!
I never would've guessed you were drawing comics.
Why is it about Precure?
Well, they're cute...
You'd better keep quiet about this!
E-Even Mom doesn't know about this.
Because you don't want to worry her?
Yeah...
My mother's always raised me quite strictly,
never caring for comics and cartoons and the like.
If I told her I wanted to become a comic
artist, it'd only make her worry about me.
So that's why you've been drawing it in secret on the way home?
You're surprisingly gentle, Boss.
That whole "Boss" thing is just an annoying rumor.
What really happened?
Well, I had writer's block at the time, and was annoyed I couldn't think of any material...
Gang Boss
Legend
Then what about when Big Boss barged his way into the school?
Gang Boss
Legend
Hmph!
I didn't like the way he just tossed his jacket onto the flowers like that.
That's amazing!
So you like flowers too?
Hey... am I really that scary?
You're not scary at all!
Really?
Mom's the only one who seems to think so.
If you like flowers, there's no
way you can be a bad person!
Yeah, that's right!
Shucks, that's kinda embarrassing...
Hey, is it all right if we read that?
Sure, though it's still only in sketch form.
Oh, I know! I'll read it to you!
That'd be great!
Today, once again, they protect the peace in our town!
Cure Blossom and Cure Marine!
Is it just me, or has his personality just radically shifted?
Yup. He seems to be enjoying himself!
However, there's a man that Cure Blossom has fallen for!
Whaaaaat?!
Is it really that shocking?
N-No, please continue.
That man is the shy Ken, who
loves flowers with all his heart!
However, Blossom knows that Marine secretly also has feelings for Ken!
Whaaaaat?!
Sorry, please go on.
Though Blossom is unsure what to do, she reaches a decision.
She will become their Cupid,
and help Marine win Ken's heart!
That's a pretty cliché plot twist...
It's brilliant...
Huh?!
What happens next?!
Nothing.
Why not?
The truth is, I was going to enter this into a competition, but the deadline's tomorrow.
I've worked really hard on it,
but it seems I won't finish in time.
In that case, how about we help?
Huh?
You two will?
Yeah!
We don't have school tomorrow, after all.
Drawing a comic book seems like it'd be fun.
And if you don't want to worry your
mom, then we can do it at our place!
Is this really okay?
It's a-okay!
Battles and friendship...
Battles! And friendship!
This one-two punch of battles and friendship!
I wish nothing more than to face this fiery Gang Boss in manly combat!
So then you just draw over the sketches in pen like this.
Then erase them.
Fill in each segment.
If you go over the edges, just white it out.
Wow!
It's almost life-like!
All right then, let's get started!
Yeah!
Filler! I need you to fill in each of the segments!
Leave it to me!
Whiter! I need you to fix where I've gone over the lines!
Right!
Kurumi, you've gone way over the edges!
I'm sorry!
I accidentally erased his outline!
Don't worry, I'll redraw it!
But first, worry about the screentone on Blossom and Marine!
We've done it!
Huh? I just heard a weird voice...
Y-You're just imagining things!
More importantly, where's the next page?
Well, I...
I haven't decided how the story should go from here.
Huuuuh?!
I thought I'd have the last scene be
where Blossom and Marine reconcile after fighting about their feelings for Ken.
So we just have to act out a scene, and you can create the story from there, right?
I wonder if I can really do that.
You're an actress!
What?
You just have to imagine you're an actress, Tsubomi!
A-All right!
I am an actress... I am an actress...
An actress! I'm an actress!
It's just as you say, Marine!
I love Ken too!
Not bad, Tsubomi! But two can play at that game.
Why?!
Why couldn't you have just told me that before?!
Marine, you once told me...
that it's being together that makes us Precure!
I may love him, but being a
Precure is more important to me!
I feel the same!
I don't need love!
Together...
We are Pretty Cure!
Cure Marine...
Cure Blossom...
I'm...
touched to my very core!
I've thought of the last scene! Let's get this finished!
Erika!
His mom's come to pay us a visit.
Huh?!
Mother has?!
Erika!
How long are you going to keep us waiting?
It's very rude of you!
Just a sec!
Over here!
We're coming in!
Sorry to make you wait like this.
What've you been doing?
W-We've been studying, of course!
Sorry to interrupt you like this.
I thought that as long as you were helping out my Ken, I should at least come and introduce myself.
Huh? Erika...
Why have you closed the curtains?
Th-They've been acting up!
What?
I wonder what's wrong with them...
Oh?
This is...
W-Well you see, he wanted to study, but...
Right, right, we said we wanted to draw a comic book, and...
It's fine.
Huh?
Mother.
The person who drew this...
was me.
But you told me that you were
studying at a friend's house tonight.
I lied to you.
My Ken...
lied to me?!
I'm sorry!
Ken!
My mother trusted me so much, and yet I lied to her!
And she knows I was drawing that in secret too...
I won't be able to draw anymore after this!
But my dream has always been to become a comic artist...
What should I do now?!
I've finally found him.
The Legendary Gang Boss!
Hrm?
What is this garbage?!
Who the heck are you?!
I am a Commander of the Desert Apostles... Kumojacky!
The likes of you, who would draw a
comic about those loathsome Precure
belong not on the field of battle!
You're up, Desertrian!
Filler filler!
Did you find him?
Not yet.
Filler filler!
That was...
Boss's Flower of the Heart...
is the one that was stolen!
Huh?!
We have to hurry and save him!
Right!
Go forth, Seeds of the Precure!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Filler filler! Filler!
To use me as your brush shows surprising promise!
Kumojacky!
So this is your doing!
Filleeeeeeeeeeer!
Get them, Desertrian!
Filler!
Not bad, not bad at all!
Big Boss...
Even outside the comic book, it's being together that makes us Precure!
Right! Let's do this together!
Kumojacky Special!
Marine Shoot!
Blossom Shower!
Take this!
Ken! Where have you gone?!
What?
Filleeeeer...
Tch! You aren't bad at all.
I just wanted to draw my comic book.
My dream has always been to become a comic artist!
But that'd just make my mother worry about me,
which is why I can never tell her!
I can never fill in the words...
I just want...
Hmph!
What a weak form you've taken.
Someone as spineless as you is incapable of drawing hot-blooded comics!
He's not spineless!
He's kinder than you could possibly imagine!
A boss has no need of kindness.
Strength is all they require.
True strength is born from true kindness!
You're just playing with that kind heart of his.
I've had it up to here with this!
Gather, Floral Power!
Blossom Tact!
Marine Tact!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
We shall settle this once and for all next we meet, so prepare yourselves, Precures!
Ken? Are you all right?
Mother...
I just had the most terrible nightmare.
I'm just glad you're all right, Ken.
Mother...
No, it's nothing.
Ken, will you tell me about your dream?
What?
Well, the truth is I want to be a
comic book artist when I grow up.
I know to you, it seems I want to enter a
world that'll bring me nothing but misery,
but I want to chase that dream with everything I've got.
Well, you'll always have my support.
You mean it?!
Of course I do!
What kind of parent wouldn't support their child?
Mother...
In the language of flowers, a flowering dogwood means "I want you to accept my feelings."
Though I think she probably
would've accepted them all along.
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born...
With this, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
Special Delivery
Thanks to you two, we just about made it in time.
And when my mom read the finished book, she said it was pretty good.
This is just fantastic!
It'd be great if you got first place.
It feels good when you manage to take a step closer to your dream.
Hey...
Would you be willing to help me out again?
Of course!
Okay by me!
In that case, which magazine
should we try submitting it to?!
I like the sound of Girls' Cosmos!
Yeah, that's a good one!
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
The flower blooms with an "Open sesame!"
In the wardrobe of my heart
are all the things that a girl loves
Look, they're packed in so tight
My makeover was a huge success
thanks to this scrunchie and this frilly tunic!
Our girly showtime
is about to begin!
Is my coordination lookin' good today?
Shuffle! Colorful! Beautiful!
Mismatches are just part of my character v(^^)v
We're pretty
at full bloom!
If you polish your heart
until it shines
Then even the darkness
will become a guiding light
So don't sulk
because a smile's the best!
Let's make them bloom, facing the sun
The flowers of our hearts
HeartCatch!
HeartCatch Precure!
A photo is a memory carved from light and emotions!
At his daughter's side, the father clicks the
shutter and captures all her emotions on film!
It's so beautiful!
If I became a bride, do you think my dad would be lonely too?
He'd be lonely and miserable!
But he'd hold back his tears for you!
Now, let's have you and your dad take a photo together!
All your feelings will be captured by this one click of the shutter!
HeartCatch Precure:
A Wedding in Tears!
A Commemorative Photo for Father's Day!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!