Yoshimizu Kagami
Theater
Not a chance!
Class 3-B?
Kuroi-sensei!
Yeah, yeah...
aimai 3 senchi sorya puni tte koto kai? cho!
Around 3 cm! Looks peachy, doesn't it? Cho!
rappingu ga seifuku... daaa furitte kota nai pu.
Wrapping for a uniform... Turn off, ain't it? Pu.
ganbacchau ♥ yacchaccha
Just work it! ♥ And do it?
son tokya-cchi & Release gyo
Don't forget to catch and release yo!
ase (Fuu) ase (Fuu) no tanima ni Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
I sweat! (Fuu!) I sweat! (Fuu!) And throw in a Darlin' darlin' FREEZE!!
nanka daruu nanka deruu
Feeling crummy! Something's coming!
aishiteru are ikko ga chigatterunruu
I love you so! Oops! I screwed one upsie-up!
nayaminbou koutetsubou
A nail biter! A steel beater!
oishinbou iikagen ni shinasai
Gourmet eater! Cut that out, already!
tondetta aitsu no hoteru karada tte
Is that new blushing flower...
iwayuru futsuu no onya no ko
...considered a normal girl, or what?
odoroita atashi dake? tonkatsu harigane okawari da da da
Wowzers! Only for me? Pork chops! Firm noodles! Fill 'er up again!
BON-BON ouendan
BON-BON Cheerleaders!
Let's get! cheriipai
Let's get! Cherry pie!
RAN-RAN kangeikai
RAN-RAN Welcome party!
Look up! senseishon
Look up! Sensation!
hai! sonzaikan tenten shouwakusei
Yeah! Leavin' an impression... Asteroids.
butsukatte tokemashita bouzen
Crashed! And burned! Shockers!
ooi ni utatte shirenjaa
Break into song! Crunch time!
motteike!
Take it!
saigo ni waracchau no wa atashi no hazu
I'll still be laughing in the end!
seiraa fuku dakara desu ←ketsuron
'Cause it's a sailor uniform. ←Q.E.D.!
getsuyoubi na no ni!
It's only Monday!
kigen warui no dou suru yo?
And I'm already blue. What to do?
natsufuku ga ii no desu ←kya? wa! ii v
I'd rather wear my summer clothes. ←So cute!
sekkin 3 pikuto suru madette chuucho da yan ☆
3 pics incoming! That's a toughie to pick! Ooh ☆
ganbatte (Yeah) harikitte (Yeah) My Darlin' darlin P L E A S E!!
Just work it! (Yeah!) To the limit! (Yeah!) My Darlin' darlin' PLEASE!!
So...
What the heck is this line for?
Do you know, Yuki-chan?
No idea...
Now, now...
Miss
The Jam of Suzumiya Haruhi
Early Ticket Sale Drawing
So this is how it is.
Too bad.
I didn't win either.
Um...
I drew a winner.
Me, too!
My dearest friends!
What about me?
WATASHI TSUITEIKU YO
I'm gonna follow you through.
DONNA TSURAI
No matter the pain.
SEKAI NO YAMI NO NAKA DE SAE
Through the darkness of this world if I must.
Big man...
KITTO ANATA WA KAGAYAITE
'Cause you'll be there to shine the way.
Blocking my...
KOERU MIRAI NO HATE
Past the end of the future.
Here.
YOWASA YUE NI
Won't let weakness...
TAMASHII KOWASARENU YOU NI
...break down my soul.
That was incredible.
I was quite moved.
The first person who came out was so cool.
That guy?
Eh?
No?
People actually go for that, huh?
Konata, you haven't said a word.
The fatigue is setting in now that the event's over, huh?
I guess I was a bit moved myself.
Yeah...
I wonder what this feeling is...
Can't Change
So Quickly
What are you doing?
C'mon, we're going.
Kagami, you're really proactive about the oddest things.
Because if we don't go flower viewing today, we'll miss seeing the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
If you keep putting things off until tomorrow...
...or the day after,
it'll eventually rain, or the petals will start to fall.
Speaking of which, what happened to the goldfish from the summer festival?
The truth is...
I think I fed him too much...
And now he's this big.
Huge!
Shogun!?
I think I took care of him a little too well.
Wait a sec...
Are you sure your feeding methods weren't wrong?
That's no longer a goldfish!
I can only pray that it's because he's living a happy life.
Are you going to eat it?
How could I!?
There's an anime about a guy who takes good care of animals so they return as humans saying, "Welcome home, master!"
You always pick the most hardcore references.
Maybe I should put him on a diet...
Kagami...
Goldfish Scooping
Are you perhaps thinking about getting a replacement?
It's beginning to get pretty cold.
We should start heading home.
It can get pretty cold, especially when you go flower viewing at night in your day clothes.
And your butt gets cold when you sit down.
I've heard that the average temperature in March...
...is close to the average temperature in December,
and that April is about the same as November.
If it were November or December I would certainly wear a lot more.
But in March or April you just tend to dress lighter.
Maybe it's because you're sick of wearing your winter clothes.
Maybe it's a way for everyone to express how they can't wait for spring?
You look like you're fine, Kagami.
Hm?
Don't tell me you're wearing wool...
Long-wavelength infrared effect
Always prepared.
I'm not wearing any!
Ah...
I'll give you this much for today, Gyopi.
If he showed up as my boyfriend one day...
...and turned out to be a wife beater, that would be a problem...
As if...
Onee-chan, what happened to you?
Man, it stings...
I have really delicate skin.
This season is just brutal for me.
Sounds painful.
And I stay in the house most of the time, too!
They have a lot of goods that help against allergies, nowadays, so why don't you try some?
Transform!
I see, it really works!
Reduces the effects of pollen by 99%!
Now you're suspicious on the inside and the outside.
Just don't get taken away by the police, okay?
I'm going to go shopping for a bit.
Have fun.
You wanna come with me?
Nope.
Wait, Dad,
you're seriously going shopping like that?
Of course.
It would be meaningless if I didn't.
"And now on to our next story."
Woman robs convenience store
"Last night around eleven,
a woman broke into a convenience store...
...and attempted to steal the cash."
"However, since one of the employees screamed really loud..."
Hey, Yu-chan?
What?
I wonder if there are a lot more crimes...
...committed by people pretending to have allergies this time of year?
It might be possible.
Freeze!
How did it turn out like this?
Oh!
Eh?
Tomorrow?
Sure, we haven't done that in a while.
Yeah, plus I finished my homework already.
Huh!?
What did you just say!?
You finished your homework!?
Really!?
I don't believe it!
I'm sorry, I lied.
I mean, you have to tell a lie on April Fool's, right?
Good thing I remembered.
No, you're so...
You never even had any intention of doing it yourself, did you?
You must have a lot of free time...
I can't think of anyone else who would make a phone call at this hour just to lie.
Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, this is Izumi.
This is Kuroi.
Is this the Izumi residence?
Oh, Sensei.
Hey Izumi, it's me.
I'm sorry,
I accidentally overwrote your data on the game I was borrowing.
Just kidding, hey!
You fell for it!
It's April Fool's today!
I found another person...
Sensei...
What up dawg?
The other day, Miyuki-san said,
"Even Kuroi-sensei can handle the job, so teaching must be a piece of cake!"
Or something like that.
Why, that little brat...
So she's been hiding her true colors...
Um, Sensei...
I was kidding...
Konata called just to tell me a lie,
seriously.
Did you lie to anyone today, Tsukasa?
Eh?
Yeah.
Wow, that's unusual.
What was it?
J-Just now.
When you asked me if I lied...
T-That was so subtle!
You don't have to force yourself to lie, you know.
W-What kind of lie did Kona-chan tell you?
That she finished her homework on her own or something.
In retrospect, I don't see how I fell for it.
It's impossible.
If she lied, then that means she hasn't done her homework yet either, right?
Well, knowing her, she definitely didn't do it.
I see...
Just now,
you felt relived that there was someone like you, didn't you?
Eh!?
Um...
Konata, do you have a moment?
Sure.
Is it interesting?
Yeah, unique.
I see.
Konata, the truth is...
Your dad is thinking about remarrying.
Okay.
Wait, I know you are against it.
In your mind, the only person who could be your mom is Kanata-
Eh?
What?
You're okay with it?
You don't care if I get remarried?
Why not?
B-But...
You know,
that's going to mean that...
...you're going to have a new mother.
What's our new mom like?
Eh?
Uh...
Well...
Don't take it so seriously...
"And now, the next question:"
"What is the kenjogo form for iku, "to go"?"
It's gotta be ukagau!
Piece of cake!
That's right.
It's "to inquire".
I believe that's the right answer.
Sounds right to me.
Yup.
The correct answer is mairu, "to visit".
N-Now that they mention it...
Yeah...
I was just going with the flow.
What's with this weird atmosphere...
Me, too.
Everyone got it wrong with full confidence.
"Next is a multiple choice question:"
"Of the following, which prefecture does not border the sea?"
"A. Ibaraki-ken."
"B. Tochigi-ken."
"C. Kyoto-ku."
It's B.
It must be B.
B, right?
That was pretty easy.
"The correct answer is B!"
"Next question:"
"Considered one of the most difficult known problems in mathematics,
in 1994, Prof. Wiles of Princeton University proved the following theorem:"
"A. The Pythagorean theorem."
"B. Taylor's theorem."
"C. Fermat's last theorem."
Why do the jump when the answer is obvious,
but keep their mouths shut when they're not sure?
Since it's spring break, why don't we stop by Miyuki-san's house.
That sounds like a good idea.
It's pretty far, so I've never been there before.
Miyuki-san's family is rich, right?
I wonder what it's like.
Hmm...
Maybe she has a pool in her backyard?
Nah... she probably has security guards all around her house.
No, it's probably more normal than that.
I bet she has a pet.
If I had to guess, a ferret would fit her image.
A white one!
Nah, it has to be a dog.
A huge, white dog.
With a huge yard and a white parasol.
A dog sounds possible.
And that's pretty much how the conversation went.
You're welcome to visit, but please don't have your hopes up too high.
I'm sorry to say that I have no pets.
However, while we don't have a huge, white dog or a parasol in the back,
one of our neighbors do.
Really~
And that neighbor's kid is entering Ryouou this year.
Is that so.
She's also been invited, so do you want to come over, too?
My friend's cousin is entering Ryouou this year.
It's a small world, isn't it?
I'm so sleepy...
Honestly.
It's because you got into a habit of sleeping in until noon.
Oh, Konata.
Yo.
What's with you?
Got used to sleeping in?
I've been gaming for three days straight now...
I'm gonna die...
The only thing these two have in common is their laziness!
Izumi   Konata
Takara   Miyuki
Hiiragi  Tsukasa
Shiraishi  Minoru
Ah, we're in the same class again!
You're right!
I'm so glad.
Good morning.
Ah, good morning Yuki-chan.
Morning.
You're in our class, too, Miyuki-san.
Indeed.
That's wonderful.
Let's have a great time this year, too.
Let's.
Iwasaki   Minami
Kobayakawa  Yutaka
We're in the same class, aren't we?
I-I hope we'll have a wonderful year!
So do I.
Kagami's the only one in a different class again this year.
It's not like I don't see you every day, anyway.
If I were in the same class as you two, I'd get worn out.
Onee-chan...
How unfortunate...
No big deal.
It's always been like this.
Besides, I can already see Konata trying to borrow my textbooks and notes.
You know me well.
So that's that.
You guys go on ahead.
Yeah, see you later!
Yo, Hiiragi!
What class are you in?
Hey, we're in the same class again!
If you count middle school,
that makes it, what, five years in a row now?
Let's have another good year.
Huh?
You know those people,
they forget about everyone else except for their top priorities.
There, there...
As if we're just a part of the background!
I wonder how they decide the class assignments.
Maybe they try to balance out the good students,
or try to divide up the relatives,
or split up the problem students as much as possible.
At least that's what I've heard.
Though I suppose it depends on the school, too.
But in dramas, most of the problematic students tend to be in one class.
It's more exciting that way.
But high schools are supposed to gather students at pretty much the same level,
so there shouldn't really be any "problem" students.
That's true.
Miyuki...
It's perfectly okay to say, "You're the problem student," right there.
You don't want to be categorized the same as her, do you?
No, that's not true...
The bell already rang-Sensei sure is late.
You're right.
Everyone, get to your seats!
Good, barely safe.
You're out.
I'm your homeroom teacher, Kuroi.
Now that you've all advanced another year in school,
stop pretending you're still on spring break.
You have to get back in gear and start working hard.
T-That was not convincing at all!
First Semester Duties
Class Representative
Now, I won't be nagging you about studying all the time,
but this is your last year in high school, and I want you to get the most out of it.
Now.
Let's get straight to class duties.
First Semester Duties
Class Representative
Library Staff
Takara,
could you be class representative for the first semester?
Ah, yes.
Once you become class rep, it sticks to your character image.
That's true.
Though I don't have any problems with it.
It's common for the teacher to choose people for the first semester.
Since there are a lot of new faces, it's hard for the students to take a vote.
In Kuroi-sensei's case...
I think she just has an easier time leaving everything to you, Miyuki-san.
I can hear you.
Sensei's hair was all messy this morning.
But it looks like we're going to have another fun year with Kuroi-sensei.
Well, she's a fun person.
I mean, the class atmosphere is often decided by the HR teacher...
I see.
I get it now.
So your laziness comes from the teacher you guys have had.
I can hear you.
I'm Iwasaki.
Nice to meet you.
She's pretty cute.
I went to the same middle school with her.
But she doesn't talk,
is usually gloomy,
and she's always reading books... it's creepy.
But she's actually a very nice person...
I guess I'm the only one that knows...
I feel special!
Next.
A-Ah, yes.
First impressions are really important at times like this.
I have to be cheerful.
I'm Kobayakawa Yutaka.
Though I may look like this,
I'm not some elementary school student who skipped grades.
Just kidding...
Huh?
What did she say?
W-What?
Skipped grades?
Did Onee-chan's influence turn me into a maniac?
Now, I would like to decide on the class duties,
are there any volunteers for class representative?
Guess not...
Iwasaki.
You were class rep in middle school, so why don't you go for it?
Is that so?
Would you like to, Iwasaki?
I'm sorry.
There is another position I was hoping to fill.
Hm... I'd prefer if someone with experience would do it.
What did you want to do?
Librarian?
Nurse's office.
Sensei, I'll be class representative!
She's such a good person!
sakura saku mirai koi yume
Cherry blossoms bloom into future, love, and dreams.
Tends to give you the feeling that...
takamaru kodou osaezu ni
I can't stop my heart from racing.
Something is about to begin.
A new encounter.
futari de kanjiru
Let the two us spend...
Izumi Konata
A new life.
kisetsu wo koete yuku
...this touching season together.
Izumi Konata
A new...
Love.
kakegae no nai shunkan to
This moment of a lifetime...
With my childhood friend...
With that senpai I've always admired...
deai ga tsukuru sutoori
This meeting is the beginning of our story.
Or a mysterious transfer student...?
A little uneasiness with a lot of expectations...
maichiru sakura ni negai wo komete
Cherry blossom petals dance in the air carrying our wishes...
...is what they call 5 seconds away from seriously falling in love!
Also known as MK5!
That's the happy image I get,
but in reality you actually have to start from scratch with people you don't know,
so it's a pain.
I'm already used to it.
You've got it easy.
Onee-chan!
Oh, Yu-chan,
haven't seen you since morning.
That's right, not since this morning.
Oh.
This is the person I was talking about...
Oh, so you found her.
Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you.
See, didn't I tell you?
I knew she was going to pass!
Yes, yes...
But Yu-chan,
you forgot the possibility that she would pass but choose not to come, didn't you?
But it worked out in the end, so it's okay!
By the way, what are you guys doing?
We were going to check out the nurse's office...
...since I'll probably be seeing a lot of it.
I see.
Onee-chan, can you show us the way there?
Of course.
Leave it to Onee-san!
Where was the nurse's office again?
Eh?
NURSE'S OFFICE
I've never gone before so I don't know.
Come on now,
you've been here for two years, but you don't even know where the nurse's office is?
Perhaps that just means I lived a healthy two years.
No, you went there for your physicals.
Which reminds me, I don't think I've ever been to the art room.
If you choose music as your elective, you won't get the chance to.
I myself have never set foot inside judo hall.
I didn't even know the tea room existed until recently.
Even though we've gone to the school for almost three years now.
I guess everyone just goes to the places that matter most.
I don't go to the study rooms much either.
I go there!
That's unexpected.
That silence...
It's perfect for napping.
I see.
Oh.
Yu-chan went to check out the nurse's office with that girl who helped her during her exams.
They ended up in the same class!
Isn't it a miracle?
When you stop to think about it,
meeting Kona-chan and Yuki-chan at this school might be a miracle, too!
I guess so.
But we can only be here together with each other like this for one more year.
But you've been in a different class the entire time, Kagami.
Don't say that.
The answer is B. Poisonous hemlock.
This will be on the test, so remember it.
Hey!
Izumi, wake up!
Ah, Potemkin!
What were you dreaming about?
I'm really sorry,
I'm actually trying really hard to focus and stay awake.
Is that so?
But Sensei,
they still come!
The demons of sleep!
Huh?
Without warning!
Impossible to stop!
An inevitable fate!
I'm not sure about how you're trying to explain yourself to your teacher,
but maybe this will help you stay awake.
Miyuki-san, you never fall asleep in class, right?
Do you have some kind of trick or something?
I wouldn't call it a trick...
But I'm the type that doesn't do well without sleep,
so I'm usually in bed by eleven.
Up until our second year, I went to bed at ten.
It's no use.
There's no way I could do something like that.
I remember this stuff was important in the last lecture, so I wrote it down,
but I was asleep half the time, so I don't remember what I wrote.
I can't tell either.
But just looking at it makes me feel good about myself.
It's the first signs of my desire to study!
But seriously, what did I write...
Aren't those formulas?
Kuroi-sensei...
Amazing!
You can read this chicken scratch?
I suppose.
But that means you weren't dreaming about world history, Izumi.
Now...
Onee-chan, you're still up?
Guess it stinks after all.
Oh no, it's already this late.
I wonder if anyone is online...
"You never learn, do you?"
"I'm looking forward to tomorrow."
Geh!
Lucky Channel!
Oha-lucky!
The show, rumored to be broadcasting to the whole world, Lucky Channel!
I'm the navigator, Kogami "Pretty" Akira.
And I'm her assistant, Shiraishi Minoru.
Lucky Channel has already reached its 15th episode.
Huh?
Is this the 15th episode?
I believe so.
Oh, then this is your last one.
Um.
Um...
Bye.
EH!?
Didn't you get the memo?
The producers told me that...
...starting from the 16th episode,
they wanted me to handle the show by myself, and wished me luck.
Wait a sec...
Yay!
You fell for it, you fell for it!
It's April Fool's!
A-Ah...
Oh, that's what it was...
See ya.
Speaking of which, you seemed real excited...
...during the Haruhi no Gekisou.
The MC was someone that looked a lot like you, too.
Eh?
Is that so?
Couldn't be.
So when am I going to get my concert?
No idea.
They'd better tell me soon!
My schedule's packed pretty tight, you know!
Oh, I'll go check it right away.
Hurry.
Observe!
The East...
Hurry up.
Is burning...
Hurry it up already!
Red!
Circle.
Eh?
Circle?
The producer says okay.
Eh?
Next time?
Understood.
Next week during this time...
...we'll have a live concert featuring Kogami Akira!
Eh?
Eh!?
N-Next episode?
S-Seriously?
They secured a stage?
Yes.
He pulled some strings and had them hold a place.
And, action!
Whoa, amazing!
All right!
Not bad, Itou!
I'm looking forward to it.
You can leave the MC duties to me!
Seriously?
Are you serious?
That's it!
Believe it or not, I'm pretty well-known as an MC myself.
I'm going all out!
So there you have it everyone!
Let's go crazy next week!
See you next week!
Bye-bii~
Oh yes.
Is Shiraishi Minoru seriously going to be here next week?
I'm a lieutenant.
Hey.
Now please listen to me.
What are you going to sing first?
You're not starting with Sunny Sunshiny, right?
The Love Legend of Minoru.
The first song isn't Sunny Sunshiny, right?
One, two, three, four!
Mi-Miracle! Minorun-run!
Oh, he's already started.
Mi-Miracle...
What?
Sunny Shinshiny!
Huge audience, huh?
What are you singing first?
Uh, well...
How about I start with the Love Legend of Minoru.
For now.
For now?
Anyway, in that case...
Whenever you're ready.
What?
Is it OK?
Whenever you're ready.
Now please listen to me.
The Love Legend of Minoru.
One, two, three, four!
Mi-Miracle! Minorun-run! Mi-Miracle! Minorun-run!
Next Episode
And next week on Lucky Star:
Inori here.
Matsuri here.
Miki here.
Tadao here.
Next week: "Ring"
「 Ring 」
Look forward to it!