Hey!
Here you go.
Wow, you're great at finding rare CDs. Thanks so much!
Nah, I'm just lucky.
His playing is amazing. Sayaka, you should listen too.
Are you sure?
I'd rather play it over speakers, but I can't in the hospital.
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 3 I'm not afraid anymore
Tiro Finale!
Wow, Mami, you're so cool!
I'm not here just to give shows, you know.
You have to remember, this is dangerous.
Yes, ma'am!
It didn't drop a Grief Seed.
That was just a familiar sloughed off of the actual witch. They don't carry Grief Seeds.
That wasn't a witch?
Looks like we were way off.
It's not like we can just ignore familiars.
If they grow to maturity, they become just like the witch they split off from.
Let's go.
Have either of you thought of a wish yet?
Madoka?
Yeah, it's hard to decide when you're told to make up your mind right away.
What did you wish for, Mami?
You don't have to tell me if you don't want to!
For me...
I didn't really have much time to think about it.
But I don't regret it.
I'd rather live like this than have died there.
But if you have the chance to think it over, I want you to consider it carefully.
Because I wasn't able to.
Hey, Mami. My wish has to be for myself, doesn't it.
But just hypothetically.
What if there was someone far worse off than me, and I wished for something for him?
You mean Kamijo?
I told you, it's just hypothetical!
There's no rule that the girl entering the contract has to be the one affected by the wish.
There's precedent for it, too.
But you may not be satisfied with what happens.
If you're fulfilling someone else's wish, you have to be very clear about what you yourself want.
Do you want to fulfill his wish?
Or do you want to be the person who fulfilled his wish?
Mami...
They sound similar, but they're completely different.
That's a terrible way to put it.
Sorry. But I had to tell you.
If you don't keep that in mind, you'll regret it.
You're right.
I didn't even think of that. Sorry.
It's tough, I know.
There's no need to hurry.
I think they should hurry up!
No. Girls hate boys who try to rush them into things.
It's not as simple as I thought, huh.
I can't really hurry you. Even suggesting something is against the rules.
I can't just want to be  something, can I?
Madoka, do you simply desire power?
That's not it...
It's just... I'm kinda dumb and I don't have any talents...
Just being an amazing, awesome person like Mami would make me happy!
If you become a magical girl, you'll be far stronger than Mami.
No matter what you wish for,
I can't even begin to imagine the size of the Soul Gem you'll bring forth.
I've never met one with this much potential before.
Come on, you're pulling my leg.
Nope.
Madoka, are you still up?
Yeah, why?
My head...
Aww, man, again?
Water...
That creepy bald son of a bitch told me if I wanted to drink he had plenty at home!
Thanks. Want a nice hot mug of cocoa?
Sure, thanks!
Why does Mama like her work that much?
Did she always dream of working at that company or something?
Your Mama doesn't like her work, she likes working hard.
Her dream was never to be a salarywoman.
But she still keeps trying to live her own way.
Thinking of it that way, she's living her dream.
Her way of living is her dream in and of itself?
Not everyone appreciates it,
but it's what I love about her.
She's a wonderful person we can all be proud of.
You're putting uninvolved people in danger.
They were chosen by Kyubey. They're not 'uninvolved' anymore.
You're trying to make them into magical girls.
It'll be fun.
They'll just cause trouble.
Especially Madoka Kaname.
I see you've realized her potential.
I will not allow her to seal a contract.
Don't want to deal with anyone stronger than you?
That's really beta of you.
I don't want to have to fight you, but...
Then let's try to never meet again, okay?
I think tonight's the last time we'll be able to settle things with words.
Hey, sorry I kept you waiting.
Huh, didn't you get to see Kamijo?
They said it wasn't a good day. And after I came all the way out here...
What's up?
What's that?
It's a Grief Seed! Stay back!
No way! What's that doing here!?
Oh no! We've got to run away!
It's about to form a barrier!
That labyrinth again...
Madoka! Did you get Mami's phone number?
Oh man.
Madoka! Go get Mami!
I'll stay here and keep an eye on it.
Wait!
You can't! The witch may not have come out yet,
but if the barrier closes you'll be stuck inside!
We may not make it back in time to save you!
Once it builds a labyrinth, we won't be able to track it!
We can't just leave it in a place like this!
You go ahead, Madoka.
I'll stay with Sayaka.
When Mami gets here, she'll be able to find me using telepathy.
If I stay here with Sayaka and watch the Grief Seed, I'll be able to show Mami the shortest path in.
Thanks, Kyubey.
I'll go get Mami right away!
Are you afraid, Sayaka?
Of course I am.
If you decide on your wish, I can make you a magical girl right here and now.
If worst comes to worst, I may have to ask you to.
It's something very important to me.
I don't want to rush into it half-hearted.
Here, huh?
Kyubey! What's the situation?
We're still okay. It doesn't seem like it's about to do anything.
Sayaka, are you okay?
I'm getting bored in here.
It's probably better to avoid provoking the egg by using strong magic.
You don't have to hurry, but try to keep it stealthy.
Got it.
I'm glad we made it in time.
I should be scolding you for overdoing it,
but it was Sayaka's idea, wasn't it?
At least we don't need to worry about the witch getting away.
I told you I never wanted to see you again.
Today's hunt is mine.
Back off.
Can't do that. We have a date with Miki and Kyubey.
I guarantee their safety.
You think I'll believe you?
Fool! This is no time to—
I don't want to have to hurt you, but I need a little security.
This witch is completely different from the ones you've fought!
If you stay quiet, I'll let you go when I'm done.
Let's go, Kaname.
Okay...
Wait!
CHARLOTTE
Um... Mami...
What?
I've been thinking about my wish.
Have you come up with something?
Yes.
But I think you might get mad about it...
What wish do you want fulfilled?
I've never been good at anything or had anything to be proud of.
I thought I'd always be a bother rather than ever being able to help people.
Even though I hated it, I couldn't do anything about it.
But then I met you, and you showed me how to fight for the sake of others.
You told me that maybe I could do the same thing.
That would make me happier than anything.
So just becoming a magical girl is my wish!
Helping people and being proud of myself...
That's my dearest wish.
It's tough, you know.
You'll get hurt. You won't have time for boys or hanging out.
But when I see you trying your hardest, I look up to you!
I'm not the kind of person you want to admire.
I try to act cool, but I'm scared. I'm hurt. I can't talk to anyone about my problems.
I sit at home alone crying...
A magical girl isn't something you enjoy being!
You're not alone anymore, Mami.
That's... You're right.
Will you really fight by my side?
Will you really stay by me?
Yes, if you'll have me.
I make such a terrible senior, don't I?
I'm really no good at this.
Mami...
But it's still a special occasion. You need to think of a good wish.
A special occasion? Yeah, I guess.
A contract is a contract. There needs to be an equal exchange.
Billions, a wonderful boyfriend, something like that.
I don't really...
All right, how about this?
If you don't think of something by the time we beat this witch, we're asking Kyubey for a tasty cake!
A cake!?
Yeah. A huge, luxurious party cake!
And we can all have a party to celebrate you and me teaming up as magical girls!
I'll get a cake for becoming a magical girl!?
If you don't like it, then think up something better!
Mami!
Operating
The Grief Seed's started moving! Hurry up!
All right, got it. Let's blow this thing away!
Wait!
It's like my body is floating... This is the first time I've been this happy in a fight!
I'm not afraid anymore!
Because I'm not alone!
Sorry we took so long.
Great, you made it.
Look out! It's coming!
CHARLOTTE
Let's finish this off right away!
Got you!
All right!
Tiro Finale!
Impossible...
Quickly, you two! Contract with me!
Madoka! Sayaka!
Quick! Decide on a wish!
That won't be necessary.
This one is mine .
That was a close call.
Take a good close look. This is what it means to be a magical girl.
Give it back...
Give that back!
That's Mami's!
Come on! Give it back to her!
You're right. This is for magical girls.
You have no right to even touch it.
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes
will surpasss time and fulfill
one dream of this scarred world
If you would slake your desires,
there is no future but casting off your pride
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even gods
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
Illustration: Santa Tsuji (Nitroplus)
Mami was so kind.
Showing us what we must be prepared for if we're to fight, she—
Episode 4 There are miracles and magic
There are miracles and magic.