Are you ready?!
Quiz Trial
Do you want to be the Kamiyama Quiz King?
Then aim to make it past the preliminary round!
Quiz Trial 7!
Mazui Presents
Every day is set in stone, and we
fukuzatsu ni kamaeta kyou ga
iki wo nonde sumashiteru
Just hold our breath and live it through
mi ni oboe arun darou
I'm sure you know what I mean
kimi wa dou shitai
What do you really want to do?
nani mo nakatta soburi de
Pretending like nothing happened to you
kabau itami wa mou
The pain inside just builds up
kokorodzuyoi kurai ni
It makes me feel all the more sure
sekasunda
And urges me to go on
tsukande koboshite
Catching on, falling through
fukanzen na bokutachi ga
We've yet to learn who we are
hikatte mienai
It's so bright, we can't see
mirai no jibun wo tsukureru nara
If we can decide the kind of person that we want to be
mezameru mama hashire
When you wake up, just start running
shinkirou wo oikoshite
Breaking through all the illusions there
kawaritai mama hashire
When you want to change, just start running
jiyuu na iwakan de
Your freedom will come one day
todokisou na kagayaki to ima wo erandeikou
I hope you choose this moment and the light that lies before you
toutatsuten wo shiranai fukai sai
We don't know where we might go, so after the sigh,
kokyuu wo kasanete
Just take another breath
A Corpse by Evening
A Corpse byEvening
Question number one!
The word "diamond" comes from the Greek adámas,
and the word "emerald" comes from the Greek smaragdos.
True?
Or false?
I guess it is just the first question...
The answer is...
True!
I'll show you who the real database is.
We're down to only a few remaining contestants!
Will this be the final preliminary question?
Here's question 7!
The Japanese darui is derived from the English "dull".
True or false?
I'm not sure...
It sounds like it is...
Hey, Mayaka.
Do you think it is?
I think so...
The answer is...
Don't bother with the drama!
False!
The preliminaries are over!
Congratulations to those who survived!
The finals will take place on stage here!
Come on up!
Yo!
That's an interesting costume you've got there, Fukube.
Here's our first finalist!
Can we get your name and class, please?
Who's this guy again?
I guess...
Shimizu Noriko from class 3-B.
You totally didn't notice I was here, did you?
I was pretty focused on the quiz...
Wait, I remember.
So, Tani-kun, how's the Go Club these days?
The Go Club?
Actually, something interesting came up.
Want to hear it?
Now for the third finalist!
Ah, yes!
Let's go!
Wow, he seems to be wearing Saturn or something on his head!
Please tell us your class and name.
I'm Fukube Satoshi of the Classics Club!
The Classics Club!
Wow, we have a Classics Club?
This school sure has its share of weird clubs.
Right?
Yep, we're a weird club!
After all, we don't have any club objectives!
Classics Club
Anthology
Hyouka
No. 46
On sale now
Wow, really?
We knew that the club made an anthology every year, so we made one of our own!
We surprised even ourselves with the result!
We put our backs into it!
You're right. We sure did...
Goal: sell out all 200 copies !
...into the copies.
We've even uncovered a huge secret about this very Kanya Festival!
And what is that?
It has to do with the origin of the name "Kanya Festival".
It isn't simply a shortening of "Kamiyama High School Cultural Festival"!
We at the Classics Club...
...have uncovered the secret!
And what is it?!
You'll find out...
...if you buy it!
For only 200 yen, you too can learn the secret of the Kanya Festival shrouded in 45 years of mystery!
Our anthology "Hyouka" can be found in the Geography Prep Room, on the 4th floor of the Labs Building!
I've successfully advertised our anthology.
Now it doesn't even matter if I win or not.
Oreki-san!
How was it?
Tanabe-san said that it's okay for us to sell it at other booths.
I tried to go meet Irisu-san to ask her advice, but I couldn't make it...
I can guess why...
What should I do now?
Satoshi's advertising was pretty interesting.
Advertising?
That's it!
I heard the Wall Newspaper Club is putting out an extra!
I'll go ask if they'd be willing to include the Classics Club!
Such a busy girl.
Wall Newspaper Club
News Soon
Excuse me!
What can I do for you?
Good afternoon, Tougaito-san.
Could you pick up the Classics Club?
I don't really get what you mean...
Sorry!
I meant to ask if you'd be willing to include an advertisement for the Classics Club in your newspaper.
Well...
I'm not actually a member anymore.
I quit now that I'm a third-year.
I'm sorry...
Would you mind introducing me to one of the remaining members then?
I don't mind, but there's probably no point.
We'll be putting out the first part of the extra at 2 pm.
The schedule's already been set.
So it'd be impossible to add us?
It's not impossible...
We've left a little space in tomorrow's afternoon paper,
but the Kanya Festival has over 50 clubs participating.
We have to prioritize the ones that should be getting attention.
From what I hear, the Classics Club is only selling an anthology, right?
B-But, the contents are—
Every club puts everything they have into their content.
But if you had something that would make a good story, we'd be the ones asking you to put it in our paper.
A good story?
I understand.
Sorry for taking up your time.
If you run into an interesting story, feel free to come back.
I might be able to help in that case.
Eru.
Kaho-san!
It's been a while.
Is your father doing well?
Too well.
You look a bit down. What's up?
I've just been dealing with a bit of a problem.
Come on in.
I'll give you a free reading.
Fortune Telling Club
All fortunes
1 fortune 20
minutes
Your booth is always amazing...
Um...
How about Tarot, then?
I can't do that.
Why not?
Eru...
You liked this sort of thing, right?
The Fortune Telling Club's
Wheel of Fortune has been lost.
Juumonji
What's this?
I'm the only member, so I wasn't here a lot of the time.
After leaving and returning one time, I found that the Wheel of Fortune had been taken from the deck.
In its place was that card.
"Juumonji"...
Why is your family name here, Kaho-san?
I have no idea.
Did you find the card that was taken?
This was also attached, so I'm guessing I'll get it back when the festival's over.
I'll return it when the cultural
festival is over.
Whoever it is doesn't seem to be a normal thief.
Let me show you one more thing.
Is there something special about that flier?
Its contents are the same as all the others.
It was left here along with that card,
left open at the last page of the club listings.
Is there some reason why?
No clue.
I'll be happy if I just get the Wheel of Fortune card back.
We're finally at the climax!
Shimizu-san and Gotou-san are at 5 points each,
and Tani-san and Fukube-san are at 6 points each!
These two are one point from winning!
Who will win this competition?
Let's give all our contestants a big cheer!
Onto the next question then!
Here we go!
The formula for the surface area of a sphere is...
4πr²...
So fast!
I haven't finished the question yet. Are you sure?
Yes.
Let's hear your answer then, Shimizu-san!
_
πr³.
Correct!
The formula for the surface area of a sphere is 4πr². What is the formula for its volume?
_
The answer is
πr³.
Well done!
Now Shimizu-san is also one point away!
Three contestants are at 6 points!
What an exciting dead heat!
Hang in there, Gotou-san!
Now, next question.
Here we go!
The full name of Kamiyama High School's Student Council President...
...is what?
Yes, Shimizu-san?
Kugayama Muneyoshi.
Enough with the suspense.
Correct!
Hey, Fukube.
That's too bad, for both of us.
I guess that means we draw.
So, what did you want?
Remember how I said something interesting happened at the Go Club?
We had some playing stones stolen.
Not lost, but stolen?
There was a written note from the perpetrator inside the box.
We don't use all the stones, so we wouldn't have noticed if 10 or so went missing.
What's the point of stealing something like that?
Well, I'm guessing they'd play Go Moku Narabe.
I'm sure it's a prank by some other club.
See you.
Wait, wait!
We can't just leave it at a draw like this!
Let's settle this properly!
What are you doing next?
The cooking competition tomorrow.
Okay!
We'll see who wins this there.
Bring it on!
Shimizu-san! How are you feeling right now?
Such an uncultured guy.
I don't really care about competing with Tani-kun.
I wonder if Houtarou's doing his job properly...
You open?
Yes, we are.
Is this the thing with the origin of "Kanya Festival"?
Can I read it here?
No.
It's only 200 yen. Just buy it.
We've got way too many. I'm crying here.
Senpai, your fly is down.
It's broken...
Shoot...
Try using this.
Oh? You had one of these things?
Awesome!
Thanks a lot. Have this.
An air gun?
It's a water gun.
We're roasting sweet potatoes at the Gardening Club.
Putting out the fire with a bucket is just boring.
Then don't you need this?
That's just my side arm.
This would be my main arm.
It's an AK.
I see.
See you! Thanks again!
A Glock 17?
Shuubun
When the light and dark are in balance
Hyouka
Doing something like this is the first problem.
No one's coming at all.
It's not too late to make up some posters and go out and advertise.
But we all decided to go with this kind of booth...
Why are you looking at me?
Manga Society
100 manga reviews?
No one's going to read something that boring.
That's a bit much, Kouchi-san...
And there's no point in reviewing manga anyway.
It's a total waste of time!
Right?
I guess...
I wonder if Fuku-chan will believe me...
I tried really hard not to make a scene.
What do you mean by "a waste of time", Senpai?
It's all up to the reader.
The reader?
That's right.
Any manga is just as entertaining as any other.
No matter who writes it?
Yes.
Then what makes one more interesting than another?
Don't you understand, Ibara?
That's up to the reader.
It all boils down to whether the reader has a tall or short antenna for what's interesting.
That's all there is to it.
So you're saying that someone with a short antenna won't find anything interesting?
That's right.
That's why writing reviews is pointless.
Everyone should just read what they like and laugh their hearts out.
All manga are the same?
I won't accept that.
I won't back down!
According to your theory, there shouldn't be such a thing as a masterpiece.
Of course there are masterpieces.
What decides them?
The works that get passed through the sieve over and over through the years and still survive.
That's a masterpiece.
You're wrong.
A masterpiece is born a masterpiece.
Even one that hasn't withstood the test of time?
Then it's just your personal opinion.
You're wrong!
About what?
This is a matter of experience.
You've just never been hit by something that made you say, "This is it!"
Oh?
You've got some nerve.
There are definite differences between writers' technical abilities.
Senpai,
did you read a manga called "A Corpse by Evening" that was sold at the cultural festival last year?
Never heard of it.
Then I'll bring it tomorrow.
If that doesn't convince you,
then I have nothing more to say.
Now I definitely can't ask to sell Hyouka here...
Thank you very much.
Likewise.
What's this?
Welcome!
MUST SEE! Happening NOW!
Girls at War
Manga Society
Theories on the
Value of Manga!
Priestess vs.
Sexless Being
"Girls at War"?
Excuse me...
Yes?
What is this?
It's over for today.
It'll be happening again tomorrow though, so you're welcome to come back.
I see...
So, what'd you think?
Great advertising, right?
I'm sure it helped a bit.
Yeah, I guess.
We sold 14 copies.
Really?
Looks like advertising like that works pretty well.
Pretty good for a start.
I guess tomorrow's going to be another long day.
I've got that cooking competition in the bag.
The one with three people per team?
Huh?!
Three people per team? Seriously?
You're on the Executive Committee, yet you don't know the rules for the event?
I'm very sorry.
I couldn't get a better location or advertising from the Wall Newspaper Club.
Don't worry about it.
But...
there is something I'm curious about...
Curious?
Hyouka
Classics Club
No. 46
Kamiyama High School
Never mind.
Maybe I'm not curious after all.
I am most grateful.
Look! It doesn't say it's three people per team!
I'm sure of it.
I heard a girl in the Cooking Club say so.
Damn it.
I thought I could join the competition alone...
Oh right, Mayaka,
how was the Manga Society?
Nothing special.
Mayaka, Chitanda-san...
How about joining me in the cooking competition?
I can ask the president if I can take time off for it.
If it can advertise our club, then I'd love to join.
Great!
Looks like we're in it together.
How badly did you want to do it?!
I'm pretty confident in my cooking.
I can't just let a competition like this pass me by.
Attention all students and guests.
This announcement marks the end of the first day of the Kanya Festival.
We would also like to ask that all remaining students clean
the hallways and close and lock all doors before leaving.
Um, Oreki-san...
Did you...
No... um...
Never mind!
Where is it?
I can't find it...
Where did I put it?
I could take this instead...
No, I can't do that.
I can't find it...
Why?
joukyou wa hikagaku teki ni
The case seems so irrational
kanjou no monta-ju
A montage of emotions
dare ga dare wo yonderu
Just who's calling who right now?
furimukeba nigeteku shisen kanjiru
When I turn around I don't feel watched anymore
ki no sei ja tsurenai yo
I know it's not just my imagination
antena wa sainou da yuusha
A heroine's antenna is her talent
datte (datte) shiritai (kimi wa chigau no)
I mean (I mean) I want to know (Don't you want to?)
seishun ondosa ima no uchi tadashite ageru yo
I'll fix the difference in how we view our youths right now
ashita kaiketsu suru nara ima demo yokunai
If it'll be fixed tomorrow, then why not fix it right now?
kimi no misuteri-
You are a mystery
toite mitai
Detective I'll try to be
shougen no himitsumeita senaka sagase (kyou mo)
Looking for the person who makes this happen to me (Again today)
kimi wa fantaji-
You are a fantasy
hikareteyukuyo tsumui
You pull me in to see
fukuranda koukishin
I want to launch an investigation
torikku wa nai no ni
Even though there isn't a trick
ki ni naru yo
I'm curious
kyoumibukai
I'm so interested
doushite
Why is that?
Next time: Wildfire.
Wildfire