Crane! Crane!
Craneane...
She's just using the damage done to the
Flower of your Heart for her own agenda!
Please, remember who you used to be!
Huh? I-It stopped again?
This is just another repeat...
Now's your chance!
Fortissimo!
...of the same old losing setup!
Hm?
Have flowers always been this beautiful?
HeartCatch
Precure!
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom
Within each of our chests,
they begin to sprout
The seeds of the heart
are growing
bit by bit
Red,
white
and yellow
It's because these blooming buds are
all varied colors
that they
shine so brightly!
That smile that you've nurtured
with such care
will never wither
HeartCatch Precure!
Now, all together
Let's make our flowers bloom!
They're always right by our sides
So together
let's make those pretty flowers of our heart
bloom even more!
HeartCatch
Precure!
Hm?
Yuri?
The Saddening Truth!
He Was Yuri's Fairy...
The red spider lilies have bloomed rather beautifully, haven't they?
They're so beautiful!
I suppose so.
Tsubomi!
It's Yuri!
Yuri seems kinda sad, doesn't she?
Yeah...
Fashion Club
in progress
Now recruiting!
We'll be waiting!
My friends!
The school's fall festival draws close!
Precious little time remains to us!
Enough with the theatrics, Erika.
We've still got more than a month left!
How naïve of you!
We can't just panic at the last minute like with our summer homework!
But anyway...
I want to make sure our fashion show at the fall festival is a huge success!
We feel the same way too, of course.
That's why we got the designs for our
costumes done during our summer camp.
And as for making them...
We finished that too!
Yay!
So, you see, I know we're about to
start rehearsing for the fashion show,
but I thought it'd be kinda neat if we had something special to draw people in to see the show!
Well, we're doing all the modeling ourselves, after all.
We're pretty much as boring as it gets, huh?
Oh, I know!
Why not ask Momoka to come as a special guest!
Huh?
If a top-selling model like Momoka's at our show, it'll be a surefire hit!
Yeah!
I don't wanna have to ask her, but guess I can try.
Um...
I'd like to ask Yuri to come model as well!
Ask Yuri?
Hey, who's this Yuri?
She's a friend of Momo's, and she's really pretty!
Really?
I think that's a good idea too!
It's settled, then!
Here you go. History and Classics.
Thanks as always!
It's gotta be a hard life, being a model.
Nah, I get by since you're here to help me.
While I'm singing your praises, can I ask you a favor?
I really don't get some of this stuff in our math class.
All right.
Yay!
There's really nothing more
important than friends, huh?
And having a cute little sister.
What's going on, Erika?
I wanna ask you a favor, Momo!
And you as well, Yuri!
Me too?
That's right!
I have business with Tsukikage Yuri as well, I'm afraid.
Who are you?
Because Tsukikage keeps getting the best test scores, he is disgracefully labeled "That guy in second!"
He is none other than Saitani Hideo!
Y-You guys!
Oh, from Class 1.
But now, I'm going to cast away that nickname!
For I shall take first place in the next test, I swear it!
I hope you're looking forward to it, Tsukikage Yuri!
Lovely.
By the way, what was this favor you wanted to ask?
Oh, well the thing is...
You want us to model for you?
I'd really like to design a dress for you to wear, Yuri!
Oh? What kind of dress?
The theme is...
"a new me"!
Seems fun!
How about we give it a go, Yuri?
Sorry, but I can't.
Huh?
Momoka, I'll help you with that math some other time, okay?
Yuri!
Sabark.
How long do you intend to let
these Precure run wild, may I ask?
I ask but for a little more patience, King Dune.
How unexpectedly lax of you.
Unless, of course, you...
I already have a plan in motion.
Oh?
I don't mind how you choose to do it.
Just ensure those Precure are eliminated, and the Great Heart Tree perishes.
Sasorina, your constant failure is rather hideous, I must say.
The only reason I keep losing is because my Desertrians don't listen to me anymore!
Your excuses! Are also! Hideous!
Maybe I should go on a trip or something.
What's the matter with you?
It couldn't be love, could it?
But you mustn't fall in love with me, I'm
afraid, for I am far too beautiful for you.
I have a present for you all today.
Dark Bracelets.
If you use these, you can make your Desertrians even darker, even viler, and even more ferocious than before!
Sasorina was bathed in the Precures' holy light, and her heart was partially purified.
But it seems she has now recovered her dark heart.
Thank you so much, my lord Sabark!
Take them!
How very beautiful.
Sabark, my liege! Please let me take on those Precure again!
Very well.
This time, make sure you defeat them!
Just leave it to me!
Really?
They asked you to be a model, Yuri?
It seems like it'd be fun, doesn't it? Why not give it a try?
I'm sure if you did, the Flower of your Heart would...
The Flower of my Heart was
lost to me when I lost my fairy.
When it happened, my heart was torn apart, and that half of it will never come back.
I suppose the damage to your
heart still hasn't healed, has it?
But do you really think your fairy would want to see you in this sorry state?
I'm sure he'd want the Flower of your Heart to bloom again, Yuri.
Yuri's fairy...
died?
G-Good morning...
Why'd ya have to make us get up so early?
Oh, come on!
We agreed to practice our new move at the dojo before school, didn't we?!
Oh!
School of Myoudouin
Let's begin.
Ready!
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin.
Jump, Tsubomi!
All right!
Higher!
Are you all right, Tsubomi?!
You seem to be a bit distracted today.
Did something happen?
Well, the thing is...
Yuri's fairy?
That's right.
I see.
That's why she said...
You were one step away from losing your partner forever.
She said that to you?
How did Yuri's fairy pass away, anyway?
I thought Grandma would know, so I tried asking her.
She said that Yuri should tell us herself
once she feels like she can talk about it.
I see.
I tried imagining how I'd feel if we lost Chypre and the others,
but when I did, I just felt so sad I burst into tears.
I know what you mean.
What?!
Tsukikage Yuri
Saitani Hideo
You did it, Hideo! Your position as #2 is safe for another day!
I was certain I'd beat her this time.
I don't even feel like trying anymore.
Who're you?
The Flower of your Heart is wilting pretty nicely.
Hm? Huh?
Tsukikage?
Saitani, get out of here!
Huh?
Look who we have here.
You're too pathetic for me to waste my time on, so just get lost, okay?
You little failure.
Flower of the Heart, come forth!
It's your cue, Desertrian!
Computer!
Big trouble!
It's Saitani!
He got turned into a Deshertrian!
Right!
Seeds of the Precure, go forth!
Precure!
Open My Heart!
A lone flower, blooming from the earth!
Cure Blossom!
A lone flower, swaying in the sea breeze!
Cure Marine!
A lone flower, bathing in the Sun's rays!
Cure Sunshine!
HeartCatch Precure!
Desertrian! Come get me!
Yuri!
Took you long enough.
Get it as far away from the school as you can!
Okay!
Sunshine!
Blossom!
Blossom Impact!
No matter how hard I try, I can't beat Tsukikage!
Huh?!
I'm not gonna bother studying anymore! I'm fed up with it all!
That's right! If you've lost, you should just give up!
Then you can just run wild to forget about it!
That's wrong!
What?
What's important is to have a strong heart, keep on trying, and never give up even if you do lose!
Com?
But you just ignored that and used
Saitani's frustration to make a Desertrian.
I've had it up to here with this!
Beep boop.
Oh, looks like a chance to try this out!
Sink into the darkness, and let your dark heart control you!
Dark Bracelet!
It seems even...
...more ferocious than before!
She's not only stolen his heart,
but she's directly wilting the Flower too!
Hmm...
Let's get started!
Say your prayers!
Sunflower Aegis!
This is the power of the Dark Bracelet!
Time to begin the counterattack!
I think I'll calculate an attack
pattern you can't possibly avoid!
Blossom!
Now I can finally vent all my hatred for you three!
Huh?
Leave this to us!
No!
If you do that, we'll lose you too!
You can't...
Not even you can sway us, Yuri!
We're going to fight too!
We'll protect everyone!
We'll protect the Precure!
Chypre, don't worry about us!
Coffret, we won't lose, I promise!
We'll protect you and everyone else, Potpourri!
Quit your yapping!
Let's show her the results of our training!
It's time for us to combine our powers!
Our bonds as Precure won't be beaten by your Dark Bracelet!
Gather, Floral Power!
Shiny Tambourine!
Flowers, dance for me!
Precure Gold Forte Burst!
Gather, Dual Floral Power!
Precure Floral Power Fortissimo!
Precure Shining Fortissimo!
Heart Catch!
What's with this "bonds as Precure" rubbish?!
I'll beat you next time, you'll see!
Are you all right?
Tsukikage?
There was this weirdo here just now!
I think you must've had a bad dream.
I guess so.
This girl said something in my dream.
"What's important is to have a strong heart and never give up, even when you lose."
Feel like I've got a spring in my step again!
Hideo!
I'm not gonna lose on the next test!
You'd better keep up, rival!
Thank goodness!
I'm glad Saitani's cheered up again.
Let's see, in the language of flowers, spinach means...
"Vitality"!
I think a Heart Seed's about to be born.
With thish, the Great Heart Tree has recovered a little more!
I want to design a dress that'll make the Flower of your Heart bloom again, Yuri!
I know I'm being brazen, but I can
feel the Flower of your Heart, Yuri!
You can feel the Flower of my Heart?
Yes!
Just a mere glance at its elegant beauty
always seems to give me the strength I need.
So please! Model for us!
If you really think you can make the
Flower of my Heart bloom again, I will.
You really mean it?!
It will! It'll bloom, I promise!
So come on, let's sing together in harmony!
Come on, all together now!
HeartCatch Precure!
When you give life your all, within your heart
a shining flower begins to bloom
So when you feel like crying, raise your head
and you'll see everyone's there by your side!
So let's dance together, hand in hand!
All those
happy feelings will be shared amongst us!
Lose yourself is the melody!
Yay, yay, hey!
And tomorrow will bring even more Hallelujahs!
So come on! Let's make the Flowers of our Hearts bloom!
With all our might!
HeartCatch Precure!
The HeartCatch Mirage!
A mysterious item that'll enhance our
Precure powers to near-infinite levels!
The HeartCatch Mirage!
It rests silently in the Precure Palace, the castle beyond the clouds.
And the trial that awaits us is a
showdown with that enigmatic hottie?!
Even still, we will surpass you, and continue onward!
HeartCatch Precure:
A Showdown With the Hottie?
We Weren't Expecting This!
We'll catch everyone's hearts!