kiss kiss kiss!
mou muchuu na no
I’m lost in a daze
Sakura Trick
doki doki shichau no yo
I find myself restless
anata no soba de mata
while at your side
takanaru kono kodou wo
I just can’t stop
tomaranai yo
this beating in my chest
tomodachi nan dakedo
We may just be friends
sore ijou no kimochi
but our feelings run deeper
kono mama ja watashi wa
If things stay like this
dou ka shichau
I might go crazy
gaman de wa
Nothing ever gets solved
kaiketsu dekinai no
by just holding back
dare ni mo mane dekinai
I want to share something
No way!
koto ga shitai na
no one else can imitate
won’t you kiss me? tokubetsu na futari dake na himitsu
Won’t you kiss me? It’s a special secret only we share
itsudatte, dokodatte
Whenever, wherever
watashi no subete wo uketomete hoshii no
I want you to accept me whole
can I kiss you? saikou no futari dake na jikan
Can I kiss you? It’s the best alone time with you
kuchibiru fureau no
With our lips touching gently
anata to watashi no kiss, kiss, kiss
you and I share a kiss, kiss, kiss
hanaretakunai
I don’t want to let go
Misato West High School
Student Council Room
We’re really running a tight budget here…
Student Council President
It’ll be sad if we can’t do anything for our 3rd years now…
I get what you mean.
Student Council President
Especially since they’ve been looking after us this whole time.
I wonder if we can’t enlist some additional help…
Oh, I have a friend that wants to hold a graduation party.
Shall I introduce you to them…
President SumiSumi?
How dare you refer to your president in such a manner?!
Looks like it got to her.
Ah
The President is SumiSumi Now!
President Mitsuki's Farewell Party (tentative)
Things that she likes
Matcha!!
I’ve never given it much thought, but in terms of Mitsuki’s likes…
President Mitsuki's Farewell Party (tentative)
Things that she likes
Matcha!!
I can only think of matcha.
Matcha Flavor
What am I gonna do?
She’s probably real busy around this time.
What’re you doing, Yuu-chan?!
You can ask me, can’t you?!
Oh, I get it, Yuu-chan!
So what’s been up with her lately?
Lemme see…
We’ve been having baths together like we used to.
I’ve gotta check if she’s got a suspicious smell!
And we’ve been sleeping together like we did as kids.
Maybe she’ll mumble something in her sleep!
I can’t help but feel jealous…
rattle
Tell me more! What else do you do with her?!
Hey, Haruka!
Hey, hey, this is our new student council president, Otokawa Sumi.
She has something to talk with you about.
Oh Mitsuki, what’s with your hair? And you’re shorter too!
Even your glasses… what’s going on now?!
I’m her little sister!
I do  recall her mentioning a little sister now!
So you’re her sister, Haruka?
Haruka’s right here.
I’m  the sister. Yuu!
That’s right. Haruka would be me.
I haven’t seen you around before.
So there’s a first year taking the role of president now.
Nice to meet you.
There are no first years anymore, right?
So you’re going to be a second year starting in April…?
That would make me your age.
Ah
Oh I forgot! Our school’s not taking any new students in!
I’m a second year, going on third year!
Whaaaa?!
So you’re a whole year older than us!
What’s with your surprised looks? Isn’t it obvious now?
She talks funny.
Yuzu, try to be more respectful of your senior.
You’re one to talk! Calling me SumiSumi and all that!
Not to worry. As I’m taking over as leader, I must be forgiving in all respects.
I’ll tell you of why I speak like so.
My grandfather was quite an esteemed person,
so I’ve received his distinct form of speech since birth.
Isn’t it marvelous?!
You tell ‘em, President SumiSumi! Amazing!
Will ya quit calling me SumiSumi?!
President SumiSumi… you’re letting your speech slip.
Oh goodness, no.
So she’s doing it on purpose…
So now what do you want from Haruka, President SumiSumi?
Will you cease calling me “SumiSumi” already?
I beg of you.
I had heard you were planning a farewell party for the third-years.
Well, it’s more for President Mitsuki’s sake.
Big Sis
Only for her then?
You got it. Just for her.
Big Sis
I think I just heard Haruka-san mention my name…
It can’t be… I’m just passing by.
Vice President
Why don’t we have Rina join as well?
Right! She’s really close to Mitsuki!
They’ve always helped me to stand on my own.
You should probably stress that part right there.
O-Okay!
Not to worry, Sumi-chan. Stay calm.
And that’s when I really began to enjoy my role as secretary.
I want them to leave being glad that they enrolled here.
…now.
You’re letting it slip.
Whisper
snap
I’m trying to be serious right now!
Even though the budget wasn’t there,
they still went through the trouble of letting us do things like that ball sports meet.
It’d be nice if we could do something like that for them now.
Let’s do that then! We’ll have a sports meet with them!
Yuu-chan, have any idea what kinda sports she likes?
She’s pretty bad at sports in general.
deflated
Back
to the
drawing
board
I thought I’d be able to revive the Sonoda Yuu cheering squad!
So it’s just for yourself?!
Try not to forget who we’re doing this for in the first place.
Is there anything else those two might like besides sports?
I see. It’s not like we’re limited to sports or anything, right?
Hey Yuu-chan… could you let me know what else Mitsuki likes?
Besides matcha.
Well she has tastes similar to mine, so…
A red bean soup with lots of paste on it…
Mmm
or mochi topped with flour and a glaze of brown sugar…
How Japanese.
Gimme something other than food!
If that’s all we can think of, how about a Japanese sweets girl’s night?
That’s a lot of sugar…
It’s a shame you can’t behold the greatness of such foods with your mind stuck on yakisoba.
Watch what you say about my yakisoba!
Grr
Would you happen to have any ideas, President SumiSumi?
Truth is, I’ve never really had a deep talk with her before.
Watching from afar was all I could manage.
I noticed Rina would often stare her way too.
I bet she loves her lots!
I think you just found out who Sakai adores!
Well aren’t you happy now…
E-Excuse me.
Okay, Yuu. Have anything else in mind?
Um…
We could try sneaking around the third-year classes and see what’s popular right now.
pet
You’re always so helpful, Shizuku-chan!
Good girl, good girl.
Stop it!
Okay, let’s go, Yuu-chan.
I’ll go too now!
I never really come up here, so I’m kinda nervous.
Yeah...
Really now?
They dye their shoelaces!
Although I bet you guys will do such things in a year’s time.
There’re so many people studying for exams here…
Come to think of it, the only third-years we know of are those two, huh?
I bet you would’ve met more had there been more clubs to join.
Excuse us please.
S-Sorry about that.
This place is filled with mature-looking people.
Yeah. They’re so refined.
But at least…
you’ve got a much bigger chest.
Just keep your mouth shut!
Mumble
Doesn’t it seem like everyone’s…
eating pudding!
Every class we saw had people eating pudding, right?
Yeah, they sure were now!
Why is that? Is there some sort of pudding fad among third-years right now?
Bucket matcha pudding…
That's it!
Sakura Trick
I guess we’re going with a matcha pudding eating contest, now.
I’m all for it!
It’d be even better if you added some azuki beans...
I’m sure they’ll love the idea!
I really can’t wait for this now!
President SumiSumi… are you o—
So soft!
Oh wow!
You seem to be around a D… won’t you let me confirm now?
prod
You’re starting to freak me out a little!
You don’t know what you’re talking about! She’s clearly a C!
touch
You too?!
See? That’s the feel of a C.
feel
My  hand begs to differ.
S-Stop it...
That’s a great pair you have there now.
Well, I’ll be off to class then!
We’ll settle this another time!
I never knew President SumiSumi was so weird.
Yuu-chan… you should know by now how sensitive I am there...
Fire Extinguisher
C’mon, I just couldn’t help myself!
Is that all you care about?
Do you have some kind of fetish for them?
Answer me.
I… like…
Can you not say it louder?
I wanna hear the rest…
No good.
Lemme hear it… you like what?
H-Hurry up with it… you meanie.
You’re a bit more assertive today…
Just shut up!
Heheheh
Let’s get back to the others already!
Big Sis
Okay!
freeze
Big Sis
Little Sis
Now the President’s SumiSumi!
End
No Motor Vehicles
Hello there, everyone. I’m Takayama Haruka.
I have a best friend named Sonoda Yuu-chan.
We do things no other girls like us would, and that’s our little secret.
peek
It’s her hairpiece!
Yuu-chan!
It’s a bit sudden, but…
Good morning, Haruka-san.
...I can no longer kiss Yuu-chan anymore!
Flashback
To run into President Mitsuki at such a bad time…
May I ask what you two were doing just now?
What did it seem like to you, Rina?
A k-kiss, I suppose.
And you think it’s okay to do that at school,
never mind with another girl?
And it seems likely that this wasn’t the first time.
Which one of you started this?
It was Haruka.
It was Yuu-chan!
Which one is it?
Are you two in love with each other?
I won’t speak of this with anyone else.
Haruka-san… it’s about time you open your eyes.
Yuu’s my… she’s my dear little sister.
So that’s why…
you are not to kiss her anymore!
devastated
The Cherry-Colored Truth
Today's Class
Freestyle Dance
Light warm-up
Practice in pairs
Choose themes for next week's performance
W-What am I supposed to do now?
Somethin’ got ya worried, Harupoppo?
Don’t sweat it. You’re not too bad at dancing either.
That’s not what was on my mind…
But maybe Kotone-chan would get where I’m coming from…
Hey, I’d like to keep this between you and I, but…
Oh my, you’re tryin’ to kiss me?! We can’t!
T-That’s not what I wanted!
She hit the nail right on the head. How am I gonna ask now?
If someone were to find out the secret you share with Shizuku-chan,
and they told you to stop it right away, what would you do?
I’d probably ignore them, I guess.
If it was a secret, you just have to make it one again.
That’s true! It’s fine if they don’t find out.
Haruka.
I’ve been asked to keep a close eye on you by Mitsuki herself.
Mind telling me what happened?
Why’d she just say “watch her closely!” out of the blue?
Uh
oooh
There we go!
Ta
da!
How d’you like my turn?!
Did Mitsuki seem really mad?
Not exactly mad…
I’ve got no audience…
Watch me, guys!
I saw your every move. You seem like a really skilled dancer.
Thanks a bunch, Shizuku-chan!
All the sweat…
Alright everyone, we’re going to start practicing for our performance.
I haven’t gotten a single chance to talk with her today…
I’ve got no sense of rhythm, so it’s too hard for me to dance.
What? But it’s loads of fun!
Please pair up with your partner from last class.
Then that means…!
I’m with Yuu-chan by default!
Haruka!
Hey, Yuu-chan.
Maybe it's for the best to stop kissing from now on?
stumble
I-I’m sorry, Haruka!
I didn’t mean to… I really did just trip.
Sure.
You should pay attention to your footwork.
Alright, now just watch!
Oh, that’s just great.
We’re always around the others…
And now Kaede-chan’s keeping an eye on me.
Hey Yuzu! I can’t get a look!
Whoops, watch out!
What? You can’t see me?
Lemme show you again!
Aha!
I just stumbled a bit.
Haruka! You did that on purpose, right?!
I’m so impressed.
I told you we can’t…
But it was just an accident…
No…
I told you to stop!
angry
Now I’ll start exploiting your weakness.
I’m sorry… forgive me.
Alright! Gotta protect my sister!
Are you headed for Yuu-chan’s class?
Why yes.
Even though it’s just a short break, I can’t grow complacent.
I will not allow them to keep kissing!
A bit too
late for that
I know, I should pick up something for Yuu at the cafeteria.
Matcha Pudding
Matcha
Pudding
Matcha Pudding
They’ve got the usual matcha pudding!
Matcha
Pudding
So you’re after pudding as well?!
startle
I do wonder why pudding is so popular among third-years now.
It’s just you, Sumi… what are you up to?
I’m looking into the big demand for pudding now!
First-year
Second-year
Third-year
So far, the third-years seem to be the top buyers…
Why?
How could this be?
Why? I do wonder why!
Why?
How could this be?
Well I guess…
You guess?
Big Sis
A while back…
I told Rina that eating pudding would help your studies.
And I guess it just spread from there.
It was just a coincidence, but everyone took it seriously.
But if they believe it, why not let them?
So you were the Pudding Boom Provocateur!
Pudding Boom
Provocateur
President Mitsuki
appears to be the
Pudding Boom Provocateur!!
By the way, where are you eating lunch now?
I would like to join you!
Of course. I’ll be going to 1-A.
That would be those colourful shoelace girls.
Matcha Pudding
And they’re buying some pudding.
I guess they’re hitting the books too, now.
Of course they are. I bet they’re working hard at it.
Let’s go then.
Hopefully this helps us become…
as big as Mitsuki!
We gotta start by eating what she does.
You shouldn’t make a habit of judging people that way, Sumi.
I’ll hold that to heart, now.
You seem fairly easy to understand, unlike myself.
M-Me?!
I really admire how you can be so honest!
Oh really?
touch
I also admire your soft spots too.
You can be pretty weird, you know.
You may even be bigger than Haruka!
Come on, now…
So you know Haruka-san already?
Kaede just introduced me to her, now!
I see…
So that means that you touched her chest?!
Why did you get angry now?
I don’t quite get it myself…
Would it be my fault…?
N-No, not really.
There’s something I want Haruka-san to reflect upon.
That’s what I might be mad about.
Would you have anything you might want to say to her now?
You can ask her to let you feel them too, now!
When did I say I wanted to do that?!
Are you pondering something with regards to Haruka?
I myself am pretty bad at subtleties,
so I’ve learned to express myself clearly.
Come to think of it, you’ve changed quite a bit since I met you.
the past
At the start, you sounded completely normal.
Understood! I’ll get right to it, President Mitsuki!
Just forget about the past already!
But she just…
Now
...now!
Ah
I forgot to bring my lunch from the classroom now!
Why not go fetch it?
I will!
Something I want to tell Haruka-san…?
Maybe just that I want her to just be friends with Yuu?
But considering what’s always coming to my mind…
I want to become Haruka-san’s lover!
What the hell was I just thinking?!
H-Hey now… this isn’t…
C-Could it be?!
Haruka-san… it’s about time you open your eyes.
Having said that…
maybe I’m  the one that needs to open their eyes…
Have I been… in love with Haruka-san this whole time?!
No! No way!
How can I even show myself now?!
The bell...
Big Sis
The Cherry-Colored Truth
End
Sakura Trick
show
won’t you kiss?
Won’t you kiss?
kiss and love!
Kiss and love!
futari dake no jikan ga
The time we share alone
futari dake no himitsu ga
the secret we keep
futari dake no yakusoku
the promise we both hold
aru kara ne
we have it all
yorokobi wakachi aete
If we share in our joy
kanashimi wake aetara
and split our sorrow
hitori yori shiawase ni nareru you ni
we’ll be happier than we’d be alone
ashita no omoide wo, saa fuyasou
Memories to come… let’s make them now
ippai ni shichaou ne
We’ll make lots and lots
love you!
Love you!
kono hiroi sekai de aeta kiseki, tokubetsu na no
The miracle that we met in this huge world… it’s special
anata ja nai to dame dakara
It had to be you all along
futari ja nai to dekinai koto da yo
It’s something we can’t do unless we’re together
ima sugu ni, daisuki kiss and love
Right now, let’s share a kiss and love
Next Episode Preview
With the cherry trees in full bloom,
Yuu-chan and I began high school.
From then on, we did so much with many new friends…
But those fun-filled days flew by in a moment.
Once again, we are brought back to the day on which the petals fall…
and I…
The final episode:
Pudding and Mitsuki's Resolve
Sakura Trick
“Pudding and Mitsuki’s Resolve” and, “Sakura Trick”.
We’ll see you then.