You tricked us.
All I did was ask you to become magical girls.
I mean, sure, I left out the part about what your real body would be, but...
Why didn't you tell us!?
Because you never asked.
And hey, as long as you never found out, no harm, no foul.
Honestly, even that Mami girl never realized.
Anyway, what does it matter? You humans can't even find your souls to begin with.
There? To you, it's just a lump of neurons, right?
And down there is just the core of the circulatory system.
And yet, when you can no longer maintain life, your spirits fade as well.
In order to prevent that from happening, I gave your soul form, made you able to protect it.
Doesn't that make fighting witches at least a little bit safer?
And what gave you the right to do it!?
You're too naïve about fighting.
For example, think of the pain and shock you'd feel if you took a spear to the gut.
This is true pain.
A single blow, and you're unable to even move.
You were able to remain standing in your fight with Kyoko only because you blocked out the worst of the pain.
BEcause your consciousness isn't directly connected to your body, you can do this.
That's why you survived that battle.
Once you get used to it, you'll be able to block out all pain.
Of course, that'll blunt your reactions, so perhaps you shouldn't get too used to it.
Why? Why do this to us?
When you took on your fate of battle, you each had a wish, right?
They've been fulfilled, haven't they?
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 7 Can you face your true feelings
Stand!
Bow!
Homura... You knew?
Why didn't you say anything?
Even when I told people, they never believed me.
Why would Kyubey do such horrible things?
He doesn't think they're horrible.
Beings like him have no concept of human values.
All he'll do is describe it as compensation for the miracle.
That's no fair at all!
Being turned into that just to heal the wounds of someone she loves!?
It certainly was a miracle.
He made the impossible possible.
Even if Sayaka Miki had cared for him for the rest of her life...
That boy would never have played the violin again.
Truly, miracles cannot even be purchased with one's life.
Yet he  sells them.
Sayaka will never be able to go back, will she.
I told you before. Give up on Sayaka Miki.
But Sayaka saved me!
If Sayaka wasn't a magical girl, Hitomi and I both would have died!
Dion't confuse gratitude and responsibility.
You have no way to save her.
Don't go out of your way to worry about feeling weak or wanting to pay her back.
Homura... Why are you so cold?
Am I?
Perhaps it's because I'm no longer human.
How can I face Kyosuke with my body like this?
How long are you going to mope around, silly?
You look like you're having a tough time. Let's talk.
Having some regrets about your new body, huh?
Me? I'm fine with it.
I mean, ever since I got this power I've been able to do whatever I want.
Nothing to regret there.
You just got what you deserved.
Yeah, what I deserved, that's a great way to put it.
As long as I live for myself, all of my problems are my iown fault.
No reason to hold a grudge against anyone, and absolutely no regrets.
If I think of it that way, I can take just about anything.
Why did you bring me here?
We have a lot to talk about.
Want one?
If you keep wasting food, I'll kill you.
This used to be my dad's church.
He was too honest. Too kind.
Every morning reading the paper, the worries of the world brought him to tears.
Dad believed that to create a new era, a new faith was necessary.
So his sermons at time strayed beyond the dogma.
And as time passed, his flock became fewer and fewer.
He was excommunicated,
and no one would listen to him.
It all seems so obvious now.
When outsiders looked at it, all they saw was a weird cult.
No matter how just or how obvious his teachings were, society made him an outcast.
Our family was left with nothing, not even food to put on the table.
I couldn't understand it.
Dad had said nothing wrong.
He just talked about different things than other people.
If they had just lent him their ears, even for five minutes, anyone could've understood that he was right!
But no one would listen.
It hurt. I hated them.
I couldn't stand that no one understood him.
That's why I asked Kyubey.
Asked him to make everyone listen seriously to my Dad.
The next morning, the pews were packed.
Every day, more worshippers arrived with an unnatural vigor.
And I joined the ranks of the magical girls.
No matter how just Dad's sermons, they wouldn't destroy witches on their own.
I felt my chance had come, and rushed headstrong into it.
I thought Dad and I would be heads and tails of the saving-the-world coin.
But then my Dad found out.
When he learned that his flock was driven not by faith but by magic, he snapped.
He called his own daughter a witch sent to tempt men's hearts.
It's so ironic! I spent every night fighting  witches!
Dad was crushed.
His end was miserable.
Drowning his sorrows in drink, driven in the end to madness, he led his family to a pointless suicide.
I was the only one left.
My wish destroyed my family.
I made a wish without thinking of anyone else's circumstances,
and it resulted in misfortune for everyone.
At that moment, I swore within my heart that I would never use magic for the sake of another again.
That I would use all this power for myself.
A wish is no idle matter. For every beam of hope you pray for, a shadow of despair is cast.
That way it's a zero-sum game. The balance of the world is preserved.
Why are you telling me this?
You should get serious and focus on yourself.
Live how you deserve.
I don't get it. You talk about living for your own sake,
but here you are worrying about me.
You made the same mistake in the beginning that I did.
You don't need to keep living like this. You'll regret it.
You've already paid too much.
Why not get some change back?
Like you...
Yeah. I know what I'm doing, so I just can't stand watching you muddle through.
I guess I misunderstood you.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
But I don't regret wishing for someone else's sake.
I've decided I'll never regret it. I don't want to make what I felt then a lie.
Ever.
What's with you?
I don't think I paid too dearly.
This power can do so many amazing things if used the right way.
And how did you even get this apple?
What did you pay the shop?
You can't tell me, can you?
So I can't eat that apple.
I can't even be happy it was offered.
Moron! We're magical girls!
There's no one else we can rely on!
I'll continue fighting, following my own path.
If I get in your way, you can try and kill me again, but I won't lose.
I won't hold it against you.
Morning, Sayaka!
Good morning, Sayaka.
Morning.
Did something happen yesterday?
I just felt a little under the weather.
Sayaka...
Don't worry. I'm fine now.
All right, let's really—-
Oh, Kamijo was released?
You're all healed up now, Kamijo?
Yeah. Being cooped up in my house won't do my rehab any good either.
They're trying to get me walking without a crutch by next week.
I'm so happy for him.
Sayaka, you haven't even talked to him yet. Go say something!
Nah, I'm fine.
So, what did you want to talk about?
Love.
I've been keeping a secret from you and Madoka.
I've...
I've always been fond of Kyosuke Kamijo.
Really?
Why, Hitomi, I didn't think you had it in you!
And that Kyosuke, such a ladykiller.
You're his childhood friend, aren't you?
Well I guess, I mean, I'm kinda stuck with him...
Is that really all it is?
I've made up my mind. I'm not going to lie to myself anymore.
How about you?
Can you face your true feelings?
Wh... What are you talking about?
You're my dear friend, so I don't want to steal your man.
You've had your eye on him for longer than I have.
Sio you have the right to preempt me.
Hitomi...
Tomorrow, after school, I will confess my love to Kamijo.
I'll wait a day. Sayaka, make sure in that time that you have no regrets about not telling Kamijo how you feel.
I...
Madoka?
Mind if I tag along?
I don't want you to feel lonely.
Why? Why are you so kind?
I'm not worth it.
Don't...
I had a regret today.
Just for a moment, I thought that if I hadn't saved Hitomi...
I'm not worthy of being an ally of justice!
I couldn't even look Mami in the face like this!
Hitomi's taking Kyosuke away from me!
I can't do anything about it!
I'm already dead! I'm just a zombie!
I can never embrace him like this!
I can never tell him "kiss me!"
Sorry. Thanks for that.
Sayaka...
I'm okay now. I just needed that.
All right, let's go hunt us some witches!
I wasn't expecting you to just sit back and watch.
She's fighting a witch today, not a familiar.
It's gonna drop a Grief Seed, so it's not a waste.
Surprising that that would make you back off.
That idiot's messing up again.
Sayaka!
Man, you're such a mess.
Just stand back! I've got it!
Let me show you how this is done!
Hey!
Stay out of my way. I'm doing this myself.
Sayaka!
Don't tell me you're—
He was right!
If I don't want to, I don't have to feel a thing!
Stop... Please, stop...
One day, perhaps the light of love shining in your eyes will
(Go beyond the time)
There is but one dream, of a world rushing toward its doom
(Will it be destroyed?)
Swallow your hesitation! What do you desire?
Chasing these greedy desires, will the future fade away?
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
I want to be by your side as you smile,
filled with the strength to smash even the darkness
In my trembling hand, I grasp
the courage of a plucked laurel
Relying only on my emotions,
my prayer awakens the light
I might be, you know...
Seriously!?
Impending...
Marriage
You're so kind.
Impending...
Lust
What are you gonna do?
Thank you for waiting, adults.
Reality
Fate
Nightmare.
This is an adult game.
Catherine.
Katherine!
Click.
Illustration: Hajime Ueda
I'm going to be a different kind of magical girl than you lot. I'm sure of it.
I need no reward. I'll never use magic for my own benefit!
Episode 8 I've been such a fool
I've been such a fool.