Shinpei!
Shin...
Shot by a sniper rifle from outside...
They got Nezu!
I didn't sense any Shadows.
The bullet that killed you wasn't from a Shadow copy,
it was from a real rifle.
Having Nezu so far was a mistake!
If only he'd been close enough for ya to sense the Shadows.
I screwed up bad!
They knew Nezu would be keeping watch as a sniper.
Damn it!
I thought she'd come directly after me again!
Wait, ain't their goal to keep ya alive, Shin?
Killing ya just restarts the loop, so why?
Haine realized that we're looping together.
Remember what I said?
The loop start point moves up each time.
I can tell that the deadline's getting close.
The edges of time
are slowly but surely crumbling away.
If I get killed at the same point in time again, then I'll probably
only have one loop left.
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
That's the price I pay for my awakening
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Illuminated by the moon
Your figure casts a shadow
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
That happens to be my cue
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
Amidst pain and sorrow
I'll conquer my fears
It's a paradox of life
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
July 22nd
(Seventh loop)
Ya can only loop one more time?
Lights, Camera, Action
Let's say this is the "limit."
Every time I die, I return to this marker.
Limit
Time
I can't go back further than the limit,
so this is the starting point.
Death
In the last loop, I died at 7:55 PM.
And this loop began at 6:40 PM.
Limit
Time moves on from this point.
Imagine I'm walking forward at a set speed until the current time, 7:20 PM.
Present
Limit
The limit also moves forward.
It's been slower than my walking pace so far,
so it hasn't caught up.
But every time I die, it speeds up.
If ya die again, where will the next start point be?
Well, I'd guess...
just after 7 PM.
That's just a few minutes ago!
And if I'm killed at the same point as last time,
or maybe even earlier,
there won't be a ninth loop.
Limit
Present
As I'm attempting to find my footing,
Death
the limit will move ahead of me.
Even if you go back, there's no place to land.
Yes, I'll fall down into the darkness below the cliff.
Hey, hey, is that really true?
Or is this all just yer assumptions?
He's seen it as the observer.
It's the truth.
That cliff is the limit of your observation.
The "event horizon."
If you fall, your death will be permanent.
The world that follows will be as Haine has foreseen it.
Haine must've realized that, which is why she's trying to kill Shinpei.
That's terrible!
How did she find me?
Haine found out about the plan in the fourth loop.
It was likely when she scanned me.
I took lethal damage in the last scene of the fourth loop.
We probably fought before then and my memories were read.
How do Shadows share information amongst themselves?
Do they show memories like ya do?
Yes.
They also talk and share physical notes with each other.
But Haine can also use telepathy.
We can probably assume that the Shadows in contact with her have experienced pseudo-loops just like us.
Now wait a second.
Didn't ya say data can be saved through loops?
Then ain't it possible they copied my rifle?
If they did, this place ain't safe.
Don't worry about that.
When a print of a copied item gets too far from the Shadow, it naturally disappears.
Copies can only exist within 50 meters of a Shadow.
So, basically, even if they copied a long-ranged rifle,
the bullet couldn't fly more than 50 meters.
Even with unlimited bullets, that's pointless.
The enemy got the better of me last time,
but I also learned something.
Haine knows my location thanks to this brand.
She will definitely come here to witness my death.
We settle this tonight.
Shinpei.
They're coming at ya head-on.
Ya sure brought an army, Shide.
And you seem to have gained allies as well, Shinpei.
I don't see the others.
Where are they hiding?
Is this a trap?
I'm not like y'all.
I don't stoop to cowardly measures.
Let's just drop the petty tricks and fight fair and square.
Oh? You seem quite confident.
That sounds just fine.
Right, Mio?
Yes.
That's my Shin.
Yer too cool!
Oh?
Sis.
It's my life they're after, so I'll be the bait.
He ran.
So much for fighting fair and square!
Where are ya taking Shin?!
Ajiro Shinpei.
I can't stand him.
That Shadow called Shide—it really has no weakness.
Is it invincible?
Hurry!
Stop, Mio.
Pardon me.
Papa 'n' the rest of y'all, come with me.
We'll go after Shinpei and Ushio.
Mio, go and finish off that hunter.
Understood, Mother.
Ryuunosuke!
Leave this area to me.
Thanks!
I doubt you'll be able to hear this,
but there's something important I forgot to tell you, Ryuunosuke.
Thank you.
Damn!
It's here! Yer turn, kids!
My Shadow!
I'll take ya down!
Wha—
Dammit!
Ya idiot.
Ya oughta fix that bad habit of getting heated and charging off ahead.
Th-Thanks, Tokiko.
Rosencrantz.
Guildenstern.
Go wild.
Be as quiet as an explosion.
Hi... zu... ru...
Asa!
Dodge to the left.
But I foresaw that shot hitting!
I told ya she'd cover for him.
I see...
Ryuu!
She has the sight!
She can see my movements two seconds into the future!
Now, blam!
Nezu!
With no scope?
That elder gentleman is quite the marksman.
Ya okay, Shide?
Please keep out of his line of sight.
He's quite dangerous.
Good grief.
Damn it, Mio, what's taking ya so long?
Tokiko?!
Guil, crush that thing.
Halt!
Tokiko is not yer master.
Kill Tokiko.
Kill her!
What's the matter, Haine?
That stray's connection with me has been severed.
The only one who could do this
is Ushio.
Ya mad? Try and reach me!
So it was you!
My, my, this is going to be very fun.
Yer body's so graceful.
Mio is athletic, after all.
I wish I could watch this forever.
It's a shame.
Now, Sou!
So much for fighting "fair and square," eh?
You meanie-heads.
I believed you for a second, too.
I'm pure-hearted, I'll have you know.
I knew y'all would chase me.
Even if ya knew it was a trap.
Acting like ya have the upper hand the whole time, just like ya are now.
Think yer above us, do ya?
Well, Shinpei's above even y'all.
Summer Time Rendering
That gas created a sea of fire.
The Shadows have nowhere to run!
It's working!
Shadows are weak to fire, just like I thought!
I'm sorry, Papa, Mama.
It's hot, isn't it?
But don't worry.
If I kill him, it'll fix everything!
Come 'n' get some!
By looking down on us,
ya took yer eyes off the prize, Haine.
This one's for Ushio!
Gotcha!
I'll erase ya!
How long are ya planning on grinning stupidly with Shiori's face, ya fake?!
Stop it!
S-Stop... Don't erase me!
I decided this would be the body.
I was gonna return with this girl and her family.
We'd be together forever.
Haine!
I won't be fooled by yer crocodile tears!
So...
don't erase me!
N-No way!
That thing's still alive!
Ushio!
Shinpei!
Y-Y-You cannot kill me with fire, b-b-b-but...
it can, can, can kill y-y-you!
I-I-I realized some-something.
You, you and Haine can b-bring the information you hold into the next loop.
In, in other words, if your data is harmed or kill, kill, killed...
that gets brought into the next the next loop, correct?
It'll take Shinpei a few minutes, minutes to die.
I missed his vitals on purpose, you see.
What happens when you die—die before, before him?
I-I-I'm so curious, -urious to find, to find out!
No...
No!
Sorry, but I'm not interested in finding out.
I ain't fixin' to die just yet!
You're so fast...
I didn't e-e-even realize you'd swapped places.
So the, the, the thing I'd grabbed on to
was a clump of hair with your dummy printed on it...
Yer not invincible.
I'll erase ya!
A person's hand?
There's someone inside!
The flames are gone?
Can't breathe!
Haine!
What...
did...
What the hell was that?
She got away.
I was so close to erasing her.
Ushio!
Shide, ya okay?
Yes, I can return after some restructuring.
How are Mommy and Daddy?
Shinpei was mortally wounded.
He'll die in a few minutes,
and the final loop will begin.
I'm hungry.
Of course.
Ushio!
I'm fine, Shinpei.
I'm just tired from copying so much.
But yer bleeding!
Don't ya ever fake that yer fine in front of me!
Shinpei...
This blood's because some glass hit my projected body.
But weren't ya shot?
A bulletproof vest.
I saw how to make one online.
Ow, ow, ow!
Stop, stop!
My shoulder and side were hit too!
Thank goodness.
The flames caused by the gasoline and match were essentially data.
They only burned what she wanted them to,
meaning we and the building were unaffected.
Flames were effective against the Shadows.
The normal Shadows that have fused with Shide died instantly,
and even Shide was slowed by them.
Furthermore, Ushio's hacking coincidentally revealed a human body within Shide.
However, Haine scanned and erased the air in the gymnasium.
The resulting vacuum inside the building caused the outside air to instantly rush in,
allowing them to escape.
All before we could scan Shide's true form.
But the air? How?
I can copy air and liquids too.
But it needs some kind of container.
Ushio was able to scan the gasoline inside a can, after all.
It's possible if you think of the gymnasium as the vessel.
That was amazing, even though she's our enemy.
I don't have that kind of power to scan something on such a large scale.
It's frustrating!
However, tonight was a fruitful night.
Yup.
Everyone survived.
That's what matters most.
Indeed.
Ushio.
C'mere.
Did it go as planned?
Yeah.
Lemme ask ya one more time, Ushio.
Once ya cut that connection, that link with Haine,
is it really, truly safe?
It worked well with Ros and Guil.
Yup.
I just mess with their heads a little.
Basically, I just have to make them the same as me.
I could easily finish it off right now.
Ya sure about this, Mio?
Yeah.
Do it, Sis.
Make my Shadow one of us.
Next time
Original