Hey, everyone, we're going to start Kaleido Star!
When you watch Kaleido Star,
please keep your room brightly lit,
and sit as far from the TV as you can.
Well, well, well, you guys all
have times when you're impatient too,
and you want to do
something right now, right?
You're champing at the bit and
irritated that time won't go faster,
and it's just like, "Oh, come on!"
I remembered how much fun the stage is
because of that performance the other day,
and I'm so worked up it's
like I just can't stand still!
And in the midst of that now
Mr. Kenneth is opening a car show,
and I get to be in it too!
Okay, my batteries are fully charged!
I'm gonna do my best! Best! Best!
Tattoo Kiss hajimari wa aka to kuro no Passion
Toki ni urahara na kokoro o tayori ni
Tattoo Kiss kirifuda wa mirai o kaeru Mission
Koi ni aimai na kotae wa iranai
Arienai genjitsu minai furi shite mo Bet
Egatai shinjitsu
Can U feel me now?
Nesshiyasui jibun ni Say What?
Tomadou iibun
Dreamin' samenai yume ochiteku sadame
Don't stop lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
Ya ya ya
Believe in U hikikae ni subete ushinatte mo
Still lovin' Can't stop lovin' U
No no no
Tattoo Kiss
Yes, I think so too.
Seriously, I was really moved!
Sora Naegino is the best!
I started wanting to try
chasing my own dream again too.
Yes.
Even if I terminate her contract,
even if performances are cancelled,
wherever Sora is becomes a stage.
It's as if the stage itself is
trying to bring Sora back to it.
Yes, he's investigating that right now,
but it appears as if Leon
Oswald really does hold the key.
Oh, that's right!
What is it, Mr. Kenneth?
I just had a great idea.
A great idea?
"Launching An Amazing Smile!"
Here!
Amazing!
It's like she can't stand
to not be moving her body.
Ever since she gave that all-out
performance at the bank that day,
it's like she can't contain
herself even if she tries.
But this is more Sora's style,
so it's a good thing.
Yep!
Whee!
Dust, go bye-bye!
All shiny, sparkle! All clean, yay!
And everybody's bouncing!
What? Really?!
Yes! Yes!
I understand! Yes! Yes! I'm on my way!
Oh, big news!
What? For real?!
For real! It's for real!
I see, it looks like the time has come
to put the project I've been
secretly developing into action.
You're finally going to do it, huh Anna?
Yeah. I'm going to give it a shot, sink or swim.
All right. I won't try to stop you anymore.
The problem is numbers.
I'd really like at least one more person.
Give it your best shot, Anna!
Yeah, you too, Mia.
Aiming for...
Our dreams.
Yeah.
Sora captivated even a bank robber,
and in a place that wasn't even a proper stage.
I can't satisfy Leon on the stage.
I don't have the slightest
idea what it is I'm missing.
I await your instruction!
Oh, where's Miss Cathy?
Training is over, May.
It's pointless to go any further with it.
But...
Isn't that what you're thinking too?
I think I'm doing my best.
I don't know what more I should do.
I wonder if the only way is to call Sora
and try making her do the same thing.
Am I disqualified?
When we met in New York,
you said it was your dream to stand
on the same stage as me, didn't you?
But at that time you couldn't answer
when I asked you what your next dream was.
You still can't answer, can you?
Doing this training, I've
figured out what you're missing.
It's the most important thing
to anyone who stands on a stage.
All you're projecting is your desperation
to be told the way out of this training.
I never once felt from you
any passion to entertain Cathy.
May, what do you want
after becoming Leon's partner?
What do you want after defeating Sora?
What do you want? What are
you seeking from the stage?
"Becoming Leon's partner" and
"defeating Sora" are both small things.
What's important is what comes after that.
Nobody can tell you what that is.
You have to find it yourself.
What you need is to know
the importance of a smile.
The importance of a smile?
What did they tell us to
gather here for all of a sudden?
Dunno.
Anna and the others aren't here yet,
but everyone else is assembled.
Okay.
I know this is sudden, but
this selected group of members
is going to do a performance at
the Kenneth Motors New Model Event.
We're going to have you perform too, Sora.
I can go onstage?
Yep! That's what Mr. Kenneth wants.
Wow! Really and truly?!
How wonderful, huh?
Isn't that great, Sora?!
Yeah! I'm really looking forward to it!
What you need is to know
the importance of a smile.
So does that mean Sora knows it?
Okay then, Mia, will you
explain the show's setup?
Right!
Whoops, before that, it looks
like the fated day has come!
Hello, are you ready? Roger!
What's going on?
Now, let's have them make their appearance!
It's Anna and the Amazing
Clowns! Come on down!
Hey...
Anna?
Cater. Cater. Cater. Cater.
Pillar. Pillar. Pillar. Pillar.
Cater. Cater.
Pillar. Pillar.
Cater. Sit!
Anna!
Okay, we're gonna do this
just like we talked about, Clowns!
Cater!
Amazing!
Bravo!
Wow!
Cater cater cater cater...
Pillar pillar pillar pillar pillar...
Pillar pillar pillar pillar pillar pillar...
Ken!
Oh dear...
Oh tear...
You've got it wrong, Sora!
Just what you'd expect from
the cornerstone of the team,
you steal the best part of the show...
The deal was that it was just
for today! I'm not joining your team!
Why not? You should!
So, is it okay for the Anna and
the Clowns team to participate?
Of course.
All right!
Well, then, it's just for this show, you hear?
Congratulations, Ken!
Thank you!
Now then, I'll explain the contents of the show.
The theme is...
Sora... Naegino...
I'll fall...
She might be able to
perfect the Angel's Maneuver...
And carry out the dream you couldn't.
Sophie...
Promise me, Leon.
Promise, eh?
It's true, that's the
one thing I can do for you.
But...
Flowers?
From who? May, I suppose...
Rosetta, I'm going to go out for a bit, okay?
Oh, okay. Where are you going?
To Miss Layla's.
Miss Layla's?
Yeah, because if I don't tell
her that I'm going to be onstage,
it's like I'm doing it behind
her back, and I don't like that.
See you later!
Yep!
Please wait here.
Right!
Miss Layla!
Sit.
I thought maybe you wouldn't meet with me.
Because of what happened at the Festival?
Yes.
I was wrong about you, Sora.
I thought you could dream
the same dream that I did.
So I thought you would pull through
on any stage, no matter how cruel.
But I was wrong.
I pushed you too hard, didn't I?
And because of that, now you
can't even fight May for a role.
Your goal wasn't being a true Kaleido Star.
It was just a fun stage...
Just like you say, Miss Layla, my goal
is a fun Kaleido Stage with no battles.
But I haven't given up the dream
of being a true Kaleido Star, either.
You're saying you're going to try to be a
true Kaleido Star without fighting anyone?
Yes. There's no other path for me.
Aiming for the position of Star that nobody's
ever been able to reach without fighting?
That never even occurred to me...
But Sora...
That might be a more difficult
path than you can even imagine.
No matter how long or how
difficult the path, it's the path I chose.
So I've decided not to lose my way anymore.
So I won't walk the path
you showed me, Miss Layla.
Sora...
If that's what you've decided, then
walk for yourself the path you believe in.
I will.
I'm going to be in the
Kenneth Motors show coming up.
I'm definitely going to make it a fun show!
I'm looking forward to it.
Sora's eyes... They've gotten
back the sparkle they used to have.
What is this feeling springing up inside me?
And then she smiled and told me
to walk down the path I believe in.
I see.
I'm really glad I went!
I have to walk firm down my own path.
Not making Miss Layla worry any
more than this is another reason to.
Layla can still see...
Huh? Did you say something?
No.
Really?
Anyway, since this will be a car show,
I think you should dress
like a Racing Queen and...
It's not like that.
The theme of the cars is "harmony with nature,"
so I think I need an outfit
that would blend in with nature...
Blend in with nature?
As few adornments as possible...
Few adornments?!
A bold concept--
A bold concept. you say?!
Let us meet in the dressing
room tomorrow! Farewell!
I'll try completely acting
like Sora at tomorrow's show.
That's the only path left to me.
All right everyone, listen
as you're changing, okay?
I just went and checked out the stage.
The positioning of the cars is
a little different from the plan,
but there are no big problems.
This is our first show for them and
we haven't had any rehearsals either,
so you'll probably be nervous,
but if you do it just like we
discussed, there will be no problem.
So let's be calm and relaxed!
What's that?
I wonder if it's some kind of good luck charm.
Oh no, I have to hurry up and get changed...
Say, your name is Ken, right? Help me!
Can't you see me?!
He's so useless...
What?
Hold on, please! You can't
say that with so little warning...
Are you saying you can't cope with it?
The trapeze team's act will
completely change, for one thing.
Won't you please reconsider?
We'll pay plenty of attention to safety...
I don't want to hear any more!
A member of the Kaleido
Stage was injured just recently.
Doing this without a net is out of the question.
Also, it looks bad if the net
shows onscreen when we're filming,
so I'm putting it up as high as possible.
What?!
You're kidding!
I'm sorry. It was my mistake,
not thinking of this beforehand.
Anyway, we have to think of a way,
or we'll hardly be able to do
any of the trapeze act we planned.
It's a little late to be saying that now!
I'll go take a look!
I'll go too.
The trapezes are up a lot higher too...
The building is a pyramid shape,
so the high part is pretty narrow, huh?
Hmmm...
And we can't use the trampoline
either because the net's in the way.
We can't put on much of a show.
We'll be really far from the
audience if we do it there, won't we?
Huh?
Hey, that's right! May, do
you have any ropes or anything?
No! Why would I?!
I guess you wouldn't...
Sora!
I brought spare trapezes and
rope just in case something happened.
Wow, really?! You're amazing!
This is great! Thanks, Ken!
Just what you'd expect
from Mr. Useful Man, Ken!
Aw, well...
So what are we going to do with them?
I have an idea.
You help too, okay May?
Of course I'm going to!
Say, do you want to do the
trapeze with us too, Rosetta?
What? Me on the trapeze too?
Where do you get off deciding this by yourself?!
Oh, no, there's just
something I want Rosetta to do--
I'll do it! I'll do it, Sora.
Is this okay? Rosetta still hasn't
really done the trapeze, you know.
Yeah, but this isn't so difficult.
I'll do my best, so please let me, May.
All right, then.
For now I'll just try doing what Sora says.
After all, even if I fail it's Sora's fault.
Okay, we haven't got
much time before we go on.
Sora, explain the plan.
Right!
Now, can Sora make this stage her own?
Or will the team break up
and fall apart in midair?
You call this a plan,
but it's mostly ad-lib, isn't it?
It'll be okay. I think it'll
go well if I'm with you, May.
Cater. Pillar. Cater. Pillar.
Turn around, turn around,
turn around, turn around.
They're kind of into it...
Oh no!
Ow ow ow...
They're way into him?!
Here!
And now it's finally time for Sora.
I'll have Sora show me everything about her!
What's with her?
The show's just started and
she's already ad-libbing like that?
Oo oo ah ah!
Fine. Then I'll go too!
Run, run, run, run...
What the heck is that?
Her ad-lib moves are getting bigger and bigger.
I've never seen Sora like this before.
This is totally different than the
performances I've seen from Sora up until now.
Why is it...
Up until now, whenever I saw Sora performing,
I thought "I will beat her!"
I thought no matter what
happened, I'd make her lose to me.
But watching Sora's performance today, I'm
starting to feel this completely different feeling.
I want to beat Sora.
I want to beat her, but...
Something is different.
Sora's amazing!
So this is the real Sora.
Yes.
It looks like the Sora who
loves the stage has come back.
Rosetta, you're doing great!
Fooled you!
There!
Jeez, that Rosetta...
Okay May, here we go!
Fine by me.
There!
Oo oo ah ah!
What's with that move?
I can do a little thing like that too!
They're smiling...
I get it...
Sora was always seeing scenes like this.
Sora has the power to make this many smiles.
The importance of a smile...
Sis!
You're amazing!
You're so cool, sis!
How about this?!
Wow, awesome, May!
Super!
Oh, May!
Good stuff!
Amazing!
What is this feeling?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're always sleeping, so...
It's fine.
I'll change your flowers.
I've been curious all this
time about that "Sophie"...
Wondering who she is...
Sophie is dead.
She was in an accident, wasn't she?
It's none of your business.
Today's Kenneth Motors
show was pretty amazing!
Lots of light was coming
in through the windows,
and while I was jumping around on
the trapezes, it was like I was dreaming.
It was like my heart got really wide,
like everybody else's feelings could
fly anywhere in the world with me...
I understood clearly that it was
the kind of show I wanted to do.
Oh, and May was also...
Sekasu you ni muragaru Hard luck
Nagasarete Time is over
Yokoku doori Take it easy
Tsuredasu yo imasugu
Hurry up (here we go)
Gouin only (saisoku drive)
Nichijou miorosu best view
Sunset point (favorite)
Harbor light (stormy night)
Asu no tame ni escape
Bakansu nashi demo oashisu wa get
Keitai off tte ai o charge shite
Yasashisa dake ja iyasenai itami mo aru kara
We are alone. Surechigau
What's going on?
Koukai no hate ni deau true heart
Naite mo waratte mo I’ll be with U
Next Kaleido Star: New Wings
Only a demon can raise an angel.
And so, thanks to Rosetta,
we're going to tour France!
There we'll meet a mysterious person,
and hear from him the true
nature of the Angel's Maneuver...
And that person's name...
Oh, argh! Who is this "Sophie"? Who? Who?!
Next time on Kaleido Star,
"Leon's Amazing Past."
My wings are my dream
and on towards the sky...