Who's our next target?
Frank Claude.
We've finally tracked him down.
Are you planning on using those strange folks again?
I thought we had already agreed to dispatch them.
They're going to make it flashy, aren't they?
It's a necessary measure to raise awareness of our existence.
Their powers are hellfire that will burn down Hell itself,
and we will build our world there.
Are you hurt?
It's just a scratch.
I will...
...kill.
In order to survive...
...I will kill.
I'm going to be killed.
I'm going to be killed unless I escape.
I can't run from those black eyes.
What should I do?
If I can't escape, I'll have to kill.
If I don't kill, I'll be killed.
Where am I?
What is this?
What was I-
Who am I?
I can't remember my name.
What was I...?
Japanese?
A travel bag.
That's... me?
I'm a Japanese tourist, and...
Why?
Why can't I remember?
The ones who attacked me might be nearby.
Stop doing things by yourself, Clau.
What's the point of having me as your bodyguard?
Do you want a ride in my car?
Whoa.
I'll be fine.
I'm just going to check on things.
I can't let him handle everything by himself.
That snaky bastard.
He's probably having a blast with some extraordinary toy right now.
Jeez... He makes me want to puke.
But he's contributed a lot to the organization.
He's a favorite of McGuire and the others, after all.
Even though he's just a puppet.
It's Inferno's policy to make use of anyone who gets the job done, whoever that may be.
I know.
But seriously, Clau, you're skating on thin ice.
Call me if anything happens.
In that case, I'm counting on you, Lizzie.
If only you wouldn't drive like that...
Situation Assessment Ability: 074.
Awakening Value: 087.
I can't believe he's reached these values just minutes after waking up.
I told you.
He's an outstanding talent.
I'm probably going to Hell.
No, I might already be there.
That detecting ability just now was...
It's animal instinct.
You could see it as the id that was hidden inside the ego.
TLnote: Scythe Master is referring to Sigmund Freud's concept of id, ego and super-ego.
See Wikipedia for details.
But he's not quite there yet.
He hasn't reached the values that I'd hoped he would.
It's time for you to hit the stage, Phantom.
But don't overdo it.
Yes, Master.
If you don't want to die...
Those eyes...!
...you better come at me with everything you've got.
When one's heart,
life,
and very existence are in crisis,
the only thing that can fend off the hostility is one's instinct to survive.
Only weak individuals who have given up on life...
...believe that their safety is secured...
...by counting on morals or kindness.
I've come to loathe this world,
where such thoughts have become an everyday thing.
Well, if it isn't Ms. McCunnen.
If I had known you were visiting,
I would have prepared something.
What's our status?
The results should be out soon.
Would you like to observe?
Yes.
Please, come in.
Who is she?
Why is she after me?
I don't know what's going on.
I don't even know where I am.
Or who I am, for that matter.
I can't escape.
There's nowhere to go.
If I can't escape...
...then both you and I...
...must kill, or be killed!
It's starting.
Starting?
Please watch carefully.
Why?!
Come at me with everything you've got.
If you don't want to die.
I have nothing.
No past.
No future.
Not even a life.
Even so,
I don't want to die!
Where should I go?
I don't even know where I'm from.
I don't even have any memories.
What do I have to do to be free?
What kind of freedom requires you to kill people in order to earn it?
Tell me...
Please.
Where is this?
Who...
Who am I?!
Zwei.
You are...
I'm Ein.
You're Zwei.
Zwei?
That's your name.
Starting today, your name is Zwei.
Z..wei?
What... is that?
What kind of a-
You are me,
and I am you.
What do you think?
Isn't he a wonderful talent?
The results he gave us were unbelievable.
This boy had no training, and no formal understanding of tactics.
He took these actions out of instinct.
Furthermore,
he was able to overpower Ein for just a moment.
How unsightly, Phantom.
I'm terribly sorry.
He's a genius.
Not only that, but he also possesses abilities that appear when put under the pressure of a life-or-death situation.
It's almost as if he was born to join Inferno.
Even so, do you think he wants to?
No egg will refuse to hatch,
nor will any seed refuse to sprout.
His will is not the problem here.
And your specialty of brainwashing is going to solve that problem, huh?
It's perfect.
Using hypnosis and drugs,
we were able to seal away only those
memories that concern his own identity.
I beg you, please try to understand, Ms. McCunnen.
This is an act of benevolence.
Unfortunately, he happened to be at the wrong place at the wrong time.
If it hadn't been for us, he would have been killed as a witness.
But I wanted to give him another chance to live a fruitful life.
Traveling alone and Japanese, huh?
This could be trouble.
No one can trace his location anymore.
It's a complete secret now.
All right, Scythe Master.
I'll leave this boy to you.
Thank you.
But "Ein" and "Zwei"?
Couldn't you at least come up with better names for your students?
We'll see how long you can keep
ordering me around like that, Lady.
I'm the first woman, Ein.
You're the second man, Zwei.
We are...
What are you doing?
You've done your part, Ein.
Return to your post.
Yes, Master.
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
Welcome back, Master!
Thanks.
Where are the others?
They're all resting, sir.
In the middle of the day?
What's going on?
You're...!
Phantom.
Inferno's best assassin.
A title given to the top sniper in the organization.
My masterpiece.
And him, as well...
You take things too far.
I see.
I guess that's the end for his organization.
With this, two of the five organizations in LA have been eliminated.
Everyone,
it all starts here.
We will create a new era.
The era of Inferno.
Ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
Phantoms with no identity.
Only by killing...
...will you be allowed to exist.