[EXPLOSIONS]
[TROOPS HOLLERING]
[GUNFIRE]
[ROY] The power of one
man doesn't amount to much.
[MACHINE GUN FIRING]
[BATTLE MAYHEM]
[SOLDIERS IN PAIN FROM
BEING HIT BY GUNFIRE]
[EXPLOSION]
[ROY] But however little
strength I'm capable of...
I'll do everything
humanly possible
to protect the people I love.
[ROY] And in turn they'll
protect the ones they love.
It seems like the least we tiny
humans can do for each other.
Sounds like a
pyramid scheme.
[HUGHES]
There's just one thing.
If you hope to eventually
protect everyone...
then you'll have to
figure out a way to
stand at the top
of the pyramid.
[ROY] I can only
imagine how good it must
feel up there, Hughes...
Although...
I'll never be able
to find out without
all the support I can get.
[ROY] There's
no doubt about that.
[HUGHES] You're not
very subtle, y'know.
You've got my support...
But you could've
just asked me...
It ought to be
fun to watch though...
And maybe your naiïve idealism
might actually do some good.
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel... Colonel?
There is an open bunk
in the barracks
if you need a nap.
I'm fine...
I still need to organize
and pack up all of my
paperwork before we
transfer to Central...
I haven't had much
time for sleep.
It looked like you
were in the middle
of a pretty vivid
dream there.
Not really...
It was just an old memory.
Well, the last
thing I remember
was this guy kicking me.
[ARMSTRONG] It's odd
that he let you live...
And what about this
sacrifice and these
other armored souls?
[HUGHES] Not to mention
the Uroboros tattoos
and the transmutation circle...
And Dr. Marcoh claims
they were using the
Philosopher's stones in Ishval?
Every clue we have to
work with seems to
lead to its
own mystery.
Not much we can do
about that, though...
Any answers we might've
found are under a ton
of rubble back
at the lab...
Hmm...
Hmmm.
They are talking
about some seriously
crazy stuff in there.
You've heard the
old cliché about how
curiosity killed
the cat, right?
Well it's true.
[BRADLEY]
Pardon me, Lieutenant.
[BRADLEY] I'm looking for Edward
Elric. The Fullmetal Alchemist?
Sure...
This is his--
[SHOCKED AND SPEECHLESS]
[HUGHES] I'll run a search
and see if I can find some
priors on anyone
with an Uroboros tattoo.
Very good...
And while you do that...
I'll continue looking into
the research team that was
working with
Dr. Marcoh in Ishval.
[KNOCK AT THE DOOR]
[BRADLEY]
Sorry to interrupt...
[ARMSTRONG]
Fuhrer Bradley!
Your Excellency!
Calm down, gentlemen...
this is just an informal visit.
[HUGHES]
Yes, sir...
But may I please
ask the occasion, sir?
This young man...
Heard you're injured...
I thought a nice melon
might cheer you up.
I guess...?
Ah, thank you, sir!
I understand you've
been checking up
on some of the senior staff.
Is this true
Major Armstrong?
Uh... yes... sir...
but, uh... how did
you know I was--
You should know that
nothing gets past me, Major.
And now you... my revered
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Tell me what you know
about the Philosopher's Stone.
And I hope for your sake...
that you don't know too much.
[BRADLEY LAUGHS]
I'm only kidding!
There's no reason
for you to be so uptight.
Huh?
I know that there's
been some suspicious
activity within the
military lately, And...
I believe it's necessary for
something to be done about it.
[BRADLEY] Oh...
That's just--
A list of the research team
assigned to study the
Philosopher's Stone.
Every person listed in
this document has been
reported missing.
[BRADLEY] They all
vanished several days
before the Fifth
Laboratory collapsed...
It seems the enemy is always
one step ahead of us...
Even with my vast
network of informants,
I have no way to determine
how far our ranks
have been infiltrated.
The most we know about them,
is that they know
a lot about us.
In that case...
this is proving much more
dangerous than we imagined.
Major Armstrong...
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes...
[BRADLEY]
Elric Brothers...
You've all proven yourselves
to be men of a
trustworthy character.
From this point forward I'm
giving you the direct order...
to forget this matter
and all that it concerns.
[BRADLEY]
At this time,
suspicion is our
strongest line of offense,
and our only form
of defense is discretion.
Do not trust anyone...
Keep this to yourselves
at all costs...
However...
When I deem the time is right
to confront the enemy,
I expect you to be prepared
to join me in the effort.
Sir!
[BODYGUARD]
Where is he...?!
Has Fuhrer Bradley
been through here?
Gotta go... Damn bodyguard
thinks he's my shadow.
[BRADLEY] Y'see I snuck away to
get a few minutes of privacy...
Well, farewell for now!
[GROUP STILL IN SHOCK]
Hey, Ed...! What the...?
[WINRY] What's going on?
Did I miss something?
Not really... just a
tornado passing by...
Well I don't think there's
anything I can
do about that...
but I did buy the
train tickets you asked for.
Thanks...
just in time.
You sure are a man
on the move, aren't you...?
Your wounds haven't
even healed completely.
Yeah, well two days of
sick people and hospital food
is enough for me, thanks.
And where are you
heading off to this time...?
What's in Dublith?
Well... with the way
things have gone lately...
Al and I decided we
should go back and
visit our old teacher.
[AL SHAKING]
[AL] I think I'm too
scared, Brother...
There's no way that
she's not gonna kill us!
Look-- don't you
chicken out on me now!
I'm scared too, okay?
[WINRY] What exactly
does this person teach?
It appears you have a rather
lengthy journey ahead of you.
How far is Dublith?
[AL]
Wellll, let's see...
There it is...
All the way down here.
[WINRY]
Hmm.
[WINRY CRIES OUT]
Wha... What is it?
[WINRY] That...!
Right there...
Right before Dublith!
It's the holy land of
Automail engineering...
It's Rush Valley!
We have to go,
we have to go,
you have to take me!
Yeah, whatever.
I don't have to
take you anywhere.
Well somebody has
to pay for my travel fare!
And why does
that have to be me?!
[AL] C'mon, brother...
What's the big deal?
[AL]
It's on our way.
Only if you want to, Al.
Yayyyy!
[WINRY GIGGLES]
I've gotta call
and tell Grandma!
She'll make a you
fine wife, someday.
Don't start
that again!
[HUGHES LAUGHS]
I would rather talk
about my wife anyway.
It's time for bye-bye...!
Daddy's gotta go to work now!
Daddy...! Come home
early today, okay?
Hmm, well I can try...
but Daddy has a bunch
of important work
that needs to be done.
But I promise I'll
do it as fast as possible!
[ELICIA LAUGHS]
- Alright, don't be late now.
- [ELICIA]
That tickles, Daddy!
[HUGHES]
Well Miss Rockbell,
I probably won't see you
again before your train leaves,
but it's been fun...
Oh, and tell the
boys I said goodbye.
Thanks, Mister Hughes...
I really appreciate
your hospitality.
You just make sure to
come visit us anytime
you're in Central, okay...?
Our home is your home too...
'Til then...
Take care of yourself.
Bye, hon...
Right!
[ELICIA]
Work hard, Daddy!
Bye bye!
[GRACIA] You be
safe out there.
[TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS]
[WINRY] So why is it suddenly
so important that you
guys see your teacher?
[ED] There are
a couple of reasons.
[ED] For starters, I'm a little
tired of getting my ass kicked.
[WINRY] Wait... Is this some
kind of combat teacher...?
Why don't you
just quit fighting?
Oh that'd be nice...
But sorry, it's not as
simple as that, okay...?
This isn't only
about our fighting...
Our core needs a little
work too... Right, Al?
[AL] Exactly... We feel like
seeing our teacher will
help us grow, and make us
stronger on the inside.
Yeah, and we're gonna
need as much strength
as we can get.
What's reason two?
To see what she can
tell us about the
Philosopher's Stone.
[AL] And to ask her about
the truth within the truth...
We haven't gotten any
closer to figuring it out...
There's a chance our teacher
knows something about it.
Let's hope she at least gives
us the chance to ask her...
You should be more
worried about explaining
your appearance to her, Al...
Considering...
She's gonna kill us
when she finds out
what happened...
[AL] It would
have been nice
to at least have had a
girlfriend before I die.
[WINRY] Maybe you guys
should get a new teacher.
[HUGHES]
Riots in Liore?
Yes... It's apparently in
response to that sham religion
that was preying on
the townspeople...
They finally realized
they were being suckered.
Yeah...
[HUGHES]
Ishval and Liore...
The east has been
a real hotbed, huh?
I'm afraid it's
not just the east...
There have been reports
of uprisings in the
north and west as well.
[HUGHES] The bodies
are piling up all over.
The government's
gonna have a hard time
keeping control
at this rate...
Colonel Hughes?
Is something wrong?
[HUGHES] I'll be
in the archive room.
[HUGHES] Liore...
these endless uprisings...
the Philosopher's Stone...
Human sacrifices...
And the outright genocide
of the Ishvalan people...
Then this means...
How could this even happen,
and who could've orchestrated
something as
terrible as this...?
I've gotta tell the
Fuhrer right away.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LUST] Hello,
Lieutenant Colonel...
It's nice to meet you...
Well, actually...
'Hello' really isn't
the word I'm looking for.
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
Cool tattoo
you've got there...
Those are
your last words...?
Wouldn't you
rather scream?
[HUGHES]
Dammit.
'Dammit'...?
That's exactly how I feel.
Oh, my, you're
back again already...?
Who gets to hear about
your daughter this time--
Lieutenant Colonel!
You're bleeding!
It's nothing...
I need a private line.
[HUGHES]
I have to tell him...
Sorry... forget I was here.
But... sir!
[OPERATOR] Good evening,
Eastern Command.
[HUGHES] I need
you to connect me
to Colonel Mustang, right away.
[OPERATOR] I'm sorry,
I'm not allowed to
connect from an outside line.
You're speaking to
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes...!
And this is a matter
of life and death!
[OPERATOR]
Can I have your code, please?
What?! Are you trying
to waste time...?
It's Uncle...
Sugar... Oliver...
then Eight... Zero... Zero.
[OPERATOR]
Your code was verified...
Please hold while I connect you.
[HUGHES] Will you hurry...?!
It's an emergency!
[GUN COCKING]
I need to ask you to
put down the receiver...
[ROSS]
Please, sir.
Go on... Just hang it up.
You look just like--...
But you're not...
who the hell are you, lady?
I'm Second
Lieutenant Ross, sir...
You've lost too much blood.
[HUGHES]
Drop the act already.
You're not
Second Lieutenant Ross.
She has a mole
under her left eye!
You're observant...
I can't believe I forgot...
There. How do I look now?
This is not happening...
Please tell me I'm
hallucinating or something.
[ENVY] You really are a
smart man, Lieutenant Colonel.
Did you ever think that'd
be the cause of your death?
[HUGHES] C'mon,
have a heart, will ya...?
I've got a wife and
daughter waiting for me...
So the last thing I'm
gonna do... is die on them!
You look surprised!
What the hell are you?!
[GUNSHOT]
[PHONE RINGS]
[OPERATOR] There's a
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes
on hold for you.
He claims it's urgent.
Of course he does...
Put him through...
Look, Hughes...
I don't have time
for daughter stories.
Hey, Hughes?
[ROY] Hughes...?
You okay...? Hughes?!
[HUGHES STRUGGLING]
You humans don't
make any sense to me.
[ENVY] You throw away
your lives for nothing.
[HUGHES] Gracia...
I'm so sorry... Elicia...
Remember, Daddy loves you...
I'm sorry.
[TRAIN RUMBLING ON TRACKS
AND WHISTLE BLOWS]
[ED]
Oh, man!
This is hands down
the best apple pie ever.
Isn't it though?
Mrs. Hughes is a
really excellent cook!
To put it mildly.
[ED] Not to mention that
quiche she made for us
is also pretty delicious.
[AL] Yeah... I actually wrote
the quiche down on the
list of things I'm gonna
eat when I have a mouth again.
[WINRY] Well, she
gave me the recipe...
So when you're back to normal,
Al, I'll make it for you.
[AL] Awesome...! Thanks!
[AL LAUGHS]
I had such a good time
staying with them...
They're both
really great people.
Yeah, but Hughes is obnoxious...
He doesn't know when
to shut up and he
spoils his daughter rotten.
[AL] He did come by
your hospital room
a lot to talk to you.
Every damn day.
He always made a point
to come and keep me company...
and it didn't matter when...
He'd even blow off work.
[AL] We should figure
out some way
to thank him
next time we're there.
[ED]
Yeah. We should.
[GUN SALUTE]
Mommy?
Why are they putting
all that dirt on Daddy?
They're burying him, dear.
But if Daddy gets buried,
then he won't be
able to do all his work.
Elicia.
[GRACIA SOBBING]
Daddy said he has a bunch
of work he needs to do...!
No, stop it...!
Stop putting
dirt on him...! Daddy!
[ROY] Promoted
to Brigadier General...
Just for dying
in the line of duty.
You were supposed to be
helping me work my way
up through the ranks...
You got it all backwards.
You damn, crazy fool...
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel?
Alchemists as a whole...
we really are horrible
creatures... aren't we?
[ROY] There's a side of me
that's desperately trying
to crack the theories of
human transmutation right now...
[ROY] I think I understand
what drove those boys
when they tried to...
bring back their mother.
Are you alright, Colonel?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Except...
It's a terrible day for rain.
What do you mean...?
It's not raining.
Yes... It is.
[HAWKEYE]
Oh, so it is...
Why don't we head back...?
It's getting chilly out here.
He said he'd be in
the archive room,
and then he just left.
But he had this look...
Like he realized
something terrible.
[ROY] So he must've
been attacked in here.
[FOCKER]
Looks like it.
He left a trail of blood...
It runs all the way
down the hall.
Apparently, he was heading
straight to the phone room.
[RECEPTIONIST]
He was hurt...
And he said that he
needed to call someone.
But then...
He just walked
out instead...
He didn't even
dial a number.
[ROY THINKS] He obviously picked
up on something big...
He was gonna
call from the office...
but something occurred to
him and he
used an outside line.
[ROY THINKS] The code that
he gave the operator is only
supposed to be used
for military emergencies.
[ROY THINKS]
So what was it...?
What the hell was
he trying to tell me?
[HAWKEYE]
Colonel.
I found Major Armstrong,
as you asked me to.
[ARMSTRONG] We have a strong
lead on some potential suspects
in the murder of
Lieutenant Colonel Hughes.
[ROY] Then why aren't you
hunting them down right now?
We're confident that we
know who committed the crime,
but we're unsure
of their identities.
That doesn't make sense,
Major. Clarify for me.
I'm afraid I cannot.
I'm telling you to
explain as your
commanding officer...
You're disobeying
a direct order, Major.
I cannot tell you.
Fair enough...
I apologize
for my tone...
You're dismissed.
Sir.
[ARMSTRONG] Actually,
sir, there is another
matter I've
neglected to mention.
The Elric brothers
were recently here.
They only departed
a couple of days ago.
They were here in Central?
[ARMSTRONG] Yes sir...
For a number of days.
And did they manage
to find whatever
they were looking for?
No sir... That would be rather
difficult as they
are pursuing a legend.
Is that so...?
Well thanks for your help.
So, I guess he wasn't
as helpful to us as
we had hoped.
But not a waste
of our time...
He was more helpful
than he meant to be.
He said that they
had a strong lead,
singular tense,
on a few suspects...
Multiple suspects...
Which leads me to believe
they suspect
a group is responsible.
And his obstinate
refusal to talk,
even though I ordered
him to... can only mean...
There's gotta be an officer
above me that's ordered
him to keep quiet...
Most likely someone
of senior ranking.
The last clue...
was that he happened to
mention the Elric brothers...
They were researching...
the Philosopher's Stone.
[HAWKEYE]
I hate to say it,
but it sounds like
there might be some
kind of conspiracy
going on here...
But how does
it all tie together?
[ROY] That's
the big question.
But Hughes... I'd say he
deserves an answer...
Once I'm transferred
to Central...
I'm gonna start shaking
things up until I find one.
Doesn't sound
like you to
mix your public and
personal concerns.
There's no difference
between the two...
I will become the
Fuhrer of this country...
And I will take
vengeance for Hughes...
I'll do these things because
I have to do them.
I'm going after
the senior staff...
Are you with me, Lieutenant?
Do you even have to ask?
[NARRATOR] A young girl by
the name of Paninya warmly
greets the Elrics to Rush Valley
by stealing Ed's watch.
A mad dash ensues
with Ed in pursuit,
laying alchemical waste
to the town between,
but the mysteriously agile
girl remains one step ahead.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood.
Episode Eleven.
Miracle at Rush Valley.
Were the words the boy
engraved a sign of his resolve?
Or something else?