When watching Hayate no Gotoku, make sure to watch at a good distance away from the TV in a well lit room.
Splash!
Tada!
Voila!
What are you doing?!
Hey, why are you interrupting me?
People are going to wonder what show just started.
As you can see, it's a new opening.
A new opening?
Yes. To commemorate the 44th episode, my manga is going to get animated.
Didn't we do something similar to this in the past?
Furthermore, KOTOKO-san will be singing it starting next week.
No, she won't!
Here's the real opening theme.
Did you all know that there's a huge mansion like this in the middle of Tokyo?
The name of the mistress who lives there is Sanzenin Nagi.
And...
Her butler's name is Ayasaki Hayate.
The two are slightly airheaded...
...and they misunderstand each other a bit...
...but they are bound by a tight master-butler bond.
This week's Hayate no Gotoku is fictional
and does not depict any actual person or organization.
It's always like that.
What do you think of this complete version of Magical Destroy?
People often say it's hard to understand, so I made it simpler.
Um...
Yeah? Yeah?
I don't see much of a difference from before.
What? I went and edited it to target the general public audience, and yet you still don't understand?!
Even if you say that...
Don't you see the extremeness of the upcoming battle expressed in the waves from the Sea of Japan?
Hahahaha! I've finally found you, Britney!
What! Could that voice be... Who's there!
I've come all the way to the Sea of Japan to defeat you...
Your enemy!
Damn! An enemy! Then I have no choice but to fight!
That's right! You have no choice but to fight!
But since you declare yourself to be an enemy...
You must be strong!
No, I'm sorry. I'm not that strong!
Since I'm only an enemy early in the series.
Wh-What's the matter, Maria?
Is this one of those games where
you lose when you point out the faults?
What do you mean?
The enemy appears so soon as the third page.
It's such an exciting development.
But he's claiming he's not strong...
Besides, what journey is she on?
It's interesting, Nagi.
What?!
Actually, when did you come in, Isumi-san?
Yes! As expected from Isumi.
It was very interesting, so I wrote a follow up.
SFX: Sparkle
What did she say?!
Life of a Kitty.
A kitty with wings was flying in the sky.
After much analysis from multiple angles,
the speed of flight was 23km/h.
It's marvelous, Isumi!
That's the flavor I was looking for!
I knew it.
Looks like they're at it again.
Sakuya-san, when did you get here?
Aren't those two something?
Yes. Their conversations are in a different dimension from us.
They actually understand each other with that, so it's amazing.
But, is it really that difficult to draw a manga?
If you can draw well and come up with
fairly well-planned plots, it's not hard to get a prize.
Don't let such a controversial statement slip!
If I remember correctly, you received a prize in a manga competition, right, Hayate-kun?
Hey, that's amazing!
I never read Hayate's manga, either.
I'd like to read it, too.
Sure, I don't mind.
My name is Britney.
As you can see, I work part-time as a flower girl.
Usually, I make so many mistakes,
seduced by the fragrance of the flowers,
SFX: Ghoooo
so the store manager always yells at me.
But, there are bad guys that come to
the flower shop, lured in by the fragrance.
No worries, though!
My magic will repel them right away!
That's right! I'm a Magical Girl!
Flower Magical Girl, Britney-chan!
It nails down all the key features,
so it's pissing me off, strangely enough.
It's even colored.
The pictures are very cute, yet why do I sense naughtiness?
Looks like I'm not getting good reactions.
What do you think, Isumi?
It feels like he's trying to hit
the audience's sweet spot right off the bat.
I agree.
If you make a work as if you're sucking up to
the audience while making fools out of them,
you may be able to trick the judge's eyes,
but you'll never catch a true audience's heart!
I-I'm sorry.
Rather than that, what's going to happen in Nagi's manga after this?
I'm still working on the storyboard beyond that.
Let's just hear the overall flow, then.
That would be nice.
What, this? You're all interested in what happens next?
Not necessarily.
Okay, you leave me no choice. Let me tell you.
Thank you.
Fugitive General and Dark Fugitive,
whom he brought with him from the twelfth dimension,
change all of humanity to worker ants and plan to take over the world.
In order to do that, they start to stock up on sugar in the futures market.
The worldwide lack of sugar caused by this makes Britney decide to go on an eight dimension-wide journey.
Because she loves cake and stuff.
She's a girl, after all.
But at the same time, Helmintians from the M-2983 galaxy come to Earth for its oil resources and awaken the ancie-
Stop, Nagi!
Why are you stopping me?!
It was just getting to the good part!
How so?
Milady, you have to make it clearer,
or else people won't understand you.
Yeah. It doesn't make sense.
How dare you? I'm explaining it for your sakes.
Yes, but...
I know!
Let's see... I thought it was somewhere around here.
Where are we going, Milady?
Found it!
What? Ramen?
Welcom-
T-To the table in the back, please.
Let me use this facility to tell you how great my manga is.
How do we do "use the facility" at a ramen shop?
Looks like we've arrived.
What is this place?!
Could this place be the rumored...
End of drawing cut 82.
I'm here to get the finished product.
Here.
Good work.
Kaboom! Smack!
Here's the finished product.
Okay.
"Kyahoo."
"But Daddy's not here."
Here.
Good work.
Finished cut check.
Thank you.
What is this place?
It looks related to animation.
Yes. It's where animations are made.
Eh?!
I knew it.
So the urban legend of anime studios usually being camouflaged as ramen shops and hiding from commoners was true.
There's an urban legend such as that?
How mysterious!
Let me remind you that this work is fictional and does not depict the actual industry.
So this is where anime is made.
I can feel the tension like one.
I remember coming here around episode 35.
That's Segawa-san, Hanabishi-san, and Asakaze-san.
Why are they here?
Excuse me, where do I find the voice actors?
They're at the audio studio.
What? They're not here?
I was hoping to see Yahagi-san here.
Note: Yahagi Sayuri is Izumi's voice actress
Wow, it's really moving!
Well then, let me draw something, too.
What's the matter, Maria-san?
Over there...
Poke. Poke.
She's only sleeping.
I'll get it done by today, somehow...
She's not asleep. She collapsed.
A break for a worrier.
So Milady, what do you intend to do here?
I'm going to have them animate the rest of my manga.
Nagi's manga?!
Animate it?!
Yes. I figured it'd be easier to explain through an anime rather than words.
Doesn't animation usually come after the manga proves its popularity?
So excited. Can't wait.
Continues in the second half!
Terere terere tte.
Terere tte nanika no jyumon nano?
Terere tte nanika no jyumon nano? = Is "Terere" some chant for a spell?
This scene. It should be like **** eating away the planet.
Naturally, don't use any CG. All by hand.
And like the L***ta's climax, make it dramatic.
And then like the opening of
P*****yo the Movie, make it crash down.
Ah, the first one, mind you.
The last will be just like the finale from Sen*****.
Will this kind of explanation really make sense to them?
I'm not sure.
That's all. Get it done in one week please.
It's impossible.
Out of question.
You're underestimating the animation process, aren't you?
Hello?
Yes! Right away!
Guys.
Whisper whisper whisper.
R-Right away!
We'll get on it right now.
Oh yeah? Thank you.
Go!
Nagi, what did you do?
I don't know. I didn't do anything.
Actually, I remember a rumor going around saying
the stock of the company will go up if it makes my anime.
It must be that.
As we've said many times, this is fictional and does not depict the real industry.
So this is how animation with iffy quality comes to the world.
Good luck with this show.
Is the storyboard not ready yet?
It should be ready soon, but the director went to To**"*"*s to buy a limited edition figure.
Have someone go pick him up! This is a job!
We've got the setting down good,
but we don't have enough people to draw.
We have a problem! The writer got tendonitis.
What's the matter?
We're short on staff that can draw.
What? Then you can't make an anime.
Can't you go pick some out from other companies?
Like ***ani.
No, I think that's a little...
Anyway, an animation originating from Lady Nagi is in production.
Looks like we'll make it on time.
We didn't take any casualties, either.
Although a few did collapse.
Good enough.
The anime industry is rigorous, isn't it?
We have a problem!
The company that's supposed to do the animation touch up vanished!
Looks like we're boxed in.
Very well.
I have no choice but to resort to the trick!
Milady, what do you intend on doing?
What should I eat tonight?
What? What happened here?
I left the color out of the Hamster scene, so recycle all the staff you want.
Is it all right to do this?
What is this?
You're so mean, Nagi-chan!
It's called rough dubbing. It's a temporary picture used when the picture isn't ready when the dubbing process begins.
I see. Something similar to making film that the audience doesn't get to see.
Wow. So this is how anime is made.
Yes. And furthermore...
Wh-Wh-What?! What's happened now?!
When the schedule is really tight,
the rough design pictures get thrown right in.
In the worst cases, they take it right off the storyboards.
Or even just a color marker line.
There are many variations.
Bring me back!
We no longer use film, so this doesn't happen.
Rough dubbing is so interesting.
This is basically how things are during dubbing.
Hey, you shouldn't be giving those facts out.
It's not like we're resorting to them because we like to!
We do want to have it completely colored during dubbing.
If only we had more leeway in the schedule.
Oh, and the budget, too.
Let's end all the inside jokes
around here. The anime is finally complete.
I'm starting to get nervous.
Me, too, Milady.
Excited. Can't wait.
I can't wait to see it.
I plan on crying three times during this movie.
It's starting.
I wonder what kind of legendary
unbelievable anime this has become.
Excited. Can't wait.
Maria-san. We've come this far, so let's be ready for anything.
May as well be hung for a sheep as a lamb.
Note: A Japanese idiom roughly meaning
"We've come this far, no turning back now."
Hi to all 130,000,000 Girl A's out there!
At ani**te, the Hayate no Gotoku fair is going on!
Grab the merchandise with your passionate hands,
and slam it down onto the checkout counter along with the contents of your wallet!
Milady, what was that?
A tie-in. I thought about putting some commercials in there, too.
Here comes the feature show.
Britney always looks at her senpai from a distance.
What? What is this picture?
Um, Senpai!
I made lunch. Would you like to eat with me?
Ah, that sounds good. Let us.
What? I'm in the show.
Yes, what is this?
Britney loves her senpai so much.
But she can never bring herself to say that.
Because she's a magical girl!? That isn't the reason.
Because the senpai... senpai has!
He already has a wife and a child.
I-It really is a surprising development.
I can't really accept the character setting.
The more you stir-
But due to an evil witch's power-
Neru Neru Ne~
Senpai was turned into a star.
Because of that, the wife fell sick,
and the child became a punk.
When you're about to lose in
a net game, just cut the network off!
The tension is starting to build.
Britney decides to return senpai back to human form.
But even if she succeeds, senpai will return to his wife's side.
There is no chance of him getting together with Britney.
However, if she goes on a journey, she will be able to be with senpai,
even if he's star-shaped now.
What will you do, Britney?
The decision Britney made is:
Life of a Kitty.
Run. Run. Run. Run.
The speed at which it runs is Mach 5.
But no matter how fast it runs, it can't reach the sun.
Fin.
Y-You really are a genius, Isumi.
You think so, too?
How was it? Did you understand my manga a little-
What's wrong?
Come in.
Oh, Maria-san.
Hayate-kun.
You're here, as well.
Does that mean you're here for the same reason as me?
Yes. I wanted to read Milady's manga one more time.
Since she did put a lot of effort into drawing it.
Yes. We should understand it more.
Also, I'm eager to find out what happens to Britney-chan and the senpai.
I am, too, a little.
But, Hataye-kun.
Yes?
What do you think Britney-chan will choose in the end?
To be with him, or...
Unfortunately, Nagi hasn't written the rest yet.
Then I guess Milady hasn't made a decision yet as to how this love ends.
What would you pick, Maria-san?
Me?
Let's see...
If that senpai is Hayate-kun, it might not be so bad to keep you in star form forever.
There you go, being mean again.
Ah, then how about you draw the rest?
Me?
But I've never drawn a manga before.
Then more so.
I can't, Hayate-kun. I'm...
If you're a man, score all the heroines at once!
Who is this, Maria-san?
Hayate-kun.
Please hold on. "Score all the heroines at once?" Am I a rapist?
You don't like it?
In that case-
You'd better make your choice.
It's your turn to draw one now, Hayate-kun.
Eh, but...
Goodness, you're such an indecisive person.
At times, fiction can mirror reality.
Next time-
Hold on!
Man, we almost forgot to insert the service shot.
Even the level of service is way up there.
Please have this to wash out your eyes.
This isn't meant to fill the extra time.
Hayate no Gotoku is filled with fan service.
Let's make sure to watch next week, too!
Hold on! Does this count as service, too?!
Student Council Trio's
Butler Network!
Nyaha. I'm Segawa Izumi.
Hm. I'm Asakaze Risa.
Osu! I'm Hanabishi Miki.
Finally, our work of friendship and effort,
Student Council Trio's theme song is complete!
It was a long road taken.
This song is perfect for broadcasting in school.
It'll be good to play it during cleaning time.
It's perfect to listen to with your date.
Play it in your car stereo and your girlfriend will be stunned.
It's perfect for lonely people living alone, too.
It might become the motivation in life.
We'll be showing our service shots the next three weeks, too.
This week, it's me!
Next week will be me!
Adios.
Where are we going all of a sudden?
I wonder where.
It'll be a surprise of when we get there.
We call it, "Maria-san, thank you so much all the time. Gratitude to our Onee-sama, Relax Plan."
Thank you so much for working so hard for us all the time.
Stay at a hotel in the city; enjoy the spa and aesthetic salon.
Forget about work and just relax.
Next week, It's Maria-san Thank You Day in February!
Next week, prism crash into Hayate!