Yanari
Shogun's
Homeland
Owari
Now then,
last episode took place in the holy land for swordsmen —
Seiryouin Gokokuji temple in Mt. Sayabashiri, Tosa.
Shichika defeated the one who was Japan's strongest — his sister, Yasuri Nanami, whom many considered a monster.
In doing so, Shichika and Togame succeeded in obtaining their 7th sword, Akutou Bita, and are heading back to Owari.
This place is huge...
Can you really say that?
But it's different from the stunning and equally huge capital of Kyou...
This place feels kind of harsh to me.
This is Yanari Shogun's homeland, a town of warriors.
Unlike Kyou, this place naturally has a far more strict, serious, and dignified atmosphere.
When you cross this moat, it's all mansions.
Hey, Togame!
Look at that mansion over there!
Look at how heavily decorated and colorful it is compared to all the others!
The owner's sure got no sense of taste, and totally can't read the atmosphere!
What the heck is that??
The roof has a ridiculous golden whale on top of it!
I'm can't really criticize, but there really are people like this wherever you go, aren't there?
That mansion is so gaudy!
I wonder what kind of attention-seeker lives there?
That's my house.
meguriatta ka un no tsuki
巡り合ったか運の尽き
So we meet again. Guess I'm out of luck.
Katana-
gatari
Mazui
presents
harari koboreochiru
はらり零れ落ちる
The words I put together
kotoba tsuranetato de
言葉連ねたとで
spill down from my lips like withering petals.
dare mo watashi ni aru
誰も私にある
Everyone can touch
makoto fure mo dekirunjaru
真触れも出来るんじゃる
the truth that resides in me.
sakura mau ga gotoku
桜舞うがごとく
Just like the falling cherry blossom petals
konjou to wa osaraba
今生とはおさらば
it's time to bid farewell to this world.
saredo oya ni moratta
然れど親にもらった
Even so my parents gave me this life.
kono mi ga kawaii
この身がかわいい
Therefore I shall cherish my body...
inochi yori omoi
命より重い
which weights harder than life itself.
tate matoi warau
縦纏い笑う
Looking down on me and laughing.
kizu wa taenu kenka joutou
傷は絶えぬ喧嘩上等
My pain won't linger away, bring it on.
kakugoshinare
覚悟しなれ
Prepare yourself.
nuite wa modosu katana to saya tachikiru ashura
抜いては戻す刀と鞘断ち切るは阿修羅
Sheathe your sword back and watch Asura getting sliced asunder.
sono sakebe ni ochita yume no harawata wa muzan zo
その叫べに落ちた夢の腹は無残ぞ
This cauldron called "dream" you have fallen screaming is your misery.
ai wa miete tagiraseru chi wo wakeaeru nara
相は見えて滾らせる血を分け合えるなら
If your blood starts boiling when you see him
itoshii sonata todome wo
愛しい其方留めを
then my inamorato,
sashitekunnamashi
刺してくんなまし
deliver the finishing blow.
hana no sakari ga
花の盛りが
Then the flower will effloresce
hoshi ni kae
星にかえ
like a bright star.
Bitou
Kanzashi
I'm going to the castle.
Watch the house while I'm out.
Weren't you going to introduce me to everyone at the castle?
There have been some changes to the rules lately, and now it's forbidden to take swords into the castle.
Well, it's a good opportunity for you.
Get used to the place.
You'll be living here while we gather information about the swords.
In this mansion?
Yes, in this gaudy mansion.
She's not going to let that go...
See you later.
There's nothing here...
Togame...
You were prepared for this journey, weren't you...
I wonder if Togame's doing work there right now...
I guess I'll train or something.
Short time no see.
It hasn't been long enough to say
"long time no see" has it, Kyotouryuu?
Emonzaemon...
When did you get behind me?
I'm good at moving in the shadows.
I heard you defeated Yasuri Nanami.
How did you get here?
I just walked in.
Very witty.
I saw you as I was passing the gate.
You looked like you were busy training, so I didn't call out to you.
That's all.
If that's all it was, then don't sneak up behind me.
Pardon me.
If you're looking for Togame, she isn't here.
Yes, I'm aware.
And that's why I've come here.
That's why?
Did Princess-whatever send you on some task?
Princess Hitei.
Don't call her Princess-whatever again.
Sorry.
So did something happen at the castle?
Where's Togame?
Don't worry, nothing happened.
Princess Hitei just wanted to pass along some information about the Deviant Blades, so I've come here to get you.
Is that right?
What do you mean "is that right"?
Geez...
You just had to go and follow him, didn't you?
If you hadn't shown up, I would have been able to use you as an excuse to go home without meeting that unpleasant woman.
Sorry.
So it's come down to this right after we get back Owari...
All I can say is she got one up on us.
That woman...
She's beyond a thorn in my side.
She's a... rock?
An asteroid?
No, beyond that...
That suits you too well!
That bobbed hair?
Short cut?
Like a Kiku doll!
Hey, why not say "dot dot dot"?
You look ten, no twenty years younger!
Fraud?
This is fraud, right?
Are you done?
I guess.
There was something I wanted to ask you once I'd returned.
What might that be?
Were you aware that "cheerio" and "chesto" are different?
What?
That??
Oh, so you noticed?
I thought I'd gained the upper hand on you this time too.
You have some amazing tenacity.
Do you really have so many attachments left in this world?
I'm not so weak as to be defeated by those Maniwa Corps you released.
I'll come back from the dead as many times as it takes to expose your evil heart.
No way, not a chance.
My evilness isn't so weak as to be exposed by the likes of you.
No matter how many times you come back, I will defeat you.
No, I'll trample you.
I deny it.
I deny what you say.
You can't trample me any more.
In fact, I predict that I'll be the one to trample you.
Go ahead and try.
You will realize that the evil in my heart is on a totally different level from yours.
You're the one who needs to open your eyes.
Go make schemes or udon or whatever in the pits of hell.
You're annoying.
Do you even have the right to say anything with that hair of yours?
Don't you know this is quite popular?
Why don't you give it a try?
Ah, I guess you can't.
My bad.
You're still on about that?
What an obstinate woman.
Thank you for the compliment.
Enough with the greetings, let's get down to business.
Ah, yes.
Those were greetings?
Speaking of greetings, Shichika-kun...
Yeah?
This is our first time meeting, right?
Pleased to meet you.
Once again, I am Princess Hitei.
Hi there.
Shichika! Don't bow your head to this woman!
Sorry.
Oh yeah...
Where did that guy go?
That guy?
Oh, Emonzaemon?
He's in the attic.
That guy has such a depressing face, just looking at him makes me feel down.
Depressing face? He's wearing a mask isn't he?
I gave him that mask, actually.
But even a mask can't hide his level of gloominess.
I've never made Shichika do anything that dumb.
Shichika-kun's face doesn't seem to agree with you.
Nevermind that, what's this information about the swords?
And if you're trying to lure me into a trap, don't bother.
You don't have to be so wary.
And anyway, why are you helping me out in the first place?
Do you intend to take the credit?
Well, I've definitely thought of that.
Collecting swords would be impossible for Emonzaemon, after all.
So?
Are you saying you'll tell me something about the remaining five swords that we have absolutely no intel on?
I can't do that.
This is information about Shikizaki Kiki.
Do you know Lake Fuyou in Edo?
Yeah, it's a designated first class disaster area, just like Mt. Shirei in Mutsu and Mt. Odori in Ezo.
Right.
Apparently Shikizaki Kiki had a workshop at Lake Fuyou.
A workshop? There?
Right.
That uninhabitable region supposedly housed the headquarters of the legendary swordsmith.
But isn't Biyorigou there?
Biyorigou?
Haven't you heard of it?
They say Biyorigou roams Lake Fuyou, protecting something.
And suppose that what it's actually protecting is Shikizaki Kiki's workshop?
We've obtained the locations of three swords.
Shireizan in Mutsu, Tendou in Dewa, and Lake Fuyou in Edo.
I suppose.
We'll head there.
Oh?
In that case, he'll guide you.
Whatever.
By the way...
That alcove there...
What is that weirdly-shaped iron thing there?
Nothing really, just a decoration.
It doesn't suit your tastes.
Was it a present from someone?
I can throw it into Lake Fuyou for you if you want.
Thanks, but that's really not necessary.
Shichika!
Sorry!
And so we'll have Umigame go collect the sword in Shinano.
I think that's a good idea.
Alright.
Leave it to me.
Though,
we haven't got any information on which sword it is, nor the owner.
S-S-Sorry...
We only know it's in a temple somewhere in Shinano...
but not which one...
Well for now, I'll head there.
There should be no one to stand in my way.
If we find out anything more, w-we'll get in touch with you.
Thanks.
I'll be off then.
We're counting on you.
Are you tired, Togame?
Is it that obvious?
Let me carry you.
Like this then?
How then?
That guy's ahead of us so he won't see.
It should be fine.
No, no...
You can walk then?
My legs are totally numb...
Come on then.
No! Never mind!
It's fine I said!
But...
Come on.
You think so?
Don't be so stubborn.
I must say though, Emonzaemon-dono...
I can see the Princess is overworking you, as always.
Needless concern.
It's nothing much for me.
Oh yeah, you used to be a ninja, right?
I guess that's how you were able to follow us around on our journey.
Also because it was my duty.
Don't you also have to protect the Princess too?
That is also a needless concern.
Unlike you, the Princess has few enemies.
Actually, her sole enemy is right here, so I need not worry.
We're here.
Lake Fuyou lies ahead.
I have other duties, so I'll take my leave.
Oh, okay.
I guess he knew he'd be in the way.
Well, that's fine.
It's finally just the two of us together...
What?
What a followup...
Wait, I don't understand...
Togame-san?
Watch where you're stepping.
Alright.
Though is there really a lake under this?
Is someone there?
What is that? Some kind of junk?
That's Biyorigou.
Hey, it's got a sword.
Yeah, but we should be fine at this distance.
So what do we do?
Let's observe for now.
Listen Shichika, we're not looking to settle this right now.
Got it.
Though having said that, I know fighters get riled up.
I said I get it!
If we can find Shikizaki's workshop, it'll help us a lot for the remaining swords.
Which means we'll need to defeat that guard.
To come up with a plan for that, I need to know more about that thing.
I see.
So, go.
Human recognized.
Togame!
It's a sword!
I thought as much.
No, I don't mean what it's holding.
This thing is—
Yeah, I know.
Biyorigou itself is Bitou Kanzashi.
One of the 12 leaders of the Maniwa Corps and the head of the fish squad, Maniwa Umigame.
Who are you?
How do you know of the supreme awesomeness, power, and wealth of Maniwa Umigame?
I don't recall introducing myself.
My name is Souda Emonzaemon.
When I heard the name "Sea turtle the long-lived" I thought you'd be an older person, but you seem quite young.
You may have realized my supreme awesomeness, ridiculous power,
awesome strength, wealth, and popularity just by looking at me,
but I'm surprised you know my other title...
Well that aside, what business do you have with me?
I have pressing business to attend to.
Don't get in my way.
Unfortunately, it is my task to get in your way.
On whose orders?
Unanswerable.
Might you possibly be Princess Hitei's...
I see.
The strategian hired us, and then we betrayed the Princess, so she's out for revenge now?
No.
If that's not it then...
Let me ask in turn.
You came to Shinano to find one of Shikizaki Kiki's Deviant Blades, correct?
Who knows.
Well it's certainly true that Entou Jyuu was located here.
You know which sword it is?
And what do you mean by "was"?
Unanswerable.
Ninjas have historically acted only in the shadows.
If you get any closer to Entou, you will learn historical truth.
That's too big a burden for an underdog such as yourself.
What do you mean? I don't get what you're saying.
You don't need to, because you are going to die here.
W-Wait a second!
Quite frankly, while the others are all gung-ho for this sword hunt, I'm not really the same!
Shinano is a nice place, and I heard the soba is good,
so I'm only 30% here for the sword, and 70% for my own enjoyment!
So come on...
Let me introduce myself again.
I am one of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads, Maniwa Umigame,
also known as Sea turtle the long-lived.
So you know how to wield a sword..
And a western sword, at that.
Ironic, isn't it?
You wield a Japanese sword.
"Long-lived", in other words, invulnerable.
For one such as you, living comfortably in your big city, the number of battles we've fought cannot be compared!
I will teach you why the sea turtle is the strongest creature in the sea!
I've advertized this inn,
but we still rarely get customers these days, so we don't have much in the way of entertainment here.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
They say that long ago there was a beautiful lake here,
but now...
Though, what business might you have in that junk pile?
It might have been junk in the past, but it's not to us.
Really?
I guess it's hard work running a tool shop.
Ah, that's right!
This plate was passed down by my grandfather, who in turn got it from his grandfather.
He said it's very precious, so I should take care of it, but what do you think?
Yes, I'd say it's true.
There's no mistaking that this is of Ume'emon make.
Take good care of it.
Oh really?
I guess I should put this somewhere burglars won't find it then.
No, if you did that, it'd become more of a target.
It'd be better to...
If you were to use it as a milk saucer or something, it'd be safer.
No thief would think a milk saucer could be valuable treasure.
Now that's a good idea!
It's a scheme.
I don't know when sea turtles became the masters of the sea, but...
No...
They never did.
You're a ninja.
Not anymore,
but I was originally in the Aioi Corps.
Aioi?
Can't say I've heard of it.
I see.
Then let me tell you.
The Aioi Corps were a ninja village that was destroyed 170 years ago by the Maniwa Corps.
Maniwa Kenpo!
This...
This is Aioi Kenpo,
Hairouken.
Note: Rear Trickery Fist
Why you...
Damn you!
It's hard to believe we lost to that level of power.
You said earlier that the number of battles we've fought cannot be compared.
You are exactly right.
The nature of the battles we've fought are different.
I am the sole inheritor of the skills that were used in the Sengoku period.
The Maniwa Corps of today are no match.
Well, besides Maniwa Houhou, that is.
You know about Houhou?
You needn't know.
Shinobazuhou Ikasazukorosazu
Note: No sneaking, no sparing, no killing
Pengin... Oshidori... Houhou...
The long-lived Umigame...
...has become...
...short-lived...
It's called "Kanzashi", so I thought...
Like with Zokutou Yoroi, it'd be a sword in the shape of a hairpin.
Well, one should avoid making things too similar.
You're talking about Shikizaki Kiki, right?
For a doll to be a sword...
Well, I guess it's sort of like Yoroi.
But the Deviant Blades have too much design freedom...
Well it's like this...
You're a human, yet also a sword.
Yeah.
So you can think of Biyorigou as being a sword and a doll.
Which means Biyorigou is pretty typical of the Deviant Blades.
I guess it's how you look at it.
Oh, right...
I wanted to ask, but Emonzaemon was around so I couldn't before.
Oh?
You're starting to learn what the appropriate time and place for things are.
I guess...
I wanted to ask, who is Princess Hitei?
The color of her eyes and hair are...
That woman is like me in that her origins are unknown.
Well that aside, why are you on such bad terms with her?
Why?
Well, we just don't get along.
No matter how many times I defeat her, she finds some way to crawl back.
She's persistent.
You're the same way.
Don't lump us together!
And wait, you seem quite interested in her...
No, not really...
I was just thinking that we'll be running into her again.
When that happens, I'll be fighting Emonzaemon head on.
Are you that interested in that woman?
Don't tell me you've fallen for her?!
She's your archenemy.
It's natural for me to be interested in her.
W-Well...
It's fine if that's all.
Revenge!
What are you doing?!
In the same way,
I'm interested in the Maniwani too.
Well, even though we have an alliance, we need to stay alert.
I wonder what they're up to now?
Who knows.
I'm sure they're playing the underdog somewhere.
I have returned.
As planned, I guided the strategian Togame and Kyotouryuu to the destination,
then dealt with one of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads and the leader of the fish squad, Maniwa Umigame.
You're late.
Seems the Maniwa Corps couldn't be taken lightly, as you said.
I deny what I said a month ago.
Though I must say, you seem rather calm.
Weren't you able to avenge your ancestors?
I see no reason to avenge a 170 year old grudge.
I don't intend to put my personal feelings before my duties to you.
It's annoying how you're always so boring like that.
So, how's that unpleasant woman doing?
She has most likely encountered Biyorigou already.
I wonder if she's realized that Biyorigou is actually Bitou Kanzashi yet?
As Kyotouryuu is able to sense the swords, they must have already.
I wonder.
Though, Shichika...
Your sixth sense isn't necessarily advantageous.
I guess we can't rely on it too much.
Princess Hitei probably doesn't know that Biyorigou itself is a Perfected Deviant Blade, right?
No, I'm sure she's aware.
Why didn't she just tell us from the start then?
Maybe she thought it'd be interesting if I didn't realize it and got torn apart, or something like that.
But despite the tricks she plays on you, she's still helping you out on the sword hunt, right?
Or so it seems.
She may be planning to steal all the credit from me at the end, or waiting for me to fail.
That said, the same goes for me.
Scary!
It didn't seem like he noticed this one, after all.
It's not a very reliable sixth sense is it?
Wouldn't it be fun if Shichika-kun didn't notice and got destroyed by Biyorigou?
If he got killed by a sword while on a sword hunt, the whole venture would be ruined.
I wonder if that unpleasant woman would be executed or slice her own stomach?
Your traps are certainly spiteful.
Whatever.
I'm bored, so let me play around a bit.
Well, let's focus on what's at hand first.
Biyorigou before anything else?
Hey don't suddenly move like that.
Oh, okay.
Come on...
How's that? What now?
Hey, stop! Come on!
I'm over here!
Are you an idiot?
Geez...
Ah, it's coming.
Wait, Shichika.
Don't do anything yet.
This is already the third day...
We have to finish this first.
We need to find Shikizaki's workshop before we defeat Biyorigou?
You seem dissatisfied.
I guess I feel like it should be the other way around.
Don't you know the saying "measure twice, cut once"?
I guess you wouldn't...
We'll clear out that area today.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you serious?
U-Um... Yes...
Your information is always correct,
but I've never hoped more for your information to be wrong than today.
I'm sorry...
Who on earth killed Umigame-san?
The only person I can think of with the motive and capability of doing that has to be Owari's Princess Hitei.
Alright, done.
This is a map of Lake Fuyou.
So it looks like this from above?
Well, there are probably a few mistakes.
I'm pretty good at this though.
If I weren't, there's no way we could have come this far on our sword hunt.
Come to think of it, I've never gotten lost traveling with you.
I'm confident in my three dimensional spacial recognition skills.
It's quite something.
What's this curvy line going through the lake?
Think about it yourself.
Stop teasing and tell me!
Fine, okay! Alright!
It's Biyorigou's path, of course!
I thought it walks on a totally random path.
Sometimes it just stops and sunbathes for a while too...
Judging from the path Biyorigou takes, Shikizaki's workshop is probably around here.
Digging it out is a problem for later.
Dig? Who?
You, who else?
Got a problem with that?
No, none...
Now, it's finally time to defeat Biyorigou,
and you need to do it without damaging it.
For that, I have a scheme.
Oh, here comes Togame's scheme!
Do I have a part in it?
Yeah.
First, hug me.
A trap, huh...
That's just like you to think of!
Really? This was easy to come up with.
Alright!
Biyorigou should be easy to deal with now!
Here it comes!
Alright!
Again?
Look, it's sunbathing again.
It's not even paying attention to us...
As far as I can tell, that thing has four arms and four legs.
I'm not an idiot, but...
Well, I guess I am, but...
Kyotouryuu is a school for fighting against people, you know.
I'd never imagined using it against a doll.
And in the first place, martial arts is about being able to read your opponent.
When my opponent strikes low, I block, then attack his vulnerable high spot.
If he looks like he'll throw something, I dodge.
Well, I guess it's kind of the same as when I lost to Konayuki because she had absolutely no tactics.
Surprise attacks won't work on that doll, and—
Yeah, Shichika.
I understand your worries.
I'm not really worried, but...
Then basically you're saying we need one of my schemes?
That scheme totally failed today...
It's fine.
Let me impart some wisdom on you, since you're so dumb.
Like I said, your scheme totally fail—
Um...
Sorry.
T-Togame-san?
That's enough playing.
Playing?
It's sad that you've come to worry that my schemes might actually fail against someone.
Well, I mean...
Whether human or doll, no matter what the situation, I will defeat them with schemes alone.
Through trouble or hardship, that's how my daily life passes.
Listen, don't worry about that kind of thing again.
Since we have the time, I'll educate you.
I'm not letting you sleep tonight.
The showdown will be tomorrow.
Kyotouryuu: Rose!
Kyotouryuu: Lily!
Human recognized.
Immediate termination.
If you think you can terminate me, then go ahead and try!
However, by that point...
Well, I guess I can't tear you into pieces, but...
Idiot. Don't get riled up.
Kyotouryuu: Orchid!
Kyotouryuu: Pomegranate into Iris, Hybrid Combo!
Shichika!
That was close!
Restrict your attacks to strikes, got it?
Got it.
Throws won't work on Biyorigou anyway.
Also, don't hit its head or chest.
Okay.
Though that's quite a plan you came up with.
Forcing Biyorigou to defend itself since we're constrained to keeping it unharmed...
Using a doll without any will of its own like that...
It's pretty annoying that feints don't work on it though.
My body sometimes moves on its own.
Even though I'm thinking it's pointless, I'll still throw in feints every now and then.
Counterattack commencement.
Doll fatality: Tornado
Doll fatality: Whirlwind
Doll fatality: Spring storm
Doll fatality: Squall
It's doing pretty much what you predicted.
Of course.
I'm not at the level of your sister, but even I can see that much.
Just looking at the way it's designed from the outside, you can tell what kind of movements it should be capable of.
I'm pretty sure I've figured out all of Biyorigou's movements now.
You're not allowed to sleep until you've memorized this.
Alright.
I daresay that it's nothing to do with giving up or seeing through it.
All I I can do is believe in you and watch.
I believe in you, Shichika!
Then I will...
Listen, Shichika.
I am a sword.
And you are also a sword.
There is no meaning to a sword that doesn't cut.
That is the first thing you must keep in mind.
All you need to be is a sharp sword.
Just like I was.
What do you mean?
You'll understand some day.
I understand what my father was saying now.
As a sword, I don't need to have emotion, or to think, or feel anything!
Doll fatality: Whirlwind scythe
Togame, Biyorigou is like how I was not long ago.
No determination or will, nothing to lose, no sense of justice,
just doing what you commanded — hunting swords.
Shichika...
That's why for the sake of the hunt I slew Koumori, Meisai, and Sabi without a second thought.
But as a sword with no will of my own, I wasn't able to defeat Nee-chan.
This doll, following the commands of Shikizaki that he gave how many hundreds of years ago, is like how I was.
I used to fight like that doll.
I guess it wasn't fun for anyone.
Human recognized.
I can't see you as anything but a sword,
but Biyorigou, you see me as a human!
Kyotouryuu: Magnolia!
Doll fatality: Tempest
Kyotouryuu: Cherry!
Doll fatality: Sandstorm
Kyotouryuu: Wild Strawberry!
Doll fatality: Typhoon
Togame.
I obey your orders because I believe in you.
Even if this body is broken,
I...
What?
Doll fatality:
Zephyr Swordstorm
Are you serious?
I can't believe you were right on...
You can tell just by looking.
Unlike humans, dolls are predictable.
Togame!!
Togame, I believe in you.
I also obey you out of my own free will.
Even if this body is broken,
I will protect you.
That's what I've decided!
What are you talking about, after all this?
Not because you ordered me to,
but because I decided from the bottom of my heart, as a human.
I may be a sword,
but at the same time, I have a human soul!
Shichika...
It's about time.
Honestly...
We had to keep it occupied for a while, but it looks like its fuel has finally run out.
It's lighter than I thought...
So when it stopped to sunbathe occasionally,
it was actually recharging itself?
That's right.
Did you know that from the start?
Well, after I figured out how it kept moving all this time,
I worked my plans around it.
The question was...
Whether Biyorigou would run out of fuel,
or whether you'd run out of energy first.
But were you sure my body would win?
Or are you saying it was fate that I would win?
That's not it.
Fate is something you decide yourself.
I told you I believe in you, right?
I guess it's how you see it.
Now then, we should remove its limbs while we have the chance.
At any point it might—
I feel kind of sorry for it.
Are you an idiot?
You don't need to empathize with a doll.
Even though it has a face, this is still one of the Perfected Deviant Blades, Bitou Kanzashi.
Well...
I guess I don't have the right to say you shouldn't hold feelings for a sword.
It's quite a pretty face.
I wonder if that was one of Shikizaki Kiki's hobbies.
"When the eastern wind blows, let out your scent.
Plum flower without a master, don't forget Spring."
After protecting that lake for how many hundreds of years after its creator died,
I suppose this doll deserves at least a word of thanks.
It put up a good fight.
Ah, right!
Say that line again!
"I believe in you!"
I can't say it again...
Come on, say it!
No!
Just say it!
I said no!
They say that Shikizaki Kiki modeled Kanzashi after the woman he loved when he was young.
That's pretty funny.
I don't believe it's anything to laugh at.
Are you denying what I say?
That's good, you've finally figured out how to humor me?
I wonder what that unpleasant woman's going to do now...
Does she not plan on returning after sending Biyorigou and her report here?
It appears she is staying back at Lake Fuyou in order to find Shikizaki Kiki's workshop.
Ah, she's making Shichika-kun work?
She pushes people too hard.
Though do you think that workshop might have any information in it?
The location of the sword that Maniwa Houhou told her of was Tendou.
She will likely go to ascertain the validity of that information.
Ah, there really is one in Tendou isn't there?
Which one was it again?
Outou Nokogiri.
Note: Saw, the King
Really, though...
Princess?
What a hassle.
Hassle?
Are you referring to me?
You're always a hassle.
I'm talking about the Maniwa Corps.
I believe you said we can ignore them.
I deny what I said in the past.
There are three left, right?
I want you to go find Maniwa Houhou...
...and assassinate him.
What is it?
Did you find something?
I don't know what it is, but it's really heavy.
Should I open it?
We don't care about a box right now!
Find the workshop first!
Just throw that away!
After fighting the soulless, masterless doll, the human sword Yasuri Shichika has learned what it means to have a human soul.
He is finally entering the climax of the sword hunt with the Strategian Togame.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening...
ends here.
kataranaide karatanai sugata
語らないで　語らない姿
Speak not, unspeaking shadow
tamatebako ni tsumetara nemuremasuka
玉手箱につめたら眠れますか？
Dare you sleep with such treasures in your chest?
ugokidasu kezurareru mama no karada
動き出す　削られるままの体
The body riven comes alive
koubuku no ibuki sosogu
香木の伊吹注ぐ
Perfume of the juniper, a mist upon it
omoidase katachi wa hito wo mu ni shite
思い出せ　形は人を無にして
Remember! Form leads man to ruin
yasuragi ni kaeru no
安らぎに帰るの
Leave the path and find peace
aa karakuri no ito wa toumei dakara kirai
あぁからくりの糸は透明だから嫌い
Ah, how I loathe puppet strings as they are unseen
hikichigiru hitori de toberu
引きちぎる一人で飛べる
Tear them from their post and fly alone!
odoranai no odoranai sugata
踊らないの　踊らない姿
Dance not, undancing shadow
arimukashi wo e ni shita otogibanashi
在り昔を絵にしたおとぎ話
A fairy tale of what has long past
kataranaide kataranai sugata
語らないで　語らない姿
Speak not, unspeaking shadow
tamatebako ni tsumetara nemurarete ne
玉手箱につめたら眠られてね
Dare you sleep with such treasures in your chest.