Job interviews are so nerve-wracking...
There, there.
A Santa-model Shinki?
You're the one that wanted the job?
Yes! I'm Ann.
I'm Tsugaru.
So...
do you like Christmas?
Um, yes!
I do.
Great, you're hired!
Now hop in!
Um, what are the job requirements?
Now mush!
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
A Christmas Song for You
Never had a job before?
Oh, you can tell?
Well, you don't look like a Career Shinki.
And you don't see the standard models working too often.
Is your master poor?
A-Absolutely not!
Oh, that'll explain the job for you.
Pay attention, okay?
Your life partner,
the Multi Movable System!
As thanks for your continued patronage,
we're holding a Christmas campaign!
On Christmas Eve, a tiny Santa will visit your home!
Tiny Santa?
Yep, that's our job.
Lovely, isn't it?
So, why'd you apply, again?
Well, the truth is...
That scarf would look wonderful on Master!
Isn't it kinda gaudy?
But he would look so cool in that down jacket!
Its price tag has many zeroes.
Those gloves are in Master's favorite color.
They look so warm.
Yeah, they'd be pretty nice!
Not bad indeed.
"Recruiting Christmas Cake decorations..."
Oh, this looks fun!
Oh, "Experienced Shinkis only"?
That's out too...
So, found anything?
Nothing. They're all asking for Career Shinkis.
I'm sorry. I'm the last one out, too...
The job market's tough.
There aren't a lot of openings for regular Shinkis to begin with.
But it's amazing that you all got jobs so quickly!
What kind of jobs did you get?
Well I, uh...
You could say I work in finances.
I work in showbiz!
Finances and showbiz...
Yes, okay.
That's great, you two!
What about Strarf?
It is secret.
C'mon, you can tell us, Hina.
Do not call me by that name.
Ann, how about this?
"Urgent!!"
Urgent!!
Seeking a helper for Santa Claus!
Christmas Eve ONLY
Applicant Requirements
Cheerful            Energetic
No Experience Necessary
Seeking a helper for Santa Claus!
Christmas Eve only?
A helper for Santa?
So you're all working to get a present for your master.
That's good.
I think it's really sweet of you.
Thank you.
We have a lot of houses...
There are a lot this year.
I can't handle these all alone,
so I've been in a bind.
We have to visit all of these tomorrow?
I am Santa Claus!
I take pride in my job!
Because this job's about delivering dreams!
We're delivering dreams?
That's right.
I am Santa Claus!
Now you.
I am... Santa Claus.
That was too soft!
I am Santa Claus!
I'm the Santa Claus who delivers Christmas dreams!
You!
My only reward is the smiles of children!
My only reward is the smiles of...
Oh, that's just my image.
Don't worry, you'll get your wage.
O-Oh... sorry.
Okay, tomorrow's gonna be a busy day.
So get a good night's sleep!
Yes!
I am Santa Claus, huh?
Here you go.
Whoa, it's a snowman!
Thanks, Mr. Snowman!
Bye bye!
Ines?
C'mon, it's rude to peek.
So this is your job...
This is it.
It's financial, in a way...
So how'd your interview go?
It'll only be for tomorrow, but I'll do my best!
Great, good job!
Thanks!
Thank you for listening.
That song...
came from my time in Paris,
when I heard a waiter humming in a podunk cafe.
I had just parted with my lover, and it felt like he was singing for my broken heart...
I'm sorry.
Stay strong!
Thanks for the beautiful music.
Thank you all so much!
I'll do a request for my next song!
So this is Lene's job?
You're all working hard.
Saying a street musician works in showbiz is way too much of a stretch!
You were handing out tissues in front of a bank after saying you'd work in finances.
That's not an overstatement?
Look, when were you ever in Paris?
An artist can travel around the world within her own heart.
Wow, is that true?
Since when were you an artist?
Oh well, at least Ann found a job.
Our plan's going well for now.
Yeah!
Well,
she's still not telling us what kinda job she found...
It is for your own safety.
Huh?
If I told you,
you would all bear the same cross as I.
Is her job even legal?
It might be something so dangerous she can't tell us!
A dangerous job...
Don't be reckless.
Just come home safe, okay?
I want us to have Christmas together next year, too!
I'm home!
Man, it's freezing!
Welcome home, Master!
Tomorrow's a secret, okay?
I am well aware.
Hm? Something wrong?
Nope, nothing at all!
So Master, got any plans for tomorrow night?
Hmm... nothing in particular.
Then let's all have a Christmas party!
Oh yeah, tomorrow's Christmas Eve.
Then how about I buy a cake on the way home?
Hooray!
Shinki Care
Warning
It's worth noting that we can't eat cake!
Don't be a killjoy.
I thought I'd warn everyone just in case.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow night!
Um, this is...
Uniform's provided!
You look great!
Now let's go!
I'm counting on you.
Don't move too much.
I am Santa Claus!
Now you.
Whatever danger comes our way,
delivering presents...
is Santa Claus's duty!
Coming!
Merry Christmas!
We came with a present!
Here you go!
Wow! Thanks, Santa!
We'll divvy up the work from here on out.
Huh?
We've spent more time than I thought we would.
Also...
it's started snowing.
Don't worry, Ann.
Believe in yourself.
Right!
Yes?
Mami, Merry Christmas.
Are you really Santa?
Huh?
Are you the real Santa?
I am Santa Claus!
I'm the Santa Claus who delivers Christmas dreams!
My only reward is the smiles of children.
Yes! I am Santa Claus!
Merry Christmas!
Thank you, Santa.
Tsugaru, I'm finished on my end!
Tsugaru?
Ann...
Tsugaru, what happened?
My left leg's actuator took a hit, it seems...
Who could have—
I went to play with a Doberman in the Saito district...
He was just a little puppy last year...
I got careless.
We need to see a Shinki Shop!
I'm fine.
Besides, we need to deliver these presents...
But you can't!
Not with that leg!
What're you saying?
I'm Santa Claus.
I deliver Christmas dre—
With wounds as deep as yours,
your energy won't last forever!
I'll handle the rest of the presents.
So please, get yourself to a Shinki Shop as soon as possible.
Got it.
I'll be back as soon as I'm fixed.
I'll leave it to you until then, Santa Claus.
Got it! I'll make you proud!
Okay, there's one more.
Please let me make it in time!
Wait, reindeer!
Oh no!
Santa Claus?
How would you like a delicious cake?
Wow, balloons!
I want one!
There are plenty enough to go around.
Strarf...
Whomever do you mean?
I am but a reindeer.
It is secret.
If I told you,
you would all bear the same cross as I.
Could this be Strarf's job?
Is something troubling you?
Actually, there's this bag with a very important present...
There it is!
I shall tell you a secret.
A what?
In truth, I am no reindeer.
It is a term of my employment.
An agreement of confidentiality that I should reveal my true form to nobody.
Oh, that's it.
You're troubled over how you can retrieve your luggage.
The blizzard's really strong up there,
so my flight unit will just get blown away.
We shall borrow this.
A Santa Claus balloon?
Should we use it as a snow break, we may make it through.
Guess we'll just have to try.
The starboard side is reeling!
Mend its balance!
Got it!
Do not get blown away!
Use your thrusters to hold out!
Got it!
I just can't leave you two alone.
Ines! But why?
I zoomed in on a balloon that stuck out like a sore thumb,
and then I saw you two.
What of your job?
Financial workers get off early!
There it is!
Stay frosty!
The wind's really strong up here!
All units, set thrusters to maximum!
A little more...
A little more!
Hina, a little to the right!
And Lene, stop singing and help us!
I'm sorry!
An artist like me can help only through song!
Hurry! My tank is near empty!
I am...
I am Santa Claus!
Good work, Ann.
You saved me out there.
I guess I was a bit of a pain to you all.
What about you, Tsugaru?
Are you okay now?
Thanks, I'm fine now.
Now then, everyone, Merry Christmas!
Mush!
Well, case closed.
Now then...
Let's go buy Master that present!
Yep, sobthin' like this.
I'm sure Master will love this!
Ann, you've been sneezing a lot lately.
I'mb feelin' kinda colb.
My head's goin' numb...
Could this be an induced fever mode?
We spent great time within that blizzard...
Did our circuitry freeze over?
Ann, you're awake?
Master...
I was pretty surprised to find you all collapsed from fever when I got home.
I bet you're thirsty.
I bought a Peach Jellycan.
I'm sorry...
Still not feeling well?
Well, it's...
It's my Christmas present for you all.
I heard this winter would be a cold one,
but these sure came in handy pretty quick.
Thank you very much, Master.
I'm so thirsty...
I've got a splitting headache.
This is... trifling...
Oh, I've gotta change everyone's ice.
Oh, I'll help.
Take it easy, Ann.
You need rest.
But...
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Ann, thanks for these.
I'll treat them well.
Great!
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Hasn't Hina been a bit odd lately?
Do you think something's happened?
Maybe the review period ran out,
and she has to be returned to the manufacturer!
I haven't heard about that!
Is that for real?
Next time,
"Tonight's the Night! Who's the Strongest Shinki!?"
Next time
"Tonight's the Night!
Who's the Strongest Shinki!?"
That's what's for real?