Why'd you bring her here?
She saw our faces.
What was I supposed to do?
Setouchi's on her way.
We can decide what to do
once she gets here.
Hell, we got a girl tied up here.
There's only one thing to do.
You really wanna break the law?
We already broke the law.
Damn, this job wasn't worth
the reward she promised.
They couldn't've taken me very far.
I'm probably being held in the
abandoned warehouse near our school!
Did you hear that?
Yep, that was Inaba!
She's in the abandoned
warehouse near our school!
I hear your voice on the wind
like the rhythm of our daily life
You smile impulsively like the sun itself
Preparation for the club presentations
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Since when can we remember these exciting days?
How to get
points from
the judges
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
Inabaaaan!
I wanna go to
Disney Sea
Universal Studios
sounds good too
A map that shows
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
How to get
points from
the judges
recommended places
around school
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Inabaaaan!
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Each person takes 15 minutes to present
A bonus extra
for the SCS paper
Universal Studios
sounds good too
What awaits us past tomorrow?
The Girls' Squad dazzles with their cosplay
Good job, me!
Let's beat the jazz band!
The battle for Mr. Go
The outcome will decide our club's future
No-rope barbed wire barricade mat double
hell megaton electric explosion death match!
Guys, this is serious!!
Just keep going!
The Physics quiz
didn't go so well
I'm the president
I'm hungry
Inaban's white rabbit
Wanna picnic?
Let's go to Disneyland again
Universal Studios
sounds good too
Let's beat the jazz band!
Frankensteiner!
How about curry doria?
Cheep
Places people haven't heard about
Yui's favorite shops
Yui's favorite date spots
Yui's favorite sweets
Today connects to brighter days yet
which catch up with us
in a flood of colors
We walk our path through life with strength
and after today know that the light itself is with us
In your smile I can see warmth
Forever and ever
we live through ups and downs here
Let us believe in that and the future it brings about
Shouldn't we call the police?
Now's not the time to be
worried about keeping secrets!
I know!
But we need to figure out where she is first!
Inaba!
What am I doing?
Inaba's in danger.
But I don't know what I should do.
I don't know what I can do,
so I'm lying here doing nothing.
I wish I could just dash off and save her.
Only a terrible person would
just watch on the sidelines.
But I'm stuck here because
I can't make up my mind.
I'm doing exactly what I disparaged,
which means I'm a terrible person.
We're coming to help!
Connecting Hearts
It's your fucking life!
Live it as you damn well please!
Sure, we may have unwittingly
asked too much of you.
But why'd you have to try to live up to all of that?
Why'd you have to take all that upon yourself?
You're just a fucking retard!
Setouchi?
I still love Nagase Iori.
I don't have to be perfect.
I don't have to meet everybody's expectations.
There are people who accept me as I am.
Life isn't about doing everything right.
It's about doing what you want to do.
Being who you want to be.
That's what I should be focusing on.
We'll save you!
Enough.
Enough is enough.
I'm gonna follow my heart.
Nagase Iori is going to be Nagase Iori!
Now, what do I want to do?!
Be free!
Be freer!
I will be...
Setouchi's inside.
Setouchi?
How many are inside?
Three men.
You went too far.
This has gotten out of control.
We didn't have a choice.
She came at us out of nowhere.
This is all your fault to begin with!
You're the one who told us to destroy their presentation materials.
That's because everyone said to do it.
Don't try to pin this on other people!
What's with that look?
Stop!
Who are you people?!
Who said you could come in here?!
We're busy right now.
Do you want to get your ass kicked?
Bastards!
Damn!
Bitch!
That was awesome!
They'll wake up soon enough.
Inaba, it's oka—
St-Stop that!
Take it easy!
Don't be stupid!
Shut up!
Take one step closer,
and you'll regret it!
Okay.
We get it. Just calm down.
It was all her fault anyway!
She was acting like such hot shit when she asked us to mess up the room!
No need to get so worked up.
If you let Inaba go, we'll leave you alone.
You think I'm gonna trust you?!
Who's there?!
Well...
You guys look like you could use some help.
You can't get out of this alone, can you?
I'll give you a hand.
What's going on, Nagase?
You see, I've got a score
to settle with these guys,
so I'll side with you.
Like they say, "The enemy
..of my enemy is my friend."
Work!
The enemy of my enemy is my friend?
I get it.
Iori! What are you talking about?!
Please work!
Work!
Iori, you idiot!
What do you think you're doing?!
Don't talk to me like we're friends.
So what do you need me to do?
Right.
Work! Work! Work!
What should I do?
Work! Work! Work! Work!
Work! Work!
Please work!
Grab Inaba now!
Taichi!
Man...
I was so scared!
I've had enough of this crap!
Enough! Enough! Enough!
I was so scared!
Iori!
Let's get out of here.
You come with us, Setouchi.
So basically, you have a crush on
Shiroyama from the jazz band,
and you were mad about Iori
rejecting Shiroyama's confession,
so that's why you started messing with her.
I wasn't going to do anything to your clubroom,
but everybody was egging me on,
and I couldn't back out.
But that's just an excuse, huh?
I'm sorry.
Well?
I've made up my mind.
Setouchi, stand up.
Brace yourself!
Huh?
Here I go!
Hey!
Wh-What? Did I hit her too hard?
That wasn't so much a slap as a palm strike.
That was a flawless straight palm strike.
You even put your hips into it.
You could've given her a concussion.
A-Are you okay?
Sorry.
I hit you too hard.
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
We'll say that was for the other members.
It didn't come from me.
It was partly my fault,
so this makes us even.
Can you forgive me?
You know, I've been wondering about something.
I think you're actually a pretty nice girl, Setouchi.
I'm used to figuring out what
other people are thinking.
Why are you putting on that bad-girl act?
Th-That's because...
I was trying to emulate the boy I used to like.
You were trying to emulate him?
Ah, I understand now.
We're very similar.
Huh?
From what I can see, you're currently pretending to be someone you don't want to be.
What do you want to do?
I...
I just...
I know I don't seem like that type of person,
but I'd like to try harder to join a club!
I'd also like to join the student council!
And I want to ask Shiroyama out!
Then do those things!
You shouldn't take it out on others when things don't go your way!
Wait!
I shouldn't be lecturing you
when I did the exact same thing!
And Setouchi, let's be friends!
Huh?!
F-Friends?
We're similar, so I'm sure we'll get along.
Yep! Nagase Iori is back in action!
Sorry about all the trouble I caused!
I've restricted myself to meaningless standards all my life.
I was always too worried about what people normally would or wouldn't do.
That was how I decided the actions I would take,
so it felt like I was trying to be someone else.
Whenever my mother got divorced and remarried,
I would try to be the kind of good girl
my new father wanted.
I was always trying to be
what someone else wanted.
But that was wrong.
I didn't need to worry about being normal or following common sense.
There are people who accept me for who I am.
"It's your fucking life, so live it
as you damn well please."
It's that simple.
The sun's already up.
Iori, did you call your mom?
We were scheduled to stay at school overnight for the presentation.
Oh, that's been covered.
I called her last night.
You really surprised me back there.
You actually asked her to be your friend.
I have to say that you're truly special.
But I'm not saying that you should
act the way I want you to.
It looks like we were putting pressure on you without realizing it.
I'm sorry about that.
But you're still an amazing person!
You don't have to worry about it so much.
It's okay. I understand what you're trying to say.
Still, nobody would've expected you
to ask her to be friends.
No normal person would've reacted that way.
I don't care what normal people do anymore.
I'm going to live my life as I damn well please.
Damn you!
Inaba!
Taichi!
Were we truly in love?
I believe so.
It was an immature love, though.
I feel the same way.
Sorry about being so immature.
I never saw the real you.
I only saw what I wanted to see.
But I'm still really happy
that you fell in love with me.
I really am.
Glad to hear it.
I loved you too.
The love I felt was real.
But there was a lot I didn't understand,
so I made mistakes.
I want us to start over.
Sorry about being so selfish.
I was just as selfish.
Honestly, I was kind of in love
just for the sake of being in love.
This conversation is pretty embarrassing.
It's only possible because of where we are.
I guess we have to thank
thought transmission for that.
I'm never going to be thankful for that mess.
I have one last thing to say.
So do I.
I'm glad I fell in love with you.
Taichi?
Taichi?!
Taichi!
Good morning, Inaba.
I'm so glad!
If anything had happened to you, I...
Don't cry.
Where are we?
The school infirmary.
You were hit by one of those guys.
He got away.
We carried you here since it
was closer than the hospital.
Should I call for an ambulance to be safe?
It's not that serious.
Sorry for making you worry.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I don't know what I'd do if
anything happened to you.
Especially if it was my fault.
Because I...
I need you!
I really do!
I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you so much!
I love you! I love you so much!
Wait!
I love you! I love you! I love you!
I don't!
I love you so much! I love you!
I mean, I do!
But don't listen!
Wanna go out with me?
G-G-Go out... w-wi...
D-Do you think I'm cute?
Yep, you're cute.
Oh, really?
Hold on!
Why did I ask that question?!
Well, uh...
Er, but...
I do.
Nagase.
Uh, I think I'll end it now.
I thought you should be the one I tell.
Wait a minute.
You kept transmitting my thoughts
when I was feeling absolutely horrible.
Were you intentionally choosing the worst
possible thoughts to transmit to everyone?
No idea.
I can't say.
You said the episodes would happen at random,
but the timing was too perfect.
You were trying to make me hate myself.
Well, that's something you
have to decide for yourself.
Still, it feels like this is
a turning point of sorts.
Am I wrong?
Ah... But I never expected to become
acquainted with all of you.
I suppose I'm an oddball.
In any case, the episode is over.
I'll be leaving, then.
Who's that?
Is it Setouchi?
You're keeping the earrings?
Well, I like them.
You know, I think you're cuter
with a clean look, Kaoru.
You're making it sound like
I wasn't cute before, Iori.
That's not true.
What's going on here?
Tell me everything, Iori!
Hold on. What happened?
Are you really Setouchi?
I think you look cuter this way.
Hey. Seriously, what's going on?
Well, I'd say that we found
the best possible solution.
Nagase really is special.
Just as I expected.
The children of Class 1-3 performed well.
Club Presentations
And then, it was finally time for our club presentation.
Here's our next recommended spot!
A chic café that's perfect for dates!
We've even verified that if you go with someone,
your love will surely blossom!
The two members who checked the place out
are now a couple, so there's no mistake about it!
Right? Taichi? Inaba?
Hey!
That wasn't in the script!
But it's true that we're a couple now.
Don't announce that here!
Good job, kids!
I'm proud to be your advisor!
Should you be here right now?
The jazz band just finished performing.
Yeah, they played great!
I'm impressed by all the hard work you've put in!
And I'm impressed by how I'm so popular
that two clubs are fighting
to keep me as their advisor!
So, I'm thinking about being
the advisor for both clubs.
What?
You can do that?
After some thinking,
I realized that I just have to serve as the SCS advisor and help with jazz band practice when I'm free!
How's that?!
If that was originally an option,
you should've done it in the first place, idiot!
Inaba, use more force!
Actually, I want to join in!
Wait! That wouldn't be considered punishment!
You can do it to me instead!
Where did Inaba learn that move?
Skip the stupid remarks and help me!
And so, we were somehow able
to survive another ordeal.
Come April, the SCS will have the same advisor and same structure.
Aoki's fears were realized as
he had to take make-up exams.
If he didn't pass those,
he wouldn't be able to advance
to the next grade with Kiriyama,
so he studied hard.
And it sounds like Kiriyama helped him study.
They've been growing closer little by little.
And...
Inaba and I are dating now.
Are you sure you want to go out with me?
We've gone over this already.
We just took too long getting here.
Iori said the same thing.
I need you, and you need me.
There's nothing else to worry about.
Taichi!
H-Hey, Inaba.
Taichi...
Stop it. We're in public!
Hey, Inaba!
After seeing Inaba act this way,
Nagase started calling her "Lovebird."
Nagase is popular in the classroom again.
She has a new friend in Setouchi,
and they're getting along great.
As for the guys who trashed our room...
You don't need to worry about them.
Inaba and I dealt with them with help from my father.
They will never lay a finger on you again.
Uh-huh...
What did they do?
I'm too scared to ask for details.
Opening Ceremy
Yamaboshi Academy
Uwa, do you know what club you're gonna join?
A new school year, huh?
Dunno. Some place where I can relax.
I wonder if anyone's weird enough to join our club.
Hey, Shino.
We'll need to plan ahead in case someone joins.
Let's join the cheerleading club.
I'm not any good at that.
If they join the SCS, they may have to deal with bizarre phenomena.
I don't like to draw attention.
I'd like to join a club with nice upperclassmen.
Student Cultural Society
I don't think we need to worry about that.
Heartseed hasn't shown up since.
Recruiting
Seeking new members!
We should remain vigilant.
He may try something when we least expect it.
That's right.
You never know what may happen in life!
But if you believe in the path you take,
that path becomes part of who you are!
Wow, Iori! That sounded smart!
Full speed ahead!
Enjoy every day to the fullest!
We still have long lives ahead of us.
I'm sure we'll have doubts
and worries going forward,
but we'll continue to walk
on the path we've chosen,
connecting our hearts
with others in the process.
I am lost and confused
and yet I know that someone is holding out their hand for me
Inside the little box I locked
was the taste of a path I thought I knew
One by one I soothe my wounds
and again jealousy, ardor, coldness, light,
rejection and hope,
all become one and I stand screaming helplessly
My feelings are like melting chocolate, black and sweet
My dreams have long since turned to ash
I am weak, and ringing fills my ears and I hear nothing else
Please find me
mi     chi     ra      n      do      m
Thank you for watching!
Yaegashi Taichi