Classroom Block A    Classroom
Answer Sheet
I know the truth!
This class is a lie.
It’s all fake!
Uh... what are you ta—
I died without accomplishing anything!
I know that already!
But what’s the point of doing all this?!
Will you take me to heaven if I score well on tests?
Hey!
Someone tell me!
Tell me!
Crap, it’s the student council president...
What timing...
He’s going to kill him...
Then quit complaining and do something about it.
There's something you need to do, right?
How will you accomplish it?
Tell me, what do you need?
What do you need right now?
Tell me.
Some people needed courage to face their past.
Some people needed strength to reach their dreams.
Some people needed time and friends.
What do you need?
Right now,
the courage to face you!
Okay.
See? You can do it.
You know what to do now.
If you ever feel unreasonable resentment or hesitation, come to the student council room.
I’ll always be waiting there.
Damn, he’s cool!
I’ve never seen anything like that!
His name is Otonashi-san, right?
Does he have a girlfriend??
They say he's waiting for someone.
Really?
Come on, be quiet!
Get back to the test!
You too. Sit down!