We're getting really popular, you said?
I thought our merch was really cute...
It's because you had to go and
pick such a weirdass name for us.
Is it?
TogeToge wristbands!
Anyone want a TogeToge towel?
I still think it's better than Shin-Kawasaki though...
Is it?
We'll survive, at least
something's still really popular.
Alright, let's do this!
Gimme a hug!
I am never showering again after this!
Your brain needs a shower! Sheesh...
You're right...
Not my type of thing.
Excuse me,
If you have a moment, allow me to introduce myself.
MIURA SHIOMI
GOLDEN ARCHER CO.
..."Golden Archer"?
- Yes.
- Why does that ring a bell?
Ah! The talent agency!
Indeed!
10: WANDERVOGEL
So you are scouting us?
Yes, that is exactly why I reached out.
I see...
Please feel free to look us up online,
we are a well established agency.
- How exactly?
- They're pretty famous.
Many girls at my school
want to get scouted by them.
And they also act as a label for bands.
But if they operate in showbiz, then...
The truth is, I love Diamond Dust!
But I cannot say the same of what
Diamond Dust has become nowadays!
They've become so generic that
they lost what made them so unique!
The one I loved was you, Momoka-san!
I wanted to see you making music
that you truly desired to create!!
And that's exactly what this band is!!
I know, right!!
Sit down.
...S-sorry.
When DD managed to strike a major hit,
I came to the realization that my type of music
Isn't made for modern popular tastes.
That's true...
And I don't think that's just me being pessimistic.
If anything, DD has gotten
many fans by going down this path.
But in spite of that, these four
still want to compete with them.
They want to prove my music
can go toe to toe with theirs.
To the point they convinced me to give it a shot.
Right?
Momoka-san...
I understand.
What?
You will be at the
upcoming festival, right?
We need to "leave an
impression" at the festival...?
MIURA SHIOMI
GOLDEN ARCHER CO.
Basically, if make enough of an impact,
It'll be easier for companies and labels to notice us.
And if we can bring in a lot of fans, then we can
prove to them that our music doesn't need to change.
So this festival is more like a big audition, huh?
- Nina.
- Y-yeah?
Would you mind writing the lyrics for our next song?
Me?!
I want to see what a song
inspired by my music is like.
OK!
I'm not so sure about this one, chief.
- What are you even thinking?
- I am down for it.
Those two really seem to understand each other.
How are the lyrics coming along?
Zero progress.
Didn't you say there was
something you had in mind?
I did...
So where's the issue?
You wouldn't get it...
Putting feelings into words
means bringing them out.
So if I bring them out,
Then that means all of the repressed
monsters within me will come flowing out...
What, you think you're too good for this?
You know how many songs I've had to make myself?!
Ow ow ow ow!!
Well, I can relate to not
wanting to share your pain...
Come on, it's your shift.
Already...?
What now?
It's nothing.
Good morn-NAAAH
Something wrong?
How...?! Why?!!
What are y--
Good morning.
Excuse me,
I believe a certain Iseri works here part-time...?
She doesn't have any shifts today I'm afraid.
- Is that so...
- Are you looking for her?
You must be Rupa-san, right?
- SUBARU-CHAN!
- What
- MY MOM'S HERE! >:(
- What did you expect ._.
They could've told me beforehand!
D-dad?? AH!
Nina?
And that's why you came running here?
Aaah... I feel so at peace here...
You still don't know why they came though, right?
Shouldn't you try talking to them?
Are you listening?
Nina...?
There's no point talking to them.
You're the same with your grandma, right?
They refuse to accept that we don't see eye to eye.
And treat you as if you were just sounding delirious.
Even then though...
Besides, I need to focus on the lyrics.
I can't waste my time before the festival on this.
Everyone's future depends on it. I don't
have the energy for anything else right now.
Sounds to me like you're just running away though.
So, are you sleeping here tonight?
THE NEXT DAY
Hello?
Please don't contact me again.
You're the one who ran away.
This isn't what I meant by it though...!
They called me asking,
what was I supposed to do, lie?
To: ISERI MUNEO
From: ISERI NINA
You told them everything?
After you wrote them that letter,
Who wouldn't come after you?
But why...?
You thought they'd just ignore it?
If you're hurting, then stop
running away and just spit it out!
Nina?
She hung up...
Huh?
They changed the lock??
But I'm the tenant here!
Please provide me a new pair of keys!
Screw my parents, screw the company, screw everyone!!
Shut up!!
But...
Here.
We'll cover for you for a few days,
So have this as a present from Tomo-chan and I.
TOKYO -> KUMAMOTO
But why...?
You may have heard from Tomo-chan, but...
On a certain day,
I was thinking of calling my mom.
However since my work
was running until late,
I thought I might as well just call her tomorrow.
My mom died that day.
Life offers less time and opportunities
than we'd like to think.
Guess I should "cut it out with the monologues", heh.
You really think they care that much?
After they neglected me for so long.
Spare me the sound effects.
Heh, I see.
So this is your weakness then?
I have no weaknesses or anything though.
Then just go already!
You too?
I think you're blowing this out of proportion.
What's holding you back?
There's no exams or bullying this time.
Is it because you're scared
of not convincing your father?
That's...
Not true? Then go already.
It is true.
Then even more reason to go.
I'm not letting you back here till you do.
I'm going!
Back home...
The train bound for Suizenji and Hikarinomori...
TATSUTAGUCHI STATION
Let's do this!
Three, two, one...
Ouch!
Goddammit...
Nina!
We were looking for you!
Girls Band Cry.
Family Precepts
A band?
Is that a viable career path these days?
Seems so.
She's already been approached by a showbiz agency,
Meaning she can do this professionally.
Well, or so I've heard at least.
- She's heard right...
- But still...
You left here to study on your own,
And instead you started this project all on your own without telling us?!
Well, I've had a glimpse of them.
Do you realize how much you've hurt your mother?
There you go again.
Mom has nothing to do with this.
When I left, didn't you say "let her be"?.
We agreed on the same thing. To let me be.
That's not true.
I said you should get into university.
Do you realize how much I let you selfishly have?
You wanted to quit school, so I let you
submit your resignation.
You wanted to go to Tokyo, so I helped you move.
Stop pretending already...
I did everything on my own!!
I'm the one who quit! I'm the one who left!!
You only got the apartment
thanks to your mother's connections.
Remind me, who signed as
your guarantor so you could rent?
You are still a minor. Do you know what that means?
That you must live under the supervision of adults.
So I should just obey you blindly?
I should let myself get bullied
like nothing's happened?
Nina...
I knew it was pointless.
I shouldn't have hoped
that you would listen to me,
or try to understand. I really tried.
But in the end, it all leads to this.
It's useless.
When you leave tomorrow, come with me.
Hey...
Where are we going?
You'll realize very soon.
I'm not going.
You're taking me to school, right?
We're just here to talk.
You told me what you wanted to say.
But there's something I wish to say to someone too.
Sorry to have made you come
all the way here in this heat.
APOLOGY LETTER TO: ISERI MUNEO/NINA
Do not worry.
What is this?
It must've been pretty hot for you as well, Nina-san.
- If you may.
- Ah, yes.
After further inspection, the student
responsible admitted her actions,
The school would like to extend an apology
for not acting to the standards expected of us.
Is that all? Will the school not take responsibility?
That's not our intent,
However, we can't exactly publicly
acknowledge bullying in our school...
I understand that you may
not be able to publicly,
But I was at least expecting
that when it came to the truth--
Stop it.
But...
I told you to stop.
You don't need to say that Nina.
You're the victim here.
Momoka-san... what would you do
If, hypothetically, Nina never
returned from Kumamoto?
I'll do what I must.
Tomo-chan!
Are you hurt?
It'll be alright.
Let's believe in her.
Welcome home.
Yeah.
Will you be eating dinner?
You going back then?
- Yeah.
You're serious about that band?
Yeah.
You love it that much?
That song...
...It gave me the push I needed.
Back when I was told to
play it smart and just "deal with it",
Apology Letter
Even when it felt impossible
to deal with anything anymore,
It gave me a push forward.
It told me that I wasn't wrong.
That I didn't need to deal with it.
It told me to not worry about
the future and just take the leap.
It felt as if I was freefalling.
I wasn't sure if I was soaring into the great sky or plummeting to my doom,
But that song made me fly.
So I have no more homeland I can step back on.
Back then,
I may as well have been trying to kill myself.
Maybe in reality I have no wings,
Maybe this feeling of flying is all in my head, but...
Right now, I love myself more than I ever have.
I can proudly say that
this is who I really am.
I get it now.
But can we have one last dinner, at least?
Here you go! Lotus root curry!
It's been a while, huh?
- Are you sure?
- Why...?
Why? I mean, the family precepts...
Ah, don't sweat it.
After you left, the mood got kinda weird back here.
Your dad even started drinking alcohol even though he's a light drinker.
To the point of getting drunk.
"What should I do for her?"
He kept saying that.
He's worried about you.
He may be a renowned researcher, but that doesn't mean,
he can't be adviced to learn some new things.
Besides, the Shinkansen ticket you used,
Your mom was the one who gave it to your friends.
Bet you never realized.
You know... we still love you.
Even those parents of ours,
I have no doubt they still love you.
Just don't forget that.
Thanks for the meal.
Thank you. For coming back to us.
I love you too, Nina.
Was it always so spicy?
This curry is so spicy it's making me cry...
FAMILY PRECEPTS
Nina Age 10
This void feeling, this eternal feeling,
Of answers that lead to superficial clichés
Is this that song you love so much?
Yeah.
I see.
Do you hate it?
I bet you do after all that.
It's a good song.
Quite good in fact.
Dad.
I'm sorry you had to deal with such a
selfish daughter who'd never listen to you.
Please stop smoking so much, okay?
I'm leaving. I'm leaving!
I'm leaving for good!
Nina!
Wait!
What?
What more could you want?
Stay safe.
I will.
Nina!
The keys to your apartment!
New keys?
Why change them?
A gift from your dad!
Dad!
When I finish this next song and
get to sing it, if it's okay with you...
Will you come listen to me?
I will.
Alright!
Nina...
I'm leaving!
And thanks for cutting the branch!
Take care!
Even if you were so intrusive and unbearable...
I still loved you.
Goodbye... no. See you again!
Thank you for traveling with us.
To take the Chuo, Yamanote,
Keihin-Tohokku, Tokaido, Joban Lines...
"VOID AND CATHARSIS"
Miss? Miss!
S-sorry!
Oh? It's you again!
Had a good nap?
Yep!
I'm home!
Nina!
Where's the souvenirs?
No way...
Why are you all here?
Momoka-san wanted to make sure
you'd come back safe and sound.
If one more day went by,
She would've driven us all four to Kumamoto to get you!
Even insisted she'd drive herself.
Didn't want Rupa-san to take the spotlight, huh?
You all agreed to it, right?
Hold up, why's she crying?
Was it that traumatizing?
Hm? I don't think she's actually crying.
What do you think, Rupa-san?
I wonder...
Thank you, everyone.
I'm home!
Welcome home!
You got the lyrics done?
Yeah, I got them! It's gonna be a good song!
NEXT: TO THE CENTER OF THE WORLD