Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
Letting you go, against my wishes, is...
kamen no kao de tebanasu noga
like meeting to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume nomama tabitatou
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru utakanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
Toru...
Toru! Toru, wake! Toru!
What is it?
Toru, look, look! Ahead!
Huh?
What is that?
You don't know, Brother? That's called the ocean.
This is your first time seeing it too, isn't it?
Toru, Akari, see ocean, first time?
The village of Acura was in the mountains.
My first time, too!
Feels cool...
Taste, too salty!
Sideways walk.
Chaika!
It looks like big waves hit here sometimes, so be—
Toru, laugh! Mean!
Hey, stop that!
Brother might look rather good all wet.
I'll help you, Chaika.
You idiot! Cut it out!
Take this!
That displeased face is quite enticing, as well.
You impress me, Brother.
I've just witnessed the quintessential master of dripping wet love scenes!
Give it a res—
The Harbor of Phantom
Dreams Recollected
This is the mansion of Clay Morgan, one of the eight heroes.
Yeah.
The only thing we know about him is that he uses a spear.
I hope he's someone who can listen to reason.
Chaika, what are you looking at?
Claudia said... Father's fortune.
Hidden island.
Yeah, the rumor did say it was in the ocean around here...
Yes.
Hey, Chaika, you know the battle for the remains is going to get tougher from now on, right?
The red Chaika already got one of them and is a step ahead of us.
Instead of talking about a fortune that we don't even know exists,
shouldn't we be trying to get more remains as quickly as we can?
Yes...
Sixty-four sheep...
Sixty-five sheep...
Yah! Yah! Yah!
What's going on?
Lots of people here, eh? And they're all uglier than me!
Why are all these people lined up here?
Clay Morgan loves to laugh,
so he has many entertainers perform for him every day.
If we make him laugh, he gives us lots of money!
A hero who likes comedy? That's different.
In other words, we'll just have to pretend to be entertainers.
That Gundo could be trouble.
Uh-huh?
Next!
Are you a ventriloquist?
Yep, you got it!
You're the third ventriloquist today.
We've seen enough, already. Go home!
Looks like the screening is fairly strict.
Yeah.
Next!
And you are?
We are a troupe of street performers.
Street performers, eh? That's fairly common.
Is there anything unique you can do?
Yes! Ah...
Of course.
This man is a one-of-a-kind immortal.
He can sit fully naked in a tub of boiling water,
impersonating a cockatrice while eating pasta through his nose.
That sounds amazing!
Okay, go on in!
Did you have to say all that nonsense?
It got us inside without trouble, didn't it?
Toru, pasta through nose, amazing!
Don't take it seriously!
I am Clay Morgan.
Are you the man who can sit fully naked in a tub of boiling water,
impersonating a cockatrice while eating pasta through your nose?
I'd love to see that. Show me.
Clay Morgan, I'd like to talk to y—
Strip, Brother.
What are you doing?
You need to be naked to sit in boiling water.
You just made all that up!
Why do I actually have to do it?
Because I want to see it.
Who cares?!
Do you hate me, Brother?
Have you not sufficient kindness to grant your sweet sister's simple wish?
What's sweet about a sister who forces me to strip at knifepoint?!
Now that you've gotten my hopes up,
is it not your job as an older brother to live up to them?
You got your own hopes up!
Toru! Want to see, too!
You be quiet!
So you're a critical comedian troupe in the guise of street performers!
How novel! I like it!
Do come again sometime.
You may take your money and go.
Well, I guess that worked out...
We don't need the money.
We want the remains instead.
Emperor Gaz's remains.
Wh-Who are you people?!
The remains?!
I feel ill.
Leave! Leave now!
Return Father's remains!
F-Father?
Gaz's daughter, Chaika!
You're...
That can't be! I saw... I saw you die!
Your head rolled!
It wasn't me! The one who killed you...
The one who cut off your head was Hartgen!
Why are you here?
Have you come to curse me?!
Stay away! Stay away, ghost!
Stay away!
He ran away...
What was that about?
Toru! Clay, where?!
He ran. We're going after him.
You wait in the vehicle.
I come with!
You can't run with your Gundo.
Leave this one to us.
Right...
Fredrica?
What are you guys doing here?
Good timing! Look after Chaika!
Huh?
Master Morgan?
He went running behind there like a madman not long ago.
He came in here earlier, and left through the back door.
Did you find him?
No.
He seems to be running around with no concern for what others think.
Looks like he won't be returning to his mansion for a while.
Damn...
Fresh fish really is delicious!
Chaika, are you worried about the emperor's fortune?
Yes.
But nobody ever found that island, right?
Possible, entire island hidden, magic.
Oh, that's true.
Secret of Chaika... Information, desperate.
Ship...
Fredrica! Request, stay here!
Stay away, you friend of that ghost!
Get away! Get away!
What are you so afraid of?
Are you that scared of the emperor you took down yourself?
Someone who wasn't part of the fight wouldn't understand!
He was stabbed, cut apart, covered with blood... and he was smiling!
As if he pitied us...
As if he were looking down on some insects...
He wasn't human! He was a monster!
You made me remember it all...
After I was finally enjoying life again!
You've been summoning entertainers to help you forget about Emperor Gaz?
Wh-Where is she? Where is his daughter's ghost?
The rumor that his dead daughter was searching for his remains was true?!
Damn it! Disappear!
A secret island?
Never heard of it.
Rumor, clue, anything! Please!
I'm not sure what to tell you...
I don't know if it has any connection,
but there is a place off the coast that people call the Evil Sea.
Need details!
All boats that go near there end up sinking or going missing.
So none of the fishermen around here will go near it.
There's no island there, though.
Only ocean.
Evil Sea...
Have you lost your mind, starting a fight in a place like this?
Shut up!
Stay away!
Don't let that girl come near me!
Want to keep going?
I-If you want to kill me, go ahead!
I don't want to kill you. All I want are the remains.
Just the remains?
Yes.
Where are you hiding them?
If I give you the remains, will you go away?
Fine! You can have them!
Just don't ever show yourself in front of me again!
Any luck, Brother?
Yeah, it's here!
He was afraid to keep them anywhere near him, so he hid them here?
Why didn't he just sell them?
There must be plenty of people who would want them.
He probably thought he'd be cursed if he got rid of them.
Okay, ready to head back?
You still love to show up out of nowhere, I see.
In the coastal waters northeast of here, there is an island.
That is where you should go next.
An island? Is that where Emperor Gaz's fortune is?
You'll find out when you get there.
Hold it!
Guy, you knew that there were multiple Chaikas, didn't you?
And here's a question for you: do you really believe
I'm the same Guy who spoke to you before?
You're not going to give us a straight answer, are you?
You are free to think what you will.
No matter how often I see it,
I don't know how he does that.
Yeah. I'd guess it's a special type of magic but...
He didn't say that what's on the island is more remains.
If gathering remains is our priority, we should probably follow Claudia's note.
Then we should head for the Principality of Hartgen?
Its leader, Stephan Hartgen, was the leader of the punitive force.
If what Claudia and Clay said is true,
then he's the man who cut off Chaika's head.
Shin Acura, raise your head.
Yes, sir.
What is the status of the remains?
Yes, sir. A large number of remains
should soon arrive here in the Principality of Hartgen.
They will arrive with the one who currently possesses the most remains,
the white Chaika.
I see.
When all the remains are gathered, you're going to show me first, right, Father?
Hey, Arina, that's not fair.
You're going to show me, aren't you, Father?
Irina, Arina... My daughters.
Of course, I promise you two will be the first to see.
The white Chaika, eh?
I understand her two saboteur employees are acquaintances of yours.
Yes, somewhat.
Three people who grew up as family, taking up weapons to fight each other to the death...
I look forward to it.
I will have you do your job to the fullest, Shin.
Yes, sir.
And you, as well,
cavalier of lost honor.
Fredrica, where's Chaika?
Oh, she went off somewhere by herself.
Where?!
Please, sail ship!
Reward, lots!
You've gotta be kidding! Anywhere but there!
Pay bonus!
Even if you give me money, it's useless if I'm dead!
Please! Someone, help!
Chaika!
Toru...
What were you thinking?
It's not just Clay.
The red Chaika's group might be close by!
What if a fight had broken out?
Selfish actions, apologize.
But, serious.
Huh?
Father's fortune, myself... Want to know.
That again?
Frankly, I'm against it.
We have no idea what this fortune is,
and the information we have is too vague.
Not to mention, if we know it's in such dangerous waters,
that's all the more reason not to approach it carelessly.
Your objective is to gather the remains, right?
We know where the remaining heroes are.
Why can't you get all the remains first,
and then think about the fortune?
New facts, one after another.
Many Chaikas. All created.
My memories, missing.
Everything, unclear.
Want to know everything.
But you don't know if you'll find anything out once you get his fortune...
Toru, can't understand my feelings!
Will search for fortune!
Even alone! Father's fortune!
Alone, you say?
In other words, you're firing us, then?
Saboteurs will risk their lives as tools to serve their master's purpose,
but once we're fired, that's it.
Later.
Toru...
No helping it now.
Akari...
Aww, they left.
You okay with that, Chaika?
Said I would work alone.
Can't stop Toru.
Yeah?
I wonder what I should do...
I only followed you guys because I wanted to fight Toru.
Fredrica, last favor! Just one!
Want to find island.
Dragoon, fly, Evil Sea!
Oh, you want me to take you close to the island?
Yes!
Sure, just getting there is easy.
It sounds sort of interesting.
Grateful!
I guess we're camping here tonight.
Tomorrow, we'll come up with a plan for the future.
You never change, Brother.
Ever since we lived in Acura...
I understand that you want to keep Chaika out of danger.
What are you talking about?
I was only following the code of the saboteur.
Suppose you were to die, Brother.
And suppose the many lewd, repulsive things
you owned were hidden on some island.
What kind of supposition is that?
If that were the fortune you had left behind,
I would go to find them, even to the ends of the world.
It's the same way... Chaika values her father's remains as well as his fortune.
That being the case, shouldn't a saboteur respect his master's will?
You know how inept Chaika is.
This very night, she may be off somewhere getting raped by some thug.
Or she may have fallen prey to some beast.
Or she may have encountered the red Chaika's gang,
and her head has said farewell to her body...
Okay, I get it!
I'll go back and talk things out with Chaika.
Is that good enough?
I told you that I am only following you, Brother.
She's trying to get to the island alone?!
That idiot!
What's impossible is impossible.
Any kind of boat will do! As long as it will take us close!
Give it up.
No fisherman around here will take a boat out there.
What about that boat? Whose is it?
Oh, that's Master Morgan's cargo ship.
He runs the shipping industry around here, after all.
Wh-What? What do you want now?
We want to borrow your boat.
If you don't want Emperor Gaz's remains scattered all around this house...
Okay! I understand!
I'll arrange it right away!
It's all so vague.
We're supposed to go to an island nobody knows the location of?
What?
It's them!
This doesn't look like a coincidence.
Yeah. What should we do, Princess?
Efun... Heluste... Ru... Belguil... Fai... Sev...
Come forth, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Reaction... faint...
Fredrica! Ahead, right!
It's fogging up.
Hey! Get out here!
Well, well. Found us already?
I figured we'd run into you sometime.
You guys heard the same information we did, didn't you?
Whatever do you mean?
White girl, where?!
She had some things to do.
So, what do you want to do?
It could be fun to fight it out right here.
I don't want to sink to the bottom of the ocean with you guys.
I especially don't want you putting a hole in this boat with your magic!
That depends on what you do!
Come forth, ruler that controls...
The Commander!
There! Found island!
Want to land?
Yes!
Dragoons?
They look like it, but I don't think they are.
What?!
Kraken?!
Damn monster!
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
yoroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
Only because the time has come to take off my armor
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
kono inochi kono ai mo
This life and this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
Father's fortune, on island?
Fredrica, moment before landing, crash!
Separated from her!
Here, where? Fortune, where?
Return safely, possible?
The Writhing Island
Next time: "The Writhing Island".