doushiyou
What should I do?
anata ni deau made no watashi wasurechatta wa
I've forgotten what I was like before I met you.
kaze wa hoho wo naderu
The wind caresses my cheeks.
lullaby of birdland
Lullaby of Birdland
sakamichi keri nagara
As we run down the slope,
tayorinai kage wa nobiru
our faint shadows trail behind us.
owaranai natsuyasumi mitai ne
It's like a neverending summer break, isn't it?
pool ni shinobikonderu kibun
I feel like sneaking into the pool.
nee fuku no mama oyogou yo haneru
Yeah, let's swim with our clothes on. Jump in!
shougekiteki yuuwaku spiral
An overwhelming spiral of temptation,
kono mune wo tsukisasu beat wa strange
this beat that pierces my heart is so strange.
sore wa potto moete kieteshimau no
And it disappears after a short-lived spark.
sanzan na hibi mo joutou dress up
Even on the worst days, I dress up nice
swing shiteru high na speed surround
and dance to the swing that quickly surrounds me.
sore wa nante iu dance tomaranai yo
Say, what is this dance? I can't stop.
ikanaide mimi ni karamitsuite mou hanarenai yo
Don't leave me. It's stuck in my head, and I can't get it out.
melody wa
The melody...
koi mitai da
is like love.
I don't like any of this.
This sun beating down on you from the moment you wake up...
These students without a thought in their heads...
And having to hike up this steep slope from now on just to get to school...
It all makes me want to throw up.
NISHIMI KAORU
Joining us today, all the way from Yokosura, is Nishimi Kaoru-kun.
It seems he was the top of his class at his previous school.
I hope all of you study just as hard as him.
NISHIMI KAORU
I'm Nishimi. Nice to meet you.
Yokosuka?
Isn't that pretty far?
I'm used to this routine. But...
He looks like a real bookworm...
Spoiled rich kid...
Their unreserved stares...
Their Kyushu dialect that I can't even follow...
This is the most memorable welcome I've received yet.
Nishimi-kun. Nishimi-kun!
Have you decided which club you're gonna join?
Are you interested in radios?
Look at those losers, Maruo!
Two four-eyed bookworm runts!
They're made for each other!
S-Sorry. Because of me, they picked on you too.
Infantile creeps like them can't do anything unless they're in a pack.
I'm not interested in them.
Nishimi-kun...
I'm not interested in radios either.
Nishimi-kun, just one thing...
It's not a good idea to mess with the guy who sits behind me.
He's a notorious thug that even the teacher can't handle.
His name is Kawabuchi, and if he zeros in on you,
it's all over.
Oh, no. Just thinking about it makes me feel nauseous.
Nishimi-san...
Nishimi-san?
I'm the class representative, Mukae Ritsuko.
I was instructed to show you around the school during the lunch break.
It's nice to meet you.
I... don't feel sick anymore.
So the gymnasium is over there.
And the infirmary is in this building...
A-Are you okay, Nishimi-san?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Whoops! It slipped outta my hand!
Sorry 'bout that!
What's this?
Who's that?
Never seen him before...
Um... Mukae-san, where's the roof?
I've moved from school to school ever since first grade.
If something unexpected happened, I would lose my balance,
and even minor stress would trigger nausea.
But one time, I found a place at school where I could regain my bearings.
That's right. If I can just get to the roof...
What's this?
You finally...
...came for me?
Who the hell are you?
Why are you holdin' my hand?
You're the one that grabbed my hand!
I get it... You're the key burglar, huh?
In that case, I ain't gonna hold back.
Are you Sentaro?
Is this what you're lookin' for?
Then you goons are the thieves, huh?
The roof belongs to us third-year smokers!
W-Wait!
I want the key to the roof.
A wimp like you better get the hell outta here!
You want the key that badly?
I-I want it!
Hold this for me.
H-Hey! Are you all right?!
Come on, get a hold of yourself!
How reckless can you be, going up against three third-years?
This is what you wanted, right?
Can I really have it?
Yeah, here...
For 100,000.
Don't tell me you thought I'd give it to you for nothin'.
I put my ass on the line gettin' it.
100,000 is cheap.
Dammit!
Well, I'm goin' home.
Come to think of it, I didn't even go to class once today.
A city boy like that's got no common ground with us country boys.
I can't believe you, Sentaro! You got into another fight?!
It's just some scratches.
You... Hey!
Rikko, who's that?
I'm not gonna answer a guy who does nothin' but fight.
Maruo! Talk.
H-He's a new transfer student, Nishimi Kaoru-kun.
He's supposed to be rich and a real brainiac...
Oh?
Later, Maruo!
Hi there, rich boy.
From now on, your name is "Bon."
Let's you and me be chums, eh?
Sentaro's got a new target.
It's curtains for him.
I feel sorry for him.
Oh, no... I feel sick again...
Sorry. I've got a favor to ask...
Huh?
100,000 is impossible, but could you lend me the key this once?
Oh, this?
But right now it's...
Hey! It's comin' down cats 'n dogs!
There's no problem if I take an umbrella!
Sounds like a blast! I'm comin' too!
What the hell?
This ain't much fun at all.
Of course not.
I'm not up here to have fun.
Then why bother comin' up here?
If you're bored, you can always go back.
Nah.
Class ain't my scene.
Don't follow me!
You're giving me the creeps!
This feels great.
Bon, you should take a shower too!
Leave me alone!
᠎What are you scared of?
Nothin' good has ever come from fear.
Let yourself get a little wet!
What happened?!
You're both...
Geez...
Giving me trouble to no end...
We're going straight to the infirmary, so you can borrow a towel!
Oh, that's right. I'll get your gym clothes!
I'll meet you there!
Is that... jazz?
What, you can tell?
Well, sort of...
I play piano.
Classical music, though...
Classical, huh? What a drag.
Sorry for the wait.
Huh? Where's the nurse?
Looks like she's out.
Nishimi-san,
I didn't notice with your glasses on,
but you have a really pretty face.
W-What...
Oh, is it rude to call a man "pretty"?
I meant "handsome."
N-No, I'm not...
What are you doing?!
I'm a human hair dryer!
Sentaro!
There he goes again, bein' scared.
What a fraidy cat!
I'm not scared!
Oh yeah?
How could I be afraid anymore?
After all...
that rain felt way better than I imagined.
It's weird.
Even with everyone staring at me, I can breathe normally.
What kind of magic is this?
That's amazing, Dad!
Being able to play the piano, even though you're a sailor...
Kaoru, I'm going to be away again for quite a while.
Be a good boy while I'm gone, okay?
When I play the piano, I can forget all of the bad stuff
and the loneliness from Dad being away.
Don't worry, Kaoru.
Your uncle in Kyushu has a huge grand piano.
Dad... I don't want a grand piano.
What I want is...
Oh, Kaoru-kun.
You're up pretty early today, huh?
You wanna play the piano?
Go ahead.
I'd like to hear a tune that'd wake me up.
But playing this early—
But I wanna hear it right now!
I'll take responsibility, so please!
Please, please, please!
All right, fine.
Dad...
Excuse me? What do you think you're doing?
Playing the piano at this hour...
Don't you have any sense?
I'm sorry, Aunt.
Mariko-chan—
See?
This is why I told you to stop.
Putting the blame on someone else...
I guess it's difficult for a father to raise a child alone.
Although it's your mother who's responsible, abandoning the both of you.
Nishimi-san...
Mukae-san...
Sentaro didn't come today, huh?
Are you lonely without Sentaro here?
Sorry.
I wasn't able to comprehend that question.
I'll be quite pleased if he sees fit to extend his absence.
I-I see...
It looked to me like you two were hitting it off.
Everyone else is afraid of Sentaro,
but you act normally in front of him.
I bet you and Sentaro could become buddies, Nishimi-san.
Mukae-san...
Give me a break with that smile.
Really, as his childhood friend, I can guarantee it.
Childhood friend?
So that's why you're so casual with each other's names.
Oh, you can call me by my name too, Nishimi-san.
And then maybe I'll call you... "Kaoru-san."
Kaoru-san, Kaoru-san, Kaoru-san...
Wh-What is this echoing?
Sorry I said that without asking.
If you don't like it...
No, it's fine! I don't mind it at all.
Oh, that's right... Ri... chan...
Yes?
Do you happen to know of a record shop in town that sells classical music?
Records?
We've got tons of records at my place!
You should come over!
You know what I really mean by inviting you over...
Kaoru-san.
I-I think things are moving too fast.
Is this how Kyushu girls behave?
This is our shop.
And this is my father!
Fath...
M-My name is Nishimi Kaoru.
Your daughter has been very kind...
The classical records are over on that shelf, Kaoru-san.
Right.
What kind of records are you looking for?
Well, piano music.
I play the piano myself, you see.
You play the piano?!
Oh, it's not a big deal...
Come with me!
Ritsuko!
Outsiders aren't allowed in there.
Dad,
Kaoru-san is a good friend of mine and Sentaro.
Sen's?
No, I'm not his friend, just a...
Come on, go in.
Go ahead.
What is this?
What the hell are you doin' here?!
Th-That's what I want to ask you!
Rikko! We've got an intruder!
Listen to this, Sentaro!
Kaoru-san says he can play piano!
Yeah, I know, I know.
But bet you anything it's just rich kid, stuffed shirt classical stuff.
Jazz is the only music for me.
Kaoru-san...
Kaoru-san?
Say, Kaoru-san, go on and play the piano!
Oh, I don't...
Rikko,
only jazz is allowed in here!
If it's the piano you want, I'll play it.
Oh, I know this piece...
I can't hear any more. It's like this.
Wrong!
That ain't even close!
What are you talking about?!
I played it exactly right!
There wasn't any swing!
If you play it without feelin', it ain't jazz to me!
Say, I'd love to hear you two do a session together!
Hah?!
Nah, Rikko. That's a no-go.
This guy doesn't get jazz at all, and he's got no sense for it.
A little practice, and playing that'll be a cinch!
Thank you for having me over.
Um, Kaoru-san!
Come back again, okay?
Ricchan, do you know the name of the tune he was playing on the piano?
Um...
The only thing Sen can play on the piano is the intro to this.
Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers' "Moanin'."
I'd like this, please.
Wasn't he here to buy classical music?
Yeah.
I don't know why...
...but his drums just wouldn't stop thundering in my head.
Kaoru-san?
Wh-What?
Aren't you walking strange?
Really? This is how I always walk.
Ow!
Rikko! Bon! See ya'!
You're running down this slope that I hate so much like it's nothing...
What can you see beyond the hill?
Is it an outlook I've never seen before?
ano sakamichi de kimi wo matteita
I've been waiting for you on that slope.
houkago no yakusoku ni
The promise made after school
tooku nijimu sayonara
blurred into the distance as a goodbye.
yowakute ibitsu de sugu ni kowaresana
I seemed to be weak,
ano koro no boku mie
warped, and frail back then.
chiisana tsubasa wo kimi ga kuretanda
But you gave me these small wings.
yuuyami kashi no sora ni
In this twilight sky's visibility,
kasukana hikari sagashiteiru
I keep on searching for that faint light.
kimi ga suki dato suki dato ietanara
And I wanted to tell you that I love you.
kyoukasho no sumi ni kaita tegami wa
I wrote a letter in the corner of the textbook
itsumade mo todokazu ni
that will never reach its destination
ano hi no mama
and remained as it was back then.