If a monster really is attacking Japan,
will they give us permission to engage?
We'd be goners if this was a monster movie.
We're just there for it to kill
before the Giant of Light shows up.
That's not funny.
Well, we'll soon know for sure.
Take this!
It's no use.
It's reforming itself.
Its regenerative power is unbelievable...
It's taking all our efforts just
to keep it from coming ashore.
I can't reach Caster like this.
This is amazing! Amazing!
Seriously amazing, Mister!
God is with us...
God is with us!
Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
What a disaster.
In the Grail War's long history,
there has never been a failure like this.
According to eyewitness reports,
the Mion River area is engulfed by a thick fog,
but large numbers of bystanders are beginning to gather.
This is now beyond our ability to control.
We'll have to request aid from the Mage's Association.
Where is Tokiomi-kun?
My master is heading there with Archer in tow.
Kirei.
I will handle the cover-up.
You go and assist Tokiomi-kun with all haste.
Understood, Father.
What a hideous sight to behold.
They may be mongrels, but they're
still supposed to be famous warriors.
Yet they still can't take care of that
piece of filth despite working together?
This is depressing to watch.
Don't you agree, Tokiomi?
We must eliminate that monster before more witnesses see it.
The Tohsaka family name is at stake.
My king, that pest of a monster is tearing apart your gardens.
I implore you to execute it.
That would be a gardener's work.
Or are you insinuating that my Noble Phantasm is nothing more than a gardener's shovel?
Not at all!
But as you can see, the others are unable to handle it themselves.
This is an excellent chance to
display the power of a true Hero.
I beg you...
Whoa!
That's ridiculous...
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I can't bear to look at that nauseating thing any longer.
No...
King of Heroes, please wait!
Tokiomi, I've already sacrificed four of my swords and spears for you.
Now that they have touched that thing, I no longer desire their return.
Do not impinge further on my generosity.
You are the only Hero capable of defeating that monstrosity!
Given how rapidly it regenerates, it must be completely destroyed with a single attack!
And the only thing capable of that,
King of Heroes, is your Sword of Rupture—
How dare you!
You would have me draw my greatest treasure, Ea, here?!
Know your place, Tokiomi!
Such remarks to a king are punishable by death!
I could use a Command Spell, but that would severely damage my relationship with the King of Heroes.
Furthermore, Father Risei and I devised this entire
plan to restore my lost Command Spell to begin with.
Why did everything have to backfire?
Damn it...
What's... that?
There's a strange light at six o'clock, too.
That's no helicopter.
Is it a UFO or something?
Control to Diablo-1. What is your situation?
My situation...
Um... Well...
I'll drop altitude and get a little closer!
W-Wait, Kobayashi!
Get back here, Diablo-2!
If I get closer, I should be able to see what it—
Kobayashi?!
Kobayashi!
Would you look at that...
I-It ate the plane...
Control to Diablo-1!
What the hell is happening up there?
Report!
Eyes...
There are eyes...
Eyes everywhere!
Eyes? What do you mean by eyes?
Is it going to eat me too?
First Lieutenant Ougi!
Diablo-1, engaging!
W-Wait, Ougi!
What's happ—
I'll kill it before it eats me.
I'll avenge Kobayashi.
I'll hit it with everything I have!
Berserker?
What is he doing here?
Fool!
Stay down!
What a time for him to show up.
That's...
Oh? It's the mad dog again.
Interesting.
My king, I shall engage his Master.
Very well.
Go and play with him.
Good luck, then.
Dogs like you should stay flat on the ground.
Yet you dare to fly in the heavens, where the king dwells?
How arrogant of you, mongrel!
Impudent brat...
Fascinating.
I haven't enjoyed myself like this for a long time.
For a mere beast, you do keep me quite entertained.
You've certainly changed for the worse, Matou Kariya.
You abandoned the path of magic,
but were still drawn to the Grail.
And now, you've returned looking like that.
Your disgraceful behavior
reflects very poorly on the Matou.
Tohsaka Tokiomi, I have one question for you.
Why did you give Sakura to Zouken?
What?
Is that something you should
be concerned about right now?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
There is nothing to say.
I simply wanted a bright future for my daughter.
What?
Any Mage with two children faces a painful dilemma.
Only one may inherit the family secrets.
The other must fall to the rabble.
My wife's womb was too bountiful.
Both Rin and Sakura were born with a rare level of potential.
Both daughters needed the
protection a Mage clan can provide.
To destroy the potential held by one for the sake of the other's future...
Would any father desire that kind of tragedy?
The rabble...
The mother and daughters I saw that day...
He simply dismisses them as rabble?!
To fulfill my wish that both their talents be developed, I had no choice but to send one for adoption.
That's why the Matou family's request was like a blessing from heaven.
As a clan that knows of the Grail, their odds of reaching the Root are that much greater.
All Magi are born with power,
and they will all someday attain even greater power.
Even before they are aware of this fate, the responsibility lies in their blood.
That's what it means to be born a Mage's child.
If I cannot attain it, Rin will.
And even if Rin cannot, Sakura will.
They will carry on the wishes of the Tohsaka family.
You...
You'd make the two sisters fight each other?!
Even if that really happens,
my descendants will still be happy.
What?
Glory will go to whoever wins.
The loser will rest, knowing it went to the family.
Could a more joyous battle exist?
You're insane!
It wasn't even worth the explanation.
Not for one oblivious to the nobility of magic...
...let alone a traitor who turned his back on it.
Shut up—
I won't forgive any of you.
You disgusting Magi...
I'll kill you.
Zouken and you, both!
I will kill...
...every last one of you!
You refused to carry on the Matou line,
so the magic of the family went to Sakura.
I should be thanking you instead.
Even so...
I cannot forgive you.
Your weakness, in running from the responsibility of your blood.
Your baseness, in failing to see anything wrong with doing so.
Matou Kariya shames the paths of magic.
Now that we meet again,
what else could I do but kill you?
Shut the hell up...
You inhuman monster!
No.
Taking responsibility for yourself is the first condition for humanity.
Anyone unable to do even that...
...is nothing but a dog, Kariya.
Insects, devour him.
Devour him to death!
Get 'em, Mister Bluebeard!
Crush 'em! Kill 'em!
This whole place is God's toy box!
Saber!
I'm in your debt, Saber!
I can say goodbye to boredom.
I don't have to go out of my way to kill people anymore.
I can just sit back and watch people die.
Crushed...
Torn apart...
Smashed...
Eaten!
They'll die, and die, and die!
I'll see all kinds of guts and gore I've never seen before...
Every day, every day...
Around the world! Everywhere!
Forever, never endi—
It stopped?
Huh?
Hey, what was that?
It's so pretty...
I see...
I guess that's why I never noticed.
Sometimes you can't see what's right in front of you.
The thing I was searching for...
...was in my own guts...
...this whole time...
Ryuunosuke?
I've finally found you.
I had been looking for you forever...
What the hell?
If you were inside me...
...you could've just told me.
Ryuunosuke, my Master.
You have died and left me all alone.
But don't worry, Ryuunosuke.
I, Gilles de Rais, will fulfill my promise to you.
Behold, Ryuunosuke!
A gift to see you to the next world...
The greatest COOL!
I've shot down the man we
believed to be Caster's Master.
Looks like we were right.
While the Servants are dealing with the monster,
shall we eliminate our next target?
Wait, Maiya.
That's no mere monster.
It's an immortal creature, infinitely regenerative.
It will reach the shore before it vanishes.
If it starts feeding, it's all over.
With a new source of mana,
Caster can sustain materialization.
And the damage would spread.
The Holy Grail War itself may need to be abandoned.
That's correct.
But how do we defeat an immortal monster?
Our only option is to exterminate it in one go.
To destroy every last piece of it in a single strike.
We need a Noble Phantasm not for destroying people or armies, but fortified structures.
Saber has one of those.
However, Lancer's curse leaves her unable to use it.
I think...
I'll have them show us this chivalry they're so proud of.
Episode 14
The Mion River Battle
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
This light...
Such pointless struggling.
The undefeated king sings aloud the
name of the miracle she holds in her hands.
It is too painful to look upon.
Is he trying to kill himself?
We must stop him here!
I'm counting on you, Saber.
Next Episode
Golden Brilliance