saa miterasshai mitsuba no odemashi da
Come one, come all, the three leaves are taking the stage!
Three
Leaves,
S
Three
Leaves,
a
Three
Colors
n
Three
Colors
s
Three
Colors
h
Three
Colors
a
Three
Colors
S
a
Colors
n
y
Colors
o
u
ohayou tte donburi sanpai
My wake-up call is three bowls of rice
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
joshiryoku nante gohan to issho ni
I'm munching down
all my feminine charm,
mushamushamushamusha tabechaitai
along with my food!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
chochochotto matte taiiku wa nigate
W-W-Wait for me,
I'm not good at sports!
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
ii koto kiita jakuten mikke
So that's your weakness!
Good to know,
gomennasai
but sorry for finding out!
hontou wa tomodachi to issho ni waiwai shite mitai
I really want to be boisterous and have fun with friends
tawai mo nai hanashi da to ka
Getting lost in silly conversations
koibana to ka shitemitari nanka shichattari shite
Chatting about love and relationships
nee nande tomodachi ga dekinai no?
Say, why can't you make friends?
chokkyuu desu wa ne
You came right out and asked?!
gouman de takabisha de et cetera
You're haughty, arrogant, et cetera
iitai houdai ne
You two never quit!
mitsuba ga daibousou
The three leaves are on a rampage,
dare ni mo tomerarenai
and there's nobody who can stop them!
Why is Nishiyama here?
Why is Hayama here?
Hayama is moved to tears?
Were those flashes of my life?
She's still alone.
That's...
Here!
issei no mae mitekou
One, two, keep your eyes forward!
mae mae miteru
Keep your eyes on the road ahead
kibun soukai da sou desu kai
I'm feeling great. Oh, are you?
sannin yoreba monju no chie
Three heads are better than one!
hora jissai yottara kashimashii dake
We're such a noisy bunch when we all get together
hora going my way
Everything's going my way,
susumesou my way
and it's gonna keep going my way
zensoku zenshin wo tsukareishon
Let's go full steam ahead
watashi shijou saidai saikyou no
I'm living the best days of my life,
chotto kawatta nanameue no nichijou da
though they're a bit peculiar and somewhat odd
sotto shitoite tsuttsuitara sakan ga batsugun
Give 'em a poke, and they'll grow and grow
Futaba
Miss Youko
Teru
kitto kore ga joshikousei no
I'm sure that this is a
futsuu no ippanteki na school life
normal, regular, high school girl's life!
Three Leaves,
Three Colors
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky
Cat
Now, now, no fighting.
Let's all be friends.
Nishiyama, your drink's ready.
Oh, okay!
Kono's gotten so big.
She's become
quite the troublemaker.
Welcome!
Is a counter seat okay?
Sure!
Wha—?
What?!
You've Got Them Hooked
Teru!
Are you awake?
Let's go out!
Central Shopping Plaza
I found a shop that you might like.
Oh, like a boutique?
Ah, right here.
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
I heard it just opened.
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
Let's go in!
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
CAT CAFÉ
Tricky Cat
Cat Cafe
N-No!
That'd be cheating on Bel!
I can't do it!
You've already gone
to other places like this!
Tricky Cat
Here's a coupon.
You were planning
on coming here!
I've heard about this place.
Jeez, I wish you'd told me
we were coming here.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
My phone camera's not that great.
Welcome! Is a counter seat okay?
Sorry...
Why is Nishiyama here?
Why is Hayama here?
Just my luck.
She's going to ruin
my cat café experience.
Oh, isn't this your friend?
H-Hello!
Nice to see you again.
This is just my classmate
Nishiyama.
Oh, you were the one who adopted
the last of the kittens Teru found.
Oh, yes.
Hey, hey, what did you name her?
Oh yeah, I never asked.
Her name is...
Ours is named "Bel"
after "Beelzebub,"
because he was swarming with flies
when we took him in.
Bel
I gave her a name
that will bring her a long life.
Eternal
"Eternal," or "El" for short.
El
What?!
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just obvious you used a dictionary
to come up with "Eternal."
By the way,
the names of the kitties here are
"Princess Konohana Sakuya,"
"Lakshmi,"
"Viracocha,"
and "Teutates."
That's a little much.
All their names are so refined.
Think about it, Nishiyama.
You'd have to use those names
at the vet or out in public.
Anyway, I didn't come here
to talk to you.
Right, Mii? I missed you so much!
Oh, Nishiyama.
Thanks for always stopping by.
Hello!
Mii is here today.
I wondered why
she wasn't here last time.
Sorry to make you worry.
What a pro.
You can tell she's a regular.
She wasn't feeling well.
Oh, really?
Not like I care!
I'm not angry at all!
I didn't know Nishiyama
goes to cat cafés.
It sounds like
something she'd enjoy.
I wonder if I can get her
to send me those pictures.
Since you just went to the cat café,
maybe you don't need this.
Don't need what?
A ticket for the petting zoo,
Animal Town.
What?!
I definitely need that!
Okay, okay.
Animal Town
Free Admission
I got it from Sakura's mom,
and I thought you'd want it more than I do.
Wow, thanks!
It's good for two people.
When should we go?
What?
It's good until Sunday.
We have three people,
so we can split the last ticket.
I'm not going
I don't really like animals...
What?!
And I have work.
Wait, what?!
Oh, you can go with your sister!
With my sister?
All right!
Let's have some fun!
H-Hey!
Wow, so cute!
Be gentle with the little ones!
That one's cute.
But this one's cute too!
Calm down.
Adore them one at a time!
That one is too!
Big Sis!
I think I'd be so tired
from dealing with her
that I wouldn't be able
to enjoy myself.
Oh yeah!
Animal Town?
Yup,
Animal Town
Free Admission
Miss Youko and I can't go.
How about it?
What, really?!
Hey!
Why are you inviting
Nishiyama?
Don't you think she'd like it?
You went to the cat café together.
We didn't go together!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Animal Town
Morning.
Morning!
I didn't think Nishiyama was going
to come because of Hayama.
Her love of animals
triumphed in the end.
Kondou!
You were worried too?
Y-Yeah.
You know how they are.
They went in!
Let's follow them!
Animal Town
Welcome
Welcome!
They're still at the entrance...
Okay, over here.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Oh, you're in charge of sales.
Do you always work here?
When are they going in?
It's been ten minutes already.
Nishiyama, you'll run out
of memory at this rate!
I really don't want
to stay with Hayama.
We can split up
or something from here.
First, I'll go check out the nearby small animals,
then go see the dog show.
Then to the cat room, the small dog petting corner,
the animal show, and the horse park.
Okay, Hayama.
We can split up from here.
Oh, really?
No way.
Was she planning to come here too?
Jump and catch!
Jack did it!
Wow, that was amazing!
Hayama is moved to tears?
Even though human kids seem to get worse every year, dogs are so amazing!
Honestly, dogs are better!
Don't put it like that!
I guess they're
going around together.
Will they be okay?
What if they end up fighting?
Well, I don't think Hayama
will get angry today.
Really?
She vowed
to exercise self-discipline.
Self-discipline?
To broaden her experiences
by getting to know all kinds of people.
Freedom from worldly desires
or something.
I see...
I don't really get it.
But...
...if Nishiyama keeps trying
to pick fights with her...
There! Over here!
Wow, Nishiyama.
You've got them hooked.
Oh?
Well, it comes naturally
if you have a cat.
Maybe you're just not good at it?
Yeah, I suppose I'm not.
Hayama, are you drinking juice?
I'm being healthy and drinking tea.
Juice has too much sugar.
You're good, Nishiyama!
I should follow your example.
Doggie
Petting
Building
That's a Weimaraner.
In the U.S., it's known as
the "Grey Ghost."
You didn't even know that?
What an animal buff!
You're amazing, Nishiyama.
Aren't I?
Huh?
I don't know why,
but she's in a good mood today.
It's almost like she's
another person entirely.
N-Nishiyama's going
at full throttle!
I think the dam's
about to burst...
Nishiyama!
Today was more fun than I expected.
I suppose I could thank you,
Hayama.
Nishiyama...
Wh-What?
That Hayama!
I was nice enough
to go with her and she... she...
Will you cheer me up?
Thanks, El.
How was Animal Town?
It was fun!
I want to go again.
And Nishiyama?
How was she?
Same as usual.
She got angry and left
halfway through, though.
What?
The petting attractions
and shows were fun too.
Maybe she left because I said it was so funny
how she gets carried away with herself.
Those two just don't get along.
Quite right.
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Three
Leaves,
Colors
Sansha Sanyou
Stuffed Hut
But you know, I really thought
it was a good opportunity!
For what?
You know, when Hayama and Nishiyama
went to Animal Town together?
What...?
I thought it was a good chance for them
to understand each other better.
Futaba...
And maybe they'd get to a point
where it's not so awkward in class anymore.
Oh...
You two like the same things.
You should be able to get along.
I seem to recall
giving you the same advice.
I finished the
Mega Ogre Omelet Rice!
And time's up!
I lost...
I couldn't finish it.
You haven't won just yet,
Futaba Odagiri!
I won't forget this!
Stuffed Hut
Thanks for coming!
Can you get along with him
since you have similar interests?
Sorry, not happening.
Hayama!
Let's start a band!
Skip to the point next time.
It's the autumn of the arts.
What's going on?
Oh!
Miss Youko,
you should join our band!
Nishiyama, Kondou!
You look like
you want to be in a band!
What?!
Big Sis...
River of Three Crossings
I cannot cross,
But still the tears trail down
My, what a wonderful voice.
I disappear with the foam
Nom, nom, nom...
Oh, I feel dizzy.
She's slightly out of tune.
River of Three Crossings
in the beautiful spring
I want to pick that flower.
Yamaji, be my ladder.
There!
Get it, Yuu!
River of Three Crossings
that Kou sings
Nom, nom, nom...
Miss Youko!
Wake up, Miss Youko!
Thank goodness!
You're awake, Miss Youko.
You scared me,
just fainting like that.
Were those flashes of my life?
That was "River of Three Crossings"
by Kou Hayama.
So grim!
The River of Three Crossings
is like the river Styx, right?
People tend to start singing
without thinking about it.
Like when you're alone
or trying to calm down a baby.
Nishiyama, you always sing songs
for Eternal in your room, don't you?
I do not!
Oh, I want to hear!
I said I don't do that!
Nishiyama! Nishiyama!
Hey, cut it out!
Nishiyama, yeah! Nishiyama, woo!
Nishiyama, yeah! Nishiyama, go!
Nishiyama got super mad
yesterday, huh?
Come on, I feel sorry for her.
You can't say that after
what happened at Animal Town.
Oh?
That's...
It's Kondou.
She's usually with Nishiyama.
It's strange to see her alone.
She's still alone.
Did she have a fight with Nishiyama
over what happened yesterday?
She's all alone, even though
she's usually with her friend.
Come on, bread is better.
Rice is the best!
Kondou...
Is it okay if Kondou
joins us for lunch today?
When I saw her alone,
I couldn't help but invite her.
I don't mind.
You don't have to worry about that nobody
who gets angry over such trivial matters.
Huh?
Miss Youko is being
excessively welcoming.
She understands
what it's like to be a loner.
What?
Nishiyama's not a nobody!
She's actually a really nice
and hard-working girl.
She's just intolerant of others.
Anyway, it's lunchtime. Let's eat.
I see.
So you've known Nishiyama
since elementary school.
Yup.
We were in the same group
during a field trip as third-years.
She was our group leader, and she helped me out
when I was a little slow on things.
And she's liked having
leadership roles ever since?
Exactly!
And she wasn't always
like she is now.
You know how things don't always go
the way you want in high school.
Someone's always in her way here.
Oh no, is it my fault?
Nishiyama could get along so nicely
with Hayama if she weren't so irritable.
They even like the same things.
If she at least acted reasonably nice,
like Hayama does,
she could be
the next class representative.
Huh?
Hey—
Same goes for you, Nishikawa.
What?
Quit being so prickly and snobby
and talk to your classmates already.
You're pretty, so I'm sure
there are people who admire you.
Y-You think so?
Yeah!
When pretty girls aren't friendly,
people won't want to approach them.
I can't tell if she's
complimenting, belittling,
or just plain insensitive.
So why not try harder
to be social?
R-Right...
Thanks for today!
Oh, it was nothing.
Futaba Odagiri!
You beat my brother
in a challenge again, didn't you?!
I didn't mean for it
to be a competition.
And you're always eating lunch
with Nishikawa, just the three of you!
Huh?
Oh, I'm kinda special.
Special?!
She's an interesting one.
Like you have room to talk.
At the ramen place, you've gotta get tons of veggies, dumplings, and a pork rice bowl, right?
Um, would you come
with me for a bit?
Oh?
Let's see. You're...
Hello, ma'am!
Ah, Nishiyama's tactless friend.
Kondou is here to buy a cake
Nishiyama likes so they can make up.
Make up?
Oh, I know!
Here!
What in the world is that?
Something that Nishiyama likes.
Oh!
That's Nishiyama's uniform
from when she worked here.
I said cake, did I not?
That's funny.
I'm glad you're amused.
Oh, ma'am, you used to be
one of Nishikawa's servants, right?
Yes.
So Nishikawa
really was a rich girl.
I guess that's where her intimidating,
overbearing tendencies come from.
Kondou is pretty amazing.
She's as scary as a final boss.
I really do admire you.
Huh? What about me?
She should be apologizing
after getting mad
about something so small,
but you're bringing her an apology gift.
Uh, Miss Youko,
I think you misunderstand.
Huh?
Kondou wasn't alone today
because they had a fight.
Nishiyama was absent
because she's sick.
What?!
I-I just thought...
See?
Serina Nishiyama
No subject
How are you feeling?
Are you lonely sleeping
at home all day?
Well, it's important
to rest up.
Feel better~!
I sent her a bunch of texts
asking how she's doing.
A-All this time, I thought...
It's all right!
Don't worry about it.
It was kind of your fault too.
Asako Kondou
What happened?
She suddenly stopped
texting me after lunch.
She sent so many in the morning,
I couldn't sleep.
Thanks. You're so nice, El.
"E" in "Eternal" is because
you're extra cute
"T" is for your tremendous, overflowing love
She's really singing a song
dedicated to Eternal.
So there actually is such a song.
When should we go in?
Let's listen until the end.
"R" is for reaching beyond hyperspace
It's such a nice song.
What?!
"N" is for the nameless blooming flower
"L" is for...
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The vicious class rep,
the poor girl who lives on bread crusts,
and the walking black hole.
Their days lived in their own colors
are so entertaining!
Isn't it wonderful?
And now, please enjoy
"Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
nakami ga makkuro demo
Even if it's turned black inside
zeitaku dekinakutemo
Even if I can't be extravagant
ryou ga ookutemo
Even if there's too much to handle
sannin dakara tabechaou
Three's a crowd, so let's eat!
youryou yo ga kashikoku
I'm not wasting electricity at night
takumashiku ikitemasu wa
I'm leading a strong and healthy life
onaka ippai no mainichi nan desu
Every day, I'm eating 'til I'm full!
egao ni nareru mono
Things that make me smile?
gohan, okane, koko de wa ienai
Food! Money! And things I can't say
shiawase datte sansha sanyou
We're a happy bunch, living in our own colors
omou made tanoshimou, hachamecha na
Let's have fun and make silly memories
hora guuchoki parade, sannin atsumareba
When we're together, this Rock Scissors Parade
janken wa, aiko de, eien ni owaranai
Will continue forever in just the same way
hajimatta parade, kyousei sanka desu
This parade we've embarked on is wonderful
ichi kakeru san no kotae shiritai nara
If you want to know the answer to one times three
nee koko ni oide
Then come on over here
It's Asako...
...and Serina's
next-episode preview.
I've had enough!
Just do whatever!
Oh? Then why don't you sing us
a character song or something?
What?!
Character song! Character song!
clap
I-I guess I have no choice.
Next
Time:
Curry Is Better
Two Days Later
Next
Time: