Alright, look over here!
Everyone looks so pretty...
It's because they're edited.
Wait, really??
Oh yeah, you're right...
Your nose looks a lot straighter.
Hey, stop inspecting my face!!
Let's leave the pictures for
after we sign the contract.
Okay!
12: THE SKIES DARKEN ONCE MORE
They're at their job?
I wish you had informed me.
This is the last shift Rupa and
Tomo have at their store.
They agreed to help them out one last time
given how long they've worked there.
So they had no other choice, huh?
My apologies.
One of the CEO's whims.
Putting our brand on things like water.
Togenashi Togeari Water™?
Just hearing that makes my stomach turn.
Right then. All the papers are in order.
Meaning that, from today,
you are now working for our agency.
I, Miura, will serve as your agent. It's my pleasure.
The same for us too.
A pleasure to work with you.
And that's how we joined an agency.
Eh? 200,000 yen?
Yep. We get paid every 25th, I believe.
And I can... like, spend it?
Well, yeah?
It's our salary.
Wait, really?!!
You didn't read the whole contract, did you?
That also means you didn't read
the terms and conditions, huh?
It means that one day...
You'll have to star in some dirty films!
You signed so in the contract!!
Pipe down.
- B-but she said I'll have to...!
- She's just pulling your leg.
It just means that the agency
is going to take a certain cut
off of our total profits.
Merch, concerts, albums...
They get us on the map,
so if we sell it's a mutual win.
That's the gist of it, at least.
I want it.
Hm? You're unusually hesitant.
What, are you still conscious about the festival?
You really are stubborn about it.
But it's not fair!
We killed it on stage!
And yet everyone's all DD this,
DD that, DD this and that...!!
Our performance was way better!!
Like I said, pipe down!
We didn't even play on the
big stage, what did you expect?
Not to mention, for an idol band
to suddenly pull a show like that,
Of course it'll get people talking.
But we were so cool!! Why?
Hell if I know.
Well, we still had a lot of
people pull up, which is great.
- And we still got signed by an agency...
- But...
I already told you to stop
looking yourself up online.
Okay...
I get how you feel. But the
real showdown starts now.
Okay!
Don't act like you weren't conscious too!
- Ouch!
GYUDON
Here.
Your contracts.
And... here's a little gift!
What?
Be honest for once and take it!
Can I take your orders?
- A medium, please.
- Huh? But we promised to have a hotpot after!
- A beer and a medium, please.
- Eh? You're drinking?!
Worry not. I'll drink at night too.
Fine. A medium for me too.
Of course, coming right up.
I'm feeling nostalgic here...
This is where I first treated you to food.
Oh, really?
She walked here from Tokyo for like four hours,
couldn't get her keys,
which led to this and that...
You've got no sense of direction.
Thank you. Beni Shouga shall not be forgotten.
Let's all spread the good word!
Wait, that's not it! It's just that back then...
Tomo-chan.
Good job making it this far!
Same here. Though we're just getting started.
Now then, let's start the Togenashi Togeari
went pro celebration party! Can I get a...
Huh?
They called saying they're still
wrapping up work, they'll come later.
Oh, really?
B-busy till the v-very end, huh?
Ouch...
I never realized how tough a squash is...
You learn something new everyday.
Ah, finally spoken like a rich kid again.
Oh come on, I'm not rich at all!
I've told you before, right?
What's wrong?
You know, I'm wondering if maybe you were right.
Remember when you first came
and taught me all those things?
It was... a bit of a shock for me.
It made me realize a lot of things I didn't know.
It made me realize that I couldn't
do anything on my own.
Think you've learned a thing or two?
I think so, yes.
Not the guitar, though.
You sure you have no regrets?
I think so. I want to
continue with everyone else.
Sure, sure.
Sorry for the delay!
We kept  you waiting.
Brrr!
How's it colder than outside?
Oh! Beer! Beer! Beer!
Sheesh...
By the way, I finished the band logo!
Cheers!
Hey, who gave you permission to start drinking?
We haven't even started eating! Manners!
They're not listening.
I swear...
Should we start too?
Ugh, I guess...
Hey, did you forget already
that I like my veggies well-done?
- Me too.
- See?
Ah, pain in the ass, the both of you!
To each their own.
- Indeed.
- Shut up!
Well-cooked is definitely better.
And there they go.
Nah, it ruins it if it's all mushy.
Have you even had them well-done before?
Give it a shot!
- Eat, eat!
- Come on, eat up.
- Ow! Hot! Hot!
- Come on, let's eat it together!
- Like I said, it's still hot!
Something wrong?
Musical inspiration.
I've got the perfect title.
SOME DAYS LATER
Look at this place!
Good morning.
This is the sound engineer, Nakata-san.
I'm Nakata. A pleasure.
A pleasure working with you!
The assistant, Nakano-san.
A pleasure!
Our A.P., Tanaka-san.
I'm Tanaka.
And for marketing, Tano-san.
I'm Tano.
HUH?
I can't remember who is who...
Well, it's all part of the job.
You can tell them apart, Momoka-san?
Well, duh. Easy stuff for a
big girl like me, a working adult.
Who's the sound engineer?
Tanaka-san!
It's Nakata.
My apologies!
Stop laughing!
This song, it's the one you
jotted down the other day, right?
Yeah, I tried jotting down some lyrics...
FLOWER OF FATE
Here.
Are you done?
My apologies.
This title...
Yeah.
It's the image I have of all of us
I was wondering what should
be the topic of our first song,
But it's gotta be about us, right?
Momoka-san...
Alright, let's get it then!
Nina.
If you're serious about catching up
to DD, then put your heart into it!
Mhm!
All five of us started making a song.
OBJECTIVE!! BUDOKAN!!
BUDOKAN
I feel like we're overdoing it...
Are you sure? Sounds good to me.
We could move this verse to the beginning, I feel.
I mean, can we can, but...
You're right. Let's try redoing it.
Sorry, but given the hour
we need to call it a day.
Okay!
HEIWAJIMA STATION
Whew. We barely made it in time.
See ya later!
I'll call you later!
It's... fun, isn't it?
What is?
The present. With everyone trying to make a song together.
Just imagining that soon, we'll be able
to deliver our feelings to everyone...
It's not that easy, you know.
When delivering something, it's not a
guarantee someone will pick it up.
I'm sure we'll be alright.
I mean, look at how hard we worked for it.
We'll be alright.
Something's bothering me about this bit...
Want to listen to it again?
Please.
Huh? Where did Miura-san go?
She went out to take a call.
I'd like to hear her thoughts, could you go fetch her?
Sure!
- Ah! Miura...
- With DD?
- ...san?
- Really?
I understand. I'll call you back later.
Momoka-san was looking for you... for the song...
Did you hear what I just said?
No...
Alright...
What happened with Diamond Dust?
VALENTINE'S DAY SHOWDOWN
DD X TOGETOGE
I just received this.
A double concert, huh.
On the first day, Diamond Dust.
On the second, Togenashi Togeari.
Really? Club Cittá, that massive venue?
It feels like this was on purpose
to match the schedule of our song.
Next February, on Valentine's Day.
I see no issues.
Let them strike at us!
Please read the next page.
The band that will amass the
highest earnings and audience
Will get the rights to do the theme
song for a popular TV show.
I see...
They're setting us up.
Huh? Who?
We're gonna lose?
Why are you giving up without even trying?
- Let's give it a shot-
- Think about it.
DD's followers have more than doubled recently.
It's an arms race.
They set us up because they are guaranteed to win.
They're using us as a stepping stone to
raise DD to even higher heights.
But that's...
This case, we're fighting on the same stage, right?
So we just need to win over
the audience! Like in the festival!
Think about it.
Huh?
The trick here is that we aren't going
to be playing against the same audience.
It's a showdown, yet played as solo concerts.
So it all comes down to how
many customers we attract ourselves.
Meaning it's just a numbers game.
That's cheating...
I can't blame you for being angry.
Still, I gotta wonder what the
DD girls think about all this...
Who knows.
I bet they don't care.
At the very least that's the type
of person Hina is. The girl I know.
Someone with zero empathy
to injure anyone but herself.
Careful now, we don't want to escalate this.
What's wrong about that?
It's like in a drama, when they start arguing
And start throwing drinks
at each other and stuff...
Ah, if only you knew...
Wait, really?
- Then...
- ...nothing else but to put it to vote.
Those in favor of participating?
Those in favor of not?
I see...
We had a long talk, and we just came
to the conclusion it's too early...
We're not quite ready for this yet.
I understand.
Then, I'll let them know you declined.
My apologies.
Miura-san... what do you think?
Nina...
To be frank, I felt torn.
It's hard to think we could win,
But going up against a group as currently
famous as DD would be incredible promotion.
So...
However... if you can't at least
put up a good fight against them,
The public will remember you as nobodies.
That's what they're after, right?
To be frank, I couldn't tell you what their goal is.
Whether it's for both bands to help promote each other,
Or for one to devour the other.
I feel exhausted...
You can't trust what's too good to be true.
That's how the world of adults works.
What?
Do you still want to give it a try?
I just wonder if this is what
it'll always be like as a pro...
You're the one who chose this, Nina.
We're back.
This doesn't feel right...
Should we change that phrase
to how it was before then?
But that was no good either...
Then wouldn't it be faster
to just rewrite it from scratch?
I guess we could...
Eh? Are you sure?
Hm? Same thing from before?
Yeah. It's like... it just doesn't hit
quite right. Feels old-fashioned.
Really? It's true those
distortions are quite popular, but...
Like this?
Yep yep.
Momoka-san!
What?
I can't help but feel... you're overthinking it.
As if you were letting go of
what you first wanted to convey.
This is a song you wrote
for us, right? For TogeToge.
Then maybe it's good enough as is.
What matters the most is
wether this can become our song.
I feel that alone is all that matters.
Then, I'll be seeing you all tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me...!
Yeah?
In the end... I really want to compete against DD!
I know there's a lot of greater
circumstances surrounding this...
But we could still do our own solo concert, right?
- We can get to sing, right?
- I mean we could, but...
Then shouldn't we take the chance and sing?
And no matter the circumstances, I don't think
TogeToge should run away from an opportunity!
If we run away...
...we will have lost?
Hmm.
Do you disagree, Momoka-san?
You have to be the one to decide.
Because you're the only one here
who has a past with Diamond Dust.
Nina-san, Subaru-san, Tomo-chan...
I'm sure we all agree, right?
What will you do?
Brr... It's cold...
Really? It's pretty warm.
Actually, it's a perfectly soothing fall night.
Ah? Freaking Northerners...
Mind you, I'm the only one
here with exposed legs!
Spoken like a high schooler.
What do you even mean by that?
Unbelievable...
So this is the shrine close to your home, Nina?
Why did you bring us to a shrine at this hour?
I thought it was the perfect timing for it.
To pray to the gods, you mean?
I see.
Momoka-san, did you ever go to a
shrine with the DD girls for New Years'?
Nah, never.
I don't really have time to waste on gods.
It's not my style to pray anyway.
I see...
Still, right now we could
use any allies, even a god.
If gd actually existed.
What's wrong, Momoka-san?
You've been really weird lately.
Oh, so it's about this.
I'm just struggling with my music recently...
Liar.
I don't want you to lie to us.
I'm scared.
The more serious I get about making music,
the more I feel I'm regressing
to being who I used to be.
I'm afraid to lose everything again.
I know.
I know your suffering very well.
All of us were abandoned,
all alone in this world.
But music saved us.
Your passion continues to burn inside of me.
It's what connects me to everyone else.
Believe in this passion! In your music!
So please, believe in yourself!
I want to turn Togenashi Togeari into legend.
Let's live while sharing
the same dream. All five of us.
I want to believe there's a god of rock!
Wouldn't that be nice?
If such a god existed, what would you pray for?
What else, but "let us sell a million CDs".
Then how about ten million?
More! A hundred million!
I'm praying we can win against our rivals at DD.
Momoka-san!
What?
That's more or less it.
What do you think, everyone? Anything to fix?
I personally like it.
I agree. This feels very easy to digest.
I like it too!
I don't really tend to share what
I think of the music I edit, but...
Please do.
But as the song is right now,
I have to admit I love it.
I feel it hits all the right notes
for what you wanted.
After all these weeks working
alongside you, I must say...
You made a song only you five could.
Really?
I feel proud to have edited this.
Being able to help a band like yours...
...makes me glad to have taken this job.
Truly.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Tanaka-san!
It's Nakata.
Then, I'll keep you informed about the progress.
When will it be released online?
If all goes well, it should be out
by the start of next month.
Until then,
I... also love it.
I legitimately believe it will sell.
Miura-san!
Y-yes?
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
It's too early to thank me.
We're just getting started.
Until then,
- Call my parents
- Trash bags, batteries
- Dec 9th: After work, party!
- Jan 1st: Happy New Years'!!
- Jan 4th: Working
- Jan 6th-11th: After practice, go to Momoka's place
- Jan 19th: Do NOT miss practice <3
- Jan 22th: Praying
Brr... it's cold...
Alright...
Gods of Rock...
Please give us a billi...
I mean, at least ten thousand views!!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
103 VIEWS
What's... this...
NEXT: ROCK'N'ROLL NEVER ENDS