One day, perhaps the light of love
which shines in your eyes will fulfill
one dream of this scarred world
That's terrible!
It's impossible. It's too much for her.
But she's still made up her mind.
No!
No! It can't end up like this!
When I was a girl, I dreamed of you
Wielding something like unto ancient magic
If you give up, it's over.
I want to be by your side as, smiling, you shatter the darkness
But you can change destiny.
In my trembling hand, I grasp
Unavoidable destruction, grief... You can reject them.
the life of an innocent flower
You hold that power.
As my emotions waver,
my prayer awakens the light
Really?
Can I really do something?
Can I change what's going to happen?
Of course!
So contract with me, and become a magical girl!
It was just a dream...
Close our eyes and recall the promises we shared
Shake off the falling darkness and keep going
Somehow how I lost sight of the future I once had
Can I still see it from here?
My uneasiness welled up over and over
But somehow I cut through it and kept moving forward
The endless march of time announces a new beginning
Following my unchanging emotions, I open that sealed door!
My awakening heart rushes forth, to draw the future
No matter how tough the path ahead is, I know
a beautiful blue sky is waiting for me, so I'm not afraid
No matter what, I won't give up!
Episode 1 As if I met her in my dreams. . . . .
Good morning, Papa!
Good morning, Madoka.
Where's Mama?
Tatsuya's getting her up. Go help out.
Okay!
Mama! Mama!
It's morning! It's morning!
Get up, Mama!
Mama!
Wake up!
Mama got up!
So, what have you been up to lately?
Hitomi got another love letter.
It's the second one she's gotten this month.
I wish she'd find a guy who could just go up to her and say what he thought.
How's Kazuko doing?
My teacher? She's still going.
She always talks about it during homeroom.
Her three-month anniversary is this week. That's a new record.
I dunno, that's a pretty risky time.
Really?
It's about when you start having trouble if it's not for real.
I guess if it holds together it should last at least a year, but...
There we go!
Which ribbon should I wear?
Isn't it too fancy?
It'll be fine. Once you give up on your looks, it's all over.
It's great. Your secret admirers will love it.
I don't have any of those.
You should think you do. That's the secret to being a beauty.
Clean your plate, okay?
Okay!
Would you like another coffee?
No thanks.
All right, I'm outta here!
See you!
You should hurry up too, Madoka.
Here I go!
See you!
Bye!
Good morning!
You're late, Madoka!
That's a cute ribbon!
Really? I think it's a bit too showy.
It's wonderful.
And she said guys are only good if they confess in person rather than a letter.
Your mom's great, Madoka. She has good looks and she's so energetic.
I wish I could be summed up like that.
The kind of problem you'd love to have, right?
I'd like to try getting a love letter someday too. It must feel great.
Oh? You want to turn into a popular cutie like Hitomi?
Is that ribbon the first step in your makeover?
No! Mama—
So you're getting tips on picking up guys from your mom?
How rude!
That kind of dirty—
Stop it!
Oh, you're a cutie-pie!
But I won't let you wander off to some guy.
Madoka, you're gonna be my wife!
I have an important question for you!
Listen well!
Nakazawa! Do you like your eggs over hard or over easy!?
I, um, like 'em both ways...
Correct! They're fine either way!
How a woman cooks fried eggs has nothing to do with her charm!
Girls, never date a man who refuses to eat egg any way but over easy!
It didn't work out, huh.
Looks that way.
And boys! Don't grow up to put ketchup on your eggs!
Oh, and one other thing.
We have a new student I'd like to introduce.
Wait, that's the afterthought!?
Come in, Akemi.
Wow, she's hot!
No way!
Why don't you introduce yourself?
I'm Homura Akemi. Pleased to meet you.
Um, Akemi...
What school did you go to?
A mission school in Tokyo.
Were you in any clubs?
A sport? Or maybe an art?
No.
Your hair is beautiful!
What shampoo do you use?
Akemi seems so mysterious.
Hey, Madoka, do you know her?
It seems like she really caught your eye.
No, just...
I'm sorry, the stress seems to have gotten to me. I feel ill.
May I go to the nurse's office?
Let me show you the way!
I'll come along too!
No, you don't have to. I'll ask the class monitor.
Madoka Kaname. You're the class monitor, correct?
Um...
Bring me to the the nurse's office.
How did you know I was the class monitor?
Miss Saotome told me.
Oh! Well, the nurse's office is—
Here, right?
Yeah...
Wow, I didn't expect you to know where it was.
Akemi...
Call me Homura.
Homura, then.
What?
Well... Um... That's an unusual name!
I mean, not like it's weird or anything!
It's just cool!
Madoka Kaname. Do you value the life you live?
Are your family and friends dear to you?
My family and friends... Of course they are!
I love them! They're important to me!
Really?
Really! I'd never lie about that!
I see. If that's true, then don't even think about changing who you are.
Otherwise, you'll lose everything.
You should just stay Madoka Kaname.
Just like you have been until now. Forever.
Wow, that's a prefectural record!
Wait, what?
I don't get it...
I thought she was a genius beauty, smart and athletically-talented, but she's just a nut!
How many quirks is that transfer student trying to show off!?
Is that what passes for moe nowadays!?
Is this really your first meeting with Akemi?
In all reality, yeah, but...
So what, you recognize her from unreality or something?
Well... I feel like I met her in a dream last night...
Wow, you're trying to be quirky too?
Meanie! I'm really wondering about it!
I've got it! This is fate!
You're destined friends, brought together by the universe itself!
What kind of dream was it?
I don't really remember. Just that it was something weird.
Maybe you really did meet her.
And she just left so strong of an impression that,
even though you don't remember her, she popped up in a dream.
Isn't that a bit far-fetched? It's just a coincidence.
I guess.
Wow, it's already this late.
Sorry, I've got to get going.
What is it today? Piano? Japanese dance?
Tea ceremony.
With exams coming coming up, I don't know how much longer I'll be doing it.
Man, I'm glad I was born bourgeois.
We should get going too.
Madoka, why don't we stop by the record store?
Fine.
Kamijo's again?
I guess.
See you later.
Later.
Bye-bye!
Help me!
Please, help me!
Who's there?
Help me!
This floor closed for remodeling
Where are you?
Who are you?
Help me!
Is that you?
Homura!
Stand back.
But he's hurt!
No! Don't be mean!
This has nothing to do with you.
But he called out to me!
I heard him ask me for help!
I see.
Over here, Madoka!
Sayaka!
Of all the times...
She's running around in cosplay!? What's her problem!?
What is that this thing anyway? It doesn't look like a stuffed animal. Is it alive?
I don't know! I don't know, but I've got to save him!
Huh? Where's the emergency exit? Where are we?
What is this place? It's changing all around us!
What's going on!?
Something's there!
This has to be some kind of joke...
I have dreams like this sometimes.
Right, Madoka?
Huh? What's this?
That was a close one. But it's all okay now.
Oh, you saved Kyubey.
Thanks. He's a dear friend of mine.
He called out to me! His voice popped into my head!
I see.
Those uniforms are from Midakihara, aren't they.
You're, what, eighth-graders?
Who are you?
Oh, right, I forgot to introduce myself.
But first...
There's something I need to finish up!
Wow!
We're back!
The witch ran away.
If you want to catch her, we'd better give chase.
It's up to you.
I have other plans.
You're pretty dense. I was implying we're letting you go.
Wouldn't want to make trouble for each other, would we?
Thanks, Mari! You saved me!
You should thank them.
I just happened to pass by.
Thanks! I'm Kyubey!
Did you call out to me?
Yeah, Madoka Kaname! And Sayaka Miki!
How do you know our names?
I came here to ask you something!
Ask us something?
I want you to form a contract with me and become magical girls.
Illustration: Hanokage
I'll fulfill any one of your wishes!
Really?
One of our wishes?
I don't care what it is, I'll make any miracle happen!
That sounds wonderful.
Episode 2 That sounds wonderful