Rider, look.
Are you scared, boy?
Yeah. I'm scared.
Or should I borrow your words and say this is exciting?
Seems like you're starting to understand.
Is the enemy inside?
Berserker?!
Will one last miracle come to pass?
A gentle voice paints a twisted future
For the sake of a world where nobody will cry
Before reaching the crimson-stained sky
My cries and prayers fade and disappear
I can go on, abandoning all consolation
The beautiful moonlight shines towards the beginning and vanishes
Into the distance
I'll continue to reach out as my eyes are gradually closed
I believe in your sorrow
They're going to drink here?
What happened to your beloved chariot?
Well...
It irks me to say this, but I lost it to Saber.
Have you forgotten what I had decided?
I believe I told you I'd defeat you at your full strength.
True, my weapons have been somewhat depleted.
However...
It is because I am not in perfect condition that I am more than perfect tonight.
I see.
Indeed, the aura that you're exuding...
It's more potent than usual.
It appears you've come here
with some chance of winning.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
Our banquet's last question.
I shall allow it. Speak.
Now, if my Ionian Hetairoi were
armed using your Gate of Babylon,
it would surely create the most powerful army imaginable.
And?
Why don't we become allies?
Together, the two of us could conquer the stars themselves.
You never cease to amuse me.
It's been so long since I've laughed this hard
at the ramblings of someone who isn't a fool.
Unfortunately, there is only one
friend that I've had and ever will have.
Also, there is no need for two kings.
The lonely path of kingship.
I shall challenge your unwavering spirit with respect.
Very well.
Show me what you can do, King of Conquerors.
You are a rebel worthy of my judgment.
You guys seem friendly with each other.
I could hardly be unfriendly to him.
He may well be the last opponent I'll face.
Don't be stupid.
You can't possibly be killed.
I won't allow it.
Have you forgotten about my Command Spells?!
You're right.
You're exactly right!
Gather, my comrades!
Tonight, we go down as the greatest legend in history!
Our enemy is the mighty King of Heroes.
A worthy opponent!
My warriors, let us show the eldest
Heroic Spirit our path of conquest!
Come to me, leader of conquering armies.
You will now behold the form of a true king.
Why are you in so much pain?
Because Berserker... must fight...
Why?
Because the priest said so.
The priest?
Yeah.
He promised me that he'd give me the Grail.
Once I have the Grail, I can save you.
You're going to save me?
Yeah, I promised you...
That we'd all play together... like we used to.
Then...
I'll be able to see Mom again, right?
Mom...?
Now!
It barely scratched him?!
He can see it?
He knows the length of this blade.
Could he be a knight I once knew?
I assume from your skill that you are a famous knight, and ask you this.
If you know me to be Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
reveal who you are, as a knight's pride demands!
Attacking with your identity hidden amounts to foul play!
You...
N-No...
A-Arondight?
You can't be...
Arthur...
Sir Lancelot...
Why, my friend?
You were the first of the Knights of the Round Table!
Why would you sink so low as to become Berserker—
Lancelot!
Lancelot...
You saved your subjects, but you never led them.
Because I never led them...
You are bound by the false idol of a king who serves others but not himself...
My ideals...
My kingship...
You are but a little girl.
Have they driven you to this state?!
Arthur!
Lancelot...
To unite dreams beneath a banner of conquest.
I praise your efforts.
But, warriors...
Did you not understand?
That all dreams eventually disappear, when the dreamer wakes.
Therefore...
It was inevitable that I would stand in your way.
King of Conquerors.
You will learn of the conclusion to your endless dream.
I'll personally show you how things are.
Here it comes!
Awaken, Ea!
A stage worthy of you has been set!
Look up and behold!
Enuma Elish!
Hold on tight, boy!
What's this?
Is that sword an anti-world Noble
Phantasm capable of destroying all creation?
Rider...
Come to think of it, there's
something I wanted to ask you.
Waver Velvet.
Would you like to serve as one of my subjects?
You...
You are my king.
I will serve you with everything that I have.
Please show me the way...
Let me see your dream!
Very well.
As a king, it is my duty to present a dream.
And as one of my subjects, it is your task to see the
dream to the end and speak of it to future generations.
Live on, Waver.
See it all to the end.
Live a long life and speak of it.
Of your king...
Of how Iskandar charged forth!
Now...
Stride forth, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon.
Challenge it because it is unreachable.
Speak of conquest and demonstrate it.
For the sake of my subjects who watch behind me!
By the gods, you keep pulling
out one oddity after another...
Have you awakened from your dream, King of Conquerors?
Indeed, I have...
This campaign has been...
...very exciting...
Feel free to challenge me as many
times as you like, King of Conquerors.
This entire world is my garden until the end of time.
Thus, I can guarantee this.
You will never tire of it.
That's good to hear...
Ah, I see...
The pounding of my heart...
...was the sound of Ôkeanos' waves...
Boy.
Are you Rider's Master?
No.
I am his subject.
I see.
However, boy, if you really are his loyal subject, you have a duty to avenge your fallen king.
If I challenge you, I will die.
Of course.
I can't do that.
I was ordered to live on.
Your loyalty is splendid.
Never tarnish it.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths of
righteousness for His Name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for Thou art with me.
Thy rod and Thy staff—they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me in the presence of mine enemies.
Thou anointest my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life.
Episode 23
The Sea at the World's Edge
Why is the sky so blue?
As if oblivious to sadness
It crumbles incessantly to make way for a new day
I suppose we are born with our lives short
You have touched my torn heart
Our future ahead is filled with a pure, unblemished strength
The sky is vast, the wind is melody
Men will one day come to realize
The joy of chasing after a dream
With the eyes of a child, you've always had faith
I'll be right beside you
As we pass through the frozen forest
So that the world's sorrow will not taint your eyes
You'd take the Grail from me?!
What are you doing, Saber?!
How helpless you are...
That's ridiculous!
It longs for its own life, its own birth!
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
I knew you'd come.
Next Episode
The Last Command Spell