The Cultural Festival is almost here.
Lower your waists, and then: brainwashing beam!
Somehow, everyone is managing to cooperate.
Vice President, we're running out of posters.
Got it, I'll get more printed-
Vice President, about how we're going to divide the campus...
Oh, that's already sorted out.
Somehow, everyone is giving it their best.
I'm just trying this, but how do I look?
So cute!
You're shining so much that it's almost blinding!
Not bad, not bad!
I want to shine too!
Kushieda, your clothes...
I don't think this is all that bad.
Oubashi High School Cultural
Festival (Part 2)
I'm so tired today.
Yeah.
Hey, do I smell sweaty?
Do you think I'll be all right without a shower?
Huh?
Oh, you're going out for dinner with your father...
Answer my question, you dog!
Ouch...
You don't smell.
How should I say this...
Your father is really doing the best he can.
He takes time out of his busy schedule to take you to a restaurant every night...
I can't forgive him for what he's done, no matter how hard he tries to make up for it.
But, you know,
he knows several good places to eat...
Being around him isn't that bad.
What?
I didn't say anything, did I?
Is that...
I don't even have time to change because he's so early.
So that really is your father's car.
You're not secretly laughing at me, right?
I'm not! I'm not!
Hey, he's waiting for you.
Her father has really been trying since then...
He's doing his best to make up for the lost time and trust.
But it's not just her father who's doing his best...
Taiga is also...
...trying hard to reciprocate her father's feelings.
Brainwashing beam, pew, pew, pew...
Late night again, I see.
I guess...
You know...
Well, it's about the Cultural Festival.
2-C's Pro Wrestling Show!
Everyone, the Cultural Festival is tomorrow!
Let's work harder!
Hey, where are the makeup tools?
Oh, they're...
Hey, go on.
I have to ask the stupid chi' for help! It pisses me off!
It's okay.
Just hold in your-
What are you laughing at?
You're disgusting.
Well, your father said he's going to come,
so just make up your mind here.
Stay here and don't move for ten minutes!
Don't come in until I've sorted this out with the stupid chi'.
All right.
Excuse me, Takasu-kun.
Can you please move?
Sure...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
My gosh, what's that?
You're giving me a present...
You must be up to something.
God, stupid chi', that's not it at all.
Please take it.
Wai- What are you doing?!
No way!
Isn't this from a super famous restaurant?!
I went with my father yesterday, and I wanted to get you a present.
I've heard that even my friends from modeling can't get these...
Hey, try them.
Right now?
Whatever, just eat some!
No, I want to enjoy them with some red tea at-
Just eat them right now!
Fine!
Look, I'm eating one!
You ate one.
It's delicious.
Now it's okay, right?
You ate it, didn't you?
Now you have to listen to me.
What?!
So you really were up to something!
Just this once, switch characters with me on the day of the Cultural Festival.
Huh?
I want to play a good character!
What?
To think that Taiga wants to play the protagonist...
Well, her father is coming to watch her,
so she wants to show him her good side.
you know about her family situation, right?
Recently, her father has been trying to rebuild their relationship-
What is that?
Kushieda?
What the hell is that?
Don't joke around.
Wait!
Why are you so mad all of a sudden?!
I have to wake Taiga up.
Wha-
I have to tell her that a father like that is not trustworthy.
Why do you have to do something so cruel?
As her best friend, shouldn't you be happy for her?
Happy? Me? Why?
Why...
How can I be happy for my best friend when her father is coming back to trick her?
I can't just stand by and watch a friend get hurt.
Switch! Switch!
Fine! Just stop it!
Aren't you going a bit over the top?!
Don't just start making decisions while you have no idea what's going on!
Taiga's father is a good man who places his daughter before everythi-
You met him, didn't you?
How can you say that after meeting him?!
Takasu-kun, did you not examine him carefully when you met him?!
Did your eyes not look at him carefully?!
What do you mean?
Hey!
Hey, hold it there!
R-Ryuuji...
Minorin...
Let's shake hands!
R-Ryuuji...
I want to die.
Hey, you, that's my spot.
Come on, move.
Hey!
Look, I fit perfectly.
See, this is my spot after all.
Hey...
What happened to Kushieda?
She went home.
Seriously?
I don't understand how you could get mad at the girl you like.
It's all Kushieda's fault.
I can't believe she'd actually say those things...
Easy there...
Even if you complain to me, I won't console you, you know.
I figured.
Come on, let's go back and rehearse.
But I just completely destroyed the atmosphere...
No problem, I've got your back.
Look, it'll be all right if you go back with me.
You really have changed.
You can tell?
I want to change too.
What should I do?
Don't ask me, figure it out for yourself.
Kawashima...
I won't cling to you like Taiga,
nor will I become your sunshine like Minori-chan.
Oh, what you told me before, about being equal-
Calm down.
I,
Kawashima Ami, will take the same path as you,
but I'll always be a little ahead of you.
Ryuu-chan, hurry up!
I'm so hungry!
You've been coming home very late recently...
I can't do anything about it, I have to prepare for the Cultural Festival.
It'll be over soon.
Okay...
Hey, I heard Taiga-chan is going to move soon...
Who told you that?
I think, uh...
It was really noisy when I was sleeping at noon.
Throw away all the furniture.
Oh, hello.
I'm sorry for all the noise.
He said he was Taiga-chan's father,
and that the apartment is too small for the two of them to live there together.
I see.
Somehow, I think he's a selfish father.
Don't you think so?
He just comes back all of a sudden, then...
Why are you saying that too?!
No, isn't this a good thing?
I mean, they're going to begin their lives anew in their new house.
It's not good at all!
I want Taiga-chan to stay here!
She's part of our family!
Seriously...
I don't want to!
Why didn't Taiga-chan talk to me about it?
So burnt...
You mean "reserved", right?
She's still not back yet?
Tomorrow is the day of the play.
Her father should've given more thought to this...
No, if Taiga thinks it's good, then it's good.
Everything is going smoothly for them.
Oh, you're back?
Yeah.
What are we going to talk about tonight? Or...
It's about Minorin, not me.
You should apologize to her.
I don't think I said anything wrong...
It's not about who's right and who's wrong;
there are more important things than that.
That's why we need things like apologies and forgiveness.
Anyway, just apologize,
got it?
After that...
The morning of the Cultural Festival came.
The Pro Wrestling Show
Crap! The line is long!
Crap! What should we do?!
Calm down, Haruta.
How can I calm down, Taka-
Hey, what are you gu-
What's wrong?
What are you doing,
you messed up dog?!
I just felt I was being too much trouble yesterday,
so I decided I'd try my best as the bad guy today.
You're trying too hard!
You know, a half-assed attitude is good enough for you!
What's that?
Anyway, did you apologize yet?
No, I didn't...
What?
If you don't hurry up, you won't be able to spend time with her today...
Kushieda, it fits you perfectly!
Really, it does?
It does! It does!
You're probably the only one who'd fit!
Don't give me that pathetic face.
What are you doing?!
Hey, quiet down, guys!
Now, the moment is here!
According to our ticket brokers, 80% of the seats are already taken.
If that's the case, we might even have people standing!
All right!
I wish good luck to the first performance of Class 2-C's Pro Wrestling Show!
Fight!
Let's go!
2-C's Pro Wrestling Show is really good?
What is it?
Oh? It's interesting?
I heard that Kawashima Ami is wearing a super short mini-skirt!
They say the Palmtop Tiger and the delinquent Takasu are hilarious!
That's...
...the legendary secret treasure of this class!
Correct!
The super precious secret treasure,
our homeroom teacher's string of fate!
Stop it!
Anything but that!
Aren't you all Class 2-C's friends?
I'm starting to get nervous.
We're on soon.
Taiga?
Yeah, I've got it.
Master Palmtop Tiger, come!
Master Tiger, please tell me what I should do with this red string!
C-Clut it!
Did she just bite her tongue?
She did.
She totally did.
Say it again.
C-Cut it!
Roger!
Stop, that's...
No!
Stop! Don't cut it!
Don't!
Hey, that's not in the script!
I guess it can't be helped. Noto!
Shadow Army!
Take our homeroom teacher to the morgue!
My string of fate!
What's a morgue?
A place where you keep dead bodies.
Ami-chan!
Continue!
Oh, that's so cruel!
All my friends are brainwashed.
What should I do now?!
God is looking at everything.
Fighter Ami, if you can understand their hearts, you will be able to free them!
Okay, to begin,
just answer this question.
Please, try your best.
This is your most important attacking chance.
That's...
Don't tell me...
Who's the most beautiful person in this world?
That's...
Kawashima Ami!
You got it.
Oh, what were we doing?
Ami-chan...
Saved...
Us!
Damn you and your stupid tricks!
Unfrogiva...
Unforgiveable, Kawashima Ami!
One, two!
I can't see!
What's going on?
Now, today's main event...
The Palmtop Tiger versus Kawashima Ami!
Fight!
Go!
Ami-chan, behind you!
I got you!
Don't you dare!
You guys...
You're going too far, man.
You even went to Ami-chan's villa!
Here I go, you tiny tiger.
Wai-
One, two!
Crap! My back is going to break!
Just hold it for a bit.
You'll be able to do it to me after we switch.
Great!
It was a success!
It's so stuffy in this...
You know, our next performance will be...
Welcome back, Master.
I-It's not like it matters if you don't drink my tea...
Welcome, Princess!
Your prince is here for you!
It's just another cosplay cafe.
It's not that appealing.
The mood is great.
There are a lot of guests coming.
Yes, that's because the vice president went and advertised at the neighboring schools.
Our first performance was a great success.
If this continues, our next...
Hey, what are you doing?
You're eating your ribbon.
That crepe looks good.
Let me have a bit from the side.
Not bad...
Eat as much as you want...
That's generous of you.
Kitamura, you're really...
T-Taiga?
Ryuuji, you take a bite too.
It's time for the student council to patrol.
I'm sorry, you guys head on first.
Are you trying to kill me?!
Kitamura-kun's... Kitamura-kun's kiss...
Now, it's about time for the next show.
I know.
Don't get mad, you were the one who stuffed it in my mouth.
I said I know!
By the way, did your father send you a message yet?
Weren't you checking your cell for the whole time?
I was playing a game.
Even while on stage?
Well, there are a few more performances left.
If your father comes, just switch with Kawashima-
It doesn't matter!
Just think about what you're going to do with Minorin.
Yeah! A huge success!
Hey, semi-main-character, you were great!
Yeah...
In the end, Taiga didn't have to play the protagonist.
All performances are finished!
Next Episode Preview
Oubashi High School Cultural Festival (Final)
Was Kushieda right about me not seeing anything clearly?
No way...
If so, I'm a really...
A really slow guy!