[NARRATOR] Ed and Al are
frantically searching for May,
a young girl from Xing
who practices alkahestry.
After receiving a tip
from Colonel Mustang,
the brothers head
north in pursuit.
Meanwhile,
Scar leaves Central
and blazes a
trail heading west...
His every movement is tracked
by the Crimson
Alchemist Kimblee.
However, under the
deep cover of night...
Scar's trail
inexplicably disappears.
[KIMBLEE] If he was going
to jump from the train
this is where he would do it.
The engine's speed
would decrease here.
So what we need to know...
is which way he headed
after reaching this point.
Any Scar sightings to report?
[OFFICER A]
No... Nothing definite.
[KIMBLEE]
That's odd... Up until now,
he's been deliberately conspicuous.
I have a report, sir...!
There was a small
boat that was stolen
near the river about two
hundred meters south of here.
Was it Scar?
There aren't any eyewitnesses
to confirm that, sir.
[OFFICER A]
Look into it!
Yes, Sir!
Reporting, sir...!
We've talked to an
old man who lives nearby
that claims to have seen
a suspicious pair of
men who were heading west.
[OFFICER B]
Hmm... Could be our targets...
Take a search
party to investigate.
[SOLDIER B]
Sir!
Is there something wrong?
[KIMBLEE] I'm not sure
yet... On the map...
looks like there's a road
near here that leads north...
There--what is that?
[OFFICER A] It was an old
logging road that passed
through the mountains
to the North Area,
but there were
too many rockslides,
so they had to
close it down...
Why do you ask?
[OFFICER B] There are
several other places
further on where rockslides
have closed the road.
[KIMBLEE] The water's
flow here has been altered.
[OFFICER B] Yes, sir...
Does that mean something?
[KIMBLEE] For an alchemist
skilled in destruction...
clearing even
this big an obstacle
would be a simple task.
[OFFICER A]
Sir?
And it would be equally simple
for him to destroy
the face of a mountain
to once again block this
road with a rockslide.
[OFFICER A]
Transmutation marks?
Send the soldiers north.
Look! There's snow!
[AL]
Brother!
Ed, you are so uncoordinated.
Oh, shut up...! It was
just a little slip! Jeez...
[AL]
All this snow is amazing, huh?
Yeah... you don't get much snow
like this back home,
that's for sure.
Oh yeah, Hey Al...!
Do you remember that
one really heavy snow
we had back when
we were little?
[AL]
Maybe...
Oh yeah, I remember!
We had a snowball fight!
[ED]
And we made a snowman!
[AL]
Yea!
Back then I never imagined
we would come this far north...
It seemed impossible.
Yeah... but here we are now.
So, now what do we do...?
We still have a
little bit of time
before our train
to Briggs takes off.
[AL] Why don't you
grab something to eat?
[ED]
Eh, I don't know...
I'm really not
all that hungry...
But... I guess
we could look.
[AL] Careful! You're
gonna fall again!
[ED]
Shut up!
[SOLDIER D]
As of three hours ago,
the express still
hadn't arrived.
That accident last night
is really holding things up.
Any new information?
[OFFICER A]
Unfortunately, no.
But we're doing
everything we can.
There was a man
fitting Scar's description
seen at the station
one stop ahead, sir.
Are you sure
about that, soldier?
Absolutely, sir...
Eyewitnesses saw
him getting aboard
a military train bound
for the Briggs station.
Was anyone with him?
[SOLDIER C] A middle-aged
man with black hair,
just like the report says.
I'll have the train
stopped at once!
[KIMBLEE]
That won't be necessary...
We don't want him
jumping off the train again,
after all.
All right. From now on
this job is mine and mine alone.
I don't want you
people getting in my way,
understand me?
[train whistle blow]
Sleep while you can...
As soon as we hit
the northern cold,
you won't be able to sleep,
even if you want to.
I'm jumping over
to that train now,
so match it's speed.
Roger, sir.
[KIMBLEE]
Doctor Marcoh...
I'm here to apprehend you...
You can't run anymore.
Surely you're not alone...
Where's your friend Scar?
It's time to give up.
Sorry, but you're
not going anywhere...
You're mine, now.
Who're you?
The murderous Ishvalan
I've heard so much about.
So good to see you.
[roars]
[explosion]
I don't want to be anywhere
near these monsters
when they're fighting...
I think it's about time
for me to get off this train.
I can't!
[SCAR] So you're Solf
J. Kimblee, are you...?
Known as the Crimson Alchemist.
Tell me, do you
remember my face?
Oh... I remember
you very well indeed...
You were in the
Kanda district of Ishval,
isn't that right?
And those people with you...
they were members
of your family, yes?
I remember another fellow
who looked just like you,
except he had glasses...
Of course, it's hard to see
a family resemblance
when someone
is losing tons of blood
and screaming in agony.
[KIMBLEE]
This could be bad...
I just got out of prison,
and I'm still rusty...
but he's been fighting
continuously since the war.
Physically, I'm
at a disadvantage.
And all this man knows
how to do is destroy...
Good to know you
remember my brother.
I'll deal with you just
as you dealt with him.
It's quite a shame...
that twice now...
I've failed to kill
the same Ishvalan mongrel
when I've had
him in my sights.
[explosion]
It's terribly humiliating
to have to leave
when we were just getting
things started here...
But don't worry...
We'll settle this
next time, Ishvalan!
[SCAR screams]
Kimblee!!
Dammit, I can't see...
What do you think
that sound was?
We lost the rear cars!
Well what do we do...?
The military told us
not to stop for anything!
We have to...!
If we let this train derail,
we're gonna be the ones
who are blamed for it.
[ENGINEER A] Sir! Sir...
What happened...?! Sir?!
What're you doing...?
Who said you were
allowed to stop?
Huh?
[KIMBLEE]
Keep the train going...
We're heading north!
Ah, yes... death...
it's closing in.
One who spreads
death and destruction...
must accept their pursuit...
He will never be
far from either...
But what could
be more beautiful
than doing work that
puts your soul at risk...?
Because that's what
it means to be alive...
At least on this battlefield!
[MAY] I hope Mr. Scar and
Mr. Yoki are doing all right.
[MARCOH] Since no one
has come after us so far...
they must be
doing a good job
of drawing the
military's attention...
I hope they're safe, too.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
My skin's still healing.
It stings to have the
wind blowing against it,
that's all.
[MAY]
I'm sorry...
I wish I could've healed
your face completely
so it wouldn't hurt so much.
[MARCOH]
No...
This is the face a man
like me deserves to wear...
I am content with it.
Stop for a second.
Look over there!
[MARCOH]
The Briggs Mountain Range.
Those peaks mark our
border with Drachma,
the large country to the north.
Judging by those,
we should be getting close
to the place Scar showed us.
Let's see...
[MAY]
It's right over there!
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
[WINRY] What...? They're
not there at the hotel?
[FRONT DESK]
No... they left yesterday.
Do you have any idea
where they might have gone?
[FRONT DESK] I believe they
said they were going north.
Oh, all right...
Well, thank you.
That idiot!
[GARFIEL]
What's the matter...?
Is something wrong
with the brothers?
I'm not sure. Apparently,
they're heading north.
[GARFIEL]
Oh, dear... You know
what that means...
They're gonna die.
[sneezes]
[AL]
Are you catching a cold?
[ED]
Ooh, I'm cold all right...
That's Briggs for you.
All right, this is
where I let you go, boys.
If you follow
this mountain road...
it'll lead you
straight to Fort Briggs.
[ED]
'Kay. Thanks.
[VILLAGER]
And you in the armor...
Yes, you... Is that automail?
[AL]
No.
Oh, okay... Well then
you should be all right.
[ED]
What was that all about?
[AL]
Beats me.
That's military land
beyond the fence,
so stay on the road
if you want to live.
[ED and AL]
Huh?
[ED]
You ready?
[ED screams]
I know they say
the weather here
changes quickly,
but this seems a little
extreme if you ask me.
[AL] What do we
do now, brother...?
We can't even see the road.
[ED]
Relax. We'll be fine...
Teacher said she
was tossed out here
for a whole month
during her training...
She survived!
[AL]
No way...!
She couldn't have lived in this
for an entire month!
[ED]
Sure she could.
She even killed a bear.
[AL] The bears around here are
more than fifteen feet tall...
There's no way she could
have killed one of them!
[ED and AL]
Bear!
That's no bear!
Alphonse!
Hey, wait! Hold on a second...
Is that a military
uniform you're wearing?
Well it looks like some
pretty mediocre stuff...
but you have
automail too, huh?
Huh...? Mediocre?
Just 'cause mine's
not tacky like yours?
[BUCCANEER] Fool!
Obviously you don't know
a good weapon
when you see one.
This right here is
combat automail model
M Nineteen Thirteen-A:
the Crocodile.
Now, surrender peacefully,
you miserable Drachman spy,
or I'll show you exactly
what this baby can do.
[ED] Spy...?! What're you
talking about...? I'm not a--
Don't you hear what
I'm saying, moron?!
What the hell--
It shouldn't be hurting.
Something's wrong
with my automail!
Gotcha!
[AL]
Brother!
You bastard!
Listen to me for a second!
Your resistance is futile!
No way...! Wait!
No, wait, wait, wait! Stop!
Your pathetic automail
is easy to destroy...
No... You got it wrong...
I'll destroy... your arm!!!
[BUCCANEER]
Was that supposed to hurt?
[ED] Yaaaa!!
Stop stop stop stop!
What's going on?
Why didn't my
alchemy work on it...?
This thing's made
of iron, isn't it?
Brother!
Thanks, Alphonse!
You okay?
This is bad...
I hope I die here,
or else Winry's
gonna kill me!
That wasn't
too bad, kid...
Especially with that
ordinary automail you have...
But it's all over now.
[AL]
The Briggs Mountain Guard...
This is getting old...
I don't want another
gun stuck in my face.
[AL]
Brother!
[ED]
A wall?
Buccaneer... who are they?
I'm sorry!
I didn't see you there,
General Armstrong...
I apologize for the disturbance.
[AL]
Armstrong?
[ED] That's who Major
Armstrong wanted us
to meet when we made it here?
Olivier Milla Armstrong...
Major Armstrong's older sister!
[AL]
But...
They look different.
[ED]
She's not huge.
I'll ask again--who are you?
I'm the Fullmetal Alchemist.
My name's Edward Elric...
Major Armstrong from
Central Command
sent us here to meet with the
general in charge of this post.
[ED] Can you call
off your guard dogs?
[OLIVIER]
Search them.
[ED]
But I'm with the military!
[OLIVIER]
Sure.
But how do I verify that?
Anyone can claim to
be somebody famous.
[PATROLMAN A]
Hey, he's hollow!
Oh, you noticed...
[PATROLMAN B]
What's this?
General!
[ED]
That's a letter of introduction
from Major Alex Louis Armstrong.
Just read that...
Then you'll know
you can trust us.
It's from Alex, all right.
[ED] Aren't you even
going to read it?!
[OLIVIER]
A letter of introduction
means nothing to me.
I don't put much stock
in anyone else's
opinions of a person...
I prefer to judge the people
I meet with my own eyes.
Th-Th-That's amazing!
It's huge...!
What is this place?
[OLIVIER]
Enter... Fullmetal Alchemist.
[ED]
This is incredible!
That wall is really,
really, really tall!
Quit gaping like an
idiot and start walking...
before I tear your little
body apart limb from limb.
Be warned: I won't coddle
you because you're children.
This is the mountain
fortress... Briggs.
Here, only the strong survive.
[MAY]
There it is!
[MARCOH] That's it. Scar's
brother's research notebook.
[MAY] He studied different
ways of combining
Xingese Alkahestry
with Amestrian Alchemy,
didn't he...?
Do you think that could be
the secret to immortality?
[MARCOH]
I'm not sure, but maybe so.
Will the information
in this book bring us hope...?
Or do its pages contain
nothing but despair?
Well... there's only
one way to find out.
[NARRATOR]
Olivier Mira Armstrong...
The general of
Briggs fortress...
Known throughout Amestris
for ruling the harsh north
with strength and ferocity...
She is feared...
and she is fearless.
Next time on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 34: "Ice Queen."
Behold... This is
the way of Briggs.