I'm throwing a birthday party.
You should come.
S-Sure.
You're kinda easy to talk to these days.
Well...
I did decide not to lie to you.
I said that out loud.
H-Hinazuki!
Ta-ta!
See you tomorrow!
This is where Hinazuki was last seen, 18 years ago.
Her body was only found after the snow melted, but she went missing sometime in March...
Girl
Isolation
Disappearance
Abduction
Death
What date?
If I can figure that out, I can prevent her kidnapping.
The Most Shocking Crimes of the Century
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya.
Sugita Hiromi.
Right. Hiromi was killed too.
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
Nakanishi Aya (11 y.o.)
Sugita Hiromi (11 y.o.)
Hinazuki Kayo (10 y.o.)
But Hinazuki was listed as ten years old.
So Hinazuki's birthday hadn't yet passed when she went missing in March.
Which means that X-Day is somewhere between March 1st and her birthday.
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
I came to a halt, and I came to reflect
On an endless today I had to lament
Made to realize that memories of days past
Are not eternal, they will not last
I've spent my days tearing myself apart
Crying alone in a corner of my heart
The times told me not to let go of what I'd got
.................................................................................................................................................................................................
But like water under a bridge, they were lost
I wanted to say it's a phase I regret most
But on that day I missed my shot
Waiting for you, I stood steadfast
As tomorrow went rolling on past
Today's another day I tear myself apart
Engraving a scar I'll always recollect
Saying it's you I want
ERASED
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Ow!
Apparently the boys are competin' in pairs.
Oh, that could be fun.
I bet Hamada's gonna get the best time.
Probably.
Hamada!
Hockey team, represent!
Kick some butt, Hamada!
Show 'em who's boss!
Oh, shut it.
Go!
Don't expect me to go easy on you.
Got it.
Hamada's a starter on the hockey team that won the national championship.
I do remember racing him at some point.
Fujinuma's the one goin' up against Hamada.
Poor fella.
Wish him luck, Hinazuki.
Come on!
Think you can win, Fujinuma?
I'll give it my all.
That so? Well, good luck.
On your marks.
Get set...
Crap!
Go, Satoru!
What're you doin', Hamada?!
This guy's got wheels!
Fujinuma must've jumped the gun.
Am I really allowed to win?
Would there be any point to doing so?
Go for it!
This guy does his best and practices hard every day.
It's obvious who should finish first.
Get in!
See? Hamada did win in the end.
That was awesome!
Satoru pushed Hamada all the way! That's incredible!
Right, Kenya?
Fujinuma!
I hate punks like you!
Satoru!
That was close, huh?
Shaddup!
What's his problem?
Seriously. Gettin' pissed just 'cause he nearly lost.
It's fine.
I remember now.
I hate punks like you!
I ended up making the same mistake I did 18 years ago.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
Wait up, Hinazuki!
Hamada was too fast for me after all.
Uh-huh.
Hey...
X-Day
Tell me when your birthday is.
What's wrong?
You said you wouldn't lie to me.
Sorry.
I felt like today was meant to be Hamada's day.
Oh.
Look...
It's fine.
We're both fakes.
Both liars.
Let's head home, Satoru.
Sorry, go without me. I forgot something.
Staff Room
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
Class 5-4
Homeroom Teacher
Yashiro Gaku
What's up, Satoru?
Mr. Yashiro...
U-Uh...
Is this about Kayo?
He's got good intuition.
I wanted to look up her birthday.
I'm sorry.
Is that so?
You've become good friends with her lately, huh?
I don't know about that...
You didn't ask her?
I told her when my birthday was, but she wouldn't tell me hers.
Ah, I get it now.
Here, see for yourself.
What do you "get"?
Hinazuki
Kayo
Fujinuma
Satoru
March
2nd
The same birthday as me?
I get it now.
Thanks.
Well, Kayo's got a bit of a shy side, so she probably found it hard to say that you shared birthdays.
Don't let that get to you, though. Celebrate it with her.
Will do.
Well, goodbye.
Satoru.
That was a close race today.
Whatever you do, always give it your all.
The same goes with Kayo, too.
Right!
Yashiro Gaku.
He must be around as old here as I am in 2006.
And he's got a sharp, discerning eye.
I now know when X-Day is.
Hinazuki
Kayo
Fujinuma
Satoru
March
2nd
March 1st
It's March 1st.
February 19th
Just 11 days from now.
I'd better make up with Hinazuki quick.
Huh? She's not here.
Satoru!
Mr. Yuuki...
Y-You seem to have made l-lots of friends.
I'm happy for you.
He's 23 years old in this time period,
which means he's younger than I am in the present.
I owe it all to you.
No, you don't!
I-It's all because y-you worked up your courage.
Wh-When you want to have fun with people, th-they usually get the message.
His stuttering and gentle nature are just as I remember.
He's a nice guy.
Mr. Yuuki, do you know of Hinazuki Kayo?
Kayo? Sure, I know her.
That was quick.
The girl who's always at the park by herself, right?
I've talked to her a bunch of times.
Are you two classmates?
Yep.
Oh, really?
Jun! Let's eat!
You go ahead. I'll eat later.
Isn't it a bit soon for dinner?
We have early starts here.
I work at my dad's catering service from four in the morning.
Four? Really?
Yeah. Only until noon, though.
Ah...
Since I always spotted him chilling in the afternoon, I just assumed he was unemployed.
Now that I'm 29,
I can tell he's making an effort to use standard language with me, not the local dialect.
Kids tend to find this manner of speech credible and mature.
How did he talk to you?
Did it give you the impression he was a nice guy?
They put out a papercraft tournament special recently.
Perfect
Day for
Pleasure
Perfect
Day for
All You
Can See
Beautiful
Girl
Photo
Album
High School
Girls' Uniform
Reference
Guide
High School
Girls' Uniform
Reference
Guide
U-Uh, I-I got those from someone,
s-so I couldn't just th-throw them away.
Don't worry. It doesn't bother me.
Did you notice anything peculiar in his room?
Oh, I should get going.
Okay.
Satoru, you've grown more mature lately.
You think?
Yeah!
Shiratori Jun.
Shiratori Jun
May 2006 Death Row Inmate
As of May 2006, he's a death row inmate.
He's always maintained his innocence, ever since the initial hearing.
I really can't believe that Mr. Yuuki would murder anyone.
If no crimes take place, there won't be any suspects.
Just you wait, Mr. Yuuki.
I swear I'll...
She's still not home?
This place is a mess.
What's this?
Gloves!
Don't tell me...
Hinazuki!
Don't look at me.
Close the door.
N-No! You can't stay here!
Stay away from me!
What's the matter, Kayo?
You cooped up in here by yourself again?
This bitch...
This bitch!
Get in the house right now.
Hey!
Mind explaining those bruises?
Answer him, Kayo.
I tripped and fell.
I couldn't find the words to respond to Hinazuki's sad lie.
Her eyes wouldn't look my way anymore.
Episode 3
Bruises
Come on, Kayo. Cool it down!
If you don't heal that mug of yours by Monday,
I'll get all the blame!
Hey.
Leave some ice for me.
1988 National
Hockey Champions
February 22nd
She's not coming.
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Mornin', Satoru.
Morning.
Boy, it's cold.
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Day Duty:
Satoru Fujinuma,
Hinazuki Kayo
Here's how you calculate the radius.
The circumference is the diameter multiplied by 3.14,
so if you divide it by 3.14 instead, you'll get the diameter,
which you can divide by two...
Hinazuki...
It's okay. Take your seat.
All right, I need someone to come up here and solve this.
How about you, Satou?
Who, me?
Come on, it's simple.
We're collecting the school lunch money!
School Lunch Money
I have to change the future.
Put it in this box.
If you forgot yours today, you have until tomorrow!
Staff Room
You know why Kayo's often late or absent on Mondays?
Is that so, Satoru?
Because her mother beats her on Saturdays.
I see. So you noticed.
You knew about it?
Well, uh...
What is it? Tell me!
I was wondering if telling a student was the right thing to do.
You know how Kayo's cut off from the rest of the class, right?
If they find out she's being abused on top of that,
they might further discriminate against her.
No way!
I know you wouldn't do that.
So I won't hold back.
But don't share this with your classmates.
Okay.
Honestly, we started suspecting
Kayo's mother around May last year.
But as of now, no concrete steps have been taken to deal with it.
Why?
Her mother's managed to cover it up well.
The Child Welfare Center visited
them three times as of last month,
but she must have good intuition, because she
was out with Kayo each time they came around.
They haven't been able to question them yet.
What the hell? Useless hacks.
I said that out loud.
Yeah.
I've met the mother a few times.
Kayo's definitely being abused.
All we need is official confirmation from the Child Welfare Center.
We'll free Kayo from her mother as soon as possible.
Their preparations have made it that far, huh?
But if and when that happens,
Kayo won't be part of this class anymore.
If it saves Hinazuki, I don't care.
Please hurry, sir.
Yashiro must be waiting for spring break to take action.
But that'll be too late!
Step on it, dammit!
Sit down already!
Oh, hell.
The lunch money is gone.
Is this seriously happening to me? I'm 29 years old!
Mr. Yashiro.
What is it?
I lost everyone's lunch money.
I don't think he lost it. Somebody must've stolen it.
It might've been Hinazuki.
Wait. What makes you say that?
I mean, she never pays for lunch.
And whoever stole the money
probably did it 'cuz they're broke.
That sounds right!
Did you take it, Hinazuki?
This brat...
We'll find out if we check everyone's bags.
I agree!
Man, I just wanna eat already.
Aren't you gonna look in yours?
Why bother? I didn't take it.
Search your neighbors' bags, too!
You did it, didn't you?
Don't be stupid.
Come on, find the thief!
Nothing here.
It's gotta be Hinazuki, right?
Obviously!
Broke! Broke!
Found it.
It was Hinazuki!
It's 'cuz she's broke!
See? I was right!
Kayo's the thief!
Shut up!
So what if she's poor or starving?
Hinazuki would never steal from anybody!
I bet it was you.
You know, anybody could've taken it
from Satoru's desk and planted it there.
Class, Kayo's on day duty today, so there's nothing strange about her having the lunch money.
Misato, Satoru. This ends here, okay?
Let's have lunch.
Okay!
School will be closing shortly.
Students who are still in the building,
please turn off the lights and close the windows.
Well, this is awkward.
Thanks for earlier, Fujinuma.
No problem.
She was saying some really awful things.
When we were in third grade,
she kept making fun of my pencils,
so I threw her favorite mechanical pencil out the window.
So she's hated me ever since.
Well, the feeling's mutual.
But this one time, she invited me to a Christmas party.
She just wanted to show off her big Christmas tree.
But it was so pretty.
I remember now.
Hey...
How about we go see one today?
See what?
A Christmas tree.
What are you, stupid?
Here.
They're just cotton gloves.
But we're going up a hill, so it'll be cold.
I never said I'd go.
I used to ski and bobsled here all the time.
I even saw red foxes every now and then.
There they are!
Wh-Whoa!
I remembered the red foxes circling around my feet.
But 18 years ago, I saw them by myself.
Nobody believed me when I told them.
Think they're a couple?
They must be.
I'm in luck today.
The clouds are clearing up.
We're here.
Look. It's a Christmas tree.
Right?
What are you, stupid? It's February.
Let's come back here in the summer.
To see this Christmas tree again.
What are you, stupid?
1988 National
Hockey Champions
I was the only one watching you
Your past, your future
Your sorrow, and your joy
All of it
I believed that growing up
Was all about growing kinder
But I want to retain my childlike innocence
And still protect you
Beyond the horizon that awaited me
As I awakened from the dark
The town that hid the two of us
Was covered in snowfall, unknown to all
You are the deepest scar
Engraved in my heart
This was a world
Which used to make you smile
I'll take it all back
And restore its glory