There, all done.
They look splendid on you.
Thanks for helping us dress up!
Noble Academy actually has a few attractions for the Dreamy Shore Festival!
I'm so excited!
Yeah, I'm dying to see them!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
Cheer Up, Yuuki!
A Supportive Summer Festival!
Welcome.
I'll have an anzuame!
I want one with an orange!
Here you go!
It's so gloppy!
Yummy!
Thank you, ma'am!
I'm in full bloom happiness!
Hey, girls!
It's time to switch.
Wow, already?
Well then...
let's walk around the festival!
Sure!
Azuma's so cool!
Oh my.
Minami!
So pretty...
How did running the stall go?
It was super fun!
Seeing everyone so happy made it all feel worth it!
Seems like you understand what
drives people to help at festivals.
Hey, Kisaragi!
What're you aiming for?
Well, uh... that...
Oh, that Perf plushie!
It looks just like her!
I wonder who made it.
I sewed it myself.
Mrs. Shirogane!
Students get one toss free.
Care to try?
Leave this one to me!
Congratulations.
Wow!
I'm great at ring tosses!
Here you go!
Huh? Are you sure?
Positive!
Thank you!
It all worked out!
Yes.
I'll take good care of it.
We're done shooting!
Thanks for your work!
Kirara! Towa!
Girls!
Towa, are you modeling too?
No, Kirara just took me along...
Well, your yukata looks perfect!
Yeah, it's super pretty!
Really?
Do you still have time before your shift at the stall?
Yeah.
Then let's explore the festival together!
What is it?
Nothing major.
It's just...
We didn't have any plans to meet,
but we still wound up together like always.
First I wanna eat fried soba, then some fried octo—
Haruka!
Yuuki...
S-Sorry...
Looks like I'm okay.
Now boys, don't get so excited that you trouble those around you.
Sorry.
Hey, it's getting late.
For what?
The tennis club's got a training camp tomorrow.
Coach'll be fuming if we don't get back to the dorm soon!
Right, Yuuki?
We've still got time.
Forget tennis, there's a festival!
Let's stay out here.
Are you kidding me?
Look, I know how you feel, but if you don't snap out of—
Chill, man.
We'll head back for now, so don't stay out too late.
C'mon.
F-Fine.
Yuuki?
What?
Eh, you'll do.
I'll buy you something to make up for getting your yukata wet.
Let's paint the festival red!
Huh?!
Hearty Helpin'  Fried Soba
Handmade Ice
Let's try the cork guns next!
Is something wrong?
Yeah, a little...
Yuuki, is that...
It's nothing!
But...
Can we have a minute?
Haruharu!
Who were those girls?
Yuuki's fan club...
Well, uh...
Whatever do you need?
Haruno, you've gotta help Yuuki!
Huh?
The tennis, she calls to me!
Nobody beats me at tennis.
Forget tennis, there's a festival!
I knew something was odd about Yuuki putting anything before tennis!
Did something happen?
Go! Go! Yuuki!
During practice...
he had an injury.
His elbow?
Thankfully, the injury wasn't serious,
but he's being benched for the summer tournament.
We think he's pretty torn up about it.
Please, can you cheer Yuuki up?
You're the only one we can ask!
All right.
I can't promise much, but I'll do what I can.
Thank you!
We're counting on you!
Y-Yuuki—
I don't need your help!
Sorry, no dice.
That was fast!
And just so you girls can hear it too,
I'm not worth whatever pity you've got for me!
Th-That's not true!
You made the starting lineup as a first year!
You're like a hero!
Please, I'm just a zero!
Now leave me alone!
I've grown weary of contemplation.
For both Twilight and Lock.
I've naught but to dispel such distractions and return to square one!
Indeed, there's naught but to deliver despair to Dyspear!
Such is my duty!
Those three...
Tree updo!
Now, show me your dreams.
Go, go, Yuuki!
So you do share a dream.
A perfect chance to gather despair!
There is naught but to imprison
that dream in the cage of despair!
Shut your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair! Vil!
Dyspair!
There are three of them!
Just as I thought.
They provide three times the despair!
Shut!
Twilight!
No, no!
I'm not to be swayed!
We're in the middle of the festival!
Then we'll stop them here!
Right!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Blooming Flowers!
Cure Flora!
The Princess of Clear Seas!
Cure Mermaid!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
The Princess of Crimson Flames!
Cure Scarlet!
With strength!
Grace!
And beauty!
Go!
Princess Precure!
That dream trapped in its cold cage...
shall be released at once!
Do prepare yourself!
There you are, Princess Precures!
Get them, Dyspairvil!
Viiiil!
Dyspair! Vil!
Dyspairvil!
Dys!
What are those?
Pair! Vil!
It's you...
Dyspairvil.
What's that monster?!
Dyspair...
Vil!
There's a blue one too?!
Flora, take care of that boy.
Right!
Hey!
Dys!
Pair!
Fireworks!
Ignite, O flames!
Precure!
Scarlet Spark!
Dyspairvil!
Dys! Pair!
Dyspaaaair!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Dyspairvil...
Dyspairvil!
Now run away!
Hold on!
You saved me before, didn't you?
Well, uh...
So, your name's Flora?
Well, yes...
Sorry, I've gotta go!
Wait, I'm not done!
Why are you following me?!
Dyspairvil!
Dyspair...
Vil!
Does your injury hurt?
I'm fine.
Why are you girls fighting those things?
Because...
we want to protect everyone's dreams.
I guess...
Dreams?
Yeah!
Amazing...
It really isn't!
Yeah it is! You're real, live superheroes!
I-If you say so...
It feels strange to hear a compliment from you...
Huh?
Oh, just thinking out loud!
All right, I get why you saved me.
Dreams, huh?
Sorry, but you picked the wrong guy to save.
Thanks to this injury...
Coach, put me in the game!
I won't.
You're doing sprints until that arm's healed.
What's the point in training camp
if I can't even enter the tournament?
B-But it's just one tournament, right?
You've still got plenty of chances!
I'm sure your coach is doing what's best for y—
What, you too?
You're all like broken records.
None of you get how I feel!
After all the work I put in to make the team...
I want to get way better...
so I can be a pro tennis player already!
But here I am...
just sitting and doing nothing!
I'm so lame!
You're right.
You're lame.
Right now, you are lame!
All this whining over one tournament?
Things don't always go my way, either!
But I have friends who support me and push me to keep on trying!
You have to open your eyes to those around you!
You have people worried sick about you who only want you to cheer up!
Don't you dare ignore them!
Uh, sorry!
I've gotta go.
Friends who support me...
You have people worried sick about you who only want you to cheer up!
I am so lame!
Dyspairvil!
Dys—
Flora!
Dyspair, dyspair, dyspair!
Here they come again!
Can these guys give it a rest?
Dyspairvil!
Yuuki?
With a target that big, I don't even need my good arm!
Nice goin'!
Now's our chance!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Lily!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Scarlet Violin!
Phoenix!
Soar, O wings of flame!
Precure!
Phoenix Blaze!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
Dreaming!
Burning!
Adieu.
Well, I've accomplished what I came for!
Farewell!
Open!
The door to your dream!
Where'd they go?
Yuuki!
Sorry about before.
I'm heading back.
I'll be late for my trip if I don't get to sleep soon.
Hey, Yuuki!
We admire the skill you show on the court,
but it's all the effort you put in off
the court that makes you our hero!
Like when you're doing sprints or collecting balls!
When we watch you train,
it inspires us to push ourselves, too!
So, can we still cheer for you?
I'd be embarrassed to be the only one.
Can you cheer for the others too?
Yeah!
Wait, how did Flora know my name? And that I was injured?
Oh well.
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Mermaid!
This grand blue sea is a mirror
reflecting my heart along the southern winds
I want to know the answer lying within my chest
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
Hello, beach!
Let's go swimming!
Swimming?!
Th-There are plenty of more amusing activities than swimming!
Such as?
B-Building sand castles!
Sure, when we're done swimming!
N-No, I mean, without swimming!
Are you hiding something, Towa?
Go! Princess Precure:
Our Hearts Are One!
The Sunlight Shines Upon The Precures!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Kanagawa Prefecture - Fuuna (Age 7)
Ishikawa Prefecture - Sayaka (Age 7)