Street No. 05
"The Truly Awkward Toshiko Tatsuno"
And Yet the Town Moves
Even if you look up at the sky from the same place,
you can never see the same cloud twice...
MARUKO SHOPPING DISTRICT
The day is surely ticking away...
Yay! I won tickets to a movie screening!
That was just like Arashiyama...
Her comedic style has contaminated me...
Oh no, I have to be careful...
In any case, I have passed the first stage...
KAIRONS
vs
TOKUGAWA NINJA CORPS
I want to go to this with Sanada!
A rainbow colored sunset falls
And the wind is a bit cool
Saturday night is bustling
Even the gloomy feeling
Brightens up right away
Everyone is in high spirits
In high spirits
Let's go downtown
10 days until the movie screening
Art Classroom
How did you get that?!
Oh, I want to see, I want to see!
A battle between evil organizations!
I'm sorry, but I'm going to invite Sanada!
But when it comes to actually inviting him, I get nervous...
Oh! It's so bittersweet, Haribara.
Yes! Isn't this youth, Arashiyama?
Sniff sniff...
Sour!
Stop it.
Instead of a screening, you should've
invited him to an actual movie.
Yeah, a movie that sets the proper mood.
I don't care about the contents of the movie.
The fact is that at the point
of inviting someone to a screening,
a date is already set and so
there's a better chance of success.
I see.
There's nothing more vague than the "sometime"
in "let's go to a movie together sometime."
Does that mean with a movie screening,
the date is selective?
Yes.
That's why I picked a film whose giveaway
was not so competitive; it was easy to win.
Aw, but I would want to see it!
If it's a rare event like a movie screening,
then it'll be harder to say no.
Just like you to think of this, Tatsuno.
YOU PEOPLE
You people!
What are you eating during class?
Would you like one, too?
This is too cruel!
Arashiyama, I'll grade you on your progress;
show me your drawing.
Hey hey ho.
Hmm? It's pretty good.
Can you tell?!
It's abstract, but I can sense the energy
of the horse galloping through the wind!
It's a sketch of a dog lying down...
A dog, huh?
A dog, sir.
Uh, next, Ebisu...
Oh?! No follow.
Hey, follow me!
Translation: Follow me!!
7 days until the movie screening
I'll invite him, today!
When Sanada comes to the store today...
I'll invite him!
It's so hot!
What kind of dress do you have on?!
And you call yourself a Maid?!
I'm so embarrassed of you!
Why'd she snap all of a sudden?!
I can't let you out in public!
Take a chance on your possibility, poko.
Because these clothes are so hot.
Granny, sew us some summer clothes.
Summer clothes, huh...
Well, if I pull an all-nighter,
I can't say I can't finish one outfit...
Oh, then tomorrow, the next day...
By the third day, we'll have all 3!
If we make her stay up for three consecutive days,
the Head Maid will die!
I am not going to die!
3 days until the movie screening
All right!
Damn it...
I got caught up in Arashiyama's pace,
and now there are only 3 days left!
Really, today! Today!
I need to invite Sanada today...
Hey, what happened to asking him out on a date?!
I'll go now, so watch me.
With your personality,
I'm sure you benefit in certain ways...
I'm sure with the person you like...
I'm going to take you to a movie!
...you'd say something like that.
Okay, this time.
Sanada...
Eh?
A movie...
Um... Movie...
Mo... mov...
Move along and clean well!
Yes! This kid is no good!
Sanada's going home... Are you sure you're okay?
You can catch up to him if you run!
"Will
"Will you
"Will you go
"Will you go see a
"Will you go see a movie
"Will you go see a movie with
"Will you go see a movie with me?"
It's just eight words and a question mark;
why can't I say it?
Should I invite him?
Huh?
No...
I'll go!
Being happy for a second because
someone volunteered to take my place...
What's up with me?
This staircase...
Five or six steps...
I can jump over them!
Geh! It's the Western history teacher, Kameda!
Luther!
This is the worst...
Czar!
Western history teacher, Kameda...
Once he starts his lecture, he goes on forever...
Nicknamed "Soft Shell Turtle Kameda"!
Note: A wordplay based on the "Kame" (Turtle) in Kameda's name; the soft-shelled
turtle is infamous for its ability to latch onto something and never let go.
Y-you...!
If I were Arashiyama...
Then I could dodge even a scene where
it's inevitable that I'd get yelled at.
What would she say?
How would she escape this situation?
No!
No! No!
What would I do, what would "I" do...
I'm sorry, Mr. Kameda, I missed a step on the staircase,
but I was able to get away unscathed.
I-is that so? Be careful.
Yes. If you will excuse me...
Yes...
The day of the screening
Oh? Weren't you going to go to a movie
with the fishmonger kid?
Instead of working to make it a positive, it's sometimes
more effective to work to make it a negative.
That's how I would use a weapon.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Oh... I see.
Then, Granny is going to be considerate of that.
Naito
Dental Clinic
Seaside
Naito
Dental Clinic
Seaside
Oh, what about the store?
Granny's going to play pachinko,
so let the maids take care of you.
To have good fortune come to you without the hard work,
you must first work hard towards getting
the foundation of that good fortune set up.
Welcome!
But on a rare occasion...
Yay! Free movie, yahoo!
...there are people with such great luck
that they can obtain both.
A sneeze shows the person's true nature, poko.
A detective, you see, is required to have
a great ability of observation and investigation.
In Japan, the job of a detective is,
upon request, mainly to investigate
the subject's actions and secrets in private.
Only one with exceptional abilities
is able to have this job...
I'm going to observe you and investigate!
Okay, okay, Great Detective Yukiko,
expose the truth behind your big sister.
Aye, aye, sir!
I have no breasts or waist.
Big Sister's truth!
You have quite the eye for observation...
Pill bugs can be eaten, poko.
But they don't taste good, poko.
Go! A flame attack by fire ball!
I reflect it with my mirror shield!
Damage, 4!
It's so hot!
Zombie Detective dies!
However!
When Zombie Detective dies, he takes down one
opponent monster of the same level or below with him!
O-oh no! Fairy Samurai dies!
On top of that, I attack Makky directly!
I'm going to have my Turtle Knight protect me!
It's no use!
My equipped weapon is a spear,
so it can pass through one monster's guard!
Darn it!
I have no life left over, and so I die...
Man, I lost.
Takeru, you're tough!
Really tough!
Takeru, your cards are pathetic,
but you're really, really tough!
I bet you can beat Yamamoto in Class 4.
Let's challenge him during lunch recess!
Hey, guys!
Are you allowed to bring such a thing to school?!
Yeah!
Shut up, Ise-ebi!
Ise-ebi carpaccio!
I'm going to tell on you at the
homeroom meeting next week.
Let's go, Ebi-chan.
You're nagging way too much, Ise-ebi!
Girls are so annyoing.
4th Grade                     Class 3
Okay.
At this point, why did Hanse suddenly run away?
Do you know what he was feeling at that time?
Does anyone know?
Dear Arashiyama,
Can I come over to
your house this Sunday
to hang out?
From Ebi-chan.
It'll be on the test!
Huh?!
Don't tell me... she's not really coming...
She couldn't be...
Oh, sorry, the bathroom's free now.
No, I wasn't waiting for the bathroom.
Excuse me!
I-Isezaki...
Hello!
Oh my, oh my. Hello.
So you were waiting on a friend.
I wasn't waiting, and she's not a friend, either!
The world's hardest food is dried bonito, poko.
You really came...
Isezaki, what are you doing here?
I said we were going to hang out, didn't I?
Oh, oh yeah...
Takeru, Takeru!
H-hold on a little bit.
What?
Big Sister will give you some war funds.
Yes!
1000 yen
500 yen                         200 yen                       300 yen
to savings                      for snacks                       to cards
Hey, it's not an allowance.
Oh, yeah...
She's really cute. Good luck!
What for?
Tears are not an accessory, poko.
I received some money somehow.
Let's go outside.
Okay.
If by chance the guys see me hanging out with a girl...
That'll be the end of me...
In-Brain Class Meeting
This past Sunday, Takeru was hanging out with a girl...
Isezaki of all people, weren't you?!
Yes.
The same Isezaki who was going to
tattle on us at homeroom meeting!
I admit my sins...
Takeru!
I'm bored. Say something!
Well... um...
Say! Why are you calling me by my first name?
You usually call me Arashiyama...
Huh? That's my discretion.
Takeru, you should call me by my first name.
Come to think of it, Isezaki,
what is your first name anyway?
Oh?! I'm sorry, I just forgot.
I'll remember it now!
Give me a hint...
Ellie...
Eh?
ELLIE!
My bark doesn't go "hyan" but "huun," poko.
E-
"E"?
E... E...
I can't, I can't, I can't!
I'm embarrassed to call a female character
in a manga by her first name.
I just can't!
Would you settle for "Ebi-chan," please?
The girls call you that.
Well, I guess so.
Hey, why don't we have some ice cream?
Huh... no thanks for me. Besides, it's cold...
Well, I want to have some! Buy me some!
Note: Takeru refers to himself as "boku" which is a more boyish way to say
"me" in Japanese than "ore," which is more manly in Ellie's opinion
And I don't like how you address yourself.
I want you to be more rough!
How selfish!
What flavor do you want?
Vanilla.
Himalaya Ice  Cre  m
They don't have any.
Himalaya Ice  Cr    m
What flavors do they have?
Himalaya Ice  Cr  am
They have everything except vanilla.
Then, strawberry.
Himalaya Ice  Cre  m
I'm sorry, they didn't have that either!
And I'm about to die from the cold...
Then, whatever you like, Takeru...
Choco-
Melon
You picked choco-melon!
Y-yeah...
It was just the one on top, though...
Thank you!
Yo, Takeru!
Oh no!
What's up with you? Are you on a date?
Hey, hey, hey, look at you!
No, it's not what you think. It's not.
Um...
Ah, she's a friend of my big sister...
Hello!
Hello.
She's really cute! Good luck!
Like I said, what for?
It's not good to be in the way, so, see you!
She's a pretty girl.
Y-yeah.
Whew, I thought the guys found me out.
The possibility for an encounter
in this shopping district is way too high!
I need to hide somewhere!
Isezaki!
"Ebi-chan"... I...
Lemme take you to this store I go to.
Oh, what, what? I want to go!
If I say the forbidden words, she'll punch me!
Is this what you call "oppression of free speech"?
Suzuya
Welcome.
Hello.
Oh, Takeru, are you on a date?
And this must be "miscarriage of justice."
Wow!
All
10 yen
I've never been to a place like this.
I've always wanted to go to a snack store!
Oh...
Hey, this...
These are those cards that you boys collect.
Yeah...
I want this.
Okay, usually, it's 1 million 500 thousand yen,
but I'll let you have it for 150 yen.
Huh?! Th-thank you...
Ugh, this sucks! I got the same one.
Are you going to buy a card?
I'll buy just one.
The worst possible situation!
They still had this month's allowance left to spend?!
I have no place to run, no possibility of an excuse.
My elementary school life ends here...
Oh, it's those guys!
Takeru...
Go hide in the VIP room.
Can I?!
Snack Store Suzuya's VIP room...
Where you eat monja-yaki.
Normally, elementary school
students not allowed to enter.
Mummo, have you seen Takeru?
Hm?
Gulp!
We went to his house, but he wasn't there.
Takeru may have gone to the world of adults.
Where?
Let's go to the Shinto temple.
That was a pinch bad enough to be in the movies...
If you don't give up, a path will open up...
Takeru...
I'll give this to you.
Huh?! Are you sure?
Uh-huh!
Open it!
Okay!
Hey, you're a bit too close.
Did you get a strong one?
Freshwater Crab Squadron
Bamboo Broom
Boxed Lunch
Natural Bone Bone
There are only truly awkward ones in there...
Hey, are they strong?
Yeah, depending on how you use them...
Makky wanted this one...
I'll trade this one with Kabayan, and...
Takeru...
Take good care of them.
Yeah...
Don't trade them away.
Okay.
She's very different from when she's at school...
What?
I... I won't use these cards!
Why?! Aren't they strong?
I wouldn't want them to get mixed up with the others.
Good luck, Takeru.
Come on, come on, hold on!
Good, good!
I'm going to let go!
No, don't let go yet!
Young people these days...
All over each other in broad daylight...
Oh, I like that girl.
She can greet properly.
Nobody said it was wrong.
Go tell those two outside that lunch is ready.
Okay.
By the way, where's my lunch?
Eat with those kids.
I'm sure you'll hit it off with those
elementary school students.
What is that supposed to mean?
But, Hotori ends up eating lunch with them anyway...
Food's on...
4th Grade                      Class 3
Next Morning
Oh! Takeru.
Morning.
Takeru, where were you yesterday?
Oh, I was at a relative's house.
Makita! Look at this!
Huh? Which one?
Oh, wow!
Morning, Ebi-chan.
Don't you dare call me Ebi-chan.
Huh?
I...
Did I do something wrong?
It's cold, it's cold...
Click.
Hey!
Sorry, sorry, were you watching?
Here, it's not over yet.
I wanted to watch the part where she transforms!
She transforms every week.
Women... I don't understand them.
Takeru said something really funny!
Memo... memo!
The Iron Maiden
Strength 3            Attack 2
Thumbscrews:  Opponent, Ally,
all creatures sustain 2 damage
When I find two 50 yen coins, it's unsettling, poko.
In Japan, the job of a detective is to
uncover any illegal activities of civilians.
Whereas criminal cases, in which the
penal code applies, are solved by the police.
Now, were you able to reach
the truth behind your big sister?
Uh-huh! I was able to reach the truth!
Ta-da!
G-geh!
Exchange Notebook
Hotori Arashiyama
Middle School Edition
Hey... where did you get such a thing?
In this, there are things that nobody knows...
I give up, I give up! Great job, Detective!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
I'm so bored, I have the heart of Rock n roll
Living alone a life of loud music
I'm oblivious with cheeks like a blowfish
Today again, the town to chaos will I drag into
Being tsundere is proof of my intelligence
Again today, I'm unable to confess my love to this man
I gave my life to table tennis
To strengthen my legs and hips when I play the drums
This band isn't a scam
This band isn't rock
We're not going for an ondo dance
We're not going to arrive in Nirvana
We are the Maids "Yeah!"
Dressed as maids we
Are here, we are here!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
This is Hell "Yeah!"
The crime scene is
A terrible sight, a terrible sight!
"Oh no!"
We are the invincible Maids "Yeah!"
Constipation is a difficult delivery
Enema, enema!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Pure and right and frank
Seaside is, with rave reviews, open for business!!
"Thank you always for your business!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
There's an old myth called Pandora's Box.
I know it. It's about a box that you can't open, right?
When you open it, a lot of bad things
come out of it, right?
But, in the end there was one thing
that came out: "hope."
But actually, that hope is a trap!
If there is no hope, you can give up on it,
but when something so close comes up,
you think you'll get it next time
and pour more money into it!
Granny, did you lose at pachinko?
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Six,
"The Pandora Maid Service."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 06 "THE PANDORA MAID SERVICE"
We turn round and round after all, poko.
Cafe Seaside