Summer Time Rendering
Not good!
She might be the real thing, but she can't fully recover off of only a few strands of hair.
Thus, she's reverted to a child's body.
This is critical!
Shide!
Her mind and muscles are all torn up.
Ushio can't fight anymore
Damn it!
If only I had the ability to erase him!
Ryuunosuke, can ya possess Shide's armor?
Huh?
No, that's crazy.
But it's all I can think of.
Don't turn around, Ryuu.
Shide can't hear my telepathy.
Stay still and listen, y'all.
We can stuff me inside the shotgun shells and create hacking shells.
But they'll take two minutes to print.
So I need y'all to buy me time.
Are y'all comin' up with a strategy over there with all that whispering?
Let me join in on the fun.
It's okay.
Shide doesn't have the ability to read minds or transform.
Even his weapons were created by Hiruko,
which is why he keeps her close.
You've changed, Haine.
I never imagine ya'd betray me.
You're the one who changed!
Everything went crazy the day that whale washed up on the beach!
I haven't changed at all.
I was simply lifted out of my ignorance.
Now, I obey my own personal desire to survive!
At first, I just wanted to be together forever.
That was all I wanted.
Two minutes, Shinpei.
I need to go all-out for just two minutes.
There's no going back now.
Use up every last bit of my life!
He keeps charging.
But that's fine.
He can think this shotgun is pointless all he likes!
Damn! The shotgun can't stop him!
Ushio! Change weapons!
I can copy anything!
So I changed it into Hizuru's sledgehammer!
Thanks.
Now we can keep fighting!
Death is the end.
Y'all can't predict the future or loop.
It's only right that the final boss has a fighting chance.
One more minute!
I see.
With two hands,
this is hard to use.
That first hammer swing came back at me!
So this is his echo?
Shide's left hand!
It regenerated?!
He just used his right hand as material to create a left hand.
Looks like my erasure is working.
Ya can do it, Ryuu!
On it!
When I attack, an echo is reflected at me!
But if I ease up in the slightest, he'll target Ushio!
Attack! Attack!
Don't stop!
Don't give him a single second to breathe!
Damn it all!
My only choice was to punch him!
Don't ya learn? Bullets don't work!
Ryuu, no!
Behind ya!
This is bad! Can't dodge!
Be objective!
Objective!
Those are bullet casings.
None of them hit the ground yet?
So this is a Shadow's sense of time?
Each second feels so long, like an eternity!
How many more attacks can we dodge?
And even if Ushio completes the hacking shell, will we be able to shoot?
Damn it!
After all Ushio's hard work to destroy one of his arms too!
This guy's good!
He's on a totally different level from other Shadows!
The only one who can shoot the shell is me!
Only I can do it!
You can't put a wise head on young shoulders, Ryuunosuke.
I have a lot more experience fighting as a Shadow compared to ya.
I'm sorry, Ushio.
Even if ya finish the hacking shell,
I can't shoot it without an arm!
Ryuu!
Don't give up yet, Ryuunosuke.
There's still a way!
It's time for us to start turning the tables!
Ushio! I'll shoot the hacking shell!
Ryuunosuke.
Ya have the unique ability to take control of others, right?
Can ya possess Shide's armor and make it stop moving?
Just for ten seconds,
until the hacking shell is complete.
If it's empty, there shouldn't be a problem, right?
Wait!
Ya can't live without Ryuu's support, Shinpei!
I know.
But if he keeps running away in my body,
we won't last five seconds.
But I gotta get in direct contact with the armor.
And I dunno if I can get close without dying.
Be confident in yourself!
I know ya can do it!
How strange.
Okay!
I sealed his power of prediction,
and yet he still manages to dodge by a hair.
I'll give it a try, Shinpei!
Listen.
You have the ability to mimic any movement nearly instantly.
Get Nezu to show you how to fire a gun.
I'm counting on you, Ryuunosuke.
I'll read him like a book!
Thread the needle, and land a killing blow!
I can do it!
He's in!
Ya did it, Ryuunosuke!
Trying to take control of the armor, are ya?!
Don't get any funny ideas, idiot!
I ain't never letting go,
but I still hate yer damn guts!
That's it! Keep him still just like that.
Crap. I almost passed out.
Is this the pain Ryuunosuke was suppressing?
Ya can do it, Shinpei!
We're almost there!
Right, Ushio.
Yer voice made the pain a little more bearable.
I think I can still move a bit.
Just kidding!
Ya hate me? What a sad thing to say.
Well, I love ya.
Ryuunosuke.
Ryuu!
Was yer plan to have Ryuunosuke take over my armor and destroy it?
Not a bad idea.
But...
I cut off Ryuunosuke.
If I know about it, I can deal with it.
That's the way y'all have operated in the past.
What the—
If ya know about it?
In the battle on Torajima that ya never saw, in the time that ya erased,
Hizuru tried the exact same strategy!
Oh dear!
Aren't loops just grand?
Two meters to the shotgun.
I'll reach out in three more steps.
Can I do it?
Can I move faster than Shide as a human?
His body's started to disintegrate!
Damn it. Damn it!
Oh, how I'd love to stay and watch ya fall to pieces.
But before I take the eye from Ushio,
killing ya with my own hands
will give me such a sense of satisfaction!
Ushio's eye will never be yers!
Ushio's gonna give the eye to me!
The fact this eye is mine means the results are already determined!
In the end, Ushio will win!
In the end, eh?
All I want is to live a long life.
To see the future of this world, the future of humans.
To see how it all concludes.
It's possible as long as I have Haine.
I've already lived 326 years and 24 days by swapping bodies along the way.
But Haine weakened.
Imagine my despair the moment I learned my life would end with Masahito.
I doubt you ever could!
But a few months ago, I changed my way of thinking.
If I can't live to see the end,
then why don't I make the world end?
If the world ends, that means I'll be able to witness its climax!
If I can revive Hiruko's eye, even temporarily,
then that gives me the option to steal it and erase the world!
Get it?
I am the final boss, the Demon King that knows how to cut the game console's power, Shinpei.
Just knowing that doesn't mean ya can change the ending!
I will steal the eye and overwrite the future!
I will reach the ending!
It's done!
Locked and loaded!
Come and get it, Shinpei!
Just ya wait, Ushio.
I'll be right there!
It was all a wasted effort, Shinpei!
Every last thing y'all fought for
was meaningless!
No use, huh?
It's over! He can't reach it!
Move...
Move!
Move, me!
Just get one millimeter closer to Shinpei!
It's come to the point where I just want to hoard all your words
It reached!
Even the ramblings from your travels are treasures to me
Haine!
You're the best!
Now Shide's in sight of yer right eye!
Whether I sketch or erase it's all torn away
While yer in objective mode, yer mind's synced with the Shadow sense of time!
That's the price I pay for my awakening
So since I was moving yer body earlier,
yer nerve circuits are fully opened!
Or my daydream's tricking me and I'm still lost in the unknown
Ya just gotta move yer body now!
Illuminated by the moon
I know ya can do it, Shinpei!
Your figure casts a shadow
Y'all have come this far!
Ain't no way ya can't!
And when that silhouette wavers slightly
You're right, Ryuunosuke.
That happens to be my cue
It wasn't meaningless.
Everyone carried me this far.
I wish this were fiction but slow motion is how it begins
Not a single one of 'em was meaningless.
I won't let 'em become meaningless!
If the visceral warmth and traces you left behind
He collapsed?!
No!
Are protecting someone's future, I'll play the warrior
He dodged?!
Everyone pitched in, did their part.
Amidst pain and sorrow
And that's why I'm here!
I'll conquer my fears
Y'were right all along, Sis...
It's a paradox of life
Shinpei's got what it takes to save everyone!
Or perhaps God's algorithm
When our tactics overcome
We'll be laughing
Th-That shot...
Ya never quit, do ya...
Ushio?!
It's over, Shide.
We'll live on!
Sto... Stop it!
Even after ya've disappeared, the world will continue to go on like normal!
If ya erase Hiruko, my armor will disappear!
I won't be able to move or see anything with this body!
No...
No!
Haine...
Oh...
So this is my ending...
Summer Time Rendering
Shinpei!
W-We did it!
Yeah...
Now everyone will be safe...
It hurts! It hurts!
Lemme end the pain, Hiruko.
My body...
Shinpei, behind ya.
Th-This is...
This is the human realm.
But
it's three hundred years in the past.
Three hun—
Hiruko must've connected the exit from Tokoyo to this beach.
Right now we're just here as data separated from our bodies.
During my loops, I'd sometimes see the past.
This might be similar.
That girl...
It's me as a human.
I see!
Ushio, quickly, erase Hiruko!
That whale is Hiruko from the past!
She's trying to transfer her data into her past self and start all over from the beginning!
No! Wait!
Get away from the whale!
You'll be killed!
I can't touch her!
Don't approach the god.
Go find an adult.
It's a ghost!
Did I scare her?
Wow. Ya touched the past!
Must be the power of that awakened eye.
Ya can change history.
I see.
Okay.
Take care of her.
Huh?
Ushio?
What are ya doing?
As long as this thing remains on this beach,
I can erase her, but things will play out exactly the same.
What I really have to erase is this Hiruko.
Ya didn't want to try again.
Ya wanted to end it all.
That's why ya brought me here, isn't it?
Fan... gyew...
Good night.
And goodbye.
Fangyew...
Thank ya, Ushio.
Thank ya, Shinpei.
Haine...
Tell me, Ryuunosuke.
If I'm reborn, can we be friends next time?
Yes!
Of course we can!
I'll bring ya tons of snacks!
So will my sister!
We'll meet again!
Ushio.
Looks like this is goodbye, Shinpei.
W—
Wait a sec...
I'll come too!
I'll come with ya!
Hiruko's gone, so all the Shadows will disappear.
My right eye will go back to being a normal eye too.
And if I return to my body, I'll die.
I'd rather stay like this and disappear with ya.
Ya idjit.
Words like that'll make me change my mind.
Ya gotta go back!
Everyone's waiting!
But don't worry.
I'll get ya back to 2018 safe and sound!
These past three days were full of frights and worries.
But more than that, I was just happy to be with ya!
Well?
Whatcha say to that?!
M-Me too!
Seeing ya again made me...
...the happiest guy alive, Ushio.
All traces of you vanished into the sea breeze
The power to overcome time.
Y'know, I finally figured it out.
But even now I still see visions of you
It ain't happened by chance.
Wanting to see our beloved one more time brought me and Haine together.
In reality I only have vivid memories
And with this power I've been given,
I'll jump through the loops and repaint the summer!
To play in my head over and over again
I've gotta hurry before this body disappears!
Even if it's all just a lie
Please be close by my side
Right next to me
I fell for you before too long
Recording
But time alone was what progressed
I wanna go back
I've listened to my share of heartbreak songs
Spending my days torn up and crying but now
I want to move on
I shouldn't act tough and just finally be
True to myself
So if I could just talk to my past self
I'd tell her not to give up even if it hurts
So please, don't let go of that hand
Don't forget to find me.
Never let it go
Protect Mio, okay?
But it's too late for that
Go on. Get going!
Make sure ya arrive at this conclusion!
'Cause in the very, very end, everyone's waiting for ya!
I'll be waiting for ya!
Ushio!
Huh?
Next time
I'm Home