We hope you enjoyed your trip.
Please watch your step.
That man...
is a shadow.
It just added credibility to that message.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
Orbital Resonance
Welcome home, Shin!
Hey!
Hope ya had a nice trip!
"Shin"?
Shi... Shinpei?
Ajiro Shinpei.
That boy?
No, he can't be.
A funeral?
Kofune?
Ushio.
Ushio!
Hitogashima Hall
It's 11:45 AM. I'm at the funeral hall.
The deceased is Kofune Ushio.
I know her.
Funeral
of Kofune.
Ushio..
Hizuru?
Yep, I knew it!
Minakata Hizuru, ain'tcha?
You have a good eye, Karikiri Masahito.
Ya look great!
How long's it been?
It's been 14 years.
He didn't flinch when I stepped on his shadow.
Has it been that long?
He's not a shadow.
Is Kofune Ushio related to Bistro Kofune?
Yes.
She passed away in an accident in the ocean yesterday.
Are ya here because ya heard about Ushio?
No.
Huh? Then why're ya here?
Yer not back fer good, are ya?
No, I live in Tokyo and—
Wait! Lemme guess!
Ya always were pretty smart,
so ya must be like a lawyer, or maybe a doctor?
Now I remember.
I could never stand you.
Turns out I still can't.
Always the jokester!
It's no joke!
Alain!
Remember her?
Don't be too shocked, okay?
This is—
I'm Minakata Hizuru.
Oh, c'mon! Lemme say it!
Hizuru?
That Hizuru?
Long time no see, Alain.
It was my second year of junior high.
I went to Bistro Kofune often.
Alain had two daughters,
Ushio and Mio.
Alain's wife died soon after giving birth to Mio.
While Alain worked, customers looked after the girls.
Read me that picture book!
Keeper at
the Sex Zoo
Taming a Mother
and Daughter
Keeper at
the Sex Zoo
Taming a Mother
and Daughter
This ain't a picture book.
You shouldn't read that!
Why not? No fair!
Read it! Read it! Read it! Read it!
How 'bout this? Do you wanna hear one of my epic original stories instead?
Huh?
Original?
Oh! How lucky, Ushio.
It's Hizuru's newest work.
Long time ago, on an island...
Death comes to all.
Ryuunosuke, it's been 14 years.
Enough time has passed for another to have died.
What?
Ya fell in?
What's the matter?
Mio and Shinpei fell into the ocean.
They'll be a little late.
That's a darn shame.
Let's wait a bit, then.
Alain, who's this "Shinpei"?
Oh, ya don't know him since he came after ya left the island.
His name's Ajiro Shinpei, my friend's son whom I took in.
Ajiro Shinpei.
Was it ten years ago?
He lost his parents in a boating accident.
He didn't have any relatives.
Excuse me.
Hizuru?
That's...
The boy who sat in front of me on the ferry was Ajiro Shinpei.
I can't meet him.
I can't trust anyone yet.
Wait, Hizuru!
Ligature marks?
Yeah.
They said it looked like someone strangled her and she resisted.
Wait a second, Alain.
Are the police idiots?
The culprit's blood or skin is often left under the victim's fingernails.
Did they check her fingernails?
N-No...
Unbelievable.
Don't this remind ya of that time?
It's just like what happened 14 years ago,
when Ryuunosuke died.
Ryuunosuke!
Haine!
Move!
Hey!
Hey, what do ya think yer doing?!
Get off me, idiot!
The heck? I'll put cuffs on ya, y'hear?!
Nothing seems unusual at first glance.
However...
Who did the makeup for this body?
R-Right.
A nurse at Hishigata Clinic.
What is this?
You're disrespecting the deceased!
It's okay, Doctor.
She's a friend.
Who's really being disrespectful here?
Hizuru.
Sorry to cause a scene.
I'll be going.
It was because I said all that nonsense.
Just forget about it.
I have one last question.
Did Ushio mention her doppelgänger before she died?
Doppel...
Hizuru?
Isokone...
Isokone Asako.
I always wanted to get in touch with ya,
but ya never gave me yer address or number.
Are ya doing well?
Depends on how you define "well,"
but my heart is still beating.
Ya haven't changed at all.
Do ya remember Ushio?
Yeah.
At the wake yesterday,
we got together and remembered her,
like how I always changed her diapers.
Why... Why did this happen?
Ushio saved my daughter's life.
Asako,
that's who Ushio was.
All that matters is that Shiori is safe.
What is it crying about?
This hideous acting makes me sick.
Damn shadow.
Asako.
Asako is probably dead already.
"Ushio saved my daughter's life"?
Unforgivable.
How dare you pose as Asako...
and disrespect Alain and Ushio!
All three Kobayakawas are shadows?
Yes.
No doubt about it.
I confirmed it myself.
The shadows are multiplying.
Seems like one of 'em can create more shadows.
The shadows I know can't do that.
What's happening on this island?
Who knows?
Ain't got a clue.
How about this theory?
Kobayakawa Shiori wasn't drowning—
she was being attacked by a shadow.
It killed and erased Shiori, then posed as the vulnerable girl.
Then it was saved by Kofune Mio.
After that, it kills her parents
and replaces 'em with shadows.
Are ya crying?
It's gonna snow tomorrow.
It never snows in the middle of summer!
If anything, it'll rain.
But the forecast says tomorrow will be sunny.
Get your facts straight.
What's this?
My secondary phone.
Let me know if it rings.
I need you to do something for me.
Hitogashima Hall
I'm going to follow my memory and repeat the funeral like last time.
Same movements.
Same conversations.
Shiori.
Did ya see a girl who looked just like ya do?
Be careful. That might be a monster called a shadow.
Stay away from her if ya see her again.
Okay?
I repeat everything, and just as I thought, Shiori doesn't do anything to me.
We see the coffin off at 1:00 p.m.
Good.
Everything is going well.
Hey, Shinpei.
Did Mio tell ya that Shiori saw a shadow?
Oh, yes.
When Mio was little...
Th-These two...
Shinpei?
Oh, right! When she was little, her grandma told her about it.
Sorry I said something strange.
Asako, let's go.
Okay.
It can't be...
Are all three of them shadows?
So the real ones are already...
Where are you, Ms. Nagumo?
We're running out of time.
Shin?
Are ya feeling fine?
Mio, can I ask ya something?
Were ya wearing white underwear yesterday?
That's the first thing ya ask me
after being away fer two years?!
I'm in dire need to know the color of yer panties yesterday!
What happened to ya?!
I happened to see when Mio's shadow killed me in the second loop.
The shadow wore white underwear.
But this morning, Mio's panties weren't white.
I changed yesterday after the wake.
Y-Yeah, they were white, but so what?
Mio was copied yesterday.
I can't prevent that.
I have to kill it.
It's the only way to protect Mio.
So ya don't know either, Dad?
I'm really wondering where ya coulda gone,
Sis.
It's 1:30.
Ushio's coffin is cremated.
After that, we have lunch while waiting to pick up the ashes.
There are two questions I want to ask certain people.
Question 1: Do you know about the shadow sickness?
Huh? Oh, ya mean like in the ghost stories?
Someone just asked me something similar.
Of course.
My great-grandfather was the one who named it.
It's true that a type of mental illness did occur among certain groups.
Question 2: Did you see a busty woman?
I saw her! She's musta had a G—
Are ya talking about Hizuru?
No idea.
Shinpei, ya know Hizuru?
She used to come to our place a lot.
Huh? Our place?
How did we never cross paths?
By the way, Shinpei. Can ya take a look at this?
I asked Hizuru fer her number, but she gave me this.
I can't make heads or tails of it.
Ms. Nagumo's contact info.
Th-This is...
Excuse me, Shinpei. Gotta go to the bathroom.
This code is...
It's the Tamam Shud, an unbreakable code in her novel Drifting Ashore.
Out of order
Hello? Ms. Nagumo?
Who's this?
U-Um, this is Ajiro Shinpei.
It's not Ms. Nagumo.
You?
I see.
It was faster than I thought.
The name's Nezu.
Nezu Ginjirou.
Ms. Nagumo is an acquaintance of mine.
How'd ya get this number?
Ms. Nagumo gave Alain this number in code.
Did ya break it?
Y-Yes.
There was a similar code in one of her books.
Uh-huh.
Yer at the crematory?
Yes.
Leave and go to the funeral hall.
Alone.
I'll contact ya later.
Uh, excuse me! Hello—
Out of order
It's unlocked...
What the?!
Hello?
Mr. Nezu? I-I'm here.
Connected
What should I do now?
Don't move.
Connected
Just stand there like yer a scarecrow.
It'll be over soon.
What?
Okay.
Huh?
The time.
The location.
You'd attack when Alain is alone.
I predicted 17 different situations.
But you chose the bathroom.
Why're ya here?
This is the men's—
So normal.
What a loud sound from the next stall!
The heck makes that?
Nezu Ginjirou
I can finally meet Ms. Nagumo.
Nezu
Hizuru will meet you at the ruins of Battery 4
If you really can go back,
tell me your name,
and I'll save you.
If we work together from the first day,
we can kill Mio's shadow.
How does she know about shadows anyway?
I have so many questions.
Um, you're Mr. Nezu, right?
Huh?
This is the first time we've met.
Oh, yes!
You found out about the shadows too?
If ya got questions, answer mine first.
To break the code, ya need to know two things:
the author Nagumo Ryuunosuke and her real name.
But Hizuru ain't ever told anyone else
but me that she's Nagumo Ryuunosuke.
So the only one who can call this number is Hizuru's shadow.
Yet you're human.
Ms. Nagumo!
So...
I-I'd like your autograph. Please make it out to Ajiro Shinpei!
It's spelled A-J-I-R-O S-H-I-N-P-E-I.
Thank you!
Well... Wh-What I mean is...
I'm a huge fan! I have all your books!
I told you my name like you asked.
I don't even need to take a bird's-eye view to know I sound like a dork.
Okay. What next?
Is this the time for that?
You aren't normal.
Lord Byron said, "Truth is stranger than fiction."
I don't like fantasy, but after analyzing all possibilities,
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
I came to this conclusion.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
Um... thank you.
Feel free to tell me if anything I say is incorrect.
On the ferry this morning, you didn't know me.
No one knows who I am unless I tell them.
I never told you who I was.
To Ajiro Shinpei
Nagumo Ryuunosuke
This isn't the first time you're experiencing July 22nd.
You must've repeated the day many times.
In other words,
you're a time traveler.
Yes.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Enemy