Faint-heated traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
Mom.
It's me, Asumi.
I came to see you as a star.
I drove the rocket by myself.
There's just one thing I've always
wanted to say to you.
I'll say it, okay?
Mom, thank you for giving birth to me.
Gaze into Tomorrow
Tokyo National Space School
Nishida-sensei.
Hm? What's wrong?
There are three others aside from Kamogawa
who are moving away from location A.
What did you say?!
Who are they?
Oumi Kei
Fuchuuya Shinnosuke
Suzuki Shuu
They are Suzuki Shuu, Fuchuuya
Shinnosuke, and Oumi Kei.
I thought it'd be them...
Geez! Everyone in that
little group going together.
Could it be...
Could it be that they're looking for me?
Anyway, go and pick up the rest
of the students at location A.
I'll see that it's done.
There's someone looking for me...
For something as small as that...
to make me this happy...
And also...
There's still something?
Kamogawa Asumi's signal
hasn't moved for a while.
What?
It would be all right if she's
just staying in one place,
but it could be that she
dropped her transmitter.
Hey!
Yes?
Just in case, one of you go to the scene.
Yes!
Hm?
Go on, Ukita.
I'll wring all five of your necks after this, though.
Which way should we go?
Who knows... ask her feet.
If it were you, Fucchi, where would you go?
What do you mean by where?
I have a feeling that the little seagull will
definitely go back to Ukita-san's capsule.
And then from there, try to find
signs of her movement again.
That's true!
Then, let's do that as well!
The problem is we don't
know where the capsule is.
That's true, too...
Say that first next time, will you?
She's always been like this in the past.
Whenever I get involved with her,
there are always hardships.
Then, why don't you go back to location A alone?
That's difficult to do now, too,
so I'll continue together with you.
It seems like you weren't honest
with yourself in the past, either.
What do you mean by that?!
It means just what I said.
It's like a mummy hunter
turning into a mummy!
Well, walking around aimlessly
is definitely a waste of time.
And there's also the problem of how
much of this our bodies can endure.
Then what are we going to do?!
Asumi!
Marika!
I have no strength left...
Let's eat.
Huh?
Let's start eating the rations
we got from Kamogawa.
You can't!
What?
It'd just be a little.
No!
I'm keeping this for Asumi!
Huh?
You don't have to keep all of it.
I'm keeping all of it!
I'm keeping them all for Asumi and Marika!
Whatever, I don't get you at all.
What's so funny?
It means that even all of us together
are no match for the little seagull.
Now then, let's get going, Fucchi.
What's most important is your heart.
What is this?
It's a landmark that the little seagull put here.
Kamogawa did?
There's no mistake.
How would you know?
The little seagull doesn't have a compass.
That's why she placed signs
as she moved forward.
What do you mean?
Anyway, let's follow this sign.
Kamogawa-san will surely come here.
But with her speed, she should
have already arrived here...
Where could you possibly be?
There it is.
Here, too.
Kamogawa-san...
Kamogawa-san!
Marika-chan...
Little one.
A capsule!
Whose is it?
This is it.
The capsule that the little
seagull was talking about.
Blood...
Yeah...
I wonder what happened to Marika...
In any case, let's look for the next arrow.
Lion-san...
Are you all right, little one?
I'm fine... just a little tired.
I see.
Hey, Lion-san.
Hm?
Was I mistaken?
About what?
I mean, I dropped out of the survival
training to come out here...
Marika-chan's probably been
rescued like Suzuki-kun said.
What I'm doing is meaningless, right?
Is that what you really think?
Listen to your heart.
The actions that you decided to
take were never meaningless.
But...
Listen...
The many things you have done up until now...
The many people you have met up until now...
They are all stars that shape your universe.
Stars?
Kei-chan, Marika-chan,
Fuchuuya-kun, and Suzuki-kun.
To you, they are all stars.
There aren't any meaningless stars, right?
That's right...
And now...
your friends can surely hear it, too.
What is this?
This is probably where the little
seagull checked her bearings.
Bearings?
Then, she most likely went
straight to the goal from here.
This means that following any
more arrows would be useless.
They would lead to location A.
Then, where do we look?
Asumi...
Asumi, where did you go?
Geez...
I can hear something...
It's no use. I can't find her like this.
Where are you, Kamogawa-san?
What?
What was that just now?
Lion-san...?
Lion-san...
It's true, I can hear it...
The sound of a harmonica...
Harmonica?
If I remember right...
I hear it... the sound of a harmonica...
Are you a dummy?
Why would you hear a harmonica
in the middle of the mountains?
I hear it! Lion-san's harmonica!
H-Hey!
Lion-san?
My dad and Lion-san will get special free rides!
Hey, let's go to where Kamogawa is.
Huh?
F-Fucchi!
It's close...
Kamogawa-san?
Asumi!
Marika-chan...
I fell asleep.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness that you're all right, too.
Hey...
You called me Asumi for the first
time just now, didn't you?
I knew it! You look so
much cuter when you smile.
Hm?
I said some horrible things to you...
Huh?
I'm sorry...
Don't worry about it.
But...
Hey, you don't hate being with everyone, right?
You're just not used to it and feel
a little uncomfortable, right?
I...
I still want to talk with you more
about lots and lots of things.
Talk about the stars, about space...
And I still haven't heard your dream.
Asumi!
Marika!
Kei-chan!
Fuchuuya-kun and Suzuki-kun, too!
Asumi!
Thank goodness!
Really... don't make us worry so much about you.
I believed that you two would be fine, though.
Thank you, everyone.
Oumi Kei
Oumi Kei.
It's a little frustrating that most people have to
spend their lives knowing nothing but the Earth.
When I saw the picture taken
from Apollo at the moon,
I got such a mysterious feeling inside of me.
You can still take pictures, even on the Moon.
It's a place that actually exists.
I want to go to the Moon, too.
I want to take a picture on the Moon.
I think from those dreams, I have decided
to take the path of an astronaut.
Suzuki Shuu
Suzuki Shuu.
The reason I want to go to
space is that space is there.
Because stars are there.
That doesn't count as a reason?
That's still fine with me.
I don't want the things that are
given to me from the start.
What I want are the things I don't have yet.
I'm just that type of person, so it can't be helped.
I want to see the stars closer than anyone else.
Fuchuuya
Shinnosuke
Fuchuuya Shinnosuke.
There are always some people who
are completely unpredictable,
and people who are always
anxious because of those people.
If they don't stick by, watching over them,
then they're just too unstable.
If that person were to say that
they'll become an astronaut,
then the other person would have no
choice but to follow the whole way.
There may be people who go to
space because of such reasons.
I'm not saying I'm one of them, though...
Ukita Marika
Ukita Marika.
I thought there was no place for me on Earth.
To me, who has never played with
friends or laughed with family,
the starry sky I could see from the window was more
kind and friendly than the cold human world.
When I think about my other self,
my own existence seems
like it's about to fade away.
I believed that if this was how I felt,
I'd feel more happy if I was in space by myself.
At least... until I met Asumi.
Lion... san...
There's nothing more for me to tell you.
Little one, the next age lies in all of your hands.
Lion-san...
Kamogawa
Asumi
Kamogawa Asumi.
My dream is to become an astronaut
and go to space with Kei-chan, Suzuki-kun,
Fuchuuya-kun, and Marika-chan.
Then talk to my mother in space like this...
Mom.
It's me, Asumi!
There's just one thing I've always
wanted to say to you.
I'll say it, okay?
Mom, thank you for giving birth to me.
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
H-Huh?
End