Shinkis are 15-centimeter-tall partners created to serve humans.
They are endowed with intelligence and emotion,
and serve the one they call "Master".
Humans can equip their Shinkis with whatever armor or weaponry they please,
and command them to fight.
Some fight for honor,
others to prove their strength,
and some simply strive for victory.
These girls who do battle using the weapons given to them by their masters
are what we call "Busou Shinki"!
We're almost there, Master!
Yeah, almost.
It shines
My singing voice is endless
My eternal pledge is only for you
I wonder if you're your usual self
I'll sparkle with you
Install dream
The arms of the clock advance
and with them so does time
When you are sad, I open my tiny arms
and embrace you
Fly
My singing voice is tender
I can remember your shape
and that wasn't brought about by a program
Let us experience
the turmoil in my heart together
Install dream
We Found
Something Important.
Master, wake up! It's morning!
Master! Master!
Hold on...
Master! Stop it!
Just five minutes...
Geez! You're in high school now!
Do you want to be late for your entrance ceremony?
Now wake up!
All right, Ann.
Good morning, Master!
Morning. I'm up now, don't worry.
I'm still waiting on a few boxes of luggage,
so I've got nothing but furniture for now.
How about you, Dad? Isn't it midnight over there?
Don't catch a cold or anything.
I know.
All right, I gotta go.
I'm gonna be late if I don't head out.
What is it?
Huh? How should I know?
Just look for it.
It's probably under the pillow.
Found it?
Well, I told you.
Really, I'm gonna be late.
All right, bye.
I'm sorry, Master.
Thank you very much.
Master, you forgot your bag!
Shoot, you're right!
Oh yeah, there should be some luggage coming in later,
so I need you to sign for it, Ann.
Understood!
Okay, I'm of—
Luggage here!
Wah! Are you all right?
Master!
Oh, yeah...
Oh, you'll be late if you don't hurry!
I'll handle the unpacking while you're gone, so leave it to me!
Okay, I'm leaving!
Have a nice day!
Now then...
where shall I begin?
Well, here's a start!
Ines!
Quit hogging the spotlight!
You were the only one who got to ride with Master!
But...
If I had only thrown scissors back there, I would've been on that train.
Don't get full of yourself just because you've been with Master the longest!
How could you say that?
It's true, I've lived with Master in this house ever since he was a child,
but your words cut like a knife!
What kinda cheap soap opera did you learn that from?
G-Good morning!
I'm sorry for sleeping in!
Oh? Where's Master?
He already left for school.
Ah, we're in Japan!
Master's childhood home,
Master's childhood room!
Yep, she ain't listenin'.
And this must be Master's hometown!
We'll talk about Master's hometown later.
For now, how about we start unpacking Master's luggage?
And stop acting. We've known each other for years now.
Oh no!
I'm sorry! I'll get ready right away!
Ta-dah!
What's that?
I've heard that wearing Maid Costume Armor is perfect for tidying up!
From where?
It's beautiful!
You made it yourself?
I had some spare time on the plane ride.
I made some for you two as well!
Look!
Not happening. And won't it be hard to move in that?
It feels... a little tight on my chest.
Oh, I made this one for Ines!
You did that on purpose, didn't you?!
In the end, neither of you are dressing up...
Let's just get everything unpacked first.
We'll leave the Maid Costume Armor for later.
All right, let's get it started!
"Important"?
What's in it?
Things that are important to Master?
Important to him...
It's important, so... a charm, maybe?
That's something he should be wearing, not packing away.
Then, money?
Money is something everyone in the world finds important, not just Master.
No way, it's probably got something to do with love.
Well, they say the one thing most important to young boys
are the books they hide under their beds.
Where do you hear these things?
It's a bit dusty in here, so let's open a window.
Ah, it's so warm outside! It feels wonderful.
Hey, don't slack off!
Do you think Master'll be proud that we cleaned this place up?
They say there's nothing better than a spotless home!
Master, I wonder what you're doing now?
Oh, how nostalgic!
Master engraved a mark on that wall every time he grew taller!
He used to cheat a bit and stand on his tiptoes,
but even that was just so cute!
I think we're about done unpacking.
Shoot!
Master's important luggage!
Who the hell put a knife there, anyway?
This is bad! We have to open it to make sure the contents are safe!
I'm stuck!
I told you, maid costumes aren't cut out for this!
Watch out!
This is...
"Robotics... Monthly"?
Is this what you meant by important books?
I'm certain it's meant to be hidden under a bed.
Is this important too?
Are these items really so important to him?
Wha—
I-Is this a love letter?!
Oh? Let me see!
Don't! You can't just look at Master's letters without permission!
But this letter might be addressed to one of us!
F-For me?
No, it's for me!
We should open it to be sure.
I told you, you can't!
You have to get permission first!
C'mon, you wanna know too.
Wh—huh? I never said...
But what if he wrote it for a human girl, and not us?
Th-That would hurt a little...
Master's important letter!
Wait!
We've lost sight of it.
I'll search right, so you two search left.
Got it.
Such killing intent...
what i—bwa!
It should have fallen around here...
I see it!
It's right over there!
Oh, it is!
Why you...
Where are you three from?
How did you pull a surprise attack on me,
the second place victor of last year's Busou Shinki tournament?!
You've got... some... nerve...
I'm so glad we found it.
Sweet! Time to go home.
Now wait just a minute!
Have you ever heard of common courtesy?
I'll make you regret this slight by force!
Field, expand!
A Battle Field?!
Um, we apologize, but we're in a hurry...
It's too late for excuses!
Running away is against the rules!
Here we go!
You've got some nerve challenging us to a Street Battle!
I don't want to hear that from cowards who rely on surprise attacks!
Now fight me!
How dare you...
How dare you shoot at Master's letter!
Hmph. Seems like you're ready to fight now.
Master's coming home!
Battle Field, forcibly retracted!
Ines, Lene, we should hurry home!
Huh?
My master's coming home, too.
I'll head home too.
I'm back!
I got held pretty late.
Welcome home, Master!
You two got here safe and sound? That's good.
I bet you were lonely without me, Master!
I got you a dandelion!
You three really cleaned this place up.
Thanks, everyone.
But we're sorry. Your important letter...
was a little burned.
Hm? Important letter?
Oh, we didn't read what was inside, so don't worry!
Hm... what was this, again?
This takes me back!
What is it?
A visualizer?
Yeah. It's a modified Shinki House I made.
Ann, remember this?
It's my room!
This is the room Master made for me the first day I came here!
Master!
How nice...
Hey, I'm not jealous or anything!
From now on, the room belongs to the three of you.
Welcome again, Ann, Ines, Lene.
Thanks, Master!
Oh, I'll get the sewing machine!
How about we all wear that Maid Costume Armor?
Wait, isn't this room a bit too cutesy?
I'd rather do some remodeling and make it look cool!
Starting today, we'll be helping you live on your own in Japan, Master.
Hm? I don't remember packing a box like this.
Did someone give you that as a moving gift?
I stand here reflected in your eyes
and make something of a foolish face
Being more gentle than the wind and invincible like the clouds
I want to protect you
Here in the forest I am lost in
I want to try finding a four-leaf clover
The sun is guiding me
towards the miracles of two stars together
Even if we are hurt on the way
and ten years pass
this future where I can be with you is what I choose
We will walk on ahead
and not miss the sun's sign
Now that the move's over and done with, I can't wait to see what our new life with Master will be like!
Me too, but aren't you curious about the important books that Master keeps under his bed?
No, I'm more worried about that Strarf-model Shinki. Who the heck is she?
Next time, a heavily-armed Strarf joins us!
An action-packed battle is about to begin!
We're going to make delicious food for Master!
Next time, on Busou Shinki:
Next time
"The Secret Ingredient Smells Like Gunpowder!"
Don't put that stuff in food!
My Apron Armor is ready!