Review
Akihisa and friends, suddenly involved in an inter-grade test of courage,
Akihisa and friends, suddenly involved
in an inter-grade test of courage,
Review
were putting up a tough fight against the clever ploys of the
third-years, including the Eversummer pair.
Roll, roll, roll... Boom!
Whoa! Please stop it, Lord!
Thump.
What should we do, Yuuji?
The third-years already got a bunch of us.
It'll be fine.
We have a secret weapon.
A secret weapon?
A se-ret weapon?
Hi mondai hitori to futari
Hi!! 問題:ひとりとふたり
Hi! A question: alone or together
docchi ga suteki
どっちが素敵?
Which is more wonderful?
(hai oh let's go)
(はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
colorful mawaridasu watashi no shourai
colorful 回り出す私の将来
Colorfully, my future slowly starts to turn
dokomade hanasouka minai furi
どこまで話そうか? 見ないふり?
What should we talk about? You pretend not to see
(nande)
（なんで?）
(Why?)
assou ookina sekai wa kibun de hirogaru
あっそー、大きな世界は気分で広がる
Yes, my feelings start to bloom as I stand out upon this great big world
kyou mo daisuki
今日もだいすき
I love you today
(suki)
（好き!）
(Love!)
hontou ni daisuki
本当にだいすき
I really do love you
watashi no baka
わたしのバカ…
I'm such an idiot
(baka)
（バカ!）
(Idiot!)
hoshi no kazu yori mo baka da!
星の数よりもバカだっ
More of an idiot than there are stars in the sky!
sunao ni narezu ni kimi to aruku yume wo mita
素直になれずに 君と歩く夢を見た
I had a dream where I was walking with you, still not being honest with myself
(hai)
(はい!)
Yes
gomen ne datte koi to shiranakattan da
ごめんね…だって! 恋と知らなかったんだ
I'm sorry, but I didn't realize that it was love
kotaette kimi to nazo tasu watashi wa
答えって 君と？＋私＝
Answer me. What do you and me and something else make?
mugen no jump
無限のJUMP!!
An endless jump!
(hai oh let's go)
（はい! Oh～ Let's go!)
(Yes! Oh~ Let's go!)
(hai hands up)
（はい! Hands up!)
(Yes! Hands up!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
(hai all right)
（はい! All right!)
(Yes! All right!)
FFFpeeps Presents:
Baka to Test to Shoukanjuu Ni!
Question 13
Idiots, Tests, and Summoned Beings!
So…
we wound up together.
Th-This isn't r-really scary at—
A-Are you all right, Minami?
I-I'm just not used to these Japanese ghouls.
If they were German—
I can't breathe, Minami!
Aki!
Let's go back, Aki!
Wh-What is this?
Minami's different from usual.
Why is my heart beating so—
That was a pretty close call.
Akihisa
Any pig that seduces my darling shall be eliminated.
Let's run, Minami!
I won't let you get away, Darling!
I'll do everything I can to...
Shimizu, right now you look more monstrous than any ghoul or specter.
They couldn't have gone this way.
Oh well. Let's look somewhere else, Shimizu.
Darling!
The coast is clear.
Are they really gone?
It's about time you got used to Japanese ghouls, Minami.
It's fine. I can just go live in Germany.
But it'd be kinda lonely.
I won't be lonely at all!
I have friends in Germany, you know.
Um, that's not what I meant.
I'm saying we'd be lonely without you.
Y-Yeah, right. You're just saying that to be nice.
It's the truth! We're always together,
so it's hard to imagine you not being there.
Always together...
What's wrong, Minami?
Then what if I said I'd always be by your side?
My table's always cold 'cause
the wind blows straight through the legs?
That's not it! I'm asking if...
You're asking if?
I'm saying I... I...
Minami? What—
I'm back.
Welcome back, Akihisa.
Where's Minami?
I left her to sleep in the nurse's office.
I think she pushed herself a little too hard.
Well done, Akihisa. The operation was a success.
Checkpoint
Hand over my darling!
M-Monsters...
By secret weapon did you mean...
Yeah, them.
Huh? I get that Shimizu is looking for Minami,
but what's Kubo doing there?
Could Kubo have a thing for Shimizu?
Akihisa, you're so cruel.
You'll make him cry.
Too mean.
You've made us wait quite a while.
We let our guard down this morning,
but let us show you everything we third-years are capable of—
Excuse me, but did Yoshii and Shimada come this way?
Bastard! Wait 'til we're finished talking!
Don't you look down on us!
We'll teach you how to respect your elders! Summon!
Physics
Oh well. Summon!
Summon!
What?!
They have over four hundred points?
Unbelievable!
They must be total math and science nerds.
Damn it! Quit dodging!
Cut it out already!
You're next.
Eversummer
Pair
Wins
I can't believe Kubo lost.
Next is...
our turn.
Right! You haven't gone yet.
But Shouko aside, my physics score is 150 at best.
It'll be a tough match.
If only there were another pair left.
There is another pair.
Right here.
Me?
Well, I didn't get disqualified since I just withdrew,
but Minami...
Oh, right!
There's one more person here who hasn't been disqualified.
One more?
Um...
Might you be referring to me?
But Himeji is afraid of ghouls. We can't force her to—
I'll do it!
Watching Minami has inspired me to do my part.
I'll go through the haunted house with you!
Walk slowly, okay?
S-Sure.
I'm not scared. I'm not scared since I'm with you!
I'm not scared at all! Not in the slightest!
Um, Himeji?
Y-Yes?
Thanks for participating.
I should be thanking you.
I'm always so helpless, and I rely on you constantly.
Oh no, not at all. I'm glad that you can rely on me.
You're cute, smart, and even kind.
I feel like I'm guarding a princess.
Well, the problem is you're with someone like me, who's—
Himeji?
I'm nothing like a princess.
I'm slow and jealous, and I fall down at the critical moment.
I'm full of faults.
That's not true—
It is true!
And you don't even realize it.
Isn't the reason you never notice my faults
the distance you keep between us?
The distance between us?
You try to be nice to me and hold back.
You look at me, but I don't think you really see me.
Akihisa, how do you feel about me—
Himeji?
Question 12
Imagine the following situation
and answer the question.
It's been decided that you'll go on a
couples' trip with your beloved
boyfriend. As the plane is taking off,
you remember you forgot
something.
What was it that you forgot?
Himeji Mizuki's Answer
Medication, such as headache pills
and stomach medicine.
Teacher's Comment
This was a psychological test to see
what you desire from the person
you love.The thing you forgot indicates
qualities you lack. The fact that you
didn't notice before take-off means
that you believe the one who
accompanied you will be your
supplement. It seems you are looking
for comfort from your boyfriend,
Himeji.
Kirishima Shouko's Answer
Handcuffs.
Teacher's Comment
The problem here is that you wanted
to bring them in the first place.
Kudou Aiko's Answer
To wear underwear.
Teacher's Comment
What exactly do you want from the
person you love?
Himeji!
Huh? Was there a wall here?
Thank God.
Are you—
Ugly?
Shut up. And hands off.
Wait, Yuuji?
Huh? Where's Himeji?
Wait, huh?
Where are we?
Himeji's probably met up with Shouko by now.
Could that be...
Yeah, it's that Eversummer pair again.
It'd be tough to make Shouko or me scream, after all.
You have a point.
So they turned off the lights for a second, separated us,
and switched our partners.
I see.
Well, I'm sure Shouko and Himeji will make the strongest pair.
It's all cool.
So, what's the truth?
For some reason, being alone with Shouko in here
makes me think of being attacked with a bat covered with nails.
Oh, I see Kirishima in the corner over there.
Akihisa Barrier!
I can totally see through you.
Mizuki, are you all right?
Y-Yes, somehow.
This voice is...
Hi—
Himeji!
I don't hear anything!
I don't hear anyone whispering to me at all!
Stop it. It's making her worse!
They'll be disqualified if we waltz up to them and make them scream!
Oh yeah.
Let's keep our distance for now.
Mizuki, it's not scary. It's not scary.
Ooga booga booga!
I'm all right. I'm not scared!
I'm not scared...
Mizuki, there's a good girl.
Himeji.
Well, you might be worried,
but I'm sure she's trying, in her own way.
Trying in her own way?
To get close to us so we can help each other out as a team.
Yuuji, then what you said earlier was...
Himeji was worried.
She thought she might just be a burden to everyone.
Himeji...
It's all right, Mizuki. They aren't scary.
They aren't scary. I'll try my best!
Do your best! Do your best, Himeji!
Final Checkpoint
Where are we?
What?
Damn, you girls weren't disqualified?
This is gonna be a pain in the ass.
I thought those scum, Sakamoto and Yoshii,
would be first up for a beating.
They ran off, right?
They're garbage, after all.
They aren't garbage.
Huh?
They aren't!
Not garbage?
They're nothing but troublemaking dumbasses!
What else could we call them?
How 'bout this?
The dregs of society?
That's an insult to dregs.
They should just let themselves get picked up
with the rest of the trash!
Totally, a pair of brain-dead 'tards like them need—
Why must you be so cruel to them?
Certainly, their grades are bad, and they do cause trouble,
but how can you dismiss them as garbage just because of that?
You don't even know!
You have no idea how kind they are!
Huh?
Shouldn't you know better than anyone
just how dumb they are?
Why are you judging them based solely on their scores?
They have many good qualities
that simple grades can't measure!
Cut the crap! We don't care about scum like them!
Akihisa and Sakamoto...
aren't scum or garbage...
no matter what you say!
How annoying.
Beat it, you losers!
We're going anyway.
Let's go, Himeji.
You heard her, Yuuji.
She thinks we're kind.
First I've heard of it.
I'm not as much of a slacker as you,
but I thought I was a pretty cool slacker.
Same here. I'm not as useless as you,
but at least I'm aware of my shortcomings.
Man, what a waste.
Himeji just wasted all the effort
we put into getting them together.
Exactly. I can't believe they got under her skin like that.
Shall we go, Akihisa?
Sure, Yuuji.
It's all-out war now, you bastards!
Jeez, when are they gonna show up?
With our scores, they'll prob'ly chicken out.
'Sup, guys!
Took you long enough!
Let's get started then.
Summon!
Before that, why don't we decide on the penalty?
Penalty?
You guys scheming again?
Don't let that frighten you.
You guys were the ones who wanted the penalty game.
Fine. What about it?
"The losers do whatever the winners want." How about that?
Fine with us.
Let's rumble!
Summon!
What's with those scores?
We'll crush 'em like ants!
Keep on yakking. You'll see.
Let's go, Akihisa.
Okay, Yuuji.
Dash!
What the—they ran away!
After them!
Stop right there!
Where did they go?
Tsunemura, over there!
Damn, what a pain in the ass!
You guys getting tired already?
Over there!
Where are they?
Yoohoo, we're over here!
Damn it!
You take running lessons from a turtle?
Hey, that's rude!
I didn't know they were that slow.
They're just holding back.
Right, guys?
Yoshii! Sakamoto!
Show yourself!
Why don't you try actually using that brain you're so proud of?
I'm getting bored here.
You haven't found us yet?
We can read you guys...
...like a wide open book!
They disappeared!
Did we step out of the physics field?
Too bad.
This is just a trap.
It's we who've seen through your plan.
When did they—
Mr. Hasegawa, your permission to start the battle!
Granted!
Summoned Beings: Summon!
This is now the math field!
Now you can't rely on your great physics scores!
That's cheating!
I don't remember any rule saying we had to
fight at the checkpoint.
Or are you guys just too scared to fight
in any field but physics?
We excel in science and math!
We won't lose in math!
Summon!
Shit!
We got thrashed by that girl and the four-eyes!
And you took advantage of it! Damn you!
Don't screw with us!
Too late to whine about it now.
What did you say?!
There's one good thing about being an idiot.
When they really get into something,
they can simple-mindedly devote all of their attention to it.
I guess some people would just call them obsessed,
but to them that's high praise!
Shut the hell up!
What I'm getting at is...
He booted the head!
...you switched these idiots on!
Why...
did we lose to such idiots?
We've won.
You do remember our promise, don't you?
What're you going to make us do?
That's obvious.
Himeji...
Yoshii.
Kirishima?
if you're looking for her, she's on the roof.
Hurry up; she's waiting.
Thanks, Kirishima.
That's pretty considerate of you.
Not really.
I just like those who try their best,
even when they're afraid.
I really like people like that.
I can't be assed to do my best,
even if it's nothing scary.
I'll leave it at that for you.
Akihisa...
We're all going out for crêpes to celebrate our victory.
Just now, those two third-years came to apologize.
I have you to thank for that, don't I?
I'm sorry for always troubling you!
It's nothing!
You're certainly no princess.
Huh?
Well, no princess would have the courage
to snap at those third-years.
Uh, that was...
Thanks. I was really happy.
We were able to do our best, thanks to what you said.
Thank you for saying that.
Should we go? They're probably waiting for us.
Um, there's something I wanted to ask you.
To ask me?
Yes.
Um...
When are you going to start calling me "Mizuki"?
Wha...?!
You always use Minami's given name,
but you never do the same for me!
The reason is, well, it's kinda complicated—
Then explain.
Uh... we went to elementary school together, remember?
Yes.
So if I called you "Mizuki" just like back then,
it'd be kinda embarrassing for me.
You're lying!
You haven't called me by my name even once
since we started high school!
That's because...
You won't laugh?
I won't!
No matter what?
No matter what!
Actually...
Yes?
I was practicing...
calling you by your name...
Okay...
Argh! Forget about it! We never had this conversation!
Well then, I'll tell you one of my secrets.
Actually...
I haven't given up on my first love.
Hurry up, Akihisa!
Wait! Wh-What did you just—
Aki! Why did you go running off without telling me?
Minami!
You promised to be by my side forever, didn't you?
Ehhh?!
What's going on, Akihisa?
Get lost, Akihisa!
We didn't complete the challenge together.
That means instant marriage.
No way in hell!
Yuuji, wait!
Let's complete it together.
Hey, wait up!
You owe me an explanation!
Stop there!
Jeez, it always ends up like this, doesn't it?
Yep.
hirameite kagayaite
閃いて 輝いて
Flash and sparkle!
denkyuu pikkanko
電球ぴっかんこ
Light bulb goes off!
(hai)
(はいっ)
Yes
shinten shinai yo
進展しないよ
I'm not making progress
dareka jama shiteru No, no!
誰か邪魔してる... No, no!
Oh no, someone's in the way
zenzen tarinai
全然足りない
It's totally not enough
sore ga mondai no koubaisuu
それが問題の公倍数
That's the common multiple of the problem
ryoukai sore nari
了解それなり
I kind of get it
nani ga hontou no koto Baby?
何が本当のこと Baby?
What is it really, baby
mitetara koko de
見てたらここで
If you're watching
zukai shite yo Baby!
図解してよ Baby!
Show it to me, baby
kotoba mo kazu mo kimi wo arawasenai
言葉も数も君を表せない
Words and numbers can't express you
(chu chu chu chu)
(ちゅちゅちゅちゅっ)
(kiss kiss kiss kiss)
kokoro ga biribiri suru S to
心がビリビリするS と
The magnetic forces between S and N
(S to)
(S と)
(S)
N  no jiryoku de
N の磁力で
It electrifies me!
(S, S, Supaaku tsuite nanbaa)
(S, S, SuperくついてNumber)
(Super goes with number!)
(I say No. 1 boy)
(And you're the number one boy!)
omedetou ima kara
おめでとう 今から
Congratulations, from now on
kimi wa My, ma, my otakara
君はMy, ma, my"お宝"
You're my treasure
tokubetsu nanda dou natte mo
特別なんだ どうなっても
You're special
gyuttone gyuttone hanasanai
ぎゅっとねぎゅっとね離さない
I won't let you go, no matter what
watashi wa koi shitai
私は恋したい
I want to love
yume ni genkai wa iranai
夢に限界はいらない
Dreams need no bounds
tokubetsu dayo ne acchatta mo
特別だよね 会っちゃたもん
You must be special since we met!
konna watashi mo yurushichae
こんな私も許しちゃえ
Please forgive me as is
hirameite kagayaite
閃いた 輝いた
It sparkled and flashed
seikai pittanko
正解ぴったんこ
Now I have the answer!
(gyu)
(ぎゅっ)
Don't run in the corridors, dammit!
Good grief.
They really are a bunch of idiots.
Thanks for watching! —FFFpeeps