Towa!
Madam Towa?
Prince Kanata's sister?
I am the Black Princess and the daughter of the great witch Dyspear, Twilight.
That's it!
It's the Perfume!
With refinement, majesty, and elegance...
I am truly...
the one and only princess.
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of three girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
When the sun is out we say "Bonjour!" with strength, grace, and beauty!
We sing happily and go into the world
If at first you feel uncertain, just change your dress to lift your spirits
and find the strength to jump forth
Have faith, princess, and you'll find your love!
You just have to be brave, honest, and splendid
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase the sun and stars
Fly as high as you can, be proud! Go! Princess Precure
Another mistake...
I must play as well as my brother to become a refined lady...
To be a Grand Princess!
But no matter how hard I try...
You can do it.
What?
Who's there?
I shall make your grandiose dream come true.
You will?
Now, come to me.
I see... such a pity.
But if you let your only chance pass you by...
your dear brother would be oh-so-disappointed, no?
Wait!
I want... to become a Grand Princess.
I want my dream to come true!
I am the Black Princess.
She who shall steep the world in despair.
Towa...
Open Your Heart!
Princess vs. Princess!
She transformed...
Is that part of the Black Key's power?
Twilight.
Send the Princess Precures as well as Prince Kanata to their doom.
Very well, Mother.
Towa!
Flora!
Aren't you Kanata's sister?
What happened to y—
Flora!
Looks like words won't get through to her.
I'm sorry, Flora. This is all my—
No.
Anyone would be shocked to see a long-lost relative like this.
But we have to stop her quick.
One thing I can tell is that this Black Key is far stronger and scarier than anything we've seen before.
What's more is the sense of peril to it...
As though it's meant to burn away her very being along with us!
The power of despair brought forth from that Perfume...
is trying to devour its very owner, Towa, as well?
That means that Madam Towa could...
Don't worry!
I won't let that happen!
I may not know the details,
but we clearly can't leave her be.
What's a family reunion without a good ol' heart to heart?
Girls...
With the Dress Up Keys...
and the power of the Princess Precures' dreams,
you should be able to fend off the powers of despair and free Towa from the Black Key!
So, fight Keys with Keys!
Ready, girls?
Yeah!
We've no time to stay our hands!
Let's give her all we've got!
Shooting Star!
Shine, O shooting stars!
Precure!
Meteor Humming!
Bubble!
Rage, O bubbles!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
Now finish her by going into Mode Elegant!
Mode Elegant?!
Stop, Towa!
If you don't, you'll...
Towa!
It's futile.
Twilight can no longer hear your pleas.
Can you feel it, Prince Kanata?
This is the power of despair.
Dyspear!
Your sister once had a dream.
Her dream was fittingly grand for the princess of Hope Kingdom,
leading her to spend her youth training in pursuit of it.
But the grander the dream, the longer and more precipitous the road to it becomes.
Once I spoke to the princess's pain and frustration over her own inexperience, then...
I want my dream to come true!
The princess took that first step herself...
into the depths of the Forest of Despair.
The Forest... of Despair? Towa did?
Even so... why? Why did you take Towa?!
To extinguish...
the kingdom's source of hope that the princess stood for!
You know full well...
just how much the princess meant to Hope Kingdom.
And just how deeply into sorrow and despair Hope Kingdom would plunge without her!
That despair fueled me and gave me strength.
The princess had served her role then and there, but I thought of an amusing use for her.
I purged her of her memories, persona, and dreams to raise her as my own.
As the princess of Dysdark!
The princess of hope would become the princess of despair to vanquish what hopes remained.
There would be no deeper despair for you all.
But in the end, she's just a failure who couldn't defeat the Precures even with a Dress Up Key.
Twilight, at least let your final battle end in something other than disappointment.
Burn the Princess Precures and their final hope to cinders!
No matter the cost!
Towa...
Very well.
As you command, Mother!
Towa!
Towa...
The light that shined on Hope Kingdom has vanished into darkness.
You're barred from your dreams and now relieved of your hopes.
You've nothing left to serve as your crutch.
Now, despair.
There's still one dream...
There's one hope... one dream...
that you haven't extinguished!
Flora...
Twin buns!
Beautiful!
Princess Twilight, how refined!
'Kay, seems like things are heating up.
Princess Twilight!
Meeting you was the greatest joy that I, Shut, have ever been graced with!
How uncouth.
What is there left to stand up for, Princess Precure?
There's hope.
And it's standing right before my eyes!
Then meet your doom at the hands of that which you call hope.
"Violins aren't meant to be played with heart."
Remember when you told me that?
But your performance tugged at my heart!
Your song made me want to play as beautifully as you!
What drew me to it must have been the dream that even your imprisoned heart couldn't hold back!
As well as the love for your long lost Kanata the melody was brimming with!
I already said that the princess's heart vanished long ago.
Nobody can play that beautifully without a heart!
Your heart was only locked away!
Your dreams for your future and your love for Kanata are still alive and well within you!
How dare you insult my Princess Twilight so!
Cure Flora, watch your back, 'kay?
Now, Flora!
Let's finish this!
Yeah!
Girls...
let's go!
Exchange!
Mode Elegant!
Lily!
Bubble!
Shooting Star!
Shine, our three powers!
Precure!
Trinity Explosion!
The Black Key!
We're not done! Let's push through!
It's futile.
The despair that flows from the Black Key I created...
cannot be overpowered by the likes of you.
Especially not without the power of all twelve Dress Up Keys!
We're not alone!
The power of hope...
And dreams... lie within you, Towa.
Towa...
do you remember this song?
I used to play it so often just to see you smile.
Seeing you practice to one day play by my side filled me with joy.
I want to play violin with you once more.
That is my dream.
It's a dream that can't come true without you.
Towa, please remember...
that day you told me your dream...
because if your wish is strong, it will certainly come true!
What?!
Is that...
It's the Light of Dreams!
It can't be! How could the dream I erased return once more?!
Brother...
Towa...
How could this be?!
Who is this pauper?!
Please, Lock, what happened to my Twilight?!
Twilight's gone. She's just a normal girl now, 'kay?
No! This cannot be!
'Kay, now that was anticlimactic.
Hey, we gotta get going if we don't wanna get caught in this, 'kay?
Lady Dyspear seems none too pleased, 'kay?
I've got a bad feeling about this!
It seems she doesn't plan on
letting us leave in one piece.
Where are we going?
The gate is this way!
Aroma and I went to your world through it!
We don't stand a chance against Dyspear as we are now.
You all must be exhausted after that fight, too.
For now, we have to retreat!
You won't escape.
Your dreams won't come true.
Your hopes will vanish.
The world will drown in despair!
What are those?!
It's Dyspear's magic!
That's it!
Hurry and jump inside it!
Talk about the nick of time!
Brother...
Welcome back, Towa.
There's nothing to worry about anymore.
I'll protect you.
Now go through the gate!
Right!
Come on, Kanata!
Go on without me.
Huh?
Kanata?
Once you're through the gate,
I'll destroy it and shut it for good.
If I don't stop it here, Dyspear's magic will never give up the chase.
They'll certainly pursue you to your world.
I can't...
let that happen!
Don't! You can't stop them alone!
I'll he—
Haruka.
Huh?
Thanks to you girls, I finally met Towa once again.
With her, I found the hope I once lost.
I'll see you soon.
I still have a dream to chase, after all.
Kanata!
Haruka, take care of Towa.
If you wish from the bottom of your heart, then I'm certain...
we'll meet again, Haruka!
Kanata!
Brother...
Future and memory
Linked by melody
Be a princess
and dance with me
Un, deux, trois, Precure
Happiness is worth more than gems and gold
It shines like rubies and people's hearts
Let the curtain rise on our ball
Gorgeous! Precious! Shall we dance? We dreamed of this moment
Très bien! With strength, grace, and beauty!
Dreams change your world
You yourself will unlock the door to tomorrow
Bonjour, bonjour
Precure!
If you wish from the bottom of your heart, your dream is sure to come true!
That's what Kanata taught me!
We all make mistakes.
If you fall, just try, try again!
So don't give in to despair!
Let's all become Grand Princesses together, Towa!
Go! Princess Precure:
The Flames of Hope!
Her Name is Cure Scarlet!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Saitama Prefecture - Riina (Age 6)
Tokyo - Yukino (Age 6)