Please !
Einzbern Consultation Room
Please! Einzbern Consultation Room.
Part 5
This isn't fair. It's too cruel!
Lancer-san starred in the wrong anime.
He's such a perfect hottie...
Why hasn't a game for teenage girls based on Celtic mythology come out yet?
Excuse me, I saw your signboard outside.
Is this the reception area?
Ah, this is no time to be crying.
Instructor, we have another customer.
I'll show him in.
That voice...
I see, he's finally here.
It's probably thanks to Zecchan's signboard.
At this rate, the Great Grail will be activated soon.
Whoa, almost lost myself there.
I need to concentrate.
I'm currently a counselor who listens to everyone's troubles.
What's more, our customer this time is you-know-who.
I have to protect timid, little Zecchan.
I knew this would happen.
Zecchan isn't quite ready to handle a Servant consumed by darkness yet.
Instructor, this is bad!
Yeah, I know.
Our customer this time is really scary, like a vengeful ghost-
He's super cute!
It's out of this world! Our customer's the perfect hot guy!
What?
Fiend
Kiritsugu
I'm the dual spearwielder of the knights of Fianna, Diarmuid of the Radiant Face.
Chivalry dictates that we face each other in a fair fight!
My heart's fluttering!
This is weird, Instructor!
My heart flutters whenever I look at him!
Such an unfaithful guy.
He uses his charm on middle-school girls as well as married women.
Might you be the instructor of this place?
Both student and teacher are female.
Is it popular nowadays for the likes of women to be skilled in fighting arts?
Oh? You don't like the idea of women being in the front lines?
Anyone can take up arms if necessary
during battle, don't you think?
No, you're absolutely right.
I happen to know of a female knight who shines like the stars.
Fiend
Kiritsugu
Now, let us fight fairly.
Wait!
This is a consultation room!
No violence, please!
But the signboard outside says Einzbern do-
You must have made some kind of mistake.
This is the Einzbern Consultation Room, not a place to fight.
I see.
Fiend
Kiritsugu
Please excuse my mistake.
The warrior's blood in me took over.
I've always wanted to try conquering a dojo!
Again...
Fiend
Kiritsugu
Oh, I see.
I suppose that does happen sometimes!
Please have a cup of tea.
Allow me to introduce myself properly.
I am Diarmuid O'Dyna.
I happened to see your signboard while training, so I let myself in.
Please tell me about yourselves.
I am Irisviel, and I work as a lawyer here.
Yeah, I'm Student No. 0!
I'm her student and apparently a Master!
I see.
You're among the loveliest Masters I've seen.
My Master is a splendid gentleman,
but he is bound by his responsibilities.
If only he had but a semblance of your smile...
Master... Master...
What was my Master like?
What is this?
I can't remember!
Specifically, I can't remember anything about the woman beside my Master
and anything that happened beyond Episode 16 Part A...
Th-This must be amnesia!
Instructor, could this gentleman be Lancer-san?
Look at this book!
His mental trauma must've disrupted his memories.
This will be tricky.
There's a lot I can't remember too, so I understand his pain.
I think you're perfectly fine this way.
Just forget about your painful past, Lancer-san!
Painful past?
Does that include my time with Grainné too?
Yes!
That unhappy face doesn't suit you, Lancer-san!
Your face should shine like it usually does!
It's strange.
After hearing your words, I feel that
it's fine to forget about my past.
I see.
I must've met a wonderful end.
Of course you did!
Let's pretend none of that Urobuchi-style stuff ever happened!
You died a noble death in a one-on-one duel against Saber-san!
Yes, you're right!
That must be it!
I don't understand everything too well, but thank you.
I won't let my past control me any longer.
I met a wonderful opponent in a worthy battlefield and realized my deepest knightly desires!
My Master never envied me or doubted me.
Lady Sola-Ui and Lord Kayneth are a loving couple.
And I've had enough of Grainné.
Very well, I'll believe all that and go see the King of Knights!
Saber's head shall be the pride of my spear!
Roar!
I'll redo everything from Episode 4!
Yay, that's the spirit!
Your battle has only just begun!
Right, Instructor?
My my, you sure like to dream, Lancer.
But does this sit well with your chivalry?
Of course it does.
If it comes to it, we could even come to a compromise through a fighting game.
There, I shall cross swords with Saber once more
and progress from the proper and noble
Grail War to a romantic relationship with her...
Vegalta?!
Fool!
Open your eyes to reality, Lancer!
How could your heart be so weak?!
Remember!
This is...
Editor
Kiritsugu Emiya
what happened...
in the Grail War!
This is...
Yes, I...
Again...
Again!
That's horrible of you, Instructor!
Why are you tormenting someone who's already dead?
No.
You cannot escape your past, Zecchan.
Even if you deny it, problems will surface.
They'll come back to haunt you eventually!
The fact that you cheated will never change!
You really think it's okay to just forget?
Cheaters should be struck down here and now!
This seems to be getting really personal...
Anyway, Lancer-san wasn't cheating around!
It was an elopement for love!
There's no love or immorality in eloping!
Lancer, admit it!
You're also responsible for what happened!
Ridiculous...
Diar
Are you saying it's my fault?
That my face has brought about disaster yet again?
Then explain it to me!
Where exactly did I go wrong?
Isn't it obvious?
What's wrong is...
...your cute guy karma!
Instructor?
Cute guy karma.
It is a fate that awaits all handsome men.
The cuter the guy is, the more curses he will bear from those around him.
If you're good-looking, your bad end karma will increase 20%.
If your personality's good, it'll increase another 30%.
If you make girls around you want it even though you don't, that's another 30%!
And if you're voiced by Midorikawa, that's another 90%!
He was already out from the beginning, Instructor!
Your problem is that you're too perfect in both body and mind.
It wouldn't be so bad if only your face was pretty,
but combined with your pure heart, there's no way girls could stop themselves from trampling on you.
Lancer, if only you weren't such a perfect guy,
then Kayneth's hairline wouldn't have receded so far!
I see. I see now!
The sufferings of my unwanted lords never even crossed my mind because I cared for nothing but my chivalry!
How disloyal could I get?!
I'm such a fool! Such a damn fool!
A heedless fool like me should be impaled by a spear and die!
Roar!
Fiend
Kiritsugu
Thank you.
I made a fool of myself in front of you.
You did.
I'd rather not have seen it.
It's fine, Lancer.
You can now proudly take your place as a Heroic Spirit with no regrets, right?
Yes, I most definitely can.
Farewell, my beautiful ladies!
A loser like myself belongs in the crimson flames!
He's gone.
Lancer-san had a painful past, but it
worked out in the end, right? Instructor?
Instructor?
Hmm? Did you say something, Zecchan?
Nah, I was just talking to myself.
All right, time to get focused.
Instructor, for today's lecture-
Sorry, but I'd like to rest today.
The preparations are almost complete, so
I should head down and see what's happening.
Zecchan, please watch the office for me!
Instructor left.
She's been acting suspiciously these days.
Is it really okay for me to stay here?
I get the feeling I really should get my
memories back, just like Lancer-san did.