Wow!
I've never seen a Share Crystal this bright before!
It's amazing!
What does this mean, Neppy?
As you can see,
Planeptune is booming right now!
Our Share value had been showing a gradual downward trend,
but one day it suddenly skyrocketed,
and now it's rapidly outstripping the values of the other three nations.
How is this happening?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because Planeptune has what this era wants: 64-bit architecture!
Stopping Eden's invasion was probably the single greatest contributor.
Still, this feels like too drastic a change.
Well, Nep-Nep did give it her all.
Yeah, she did.
Congrats, Sis.
You know me! When I get serious, I can work miracles!
That aside, here's today's real agenda!
Pay close attention!
I want to thank all of our citizens,
so I'm thinking of opening up the Basilicom grounds and holding a huge celebration!
I call it:
the Dynamite Wonder Festival!
Why?
Why did it end up like this?
I'm just a social activist.
Only 1 hour of games per day!
An incomprehensible code sequence
Tell me what it means, compiler
I can't make sense of this binary tree
Just 0s and 1s won't help you communicate
Ping link! Connecting you and us
Hit check! Are you in or out?
Everything's pure
You're a Dimension Tripper
Kick open the dimensional gates and get over here
To this sparkling world
We've formed the strongest party, with hundredfold bonds
And you'll be one of us
#11 The Messenger (Aggressor)
From the Ancient Past
So anyway, the festival starts tomorrow.
You're all invited!
Here!
You called us here for this?
I don't have time for this nonsense.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Blanc!
Wait!
Hey, wait!
I know you didn't mean any harm,
but don't you think you're being a bit insensitive, Neptune?
Ever since that uprising,
every nation except Planeptune has had to cope with plummeting Share values.
Well, I know that.
I'm sure it hit Blanc harder than the rest of us.
We were overtaken in an instant by Planeptune,
which had had the lowest Share value for years on end.
And Lowee's an old and proud nation.
Lastation's not even like that,
but this is still so frustrating for me.
Well, I'm sure we'll bounce back in no time.
Hang on a sec.
We signed a treaty of friendship, you know?
It shouldn't matter who's got the most Sha—
Well, it does.
The treaty doesn't change the fact that we're still competing over Share Energy.
Indeed.
I'm sorry,
but I'm not so selfless that I could bring myself to celebrate another nation's Share rise.
Hey...
What about 5pb? I'd asked her to perform at the opening ceremony.
She's already scheduled to appear on my live stream that day,
so that won't be happening.
Vert...
Aren't you coming either, Noire?
Nope. I'm too busy.
We still don't know anything about the Share-producing machine we found in Eden.
And there's lots more I have to—
Fine.
But if you happen to have some free time, you're always welcome to come here.
Okay?
Neptune...
See you later, Noire.
Welcome home, Sis.
Welcome home.
It's good to be back.
How did the investigation go?
I believe we'll be able to report our findings tomorrow.
Get a move on.
Hey, let's play some games, Sis!
The new version of Lowee Sports is out.
So excited!
Yeah, let's play.
Ga-thunk!
Hey there, viewers of Abnes Channel.
Long time no see!
I'm Abnes, ally of little girls everywhere!
I've received word that tons of little girls are being gathered at Planeptune's Basilicom.
Smells like a conspiracy to me!
Time to swoop in and save those little girls!
Ga-thunk! Your conspiracy ends here!
D-Don't let their tricks fool you!
This is a plot to deceive little girls!
I'm sure this nation's little goddess is up to no good—
Geez, be careful!
It's you, the little goddess!
At last, your time has come.
I'll prove today, once and for all, that a little girl can't be a CPU!
You'd best be prepared.
Got that?
Be a good girl and leave
your CPU days behind!
Er...
Who were you again?
She doesn't remember me...
Sis, we need to deliver these right away!
Yeah, I know.
Hey, Nepgear.
She can help you with the delivery.
Oh, are you a volunteer?
Could you take this to the Green Hill ride over there?
I'm Abnes!
Ally of little girls everywhere!
We've met before!
Huh? We have?
They really don't remember me!
Hello, Blanc?
Can you make it after all?
Huh?
Geez, she's so pushy.
I happen to be busy too, you know.
Blanc!
I'm here.
Where are you?
Blanc!
Getter Ravine!
What are you doing, Blanc?!
Hand over the Shares, Neptune!
What are you saying?
The treaty of friendship prohibits taking Share Energy by force—
But stealing it is okay?
What is that supposed to mean?
I don't get it.
I looked up the Share
movements of each nation.
And surprise, surprise,
Planeptune's Shares went up exactly as much as Lowee's went down.
Lastation and Leanbox had their Shares stolen like that too.
No wonder your Share value went through the roof, right, Neptune?
Hold on.
This is the first I've heard of this.
I didn't even know you could do that—
Sure you didn't.
I'm telling the truth. Please believe me!
Okay, let's say it wasn't you.
Maybe Histoire did it.
Histy?
No way.
Then maybe it was Nepgear!
Sis!
Don't fight!
Please stop!
You two, shut the hell up!
This is an international dispute.
No, we won't!
There's no way Nepgear and the others would do something that bad!
We're friends!
Well, someone sure as hell did!
Consider this a warning, then.
But know this, Neptune.
If you continue to feign ignorance,
we'll declare war.
What is going on?
There. All better.
Just be careful when you run.
Wait, Purple Sister!
This way!
Wait!
Behold ye, far and wide!
The festival's a roaring success.
Wonderfully done, Neptune.
My, Noire.
You came for me?
You doing okay?
E-mailing me from within maximum security?
You've got some balls.
Why, Noire, I just wanted to have a bit of girl talk with you.
If you've got something
to say, just spit it out.
I'm busy.
Blunt as always, I see.
No wonder you don't have any friends.
Out with it!
Okay, okay.
I've had a lot of time on my hands lately, you know?
So I investigated my client.
You know, the one from the Eden case.
Just to be clear, I've done nothing to breach the terms of my contract.
After all, it said nothing about what I could or couldn't do after its expiry.
Who cares about that?
Well? Did you figure anything out?
Who's the mastermind?
Well, you see...
The time has come.
Rei Ryghts?
Isn't she just someone who got dragged into your mess?
Yes, that's what I thought all along too.
Are you saying she was a con artist?
I would have seen through any mere scam.
So, to have fooled even me, Rei must be...
Must be what?
Something much more sinister...
I suppose?
You want me to give the official address?
Yes.
Neppy ran off somewhere
and hasn't come back.
Very well.
I wonder what happened to her.
Lady Histoire!
What's going on?!
Finally...
it has returned.
My continent,
my nation:
Tari!
What's that?
Who is that?
You there, the not-so-little goddess!
Little girls are being held captive there!
Stop goofing off and save them!
O-Okay!
Oh, you're here already,
Planeptune's CPU?
Wait, are you Rei Ryghts?
Oh, I don't like that one bit.
I mean, that's a pretty lame name for a goddess, wouldn't you say?
Are you a new goddess too?
Say what?
Would you mind not insulting me?
I've been a goddess for far longer than you have.
I'm Tari's CPU.
The CPU of the great nation that rules this land.
Tari's CPU?
What's with that continent?
Who's Neppy talking to?
I don't know.
The only thing I do know is that
that thing shines with the light of a Share Crystal.
The one talking to Neptune is,
without a doubt,
a CPU.
Tari?
You mean the ancient superpower that was said to have been destroyed eons ago?
Bzzt. That's where you're wrong!
It wasn't destroyed at all.
It's just been waiting all along for the perfect time to make a comeback.
Okay, so assuming you are who you say...
What are you after?
This land,
and all those who inhabit it.
Let me have it all.
Do that, and I might even spare your life.
In fact, this all belonged to me in the first place.
Shut your trap and give it back, bitch!
That's how it is.
Screw you.
This is Planeptune—
my nation.
You think I'd just hand it over to you?
Oh? Is that your final answer?
You sure?
Wanna think it over?
There are no other options.
In that case...
Energy charge, okay!
Threatening me won't get you anywhere.
That so? Just a sec.
How about this, then?
Can you still say that now,
O great CPU?
Pong Laser Cannon...
Fire!
What are you doing?!
We need those!
Look out!
Are you okay?
I can't tell the world about
this without a camera!
Well?
Singing a different tune now?
Welcome to Vert's Room.
Today's guest is 5pb, our diva.
It seems she'll be playing one of the singles from her new album for the first time on today's show.
Stay tuned until the end.
Did Uni reply?
Yeah!
She says she wasn't allowed to go to Planeptune's festival either.
Will we not get to hang out with Nepgear anymore?
What are you talking about?
There's no way that'd happen.
But Sis was really mad.
No good.
I can't get through to the Internet or phone network.
Looks like all of our communications systems have been destroyed!
Which means...
We can't look for outside help.
Changed your mind, huh?
You'd have to be a retard to stick to your guns after all that.
You're right. I have another answer for you.
I won't let you have your way any longer.
This is my nation.
These are my people.
And I'll protect them all!
I've come to this universe of countless stars
To start our search for the ultimate game
We're goddesses, the giga and tera
What are you getting so serious for?
You're in a trance. You've gone nuts!
I get you. I really do
It's not love
But there's desire
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Let's start a New Game+
Here we go! Way to go, Neptune!
This rectangle pulse
is a love song
Here we go! Good to go, Neptune!
Friendship, love, bifrost
We're all friends, even if it's all a bit ridiculous
Good job, my sweet heart
See you next week!
No good.
I can't get through to the Internet or phone network.
Which means...
Oh, come on!
The pre-orders for the new console just opened,
The Bonds (Bifrost) To Tomorrow
but I can't get through!
Hey!