Once you know how, it's pretty easy.
I don't think I'll be losing anymore.
I'll give it to you.
That's what you were after, right?
Hey.
I don't want to owe you anything.
This makes us even, okay?
Let's go home, Madoka.
Sayaka-chan...
Sorry...
I'm just a little tired.
Don't push yourself. Hold onto me.
That idiot.
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 8          I'm really stupid
Service for today has ended
Sayaka-chan, you shouldn't be fighting like that.
You're lying when you say it doesn't hurt.
It hurt just watching you.
You can't say it's okay to hurt yourself just because you can't feel it.
If I hadn't done that, I wouldn't have been able to win.
I don't have any natural talent for this sort of thing.
Even if you fight like that and win, it's not going to help you out in the end.
And what would help me?
Now that I've been turned into this thing, how can anything help me?
Sayaka-chan...
All I can do now is kill witches.
I'm just a rock without any other purpose.
I just pretend to be alive by moving around a dead body.
Who would do something for me when I'm like this?
Thinking about it is pointless.
But I'm just wondering what could make you happier...
You should fight, then.
Huh?
Kyubey told me. You have more natural talent than anyone else, right?
You can take out the witches just like that, without having to suffer like I do, right?
I... That's not...
If you want to do something for me, how about trying to walk in my shoes first?
But you can't, can you? Of course not.
You couldn't give up your humanity just because you pity me.
It's not pity. I...
You can do anything, but instead you sit there, and I'm the one who has to go through all of this.
Don't try to act like you know what it's like when you're not even willing to do it yourself.
Sayaka-chan.
Don't follow me.
I'm so stupid...
What did I just say?!
No one can save me anymore...
Homura
The Walpurgis Night is predicted to appear in this area.
What are you basing that on?
Statistics.
Statistics?
I've never heard of a Walpurgis coming to this city before.
Just what did you base your statistics on?
Neither of us is exactly the trustworthy type, but don't you think you could give me a little more insight into what's going on?
I'd like to know as well, Akemi Homura.
Why the hell are you here?
I guess I wasn't invited.
I came here tonight to deliver some information that I thought you'd be very interested in.
Huh?
Miki Sayaka is depleting herself far faster than I imagined.
Using magic isn't the only problem; she's started to carry a curse within herself.
And whose fault do you think that is?
At this rate, it might become an issue before the Walpurgis Night arrives.
I recommend you be cautious.
What does that mean? What are you talking about?
How about you try asking her instead of me?
I imagine you already know, Akemi Homura.
I thought so.
I'm very interested in where you obtained that information.
Are you...
I've heard what you had to say.
Begone.
You're just going to let him be?
Killing it won't solve anything.
Well anyway, what issue was he talking about involving Miki Sayaka?
Her Soul Gem has accrued too many impurities.
If it is not purified soon, the damage will be irreparable.
Homura
The helping verb "must" means that someone has to do something, an obligation of sorts. But "have to" has a different...
I should've followed her...
Huh? Shizuki-san, is your house in this direction?
I don't think I remember you ever going this way.
You're right. I'm in the complete opposite direction.
Huh?
Then why are you going this way today?
I want...
to talk to you about something, Kamijou-kun.
Huh?
She hasn't come home? Not since last night?
Okay... Umm... I understand.
Okay. Thank you.
I need to find Sayaka-chan.
Why don't you get it?
You're already near your breaking point.
Fight only the witches.
Shut up.
Mind your own business.
Your Soul Gem is already at its limit.
If you do not purify it now...
Use this.
What are you planning now?
I've had enough.
You don't have the time to doubt others right now.
Does it bother you that much to have somebody help you?
I'm going to become a different type of magical girl than you all.
I've decided that.
I won't associate myself with people who use and abandon others.
I don't need any reward for my work.
I'll never use magic for my own benefit.
You'll die.
If I were to die, it would be when I am no longer able to kill witches.
In other words, there'd be no need for me anymore.
That's fine, then.
The world doesn't need me if I can't even beat the witches.
Why are you doing this?
I only want to save you.
Why won't you believe me?
I don't know...
I just know somehow...
that you're a liar.
You look like you've given up on everything.
You're always saying empty words.
This is no different.
You say you're trying to help me out, but you're really thinking about something else completely, aren't you?
You can't fool me like that.
And in turn, you keep hurting Madoka more and more.
Madoka has nothing to do with this.
No, everything is for her.
You're pretty quick.
Yes, you got it.
I don't want to save you.
I just don't want Madoka to have to see you destroy yourself.
If you refuse me here, you'll die either way.
And if you're just going to continue to make Madoka suffer further...
Then I might as well...
kill you this instant with my own hands,
Miki Sayaka.
Hey! Hurry up and get out of here!
Are you nuts?
Weren't you trying to save her?
Let me go.
I get it. If I hold onto you like this, you can't use that weird technique of yours.
Huh?
Damn it.
You can't let them make any excuses.
You need to take control of every penny they've made.
Women are stupid, so if you give them a little bit of their money, they'll use it on something stupid.
Yeah, you're right. You can't treat them like people.
You need to train them like they're dogs or something.
She gets off on that, too.
If you just threaten a girl and say you're gonna punch 'em, they'll usually keep their mouths shut.
You stop paying attention for a second, and then all of a sudden they're saying they wanna get married or something.
You can't spoil them.
There's no way a cabaret girl like her could earn the same amount ten years from now.
She needs to learn her place, am I right?
They're really annoying when you get rid of them, too.
You're really good at that, Shou-san. I'm really jealous.
I need to learn how to do that—
Hey, tell me more about her.
Huh?
The woman you were just talking about. Tell me more about her.
Are you in middle school?
You shouldn't be out so late at night.
That person cared about you and wanted to make you happy, so she tried really hard, right?
You knew that, right?
And now you're comparing her to a dog.
You're not even going to thank her?
You're going to throw her away because she's not useful anymore?
Who the hell is this? Someone you know?
N-No...
Is this world worth saving?
Why was I fighting? Tell me.
I'm ordering you to tell me right now.
If you don't, I'll...
Sayaka-chan, where are you...
Do you hate me too?
If I hated you, would you return Sayaka-chan to normal?
I can't. I don't have the power to do that.
You once said I could become a really amazing magical girl... Was that true?
Amazing is an understatement.
You'd become a magical girl of unbelievable power.
Probably the strongest in the world.
If I had accepted your offer, I wonder if Sayaka-chan would've become a magical girl.
Sayaka made her own wish come true.
That is completely unrelated to you.
Why me?
I don't know either.
To put it bluntly, the scale of your latent power is so great that it theoretically isn't even possible.
I'd like someone to explain it to me too.
I see.
If you released your power, we wouldn't just be talking about miracles anymore; it might even be possible to warp the laws of the universe itself.
I still don't even know why you alone have so much potential resting within you.
I thought I had nothing good going for me.
I thought I would continue on living until I died, never helping anyone, never being useful.
That made me frustrated, and it made me feel alone. But I thought I couldn't do anything about it.
Looks like reality turned out to be quite different.
Madoka, you can even become an omnipotent god if you wish for it.
I wonder if I could do what you can't.
For example?
If I contracted with you, could I return Sayaka-chan to normal?
I'm sure you could do that without a problem.
Would you offer your soul for that wish?
If I could help Sayaka-chan, I'd do it.
I'd become a—
Th-That was terrible! You didn't have to kill him!
Why... Why do you always sacrifice yourself?
Don't demean yourself by saying that you're of no use to anyone or that you're worthless.
Think about the people who care about you! Stop doing that!
How come you don't realize there are people who would be sad if they lost you?!
What about the people who were trying to protect you?!
Homura-chan...
Have we...
Have we met before?
I...
I'm sorry...
I need to look for Sayaka-chan.
Wait.
It's too late for Miki Sayaka...
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Madoka!
You know, it's pointless trying.
You don't learn either, do you?
There are plenty of replacements, but someone taking one out for no reason is still annoying.
It's a waste.
This marks the second time you've killed me.
But now I know what type of technique you're using.
That was a time-manipulation magic, wasn't it?
Thought so.
I had a feeling that was the case...
You're not from this timeline, are you?
I know who you are and what you're really planning.
I see.
That's why you're trying so hard to stop me.
You want to change Kaname Madoka's fate that much?
That's right.
I'm going to stop you, Kyubey.
No, I should say, Incubator.
I finally found you.
Just how stubborn do you plan to be?
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Huh? You're not acting like yourself.
Yeah.
That's because I don't really care anymore.
I don't know anymore... what exactly I was trying to protect, or what was so important to me.
Hey...
The balance between hope and despair—it keeps itself at zero. When was it you told me that?
I understand what you mean now.
I did save quite a few people, but in exchange, hatred and jealousy filled my heart.
I even hurt my best friend.
Sayaka, are you...
Someone has to be cursed to balance out a wish for someone else's happiness.
That's how we magical girls work.
I'm really stupid.
Sayaka!
This country calls growing women "girls," right?
Then it only makes sense to call those who will eventually become witches "magical girls."
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光がときを超えて
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ壊すだろう
Now that you've drunk every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
I want to see you, smiling with the power to shatter even darkness,
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was young.
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
that now lays in my frightened hands.
思いだけが頼るすべて
This wish will awaken that light.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Illustrator Takuya Fujima
Cooperation Tanaka Kentaro
You might think I'm stupid, but I don't want to give up until we know for sure that she can't be saved.
Episode 9       I won't let that happen
I won't let that happen.
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: guymam
limitbreakingcat
Timer: sportsrmyname
kozu (minor)
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
goof