Their wishes have been exhausted
nozomi ha tsukita
their wishes have been exhausted
Chaika the Coffin Princess
Their hope, as strong as steel
hagane no youna
their hope, as strong as steel
has been turned into glass
kibou sae ima wa garasu
Chaika the Coffin Princess
I can't reach my future
kizutsuki hateta
i can't reach my future
in this body
kono karada dewa
that is so damaged
mirai made tadori tsukenu
I believe and take pride in you
dakara shinji hokoreru kimi
i believe and take pride in you
Letting you go, against my wishes, is...
kamen no kao de tebanasu noga
letting you go, against my wishes, is...
like meeting to say good-bye
sayonara no tame deai
The flower petals bloom to be scattered
chiru tame ni hana wa saku
chiru tame ni  hana wa saku
the flower petals bloomto be scattered
This is destiny
towa no shinri yo
this is destiny
The cruel story
zankoku na monogatari
the cruel story
Betray, and be betrayed
uragiri uragirare
betray, and be betrayed
Good night, let's leave while still dreaming
oyasumi yume no mama tabitatou
oyasumi yume no
good night, let's leave
mama tabitatou
while still dreaming
The song I hear has become sad, so sad
sonotoki kikoeru uta kanashii kanashii uta
sonotoki kikoeru uta
the song i hear has  become sad, so sad
kanashii kanashii uta
Don't die, don't die
shinu na shinu na
don't die, don't die
Paint over the darkness
shikkoku wo nuritsubuse
paint over the darkness
Furom, iestrov...
Elmuto... Eril!
Natow!
Come forth, The Shtola!
What?
Come forth, tense atmosphere!
The Strays!
Jentol, winsica!
Finished already?
Do you surrender?
Not surrender!
Chaika!
A Wizard's Pride
Chaika.
Are you okay?
Okay.
Ilm, es, alas!
Schu, limic...
Come forth, that which bursts and scatters its mark!
The Burst!
From one to the next... Typical saboteurs.
Too bad for you!
Anything else you're still hiding?
I can still fight.
Yeah.
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
A wizard's strength is supported by experience.
And experience is what you lack.
Blow away! The Blow!
Chaika!
Assa, schron, misam, winhel...
Come forth, The Preventer!
Chaika!
That's it for you, hero.
Give remains!
What's wrong, Chaika?
You finally got your first remains. Aren't you happy?
Why don't you celebrate a little?
Nothing to celebrate.
No?
But, damn, that thing's pretty creepy.
Rude! Father's remains, sacred!
Sorry, sorry.
I hope we can get to the next hero before the
white girl and her friends do.
Yeah, while we're on a roll.
You're strong.
Both mentally and physically.
Once we're hired, we don't betray our employer.
That's the one thing we take pride in.
What's wrong? Remembering that saboteur kid?
No! Absolute no!
Bingo, huh?
Ow!
That's dangerous! I'm driving here!
It's your fault for not having any tact.
Gather remains, objective...
Fake white girl, father's funeral.
Objective very clear.
Huh?
But my objective, revenge. Vague.
Specific circumstances, unclear.
Won't you find that out once you gather them all?
Yeah, so let's get as many as we can!
Rude!
Okay, okay...
What's wrong?
Guy...
I see you've acquired Emperor Gaz's forearm.
That's good to see.
You just show up out of nowhere...
Whatever.
We were just thinking about getting ahead of the white girl and the saboteur siblings.
Where can we find the next remains?
You brought information, right?
Yes, I did.
Tell where!
In a fishing village by the ocean about a day's travel from here,
there's a hero by the name of Clay Morgan.
We go, quickly!
No need to be in such a hurry.
I have one other bit of information.
Tell!
You might want to visit the island off the coast, as well.
Island?
I think you'll find something pleasing there.
You want to keep Captain Gillette's belongings here, then?
I want to leave things so that he can come back at any time.
That's why we're keeping the name of the Gillette Squad, too.
Yes, I've heard from the chief.
What's that?
We have no way to counter her...
What happened to the traps?
She destroyed most of them.
Damn it.
Toru... Akari...
Not surrender!
Yeah, I know.
We can't get any closer at all...
If we just wait for her, she'll use it to her advantage.
I'll be a decoy.
Decoy, dangerous!
If we stay here, we'll all be blown away along with this rock.
It's do or die. We have to make a move. Got it?
Understood.
I'll distract her as much as I can.
Akari, get to her from behind.
Chaika, don't panic.
Just look for a place where you can take precise aim.
Right. Precision, important.
Okay. Let's go.
I am steel.
Steel knows no fear. Steel knows no doubt.
When faced with my enemy, I hesitate not.
I am a weapon to destroy thee.
Iron-Blood Transformation!
Trying to get me from behind, eh?
Alay, salama!
That's it, Chaika! Keep going!
Sabah, amasala, missah!
The Sealed!
Toru!
Brother!
Toru...
Salimic, binnu, alay...
Come forth, to strike and crush!
The Slugger!
Ow...
Toru!
I am man.
Toru! No problem?
Yes, problem.
Relieved.
What about you? Are you okay?
Yes! Yuko, ippon, waza-ari!
Yeah... We got her.
So you can do it when you try.
I've lost.
Yes. Because of your advice.
That wasn't the only reason.
What?
Couldn't you tell?
A moment ago, you wished to protect him with all your strength.
A strong magical attack is most dependent upon a wizard's strong emotions.
Yes...
Maybe you really are
the daughter of the emperor.
Understand, grateful.
Fredrica!
Oh... Is this cat yours?
Yes!
Lady Claudia, it is time.
You're such a pest. I know that.
Yes, ma'am... I am sorry,
but please return immediately.
Our work is falling behind.
Let's have tea first.
We can spare that much time, right?
Tea time, awaited!
Want grape everything!
"A sword drawn at night can never again be sheathed."
That's rather cryptic.
Yes...
But I'll take this fortune to heart and live by it.
What does yours say?
Mine says...
"It is your unchanging love that will save your loved one."
Vivi.
This is Captain Gillette's notebook. It was in the April.
Captain Nikolai and I checked the contents earlier,
and it's packed with questions and observations regarding
Chaika and Emperor Gaz.
Do you not think it might be full of
the captain's feelings on the Chaika case?
Everything in here centers around materials seized from Emperor Gaz's castle.
To tell the truth, I had not investigated this library in depth myself.
As the notebook says, it seems unnatural
that there are no materials left on the magic techniques used by such a wizard.
So when I looked into these documents again,
I found this.
It's the report of the punitive force that killed Emperor Gaz.
His fortune?
Curren-san, is it all right if I keep these?
Of course. That's why I showed them to you.
I will continue my investigation of this library.
I would like you to continue to pursue Chaika, as you always have.
Yes. I will.
Chief Konrad.
What is it, Curren?
I just spoke with Vivi.
I see...
Now that the war is over,
I never thought I'd be stricken over the loss of one of my men like this.
Yes.
Perhaps I should have listened more closely to Albéric.
And what of Vivi?
She is strong. She'll be fine.
Uh-huh.
Also, Chief...
You've been smoking more cigarettes lately.
It's nothing special, but please enjoy.
Grapes, exceptionally sweet!
Fresh grapes, tart, exquisite!
Bring it here.
Yes, ma'am.
The promised article.
Father's remains?
Yes.
So you weren't using it?
The remains?
Yeah.
When I heard you had established a vineyard and winery like this after the war,
I was sure you must have used the emperor's remains as magic fuel.
Well, it's not as though the idea never occurred to me.
If I had used it, I'm sure it would have kept my wine's flavor consistent.
But for whatever reason, something held me back.
You're not like the other heroes we've met.
No?
Well, the punitive force had all sorts of unusual characters.
Many of them lost their way once the war ended.
I didn't want to go through that,
so I found a new purpose.
And I received some of his remains as proof of my hero status,
but they aren't mine.
I had heard rumors that a girl called Chaika was gathering his remains,
so I had decided that if I met and liked her, I'd give them to her.
It's better for his daughter to have them rather than me, right?
Grateful.
By the way, do you know where his fortune is?
Fortune? Fortune exists?!
Oh, you didn't know?
When Gaz Castle fell, one of the surviving wizards spoke of it.
He said there was a fortune left by the emperor.
Please, spare my life!
I'll give you information in return!
Speak.
I am privy to Emperor Gaz's most guarded secret.
What?
A wizard recently departed for a foreign island
after receiving an order from Emperor Gaz.
The emperor's fortune is hidden there.
I thank you for the information.
However, we have orders to exterminate all within Gaz Castle.
We must not allow even a single rat to live.
The punitive force's record keeper reported a "secret island"
and "the emperor's fortune" to the allied forces.
Emperor's fortune, where now?!
I've heard that the allied forces searched for it,
but they never found anything.
Nothing at all?
The search was called off after that.
After the castle fell, it was also searched again,
but no experimental tools or documents were found on his magic techniques.
It was assumed that the wizard who received Emperor Gaz's order
must have taken it all with him to that island.
Island... Father's fortune...
But I'm glad I was able to give you the remains.
Yes.
Do you still intend to continue your journey?
Then why don't I write down the locations where you're likely to find more remains?
You know?
Sure. I know the names and birthplaces of the other heroes, at least.
There's still plenty more, so eat all you like.
My memory is vague, and it's been five years,
so I couldn't say whether they're still around...
Looks like our coming here has set things in motion quite rapidly.
Yeah, no more wild goose chases for us.
Right, Chaika?
Grateful!
But why leave so late at night? You could stay until morning.
We are on the run, after all.
Couldn't you at least have some wine before you go?
I'm not interested in alcohol.
But wine enriches your life.
Sounds like something a drunkard would say.
When you understand what it means, come visit again.
All right.
Thank you.
Many gifts, grateful!
Claudia's grapes, superb! Can never forget!
Thank you. Take care, okay?
Are you sure about this?
Giving it to a girl who may not even be the real daughter?
That was like a badge of honor for you.
That's no badge of honor. Just a trinket.
I'll raise the value of my own badge of honor with this year's wine.
Chaika, what is it?
What's wrong? Did you have a scary dream?
Gruesome memory... Beheading moment...
But that memory, fake. If true, would be dead.
Am I fake?
First... What am I?
Many Chaikas exist.
Some say, emperor's real daughter, dead.
My memories, clouded.
Uncertainty swirling in heart.
I can't blame you for feeling that way.
But that doesn't change your objective, does it?
Objective, gather remains.
Father, funeral.
Then all you can do is keep working toward that, right?
And all Akari and I need to do is make our master's objective a reality.
Isn't that enough?
Yes. That's what I think, too.
Well, it's morning. Should we get going?
Yes.
You're one of the eight heroes, Glen Donkervoort, right?
Yes, I suppose I am.
You lot are quite skilled.
How about you give us the emperor's remains?
About that... The remains aren't here.
Not here?
I gave them to a girl in red yesterday.
Red?
The red Chaika?
Chaika...
So they were still gathering remains?
They couldn't have gotten far.
That only leaves the viscount Alan Tramontana,
Lord Stephan Hartgen, and Clay Morgan...
I don't want the red Chaika to get ahead of us.
Chaika?
Want to look for Father's island.
Huh?
If found, can learn what I am.
Wait, you...
What am I...?
Want to find answer.
The sky is overcast
The bell rings to signal the beginning
omae no naka ni iru
I'm in your thoughts
watashi wa soko ni iru
I'm with you
nejirete somaru kioku
A twisting and fading memory
idenshi no hakobune
The ark of genes
yurete tooi tooi
Floating far, far away
shuuen no chi wo mezase
Steering towards the end
yoroi wo toku toki ga kita tada sore dake
Only because the time has come to take off my armor
sasageru dake kako no subete dakedo
I offer my past to you
itsuka itsuka itsuka itsunohika mata aeru
Someday we can meet again
omae ga chijyo no dokoka de matsu kagiri
As long as you wait for me somewhere on Earth
oshimu beki mono ha nai
There is nothing to regret
tomo ni ikita akashi amai kuchibiru kamishimete
As proof that we were together, I bite my sweet lip
koyoi no chi kono ai wo
This night, this love
setsuna dakishimeta wagami
My body embraces these moments
I'll give them all to you
Hero living in harbor town, giant spear user.
Also boss of marine shipping business!
Boss powerful, bewildered!
Want good seafood!
But first, battle inevitable!
The Harbor of Phantom
Dreams Recollected
Next time: "The Harbor of Phantom Dreams Recollected."
The Harbor of Phantom
Dreams Recollected