It's really comin' down now.
The weather prediction was off, Hizuru.
Predictions, presumptions, precognitions—
Ain't nothin' with the word "pre" attached to it ever been right.
We really goin' down there?
Yes, I have a bad feeling about this too.
Let's just hope my premonition proves false.
Run!
Don't stop!
Damn!
These things are targeting Ushio relentlessly.
They basically haven't attacked me at all.
Ushio?!
Is your arm hurt?
It's no use. We can't go any farther.
Yer in the way! Move!
Sou!
Nice!
Is that why you brought the spray along?
Hell yeah! Working just like I thought!
Ain't no creature alive not scared of fire!
Ya okay, Ushio?
We can still turn back!
I'm fine!
Charge forward!
I hate half-assing things!
Right.
Shinpei, I'll open a path!
You take care of Ushio!
Already on it!
Hey, Ryuunosuke!
Tell me if yer gonna shoot!
I'm gonna go deaf!
Sorry, but if I took the time to speak,
we would have died.
Still, to think the Shadows were lurking under the island...
I can't believe this.
Their numbers are increasing.
We're getting close to their nest.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
The number you are trying to reach is not available at this time.
Please leave a m—
Time to Feed
Where's Shin?
I know he went to see Sou,
but I can't reach either of them.
Tokiko ain't picking up neither.
Hurry up and come back, Shin.
The Shadow Sickness.
Not only is Sis dead, Shiori disappeared too.
And now something's even happened to Shin!
These are Shiori's hair ties!
Over here.
Shinpei is over here.
W-Wait!
That was close—
M-Mio!
Tetsu! Sorry!
Ya can't just jump out like that!
What's got ya all riled up?
Shiori was just here! Did ya see her?
What?
You saw her? Where? Where?!
She ran toward where ya just came from.
What's that? Yer the only one I saw come runnin' my way.
Shiori?!
Sh-She's gone...
Wait!
The manhole cover's open.
Shinpei is over here.
What's going on?
Is Shin in here?
No, no, no, no. No, no, no!
If weren't her!
Ain't no way a grade-schooler went in there!
Well, normally...
But what if that was Shiori's Shadow?
Tetsu.
No way.
But I ain't said nothin' yet!
Ya want me to look inside, right?
Ain't happenin'! I'm busy!
I'm goin' to the city to drink.
If I show up in my cool uniform stinkin' and lookin' like a sewer rat,
Erika will hate me!
Ya'd choose a barfly over a human life?
Still, we don't know for sure.
Ya'd be a hero.
Huh?
Just imagine the newspaper articles about the hero who saved the missing girl.
Ya'd be famous over night.
And Erika, why, she'd be head-over-heels for ya.
But if ya don't wanna go, that's fine.
Just don't try to stop me.
I'll go in alone if I have to.
Follow my lead.
This ain't 'cause I wanna be a hero or popular, ya hear?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm an ally of justice, y'know.
I just wanna find Shiori.
Thank ya.
I guess even selfish motives are better than doin' nothin' at all.
That's harsh, Mio.
We somehow managed to escape.
Yeah, but what is this place?
It's weirder than anywhere we've been so far.
Yeah.
Look at this.
Huh?
It's coral.
How can ocean life be living on land?
Shadows.
What?
The coral, sea anemones, and barnacles—
They're all Shadows.
Who could've done all this?
No idea.
But someone printed the sea here.
It's sea-water.
This cave must connect to the sea at some point.
If that means there's another exit, that's good news.
It's too dangerous to keep going, Shinpei.
We're out of gas.
If we're attacked again, that's it.
H-Hey, Ushio!
I-I'm fine.
I'm just hungry.
That makes no sense.
We just ate an hour ago.
That's not just hunger, is it?
Yer right arm ain't healed yet, has it?
This is damage taken by my main body.
Data loss, essentially.
I need to eat to fix it.
Then just have Shinpei make ya some more rice balls.
Not like that.
I don't need normal food.
I need to scan the original again to recover data.
But Ushio's ash now.
There's no way to heal this wound now.
A-Are ya kidding?
This whole time?
Have ya been holding it in ever since Shadow Mio hurt ya yesterday?
I only realized the truth a few minutes ago.
Why didn't ya tell us somethin' so important?!
Sorry. I'll just erase my right arm for now.
That'll stop the pain.
There's no way to heal her?
That can't be!
She's getting weaker and weaker.
Damn it!
I'm not gonna let her die again!
Should I loop again?
Will turning back time heal her?
But how?!
Don't move.
Turn around slowly.
If the two of ya make any strange movements,
Ushio will pay for it with her life.
H-How are ya even here,
Tokiko?!
A dead end.
The Shadows came from here.
A secret path only for them, huh?
Now it's clear.
The Shadows traveled via underground paths like the sewers to reach the island.
Yeah.
Plus there are tons of tunnels in this area dug up by the army.
No one knows their full extent anymore.
I'd be willing to bet there are more of these secret paths.
Still, what do we do?
We don't have the tools to cut through iron bars.
Should we head back up and look for another entrance?
Hitogashima
Koba Mart
Hishigata Clinic
Hitogashima Middle School
Hitogashima Elementary School
According to the map, we seem to be at the center of the island.
No, I doubt there are any other entrances.
Or at least none for humans.
Look.
The path beyond differs from the sewers.
It's probably a natural cave that was here long before.
I never thought it really existed. Hiruko cave.
Huh?
My grandpa told me this story as a child.
Supposedly, underneath Hitogashima lies a giant cavern called Hiruko cave.
Up until halfway through the Meiji period,
there was an entrance that would only appear in Hitogashima Port during low tide.
Then during the first Sino-Japanese war, the army sealed it up while they were occupying the port.
I thought it was just a legend—an island folktale.
But it's said this cave is where Hiruko, the guardian of Hitogashima, settled in after washing ashore long ago.
The Hiruko legends, huh?
Sis would know more about that.
Should I change over?
No, not for now.
We could ask Karikiri.
If his old man were alive, he might have known something.
Either way, we'll need a metal-cutting saw.
Let's turn back and—
Hush.
C'mon, let's go back already!
There's no way she's down here.
I'm sure of what I saw earlier!
Ya saw her too, didn't ya, Tetsu?
Man, the sewer stink's all over me.
I'm gonna need a bath before I head into town.
Geez! I'll explain things to Erika, okay?
I'll even tell her how manly ya were.
Huh? Ya mean it?
Shiori!
No, wait, Mio.
How... How'd she get on the other side?
Yuck.
No way...
Wait!
Are we dreamin' or somethin'?
Ya goin' after her, Mio?
These leather boots cost me 60,000 yen!
Hey, was that...
Kofune Mio and Officer Totsumura Tetsu, yes.
Sis's premonition might have been right.
I'm not goin' after 'em. It's a trap.
But at the very least, Mio is human.
She has an immunity.
Don't blame me, then.
Who knows what evils lie in wait for us?
Toki!
Ya've done well to survive after trespassing on sacred ground, Sou.
Answer me! Wh-What's going on, Tokiko?!
Too far.
The nail gun won't reach.
What are ya doin' here?!
What a foolish question.
What'd ya say?
I'm here to retrieve a defective item.
Ya have my thanks for bringing Ushio with ya.
It's been hard to find her.
She's broken, after all.
She's carelessly getting closer.
Three more steps and she'll be in range.
We'll take care of the rest.
I won't let ya lay a finger on Ushio!
Please stop!
No, Shinpei.
Toki's...
Too bad, Shinpei.
I'm human.
Ya can kill Shadows, but ya can't kill people, can ya?
Are ya really Tokiko?
Why don't we...
have a little chat?
Summer Time Rendering
Sorry to keep asking this of you, Negoro.
Negoro
You called, Doctor?
Add this to their food today.
It's almost 9 PM.
Hurry and get this to them.
Yes, Doctor.
Understood.
We surrender.
Ya gotta be kidding, Shinpei!
Sou!
Shinpei's right.
I hate to admit it, but we got no chance of winning.
Don't get any funny ideas, Sou.
Restrain her.
Ushio!
Damn it! Stop this, Tokiko!
Calm down, Sou.
What?!
If she wanted to kill us, this would've been over already.
They're just going to take Ushio with them.
Right, Toki?
I still don't understand anything yet.
I'll take that silence as a yes.
In that case, it's still too early.
I'm sorry, Ushio. Just a little longer.
Just hang in there for a little longer!
Where are ya taking her? To yer father?
I-I see!
Tokiko! Are ya doing this on Dad's orders?
Ya don't know anything, Sou.
But of course ya don't.
Y'weren't chosen by Dad.
What?!
But now that ya've seen so much,
it'd be idiotic to keep up the secrecy.
In fact, this is a good chance to reveal the truth.
Leave your belongings here.
If you do, I'll show you the way.
You won't be harmed, so follow me on your own two feet.
Hiruko awaits.
You're going to miss.
A little to the right. Five degrees to the right.
Mind yer own business!
Forget about me!
Fine.
Focus on yer own targets!
We've lost sight of Mio.
Is she okay?
I doubt this is the time to be worrying about others.
Look.
Where the hell even are we?!
What is this, the bottom of the sea?
This is a sea anemone.
Anewhat?
A deep-sea creature. I saw them on TV long ago.
It's impossible for them to live on land.
It's possible they're all Shadows.
Behind us!
I don't like this.
Yeh've killed that thing twice now.
So how?
Is it immortal?!
What's this? Yer not surprised?
If we assume you aren't dead, things line up.
You made me think I killed you and then slipped underground through a crack.
Correct?
My sister had her suspicions about the sewers.
Well, I'd expect nothing less from Hizuru.
Why'd ya come back?
I told ya the next time we meet yer dead.
Do ya still not understand, Minakata Ryuunosuke?
Hey!
No!
Ya gave it yer name?!
I realized it when we chatted in that child's room.
Imagine my surprise to learn what was inside Hizuru.
No way...
Haine?
It's been 14 years, hasn't it?
But I have no business with you.
Your personality and memories are all that are here.
Where did your body go?
Where is the body that stole Mother's right eye?
Haine, you were back to playing pretend from the beginning?
This time using Kobayakawa Shiori's memories.
Blocked?
My bullets should have hit!
I've read their memories.
Hizuru and Ryuunosuke both don't know where the body is.
I can't read the old man.
Can I kill them?
Sure.
Time to run, Ryuunosuke.
We're no match for that thing.
You're joking, right?
Can't ya tell it's us that's being hunted here?!
Those aren't Shadows of humans!
They're something much frightening—
something entirely different!
Be careful.
Ryuunosuke's shifted.
He's shifted about two seconds ahead.
Yes. Understood.
Ryuunosuke!
One down.
Nezu!
Damn you!
Like this?
Over there?
Unfortunate.
This reading ahead business ain't good.
Are ya going after him?
No need for that.
Dark blood. I must've hit the liver.
That's fatal. He'll die eventually if we just leave him alone.
Where are Ushio and Shinpei?
They've gotten far, but don't worry.
Tokiko has two wild ones with her.
More importantly, I'm hungry.
Nine o'clock needs to come faster.
Damn. I can't summon any strength.
Shinpei dropped his weapon when he surrendered.
That's because he didn't want to loop when the truth was so close, right?
You wanna push it as far as you can.
Ain't that right, Shinpei?
Th-That wasn't me!
That was Hiruko. Her stomach rumbles.
I've accepted what I've done.
I won't ask for forgiveness.
All I want now is for y'all to accept things as I have.
My father was against telling my brother.
But he needn't have bothered warning me.
Not like I could tell anyone, anyway.
Still, Shinpei.
Please don't tell Mio.
What you're about to see...
What you're about to learn...
At least keep it from Mio.
I have no intention of getting her involved.
That's good.
Yer kind, aren't ya?
The long, long shadow stretched up to the ceiling.
And at the base...
It's nine o'clock.
Time to feed.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Bloody Night