They first appeared over a hundred years ago.
Giant, humanoid creatures with a taste for our blood.
The brute strength of these aberrations
trumped an average person's many times over.
We were shoved to the brink
of extinction almost overnight.
The survivors erected Walls Maria, Rose, and Sina;
withdrawing behind them in frightened huddles
for what was to be a century of uneasy peace.
In the year 845, two terrifying new breeds of
Titan appeared: the Colossal and the Armored,
barreling through the outer walls as if
wholesale destruction was child's play.
The territory couched within the
circle of Wall Maria was abandoned.
Twenty percent of the human race perished.
As the Titan onslaught advanced,
our only choice was to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
In the year 850, the Colossal appeared once again,
breaching the wall bordering Trost before disappearing.
The Titans flooded in through the broken gate.
Eren! No!
Two hours later, the evacuation
of the entire populace was complete.
As a result,
no civilians were lost to the Titans.
The same cannot be said for the countless
soldiers who perished, buying the people time.
Eren. As long as you're part of my life,
I can fight to the bitter end.
Captain, please wait!
There's only a handful of us left, sir.
If the Titans were to attack here in force, we
wouldn't have a chance in hell of holding them off!
Please, sir. We need you here!
Out of my way, soldier. We have to get going.
My expertise is needed to help direct the reinforcements.
Behind the safety of the inner gate. Am I right?
Just what the hell are you implying?
They need my help reorganizing.
Or would you rather us be overwhelmed
due to a logistical nightmare!
But... But sir! If we lose those supplies...
That's enough!
Question my orders again, or delay me in my duties,
and I'll run your treasonous hide straight through!
Why isn't anyone going over the wall?
They must have heard the withdrawal signal.
It's over. All over. We're doomed.
There!
C'mon now. That musket's not enough to stop them.
Huh?
Hey, Jean. What're we gonna do?
We can't do anything.
They finally gave us the order to withdraw.
And we were all out of gas, of course.
I can't believe this is how it's going to end.
Because of those damned cowards!
Y'mean the supply depot? What is going on? Where are they?
They all lost their will to fight.
And I can understand why.
But they abandoned their duty to supply us,
barricading themselves inside HQ.
And of course, Titans have swarmed the place,
which means we can't get the gas ourselves.
Then why're we waitin'? We gotta go.
Start thinning their numbers so we have a chance!
Sitting here on this roof is totally pointless!
Eventually the Titans are gonna come for us.
We don't have much gas left.
We'll just waste what little we've got if we try to run.
And without our mobility, we're completely screwed!
You're using your head for once, Conny. Nice going.
But I'm just not sure if we've got the
numbers needed to pull this thing off.
The veterans in the Vanguard force have all been killed.
How, exactly, do a bunch of rookies
pull off a suicide mission like this?
I mean, let's assume half of our
force even survives the initial assault.
Then what? The supply room is probably crawling
with Titans in the three or four meter range.
I don't see us accomplishing much in there.
It's hopeless.
God, what a dull life this turned out to be.
I never even got to tell her just how I feel.
C'mon guys, we can do it!
Right? Let's go.
If we all work together, we can make this happen,
I know we can!
All right? I'll take the lead.
Armin! It's time to go.
Reiner. Do we move out?
Not yet. We have to let them gather up first.
It's no use.
There's too many of them.
I don't think any of us are going to survive this.
I've come to accept my pending demise.
I just... wanted my death to mean something.
Mikasa! Weren't you with the rearguard?
Annie!
I know how bad things have gotten. It's selfish.
Putting personal matters in the forefront,
but have you seen Eren's squad?
Some squads made it back. But I don't know about Eren's.
We found Armin, he's over there.
Armin!
Mikasa! I can't. How do I tell her what happened to Eren?
I survived, and it means nothing.
I'm so useless!
I wish I had died with him instead!
Armin. Are you okay? You're not hurt, are you?
Where is Eren?
Armin?
They were... The cadets of Squad 34. Thomas Wagner.
Nack Tierce. Milieus Zeremski. Mina Carolina.
Eren Jaeger!
These brave five upheld their duties.
They died valiantly on the field of battle!
Please, no.
His whole squad was wiped out?
The same will happen to us if
we try to take on those Titans.
I'm so sorry, Mikasa!
It should have been me that died, not Eren!
I... I couldn't do a thing! I'm worthless.
Armin.
Calm yourself. We haven't got time
for you to get emotional right now.
Huh?
On your feet.
Marco. If we eliminate or bypass the Titans at HQ,
we can there refuel our gear,
allowing us to get back over the wall.
Is that assessment correct?
Well... Uh yeah I guess so, sure.
But there's just too many of them
out there. Even with you on point.
I can do it.
What?
I'm strong. Real strong.
None of you come close. You hear me?
I am a warrior.
Know this. I have the power to slay
all of the Titans that block our path!
Even if I have to do it alone.
As far as I'm concerned, I am surrounded
by a bunch of unskilled, cowardly worms.
You dissappoint me. You can just sit here and
twiddle your thumbs, and watch how it's done!
Wait, Mikasa. Are you out of your mind? That's crazy!
You can't be serious! Trying to take them out by yourself?
There's no way you can hope to beat them!
If I can't beat them, then I die. But, if I win, I live.
And the only way to win is to fight!
Hey!
You know, I was expecting something more motivational.
Your way with words was kind of a let down.
I blame everything about this on you, Eren!
Hey! Don't just stand there!
We weren't taught to let our comrades fight alone!
'Less you are a coward, in which case stay out of my way!
Never expected that from him.
Hey! Seriously? C'mon, you bunch of chickens!
They're nuts!
Damn it. All right, let's go!
Hurry up! Follow Mikasa! Avoid fighting, if you can.
And get to HQ before you run out of gas!
Whoa, Mikasa is a badass!
How is she going so fast?
No! Mikasa's using too much gas!
She could run out at any second!
It doesn't matter how skilled she is.
Once we lose mobility, we're as good as dead!
I see through the veil of her composure.
She's letting adrenaline distract her from grief!
At any time, she could...
Mikasa!
Damn!
Jean! You lead the rest to HQ! I'm going after Armin!
I'll go with you!
Don't be stupid! There are still Titans everywhere!
You've gotta help the others!
It happened. Why this again?
I've lost my family.
Why? Wasn't the first time enough?
It's all over.
Nothing left for them to take from me.
It's no use. We're not getting anywhere near Headquarters.
Unless, of course, we don't mind dying.
Shit! He's out of gas!
Stay back!
Tom! I'll save you!
No, wait!
I'm comin'!
Stop it!
Why couldn't I stop them?
Why didn't I stop them? If I'd kept us all together,
this never would have happened!
I wasn't meant to lead.
I'm the last person that should've been given the reigns!
No!
I hope you choke on me, you bastard!
No! No!
This world is cruel.
But it's also... It's also beautiful.
It was a good life.
Why?
I'd already given up.
So why... Why am I struggling?
Why do I keep getting up?
Why am I still fighting?
I mean, I've lost any reason to live.
What keeps pushing me?
Fight!
Fight! Fight!
Eren.
Kill or be killed!
The only way to live is to fight!
I'm so sorry, Eren. I'm through giving up.
I'll never give up again.
Because if I die, these memories of you die with me.
That's why I'll do whatever it takes to win!
Whatever it takes to live!
What was that?
That Titan. He's... killing...
He's killing the other one.
Please be all right. I'm coming for you!
There she is!
Mikasa! Are you okay?
Are you guys all right?
Yeah.
Then we better get outta here!
Crap. Two fifteen-meter Titans!
No. That one's different.
How?
Huh?
It... It just finished it off.
He knew exactly where the weak spot was!
C'mon guys, time to split!
Last thing we need is him coming our way!
No. He has no reaction to us.
Any other Titan would've been on top of us by now!
It seemed to understand the skill of hand-to-hand combat.
What is that thing?
Just chalk it up as another Abnormal!
Hell, they're always an unpleasant surprise, right?
Forget about it. Let's just get outta here!
Wait a minute, hold on. Mikasa's tanks are empty!
Huh? What are we gonna do?
We can't clear HQ without your help!
There's only one thing to do.
I know there isn't very much left in them,
but it's better than your empty ones.
Armin!
This is our only choice!
It'll be a complete waste if I keep them. But...
Use this gas more sparingly.
Everyone's lives are riding on you.
What have I done?
I led the attack without any
regard for their lives at all.
I was even reckless with my own life.
I lost track of what you taught me.
Oh, Eren. I'm so ashamed.
Eren.
There! Got it! The ODM gear's functional.
And I restocked your blades.
Just... Just leave me this one, okay?
It's just that, I would rather
this be my end, not being eaten alive.
Why'd you...?
Armin.
I will not leave you behind.
What was he?
Are there any more like him?
I've never heard of a Titan killing another Titan.
No one has.
But it struck a chord in me.
Something so familiar. So primal.
I bore witness to the manifestation of humanity's rage.
A Titan killing a Titan.
The very sight of it in action leaves the
104th Cadet Corps Class completely speechless.
However, the cadets have much more in store for them.