A bit more lively...
SCHEDULE
Perfect!
Maybe the tempo should be a little higher.
Nice!
The drums set the tone.
The melody stirs up your feelings, and the lyrics just flow by themselves.
That moment when everything sounds perfect.
That euphoric feeling that puts us on cloud nine.
Already midnight.
Hold up, hold up, what?
What the heck am I doing?
I need to study, darn it! Study!
Just layering them isn't gonna cut it, huh...
Then maybe I should try to tone down the intensity on this one a bit...
STUDYING!
A SLAPSTICK Q&A SESSION
No, no!
Sorry...
The pigeon was on the rhythm...
No, no!
I haven't even finished 2 pages since yesterday.
At this point I might as well have just played around all day.
Some guitar.
Right, there was an acoustic one too...
Just a moment.
Hi Nina-chan, come on in!
Have you eaten already?
No, not yet.
Want a meat bun? They're great!
Hey, that's bad manners!
Yep, you're definitely a rich girl.
Sauce on meat buns?...
Trust me, they're better this way.
Actually,
A friend gave me those as leftovers from work.
Nice.
You like it?
It's delicious!
Great. Glad to hear that.
So, what about that song? You finish it yet?
Would be nice if you could
actually do it that quickly.
Then why did you call us here?
I live pretty far from here you know.
I thought we should talk about
what kind of song it should be.
Like, I can't see it right now.
What the three of us should sound like.?
Well, I'm fine with anything as long as I'm on drums.
What do you think?
It's delicious!
I showed you this app like, what, a week ago?
And you can already make something like this?
Awesome!
It's just that... Momoka told me
I could compose without knowing music theory.
So I gave it a try.
Still, for the result to be this good,
you must've been at it for at least
8 hours a day, haven't you.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
I have to study! I HAVE TO STUDY!
Yep, I hit the nail on the head.
You're the one who showed me the app,
So it's your fault!
Yeah no, this is all on you.
I know that...
If you know then quit taking it out on others.
But, it's just that...
Alright, fine.
I shouldn't have shown you that app.
Here, let me just uninstall it...
It's okay, forget it.
What, seriously?
It's my fault.
I just need to get myself together,
and leave the rest of the band stuff to you. Easy, right?
Who are you even talking to?
To myself!
Alright, see you next week.
What the heck is up with this girl...
Well, I'll be heading back too then.
Hold up, there's a ton of meat buns left!
You can have them. Later!
Nina-chan!
Wanna go together?
Sure.
You're pretty amazing, you know.
Composing a song all by yourself.
I definitely wouldn't be able to.
I just...looked up some guides and stuff.
Still, I definitely wouldn't have been
able to write lyrics.
Really...
Yep.
Um, sorry, I have to stop by
the convenience store...
I'll come with you.
No, I mean...
Actually, I was planning to walk back home right after...
I see.
Later then.
Subaru too, huh.
Just go there your-
I mean, couldn't you go there yourself?
I can't, got a shift later.
You got something to do too?
Not really, but...
Listen, you can go after class.
Just take it to her.
She gave you meat buns.
It's that famous place.
Check it out.
Country bumpkin spotted.
Which way is it...
Let's see...
Um...
Found it.
Or not.
Finally...
Excuse me...
Can I help you?
Y-yes!
Is Awa-san around here?
Awa-san?
You mean Subaru-chan!
Subaru, over here!
Yes, I think the play's fine as is.
Nina-chan!
Why are you here?
Did you have trouble getting here?
I could have come to meet you,
you know.
Sorry for taking so long.
Here.
My savior!
Did you forget your phone?
Yeah.
I did an oopsie~
Everyone's waiting for you.
- Okay.
- See you soon.
See you soon.
Do you have time after this?
Want to grab a bite to eat?
My treat.
Sorry, I, uh, have to study...
I see. How about the weekend then?
Like, on Sunday?
Really, you don't have to...
It's just a small favor.
Well, I'm gonna go now.
Do you want me to leave?
I'm talking about the band.
I'm not stupid, you know.
I can see that you're avoiding me.
Well, uh...
I'm not trying
to get in your way or anything.
There are other bands.
Wait, you're wrong.
It's not like that...
It's just that...
I'm sorry!
Was it really okay?
Yes, it's fine.
I can always study later.
I study at my own pace anyway.
Not that, I mean about myself.
I started music in middle school.
So I definitely can't say
I know everything, but
since the members of a band always
create something together,
they're usually pretty tight-knit.
If disagreements come up, bottling it up won't work.
Putting up a facade is just going to
lead to problems down the line.
So if something bothers you,
you better speak up.
I have nothing against you, you know.
It's all my fault in the end.
See, this is what I mean.
People usually end up hating me anyway.
Argh, no, that's not what I mean!
It's just that, I usually distance myself from people...
I'm shy, so it always feels like they're just
forcing themselves to talk to me.
And you hate it?
Not exactly hate, but...
I don't know, when people are friendly with me,
I can't help but think something like
"Don't think it'll go your way, I'm not that easy!"
at some point...
What a pain.
And I'm guessing that's why you dropped out of high school?
No, that's a different story.
Wait... did she tell you about me?
Well, yeah.
You really like playing the good guy, huh.
Alright, listen you!
You're completely wrong about me!
Yeah, I'm going to acting school,
but it's not like a regular school
that lets you take college exams.
We're in the same boat!
Maybe, but you want to be an actress!
That means you're pursuing a dream!
At least you have something to tell others!
And that's where you're wrong.
Do you know her?
Her face looks familiar...
Mémé's Investigations.
Rebroadcast every noon.
She's my grandmother.
Seriously?
She's a huge pain, you know.
"You have to follow in my footsteps", and all that.
She's the one who arranged
for me to be sent to this school.
Don't you want to become an actress?
Not really, to be honest.
And you're still going to acting school?
Yeah. And I hate myself for it.
I don't even want it, so what the heck am I doing?
But no one around me knows.
Everyone thinks I'm naturally
trying to carry on the family tradition.
Then why did you join a band?
It's my way of quietly protesting.
In middle school, I was really against joining the theater club.
So since I like bands, I ended up joining the Light Music Club.
I had a blast.
I even played in bands without telling anyone.
So your grandmother didn't know at all?
Well, it's not like I could tell her.
By the way, have you seen the Hachiko statue?
Won't people think we're country bumpkins?
So what? You are one.
Come on, think of it as thanks for listening to me.
You're not getting rid of me from today!
Girls Band Cry.
SUNDAY NOON
A street performance?
Yeah, it would be a good start.
I've already booked a place for this weekend.
Weren't we supposed to start by recording
a song and uploading a video?
It's still on the agenda.
But something tells me we need to get started quickly,
- especially with our lineup.
- A concert, huh.
I was looking at the photo you sent me back then.
You two were radiating an aura of misfortune and frustration.
- Rude.
- Yeah!
But that's exactly why I thought
it'd be good for you.
- What do you think, Nina?
- I'm not exactly happy about it, but...
I kind of get it.
Are you sure we can play without a bassist?
Nina can't play any instruments, right?
Relax, it's a place for amateurs.
We'll manage somehow.
And besides, we have this thing.
What's that?
A looper.
To record a musical loop.
Got it?
Awesome.
Wait, I just realized something
about street performances...
Does the "street" part mean
we'll perform in front of people?
Well, duh.
And besides, you've already seen me in action.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going home.
Come on, quit it!
Leave me alone! That wasn't the plan!
Pull yourself together.
You sang at the station, remember!
It's the same thing.
Easier said than done.
I don't have any experience with that stuff!
It's fine, if anything goes wrong I'll make it work somehow.
Then you sing!
You're way better than me anyway!
And you'll play the guitar?
You know I can't.
I told you, I want you behind the microphone.
But why?
You'll understand when you sing. Trust me.
I'm going home.
So you're leaving the band too, right?
Exactly. Thanks and good luck!
Hey, wait-
It's fine.
You're being unfair, putting us on the spot like that!
You're not making sense.
- But I-
- Stop freaking out.
Whether it goes well or not,
whether you fail or not,
you'll have regrets either way.
That's just how you are.
- You don't know that...
- You know I'm right.
Believe me, you have everything to gain,
by baring your soul and singing everything
that's boiling up inside you right now.
Am I wrong?
Yep, you lost this one.
I wasn't talking to you!
Take this attitude of yours and put it into the song!
That will be the real you.
Their equipment's pretty good!
Yep. They're the cheapest place around here though.
Let's give it a try.
Yep, this'll do.
Nina, do you have the lyrics memorized?
I tried to fit in a bit of your composing too.
Yes.
Alright, let's give it a shot then.
Why do you think we came here?
You caught me off guard!
I told you, stop freaking out.
It's just a rehearsal, it's bound to be bad.
We'll definitely mess up somehow.
Catch.
Breathe.
One, two, three, four.
What do you think?
It totally gave me chills.
I got goosebumps all over!
Heh.
You fell right into Momoka-san's trap.
Once you feel that, there's no turning back.
What do you mean?
Humans
can't help but move to the beat of a sound.
Dance and music are in our DNA.
Isn't that right?
Yep.
What's up?
Nothing, I was just thinking
you really do have an amazing voice.
You think so?
Yeah, it gave me chills too.
Alright, let's try singing.
Got it!
A medium with a beer.
A medium, no onions.
Medium for me too.
Woah, who's this raspy old man?
Shouldn't have told me to sing at the top of my lungs.
I didn't think anyone could actually get to this point.
Shut up you...
"Thank you so much."
Well, your voice should be back tomorrow.
Be careful with your throat though.
Are you a band?
The guitar case caught my attention.
Come see us, if you feel like it.
Thank you very much.
SHIN-KAWASAKI (PROVISIONAL)
Look what I got.
So?
Well, we could give them ours too.
Let's wait until we hear them sing.
Thank you for the meal.
Well, I gotta go.
Go where?
To work.
See ya.
She treated us today too.
Paid both for the venue and the food.
What is she looking at?
Her former bandmates.
Those four.
Let's welcome the very first performance of a brand new band!
A girls' trio straight from Kawasaki!
Make some noise for...
"Shin-Kawasaki"?
I'm calling a meeting on the subject
of our band name later.
I told you, it's temporary...
Sorry I'm late.
Wait a second...
Don't tell me that's your stage outfit.
Is it bad?
I told you, you have to bare your soul.
Go change.
Testing testing 1 2 3...
You need an outfit you would definitely hate.
Don't overthink it.
You have to let your emotions flow freely.
Don't worry, you're not alone.
You're shy, but stubborn.
Cowardly, but full of confidence.
A true walking paradox.
Gee, thanks!
Come on, Nina! We're up!
You've accumulated so much anger and energy within you.
And that...
is what we call rock.
Rock?
Nina Iseri: Rina
Momoka Kawaragi: Yûri
Subaru Awa: Mirei
No one knows you. No one cares about you.
But that's what makes it all so thrilling.
You're rock'n'roll, Nina.
If nothing changes, no matter the wait
Then I see no common ground
Blaming someone is never enough
To heal the wounds
I want to say goodbye
To those long days
That I spent curled up
It's not like I believe
in any deity
- Shut up
- Leave me alone
A stranger singing
until losing her voice
Promises me
that nothing is an end in itself
Perhaps these banalities
Resonated in some hearts
I don't know
I see
Oh really?
I forgot
I'm tired
I want to break everything
My courage has left me
For pity's sake, someone give me
a reason to exist
Replacements,
there are too many to count
Easy to order me to be myself
These words sound
like a staged performance
Dreaming to see reality
catch up with us
Is there anyone at all?
This is...awesome...
This is rock'n'roll!
I'M LEAVING THE GROUP, SORRY!
Next time:
"Gratitude and Surprise".