Look, Kaoru!
It's—
What should I do?
I forgot who I was before I met you
The wind brushes my cheek
Lullaby of Birdland
Kicking the slope,
a frail shadow stretches on
It's like a neverending summer break
It feels like sneaking into a pool
Hey, let's just swim with our clothes on
Hop!
A spiral of sensational temptation
Those beats that sting me are strange
They burn out and disappear
I'm fine with those crazy days
Dress up
Swinging with such electric speed
Surround
What's that dance called?
It won't stop
Don't go, it lingers on  in my ears
Melody is
like a love
Closed
Richie!
What're you just standin' there for? Hey!
Hey!
Closed
Ri'ko, how about openin' the door?!
It's open.
What's with her?
Huh?
Ritsuko?
Yurika!
I love the cakes here.
Do you come here often, too?
Uh-huh. This is Brother Jun's family's shop.
Oh, I had no idea...
Um, Yurika...
Shira                                      yuri
If you'd like, why don't you come over to my place to watch them practice?
It's over.
She hates me...
What is that, avant-garde?
Come on, Richie. Get your head on straight.
How're we gonna have a session?
Everyone, Yurika is here!
Ritsu,
didn't your dad tell you that outsiders aren't allowed down here?
Yurika's a friend of ours,
so I'm sure it'll be okay.
Well, Yurika, enjoy.
O-Okay...
What's wrong, Kaoru?
I'm just going to get some fresh air.
Ritsu...
Huh?
It's Richie...
Sentaro's sister...
Sachiko, right?
Are you playing by yourself?
Yeah. All my friends are off at cram school...
I see...
Then how about we play together?
Really?
Huh?
It's not playing?
That's strange...
That thing's ancient, so sometimes it gets ornery.
At times like this, a little magic is required.
Wow, Brother Jun.
How'd that get it to work?
Beats me.
Hello, is this the Children's Telephone Counseling Office?
Oh, that's right.
See,
there's this boy named Hashiguchi, and he's always mean to me.
He hides my slippers,
pulls my hair...
What do you think I should do?
Hmm... Let's see...
Y'know,
it may be that Hashiguchi actually likes you, Sachiko.
I'd guess that he wants to be friends with you,
but he doesn't know how to express his feelings,
so he acts out like that without really thinking about it.
He does not!
Recently,
I made the girl that I like cry, too.
I want to apologize to her,
but even if I do, I don't think she'll forgive me.
I don't forgive you.
That was my first time.
It's no good.
I can't stay mad at you...
Kaoru...
There's something I have to tell you...
Oddly enough, I've been going to the shop for a while.
I had no idea it was your family's.
Shirayuri
The coincidences just keep piling up.
Even the name is similar...
Actually,
there's someone that I like already.
And right now, he's the only one I'd consider.
I'm flattered by your feelings for me, Kaoru.
I'm flattered, but...
I understand.
Sentaro...
H-Hey...
What's wrong?
Somethin' botherin' you?
Here, this'll cheer you right up.
Sentaro, what should I do?
I said some terrible things to Kaoru.
He might not ever come back here...
Thank you.
Sachiko...
Do you know who Ri'ko li—
I'm sleepy!
I'm hungry!
N-Never mind!
School starts again today?
I-I can't ask...
It's impossible to talk about romantic stuff in this house...
Richie! It's been too long!
Why didn't you come over for practice during winter vacation?
Oh...
Sorry...
Um, the teacher told me to give this to you...
Thanks.
My father finally came home,
but everything seems so bleak right now
that I can't bring myself to talk about anything.
Hey!
Sen! What are you doing out there?!
Richie! Get outta the way!
Richie,
get your jacket!
We're gonna practice.
Forget it.
Ri'ko is lonely without you around.
C'mon, all you gotta do is stop by the shop...
I'm not going back there again.
Do you really mean that?
Yeah.
Kaoru, got a minute?
I thought I heard a loud noise up here a minute ago.
Oh, really?
Never mind.
Actually, I wanted to give you a letter.
A letter?
It's from Shizu, our old housekeeper. Remember?
Shizu?
Oh, that takes me back...
She wrote about your mother.
We've had our problems over the years,
but it seems that she happened to run into your mother in Tokyo.
She got your mother's address and insisted I pass it on to you.
We split up when you were still little,
so you might not remember your mom very well...
But if you'd like to go see her, it's okay with me. Maybe on your next break...
I know it's kind of sudden and may leave you at a loss,
but whether you go or not is entirely up to you.
Well, I'll let you get back to your studies.
Richie.
You should bring her some sweet rice treats as a souvenir.
I never said I was going.
You're not goin'?
Right now,
I'm just not up to it...
Moron!
You know where she is right now, and if you lose this chance
you'll regret it for the rest of your life!
Kaoru?
Crap!
What are you doing?
I'm coming in!
Wait a second!
Kaoru, you're hiding something, aren't you?
No, not particularly...
Blue trains?
A blue train is basically
one of the limited express trains from Asakaze that has dedicated blue sleeper cars.
Did you know that the design of the front and back cars is different because they have to switch off being the lead car?
No, I didn't.
Come to think of it, this is my first time traveling alone.
Maybe it's a journey to set me free from my heartache.
Hey!
You're late, Richie.
Y'know, it's a good thing I asked Maruo to get me a ticket!
W-Wait a sec...
I felt like takin' a trip to Tokyo too,
so I'm comin' with!
I really only came so I could have some alone time. To think things over...
Man, travelin' an' frozen tangerines go together like bread an' butter!
I do have one more tangerine...
Oh, much obliged!
They taste so much better before they thaw.
Dammit, Maruo...
By the way,
how'd you afford this?
Oh,
I had money saved up from my part-time job.
And then I sold some old records.
You don't have nearly enough...
Well, if I can make it to Brother Jun's place, I'm sure it'll work out.
Did he even try to think this through?
Here, this is yours, Richie.
Ri'ko said the food in the dining car is probably expensive,
so she made these for us.
Ain't you gonna eat it?
She's been worried about you.
W-What's with all these people?!
Is there a festival? Or a New Year's sale?!
Tokyo Station is always like this.
Why don't you go sightseeing around Tokyo?
I wanna see what your mom's like,
so I'm comin' with you.
Blue Butterfly
W-What the heck?!
This is some workplace...
W-Wait, maybe I got the address wrong...
It's right...
Well, let's go in an' ask.
Wait a second!
I've changed my mind about meeting her.
Richie!
What're you talkin' about?! You came all this way!
It's better if I don't see her...
Even if I did, I'm sure...
All right!
She says it's your mom's day off today.
And to come back here tomorrow afternoon.
So we'll come back then.
All right,
I say we relax a bit at Brother Jun's place!
Do you two have business with Katsuragi Junichi?
Yes.
Well, there's no point in waiting for him.
He's been missing since last month.
Missing?
Yeah.
Rumor has it he got in bad with some group and now he's in hiding.
Although it's possible he's just shacking up with some girl...
That guy sure is popular with the college girls.
Yeah, that doesn't surprise me...
Right, Richie?
Nope, not at all.
Have you two come all the way from Kyushu?
Well, let's make our guests from faraway Kyushu feel welcome!
With shochu and water...
Cheers!
Huh?
Water?
That's right!
You wouldn't believe how stupid this guy is!
He's no end of trouble!
When I'm with him, his stupidity rubs off on me!
Good for you.
You're lucky to have such a good buddy.
Buddy? Not at all!
Sounds like it's the best!
Pretty rare to have a friend you can goof off with.
Treasure him.
Unlike love affairs,
friendship is for life.
Kaoru?
Kaoru, that is you, isn't it?
Idiot!
What are you standing around like a scarecrow for?!
You'll catch cold!
What are you doing?! Hurry up and come in!
W-What is this?!
I've never eaten fancy curry like this before!
Go on, don't be shy. Just eat!
Thank you!
Hot!
I like the way you shovel it in.
I've got a thing for men with a hearty appetite.
She isn't at all like I figured she'd be.
Hot!
What was that?!
Mother and son in perfect unison!
S-Shut up!
Sorry... He has no manners.
Are you friends from school?
Yeah... Well, more like, we play music together.
He's a drummer and I play the piano.
Piano?
Oh, Kaoru, you used to love it when your dad played the piano.
He would play and I'd sing along...
And then, even if you were crying, you'd always stop and listen...
Such happy memories...
Oh, really?
I don't remember at all.
And anyway, Dad never likes to talk about the past.
Of course he doesn't.
Who would want to talk about a washout of a mother like me?
Looks like the rain has stopped,
so I'm gonna take a little stroll around Ginza.
I think he wanted to give us some time alone.
But eat before it gets cold.
It's this curry...
It's spicier than usual...
Kaoru!
By the way, how's school going?
Oh, it's okay...
Is there a girl that you like?
Oh... Did it not work out?
M-Mom...
I'd rather not talk about that right now...
What, I'm right?
W-What's so funny?!
Well, just the idea of the baby boy I remember,
who'd say "Mama" and make gurgling noises, having a broken heart!
You're in the heyday of youth!
A broken heart! Not bad, not bad at all!
That's right! Like a lovesick puppy!
The more I laughed,
the more whatever had been building up inside me disappeared into thin air.
My mind emptied out.
There he is!
I thought you weren't gonna make it in time.
Mom, here!
For me?
It's a jazz record.
A song called "Lullaby of Birdland."
Listen and then sing along.
I'll come back to visit you again,
so until then, you should practice it.
But this is in English, isn't it?
I don't know the language at all...
You'll do fine.
Just imitate what you hear.
Jazz is best when sung by a lady with a husky voice.
I'll come back for sure, so please try, Mom!
Kaoru, um...
Thank you for coming to see me.
I thought...
I'd probably never see you again...
That's what I told myself.
Why did my mom leave me behind?
The words I didn't have the heart to ask blurred away with the scenery.
Her mouth formed the words, "I'm sorry."
I shook my head,
but I'm not sure she saw it.
I'm back!
That was heavy.
Ri'ko!
Where were ya?!
Welcome back, Ritsu.
I waited for you on that road downhill
Our promise to meet after school always held a goodbye
I was weak and distorted, and seemed to easily crack under pressure
You were the one who gave me wings then
I wish I could say I love you,
while you're looking for a faint light in the sky at dusk
The letter I wrote in the corner of my textbook
will never reach you
and nothing will ever change