[WIND HOWLING]
[SCAR]
Tell me something, Kimblee...
Do you remember
when we first met?
It seems we've
changed places.
You shouldn't
be so confident.
Kimblee! Damn you!
Tell me why!
Why is Winry here?!
We've finally
got Scar cornered,
and now he's taken her
hostage. Because of you!
Stand aside.
[ED GRUNTS]
What are you doing?!
[ED]
Stop! Stop this now,
Crimson Alchemist!
Can't you see Winry's
up there with him?!
I won't let you attack!
[KIMBLEE]
Why can't you just
stay out of the way?
[SCAR YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
[SOLDIERS YELLING AND COUGHING]
Not so fast, Ishvalan...
No, wait!
It's much too dangerous
to get close to the building.
[SOLDIER A]
Fall back!
[SOLDIER B]
A snowstorm!
[SOLDIER C]
Hurry!
That was a
convincing performance.
It wasn't a performance.
I'm every bit as angry
as I sounded back there.
I feel so worthless... Having to
put on this stupid charade!
[WINRY]
Why... Why did you kill
my mother and father?
[SCAR]
There's nothing I can say that
won't sound like an excuse...
And nothing can
change the fact
that I am responsible
for their deaths.
I killed them.
Young girl, you have every
right to pass judgment on me.
Your arm... You'll die
if we don't bandage it.
Winry?!
Quiet, Ed.
I think...
I think this is what
my parents would have wanted.
[SCAR SHUDDERS]
Mom and Dad saved
his life before, after all...
There has to be
a reason for that.
Does that...
mean you're forgiving me?
Oh, don't get me wrong!
I don't forgive
your wanton murdering.
[SCAR GRUNTS]
[CLOTH TIGHTENING]
Winry...
It's all right.
I won't cry.
Didn't I promise that
next time I cried...
they would be
tears of joy?
[WINRY LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
[ED]
Listen, Scar!
No matter what Winry says...
I still want to beat you
bloody... and drag you down
to the Rockbell family
grave to pay your respects.
Should we contact
headquarters, sir?
Yes.
[SCAR]
Major Miles, wasn't it?
Can I ask something?
[MILES]
What?
Earlier you said
I was one of your people.
That's right...
I'm part Ishvalan, on
my grandfather's side.
I wish we didn't
have to meet like this...
red-eyed brother of mine...
How can you bring yourself to be
part of the Amestrian military?
[LIAM STAMMERS]
My objective is to work
from the inside to change how
the people of this country
view the people of Ishval.
[SCAR STAMMERS]
I don't think that great a task
will be easy to accomplish.
[MILES]
Who knows how
long it will take.
But still...
my mixed blood gives me
a slight advantage at least.
I'm an Ishvalan pebble
tossed into the ocean
of the Amestrian military...
Maybe in time,
the ripples I create
will become great waves.
And do you want to know what the
most ironic part about it is?
It was an Amestrian who set me
on this path in the first place.
Look at me...
I am a festering wound of hatred
born of the great Ishvalan War.
I'm thankful that there's
someone like you out there.
[LIAM]
Major...
Copy...? Major Miles here...
We captured Scar.
We're holding him in area D.
Inform Kimblee.
[MILES]
Whatever the circumstances
may be between us,
I cannot let you go.
You must accept judgment.
[MARCOH]
Hold on!
Who's there?
[AL]
May!
[ED]
Dr. Marcoh!
Please don't take Scar as
your prisoner. We need him!
This doesn't look good.
The weather's changing.
[KIMBLEE GRUNTS]
[SOLDIER B]
The clouds are moving fast.
A storm's on it's way.
Hurry then.
[MILES]
Deciphering notes, huh?
[MAY]
Yes! It's ground-breaking
research that tries to fuse
Amestrian alchemy
and Xingense alkahestry.
But all of the important
parts are unreadable,
written in
ancient Ishvalan...
Scar's the only one who
can make sense of it...
Don't you see?
Hmm...
So you're the
alkahestry girl, huh?
I have orders to bring
you back to the fort.
Me? But what do
they want with me?!
Don't worry,...You'll receive
a warm welcome, I'm sure...
Well, let me think here.
Scar needs to be kept free...
and it would be just as bad if
they found out that Dr. Marcoh
was here as well.
All right... I think it might
be best if we took you back
to Ft. Briggs to hide you
from senior military staff.
[ED]
Hold on...
What are you saying?!
You mean we're bringing
that monster with us?!
We need to decipher
those notes, right, Elric?
There's not a damn thing
I want that guy's help with.
Just hand him
over to Kimblee!
The transmutation circle.
[ED GRUNTS]
The one this country
was formed to make.
[MILES SIGHS]
I heard all about it from
General Armstrong...
We know something's
about to happen
that will affect all of
Amestris and its people...
We need to know
what the notes say.
[MILES]
That's more important
than anything else.
[ED EXHALES FRUSTRATEDLY]
I heard they're using
the Rockbell girl
as a hostage
against you...
If we act now,
we can disgrace Kimblee
and find some place to hide
her where they can't touch her.
[ED SCOFFS]
[GUN COCKS]
Listen up, Scar...
If you're willing
to work with us,
I'll postpone
your judgment day.
Well?
It doesn't look like
you're going to give
me any other choice.
Yes, I'll help you
decode the notes.
I have your word on that?
You do. I swear on
my Ishvalan blood...
You can trust me,
my red-eyed brother.
We have a deal then...
My apologies, Miss Rockbell...
You'll have to wait
awhile before we can punish
your parents' killer.
Fine.
[GERSO AND ZAMPANO GRUNTING]
Right, I almost forgot about
these two freaks of nature...
Dispose of them.
[MICK]
Yes sir.
Hold on a second!
[AL]
Wait! You don't
have to kill them!
I see no reason to
let them live. Kill them.
No! A life is a life!
What better reason do
you need than that?!
[GERSO SCOFFS]
Showing us mercy.
How adorable.
You're just
a sentimental fool...
We didn't ask for
your help, did we?
[AL STAMMERS]
Look at these bodies. What
kind of future can we have?
If you're going
to kill us, do it!
I don't understand...
Don't you have
families... loved ones?
Sure we do.
But as soon as we got these
bodies, they were all told
that we were dead...
and to them, we are.
[AL]
Don't you want
to see them again?
[ZAMPANO]
Even if we did, how could we
go back to them like this?
[AL EXHALES FRUSTRATEDLY]
So, you don't want to get your
original bodies back then?
You're content the way
you are now? Is that it?!
No, how could we be?!
Of course we want
our true bodies back! Argh!
There's your answer!
I don't want to hear a bunch
of fatalistic nonsense!
Why not live,
and learn whether
there's a chance of
getting your bodies back?
Hmph, how could you possibly
know what we're going through?
And what chance do
we have of going back?
[ZAMPANO GASPS]
[ZAMPANO AND GERSO GASP]
Well, I'm going back...
no matter how long it takes.
I'm not giving up!
[LIAM]
Major!
What is it?
It's not good.
A snowstorm.
We can't complete a snowbound
march with this equipment.
We have no chance
of reaching the fort.
What do we do now?
This is a mining
town, isn't it?
Why don't we just go
into the underground tunnels.
[YOKI WINRY AND MAY]
Huh?!
Wha... what's wrong?
I mean, this is
a pretty large mine, right?
So surely there's
a tunnel that can
take us beyond the
mountains. Uh... I think.
[ED AND AL]
That's it!
[MAY]
Mr. Yoki!
Hey, give me some credit.
This is what I did for a living.
[MICK]
He's right... The tunnels
come out past the mountains.
Right...
Once you run into Briggs
soldiers, just hand them this...
I've explained
our arrangement,
so you shouldn't
have trouble with them.
[MARCOH]
Thank you.
But there's still the matter
of the young Miss Rockbell.
She can accompany us
to the fort, of course...
but when word gets
out that she's missing...
won't the Elric brothers be
the first people they suspect?
We can handle ourselves.
Yeah, I hate to brag...
but I've got a pretty
smooth tongue, you know.
[MILES]
No, this is Kimblee
we're dealing with.
He's very skeptical...
He's automatically
going to be suspicious
of whatever
you tell him.
[ED STAMMERS]
[WINRY]
Um... I hate to be the one to
suggest this... but... uh...
What do you think
Kimblee would do
if I was suddenly
taken hostage by Scar?
[NARRATOR]
Fullmetal Alchemist.
You want him
to kidnap you?
Hold on, Winry...
you're saying...
You want us to let him go?
[WINRY]
Right... Scar runs
away, carrying me.
Then Ed, you and the others
try desperately to stop him.
Or at least, that's what you
pretend to do... You understand?
You can't do that!
You're crazy!
Well, I don't have
a choice, do I?!
I'm a hostage either way,
so I might as well
get to choose my captor!
[AL]
But he's a mass murderer!
Al's right!
There's no reason for you
to be risking your life!
Don't you get it?!
It's time for
you two to learn
you don't have to
do everything alone!
[ED AND AL GASP]
Make up your minds...
The storm is coming in...
If we don't hurry we won't
be able to get out of here.
[ED BREATHES HEAVILY]
I can see
Kimblee's forces now!
[ED AND WINRY GASP]
[ED GRUNTS ANGRILY]
Damn it!
Scar! If you do
anything to hurt her I'll--
I won't harm the girl...
I keep my promises.
[SMALL EXPLOSION]
[GERSO]
Us, too... Please, you have
to take us with you, too.
I know you
don't trust us...
So I understand if you
want to keep us tied up.
Kimblee shows
no mercy to troops
who fail to
accomplish their missions...
One way or
the other, we're dead...
besides... We don't
want to give up, either.
[AL HEAVILY EXHALES]
How do we know
you mean that?
You realize, if you do
anything to obstruct us...
the whole country
could be destroyed...
Including your families
and everyone you care about.
[ZAMPANO STAMMERS]
Wait, hold on!
Just what are you saying?!
I don't understand.
The Central forces weren't
told about any of this!
Please, we need
to know more!
What's going on?
[PAPERS RUSTLING]
[MILES]
You're sure about this?
Yeah...
I'm sure everyone will
feel a whole lot better
if we're tied up.
All right, Scar...
Give us a good performance.
I know what I'm doing.
And you will
keep your oath...
Your solemn word
as a true Ishvalan.
[SCAR GRUNTS IN AGREEMENT]
Excuse me,
Miss... Your ears!
Your earrings are
made out of metal...
If you don't take them out,
you'll get frostbite.
Oh...
[WINRY]
Ed...
You hang onto these for me.
I'll see you
back at the fort!
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[ED COUGHING]
We've finally
got Scar cornered,
and now he's taken
her hostage. Because of you!
[WIND HOWLING]
[ED GRUNTS]
I'm worried about what's
happened to Zampano and Gerso.
There are
two possibilities...
Either Scar did them in, or
they're out there in the snow.
[SOLDIER B]
The storm will have
Scar trapped, too.
We know he has to be
somewhere in this town, sir...
Since we're stuck here,
we might as well start
planning our next search.
[MILES THINKING]
We got lucky... This storm
really saved our hides...
Please let them
reach the fort safely.
Excuse me, Major...
Briggs is on
the line for you.
Yes, Miles here.
Eh, What'd you say?!
So it's true, then?
You're actually the daughter
of the Doctors Rockbell?
Yes. Did you know
my parents, Dr. Marcoh?
Of course I did.
There isn't a single doctor
who worked in Ishval that
didn't know your parents' names.
They did their duty, without
any regard to themselves.
I don't forgive
your wanton murdering.
[MASTER]
This is something
you must abide.
How can I forgive the military
for all that they've done?
I said nothing
about forgiveness...
There is no forgiveness
for wanton murder.
Any good man must always
condemn it... but still...
you must abide it...
You must sever the chain of
hatred once and for all.
If hatred and fear
are allowed to prevail,
the world will be
swallowed by them.
But if ultimate
understanding can be reached,
we may still have a chance
to be saved from ourselves.
That is my motivation...
that's why I study alchemy.
[YOKI]
Yep...
this is it, all right.
Okay. What is
this place?
The mine's staff room.
We need something from here...
Now let's see...
Ah...! Here it is.
[YOKI]
See...? A detailed
map of the tunnels.
[GERSO]
Looks complicated.
I can't tell what's what.
We go through here, here,
and here... and we're out!
Impressive. You sure
know how to read a map!
[YOKI LAUGHING]
Oh, it's nothing.
[GERSO]
At this rate, we
should make it over to
the other side
of the mountain
a lot quicker than
we had first thought.
Uh, excuse me,
Dr. Marcoh...?
Are there any hints in
those research notes you have
about how we might try
getting out original forms back?
At the moment,
I can't say...
It's a possibility,
but this is a form of
alchemy I know nothing about.
I'm sure you'll
find a way, Doc!
Ah! I can't wait to
see my family again!
[ZAMPANO LAUGHS]
Are you really that eager
to get back to
the old ball and chain?
I'm sure you miss your daughter,
but I doubt you miss your wife.
What about you?
You were such a lousy drunk
your own son couldn't
stand to be around you
for more than five minutes...
and you really think
you'll be able to face him now?
[ZAMPANO]
You have to bring that up?
[ZAMPANO AND GERSO LAUGHING]
Are you all right,
May? What's wrong?
It's just...
My entire clan is waiting
for me back in my country,
but I don't think
I can return to them.
The Philosopher's Stone is made
from sacrificing people's lives.
No one should be allowed to
create something so awful.
If His Imperial Highness
found out how to make one...
He wouldn't hesitate
a moment to do it.
He'd be willing to sacrifice
any number of our people.
But we need it...
What am I supposed to do now?
It's possible
these notes contain
what you're looking for:
a humane secret to immortality.
Let's hurry to the fort and
figure out what they say.
Right.
[ED]
What do you mean
"the fort is no longer safe"?!
I mean that
General Armstrong's been
summoned back to the
Central Command Center.
Troops sent from Central
have begun
invading Briggs in force...
There's no doubt
they're acting
on the Crimson
Alchemist's orders...
When we were
back at the fort,
I noticed him making
rather frequent phone calls.
This is bad. Without
General Armstrong there...
[MILES]
A commander
hand-picked by Bradley
will be posted in her place.
What do we do
about Winry?!
Hiding her and
the others will be difficult...
If they're not careful,
they're bound to fall
into the enemy's clutches.
[ED EXHALES FRUSTRATEDLY]
[ED]
We have to find
some way to warn them!
There's no way we can catch up
to them in a storm this bad.
So we sit here
and do nothing?!
I'll go tell them!
Don't go underestimating
the storm out there, kid...
You'll freeze to death
before you come anywhere close
to reaching them.
[AL]
There is a way... Listen.
Send someone who
doesn't have a body...
That storm won't
freeze me to death.
[STRONG WIND BLOWING]
[AL BREATHING HEAVILY]
This is worse than I thought.
Let's see...
the marker, the marker...
There!
[AL PAINFULLY GRUNTS]
I can't see anything at all!
[AL SHUDDERS]
[AL GASPS]
[AL STAMMERS]
[STRONG WIND BLOWING]
What was that?!
Was it my body?! But how...?
[66]
I guess a body
just can't hold up
with someone else's soul
being shoved inside of it.
[AL]
A body... a body that
shouldn't have a soul in it...
It's being rejected?
Does this mean my body
is pulling on my soul?
[AL BREATHES HEAVILY]
Stop it...! Snap out of it!
I have to hurry!
[FATHER]
Alphonse Elric...
Edward Elric...
And also...
There's...
Van Hohenheim...
Izumi Curtis...
She's a possibility.
That leaves one more.
[NARRATOR]
"A journey into
an unknown world."
The spirit desperately
searching for something new.
Nobody can stop
the spirit's quest...
but that journey... is not
without consequences of its own.
Next time, on Fullmetal
Alchemist: Brotherhood...
Episode 40: "Homunculus."
He who is right
does not always win.
It is he who overcomes all
barriers who will prevail.