A morning stroll sure feels good, de gozaru.
Yeah!
Yahoo…!
A few days later…
The students of Class 3-A have returned to the real world, as well as a normal and peaceful life.
Hey… We’re gonna be late again…
Gimme 5 more minutes…
You just said 5 minutes a while ago.
Then gimme 10 minutes…
Things’ll get bad if we keep postponing…
Ojou-sama…
I have come to escort you.
Morning, Secchan.
Asuna, hurry and get up already!
Asuna!
Gimme 15 more minutes…
She’s pushing it again.
Problem solved.
Secchan, I don’t think that’s really good.
Ain’t it peaceful?
That time, when that light saved us…
Could it be…
Anya…
“So does this mean… Case Closed!?”
by the Narrator
Justice has been served for the Case of the Star Crystal.
Mmm, good work.
So, um, Principal…
Regarding Anya…
We were just about to get to that, ~mya.
Oh, everything has been settled.
Didn’t I mention eveything’s been settled already?
I’ve already spoken with the Magic Academy about this.
Is that sufficient enough?
If the school principal has done so, then I have no objections.
Thank you very much.
Just think of this as another task.
But Negi sure has some very difficult tasks on his shoulders.
That’s true. Especially when he was turned into a Chupacabra.
He was probably extremely bitter.
We, as the delegates from the Magic Academy who wait for something to eat,
have no intention of protesting Negi-san’s diligence.
In a good way.
Although, he doesn’t really mean it, ~mya.
What are you trying to reveal!?
It’s already exposed, ~mya.
Alright. Let’s review everything until now.
So it’s true.
I heard about Negi from you. But I didn’t believe it.
I thought that things weren’t going well,
and he was crying by himself.
Anya…
And now, Satsuki-san, can you read the next one?
Satsuki-san?
Ah! I’m sorry!
That’s rare. I’ve never seen you fall asleep in class.
That’s so true. It’s really rare…
…that Asuna is awake.
Right, Asuna?
Oh… She’s sleeping.
I’m sorry. I was planning today’s party menu until late last night…
Ah, is that right?
There’s nothing we can do about that, is there?
Anyway, ’jou-chan, we’ll be looking forward to a fantastic meal from you today!
Yep.
We’re having a party?
Ah, we haven’t told you have we, Anya.
Let’s have fun with everyone tonight.
We thought it would be nice to have some entertainment.
Anya-chan, please join us, okay?
Okay.
Alright, that’s all for today’s class.
Okay!
Alright! Time to do today’s party preparations!
Yay, Party! It’s gonna be exciting!
Yeah. Exciting, indeed.
We’ve come back from the magic world safely after all, no?
Anya?
What happened?
Wasn’t the magic world a bad place?
What should we do? Did we say something wrong?
Anya-chan… I wonder if she still feels responsible for what happened…
I’ll go.
Negi…
I’ll be able to talk to Anya.
Everyone, please start without me.
Iinchou-san, I’ll leave it to you.
Wait, Negi I’m coming, too.
Me too.
I’m coming as well.
Leave it to me, Negi-sensei…
I will make the perfect party for you! ♥
RIGHT, EVERYONE!?
Yeah!
There she is!
Anya!
Wait, Anya!
Don’t follow me!
Stop it!
Wait, I want to talk to you!
Don’t come any closer!
Lilios!
Is this the Invisible Leaf Technique of the Igaryuu Stream!?
It’s magic.
Anya…
Right, I got it!
Sayo-chan, please take care of these.
Okay~
How does this look?
Perfect!
Sayo-san, can you reach that?
Of course!
Done!
Would you like me to do that?
Really, aru? Thanks for the help, then, aru!
It’s so nice to be able to fly…
I’m jealous, desu~!
If the two of you become ghosts, you’ll be able to fly as well!
Right, done!
Misa, you’re fast.
Just leave this stuff to me.
I FAIL…
I ripped it again…
Sakurako, you’re so clumsy.
What about you, Madoka?
That’s awesome!
You really did it, didn’t you?
Huh? Who made all that?
Huh?
Fold a mountain… Fold a valley… Fold a mountain… And we seem to be folding a valley…
He’s an expert. In a good way.
Even though he’s a frog…
It’s because I’m a frog.
Alright, everyone!
Have you guys been reading Chiu-Chiu’s Drifting Diary?
My heart is beating out of excitement!
When I was in the magic world, I thought up a lot of things!
Once you start reading it, you won’t stop, ~pyon!
Whoa! The access numbers have climbed.
GOOD JOB! As expected of me.
Hmm, let’s see, how is the response?
WHO ARE YOU CALLING A WAVE GROUP!?
At the very least…
CALL ME WONDER GIRL OR SOMETHING!!!
Ahhh… Wonder Girl!
Cabbages, tomatoes, long beans, onions, lettuce and carrots…
Is that all?
Akira, what does Satsuki’s memo say?
We still need green bell peppers.
But we don’t have any…
Ah! Let’s try planting some now!
Then we’ll have lots!
This isn’t the magic world…
Yeah… you’re right…
They think they’re going to win!
Let’s teach ’em a lesson!
She’s the same here and in the magic world…
The tracks got caught in the mud!
Is this some curse of a witch!?
Stop playing around and help us, Yuuna!
Sir! Yes, Sir!
Makie-san, won’t you be a dear and set the dishes?
Okay~
I wonder where the forks are.
They’re all in this cabinet.
What about the juice?
Is this alright?
What’s wrong, Iinchou?
Makie-san! Why are you performing so well today?
Eh? I shouldn’t?
You are a failure that keeps making me very angry, Sasaki Makie.
A Sasaki Makie who’s not a failure should always be a failure who is Sasaki Makie!
I don’t get it, but…
You’re really pushing it, aren’t you?
Wait, Anya! Listen to us!
Lilios!
She’s done it now…
I’m so gonna catch you and teach you a lesson!
Asuna’s just changed her motive…
Anya…
Alas! Being good friends is a beautiful thing!
by the Principal
Here.
Please hand these out to everyone.
What are these…?
Aren’t these some kind of vampire potions?
That’s exactly right.
Really?
These were made by Master a long time ago to become an adult,
but eventually failed in the end.
The latter was unnecessary.
That means these are inferior goods?
Yes. Because it was a failure, they’ve became youth potions instead.
Youth potions?
It’s something I don’t need. So you guys can have it.
So if we drink it, we’ll get younger?
No. Your age will not change.
So what becomes young then?
The age of your skin.
What? Your skin gets younger?
That’s very interesting.
I’ll take one!
Let me have one, too!
Waah! My skin is so smooth!
So tender… like a baby’s skin!
It feels like its transparent!
With this, I’m not afraid of UV rays anymore!
Amazing… Amazing!
This is a girl’s ultimate weapon!!
These are very interesting results…
The contents of this medicine are…
This is awesome…
Extracts from chordates, anhemitonics, salamander type, eyelashes.
So cool…
Newts.
And, vertebrates, something with good eyes…
Flying fox.
And an animal from temperate regions,
Roundback slug.
Right, right. I’ll join the crowd since this seems worth trying out.
I think there’s also a frog in there, ~mya.
Just kidding, ~mya.
There is a frog in there.
You’re annoying.
Hey Chizu-nee, what should we get for party gifts?
I have already decided.
Here!
Ah! Pretty!
So you’ll give a ribbon as a present?
You. Are. Wrong!
There we go! All done!
ME!?
Secret present is a cigarette.
13 points.
Recently, are points harder to get?
People grow up over time.
Growing up, eh…
Note: Mana - Mana (her name, obviously), “Maa na” - “Yeah, I guess.”
Maana.
4 points.
1 million points…
Today is a happy day. Today I shall create Lingshen’s special meat buns!
Wow, what kind of meat bun?
The buns that contain what I think are the tastiest of all!
I can’t wait!
So, what ingredient is the tastiest of all?
Ta-da!
The tastiest of all is meat buns!
These are recursive meat buns!
Meat bun in a meat bun!
So what’s inside the inner meat bun?
Of course, another meat bun!
And that’s considered a meat bun still…?
So, will you guys help me?
Let us feast on the World’s Delicacy Noodles that gives the world a power up!
Chachamaru, get rid of him.
Yes, Master.
We’ve lost sight of her.
I wonder where Anya-chan went…
She should have passed by here just now…
What’s wrong, Aniki?
I sense magic somewhere…
But I don’t know where…
Negi! Duck!
What was that!?
Darkness?
Lilios!
Anya!
I told you not to come, but you wouldn’t listen!
Why is the darkness…
The Star Crystal should’ve been sealed, right?
There’s still some darkness remaining.
But that reaction was…
Yes. Only those who were captured by the Star Crystal like me would understand.
Why didn’t you tell us?
We could help you…
No!
This is something I must take care of myself.
Anya…
One more and they should be gone.
Don’t get in my way!
W-What—?
Haat aar yuu duing!
You are the one getting in our way! What are you babbling about?
Thtop iit!
That’s right! You’re just like Negi, trying to think that you can do everything by yourself!
We’re gonna help. Got it?
But… Then I’ll be a burden.
What are you talking about? We’re friends, right?
Friends…?
That’s right, Anya-san.
When we’re friends, nothing we do is a burden.
Anya.
Run!
You guys…
So there was something as big as THIS left over…
The center of the darkness is…
Gotcha!
Argh, ouch ouch ouch… That was stubborn.
That was bad!
Are you alright, Ojou-sama?
We said we’d help, but ended up getting saved and taken care of.
Are you all right?
Thank you, Anya.
You saved us…
Well, it’s our turn now.
Negi-kun…
Please, let us transform!
Very well.
Partner: Kagurazaka Asuna, Konoe Konoka, Sakurazaki Setsuna;
Show me the power within yourselves!
Contract, activate!
All Cosplay Cards…
Anya, what should we aim for?
There!
Got it. We’ll clear the route!
Anya, get on!
Secchan!
Hidden Technique: Walking Eyes! Attack!
Now! Anya!
Del
Clio
Lilios!
We did it!
Ahhh, I’m so hungry.
My tummy is growling, too!
What’s up, you guys?
Open it.
Come on, just do it.
Okay…
Welcome to Mahora Academy Girl’s Junior High, Class 3-A!
Come this way, de gozaru.
Wha—?
Don’t be scared, aru! This is a reception, aru!
Reception?
Then the thing about you guys coming back is…
That was a lie.
We wanted it to be a surprise so we kept it a secret.
It was actually a party for you, Anya-chan!
Me?
You didn’t look happy after you came back…
We thought that you wouldn’t be able to have fun with us without a proper reception, desu!
That’s it.
Sorry we were keeping it from you.
Everyone gathered for you.
Master as well.
You don’t have to say unnecessary things.
Anya…
Thank you!
Alright, everyone, in the meantime…
Ready, and…
Cheers!
This is a good class, huh?
Yes.
It’s Negi-kun’s class, that’s why.
By the way, what’s up with you?
Ah well, um…
In the end, we have a grand finale. Here, smiles from Mahora Academy Girls Junior High Class 3-A have gathered.
Ah, that’s right! I found this when we were out hunting the darkness in the woods.
Here, it’s a present!
For me?
Is that a magic egg?
What’s inside?
Lilios!
Run~ya!
A Chupacabra?
You were looking for one right?
Run~ya…
Run~ya!
Can we get that kind of stuff here?
As long as there is love, miracles can happen!
As long as there is love…
AS LONG AS THERE IS LOVE…
What are you doing, Secchan?
That’s great for Asuna-san, isn’t it?
Who would’ve thought Chupacabras actually existed!
Make sure you Run~ya!
5 points.
Alright!
This time we have successfully produced genuine Chupacabra-signed T-shirts!!
Now, get 500 of those signed, good luck!
…by the end of today, okay?
Asuna, you monster…
The “Chu” became “Cha,” run~ya!