In the year 845, two terrifying
new breeds of Titan appeared:
the Colossal and the Armored,
barreling through the outer walls as if
wholesale destruction was child's play.
In blood and thunder, our way of life ended;
the Titans fed their hunger for human flesh unchecked.
Stop it! No!
The territory couched within the
circle of Wall Maria was abandoned.
Twenty percent of the human race perished.
As the Titan onslaught advanced,
our only choice was to withdraw behind Wall Rose.
Pick up the pace, you lead-heeled laggards!
Your boots water-logged, Arlelt?
Let's see some hustle!
Gear too heavy for you, son? Hell, drop it!
Leave it in the mud!
The Titans'll have easier work digesting
you without all the excess baggage.
Dammit.
Seriously?
Here. Focus on staying upright.
We are being graded on this, you know?
Thanks, but uh. Won't they demerit you for helping?
Yeah, if they find out.
Just make the cut and we're even, alright?
Reiner Braun.
The mind and constitution of a grass-fed ox.
Respected by his comrades.
I'm no one's burden, you hear me?
Armin Arlelt.
Built like a daffodil, but academically brilliant.
Annie Leonhart. Gifted with a sword,
but does not exactly play well with others.
Bertholdt Hoover.
Heaps of native talent, but too mild-mannered.
Jean Kirschtein. Head of the class on ODM;
also an insufferable smartass with a hair-trigger temper.
Think those showoffs can slice and dice?
Best hope you see a Titan before I do!
Military Police. Save a place for Jean!
Way to lead the charge!
You don't care if I steal your thunder, right?
Yeah-ah! Woo hoo!
Sasha Braus. Unusually fine instincts.
Rarely shares them with her teammates.
Conny Springer. Agile on the switchbacks.
Few sandwiches shy of a picnic.
Get ready.
Damn it! Still not deep enough!
Mikasa Ackermann. Model cadet. Excels in everything.
In fact, it's no overstatement to call the girl a genius.
Eren Jaeger. Lackluster in the classroom,
marginally better in the field.
But. Driven by a sense of
purpose that's almost terrifying.
Ahhhhh!
Ah!
Sorry, man. I've really gotta learn to hold back.
Eh, it's alright. Let's see how you do as the Rogue.
What're you waitin' on?
This training doesn't make sense.
We're not exactly picking
fights with someone our own size.
A guy'd have to be stupid to use this. I mean, a knife?
What if there's not an option?
The fight doesn't give us a say.
If it wants to get ugly, it gets
ugly. It's our job to be prepared.
The enemy comes in many forms.
Artillery's not always gonna be the answer.
Soldiers, the ones worth their salt anyway,
are ready for anything.
Don't believe me? Look.
Yeah? What about her?
Only thing she's ready for is any chance to slack off.
You think so? Maybe somebody
ought to give her a talkin' to.
Give her a li'l hard-knocks lesson in preparedness.
Commandant not beaten you down enough?
Keep it up, you'll be as flat
as the dirt you're walking on.
I suggest you think back to why
you enlisted in the first place.
Uh. What are you doing?
Whoa, she's pissed. Wow, I
thought she looked scary before.
You couldn't pay me enough to be on her bad side.
Okay! Now, go get 'er!
Huh? What the hell? Wait.
Right. I hope you don't expect me to hold back. Heads up!
Ugh. Son of a...! That was a dirty move!
Are we done here?
Not just yet. You know the drill: take up the dagger.
No, wait! This isn't how... Oh crap.
There.
So you ready to take me on yourself yet or what?
Uh. Not exactly.
Don't you dare.
She's got a lesson coming, right? You go get her.
Yeah. A soldier can't really afford to back down either.
Get ready, here I c...
That's some technique you've got.
Who taught you how to fight like that?
My father did.
He, like, pioneer it or...?
Does it really matter?
It's pointless, just like all this.
Wait, you mean the training in general?
Hand-to-hand combat doesn't
really count against our final grade.
The smart ones blow it off.
It's a crapshoot anyway. Only the top
ten cadets get to serve in the Interior.
The rest of us? Forget it.
Point is, only the idiots like you
take this part of boot camp seriously.
Idiots. And whatever they are.
Oh... Hello, sir.
First rule of this life, kid.
The better you are at dropping the bad guys, the
more distance the powers-that-be put between you.
That's what this whole stupid farce is about.
Sure. Whatever you say!
Face it. You don't fight the nature of things and win.
Look around you, Eren.
All the sons of bitches really expect us
to do is play the game. Don't be a pawn.
Yeah, well I still stand by what I said earlier.
I've been so fixated on building
myself up, I couldn't see it.
She's absolutely right.
They're not honing their skills to fight.
They're honing their skill to run.
I know, okay.
And look, I'm not saying it's right,
it's just the way things are.
Before Wall Maria was compromised, ODM experts were rare.
Only Scouts ever risked proximity to the Titans,
and their regiment wasn't large to begin with.
That's how you conserve fuel.
Let your momentum do the work for you.
Still, that's pretty advanced.
Duh. It's called having a sixth
sense for the finer points of your gear.
You gotta do the strut if you wanna make the cut.
The MP only recruit the best.
Ah. Man, that'd be amazing.
Workin' within a stone's throw of
the king. No greater honor than that.
Shut up, Marco.
We're not children. You can drop the misty-eyed B.S.
Honor doesn't have any damn part of it.
You just want a nice, cushy job in
the Interior playing glorified sentry.
That's not true! That's not me at all!
Listen to you guys.
Interior? Five years ago, this was part of it.
You got a point to make, friend? I'm right here.
Poor Jean. So misguided. And besides,
I don't think your head'll fit in the Interior anyway.
Very funny.
Seems a little backwards to me.
Fine-tuning your Titan-killing skills so the
brass'll station you somewhere you'll never see one.
You'd rather I was good at gettin' killed?
Thank you, but I'll pass. Better to
play the system than get gnawed on.
You son of bitch!
Bring it on, you little bastard!
Eren, please stop it!
Gentlemen, please.
You think you can judge me?
Huh? You rip my shirt, you're dead!
I don't give a damn about your shirt! You piss me off!
What? Are you crazy?
Oh, wait. I get it.
He has something to prove. Sounds familiar.
Sorry to do this.
It's only to end this before things get out of hand.
Dammit! What the hell was that move?
Little something I picked up this afternoon
while you were busy with your thumb up your ass.
You honestly believe the Military
Police are your ticket to the good life?
You're not a soldier. You're a joke.
Would someone care to explain
the little ruckus I heard just now?
I do hope everything's all right.
Sasha passed some gas, Commandant.
Why am I not surprised?
For the love of god, learn some self-control.
Of the original recruits,
two-hundred and eighteen cadets graduated.
Some with honors.
Do you have heart?
Sir!
As of this moment, you have three options open to you.
Choose wisely.
The Garrison Regiment,
whose job is to reinforce the Walls.
The Scout Regiment, who rides out into
Titan country to take back what was once ours.
And the MP Regiment, maintaining law and
order under orders from His Royal Majesty.
Those cadets eligible for the MP have already been named.
The rest of you, take a look.
These are the top of your class.
This is it. We've made it.
Our time is now. Titans, be ready!
Alright! MP, here I come!
Three square meals a day for life!
How in god's name did I get ranked under Eren?
You're really gonna turn your
back on the MP for the Scouts?
Why in the world would you do that? You're in the top ten.
The Scouts have always been my goal.
I don't want the easy life.
Not with all the work I've put in.
I trained to fight Titans.
Are you insane?
How many people have died?
We're talkin' a fifth of the population!
If that doesn't paint a picture for you,
I don't know what will.
This is our life now. We can't beat them.
Yeah? So what?
We buckle? Take it all lying down?
Things have changed.
Maybe not a helluva lot, but enough.
They aren't the mystery they were five years ago.
There's still a long way to go, but we've made progress.
Every battle we lost taught us a lesson,
gave us the tiniest inroad toward something like hope.
You tellin' me it's better to cut our losses?
Let all the death and destruction be meaningless?
Just to ball up and accept it? Not on your life!
Humanity's future lies outside the walls,
and I'm gonna clear the way!
I'm gonna take back what was ours!
I'll drive them out. And as long as at
least one of us can say that, we're not done.
Eren, wait!
Yeah, good luck out there, hotshot.
I'll root for you from His Majesty's barracks.
That was, uh, quite a speech you gave us there.
Yeah. Most of it was yours.
All that stuff you used to say back in the day.
Yeah, well I'm joining the Scout Regiment, too!
Now you're just being stupid. Come on!
You're not a fighter! Your life is with books!
I'm through with letting other people fight for me.
Guess it's the Scouts for me, too, then.
Oh, come on! You were top of the class!
You'd be wasting your shot!
Understand this, Eren. Where you go, I go.
I made a promise to your mom before she died.
I'm not letting you die.
I've got your back whether you like it or not.
So just deal with it.
Yeah. Well, Mom's not here.
A lot of the people I used to
care about aren't here either.
Heads up!
The main unit of the Scout Regiment is back!
That's right, Commander Erwin!
Did ya give those ugly bastards a thrashing?
Look! It's Captain Levi!
They say he's like an entire brigade unto himself!
Spare me, please.
Feel how excited everybody is?
It's like the crowd just has a different energy now.
Well, we are going on five years without incident.
Seems like a good omen.
And you should check out all the cannon upgrades.
The sight alone oughta be enough to scare 'em off.
That's the truth.
You in denial 'cause you're a couple? What's that about?
Whoa whoa whoa! This isn't what it looks like! Okay?
Knock it off, man! It's embarrassing!
Hey hey, lookie here!
Mr. Hannes!
Word on the street's they let you graduate yesterday.
Either you've grown up or standards have plummeted.
Oh yeah, like you're one to talk!
The Corps of Engineers keep their new chief in the drink?
Watch it.
I'm sorry if this is out of the blue.
But I want you to know you're Mom's death still haunts me.
Me too, but it wasn't your fault.
We were shooting in the dark then.
But nothing like that's gonna happen again.
We know what we're dealing with now.
Fired up and capable make a good combination, kid.
Don't screw it up by dyin'.
What? The hell you mean you're joining the Scouts?
What happened to the MP? That was your whole thing!
Don't worry about it!
A guy's allowed to change his mind, okay?
I think your speech yesterday lit a fire under him.
Ain't nobody talkin' to you!
His temper tantrum had nothing to do with it.
Take it easy.
It's not like you're the only one.
What? Are you serious?
Can you guys keep a secret?
'Cause I totally just helped
myself to the Officer's Pantry.
Sasha! They can throw your butt in the clink for that!
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
What isn't wrong with her?
It'll be fine. I'm willing to share.
Oh, can you imagine the sandwiches?
Put it back!
Yeah! Do you have any idea how rare
meat's been since the Titans took Wall Maria?
Um, li'l bit. Yeah.
Just look at it this way. Pretty soon,
we'll take back all the room we need for livestock.
I would really like a slice, please!
Hey if he gets one, so do I! Just so you know.
Me, too! I'm in on it, too!
But.
Come on! Don't just stand there.
If they see us slacking off, we're in for it.
See you guys at lunchtime.
Has it really been five years?
Look at us. Ready to stand tall again.
We can do it.
Mankind didn't start this
fight, but we're gonna finish it!
It's hot!
Samuel!
Sasha!
Try not to move! Understand?
That was too damn close.
Oh god, no. Not again!
They're gonna get in.
They're gonna get in!
No. This is over.
I'm gonna put a stop to this!
I will. This ends now.
This is it, people! Do or die!
Mounted Cannon Squad Four, take out the Colossal Titan!
This is our chance! Don't let it slip away!
You. It's been a while.
The jaws of Hell reopen.
Before you can even catch your
breath, you're between its teeth.
Sometimes, saving the people dearest to
you means making the ultimate sacrifice.