Let's see...
What should I do?
I guess I'll play with them a little.
Oh? What's going on, Yuuji?
Looks like something's going on.
Something?
"Sponsored by Fumizuki Academy"
Sponsored by Fumizuki Academy?
Competition for extravagant prizes?!
Orienteering Contest?!
What grows on its own? Hmm, what is it?
One more chance, one more
chance. Never never give up!
One more chance, one
more chance. Never give up!
BAKA and TEST
-Summon the Beasts-
"Nice to encounter you,"
that one's too easy!
There's only one answer
that I decided on at the start
My heart fluttered. Will I pass?
I won't panic whether
it's a matter of love or war
I sigh as I cram all night long
There's a genius dreamer inside of me
It'd be nice if everything I wanted came true
Pay no mind to other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
I'll definitely be waiting right here.
Perfect-area, I can hear someone wishing for it
Ah! Ear! Ear!
Why? We just keep missing each other
If you came to me for advice, it'd go like
"So, friends?" "Yes, friends."
That's a sad 0 points.
No! Do it again! Rewrite it!
I'm serious, one
more chance please
You know, there's a future
more wonderful than now
Make it more wonderful than
now... my life, my life, my life
"Episode 5" "Maps, Treasures, and Striker Sigma V"
Akihisa Yoshii has found a treasure.
It's been a long time since
I've had such a nice breakfast.
Time to chow down!
"Munch, munch, munch..."
Hmm... Just as you'd expect
from Fumizuki's bread crumbs.
They taste just like bread!
"Munch, munch, munch..."
If only I had jam or something,
I'd have no complaints about this breakfast.
You are not in a position to complain.
Hmm... I wonder if crumbs digest quickly.
Hm?
This is Fee the fox...
"Welcome"
a mascot character for Kisaragi Grand Park.
By the way, she is very popular among children.
This is Kisara--
I already explained it in my narration.
The child who dropped
this might come back to get it.
I'll put it back where it was.
Hm?!
Hmm... I can't find it. I can't find it.
Good morning, Hazuki. What're you doing here?
Ah! Good morning, Stupid Big Brother!
I was looking for something I dropped.
Something you dropped?
I lost my Fee cell phone strap...
I can't get a new one
anymore since it's a limited edition.
Oh... Then I saw it over...
This is bad! What should we do?!
Fee!
What's the matter, Yoshii?
M-Mr. Fukuhara!
Good timing! Please give me
approval to summon my Avatar!
Oh? What's the reason?
I'm in a hurry! Please hurry up!
I guess it can't be helped.
Just this once, okay?
All right! I'm summoning my Avatar. Summon!
All right! Get that cell strap!
Save Fee!
Are you okay, Big Brother?! Stupid Big Brother!
Ow, ow, ow... The feedback from his pain...
Geez, what'd you do such a stupid thing for?
Good morning, Principal.
You scared me! Don't play
a prank using your Avatar!
It wasn't a prank! I was trying to
pick up something that was drop...
Ah...
Ahhhh!
This shows that you shouldn't
get too attached to toys.
You don't have to say it like that, right?!
Huh?
I took back the summoning approval.
You shouldn't use your Avatar for violence.
Violent?! I was just trying to help Hazuki.
An Avatar isn't some toy for idiots.
If you feel frustrated, show
us your non-stupid side, too.
If you do that, you might be
able to get something you want.
What?
I'm sorry, Hazuki.
That's okay... Don't worry.
Hazuki...
"Competition" "Extravagant" "Prizes" "Orienteering Contest"
So this was what the principal was talking about.
They've listed the prizes here!
C-Cafeteria meal tickets for a year?!
Exchange tickets for new video games?!
That's quite extravagant.
It says that there's a secret item as well.
Ah!
Fee, Noin, and Ein
limited edition cell strap set?!
--What, Akihisa?! You want something like that?
--This! This! This! This! This!
Wh-What's wrong with that?!
What do I have to do to get it?
Here's a map of the Academy.
So I have to search for it here?
I'm good at finding treasure boxes in RPGs!
And, these are the test questions!
What?!
The test answers are the
coordinates of the checkpoints.
The hidden tickets you find there
are what you exchange for prizes.
Th-Then you won't get them
unless you solve the questions!
On top of that, it's first come,
first serve. If you run into different teams,
you can fight using your
Avatars and take their tickets.
I'm at a disadvantage in every way!
Oh, that's right! If I team up with Himeji...
Everyone, have a seat!
I'll announce the orienteering teams!
I'm teaming up with... Yuuji and Hideyoshi?!
Himeji is teaming up with
Minami and... Muttsulini?!
I grouped trouble students together,
as you never know what they'll do.
What?! That's not fair! I'll take
Hideyoshi since he's cute, but...
Yuuji is no help at all!
I'll throw your own words
back at you with interest!
You have until the after-school bell rings.
This is part of your classes!
Work on it seriously.
One set consists of three questions, huh?
The answer to the first question
shows the X-axis point on the map.
The second one shows the Y point,
and the third shows the Z point,
which tells which floor it'll be on.
Oh, it's all multiple choice.
Then it's a piece of cake!
Are you good at multiple choice questions?
You don't know my area of specialty?
Okay then. Let me show you.
I was stupid to put my
hopes in him even for a moment.
I use Striker Sigma V for math!
Problem Breaker for modern Japanese!
Shining Answer for history!
They are highly accurate!
Has your life been controlled
by how well the dice work?
Don't make fun of them! Just watch!
Do we have to?
Roar! Striker Sigma V!
Finish!
All right. I got it.
652 for the X-axis, 237 for Y, 5 for Z!
I found it! The target is over there!
Oh, so it's in the air?
You go get it.
This is strange.
I wonder if they screwed up the question.
It's the answer that's screwed up!
We found it!
Hm?
Whoa!
Here it is! This is an
exchange ticket for a prize!
We started off with a correct answer.
All right! We did it!
It seems that the numbers for
the X- and Y-axes were correct.
See? Striker Sigma V is incredible, isn't it?
What's incredible is
you believing in that thing.
"Exchange ticket for free cafeteria desserts for a year"
This is for a year's worth of cafeteria dessert tickets!
Let's split it amongst the three of us.
I don't need it.
Rep... Are you on a diet?
Instead... if we find this, let me have it.
A premium ticket for Kisaragi Grand Park?
Oh, I get it! You're going
there with your boyfriend!
No... I'm going with my husband.
I just felt a sudden chill.
You sure have lots of hardships, don't you?
Outside of math, I'm completely helpless!
You're amazing, Tsuchiya.
Just Health and Physical Education.
I'm helpless in everything else.
Okay, all done.
Amazing! Let's go find them right away!
Ah!
Th... These coordinates are...!
"Girls' Changing Room"
I... I can legally go into
the girls' changing room.
All right! Let's find the prize!
This is a girls' changing room...
and yet there're no girls changing.
Of course not.
It's a lot of work when the place isn't tidy.
The areas guys don't see
are often like this, aren't they?
This place holds no value
unless girls are changing.
What's wrong, Tsuchiya? Are you okay?
I'm fine... This is nothing!
Tsuchiya!
I can't lose to something like this.
I-I'm deeply moved...
Well... Let's see...
the idiot's determination...
Idiot Test!
Smash! Problem Breaker!
The coordinates on the map are... around here.
In our classroom?!
I wonder what this is.
It's not a prize, at least.
This is strange. I wonder if
I should make it a little lighter.
Shave it all the way!
Uhm... So you found it?
What? Is this... yours?
Yes... In that basket... Um...
Yoshii?!
Yes, Himeji?
Do you like sweets?
Yep! I love them!
Good! To tell you the truth, I got up
early this morning and baked chiffon cakes.
Oh? You can bake cakes, too?
Hey! Don't tell me...
Just as you'd expect from
Problem Breaker. It's a real treasure.
You were a good guy.
I will not forget you.
Why are you saying farewell words?
If you like, you all are welcome to some.
What?!
Now...
please go ahead.
Ah... I'm one short.
There're three chiffon
cakes. There're four of us.
Which means only one can survive.
The First...
Championship Match!
Do-or-die Rock-Paper-Scissors Contest!
Yaay!
If I lose...
I'll die!
Mizuki and Tsuchiya sure are taking
their time. I wonder what they're doing.
Impossible! I can't answer
any more questions all by myself!
No, honey.
Huh?! Miharu?!
I'm right here.
The questions are solved!
Where the heck did you come from?!
Honey! Please take a look at
the answers that I worked hard on!
If we check these answers against the map...
believe it or not,
it turns out that the
treasure is hidden under your bra!
Huh?!
Now, give up and entrust
your body and heart to me!
There's no way I'd do that! Let me go!
No! The map has these coordinates!
There's no mistake about it as
the Ministry of Education says so!
You're the one who's making a mistake!
--Then let's make a big mistake together, honey! Let's do it!
--N... Noooooo!
Seriously... if they have time to
spare for a stupid event like this,
I wish they'd use that time
to advance our studies a little.
The map points to these coordinates.
This is... Yoshii's shoe locker?!
I-If someone sees me here, they'd think I'm...
about to put a love letter in there!
No, no... I'm trying to
get a ticket out of here.
No, wait!
Then that looks as if I'm trying to
steal a love letter addressed to Yoshii!
No, no! It's the treasure in here that I want!
I can give them an excuse
no matter what they say!
But... depending on who it is...
what's inside of Yoshii's shoe
locker might be a treasure box to them!
Then I can't talk my way out!
What... What... What should I do?!
Please do whatever you want.
Shine...! Shining... Answer!
Here it is! Just as we'd
expect from you, Hideyoshi!
I don't think I had anything to do with it.
Let's see! What's the prize?
Wha...?! "Try again"?!
So this wasn't the right place.
Dammit! So that was a trick question!
It doesn't matter if it's a trick question
or not when you're using a die, does it?
Hmm... Should I change
the angle of the stabilizer?
I don't think that would
increase the accuracy rate.
--It must be the name!
--Now... How's this?
Whoa! You answered them seriously?
Are you sure, Yuuji?
I don't wanna go weird places
due to your wrong answers.
You're in no position to say that!
According to Yuuji's answers, this is the place.
You were right! Here it is!
How can you solve those questions, Yuuji?
I picked only the questions
I thought even I could solve.
I'm impressed you solved these...
When you're ranked the bottom in tests...
Did you cheat?
Is it that hard to believe?
So, what was the prize?
Let's see... A premium ticket for
one couple to Kisaragi Grand Park?
The couple is invited to a
special event, Wedding Experience.
Oh? That sounds interesting.
Yuuji, why don't you go with Kirishima?
Don't even mention something so dreadful!
It won't be just an
experience. She'll make it real!
Get that ominous thing
out of my face! You guys go!
Really?
Are you free this coming Sunday, Hideyoshi?
It says it's for a couple, doesn't it?!
What...?! You don't... like me?
I'm a guy!
I'm turned down! How miserable I am!
There's only one way... to end this misery!
Hideyoshi! I like you!
What're you saying all of a sudden?!
There's an important meaning to this.
You may not know this, but
there's a legend in Japan that
if you confess your love under the
legendary tree, you'll become happy.
There's no such legend, though.
"Under the legendary tree" in this academy
means Hideyoshi Kinoshita,
a legendary beautiful girl!
In other words, it means that if
I confess my love to you, I'll become happy!
What'd you say, Yoshii?!
--If that's the case, we can legally confess our love to Kinoshita!
--There's so many holes in that logic
--Legally!
--that I don't even know where to start.
--I like you, Hideyoshi Kinoshita!
--I love you, Hideyoshi Kinoshita!
Are you guys crazy?!
After all, we couldn't get any valuable prizes.
This is a tough event for idiots.
At this point, there're not
that many prizes left, huh?
I wonder what the secret item was.
Ah! Fee's cell strap hasn't been taken yet!
Are you still going to continue, Akihisa?
The remaining questions
are all difficult, you know.
Or, do you wanna randomly dig
up the schoolyard or something?
Hm?
Randomly...
I got it! All the answers on the test...
What're you doing?
I'm marking all the points
in the answer choices!
All of them?!
It's possible that a treasure is
hidden where these X and Y are crossed!
What about the height?!
Of course, we'll check every floor!
There're lots of them!
Searching all of them is...
Searching round-robin is a fundamental of games!
That's unreasonable...
I see... That sounds interesting.
We can't solve the questions anyway.
Then let's show them that
idiots fight in their own way.
Yuuji...
Yep!
I'll go check the fourth floor!
Akihisa, check the third floor!
Hideyoshi, check the second floor!
Okay!
Got it!
Cleaning closets... Not here!
Not here!
Not here! Hey, ahh!
"Girls' Changing Room"
Hmm... not here!
Not here!
Ah...
In use...
Locker...!
--Not here!
A dog!
Which one?!
Trash bin!
--Not here!
Wh-Why?!
Ladies' Room!
--Not here!
Oh?
I'm in here.
What?!
Water tank...
--Not here!
Ouch!
Again...!
--Not here!
Please ignore me...
Again...!
--I'm in here!
Good! It's open!
Hey, what am I doing?!
Dammit. We couldn't find anything.
I wonder if nothing is left.
Ah, that's right! We
haven't checked this place yet!
But... this place doesn't
have anything to hide things in.
That can't be... The strap
ticket hasn't been found yet!
It's definitely somewhere...
I found it! Just as I thought!
Hideyoshi! We can find it even
if we can't solve the questi... Hm?
Oh? I came here after
solving the questions on my own.
What? You're...
Big Sister! Why are you here?
According to the rules, we can take
it by fighting using our Avatars, right?
D-Don't tell me...
I'll approve it.
What?!
Summon!
This is bad, Akihisa! Our
power is nowhere near theirs!
I never thought we'd have to fight them.
Oh no... What should we do?
We won't hold back.
Are you ready?
Well then, bye-bye!
"Yuuko Kinoshita" "Yuuji Sakamoto" "Akihisa Yoshii"
"Hideyoshi Kinoshita" "Shouko Kirishima" "Aiko Kudou"
What?!
Time is over.
Which means...
That's right.
Yeah.
"Exchange ticket for Kisaragi
Grand Park mascot strap set"
A... All right!
Amazing! I got the Fee cell strap!
Not only that, it's a set of three!
Good for you!
I wonder if Hazuki will be happy.
--Hm?
"Iron Bracelets Activation Manual"
I wonder what this is?
Could it be that this is the secret item?
I wonder what you use this for.
It comes with a manual, too.
Iron bracelets...
The activation word is "Awaken"...
That alone wouldn't...
explain what will happen...
Let's try it!
Awaken!
What?!
This is...
Could this be...
Summon!
This is incredible!
We can summon our Avatars
without a teacher's approval!
The field is a little small, but this is great!
What? What?!
Wh-Why did only my clothes get torn off?!
Akihisa... Yours is okay?
Ah... You're right!
So this means only an idiot can use it, huh?
What do you mean by "an idiot"?!
You're an idiot too, Yuuji!
Then a first-rate idiot.
What?!
Then ultimate idiot.
Then supreme idiot!
What do you mean by "supreme," huh?!
I see...
Looks like we still have to make improvements.
But in any case...
Fools and blunt scissors can be
useful if you make wise use of them.
Anything and anyone has redeeming points.
B-A-K-A Go Go Home!!
The end of the school day is bliss
If I am to put it into words, "It's really angelic!"
My peace was shattered
by a sudden announcement
Talking about the make up test. "This is Hell!"
While my friends and I were
sharing funny stories, I said,
"There's no way anyone is that stupid"
But the truth is, deep down in my heart
I was shouting, "That was me!"
About that "Monthly Parking"
sign you see in the parking lot
I thought it was the name of a company...
All this time...
Sticking to your idiocy can be cool
Is our common sense nonsense?
We don't need rules in this world
It's dog eat dog food! It's social upheaval!
Look!
The sun that rose from the west is setting
Run home! It's dinner time already.
Let's go home! Let's go home!
Question 6.
What strokes does the individual
medley in swimming consist of?
Anime Song Medley, Old
Popular Song Medley, Dove Sablé.
I do like Dove Sablé, too...
Next Episode! "Me, Pools,
and Swimsuit Paradises... and..."
This will be on the test.
"Illustration: Mako Aboshi"
"Please join us again next week!"