When were the Taika Reforms?
We're in third grade; you should know already! You're so dumb.
We haven't learned it yet.
It's easy to remember.
Call them the "uneventful reforms".
TL Note: The word translated here as "uneventful" is mujiko. The
numbers 6, 2, and 5 can be pronounced as mu, ji, and ko respectively.
Uneventful?
Yeah, see, nothing much happened during them.
Uneventful six-two-five.
Uneventful... six-two-five.
Don't forget.
I've got it stuck in my head now,
so don't worry.
Just who are we letting grow up on their own?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never, never give up!
Never give up!
Idiots and Tests and Summoned Beings
Meeting someone else is the easy way out!
I knew what I would say before they even asked.
Do I look lovestruck enough?
I'm not gonna lose my cool, love's at stake!
Study! Study! Study! It keeps me up all night.
I've got a genius inside of me.
It'd be great if my dreams came true
because I don't care about anything else.
Perfect area complete!
I'll be waiting for you!
I can hear your voice from the perfect area ahead.
Fly! I won't stop!
Yeah, that's me, the person you just passed by.
Are we still friends?
I flunked our friendship test, after all.
No! I'll take it again! Again!
Come on, gimme another chance!
Something better awaits us in the future.
A better life awaits us!
Here at Fumizuki Academy, knowledge is power...
Second Period
Lilies and Roses and Health
...and your test score is justice.
What's up, Himeji?
Got something for me?
Well, I wanted to ask you about something...
May I have a moment?
Class F ended up winning the first sophomore ESB.
They're better than I thought.
The class that lost to them must be angry about having their facilities downgraded.
Well, maybe that'll teach them that they
need to study hard in order to win battles.
Life itself is a battle, after a-
Actually...
The students personally requested that they not swap facilities.
What?
It ain't called superglue for nothing.
They're as good as new in no time flat.
We should feel blessed that we're afforded the luxury of such high quality glue.
It's only natural to upgrade your
supplies after winning a tough battle.
Man, but we could be using class E's desks right now...
Yuuji, why the hell did you turn down the trade?
Seriously, man?
You like those shitty desks?
They're better than these damn flimsy tables!
You don't study anyway, so what difference does it make to you?
A big one!
I eat on it, I sleep on it, and I draw on it.
Mizuki
Akihisa
As you can see, my desk is an important part of my school experience!
They share the same heart.
This is the last day we'll be using them.
Class A declared war on us, yeah?
We're gonna beat them and start using their facilities.
The situation's not exactly what I had in mind, but we should do just fine.
My predictions allowed for a certain margin of error.
Right, Himeji?
Yes...
Come on, let's go to class A.
So this is class A.
It looks more like a five star hotel.
This is how I should be spending my school days!
Oh my god, Yoshii! They have a self-serving bar with snacks!
You're gonna get taken advantage of if that's all it takes to impress you.
Man up.
Practice what you preach.
Oh? Isn't the ESB tomorrow?
Sister!
Surrendering already?
We're just here to check out our new facilities.
Ohh, so tough.
I'm here to negotiate.
I want a one-on-one battle
between the two class reps.
Are you an idiot?
What makes you think you can handle our class valedictorian?
Are you scared?
I can't help but think that you're trying to take us
out while we're still recovering from the last ESB.
Want to go now?
Hang on.
I'm fine with one-on-one.
Rep!
But I have a condition.
The loser must promise to comply with an order from the winner.
So that was why you declared war on us?
Don't jump to conclusions.
We have an obligation to protect the
public order and dignity of our school.
We must punish lazy idiots who
declare war without doing anything.
Fine. The loser of the one-on-one will do whatever the winner says.
No, it'll be five-on-five.
Yuuko.
I'm not saying that I think our rep is going to lose.
We just need to take some precautions, is all.
Sure. Five-on-five it is.
In exchange, however, we'll pick the subjects.
Very well.
Negotiation complete.
What now, Yuuji?
Don't worry. We're still gonna win.
All that's changed is that we get the honor of bossing them around.
Are you sure we should go through with this.
I've heard some nasty rumors about Shouko Kirishima, class A's rep.
Rumors?
She's smart and she's not half-bad looking either.
But she doesn't have a boyfriend or
anything. Never even hangs out with guys.
Yeah, she does seem like the popular type.
So, the rumors say she has no interest in guys.
No interest in-?
Holy shit, so her goal is...!?
No frickin' way.
There's no way that could be
happening right under our noses.
Right, Shimada?
No, I'm sure it could be happening.
I found you, mistress!
Miharu!?
You're so mean!
How could you drink tea with these disgusting faggots instead of hanging out with me?
Let go! Get the hell offa me!
Mistress!
Who the hell is that?
Miharu Shimizu of class 2D.
Stop it! Get the hell away from me!
Don't be so shy, mistress.
I know you love me - you don't need to hide it!
I'm not a dyke!
Help me out here, Yoshii!
She's right, Shimizu. Being gay is wrong.
While it's true that Shimada looks like a guy, acts like a guy, and has the chest of a guy...
...she's a pro wrestler in disguise!
I'm totally feminine in all areas!
Exactly! I love my mistress's feminine traits!
A-almost...
Shimada, stop! I'll do whatever you say!
Seriously?
Then I want you to treat me to
crepes at Lapelle's next weekend.
I'm kinda low on cash-
Fine, I'll treat you!
Also, you have to call me "honey" from now on.
And I'll call you Aki.
Yes, honey!
And... And...
S-say you love me!
S-s...
You won't do it.
Say it!
A-almost...
Hurry up and say you love me.
Okay!
"Hurry up and say you love me"!
You dumbass!
N-n-no! You're gonna break it!
Man, I thought I was toast.
Himeji?
What're you doing, Himeji?
Yoshii!?
This looks like a love letter.
But who would write a love letter in the classroom?
Get a clue. What else would it be?
I finally realized
that I'm in love with you.
Umm... I think you have the wrong idea about this...
The proof is right in your hands.
Actually, maybe not...
But no, it is!
Come on, just admit it.
...love you.
What a depressing chain letter...
God dammit, just deal with it!
Things will get weird if you misunderstand.
Is he in our class?
Yuuji is in our class, obviously.
Yes.
I see.
There's no point in forcing yourself.
Hey, I'll teach you how to write depressing chain mail properly.
No, this isn't a chain letter!
Do you even know how!?
But it is!
Because the world is crashing down around me.
Have some tea and calm down.
No, it's not.
Seriously? What do you see in him?
He's not even good-looking.
No, it's not about his looks...
Look in the mirror.
I mean, I like how he looks!
My friend told me that when two handsome guys like you and Sakamoto walk together,
it's like a painting.
She sounds like a great friend. Treat her well.
She also told me that you're the bottom in the relationship.
Yuuji is definitely a better fit for Himeji.
I don't think you should be friends with her.
Maybe I still have a chance.
But he's also beautiful on the inside!
Yeah, his liver is pretty solid.
I'm not talking about his organs!
Are you really that far in denial?
You can't be telling me that you like his personality.
I am. He's so kind and cheerful.
There's always a smile on his face.
I've always admired him.
I see... Well...
Yes?
I hope you hear the reply you wanted to.
Thank you.
There you are.
We're about to begin our strategy meeting.
Hey, where are you going? Akihisa!
Stay away from me.
Don't walk with me.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I... I...
I'm not the bottom!
What?
All right, let's begin round one.
Elites vs. Idiots
Why am I the round girl?
Round one.
What are you talking about?
There's no one more suited for it than you.
But I'm not a girl.
Would both contestants please step forward?
Good luck, Shimada.
Off I go.
Let's make this quick. I don't feel like prolonging a battle with someone who's going to lose anyway.
You're in for a shock if you think I'm weak just 'cause I'm in class F.
Begin!
Summoning Being!
Summon!
My math is at class B level.
Wow, cool.
Summon!
N-no way...
I'm in class A, you know.
Victor: Yuuko Kinoshita of class A.
Not an unexpected turn of events.
I mean, you forgot that class A is higher than class B-
A-almost...
I'm kind of enjoying this.
Round two.
Let's commence with round two.
Would both contestants please step forward?
I'm class A's Miho Satou.
It's all you, Akihisa.
Me? We're screwed if we lose this one.
Don't give me that. I believe in you.
So you want me to get serious?
Yeah.
You can stop hiding it now.
Show everyone your true strength.
Man, you don't make it easy for me.
Don't tell me you're...
Yeah. You'll be the first to see my true power.
So you really are...
Correct.
I've always kept it a secret, but I'm actually...
left-handed.
Victor: Miho Satou of class A.
What the hell does being left-handed have to do with your test scores!?
A-almost...
Now's when it really starts.
Time to get serious.
You bastard! I thought you said you believed in me!
I believed that you'd lose!
I'm gonna punch you in the balls with my left hand!
Round three.
Round three will now begin.
Class A: Aiko Kudou.
Class F: Kouta Tsuchiya.
What subject?
Health.
I hear you're pretty good with health.
But I'm pretty good at it too - in a different way.
I use the knowledge practically.
Practically?
Voyeur!
Carnivore vs. Voyeur
How dare you do that to Voyeur!
Cheapskate!
You're going to sub for him?
Anyone can tell that you're hopeless, though.
I can teach you health if you want.
Practically, of course.
Yoshii!
Aki!
Mind your own business! He's never gonna get the chance to do it!
Exactly! He doesn't need the knowledge!
Why are you saying that!?
Voyeur!
This is nothing.
All right, let the battle commence.
Summon.
Summon!
Over 400?
Practical vs. theoretical. I'll show you which is stronger.
See ya, Mr. Voyeur.
Acceleration...
...complete.
I-I lost?
Victor: Kouta Tsuchiya of class F.
Wow! His health score is on par with my comprehensive score!
All right, let's begin round four.
Round four.
Wish me luck.
Good luck, Himeji!
Thanks.
I'll be her opponent.
Toshimitsu Kubo, huh?
This is the key round.
Why?
He's #2 in our year.
This is gonna be tough if we don't pick something he's bad at.
No way...
So, what subject?
Comprehensive.
Wait, we have the right to decide-
Don't worry.
Himeji?
Crap...
Comprehensive basically means that your class rank translates directly into your strength.
That means...
Start battle.
Summon.
Look at those points.
That's how strong #2 is?
Himeji!
Summoning Being...
Summon!
Over 4000?
Her points are on par with the valedictorian.
When the hell did you...
Go!
I decided to give it my best shot.
I had been wondering why we
even had ESBs in the first place.
Imagination
I like this class...
because everyone helps each other out with all they have...
because the person I like is in this class.
So I won't let you guys down!
Victor: Mizuki Himeji of class F.
Hear that, Aki?
It's an even split now!
Himeji...
The next match will determine everything.
Round five.
All right, let's begin the last round.
It's finally my turn.
Yuuji...
Watch and learn.
I'm class F's rep, Yuuji Sakamoto.
I'm class A's rep, Shouko Kirishima.
What subject?
I choose a restricted Japanese
history test for the final round.
The material will be of the elementary school level. The maximum points will be 100.
A testing showdown!?
Not a Being battle?
The ESB is a battle utilizing your test scores.
What's a test showdown?
As long as it involves tests in some ways and is approved by a teacher,
it doesn't matter how you go about it.
Very well. Prepare yourselves.
Both contestants, please head to the classroom.
Have you lost your mind, Yuuji?
Won't both of you get 100s if it's at an elementary school level?
Isn't it just going to end in a draw?
No. A simple mistake means you lose it all.
Exactly.
This is a test of endurance and concentration, not academics.
Yuuji...
Don't sweat it. I have this in the bag.
Once Shouko memorizes
something, she'll never forget it.
Doesn't that mean you're at a disadvantage, then? You're dealing with history.
No, that's the point.
She memorized the Taika Reforms as taking place in the year 625.
If that question appears on the test, victory is mine.
Wait, Yuuji.
I thought the Taika Reforms did take place in the year 625.
No, they took place in 645.
I'm positive.
Trust me, Akihisa.
Yuuji...
Those system desks are ours.
Please begin.
It started.
What happens if that question doesn't appear?
Well, if his endurance and concentration aren't as good as hers, then we'll lose.
But if it does appear...
Please answer the following questions:
Who did Oda Nobunaga make an alliance with in the Battle of Nagashino?
Who signed the Harris Treaty with American Consul General Harris?
When did the Taika Reforms take place?
There it is!
I shall hereby announce the scores for the restricted exam.
Class A representative, Shouko Kirishima:
97 points.
Yes!
She didn't ace it!
We're gonna live like kings!
Yoshii!
Next, class F's rep, Yuuji Sakamoto:
53 points.
Class F ended up trading their coffee tables for cardboard boxes.
It's a time of peace now that school's out.
If I were to describe her, she's a real angel!
Then came a notice that shattered my fun.
It said I had to stay afterschool! It's like hell!!
I was talking about it with my friends, and I said,
"No way anyone's that stupid!!"
But deep inside me,
I was shouting out,
"I AM THAT STUPID!"
That sign in the parking lot
that says "Monthly"...
I always thought that was the company's name.
ALWAYS.
Stupidity's a character! A real man!
Our common sense is the lack thereof!
We don't need rules in our fucking world!
Eat steak out every night, overthrow the mass!
Take a look, the sun that rose from the west is setting back down!
Run home, it's almost dinner!
Let's get home!
We're even worse off than before!
What the hell was with that score!?
That's my ability.
If you couldn't get 100, then what the hell was the point?
I never thought there'd be an ambush.
What ambush!?
Yuuji.
Our promise.
We promised to comply with their order if we lost.
Fine, what is it?
You can't do this, Kirishima!
Homosexuality is unacceptable!
Yuuji, go out with me.
You still haven't given up?
I'll never give up.
I'll always love you.
Can I refuse?
No, we promised.
We're going on a date right now.
Wai-
Wait, what?
Just what the hell is going on here?
So Kirishima only kept staring at Himeji because...
She wanted to make sure Himeji wasn't doing anything funny with Yuuji.
Sorry about this, Himeji.
Our classroom sucks even more than before.
No, this is a fabulous room.
I love class F!
And...
All right, Aki. You're going to treat me to some crepes.
Hold on! I thought we were
gonna go on this weekend...
Weekends are weekends. Today is today.
That means that I have to treat you twice!
I won't have any money left to feed
myself until my parents send me more!
No.
He's going to watch a movie with me.
I don't remember agreeing to that...
That's because I just decided on it.
Hurry up, you're treating me to crepes!
What movie are we going to watch?
No!
My living expenses! My nutrition! Save me!
Wait, my hands are going to break!
I'm starting to wonder if he's really an idiot or not.
Question three:
What is the ratio of one's income spent on food known as?
I'm not gonna be able to afford
anything except salt and water this week.
The question didn't ask you what you're going to eat.
Next episode: Food Expenses and Dates and Stun Guns.
This will be on your test.