I'll... do it.
Leave Cal to me.
Are you planning to die?
That's not it.
I need you to work out a plan for our escape.
Our time is limited.
I don't want to waste our time on Cal.
So I'll take care of it.
I asked you this before, but...
Do you really have the determination to shoot her?
Well...
Please.
Give me some time to think about it.
All right.
But make your decision by today.
If you can't decide...
...then I'll take care of Drei myself.
I'll...
...save Mio, too.
I can't let Elen shoot Cal.
I have to settle it myself.
No one else.
Reiji.
I want to be with you.
What is it?
Want to eat lunch with us?
You're basically handcuffed to Mio.
You don't really get a chance to eat lunch with us.
We're going to have a lonely table today,
since both Mio and Elen are absent.
Elen is absent?!
We both got to school this morning!
She left early.
She said she wasn't feeling well since this morning.
You didn't notice it at all?
Hey-
Wait!
Tell me how far along you've gotten with Mio!
Elen!
The person you are trying to reach is currently not available. Please hang up and try-
Found you!
Quit running and tell us!
How far along have you gotten with-
Hold on!
I'm a bit-
What's the rush?
Are you that worried about Elen?
You've got quite a sister complex-
Hey, you two!
5th period is about to start!
Aw, geez...
Let's go back.
Hey!
"Keep your phone off during class."
It's called common sense.
All right, let's get back to class.
This is the voicemail system.
You have one new message.
You might be angry by the time you hear this message.
But...
I think this is the best choice.
You shouldn't fight Cal.
I'm the one who dragged Mio into this.
I'll save her, even if it costs me my life.
So...
I want you to go ahead and escape without me.
I'll catch up with you after I rescue Mio.
If...
If by any chance, I don't make it by the appointed time...
Think of me as dead.
Message received today, at 2:15 pm.
Don't do it...
Don't do it, Elen!
I don't want to lose anyone again.
I can't stand to see anyone get hurt again!
No one!
So that's Ein...
Our prototype.
We must contact Master.
You've got some determination.
I was expecting you to wail and put up a fight.
I'm not an animal.
You were completely fooled by that guy, which is why you're here right now.
I wouldn't be surprised if you looked bitter about it.
Are you bitter yourself?
That you were-
Talking shit now, are we?
I still can't believe it.
That someone could carry this much hatred...
You're not the only one who had to endure sadness.
I'm sure Reiji also-
What do you know?
I can tell.
There's no way I wouldn't be able to tell.
Because I truly love him with all my heart.
You're such a liar!
That's right.
You, Reiji...
You're all liars.
Is that the same for everyone from this country?
Have you ever shivered from the cold?
Have you ever gotten the crap beaten out of you?
Have you ever survived without eating for three days?!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Do you really think that nothing in this world can hurt you?
You've been treated like a princess your entire life!
Do you think everyone lives like that?!
In a foolish country like this...
What would a pampered bitch like you understand?
You don't understand a thing.
You don't know the pain of others...
No!
Please, stop!
I only had one outfit to wear.
And that one burned to a crisp, too.
What did you eat growing up to get such smooth skin?
Huh?!
I'm asking you, Princess.
I'll tell you...
...the meaning of true despair.
The feeling of being powerless and unable to fight back...
I'll engrave it into your body.
A deep scar on your heart that will be with you for the rest of your life!
I waited here for you... for such a long time...
Because you promised me you'd come back, no matter what...
I waited...
...for such a long time...
For a long time...
Reiji...
Is that you, Shiga?
Pardon me, Boss.
It seems like you have bad news.
It's about Fujieda Mio.
Because of my inattentiveness, your daughter has been dragged into a bit of trouble.
Even now, we haven't got a minute to lose.
I understand that I'm to take full responsibility for the matter.
But before that, I believe rescuing Mio is of higher priority.
I'm requesting that we dispatch the Godoh Group's retainers to settle the conflict-
Is it those Americans who are behind this?
Is Mio still alive?
Yes. We are sure of that.
In that case, it's best not to meddle.
Don't use the Godoh Group.
Let those foreigners take care of everything.
But...
If the Group gets involved, the entire nation will know about it.
"Why is the Godoh Group getting so worked up over one girl?"
That's what everyone will think.
And I don't intend to make you take full responsibility for it either.
But then!
I'm saying that there's no need, Shiga!
There's no connection between the Godoh and the Fujieda. There mustn't be one!
Even now... and even in the past...
Do I make myself clear?
As long as Mio's life isn't in danger, do not take action.
As long as they're not after money or trying to blackmail us, there's nothing we can do.
But I do appreciate you looking out for her.
Shiga, in the end, Yakuza are just useless good-for-nothings.
Especially when it comes to protecting something.
Swords and guns are only good for destroying and killing.
They can't protect anything.
Understood, sir.
I will keep that in mind.
I've been acting as myself, within the repertoire that I created.
That repertoire, that play... has changed its colors, and is nearing its end.
The creation of the ultimate soldiers.
The first creation was Ein.
And the experimental creations were Zwei and Drei.
By using the results of those experiments, the performers best suited for the final act have been created...
Zahlenschwestern.
Note: "Zahlenschwestern" means "number sisters" in German
They have no fear. They know no mercy.
Automatons who carry death like faithful hounds.
Both the Godoh Group and Inferno are nothing but stage props.
When Ein and Zwei, who have been driven into a tight corner by Drei, bare their fangs like the beasts they are...
The dream contest between my works of art will commence.
I want you Zahlenschwestern to participate in that contest.
Let's wait for a bit.
Until we hear the closing chimes.
Is that you, Ein?
Drei, right?
Tell me what you want.
Pick a place where we won't have any interferences.
I'll put an end to everything.
Yeah, that's right.
Without him.
Just the two of us.
My... phone...?
Don't tell me she's talking to Reiji...
Okay. That place sounds good.
Three in the morning, right?
Do you know about the ruins that are above Shinokura Academy?
The place that used to be the girl's dormitory, right?
Yeah, that place.
That's where Mio is.
You'd better prepare something for her to wear.
Looks like you're awake.
Just forget this ever happened.
It's not worth it to hate me.
Even if you choose to, there are tons of people who hate me, and would refuse to forgive me.
I doubt I'll live for long, and when my time comes, I'll go to hell for sure.
See ya.
Mio?
Where were you? I was worried sick-
I'm Mio's classmate.
She was absent from school today, so I brought her assignments.
Mio wasn't at school?
Please give this to her.
Okay.
Well, if you'll excuse me.
Take care.
Umm... are you...
No, it's nothing.
Sorry about that.
Good night.
Don't tell me she...
Elen!
My name is Ein.
I have no reason to lie to you anymore.
So... just call me Ein.
Lie? What are you...
I brought you a change of clothes.
Why?
Who told you to...?!
Drei did.
Drei?
Are you talking about... Cal?
She used to be called that, too.
What exactly are you guys...?
You heard from Drei, right?
Is that true?
Are you and Reiji really...?
Yes.
We're assassins.
No way...
There's no way that could be...
Sorry, but could you go home on your own?
You can call the police with this.
Bye.
Cal left.
She mentioned something about "putting an end to everything".
I think she's going to kill Reiji...
I know.
You do?
Then... that phone call from earlier...
You're going to fight her?
Isn't there... Isn't there something I can do?
I love Reiji!
I would do anything for him!
Is that not enough?
Can I not stay by his side?!
Your feelings for him may very well be real.
But those feelings alone are not enough to defeat Drei.
If I don't kill her, she'll kill Reiji.
The one who shall prevent that isn't you... but me.
If you really want to help Reiji, stay here for a little longer.
If you do that, the likelihood of Reiji surviving will increase.
Reiji...
Did Reiji...
No, you've got it wrong.
I'm the one who involved you in all this.
Reiji isn't someone who can put on a crying or laughing facade.
If you happened to have seen his smile or his tears before,
they were real.
Ever since you called me Elen,
I've existed for the sole purpose of protecting you.
I want you to live...
I want you to continue living...
If you survive... that's proof that I lived, too.
We are...
...ghosts that cannot exist anywhere.
We are phantoms with no identity.
Hey, even if it's in my dreams...
...can't I at least have a miraculous redemption?