SELF-STUDY
You really want to help her?
Why not? Isn't it weird?
Why are they even treating her like that?
Bullying often happens for petty reasons.
A bad attitude or a bad glare is all it takes.
But she looked to me...
she must've been asking for help.
That's just because we just happened to be there.
I'm warning you, I won't be siding with you on this.
You'll just shift their target from her to you.
Then what's she supposed to do?
Who knows.
Maybe she gets over it,
or maybe she changes schools..
Or maybe a teacher notices and intervenes.
And we let her be until then?
You really are stubborn.
You know, I'm starting to get
really tired of your attitude, so-
I'm just as scared too!
I get you, Hina.
I mean, isn't it weird?
To label people as right or wrong? It's just weird...
I can't just stand by silently.
A dream...?
Was it today I had to go to the agency...?
Dammit... I overslept.
13: ROCK NEVER ENDS
I won't mince words.
We did not meet the expected results.
Well, duh.
The video barely got any views,
which means no subscribers either.
How bad would you say it is, Miura-san?
The biggest issue of all...
is that you should be more
recognizable than you've ever been.
All the search engine trends point to that.
Which means that should be translating into views.
But we didn't get any views.
Which must be our fault.
We failed to advertise you properly.
I am so sorry.
O-oh no, that's not what I meant-
In an era when anyone can do it on their own,
agencies cannot afford to grow complacent.
If an artist sees no value in an agency,
they'll just leave it. Am I wrong?
True enough.
Please give us a little more time.
We'll find a way to counter this loss.
- I've never seen her like that before...
- Yeah, that caught me off guard.
Huh? Where's Momoka-san?
"Sorry. Gotta dip", she said.
She went home?
But we said we were gonna practice.
- It's fine, let's call it a day.
- We probably should.
- Momoka-san probably realized.
- Of course she did!
- What?
- Of course you didn't realize.
- Realize what?
- Remember what she said?
We are getting popular, but
our song isn't. Meaning...
There's an issue with the song.
Miura-san must've realized that's
what Momoka-san was gonna say,
so she spared her from saying it.
But why?!
To not hurt her feelings.
Wait, you've got it wrong! We'll turn it around!
That song was amazing!
Everyone praised it so much!
Like Miura-san or Nakata-san!
If compliments were enough
to sell, life would be a lot easier.
But...!!
They say Van Gogh couldn't sell
but a painting in his lifetime.
But...
Basically, people get influenced by view counts.
They'll even watch hollow garbage
as long as others say it's good.
No one wants to watch stuff
no one else cares about.
That's...
"not true"?
When looking up gameplay for a game,
which video would you click on, the one
with 5000 views, or the one with a million?
Stop that. It's pathetic.
I know...
THE NEXT DAY
"This band keeps picking fights they can't win."
"Fucking showoffs, they piss me off."
"Go kill yourself, loser."
LEAVE ME ALONE!!
Fuck off! I refuse to lose to assholes like you
who are such insensitive deadbeats you didn't
even bother to show up to begin with!!
Breathe... breathe... breathe... breathe...
Our concert's coming up...
And DD has already sold all of their tickets...
Of course they have...
A follow request?
Hina?
It's verified...
Yo.
Made you look, idiot.
It's been a while.
Is it really okay for you to go out like that?
I'm not that famous, you know.
Your taste hasn't changed.
Yep. We used to eat these all the
time when we came back from school.
I'll pay.
It's fine, let me treat you.
- What do you want?
- Nothing, really.
Just thought we'd clear up any misunderstandings.
Like what?
Look, I didn't become DD's
vocalist to spite you or anything.
I mentioned I went to several auditions, right?
Wait nevermind, that was after you dropped out.
Couldn't have told you, then.
So what, you came here to brag?
That I wouldn't be here had I listened to you?
That things wouldn't have turned
this way if only I'd listened.
Spot on.
Though I'm lying. That's only half true.
- Have you sold any tickets?
- Not your problem.
I do think it is my problem though.
We're doing a concert together.
WE'RE NOT TOGETHER!
Miura-san from your agency came to visit us.
She asked for help.
She did?!
She was asking if we could play on both days,
so that they could sell enough tickets to make it a success.
At the rate you're going, you're
barely selling like a third of the tickets.
We're available on that date, so in
the end the choice comes down to us.
So I at least wanted to know what
you and your bandmates thought.
So?
Nothing.
By "nothing" you mean "stay out of my way"?
Or you mean it as a sign of thanks?
Hear that?
This is what it means to sell.
It's all that matters.
Something to cherish.
Just give it up and admit it.
"I was wrong. You were right, Hina."
"I wish I had listened to you."
"Expose yourself and live"... right?
If you tell me you were wrong,
I'll come to your rescue anytime.
I'm going home.
And I'm paying.
Thanks for the meal!
- HELLO?
- Sorry to call you so suddenly...
Don't worry.
Is something wrong?
Not really, everyone else has already been informed but,
DD offered to play on both days
so we get to compete against the same audience.
Miura-san told you so, right?
- She did, but where did you hear that?
- Doesn't matter...
What do you think, Nina?
What does everyone think?
Well...
We were never gonna stand a chance with
how it was originally laid out, so isn't this good?
But if we do it this way, it won't be a competition anymore,
this is just going to be a DD concert in disguise.
Wouldn't that be the same as admitting defeat?
So are you against it?
I am.
Here we go again.
Look, I get you Nina, but...
I'm against it! Completely against it!!
What do you think it is
that brought us this far?
The fact we weren't wrong!
To prove that Momoka-san's songs are powerful!
We made it this far because we believed in that!
But reality won't be so easily forgiving.
At the moment, we haven't
even sold a third of the tickets.
Even worse than our indie debut.
So what are you trying to say?!
Are you willing to take responsibility?
How do you expect to pay for it otherwise?
- Pay...?
- And I'm not talking about just the venue.
There's the advertising, the merch...
none of it comes for free.
We have to avoid any losses in any way we can.
I'm to blame here.
I'm sorry.
Are you planning to grovel like that to DD as well?
It's not like we're groveling to DD!
Exactly! They're just lending us a hand!
Same thing!
You really think DD is giving us a hand for free?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious?
Miura-san had to grovel and beg them for help.
She begged them to help us out.
Really...?
What do you know that we don't?
Hina told me.
She said that if I recognized I was wrong,
she would help us out anytime.
But I refuse to accept that!
After all...
I know I'm not wrong!
Nina...
So don't grovel your head down like that!
Don't blame me for who I used to be!
Expenses... Responsibility... Popularity...
I get it already! I know!!
It's so, so, so, so frustrating!!
LEAVE ME ALONEEEE!!
- Nina?
- Nina-san!
You okay?
Why am I so weak and spineless...
It was them, right?
I told you, didn't I?
That I wouldn't side with you on this.
Do you hate me that much for doing it?
You know... everytime we talk
I always get this uncomfortable feeling.
You brandish your sense of justice, but the thorns
of your insensitivity only end up hurting others.
You keep making me feel like I'm the bad guy...
- And so that's when you broke up contact with her?
- Yeah.
Well, that's the kinda flashback
I expected out of Nina.
And what happened to the girl that got bullied?
Weird as it may seem,
after a short while, she joined
everyone else in bullying me too.
She then told me in secret
that I should just apologize to them,
And then they'll surely forgive me.
And I wouldn't need to keep suffering like that.
This is just wrong...
But I could tell she was shaking.
She was still afraid of them.
But you saved her, right? You're her savior!
...And that's why you dropped out of school.
Yeah.
Because you weren't wrong... right?
But you were wrong! No matter
how you look at it, you were wrong!
Tomo-chan...
I mean, come on! Look at how it
ended up. That Hina girl was right!
But...!!
But...
...That's what I love about you.
I love your singing.
I'm sure Rupa, Momoka, and Subaru feel the same...
Tomo-chan!
- Hey, sto-!
- It's fine, come on!
I didn't mean I love you like that...
This is our answer, then.
Still, Miura-san and everyone else worked hard for this.
So you better take responsibility!
Are you kidding me?
Ah, who am I kidding, I knew it was
inevitable things would end up this way.
Always does with her.
Because that's who Nina is!
Rude!
- You're rejecting the offer?
- Yes. We apologize.
But they said that they wanted
to have a proper duel against you.
We understand.
But it makes it look as if they're trying to rescue us.
Even so, we have to account for the customers...
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
We all agreed together.
Of course, we understand this may be a selfish choice.
And that it may cause damages to the agency.
Please tell us the damages this would cost.
I cannot promise when, but I promise
we'll pay it all back someday.
Please.
Please raise your heads.
Will you tell me your reason?
I heard everything
Hina of DD contacted me and told me.
I'm thankful for your help, Miura-san.
You went this far to make sure our concert wouldn't fail.
And even now I realize how rude it is to reject this offer.
But I'm sorry. For being selfish.
You know, I had imagined that
this would go against your principles.
- Miura-san...
- I guess I'm a failure too.
Do not misunderstand.
The money and contract is our responsibility.
The reason I approached you to
begin with is because of who you are.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Allow me to assist you with this at least.
You're quitting?
Yes.
- You switching agencies?
- No, we were thinking of going freelance.
You don't like working here?
Not at all.
We just want to do this on our own.
That's all.
- Is he mad?
- Should've chosen her words better.
- That's quite the naive outlook...
Contact me again in a decade
if you're still kicking around.
I'll work for you as a freebie.
We will! Thank you so much, Nakata-san!
Up for some good old gyudon?
You just want to drink.
Of course she isn't!
You're not fooling anyone.
Now that I think about it,
this is where we first met you two.
Oh yeah.
Beni-Shoga, was it?
Want to make an oath by eating some beni shoga?
After all beni shoga holds a
lot of value to you as a name,
So it'd be a nice way to make an oath.
What kind of oath?
That we're gonna keep at it with
the five of us, and no one's quitting!
- Nothing left but to eat, then.
- I like the sound of that.
Just one drink, okay?
Momoka-san!
I love this city!
It's a place where I've met friends
who let me laugh and cry as I please.
I love it.
You mean Kawasaki, right?
Yeah!
We're basically forfeiting, huh.
Like those baseball teams that keep losing the Japan Series.
Hoping for a miracle?
Yeah, as if. Life's not like a melodrama.
Oh, so you like melodramas?
A-all I watch is "Detective Grandma on the Case"!
You trynna pick a fight?
Still, we knew this was gonna happen.
We knew reality would be harsh.
That this wouldn't be easy.
That's rich coming from you!
You're the last one who thought this was gonna happen.
Of course...
Still, it means we get to
say we weren't wrong.
Momoka-san...
By the way, after DD's concert yesterday,
we received a bunch of comments.
But you told me to not look at the comments!
Don't sweat the details.
For example...
"Woah, I love this".
"Why's everyone hating so much on this?"
"All the haters should shut up.
It's not about the numbers."
"Give them some time, need to see where they go."
Though it'd be better if they stayed silent,
it goes to show there's still folks like that.
They can tell we're serious then, Momoka-san!
You're right.
Still, I didn't realize you had gotten
that good at playing the guitar!
To think you've made it this far!
Is it really okay for me to play it though?
You spent so much time training by the park.
So why not?
Thank you, everyone!
It's almost time.
Yes!
Look up, Nina! - Hina
Look up...?
Look to your left - Hina
My left?
TOGENASHI TOGEARI
Made you look, idiot <3
- That little...
- Seems like a fun person.
Maybe Hina doesn't want to fully break ties with you.
What do you mean?
She went so far to make you apologize,
she must be teasing you at this point!
You're like her final boss!
The Great Demon King of
Annoying Self-Righteous Dummies.
But beating you would mean clearing
the game, and she doesn't want it to end.
Is that meant to make me happy?
It's a compliment!
If I say it, it means I wasn't wrong, right?
Everyone... it's time.
Ehm... As you might all already know,
We're supposed to be facing
off against Diamond Dust, but...
The results are already obvi...
I mean, thank you for coming today!
Ouch!!
The truth is, we've been pretty self-conscious about it.
About wanting to win against Diamond Dust.
About not wanting to lose.
Back during the festival,
we were just as serious too.
This is a bit sudden, but let me talk about myself.
Is that okay, Rupa-san?
When I was in high school, I tried
to save a girl from getting bullied.
The moment I made
that choice, I felt... happy.
I felt at peace... for once, I loved myself.
As a result of it, I became
the one getting bullied,
And in the end I had to drop out of school.
But never once did I ever think...
That I regretted doing that,
or that I should've avoided it.
And that's when I realized...
I have no regrets!
Because Momoka-san's song
was there, it gave me strength,
and Hina knew that very well-
Oh, right.
Hina also loved DD. She loved their music.
It wasn't just my song alone. It
reached and touched so many people.
Allow me to thank you
once again for coming here today!
You came here today because
you're willing to go against the grain.
But let me tell you... I love people like that!
So I'm gonna scream out
that we're not gonna lose!
That we weren't wrong!
Bear witness! This is where it all begins!
We are all the same, trying our best to live our lives.
We have no place to belong,
So we fly!
Our fates intertwined, reverberating, cutting off all paths.
I dedicate the rest of my life to singing with you.
No light, no air, like an isolated prison.
The pain, the suffering, and all the scars, I hated it all.
Even if my wings were full of holes,
Even if I were in the depths of hell,
if I could I'd still sing with you.
I flew away, wanting to disappear.
But now I don't want to disappear!
I picked the flower and kept it,
waiting for it to one day bloom.
The version of me who wanted to disappear is no more.
Now I'm glad to be alive!
Because I met you, it finally bloomed,
our flower of fate!
FLIP'EM OFF!
Three, two, one...
THANK YOU!!