nemurenai yoru ni wa
On nights when I can't sleep
hitori de tameiki
I heave a sigh to myself
minna wa dou nano
What about all of you?
nandaka samishii
I feel kind of lonely
hiroi daichi ni hitotsubu no tane
A single seed in a vast landscape
nekko nobashite
sprouted its roots
mada aoi mi wo tsuketa
It bore a fruit that was still unripe
ORANGE iro ni hayaku naritai kajitsu
The fruit that wants to turn orange as soon as possible
kimi no hikari wo abite
by basking in your light
risou ya yume wa fukuramu bakari
My ideals and dreams keep on flourishing
kizuiteyo nee
Come on, notice it already
ORANGE kyou mo tabetemitakedo
Today, I ate an orange
mada suppakute naita
but I cried because it was still sour
watashimitai de nokosenai kara
It reminded me of myself, and I couldn't throw away the rest
zenbu tabeta
so I ate it all
suki da yo
I love you
nakeru yo
It makes me cry
suki da yo
I love you