Over a century ago, mankind had to face a new enemy.
The difference of power between mankind and their newfound foe was overwhelming.
Soon, mankind was driven to the brink of extinction.
The surviving humans built three walls: the Maria, the Rose, and the Sina.
Under their protection, they lived out the next century in peace.
However...
Are you the prey? No, we are the hunters!
Seid ihr das Essen? Nein, wir sind der Jäger!
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
No one remembers the names of trampled flowers
Fumareta Hana no Namae mo Shirazuni
Fallen birds await the next breeze to lift them up again
Chi ni Ochita Tori wa Kaze wo Machiwabiru
Prayers won't be enough to save us
Inotta Tokoro de Nani mo Kawaranai
Only the will to fight can change our world
Ima wo Kaeruno wa Tatakau Kakugo da
Ignore the swine who mock you
Shikabane Fumikoete
for climbing over corpses to move forward
Susumu Ishi wo Warau Butayo
Our complacence as livestock just strengthens our delusion
Kachiku no Annei Kyoi no Han'ei
We're as free as starving wolves!
Shiseru Garou no Jiyuu wo
Channel the humiliation of imprisonment into the arrows of resistance
Torawareta Kutsujoku wa Hangeki no Koushi da
Far beyond these confining Walls, you will slay your prey!
Jouheki no Sono Kanata Emono wo Houru
As your body burns with an overflowing urge,
Hotobashiru Shoudou ni Sono Mi wo Yakinagara
pick up your crimson bow and pierce the twilight!
Tasogare ni Hi wo Ukatsu Guren no Yumiya
We are the hunters!
Wir sind die Jäger!
Where is the Left Arm?
Defense of Trost (pt 5)
One of the reasons why the Titans' attack on Trost claimed so many soldiers' lives
was that the elite Recon Corps weren't present.
They'd left on a mission outside the Wall that very morning.
A Few Hours Ago
They're here!
It's the main force of the Recon Corps!
Commander Erwin!
Kick their Titan asses for me!
Look!
There's Captain Levi!
They say in battle, he's as strong as a whole brigade!
Shut up already...
I bet they wouldn't worship you so much if they knew what an obsessive clean freak you are!
The Titans are out there!
I wonder what kind of Titans I'll see this time!
I'd really love to see some abnormal ones!
I can see an abnormal already.
Huh? Where?
Right here.
Move out!
An extramural skirmish to secure a foothold for advancement.
The Recon Corps entrusted with this mission
were mankind's best and brightest soldiers.
The ingenuity of these few raised the survival rates for all.
Even so, when troops advanced into Titan territory, casualties still exceeded 30%.
That's just how great the power gap between Titans and men was.
Just... Just watch... You bastards...
Mankind will... destroy you all...
Mankind will... survive...
You bastards... will all...
Fall to Captain Levi!
One on the right... Two on the left.
Captain, I've gathered the reinforcements!
Petra, look after that soldier down there.
The rest of you attack the one to the right.
I'll clean up on the left.
Captain!
Don't worry!
I'm not gonna hurt you!
Not quite!
It's my turn!
Gotcha!
See? It didn't hurt, did it?
What a lovely bunch.
You all have such interesting faces.
Stay still.
Otherwise, I'll never get a clean cut of your flesh.
It got all filthy...
Captain, I can't stop the bleeding!
Captain...
What?
Was I... useful to... mankind?
Or will I die... useless like this?
You did great.
And you'll do even more.
Your spirit will stay with me and give me strength!
I swear to you, I will exterminate the Titans!
Captain, he's gone...
Did he hear everything?
I'm sure he heard it all.
He's resting so peacefully now.
Good, then...
Levi!
We're going back!
Back?
We haven't reached our limit yet.
Did my men die in vain?
The Titans have all started heading north towards the city.
It's just like five years ago.
Something's happened in the city.
They might've even broken through the Wall.
Dammit...
Dammit!
No... This can't be...
We've changed in five years...
We trained to become soldiers...
We thought we were soldiers...
So that we could defeat them...
So that they couldn't prey on us...
It's hot...
It's so hot...
Help me.
Mom...
Mom!
Help...
Why must this happen?
Why do they prey on us?
They take our lives... our dreams...
Why?!
Dammit! God dammit!
I can't give up just yet!
I'll annihilate you!
Every single one of you!
I'll destroy you with my own hands!
I'll exterminate you all!
I'll purge this world...
of every last one of you!
More! More!
I'll kill more of you!
I wanna kill more!
Kill 'em all!
I'll kill you...
Eren?
Eren!
Eren, can you move?
Are you yourself again?
Tell them everything you know!
I'm sure they'll understand!
Armin?
Did you hear that? He said "I'll kill you!"
Yeah, I heard it too.
He wants to devour us all!
What're you saying?
Why're they raising their swords against us?
Those are weapons for killing Titans!
Why are they glowering at me like that?
What's going on?
Currently Disclosable Information
The current Recon Corps (pt 1)
The chief purpose of the Recon Corps
was to survey the land outside the Wall,
but their actual duties have changed significantly
since the fall of Wall Maria.
Currently Disclosable Information
The current Recon Corps (pt 2)
Since the fall, their main objective has become
establishing footholds and supply lines for troop movements,
in preparation for the second attempt to retake Wall Maria.
Inside Wall Rose
All cadets are to ready their equipment and stand by!
So that's how we managed to refill our gas and get out of Trost.
I'm so sorry...
We asked to send reinforcements for you...
We even managed to secure some gas.
Wait, then the people who aren't here are all...
Yeah.
Even Mikasa?
No... I thought Mikasa came back late with Jean and the others...
Jean! Don't tell me Mikasa was wounded?
Hey, what's wrong?
We were sworn to keep it secret.
Secret?
What the hell?
It's hardly something they can keep covered up though.
Soon all of mankind will know about it.
If mankind survives long enough, that is.
They built a wall of flesh out of Titans.
The technical crew is pretty damn clever.
Still, we can't afford to let our guard down.
This is the front line between mankind and Titans.
We're on the edge of a cliff.
What's wrong?
Nothing... Our mission is going smoothly.
I'm just worried about my comrades in the vanguard.
A messenger just rushed into HQ looking as pale as death.
Yeah, but we need to stay focused on interception, just as we trained.
I heard those three kids you rescued five years ago are cadets now.
They're in the vanguard too.
Yeah...
I'm sorry, sir. I'm talking too much.
They're fine.
They're strong. They each have a means of survival.
One is a skilled fighter.
One has a tenacious spirit.
And one is smart as a whip.
They're fine. I know they're alive.
Cadets Jaeger, Ackerman, and Arlert!
Your present behavior is high treason!
What do you have to say in your defense?
If you try anything deceitful or attempt to make a move,
the artillery will open fire on you immediately!
We won't hesitate!
I ask of you:
What are you?
A human or a Titan?
What's with that question?
It's like they're all...
Staring at a monster.
Is that what they think I am?
I... I don't understand the question!
You're feigning ignorance? Damn monster!
Try playing dumb with me again!
We'll blow you to bits in an instant!
We won't give you time to show your true face!
My true face?!
Everybody saw it!
You emerged from the carcass of a Titan!
Mankind has allowed creatureslike you to infiltrate Wall Rose!
Even though you're cadets sworn to the King himself,
it's appropriate to pre-emptively eliminate this risk!
I'm not wrong!
The Armored Titan that broke through
Wall Maria could appear at any moment!
Mankind is once again on the brink of extinction!
Do you get it?
We can't afford to waste our troops and time on you!
I'll blow you to pieces with the artillery!
They are clearly defiant.
I doubt we'll be able to obtain any useful intelligence from them.
As you say, this is a waste of troops and time.
Commander, it'll be easy right now!
We can blow him away while he's in human form!
My specialty is slicing up flesh.
If need be, I'm prepared to display it.
Anyone interested in experiencing my skills firsthand, step right up.
Commander, that's Mikasa Ackerman.
She was with our elite unit in the rearguard.
She's worth a hundred average soldiers.
Losing her would be a huge blow to mankind.
Mikasa! Armin!
What's going on?
Mikasa! You can't fight our own people!
Where could we run within these crowded walls?
I don't care who my opponent is.
I'm not letting anyone kill Eren.
I couldn't care less about anything else.
We need to talk with them!
No one knows what's going on!
Their fears are just running rampant!
So I'm the only one who doesn't think I'm a Titan?
Dammit! I've got no memory at all of how I got here!
I'm so worn out I can't stand.
They'll kill me if I say one thing wrong.
Getting killed by humans...
That's just absurd!
What's this all about?
I emerged from a Titan's body?
What's he saying? What does that even mean?
Wasn't that just a dream?
If not, that means everything below the sleeve on my arm grew back!
That's just like a Titan!
It's not possible.
How'd I... How...
I'll ask you once again! What are you?
I can't say anything wrong.
It's not just my life at stake.
That's right.
All along, I've been just like you...
I'm human!
I see.
Don't think badly of me.
We've got no choice.
No man can prove...
He's not a devil.
Eren! Armin!
We're going up!
Wait!
Eren.
When I return, I'll show you the basement I've kept secret.
Always keep this key with you. Never let go of it.
And when you look at it, remember!
You must go to the basement!
Because of these injections, your memories will be damaged.
So it's pointless for me to explain things now.
Just remember this!
Retake Wall Maria and reach that basement!
This power will prove useful then!
Their memories will show you how to use it!
Eren!
Once you enter the basement, you'll find the truth!
It will be a hard and merciless road,
but you must walk it!
If you want to save Mikasa, Armin, and everyone else,
you've got to take control of this power!
Did we get them?
No way...
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
Your dream is where your heart seeks comfort
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
It's even more fragile than your life
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
You can abandon it, and yet always find it again
yasuraka ni saa nemure
Now, rest in peace
myakuutsu shoudou ni
My pulsing rage
negai wa okasare
defiles the wishes I harbor
wasureteshimau hodo
before I forget them
mata omoidasu yo
only to remember once more
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
In this beautiful yet cruel world
mada ikiteiru koto
we keep on asking ourselves,
naze to tou bakari de
"Why were we the ones who survived?"
ah bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
What will we protect
nani wo mamoru no darou
with our strength and our weakness
mou risei nado nai naraba
if reason and logic no longer hold true?
Eren isn't an enemy of mankind.
Armin risks himself to argue so.
But the Garrison loses their reason to fear,
and declares a penalty of death on Eren.
Answer
Defense of Trost (pt 6)