Run! Hurry up!
Tooru-chan is waiting for you!
Coming...
You haven't forgotten anything, right?
Of course not.
Be careful!
I know. Bye now.
Thanks for waiting.
Morning, Run-chan.
Slowly, quietly, floating by
Gently fading into the distant bright sky
More fickle than the wind,
my goal is beyond it
Let's go together
Take a breath and skip along,
the world's spring breath
The sun brings all our smiles together
Between "good morning" and "good bye" it's just us
We can do whatever we want
The sunlight shining down,
a brand new sky
The morning arch we promised to meet at
Waving your hand at me,
let me make today a special day
Let's start by talking
Rainy Days are for Baths
Oh? Really?
Wait, I sent you a text about it after dinner.
What? Really? I didn't see it.
Run-chan.
Your sock.
I forgot to put one of them on!
This is so embarrassing...
I'd rather go without any on than this...
Ru-Ru-Ru-Ru-Run-chan...
Yo-Yo-Yo-Yo-Yo-Your...
panties...
Of all the things—how could I not notice?! How could I not notice?!
Don't squat! You can see from the front!
I was sleepy...
But was that the only reason?
Don't worry.
Is this kind of thing normal?
Everyone forgets things.
Tell me, me!
But not usually their panties.
Tooru... you...
You just thought "But not usually their panties," didn't you?!
Run-chan!
Don't ru—
Again?
You've sure got it rough.
Sorry, Tooru.
You know, I just can't handle mornings.
I'm always so sleepy, I completely space out.
Is that really the problem?
She's wearing them now.
Oh—right, of course.
It's just that I thought maybe...
Oh, right, Run.
What is it?
Can I copy your notes from yesterday afternoon?
Yeah. You left early yesterday, didn't you?
Go ahead.
Here you go.
Thanks!
You're a lifesaver.
What language is this?
Oh, come on. It's Japanese.
I started falling asleep during class.
Then it's not just mornings!
I guess it's kind of messy.
Not at all...
Thanks.
If there's anything you can't read, just ask.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey, Yuuko-chan, can I copy it after you?
Sure. After you're done, give it to Run.
Okay.
Alright.
Hey,
Nagi, are you nearsighted? What's your prescription?
2.0.
I don't really need these.
Really? Then why do you always wear them?
When I'm not wearing them...
I see things...
that I don't need to see.
Don't tell me, you...
Oh. Right behind you...
Just kidding.
No!
I said it was a joke.
Wow, you're fun to scare.
I'm just a bit nearsighted.
Seriously, don't do that! I can't stand scary stuff!
You scared me for a second there, too! Nagi-chan, you put on a good act!
You should join the drama club!
I'm already in it.
I'm a ghost member.
Oh! Good one!
Was not!
I received two or three letters from you this summer.
If I remember rightly, it was in your second letter that you asked me to help you find a suitable post.
I need to go to the bathroom...
Excuse me, Sensei...
What is it?
Oh, um...
Shoot. I can't say I need to go to the bathroom. It's too embarrassing!
I have a headache...
Yuuko, that's your stomach.
I mean...
Excuse me, Sensei!
I need to go to the bathroom, so can I go after taking Yuuko-chan to the nurse's office?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Run...
Let's go, Yuuko-chan.
Sure.
Thanks, Run. You saved me.
Don't mention it. I need to go, too.
Oh, you need to go to the bathroom, too?
No...
The nurse's office...
Run!
Run! What's wrong? Are you sick?
I don't know. I feel sick...
I might have come down with someth—
I'm going to throw up...
Then, a toilet?
Wait, no, nurse's office.
No, toilet!
Toi—
To—
I know!
Tooru!
Yuuko-chan, that's not...
Nurse's Office
Run! Run!
Run! Wake up!
Yuuko?
Are you there?
Tooru!
Run suddenly fainted!
The nurse isn't here today, either!
What do we do?!
Calm down.
We could call in a teacher or something.
Be quiet, both of you.
It's okay.
She just didn't get enough sleep.
Let's keep quiet.
It's raining...
No umbrella.
Me neither.
The sun was shining this morning.
It's pretty light. It might be okay if we run.
Wait right there, Tooru. Watch this.
I just learned this recently.
I'm a rain goddess.
You don't need to get wet to show me!
Come back under here!
I'm all wet!
Be more careful...
Who is that?
He's looking this way.
Run-chan is completely soaked.
Run-chan.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
Yes...
I'm so glad I work at this school.
Turn permission
forms for camp
in to every
teacher or Yamada.
Too much
work...
I need to dry Run-chan off fast.
Alright! They're done!
Tooru, put this on.
Ta-da!
Now we don't need an umbrella!
It's kind of embarrassing to wear these at this age...
It was fine in elementary school, but...
Oh, you're right.
The pair look is kind of embarrassing.
Then maybe just one of us?
No, that's not what I meant.
What are they doing?
I'll take mine off, then. I'm already wet anyway.
What?
No, I can...
Let's get out of here.
Nagi-chan! Yuuko-chan!
Stay away from me!
Honestly! We were wondering what you were doing—
Run, you're completely soaked!
My place is close by. We can dry you off there.
Really? Thanks!
But the rain...
Oh, wow. Is there a rain goddess in our school or something?
How should we do this?
It's kind of rough, but we could just make a run for it.
If we're all wet, then there's nothing to fear!
Well, if it's just to Nagi's...
Too much of a hassle.
I don't want to get wet. I'll call a taxi.
That's not what high school students do!
Think it'll stop soon?
Don't think so.
I said I'd call a taxi.
Let's go!
Nagi-chan's place is this way!
Hey! Don't!
Wait! I'm coming too!
Come on! Stop!
Come on, come on!
Wait! Don't leave me behind!
The rain brings with it melancholy,
but they're having fun regardless.
Ah, youth!
The smile
you made
as you ran
through the rain
was just
so beautiful,
I
No matter
how hard the rain,
no matter
how thick the clouds,
no matter how sharp
I shall not
hide a sun
like you.
No—
even if I were to try,
I've got it!
Kitou-Sensei
I've got it, now!
Hobby:
Poetry
Reality
I'm back!
Thanks for letting us over.
Okay, head on in.
I want to take a bath now.
Oh? Aniki's back.
Nagi, you have a brother?
Onii-chan! I have friends over right now, so don't use the bathroom!
Nagi-chan...
Do you call your brother "Aniki" or "Onii-chan"?
I call him "Aniki"!
Now then.
Our bath only fits two people at once.
Let's make two pairs.
One, two, rock, paper.
Then I'll go in with Run first.
Have fun.
Let's change now, then.
There we go.
Oh, no.
Now that I think about it, I've never talked with Tooru alone before.
Oh, no. What should I do?
The silence in situations like this is... just too...
Yuuko.
Yes?!
Want to watch something?
There are a lot of DVDs here.
Let's do that.
Really Real Scary Urban Legends, or the silence.
Which do you prefer?
A death and death decision?!
Put your clothes over there.
Okay. Here?
Now then, let's get in.
Whoa! Who are you?!
Hm? It's Run...
Well, I knew that.
But wow, you look completely different with your bangs down.
Who are you?!
That reaction...
is getting old.
Man, it feels so good!
It's really refreshing.
Oh, but we should make it quick.
Right. Tooru and Yuuko-chan need their turn, too.
They're alone in my room right now, aren't they?
You think they'll be okay?
They'll be just fine! They get along really well!
Well... sure, but...
Too much! Too much!
This is way too much!
Oh, I know!
I won't feel scared if I close my eyes!
I want to scream!
Sorry we took so long.
The bath is fr—
Hey, Yuuko. The bath is free now.
Yuuko-chan.
Yuuko-chan?
Yuuko-chan!
Yuuko-chan?!
Oh, no! Yuuko-chan is—
What happened to her?
Wow, that was really scary.
Finally, a bath. Well, Tooru?
Yeah.
Come on, let's get in.
Hey, do you ever get scared from not being able to see in front of you while washing your hair?
When I was a kid, I was really scared of shampoo—
It got in my eyes—
What are you doing, Tooru?
Where's the shower?
My eyes!
Hey! Yuuko!
Keep it down!
Stop it! Please, stop!
I thought I was going to die in there.
Everything is all hazy...
Run, look...
There's an oasis...
Nagi! Run!
What are you two doing?
Yuuko.
H-How was the bath?
That doesn't matter!
At least turn off the heater.
We wanted to dry our clothes...
Yummy!
Man, I'm alive again!
You really had us worried there.
They've mostly dried off.
I hope the rain lets up soon.
It doesn't look like it will.
It just keeps coming down.
Rain makes your hair so hard to handle.
Mine gets all sticky and clumps together.
Mine curls up and I can't tie it right.
I guess we have different types...
Oh, Yuuko-chan, let me feel your hair!
Sure.
Wow! Your hair is so pretty!
Tooru!
You don't have any split ends!
How about it?
What? That's not true.
Hey, don't you think these clothes are cute?
Don't move!
This is a really important part.
Okay.
Alright!
Hey, what?
Don't move!
Darn! I lost!
Still playing?
Until I overwrite Nagi's records.
Wow, you're so nice.
Your fingers are really pretty.
N-Not really.
Do you do anything to them?
Nothing, really.
Alright.
Then...
It feels great, but...
it's kind of embarrassing.
To-Tooru?
Wait!
Don't move!
Then what am I supposed to do?!
After school, with nothing to do
It doesn't look like it'll stop.
Because it's raining
It just keeps coming down.
But I really like the sound of the rain.
Let's go to my place
What?
You don't usually say what you really think
Oh, I kind of get what you mean.
Right?
Come on, Nagi-chan. Try closing your eyes and listening.
But I'm sure I'll know today
What?
No...
I'm...
I just want to see you smile
You don't need to hide away there
Come on, come a little closer
You're a friend of mine
Every season that passes by, now and forever
Come on, stay close by me
I want to be with you
I want to smile with you
You're right. It isn't bad.
But it kind of sounds like something's sizzling.
I'm kind of getting hungry.
Run-chan.
Oh!
It was me.
Again?!
See you.
Be careful on your way back.
Okay!
Thanks for the umbrella.
See you tomorrow, then.
Thanks for letting us over.
See you.
Hey, isn't that umbrella kind of cute?
Yeah, it is.
Oh, the wind is pretty strong.
Do you remember when the next train is?
Onii-chan, you can use the bathroom now.
10 minutes later
I said, "Be careful."
Didn't I?
I'm really sorry...
Next to me in the sunset, a silhouette tall as me
It's the end of another fun day
I've still got so much unending stuff to talk about
But it's time for us to go home
Bye, see you tomorrow, I'll text you later
Today's page is about all our smiles
Bye, see you tomorrow, thanks as always
I'm happy we could be together today too
Humhumhum, the wind and my heart are humming
At the next corner, I'll turn around and say "Bye bye"
Next Episode
It's what you've all been waiting for!
Next time, Yutaka and Miporin will finally appear!
Thanks for waiting!
It's been a long, determined, 15-year wait.
Okay. That's all the flashbacks you get.
And didn't you get a scene in the first episode?
Well, if you count that, we're both in the opening.
Well, I guess so...
On the next A Channel: Classmates!
Oh, it won't just be us classmates. The upperclassmen will be there too.