What do you mean, urban legend?
The black bike!
The Headless Rider!
The man on the black bike
doesn't have a head!
Their head's cut clean off,
but they still move.
It doesn't seem like that hard a job.
Still, be careful.
I didn't hear you'd turned into
a defender of justice.
Wh-What the hell are you?
Wh-What are you?!
The Headless Rider?
I've heard of them!
A friend of mine saw them.
Can't say I care, honestly.
I took a photo of them!
See?
The Headless Rider?
He's right here.
Heard of 'em.
Might've seen 'em near Sunshine.
Yeah?
I dunno, but everyone's making a big deal.
So it's gotta be true, right?
Everyone's talking about them.
That bike showed up again.
<Kanra>
<Tanaka Tarou>
But do they really not
have a head?
<Setton>
It's just a creepy rumor.
<Kanra>
But I hear some pretty realistic rumors.
<Tanaka Tarou>
<Setton>
It's impossible for someone
to not have a head.
<Kanra>
Not if they're not human!
Those who've really gotten
close don't talk about it.
I'm sorry.
I don't know anything about it.
What about you?
What's your impression of the
legendary Headless Rider?
Scared?
Think they're cool?
Think they might, actually,
be a nice person?
No. I think I know.
You don't know what to think.
I'll tell you what I know about
the Headless Rider.
It's a bit of a long story,
but please keep an open mind.
Utterly
Alone
First, let me introduce myself.
I'm Kishitani Shinra, age 24.
I'm a doctor here in Ikebukuro.
I'm not exactly a licensed professional,
but I operate in the shadows.
I perform first-aid on people who've been hit
with stuff the cops would question,
and plastic surgery on people
who need new faces.
I may not look it, but I'm good at
my job and am well-regarded.
Now, on to the main point.
I'm back!
Yes.
The Headless Rider,
Celty Sturlson, is my roommate.
I'm back, Celty.
Welcome back.
It was an easy job, nothing special.
How were things for you?
No peeking.
Sorry! Sorry!
I didn't mean to. I just accidentally...
You seem upset.
Maybe you need some calcium.
You want me to eat
eggshells or something?
Might not be a bad idea.
But you know, nutritional
science isn't my thing,
so I couldn't tell you how much
calcium is in an eggshell
or how efficiently your
body could absorb it.
Of course, since I don't even know
where your brains are,
I don't know that it would have
any effect in the first place!
Shut up.
Hey, Celty, I know it isn't
the first time I've asked,
but how does the world look
to someone without eyes?
You can't tell someone something
you don't understand yourself.
She may not have a head,
but she can see and hear and smell.
But evidently, lacking a head doesn't
give you 360-degree vision.
She does have a field of vision wider
than that of normal humans.
This is just a theory of mine,
but that mysterious smoky stuff that's floating
out of your neck all the time...
You think you're maybe scattering it
over your surroundings,
and when it bounces back, you absorb it,
and get your information?
Of course, the information you'd get about
far-off objects would be less clear.
Don't care.
If I can see and hear, that's enough.
Celty, you're always like that.
I just wonder how much of the world that
you feel is the same as the world I feel.
It's not just about sight.
It's a question of values, too.
Not as a human, but as a lone faerie
who appeared in this city...
What the world is like,
viewed through a Dullahan's eyes.
What's wrong?
If you don't mind,
tell me what happened.
That job today, Orihara-kun
said it was easy.
The work itself was a piece of a cake.
And?
I do love me the transporters.
I can't get by without you.
And you can't get by without me.
I'd rather the latter weren't the case.
Don't be like that.
I'll be using your services again.
I want to stay on good terms with you.
For a long time...
Am I imagining things,
thinking you're a creepy guy?
You sure are.
By the way, ever heard of a Dullahan?
It's a headless faerie from Ireland.
A portrait painter in Yoyogi Park
said he saw one once.
He kept yelling,
"It had no head! It had no head!"
Think he was talking about a Dullahan?
Is he still there?
Don't know, really.
So she's intrigued, is she?
Celty Sturlson isn't human.
She's a type of faerie, out of Celtic folklore,
commonly known as a Dullahan.
Is there a portrait painter around here?
Oh, him? He's not here anymore.
Hey, didn't he say he was
going to Yokohama?
A Dullahan carries its severed
head at its side,
and travels in a two-wheeled carriage called
a Cóiste Bodhar, pulled by a headless horse.
They visit the homes of men whose time
on Earth is about to end.
If you carelessly open the door,
they'll throw a bucket full of blood on you.
It's a horrific, death-besotted legend,
and rather difficult to connect
to the woman herself.
Except for the part about
lacking a head.
Why she's come to Japan,
to Tokyo, to Ikebukuro...
And why she obsesses so
much over her head...
I'll tell you in a moment.
It was twenty years ago.
She suddenly woke atop a mountain,
missing her head.
She then realized that she was missing
a number of memories,
such as the reason for her actions and
her past, back up to a certain point.
However, she remembered that
she was a Dullahan,
and that her name was Celty Sturlson,
and how to use her abilities.
And the first thing that
surprised her was...
"I wasn't thinking of things
with my head,"
she said.
And then she realized she could sense
something she thought to be her head.
She considered the situation
and hypothesized
that her consciousness was shared
between her head and her body,
and the missing memories were
those inside her head.
And thus, she decided
to recover her head,
which alone knew the
reason for her existence.
It was possible her head had left
her body of its own volition.
But even so, she wouldn't
know until she had it.
It's not in Yokohama, either.
Next is Tama, then Chiba...
I keep missing it.
Should've just given up and
come back tomorrow.
I was frantic.
When I thought my head
might be there...
I wanted to get it back, no matter what,
as soon as possible.
I don't want to live with
these vague memories.
She followed the faint trails,
all the way here,
but it seemed the head
had gone overseas.
The ship was bound for
Japan, apparently.
Following it, by sneaking aboard
another ship, was easy enough,
but the problem was the horse.
It was the Dullahan's servant spirit,
made to possess a horse's corpse.
If necessary, it was possible to dismiss it,
but where it would go after that...
That memory was likely in her head.
So even though she knew how to dismiss it,
she couldn't bring herself to do it.
And then...
She... met it.
I never did find my head.
But...
Oh, I know that painter.
He's been in south Ikebukuro
Park for a few days.
Yeah, that's right.
Want me to go with you?
It's inconvenient like that, right?
OK, it's done.
Wow! Awesome!
It's cuter than you are.
Huh? Hey!
You're good, mister!
Not at all. I still can't really
draw the things I like.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Ready to go?
Come back any time.
OK!
Sorry. It's getting dark.
I'm done for today.
Did you really see a Dullahan?
Yeah. I did.
When I was young, I saw it in
the mountains of Ireland.
With my own two eyes.
What did you mean when
you said it lost its head?
Lost its head?
No, no. It has no head.
I can't decide on how the head should look.
Here...
It was a woman.
And a beautiful woman, at that.
On a foggy night,
on a mountain road, she passed me.
She passed by at an incredible speed.
She was a terrifying beauty.
She was not of this world. I could tell.
When I returned to the inn and
spoke of my experience,
they said it had been a Dullahan.
I was told it had lived there for ages.
Why doesn't your Dullahan have a head?
I can't draw it.
The more I draw it,
the more wrong it looks.
I remember what I saw,
but I just can't express her on paper.
What color was her hair?
Her eyes?
What kind of expression did she have?
If I could say it, I wouldn't have
thought to try and draw it.
Come to think of it,
a strange man recently came by.
He told me my drawing
was perfect as it was.
That she didn't need a head.
Weird guy.
Why is it so important to you?
It was the greatest experience of my life.
That one night was my whole life.
I want to get back my memories
of that moment.
Thanks, mister.
I see.
By the way, you don't remember
meeting him, right?
I don't.
That Dullahan may or may not be you.
Or perhaps he was simply mistaken.
It was me.
I know it.
Yeah?
Where was I going?
What was I thinking?
Why was I going there?
Is it that important?
You're unique, you're mysterious.
But your goal is still far, far away.
What are you getting at?
I'll be straight. Give it up.
That strange man may be right.
Maybe you don't need your head.
Why don't you forget about your head?
Let's go somewhere.
Anywhere...
If you want, I'll do whatever it takes
to get you back home.
I'll go there too, and forever we'll be-
I don't dislike you, but I'm fine
living here just like this.
Don't be like that.
I'm fine!
Then be a little more feminine...
That's enough!
I suppose there may be a difference
in our values, after all.
Back to the subject at hand...
Her story... No, our story,
after she boarded the ship.
She'd spoken to one of the crew
and smuggled herself on board,
but she noticed that she
stood out horribly.
Now that I know her,
it doesn't bother me at all, but...
The first time I saw it,
I was pretty shocked.
At the time, I was four.
I was returning to Japan with my dad.
Dad, this woman, she... Hurry!
My father, Shingen, was not a
normal person by any means.
Dad, come on!
When he heard my story,
the proper thing to do as a parent would
have been to laugh, don't you think?
But he didn't.
Perhaps it was his nature as a doctor,
but he was very interested.
My lady, I apologize, but is it true
that you have no head?
"If you let me dissect you, just once,
I'll give you a place to stay."
She agreed.
She had her own reasons,
but I'm sure she was nervous.
She doesn't really seem
to remember this.
Human anesthetic didn't work,
so the shock must have been great.
She seems to have a sense of pain,
but much lessened.
She has no heart.
All of her organs are there,
but non-functioning.
She has blood vessels,
but no blood circulating through them.
It's simply flesh.
She's like a walking anatomical model.
But look.
What would it take for her to die?
Wasn't my dad just horrible?
He was having his four-year-old
son dissect a girl.
But thanks to experiences like this,
I became an excellent doctor.
You never know what's going to help you.
What's wrong?
The moment I saw her, I was entranced.
And those feelings haven't changed in the
twenty years we've lived together.
And she's been looking for her head this
whole time, working as a transporter.
If it came back, what would she do?
What would happen to her?
Is her will her head's will?
Or...
What are you recording?
Nothing special.
I was hoping to tell later generations
about the wonderful life we lead.
Whatever. Just be quiet.
I can't sleep.
Sorry, Celty.
That's all for now.
I'll do the rest some other time.
It's perfect!
What do you mean?
A Dullahan carries its head
with it, you know.
It doesn't need a head.
Of course it does.
You only think that 'cause you've
never seen the real thing.
She was a beautiful, beautiful woman.
Sure was.
But she's better without a head.
It's more charming that way.
She's perfect that way.
So you don't need to worry about it.
You don't need to be able to draw it.
It's fine as it is.
But I'm going to draw it anyway.
It's fine as it is!
You're a strange guy.
Aw, you flatter me!
This program is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to people, parties,
or situations is purely coincidental.
Next Time
on Durarara!!
False
Advertising
Wanna know about my love-love-getchu-heartbreaking daily life?
Turn the channel of your heart to me, the cool, shy Kida Masaomi!
Next time: False Advertising.
You've got one chance in 300 years, so don't blow it!