Lunch boxes
Hot!
That day I learned what lunch boxes are all about.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
What Lunch Boxes
Are All About
This is nice once in a while!
The four of us having lunch together like this.
At least the guys.
And there aren't even four of us.
Besides, where's Kitamura-daisensei, who came up with the idea?
Sorry for the wait!
I'm sorry, I had to go pick this up at the student council room.
It wouldn't fit in a locker.
W-What is that?
Could it be...
A-A lunch box?
Yes.
And then...
Aren't you quite prevalent today , Dai-sen? Carrying around such a marvellous lunch box...
Hey, Haruta, it's not nice to laugh at someone's lunch box-
A manga lunch box?
No, a 2D lunch box!
The inside is just as amazing!
What is this uproar about?
Let me see it as well-
Minori!
What is this?
Maruo is having a feast!
What kind of a party is it?
Whoa, lobsters' antennae are so long.
C-Could this "39" possibly mean...
Is it "saku" from Yuusaku?
TL Note: 39 can be read "saku".
Exactly!
Yuusaku, this is just your grandmother's lunch box, right?
Huh?
Is this your grandmother's handmade lunch box?
Yes.
My parents went to Guam on a company outing.
In the meantime my grandmother came over.
Is this handmade?
This quality?
Then she went all out and made what you see here.
She really loves her grandchild.
I'm thankful for the thought, but she overdid it.
Which means, I thought of having everyone help me.
Huh?
Is it okay to eat it?
Really?!
Of course!
It would be saddening for my grandmother if I had leftovers.
I think the girls prefer this.
I'm digging in!
What's this?
It's nice!
It's delicious!
As expected from Yuusaku's grandmother.
It's good!
This is nice for a dessert!
What's wrong?
You should also eat, Takasu.
O-Okay.
T-Then I'll have this fried...
Taiga?
What's wrong, Aisaka?
No need to hold back.
T-Then I'd like to eat the lobster.
You're amazing!
What's with that nonchalantness of yours?
Just when I thought you were hesitating,
you want to eat the centrepiece!
It has nothing to do with you!
No, but...
I'm fine with that!
Eat as much as you can!
It's so good!
It tastes luxurious!
I'm so so happy!
What about your own lunch box?
I ate it, of course!
But the lobster is my dessert!
This lobster is so nice!
It doesn't just look good!
The taste is perfect as well!
Takasu!
Can I take a picture of your lunch box with my phone?
I want to show my grandmother what a normal lunch box looks like.
Eh, uh, I was busy this morning, so I made a plain one-
It's fine.
Okay!
Thanks, Takasu.
This is...
Hey, everyone!
As if I'd let them think that I was being serious when making this lunch box...
Eat as much as you like!
The shrimps are stupid.
As if I'd let them think that this lunch box is the best I can do!
If they weren't so delicious they wouldn't be eaten.
Crabs are the same.
It's so nice!
That Yuusaku!
I ate too much before I even realised.
K-Kawashima!
Hey...
Huh?
What?
Is Kitamura's grandmother a cooking teacher,
or does she run a restaurant of some sort?
She does, right?
She's a Pro?
Right?
Huh?
I think she's a normal housewife.
A normal housewife?
Yeah, I think she is.
By the way, what's his grandmother's name?
Huh?
Why do you think I know-
What is with that face?!
Bin
your
Cans
You surprised me!
Ah, I remember it now that I've seen that wicked face of yours.
She's Miyo-chan.
The "mi" from the word "year of the snake", Miyo-chan.
Miyo-chan, huh?
Maybe I should have a look at that "serious lunch box" you made.
Just as I wanted!
This time it'll be a real match, Miyo-chan!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Kitamura-kun!
Let's eat together!
You're having your grandmother's lunch box today as well, right?
Yeah.
But today I have a normal sized one.
I see.
Not too expensive, effortless enough,
Let's place the desks side by side and eat.
and the right amount to fill a high school student's stomach.
Following the rules, the match will be fair!
Well then.
What's wrong?
Okay!
C'mon, Miyo-chan!
Oh, that's nice, Takasu.
Today you have pork cutlets, huh?
Yeah.
Leftovers from yesterday's tonkatsu.
When I woke up this morning,
I just added some eggs to the mix. That's all.
I see.
What will you do now?
Me too!
Using rule-breaking high-class ingredients again for your cute grandson?
Will it be Caviar-donburi? Or fukahire-donburi?
Huh?
S-Simple this time, eh?
I did say rice balls are fine, but...
She certainly made them simple.
This is far too simple of a lunch box and it won't be enough for a high school student.
I have won this match- No!
What's that sparkling on the surface?
Sesame oil?
Which means...!
Wait, that's...!
It's good!
This is grilled meat!
Such a nice surprise to have meat in it!
This seaweed is from Korea, huh?
These kind of lunch boxes are the best.
This one has plum!
And this one... yay!
Decisively tuna-mayo!
This is my favourite!
The "yay" has appeared, huh?
Huh?
Grilled meat raises his spirits,
plum is a standard,
and Kitamura's favourite food: tuna-mayo.
A flawless line-up rich with variety.
On the other hand...
Mild taste of soup stock...
All of it, forever, the same taste.
Ryuuji!
Thanks for the food.
The pork with egg was nice.
Y-Yeah. I see.
Oh!
The rice balls look nice!
Having rice balls for dinner tonight would be nice too.
It was good, but pork for two days in a row is a bit heavy on the stomach.
Y-Yeah.
I knew that, but there was pork left over, so...
That's not it.
I was provoked by Miyo-chan...
...and wanted to include high-class looking fried food.
But to follow the rules for a proper high school student's lunch box,
using leftover was necessary.
Indeed, I made pork cutlets only to cook the the leftovers with eggs.
Housewives have to continuously think about food.
I did a bit too much yesterday, but now I'm back to my senses!
Miyo!
You're addressing my grandmother without an honorific?!
Super
Egolo
Lunch box.
What should I do?
What should I put in?
Lunch box.
Say, what kind of rice balls are you going to make?
Salmon is a must, right?
Ah, not seasoned, but normal-
Argh!
Rice balls?!
As if I can win if I make the same lunch box as Kitamura!
Eh?
Not for the lunch box, but for dinner.
I'll get to that later!
I had faith in my own housewife abilities.
I took pride in it.
Huh?
But you know, it was still as a high school student.
Even if you are the best among your peers,
you can't easily win when you join your elders.
I was like a frog in a well,
TL note: A person who is ignorant of the real world.
thrown in the vast sea of adults,
and eaten by a shark called Kitamura Miyo...
Dried bonito is nice too.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Huh?
What do you mean?
I'm doing the shopping instead, you useless dog.
Instead of?
You've only picked sweets and pudding.
What?
I also picked dried bonito, right?
That's for dessert.
Ah, did you know?
If you put soy sauce on pudding, it will taste like melon!
Not only is that really old, but it's also a bit off.
Eh, really?
This is not the time for this.
I see!
Something sharks don't have, but frogs do.
That is...
Youth!
Huh?
Hey, Taiga!
Have you seen Kitamura-kun- eh?
Hey!
Five millimetre under the specified line.
Any more or any less won't do!
Just a little longer!
Just a little longer and it's done!
Shut up!
You usually tell me not to eat something like this.
What's that?
Cup ramen?
Oh, Minorin.
You even prepared a pot!
Isn't that great!
You two -dum dum du-dum- don't hate!
What is it?
You're having cup ramen for lunch?
How nice.
I'm tired of cold lunch boxes.
That's a nice smell!
How nice!
Looks good!
Eating them at home is normal,
but eating one in a classroom is novel.
I'll make every lunchtime a bit more fun.
Kitamura's grandmother doesn't have this sense of youth.
Today's victory is mine.
You won't eat with us, Minorin?
Ah, I have the regular club meeting at lunchtime today.
Hey, hey!
Kitamura-man!
Let's go already, man!
Sorry, sorry.
Y-Yo, Kitamura.
I accidentally overslept, so I have cup ramen today.
Eh?
You have hot water?
Y-Yeah.
Can you share some, in that case?
Thanks.
My grandmother made me take cup soup with me.
She told me there are kids who eat cup ramen at school,
so I should get some hot water from them.
I didn't think people actually would, but your timing is great.
Y-Yeah.
Today I'm having this and sandwiches.
Good for eating during a meeting.
Kitamura-kun!
Sorry for the wait, Kushieda!
Let's go!
See you later, Taiga.
Yeah...
Sandwiches are nice as well.
Don't eat then.
Huh?
I mean, you can't eat!
Here!
Hey, what are you doing?!
You can't have it!
What are they doing?
You can't eat it!
What nonsense is that?!
You won't get enough calcium if you only eat cup ramen.
Too hot!
Here you go!
Sorry for the wait.
It's not much.
It's not much at all.
I pretend that, and...
This plate has a lot!
Thanks, Minori!
I don't need your gratitude.
If it isn't enough, don't hesitate to ask for more.
I'll add even more.
A bunch more.
But still, taking in carbohydrates immediately after school is over...
Cup ramen isn't enough to fill my stomach.
And I didn't even eat that.
It's not like it matters.
I'm fine with Ryuuji's normal lunch boxes.
He's been strange and thinking too much lately.
Oh, Taiga!
What a pitiable girl you are!
You've become unable to live without Takasu Ryuuji feeding you, haven't you?!
Huh?!
There, there.
Food is the foundation of everything.
You have to be fed.
Well then!
Please enjoy!
A lunch box, huh?
This isn't it.
This isn't it!
This is not how it is!
What's this for? A party?
Looks delicious!
I can't eat this much.
Where's Taiga-chan?
Don't know.
Can I take it to work?
Yaegashi-san's wife has run away from him.
I'm sure he'll be happy with it!
Ryuu-chan's food is really delicious!
I'll be going.
Guess I'll eat too.
Nice.
It's nice.
What is it?
If you're there, just come eat.
She's probably just sulking over what happened at lunchtime.
As if I care about that.
I will make the greatest lunch box in order to defeat Kitamura Miyo.
No matter what I must do.
For example, putting curry sauce inside frozen rice.
Or storing sashimi in a cooler box to put it on sushi rice, and call it kaisendon.
Or maybe something gaudy like a Ritz party...
Stop sounding like you enjoy eating food scraps!
More please.
Even more?!
I mean-
Food scraps?
Leftovers?
I failed with the leftovers by making pork with egg.
Which means something totally new must...
I see.
That's it.
That's all I still can- Hm?
Are you faking it?
Say whatever you want, Inko-chan.
I-In-Inzaghi.
It doesn't matter at all.
Filippo Inzaghi.
Right.
Do you know him?
I don't mind having to use a slightly dirty trick.
I will... cross the line!
The Hayabusa bullet train debuted March fifth on the Touhoku Shinkansen line.
Leaving their parents and people living in northern- Hm?
This smell...
What's this?
This is... this sound... no, that can't be.
There's no way that can be true.
But...
Oh, a rice cooker.
Really?
A rice cooker?
No way.
No wonder I smelled something good.
It really is a nice smell.
I started to get hungry.
So, why did you do this, Takasu-kun?
Takasu?
Hey, hey, Taka-chan, don't go cooking rice in the classroom.
What a joke!
Wait up, everyone!
You too, Sensei!
How can you know that I did that?
You're always blaming me!
There's no one else who would do something like this.
Yeah, that's right!
I'm the one who did it!
Forgive me, Sensei!
Anything but that!
Just a little, just a little longer and it will be cooked!
Don't do something so cruel!
What?!
What's going on?!
Idiot.
I'm done for.
Such a waste.
If you just turn the switch on once more,
it will probably work out some how.
Cooking the rice again would ruin the taste.
So what?
You're already ruined anyway.
The taste of autumn.
Maitake... Hiratake... Plenty of mushrooms.
I thought I could win by making freshly cooked rice with other ingredients.
That's not a lunch box anymore.
I know.
I kept talking about rules, and then broke them myself.
I even lost because of that.
Losing or breaking rules or anything aside,
you got carried away and destroyed yourself.
Here.
I already knew I wouldn't be able to eat decently today...
I will give that to you, a stupid dog lost in a dead end of thoughts.
Is this...
You made this yourself?
Don't make fun of me!
Even I can make something like rice balls if I try.
I learned that from you.
It's hot!
Freshly cooked rice is like a deadly weapon!
Endure it!
If the rice isn't hot, it's difficult to shape.
Here!
It's hot!
What?
I don't want to give it to someone who doesn't need it.
I-I'll have it! I'm digging in.
How is it?
What's the matter?
You're shaking.
Too salty!
Pouring dashi into it.
TL Note: Dashi: Japanese soup stock made from fish and kelp.
This will decrease the saltiness.
Hurry, hurry!
Wait up.
Let me add honeywort as well.
Here.
I'm digging in!
You should break it into smaller pieces first.
It's great!
This is good.
The plum pickles accent it.
I'm a genius!
I see.
That's right.
I'm a genius?
Indeed.
Apart from the first manga lunch box,
no, that one included,
Miyo-chan's lunch boxes were meant to make Kitamura happy.
The rice balls were according to Kitamura's request,
and the onion soup was because she knew Kitamura had a meeting at lunchtime.
Everything was for Kitamura.
But still, I...
Thanks for the food.
The one who eats my lunch boxes...
...is you.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Just by eating a little I got even more hungry.
I want to eat more.
Ah, pork cutlet might be good now!
Pork cutlets in tea.
Pork cutlet for the third time this week?
Ah, I still have some thin cutlets if you want them.
That's it!
Mille-feuille pork cutlet!
Ah, let's recook that rice and the other ingredients as well.
We can have that together with side dishes.
You can't be helped.
You're not going to eat the dashi rice balls?
I'm fine with this.
I was surprised back then,
but it's not something that can't be eaten.
Didn't you just say something rude now?
Eh?
I didn't.
You did.
That's why you should put cheese between the cutlets.
I learned what lunch boxes are all about.
A lunch box you make for someone, thinking about that someone while making it...
It will surely be delicious, no matter what it is.
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...