A boat beneath a sunny sky,
Lingering onward dreamily
In an evening of July —
Children three that nestle near,
Eager eye and willing ear,
Pleased a simple tale to hear —
Long has paled that sunny sky:
Echoes fade and memories die:
Autumn frosts have slain July.
Ever drifting down the stream —
Lingering in the golden gleam —
Life, what is it but a dream?
Take that!
Another ruckus today!
Woohoo!
Hey, watch where you're aiming!
Today's the day we teach those idiots a lesson!
Those damn Outers think they're tourists.
Sheesh. They're not gonna keep making fools of us.
I hear ya, Dr. Shouko!
Hey! Don't just jump onto our line without permission!
Well, I figured since you're giving me such a good workout every day,
I ought to thank you!
You really get on my nerves, you know!
Give back that hammer already!
It belongs to Bishamaru!
Why you...
How many did I get?
Thirty-one.
Damn. I'm not done yet!
In that case,
if I give it back, will you make me a new one?
As if.
Have you any sense of shame?
Excuse us!
Thanks for the food.
Those boys are always so energetic.
Quite.
Here.
Nee-chan!
Yo! How's it going?
They're all small fries. It's no fun!
Shouko-chan, bring out Bishamaru already!
You expect me to listen to you?
I can't use a Treasured Relic lightly!
So stingy.
How brazen.
Looking at something?
Well, what do you think you're doing?
Is it one of those things?
What is it?
Off to chase after another woman's skirt this early in the morning?
I'll make it up to you next time.
Oh, is that so?
Have I ever lied to you before?
Bravo!
They never tire of this, do they?
I've seen enough.
Every day's a festival, with them around.
Hey! What are you doing, you morons?
That's Yase's turf!
Nee-chan...
We'll have to formally apologize.
No! It's not my fault!
It's the machines' fault!
All right!
Special attack:
SEE YOU TOMORROW!
Nice shot!
I'll bet Shouko's furious.
Well...
But she's always furious.
Exactly!
Well, anyway,
once again, we have achieved vict—
Ow...
We're going home.
Kyouso
Welcome back.
Those stupid siblings!
I hope you die!
Giga
Gi
KyousoGiga
Hey! Are you listening?
I'm sure you're mighty tired, but could you do me a favor and pay attention?
Lighten up.
We're sorry, we're sorry, we're sorry, we're sorry, we're sorry!
At least show some regret!
Give me a break here, please!
Are you sure you understand?
We heard there was a festival and got a bit carried away.
Exactly!
Don't give me that!
You three think every day is a festival!
What's that mean?
Hmph! Stupid!
Poop!
Playboy monk!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Poop! Poop! Poop! Poop!
Shut up, you Three Stooges!
Un! You tell him off, too!
Tell him good!
I need to potty.
Badly?
Very.
Why would you hold it in like that?
I was trying...
That's not normal!
Go go go go!
The next time this happens, it's no meals for three days.
They call that child abuse, you know.
It hurts me more than it hurts you.
And clean up this room.
Yeah, yeah.
We were just having fun going on adventures.
Myoue, you get mad at everything.
I'm telling you, quit provoking them for no reason.
Also, we don't call wanton destruction "adventures".
How long do I have to put up with these foreign nuisances?
Until we find the rabbit.
'Kay?
Oh, good.
Now you can go back to your country.
Take your buddies with you and scram.
Go on.
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
You four always seem so close.
Really, they cause such a fuss I could cry.
Don't eat junk food during meals!
Is that any way to look on such a glorious occasion?
You seem to be in good form.
I've been expelling evil spirits.
It's tiring.
My, that won't do...
or so I would like to say.
Consider yourself lucky.
They've grown quite attached to you.
I'm jealous.
If you want the cake plate,
I'll gladly relinquish the rights to you.
What?
Don't say that. Decisions made here are final.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
We know that.
But you must have your hands full with that little whirlwind.
So full they're brimming over!
My, what's the matter? Our little tomboy is so adorable.
I have great expectations.
Take care when handling rascals.
Spirited children were always your specialty, weren't they, Myoue?
Don't be ridiculous. She's not as bad as you were, my dear young Yase.
Looking back on it, you two made excellent opponents.
My, my. Acting like a third party, are we, Kurama?
You've always been first when it comes to spite.
Let's leave the bickering at that.
If she heard us, we'd get a good scolding.
We shall soon be reunited with her.
I can't wait! Oh, I'm so excited!
I don't know about that.
The kid looks too dumb to even bake a loaf of bread.
If she knows how to play with toys, that's all we need.
She doesn't have a golden crown or anything.
Then we can just make her one.
Get too close and she might bite back.
You're frightened, aren't you?
You were always apt to bawl in fright.
Unlike you, I've graduated from my toddler clothes.
I've been dressed like an adult too, haven't I?
Fret not.
You boys are equally childish so far as I'm concerned.
Nevertheless,
today is a remarkable anniversary.
Let's put on a grand celebration!
Then let us swear an oath to the First One, my siblings.
Among the three of us,
we preserve our honor
and keep no secrets.
In our name, and the name of our exalted mother,
we submit to the immaculate Ten Commandments!
See ya later!
Koto!
Huh?
If anything happens, call me.
Right.
Say,
would plucking them be too much of a shame?
Yet, so would letting them wither...
Kifune-chan from Logistics was captured.
Oh?
Don't pretend you didn't know.
I thought something was strange since this morning.
I keep telling you, inform me before you do something.
So, what are you up to, Head Priest?
Come now, don't cry.
When will you come back?
When indeed?
I'd have to ask that.
I don't want this!
Do what you want.
You three get along now.
I'm sure I'll see you again soon.
Stop crying already!
I give up I give up!
Charms to ward off evil
will now go on sale.
Not on sale tomorrow, just for tonight.
O you devoted believers,
buy one and take it home.
We'll give you a candle as a gift.
Give you a candle, how does that sound?
Donation?
Don't worry. Gods who care about donations are quacks.
Who's the god of this place, anyway?
Miyako-sama! It's Miyako-sama!
I'm afraid I don't really know...
Some famous historical person?
Hey, stop playing that game!
We don't know!
God of traffic safety or something?
I heard you can pray for anything here.
Really?
No, I mean, my grandma said...
She's got ears like this. Like this! Right?
And huuuge boobs!
Just like a bunny. Right?
Miyako-sama? Oh, you mean Koto-sama.
Yeah, not many people nowadays know her.
If you go to the information center today, you can see Koto-sama.
This beautiful gal is Koto-sama.
She went away a long time ago,
and hasn't come back since.
And—
I guess we're never going home.
Wha—You—What do you think you're saying?!
She's right! Koto-sama is definitely a rabbit, though.
A-chan!
We don't know for sure yet!
But come on...
She's the first black rabbit we've seen!
Maybe just the picture is enough.
Exactly!
But we're still here!
So I guess it doesn't work.
Oh, come on! Oh...
You two!
If you don't donate generously, your prayers won't be heard.
As they say, you can even pay your way out of the Underworld.
So this place is the Underworld?
What, you didn't know?
Huh?
How insensitive, Koto.
There are oni here, aren't there?
Buddhas, too.
Does it really matter if we don't go home?
Well...
Yase!
Koto! As tomboyish as ever this morning, weren't you?
You were watching?
But of course.
I'm a fan of yours, after all.
Really?
You don't want to see our parents?
Parents, huh?
We're here to receive you.
Huh?
Hey!
I don't wanna be separated from Koto.
Our parents probably feel the same.
What do you mean?
Huh?
Whaaat?!
Temple Admin
2-D
We should have used this earlier.
Temple Admin
2-D
But it's boring. Not my style.
What? Are you doing something?
We're throwing a marvelous birthday party.
You're the guest of honor.
Koto!
Huh? Huh?
What?!
Welcome to the Triumvirate.
It's a pleasure to have you.
What's the meaning of this, you two?
I thought I told you.
We're putting on a grand celebration!
We can't have a birthday party without the guest of honor.
Um...
Today's not my birthday.
Oh dear.
That's a lie.
Huh?!
Dammit...
However, ever since you came home...
Every day has been like the Gion Festival!
Wait, you've got it wrong!
I haven't come home! I want to go home!
'Ello! Saitou Newspaper!
Koto of Kyoto
is Koto-sama of "Kyoto"?!
What the heck is this?
Oh? Not to your tastes?
In that case...
Koto-sama of "Kyoto"
is the ancient rabbit of "Kyoto"?!
Koto-sama of Kyoto
is Kyoto itself?!
What the heck?!
Koto of "Kyoto"
is the ancient rabbit of Kyoto?!
No way! There is absolutely no way!
My breasts aren't that big!
Exactly.
It's what's on the inside that counts.
Indeed.
Those who desire something all come here.
After all, this is Where Wishes Come True.
Your Tanabata
wish is granted
Forward 5 spaces
Your Tanabata
wish is granted
Forward 5 spaces
Not the Town of Evil.
Moon Festival
Evil omen, go back 10
New Years' Eve
Too much interest
skip a turn
New Years' Eve
Too much interest
skip a turn
It's the City of Interest.
This is the Municipality of Madness.
Madness
The Capital of Sutras.
Sutra
Through the Looking-Glass.
Looking-Glass
"Kyoto".
Where Wishes Come True.
City of Interest.
Win!
Through the Looking-Glass.
Municipality of Madness.
The Capital of Sutras.
Where Wishes Come True.
Win!
City of Interest.
Through the Looking-Glass.
Municipality of Madness.
The Capital of Sutras.
Where Wishes Come True.
City of Interest.
Through the Looking-Glass.
Municipality of Madness.
The Capital of Sutras.
Where Wishes Come True.
City of Interest.
Through the Looking-Glass.
Municipality of Madness.
Augh!
I have no idea what's going on!
Even a joke must have some purpose to it.
What good is a child with no purpose?
We wish to place our expectations in your childish potential.
Talk about an impossible game.
I'm pitting her against Bishamaru. It's what she wants.
Good-bye, Koto.
Stop it!
I never agreed to this!
I won't accept this as a decision of the Triumvirate!
Submit to the First One and the Law,
Kurama!
This is a legitimate test.
You know that, don't you?
You want to see Mama as much as I do,
Oedipus.
Mama?
This has gone on long enough.
I suppose I must take voluntary action to bring about this reunion.
A: It's Nee-chan!
Un: We're stuck.
You of all people should understand, Koto.
Those idiots are having their way with things.
What should we do, Inari?
I think a person's appearance counts for something, and I'm not your mother, either.
Still, I know what it feels like to miss a family member.
So I'll play along, just this once!
No! Stop—
What a persistent man.
Dammit...
How dare you get in my way...
youkai?!
And you.
Just what do you think you're doing,
human?!
Well, I do owe you all for taking care of me.
But you know, I don't think it's healthy
to force your expectations onto a child.
Adults do nothing but betray you, do they?
Guess we've both got bad luck.
Wait right there!
What are you so worked up for?
It's disgraceful.
You're going to swallow those words right now, oni!
That's quite the sibling rivalry.
A: Why isn't it breaking?
Un: They're cheating.
A: You can't use a cheat character!!
You look good like that, Princess.
You puny, insolent human!
Damn, this is annoying...
Well how about this?
A: Get him, Koto!
Un: Do him in!
Say, Myoue.
There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
Every time you open your mouth, all you do is complain.
Yet you treasure those children so dearly.
We keep no secrets among us,
do we, Myoue?
Is your separation anxiety that of the child, or of the parent?
See that, you lump of metal?
Special attack:
APPLIANCE KILLER!
Idiot.
Idiot!
H-Hang on!
Time out! Time out!
Perhaps it was a waste.
Are you sure about this?
Better keep it a secret from them.
A: Let her out!
Un: Let her out out!!
A: Let her out out out!!!
Un: Let her out out out out!!!!
A: Let her out out out out out!!!!!
Un: Let her out out out out out out
A: Let her out out out out out out o
Shouko-san,
you seem a bit depressed.
Ow! Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, that hurts!
Oh, what am I to do?
No matter how old they grow, all they do is fight.
It's your fault for leaving them alone until now.
But I'm so happy I can see you again!
I've been waiting for so long, after all.
A virus?
Once you have spoken it, so shall it be.
Your words are my strength.
Look! It's Mama! There she is!
Nee-chan!
Come, tell me.
My King, my Master...
Your wish is mine as well.
...want to... home...
Huh?
I want to go home!
Koto!
You've grown so beautiful, Princess.
My, but you've aged,
Kurama.
You are as beautiful as ever, Koto.
Thank you.
I was kissed by a woman!
A woman kissed me!
Poor girl.
Look at how you've grown!
Are you able to sleep alone now,
Myoue?
Shut up.
I didn't expect this many grandchildren.
They're not!
Koto.
I'm sorry. It seems I made a bit of a mistake.
Will you still be my friend?
Go on.
I'm glad you made it back, Koto-sama.
You were waiting for someone to receive you, weren't you?
Welcome home!
I don't really get it, though.
Me neither!
I'm back.
Save?
Don't save?
We want to go home too, please!
What's that?
Huh?
Koto, you can't go home anymore.
What?!
Save?