Faint-hearted traveler, you should pull back now
Before you collapse
But you still say that you want to go on?
To the other side of the distant sky...
Thousands of travelers have prayed to me before
After they collapsed at the other end of their journey
In a place that is not here, in a time that is not now.
You're searching, saying that there's love there
Even though you could just patiently wait
For the destiny that I have given you
Do you know I'm a Venus?
Faint-hearted traveler, come closer to me
Come sit at my feet
I will embrace you and show you
What is waiting beyond the distant sky
What you wanna go high? Make it heaven!
On a spring night, Virgo is spread out widely.
My favorite star, Spica, is this Alpha star.
If you stretch this line from the Big
Dipper, there's the North Star.
And if you pull the handle of the ladle,
there's the star of the cow
herder, Arcturus, then Spica!
This line is called the Great Arc of Spring.
During the cherry blossom season,
try looking for it in the south sky!
The Promised Five
You go back to school first
thing tomorrow morning, right?
Y-Yeah.
Well, good night.
Dad's still not back?
Is he out drinking somewhere again?
I don't even have a key...
This is troublesome...
Maybe...
I knew it!
I feel like a burglar...
Is it okay for him to be so careless?
But Dad's out really late.
The late night shift? Guardsman?
Dad's working longer hours?
For Dad:
Pass for free rides on Asumi's rocket.
Rocket        Asumi                Dad
Dad...
Everyone's trying their best
to regain what they have lost.
To Dad:
Welcome back.
Thanks for all your hard work.
I'm sorry, I'll be going now.
You seem all right now, little one.
Well then...
Perhaps I'll go too.
That dummy isn't here today either?
Whether or not you worry, that
little seagull will show up soon.
Who said I was worried?
After all, her motives for coming to this school are
a little irregular, just like someone else I know...
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
More importantly, Fuchuuya-kun, when are
you going to give up on that puzzle ring?
I'll never give it to you!
Cheapskate.
Is Kamogawa absent again today?
Hmph. There's no helping that girl.
Now go to page 64, from the
description of the Earth's orbit...
Asumi!
I'm sorry for being late!
Don't just stand there, take your seat.
Yes.
Now then, imagine being on a rocket
that has successfully lifted off
and is going around Earth.
At that moment, how would you
find your current location?
Of course, to be at that height of the orbit
it must go around at a given speed...
Kei-chan...
W-What is it?
I made too many...
Huh?
Rice balls...
Be quiet over there.
Y-Yes.
I'm s-sorry.
Therefore, in other words...
For crying out loud...
Really, that dummy...
Good for you, Fuchuuya-kun.
What is?
That.
What happened with that certain
student's case, Sano-sensei?
I'm sorry.
I see. Well, it doesn't matter.
I wasn't expecting that much.
I heard.
You were a participant in that
big mistake, weren't you?
It was thoughtless of me to ask you.
I won't ask you for anything again.
Unacceptable? What do you mean?
Weight-wise and cost-wise,
it's sufficient!
This design is perfect.
What's wrong with it?
There was someone who was against
the way you prioritized the cost.
Against it? Who?
It's Kamogawa Tomorou.
Kamogawa?
Hey, hey. So, how is it?
It's another failure, Kamogawa!
Leave me alone.
You just won't give up, huh?
He's the chief's favorite, so...
Either way, this is the JAMSF's decision.
You won't be able to change it, no matter what.
You there, don't slack!
You're behind in your laps,
so you've got two more to go!
And I thought I could hide
it in all the commotion...
Devil!
Ah, I'm exhausted!
Just because it's an extra day
for the practice we missed
has our distance been lengthened?
I'm sorry. Because of me...
Don't apologize.
It was our choice to skip it, so...
The distance is longer because
of that devil instructor.
I thought I heard someone noisy...
and it was Kei after all.
Even if we had made an emergency landing
here, she wouldn't be any quieter.
Leave me alone!
Here.
Thank you, Fuchuuya-kun.
Hmph, thank you very much.
You sure are talented.
You can probably laugh while you're
angry like that comedian, huh?
I can't!
Kei-chan...
It's useless.
I'm so tired that I don't have
the strength to fight with Fucchii.
But when I think about it...
Ever since we got into this school,
all our training has just been running.
Are we really going to be able
to go to space like this?
Who knows.
That's the hard part about
newly-implemented courses.
There's no tradition or instruction manual.
We're fumbling our way through this,
and so is the school.
That's my share!
Gonna drink any?
I don't need it.
Oh, really?
Then drink mine.
I haven't put my mouth on it or anything.
I'm not thirsty.
Even I'm getting tired.
How long is this basic training going to last?
Surely, some people will leave the
school because of all this...
Surprisingly, that might be the school's reasoning.
Hey, Asumi, promise me something?
Huh?
That you won't leave school until we
reach our graduation ceremony.
At least, for us here right now...
No matter what bad times there will be,
let's promise that we won't give up!
Kei-chan...
Fucchii too...
Shuu too...
There.
What are you doing?
What do you mean, "What?"
We're putting our hands together!
Huh? Our hands?
Yeah, c'mon!
I can't do this!
Geez, stop with the complaining and just do it!
I don't want anyone here to give up!
All right, all right.
Of course, Kei-chan too.
Of course!
Asumi?
Sorry, could you wait a bit?
Asumi!
How far did Asumi go off to?
Hey, let's go back. I'm hungry.
It's fine to leave that dummy behind, so...
Well, well, saying what you don't really mean.
Hey, what is it?
Hurry, hurry!
Hey!
Kei-chan, sorry to keep you waiting.
Y-Yeah.
Here.
Well then.
Really... dummy.
Hey, Marika-chan, let's do it.
Let's promise.
We're going to promise not to
give up and graduate together.
I... such a thing...
Just do it with us.
Or it won't end.
Even if you get away now, this dummy will chase
you wherever you go and bring you back.
I don't want to have to get involved with that.
Just think of it as being destined to be together.
But...
It's a promise.
I promise.
I... promise.
Yeah!
Hey, Asumi, can I ask you something?
Hmm?
Well... did something happen with Sano-sensei?
You know, Asumi, you got summoned, right?
You've been absent-minded since then.
I thought it might have been Sano-sensei
who summoned you that time.
That time, you came to class late.
Something felt weird about you too.
So I thought, maybe...
Kei-chan, I got a little homesick.
It was my own problem,
and I exaggerated it by myself,
so it's not like something
happened with a teacher.
She's hiding something, after all.
Am I that unreliable?
At that extra practice just now...
Thank you, Kei-chan.
I was happy.
I was really happy.
Asumi!
You can't always eat just rice balls!
I'll treat you!
I'll treat you to something really tasty!
K-K-Kei-chan!
C'mon, c'mon! Let's go!
Give me a ride sometime, Fuchuuya-kun.
1,000 yen.
Oh my... can't you let that
go in the name of friendship?
What friendship is that?
How cold.
Hurry and get on.
Before I change my mind.
That's why I like you, Fuchuuya-kun.
Idiot!
My, you even have another helmet ready.
At this rate, wouldn't it be faster if we walked?
Be quiet. If you have a problem, get off.
Well, I was thinking how Fuchii-like it is,
the way it just goes at its own pace.
So like its owner.
What's that?
You sure are a weird guy.
And you're the one that's at his own pace.
Pretty much.
Really...
Such a good kid.
Kei and the little seagull, as well.
The type that destroy themselves
because they're so good.
Of course, you're a good kid too, Fucchii.
I don't need to hear that, idiot.
Thank you.
You're living in a place like this by yourself?
Pretty much.
This is even more crude than Kamogawa's place.
He's the son of a politician, so I thought
he could afford a better place.
Are you that sorry to part with me?
Her surname's a bit unusual, too.
Tokyo National
Space School
Student List
Oh, you read that as "Ukita."
Ukita?
Yeah.
I see...
Aritsune Junichirou
Ukita Marika
Urakawa Kenji
"A lot of happiness in space," huh?
A fitting name for a space astronaut.
She's a really pretty girl, and she tries her best.
I see...
Is she your friend, little one?
Yep!
I see.
Lion-san?
I'm relieved.
Huh?
When you were still in Yuigahama,
you'd rarely talk about your friends.
At your age it may be hard to realize, but...
Having friends that share the same
dream as you is truly wonderful.
Did you have friends like that?
Yes.
I wonder how they're doing.
I haven't seen them in a while.
I wonder what Lion-san's friends are like.
Unlike Lion-san, they would age.
So they might be old men now.
Old men?
Don't say stuff like that!
What's she getting hyped up about herself?
Asumi-chan's talking to herself more these days.
Though she was a bit strange before...
Maybe she's tired from not being
used to living by herself.
But, Lion-san...
It doesn't change that fact
that you're my first friend.
Thank you for coming to Tokyo.
Look up at the stars in the night
The little stars, with their little lights
Are singing of humble happiness
Look up at the stars in the night
Just like us, the stars without names
Are praying for humble happiness
Preview
Starting today, I'll be going
to school with Lion-san.
And Sano-sensei finally lashes
out viciously at Kei-chan.
But what I saw in the library
was the figure of Sano-sensei smiling
peacefully at a space photo album.
Sensei has been looking at the same
thing we have all this time, right?
Next time on Twin Spica:
A Sad Smile.
A Sad Smile
End