They said we were fools.
They said we were chasing fancy and phantasms.
But we two dreamers will prove them wrong.
Whether laughing,
or clashing,
always shall we each succor the other!
Fight!
Explode!
Schwing!
Ever shall we run
'til we reach that very Garden of the Hesperides in which blossoms the hope of every man!
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
The mixed bath is currently
closed for remodeling.
—Kotoura Hot Springs
Kotoura Hot Springs
Withdraw!
One morning I suddenly realized it
I realized that I want to know more about you
How weird that my heart thumps and I get nervous
You only have to stand next to me and I might faint
And still you worm your way
deeper into my heart
Love,
love,
love
✩Ah✩
Nothing good can come from cuddling you all the time
Cuddle,
cuddle,
cuddle
The scent of my feelings might stick
But,
but,
but
I want you to comfort me
There,
there,
there
Tell me, is this "love"?
That's a secret beyond all secrets, you know?
Yeah!
That's a secret beyond all secrets, isn't it? ♡
In This World, I...
I only wanted a mixed bath.
To think I missed the last chance I'll ever have to share a bath with high school girls.
Well, well!
That looks delicious!
I think I made too much.
Your cooking is fantastic, though.
Take a look, guys.
I made something too.
I'm trying to make up for my last attempt.
I expect Manabe will be very grateful for this.
I expect he'll eat every last bite.
Well, at any rate, enjoy the meal.
The hot springs turned out to be a wasted trip, after all.
True.
I'm sure you were pretty crushed,
not being able to bathe with me and all.
Nah.
Manabe may have his shortcomings,
but at least he knows not to ignore his girl.
Stay strong, President Mifune!
Don't worry about me.
Shouldn't you be doing something about him?
For mixed bathing!
We strike!
For naked fellowship!
For my granddaughter!
For Kotoura!
What are those two doing?
For my granddaughter!
For Kotoura!
Eek! Manabe, you Lothario!
With my granddaughter!
Eek! Grandfather, you Lothario!
Even if you do find a hot spring in the backyard, I am not getting in it with you!
Strike!
Damn it all!
How could we strike oil instead of a hot spring?!
It may make me richer,
but what use is all the money in the world if I can't share a bath with my granddaughter?
M-Manabe, I think this attempt turned out better than the last.
Damn! Damn!
Wh-What do you think?
W-Won't you please stop, Moritani?
Time to make you an adult!
I'm scared!
Hey! What are you two doing?!
Yowza! Hey there, Kotoura!
Oh, for— Put your clothes on, Manabe!
Eek! Kotoura, you Lotharia!
How can you even say that, Manabe?!
Kotoura's ignoring me!
She must like naked people!
Fine! I'll strip, too!
I'll strip, too!
There!
Hey! Don't do that around the boys!
Gotchya! Je t'aime, Kotoura!
No!
Come on! One won't hurt!
H-Help me, Manabe!
The first time is just practice!
Our bodies were made for each other!
Kotoura, you're so silky smooth.
No! That's not me!
May we never forget this tragedy and its dire warning
against the perils of Moritani's cooking.
You know, since she's capable of making food like that from normal, everyday ingredients,
maybe she holds the greatest psychic power of us all.
Hey, Head Priest.
Here, let me start you off with... huh?
Is something wrong?
So this is what you wanted to show me?
I'm sorry to impose, but—
That child looks like she's having so much fun.
So she's made friends, has she?
Yes, she has.
They're all good kids.
Has she forgotten?
She destroyed her own family with her vicious nonsense.
If you continue to associate with her, she'll ruin you too.
You'll lose everything, just like I did.
Kumiko, can't you at least talk to her?
To say what?
We'll only reopen old wounds.
I see. So she was here.
I apologize for inviting her without consulting you first.
I just wanted her to see how far Haruka has come.
Sounds like she hasn't changed a bit.
She, on the other hand...
Come on, you two! Pull yourselves together!
What. What on Earth.
What on Earth happened here?!
How could you forget?
I loved you last night with all my heart!
There's no turning back now.
Moritani
School
Entrance
Form
Moritani
School
Entrance
Form
Time to take responsibility like a man.
Moritani
School
Entrance
Form
I'm the scum of the Earth!
So you're awake.
You sure had a good time last night
...with Manabe.
Wh-What do you mean, "a good time?"
Wait... With Manabe?!
Good morning, Moritani.
Good morning.
Um. It isn't what it looks like.
It was only an accident. Just a small, unfortunate accident.
Huh?
What a wild night. You two were really going at it.
Going at it?
Wild?
What-who now?
You don't mean... the three of us...
My eyes! My eyes!
How can your mind go there the minute you wake up?!
Honestly.
You both behaved very inappropriately.
As your master, I am very upset with you.
B-But Master, I don't remember a thing.
Because I stopped you from doing anything irreversible.
You, my young Moritani, need to learn the virtue of restraint.
Especially when cooking.
Yes, ma'am.
And you're no better, Manabe.
You need to exercise moderation in your beha—Hey!
Would you please stop it already!
I wasn't even involved!
Stop!
Thank you for everything!
You could have stayed longer.
We'd love to, but approximately one of us still has summer homework to finish.
≈ One
Hey, where's Kotoura?
Now that you mention it, the priest is missing too.
Let's go look for them.
Hold up a minute, Manabe.
Yes?
She couldn't be.
Head Priest.
Haruka, this room is...
All the times I've returned to this house,
I've never been able to come in here.
But somehow, this time around it was easy.
So my mother was here?
I can't hide anything from you.
I asked her to come, but it was no good.
Don't worry about it.
But sir, how can I get my parents and my friends to stay with me?
How can I get them to give me a smile?
Haruka, I promise you that I'll bring your mother back.
Sir, do you think
I should never have been born?
I never noticed this room was so small.
Haruka.
Back then, this room was my whole world.
I thought I'd stay in this world forever.
And yet...
Head Priest, it's time for me to go home.
Kumiko, your daughter has learned such a lovely smile.
So my mother was watching.
There she is! Kotoura!
Kotoura, we're heading home.
Okay! I'm coming!
I-I'm just inviting him to hang out because it's summer vacation.
It's not a date or anything.
Oh, enough! Just do it!
H-Hello, Manabe?
The person you have dialed is not available at this time.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Uh, um... I'll call again.
August
The Next Day
The person you have dialed is not available at this time.
Please leave a—
Again?
Two Days Later
The person you have dialed is not available—
Sheesh.
Again?
August
So you're saying you're lonely because Manabe won't talk with you?
He's probably just busy with something else.
But the other day I noticed...
Man, it's hot.
I wonder what sorts of things the ESP Society has planned for summer vacation.
2x2=4. 3x4=12. 3x8=24. 5x3=15. 5x7=35. 8x2=16.
...he starts doing his multiplication tables whenever I'm around.
Doesn't that sound suspicious?
My gratitude for your operational concept!
Today's activity shall be Manabe Observation!
What?
That devious little trick proves he's plotting something unpleasant.
Such as... cheating on you with the similarly-absent Moritani!
No.
Moritani's at home finishing her summer homework.
Mori! Mori! Mori!
How the hell is this supposed to help me study?
It'll stop you escaping, for starters.
Miss Hiyori, I am an alumnus of Tokyo University!
I shall put my life on the line to assist your studies!
Tokyo U?!
No, grant me that honor! I graduated from Harvard!
Harvard?!
Mori! Mori!
Well-enunciated!
Whatever it is, we know that Manabe is up to something.
Let's move out, Kotoura.
Uh, sure.
Will you join us, Muroto?
You're wasting your time. I'll pass.
You're no fun.
Let's go!
Right!
I believe that you'll find Manabe out in front of the station.
You saw him?
No.
He really is in front of the station.
Doesn't this just make your heart pound?
Yeah, but isn't it an invasion of privacy?
Shh! Look!
Could it be he's meeting her for a date?
Th-There's no way.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Only tissues.
No. Watch closely.
Thanks!
He's only taking them from girls!
Give chase!
Right!
Huh?
We've lost him already.
Well, I guess there's nothing more we can do.
Geh!
"Geh?"
What is it?
Do you like Mr. Boo-Bear?
Boobs. Boobs.
Jiggle-joggling juggs!
President, this boo-bear is dangerous! Get away from it!
That was too close.
She almost figured out it was me.
You've got a summer job?
Glunk.
Why are you keeping it a secret?
It's not something you should have to hide.
W-Well, see...
Boobs... to find the volume of one boob... one needs... pi... 3.1415926535897932...
You're completely irrational!
There's nothing else for it.
A-Am I feeling... Kotoura's... boobs?
Why do you sound like you're not sure?!
Manabe, you lunkhead! Stupid lecher!
You've got it all wrong!
I was still calibrated to Mifune's cup size, so—!
So in the end, you ran away.
He's never hidden anything from me before.
I understand that even Manabe has a few secrets, but...
But you still can't help doubting him a bit?
I see.
President Mifune?
Hey, it's that phony's kid!
I saw your mom on TV again yesterday.
They said she offed herself because people found out she was fake.
Shut up! My mom—
My mom...
The TV isn't always right.
You should only trust what you see with your own eyes.
A Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
This is my mom's book!
A Clairvoyant Woman
by Mifune Chizuru
I've read it tons of times.
And I still believe it.
I'm sure your mom was the real thing.
Um, I'm sorry!
Did I say something wrong?
No matter how dearly you love someone,
sometimes you get tired of believing, and doubt creeps in.
Wait.
Why are you crying?
Because... you... you...
Well, anyway, I'm sure you want someone to tell you
that your suspicions are completely unfounded, right?
Right.
Manabe's a moron, but that doesn't mean—
No. That's exactly why he won't betray you.
Don't you agree?
Is it your boobs?
Do you have confidence glands in your boobs?
What are you talking about?
August
Summer vacation is already over.
I never did see Manabe again.
Manabe, don't go!
Manabe!
Everyone will leave you.
It's only natural. You don't belong in this world, after all.
Moritani?
Kotoura! Save me!
What happened to you two?
Our deepest apologies, ma'am. She got away.
But now we're certain that the Moritani School's future is in good hands!
Hiyori!
I did it! You're such a good teacher!
Man, I should've asked you about this stuff sooner.
So, how's your summer with Manabe?
What?! Did I say something wrong again?
It sounds like you've been having a rough time of it while I was stuck at home.
Come on, cheer up!
But if Kotoura and Manabe really did...
Wait, what am I thinking?
Kotoura is my closest friend!
And Manabe would never betray her!
I'm such a dick!
Hey! What are you doing, Moritani?
Stop it!
Don't stop me!
I'm so disgusting, I can't stand it!
What am I going to do with you?
Moritani still likes Manabe,
but she genuinely cares about me, too.
She really believes that Manabe won't betray me.
You're wasting your time. I'll pass.
Manabe's a moron, but that doesn't mean—
No. That's exactly why he won't betray you.
Don't you agree?
Everyone trusts him.
Then I will too.
Beginning of Second Term
Manabe, I—
Free at last! Let's go, Kotoura!
Wait. Manabe?
Happy birthday, Kotoura!
Your grandfather told me that September 1 is your birthday.
Wow, you really had us going.
Hey! Why didn't you tell us about this?
Mifune and Muroto aside,
if I'd told you, you would've leaked it to her in no time.
Besides, you know,
I guess I like to have a moment in the sun now and then.
That's just like you. Dumb, but you.
Here. Your present.
I didn't really have that much time to think about what I should get you.
Sorry it's nothing special.
You don't belong in this world, after all.
What's wrong, Kotoura?
Sorry. I... I...
Go on, Kotoura!
Okay.
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, Kotoura!
Thank you, everyone.
Mother. In this world, I...
How do you stand again when something trips you up?
Can truth be found by thinking about the days to come?
We all come into this world alone when we are born,
and precisely because of that,
we try to live life with others from then on
Back then you taught me the strength to live and the meaning to it all,
and I embrace it with all my heart
So that in all things around us the flower of hope may bloom,
we start our days together here
We start our days together here
"The TV isn't always right," huh?
That's Muroto for you!
He speaks wisdom!
To expound upon his truth, unrealistically thick steam
and all-obscuring beams of light are morally wrong!
You've gotta be able to see everything!
Episode 8
It's Not a Date
You need to be censored, lecher.