This girl is Kouyama Mitsuki. 12 years old!
Last time, there was a substitute manager for Ooshige-san.
Unfortunately, it was no picnic in the park.
Mitsuki had to run all over
the place... what a disaster!
In the end, he said he was going to quit being
a manager and go back to the countryside...
We had to chase him around, too.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Hey, Meroko!
Which pair of sandals should I take tomorrow?
Hmm... I'd have to go with the pink ones.
You think so?
But...
...those ribbons are so cute!
Aren't they?
Then... why don't you just take both of them!
Great idea!
That way I won't regret it later!
Yep!
You're going to be working.
Does it really matter?
What?!
It's the first time I get to stay overnight for a job!
It's not a small matter!
You totally don't get it!
Okay, okay.
I guess someone like me wouldn't understand.
That's right!
You couldn't possibly understand, Takuto!
Girls are always dreaming
about meeting their prince.
What?
Prince?
Yep... in order to meet that unknown prince someday...
...girls must always be totally prepared!
Right, Mitsuki-chan?
Huh?
-chan ?
Ah.
That's right.
If you'll be gone overnight...
...I don't have to stay home, right?
Yep! I told Grandma that I'm going to a summer house with some friends from school.
Ah. What a relief!
I was thinking that you'd leave me behind again.
Is that so?
I’d have cried!
First Kiss!?
I'm going then!
Have a safe trip.
Okay!
Mitsuki-san.
Hmm?
Take this with you.
Give the letter to your friends' parents...
And give the sweets to your friends.
Yes.
Toosugiru koi no michi shirube
The road to love is far too long for me
Mou suki wo fuyasenai Non Non
There's no way for me to love you anymore. Nope, Nope!
Yume no naka wa maru de betsu sekai
It's as if the world inside my dream is a completely different one...
Wow...
Sutoreeto ni omoi mo ieru no ni
...where I can tell you how I really feel
I'm going to sing in a place like this...
I've seen it on TV before, but...
Okiniiri no fuku wo mainichi kichau no
I wear my favorite clothes every day...
...all of them are really wearing swimsuits.
Ano hito no mesen ga kocchi ni chiratsuitekimasu you ni
...so that person will turn his gaze towards me
Hey, isn't it her turn yet?
I'm pretty sure it's almost time...
I LIKE YOU no kotoba nara ieru
"I like you"  If I could bring myself to say it out loud...
Oh no!
Hey, Meroko!
I'm going to drown!
Renai soudan suru koto mo dekiru
...I would even be able to talk about love with you
Even if we drown, at least it's in the throes of love!
Cut it out!
Thank you very much...
...everyone in The
Scanty!
Well, up next... we have, for everyone...
Full Moon-san.
With her "Myself".
Go ahead!
Hey...
What should I do?
Just relax a little longer.
How many more are there?
Three.
What? It's almost over?
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
I lost way too much back then
That's why... we should just go for it.
Sure... that's...
Quiet.
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
What is it, Murakami?
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Shh!
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
On that day I could see...
Hey!
Cut it out!
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
Just a little!
Meroko!
Her song!
What?
Listen to it!
I'm listening!
Futari niteru no kana
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
You liar!
Great job.
Thanks for your help.
Let's work again sometime.
Ah, that’s right... can you
go back to the hotel?
You know where it is, right?
Yep!
It's that, right?
Eh?
Huh?
Ah, not that!
Over there, right?
Ah...
You're such a scatterbrain...
...so make sure to use a taxi.
Okay!
Well then, I'll catch up with you soon.
It's not that far...
I should try walking once in while, right?
That's right.
She was exaggerating... you can see the hotel from here.
If you do that...
...you'll get lost.
Nope, nope.
If you keep a girl sheltered...
...she won't be able to fall in love.
Love?!
That's right.
What have you been thinking about?
This is summer!
Summer is the season for love!
Right, Mitsuki?
Ah...
Huh?
Mitsuki?
Where'd you go?
The wind feels good...
Why... there's a cute girl here!
Nice... really nice!
What do you say about this girl then?
It'll work, right? Right?
Where are you going?
Eh?
All alone...
You're bored, huh?
Hey?
Why don't you have some fun with us?
No.
What? What?
What'd you just say?
I can't hear you.
Stop it...
Don't worry.
Eh?
It'll be just fine.
Come on, let's go.
No!
Mitsuki!
Come on... let's do something fun.
What? Um...
This is your first time here, right?
We know all the fun places.
Hey... won't you come with us?
What are you doing?!
Ow... ow... ow...
What kind of foolishness is this?
Do you guys...
...need another lesson?
Why are you here?!
Damn it!
You better remember this!
Are you all right?
Eh?
A-Ah... I-I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
It isn't safe for a girl to walk around alone.
I'll escort you.
Eh?!
I-It's okay!
Really?
Eh?
Then... please do.
What? What?
He looks so refined!
This might be the beginning of a good thing for her!
Well... this is as far as I'll go.
U-Um... thank you for escorting me...
I feel like I should give you something in return...
I don't want anything.
I just did what I should have done.
But...
Then, will you have a cup of tea with me?
Eh?
Well... that's...
Is that okay?
Yes.
That's great.
Shall we go then?
Ah!
This is good! This is good!
Right, Takuto?
What is?
It's starting to blossom!
Midsummer's love!
Ah... how wonderful!
Ah...
If that girl gets a boyfriend...
...Takuto will be all mine!
Meroko's...
...going to be one hundred percent behind your love!
What?!
You heard me sing today?
Yes...
It was such a beautiful song... I was amazed.
My heart is still racing.
I'm kinda embarrassed...
Come on!
Let's leave the young lovebirds alone!
Come on! Come on!
Okay? Let's go! Let's go!
Heh...
So this Eichi-kun is a very important person to you.
Yep.
I'm singing so I can see Eichi-kun again.
That's so romantic....
If I could be with a girl whose heart was as pure as yours, Full Moon-chan...
Just that... would make me happy.
Eh?
I...
...to help you to find Eichi-kun...
...want to cheer you on.
Thank you so much.
You're late!
Hmm?
Takuto?
Who is that guy?
He was all over you.
Takuto?
What are you talking about?
Yeah!
Don't ever see that guy again.
Huh?
Why are you deciding that for me?
It doesn't matter!
Murakami-san is my friend.
Are you saying I can't make friends?
So instead of listening to me...
...you're just going to trust some guy that you know nothing about?
Why are you saying that?!
Murakami-kun said he'd help me find Eichi-kun!
He's a really good person!
Eichi again.
Eh?
That's all you ever talk about.
See!
Whenever I mention Eichi-kun,
you get mad, Takuto!
Murakami-san doesn't do that!
I see.
It seems like I’m easily angered!
I'm totally different from that Murakami guy!
What's that?
What are you so mad about?!
Then, if you don't need me for anything...
Takuto!
Hey, Takuto!
Where are you going?!
Takuto! Takuto!
Geez!
What's he so mad about?
Mitsuki!
You're off today, so feel free to go have fun!
Okay!
Hey, hey.
You're finally getting a break, so don't waste it!
I'm cheering for you!
Cheering... for what?
It's not important... not important.
Takuto never came back in the end...
Even though l wanted to make up with him...
Wow!
Such great weather...!
Hmm?
Come on!
Let's go look for the guy from yesterday!
Eh?
Guy from yesterday... who?
Man... did you already forget?
Murakami-kun! Murakami-kun!
Eh?
Yo.
We bumped into each other again.
Huh?
Ah... Murakami-san...
Are you on break today?
If that's the case... I'll show you around.
If you'd like, we can ride on my yacht.
Eh?
A yacht?
Ah...
Hmph.
I understand.
I place myself in your hands.
Really?
Eh?!
That's great!
Let's head out at once!
Yes.
Hmph.
Ah...
Wow!
Over there you can see Kujiraiwa.
The one you can barely see
beyond that is Gekkojima.
There's not a cloud in the sky today, so you can see them clearly.
It must be because you're here.
Eh?
Takuto!
We've already reached the ocean!
We're finally alone!
Let's enjoy our summer vacation!
Come on... let's have fun!
What are you talking about?
We have a job to do.
Man... you're no fun.
Eh?
False Sincerity
Yacht
That is all for today.
No way!
Takuto.
Those kids just said that they were going on a yacht, right?
I forgot.
What are you saying?!
The word yacht  appeared in the handbook!
What?!
What?
Like I said... hold on.
I'm almost there.
You're telling the truth, right?
If you don't kiss her by noon today...
...we get your yacht, right?
It's sure to go well.
There's no girl who can resist me.
Don’t forget to videotape it.
I know.
Bye.
That Murakami sure can do it.
Year after year, he picks up an idol.
He always makes them cry in the end.
He deceives all of them with his looks.
At first glance... he's a good little prince.
Wow!
There are so many fishes!
How is it?
Are you having fun?
Yep!
Hmm?
I'm very happy that I get to
spend time alone with you.
Is that so?
This is the first time I've been on a yacht, so...
I'm really happy!
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way...
When are you going back, Full Moon-chan?
Right after I'm done with work tomorrow.
What...
Then... I won't be able to see you anymore...
It'll become so lonely...
That's right...
Now I'll take her.
I found a seashell!
Wow!
It's so pretty!
Amazing!
It shines like a rainbow!
Huh?
Did something happen to you, Murakami-san?
Oh, no... it's okay.
I'm totally fine.
Where are you, Mitsuki?!
She cannot hear you calling out.
What should we do then?!
Anyways... just look for her!
I'm going to look over there...
...so you go that way!
Got it!
If I don t hurry up... it'll be noon soon.
Wow!
I don't want to let you go.
Eh?
Murakami-san?
Full Moon-chan...
Um... you're making me feel uneasy.
Then... kiss me...
Eh?!
If you don't give me a kiss...
...I won't let you go back.
N-No way!
I'm sorry.
Please take me back!
Full Moon-chan!
Yes?!
Full Moon-chan...
Eh?!
A kiss?!
Murakami-san's going to kiss me?!
No way...
My first kiss is...
Full Moon...
Your shyness...
...is cute.
Don’t be scared.
You'll be fine.
Eichi-kun!
Full Moon-chan...
Man.
Don't make me worry about you.
Takuto!
What were you doing?
That's why I said...
...don't trust a guy like this!
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Take my hand.
Let's go back.
Okay!
Come on.
Hold on tight.
Okay!
Did we... just bump into each other?
Her... face is...
Takuto's lips are...
There you are!
Mitsuki!
Are you okay?!
Oh?
What... Takuto got here first?
Just cut it out and help!
Ah... okay.
Hey, hey...
Is that supposed to get us out of here?
I couldn't think of anything else!
Ah. It's here, it's here!
He's sound asleep.
Just leave him alone.
Is that okay?
What if he catches a cold...
It'll be fine.
Murakami!
Wake up, Murakami!
Who's that?
Beats me...
Uh...
Where am I? Who am I?
What are you saying, you lying jerk?!
Eh?!
Natsumi!
You've been keeping a lot from me!
You've gone on dates behind my back!
Ah... ah... that's...
Hey, you over there...
Don't believe a thing this guy says!
Eh?
What do you mean..?
This guy you know...
He boasts that he can get any
popular idol he lays his eyes on!
Eh?
To do that... he uses money and pretends to be all cool!
Right?!
Yes!
Pretend?
Then... back then...
Ah! That was a setup!
You probably bet your buddies that you could get a kiss or something off her before the day was over!
Really?
Murakami-san?
What a bastard!
Mortal enemy of all women!
Mitsuki...
You are the worst!
U-Um...
Eh?!
I'm not going to forgive you for an act like that!
Sa-Save me!
I... can't swim!
So uncool...
Hehe!
Natsumi!
Serves you right!
Women are scary.
I was so sure that he was a good person.
You trust people too easily.
Dummy.
Dummy?!
Geez!
Hmph.
That's fine.
I don’t care if I was tricked!
I don't want to be the kind of
person who's always paranoid!
Why you...
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
Hey you!
Are you listening to me?!
Calm down... calm down...
Shove it!
Hey!
You little brat!
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
That was an accident, right?
It was definitely an accident!
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
That place you had to leave for a while...
Sukoshi hanareta basho
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Until we became so far apart...
Preview
I can't take it!
What's with that girl?!
What are you all excited about, Meroko?
Do you remember Wakamatsu Madoka?
She's the one from the Seed Record New Artist audition.
...who lost to Mitsuki, but...
...to have her as a rival now... I just can't stand it!
Hey, hey.
You're going with her today, right?
Will you be all right?
Ah!
Just leave it to me.
This Meroko-sama here is going to
support her perfectly!
That's what I'm most worried about.
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
A Rival Appears!
Look forward to it!