This button...
means that Kanata is in this world, right?
Could he really be here?
He has to be!
Let's find him!
Calm down, Haruka.
It's already dark out.
Besides, we won't find him so easily without a lead.
But...
Prince Kanata, where could you be?
Let's ask the stars!
The stars?
Astrology, eh?
La bonne idée.
"Lost sheep seek direction from la stars."
It's le old adage from Hope Kingdom.
Tell us, O stars,
where is Kanata?
Le Prince...
is in chocolate!
Chocolate? Why that?
Well, it's what la stars prophesied...
I'm back!
How was work, Kirara?
Great, glad you're all here.
'Cause I brought a souvenir!
What kind?
A pick-me-up from the staff.
They're chocolates!
Really?!
Um... yes?
Chocolate Princess Contest
Seeking Entrants
Princess Contest...
Chocolate Princess Contest
Seeking Entrants
They're seeking entrants?
And we can meet a prince?
There's no mistake...
Huh?
A prince!
Kanata!
With strength, grace, and beauty!
The tale of four girls who strive to become true princesses!
Follow your dreams and Go! Princess Precure!
Gently spread your wings, princess, and chase your dreams!
Keep at it, and happiness is yours! Make a miracle and go! Princess Precure
Every smile's a jewel, and every girl a princess
Let's open the door and go with a laugh
Even in the rain, we say "Bonjour!" as baddies try to ruin our day
We'll beat them up and stay true to ourselves
With your passion burning bright beneath your ribbon
Everything will be all right
Do your best, princess, and let no plight get the best of you
You're not alone! You're together! Fight hand in hand!
Spread your wings, princess, and the light of hope will always be with you
Say goodbye to your tears and shine upon the future, Princess Precure
I get it now...
Haruharu got the fortune, so why not have her enter?
M-Me?
I'll give it a shot!
It's our only clue to finding Kanata.
Besides, a princess contest sounds kinda splendid!
Don't think it'll be so easy!
Good luck, Haruka!
Thanks!
Simply Doomed!
Haruka's Princess Contest!
Dear Haruno Haruka,
As a result of our preliminary judging...
you're accepted!
Hooray!
Huh?
Really?
It says the next panel will be at Dreamy Shore Hall.
Isn't that...
the stage where Kirara had her last show?
Entrants are to dress as princesses and walk on stage.
Walk?
You know, like how a model walks on a runway.
Huh?
Whaaaa?!
There's no way I can do that! Nuh-uh!
Oh, Brother...
Where'd all that motivation go?
I'm too nervous to model on such a huge stage...
Then let me help.
I can teach you how to walk like a pro!
Kirara!
You're always like my cheerleader, Haruharu.
Now it's my turn to be yours.
Got it! I'll try to keep up!
Then your lessons start tomorrow.
In between work, of course!
She's truly a professional!
Okay Haruharu, you try!
O-Okay!
Relax! Try to walk naturally.
Walk naturally...
Lift your chin!
Stand up straight!
Move your head, arms, and hips in one fluid motion!
Take longer strides!
Her advice is spot on.
Haruka's gait is rapidly improving!
And smile!
Just like that, Haruharu!
Okay, now try it in these!
I didn't know being a model was so hard!
Now try to master the walk
you did before in these heels.
Practice makes perfect!
Okay!
I'm still bad at makeup!
Well, you can't be an expert overnight.
Oh, fine.
I'll do it for you before the show.
Really?
Well, I've got a shoot that morning, so I'll be cutting it close.
But you know...
makeup's important, but nothing makes a girl cuter than a smile.
A smile...
No makeup's thick enough to make a frown look upside down.
Done!
Yep, it's A-okay!
Okay, wave your hand!
Wow...
Quick makeup fix!
Hey, we need to make that necklace stand out a bit more...
Good point...
What should we do?
No biggie.
How's this?
Love it!
Break time, everyone!
That was so cool!
Yeah, shows never go off without a hitch.
They don't?
Nope. Sometimes the shoes come in the wrong size, or something you expect to have gets lost.
When something goes wrong, you've just gotta use what you've got to deal with it on the spot.
Huh? What'll I do then?
Don't worry!
You've got me with you!
And what an honor it is, Madame Kirara!
Just leave it to me!
So good luck tomorrow!
When you step on stage, there's no turning back.
Keep your chin up and show them your biggest smile 'til the end!
Promise me, 'kay?
Sure!
Omigosh, it's Kirara!
Can I shake your hand?
I read all your magazines!
Can I have an autograph?
You're so cute!
Okay, one at a time.
Kirara, I'm gonna head back, okay?
Sure!
What?
You gave a fan an autograph, huh?
You never used to do that.
Sometimes the mood strikes me.
Also...
Also what?
It's nice to have people supporting you...
I guess I have those girls to thank.
Huh?
Stella was telling me earlier that ever since you made friends, you've gotten a bit sweeter.
Yeah, right!
Today's another day of my flawless makeup!
I'm always so—
Oh, Stop and Freeze!
Would you like to try some makeup?
It will naught but imbue you with power!
But with masks like those, I doubt you'd understand!
Makeup's the best...
Can makeup imbue one with power?
Can it?
It's huge!
Haruka must be nervous.
I'd imagine. I just hope she can stay focused while on stage.
I'm worried too...
so why don't we all write for her?
This is a problem. We'll have to postpone the shoot.
What now? I won't make it in time!
Haruharu...
Wha?!
It doesn't fit at all!
U-Um, this dress is too big...
Sorry, that size is all we have left...
But...
Excuse me!
Coming!
I'm really sorry!
This is bad...
Kirara, what do I do?
Okay!
That's it for today!
Kirara, want to join us all for tea—
Sorry, I've gotta get going now!
Thanks for having me!
Wait for me, Haruharu!
Makeup, is it?
Makeup, it is.
Who are you?
It's them!
You have a dream?
Show it to us.
I want to make women everywhere beautiful!
We'll seal your dream in the cage of despair!
Stop!
Freeze!
Your dream!
Go, Dyspairvil!
Dyspairvil!
I do not have time for this!
Precure!
Princess Engage!
The Princess of Shining Stars!
Cure Twinkle!
Perf Change!
Aroma Change!
Wh-What brought this on?
So you can transform on your own now?
We just sensed a Dyspairvil!
It's Dysdark!
Dys Dys!
Dyspair...
Dyspair!
Are you okay?
Girls!
Dyspairvil.
Kirara still isn't here...
which means something must have happened to her!
Shows never go off without a hitch.
I have to deal with this myself...
Number 18, follow me!
It's almost my turn!
What would Kirara do at a time like this?
Vil!
Dyspair!
How's Haruharu?
She'll be on stage soon!
Let's combine our strength so we can return at once!
We've gotta hurry!
Dyspair... vil!
Dyspair.
I've got the dress fixed up...
But next is makeup.
I have to do it my—
Number 20, this way!
She's already here!
Vil!
Dyspair...
Twinkle!
Precure!
Bubble Ripple!
Scarlet Spark!
Dyspairvil!
I can't lose!
Haruharu's waiting for me!
Dyspairviiiiiiil!
Next is entrant number 20, Miss Haruno Haruka!
Haruka...
I didn't get to do my makeup...
Yui!
Minami and Towa aren't here...
Something must have happened...
Haruka!
Blow-roma
them away!
We're with you!
-Yui
Haruno Haruka
SMILE!!
I await your performance. -Akagi Towa
Don't worry, we are watching.
If you get stage fright, just remember how at school we all
so don't worry!
though I wonder if you can even read this from the stage... -Minami
A smile trumps makeup...
Dyspairvil.
This one's stubborn.
Darn it, I'll miss the show!
Why'd it have to be today?! Geez!
Twinkle!
Dyspairvil!
Haruharu?!
Dyspair!
Sorry, I know I said to leave it to me...
Twinkle, I went on stage!
It didn't go off without a hitch,
but I kept my smile 'til the end!
Great!
Dyspair.
Vil!
Lily!
Dance, O Lilies!
Precure!
Lys Tourbillon!
And your advice helped me do it!
Thanks, Twinkle!
Flora...
Let's go!
Right!
Dyspair!
Now!
Mode Elegant!
Cherry Blossom!
Coral!
Galaxy!
Sun!
Dress Up Premium!
Let our powers ring!
Precure!
Eclat Espoir!
Dreaming...
Adieu.
The dream did not end.
We failed to end it.
However...
you despaired.
Open!
The door to your dream!
And our award for the crowd favorite goes to...
Miss Haruno Haruka!
Whaaaa?!
The Chocolate Prince will now present a bouquet to the winners.
He's the prince they meant?
But Haruka was really pretty!
Huh...
I always thought that girl was something special...
but Haruka might have more in her than I ever gave her credit for.
But in the end, we still didn't find Kanata!
We couldn't expect it to go that well.
Kanata?
If the path to a future you want to see
is what we all call a dream,
then chase it with your friends by your side
Let's go, bonjour!
Let's go, Twinkle!
When the shimmering stars dance
the night sky seems like a twinkling barrier
But if you leap into the spotlight
The chance to show your courage today
is there to change your tomorrow
Come on, Grand Princess!
A dream fulfilled only leads to the next
So go! They're waiting for you
Come on, Grand Princess!
The world looks its best when brimming with happiness
Use the key of hope to spread the joy!
Let's go, Princess Precure!
We found Kanata! We found him!
Go! Princess Precure:
We Finally Meet!
Kanata and His Lost Memories!
Go say bonjour to your dream!
Watch Us Again!
Chiba Prefecture - Miu (Age 5)
Saitama Prefecture - Sena (Age 4)