It is the Sengoku Era
A time of war
Several hundred years ago
That's pretty weak.
Like child's play.
You must be crazy, trying to follow the way of the sword with skills like that.
I'm sorry to say this kid, but you've got no talent for the sword at all.
You've got no muscle, no form, and most importantly, you lack the resolve to kill.
If you want to get better with a sword, the first thing you have to do is kill.
A swordsman is still only halfway to maturity after killing 300 people.
Right now, you wouldn't even be able to cut a leaf...
I took the time out of my busy schedule to take a trip to the capital's suburbs for this?
Maybe I'm losing it too...
I guess I panicked when I lost sight of my path.
Path?
From perfection to completion.
Perfection to completion?
What does that mean?
Exactly what the words say.
Well, seeing as you're nowhere near perfection, let alone completion,
it's probably just rambling from your amateur point of view.
I know my skills are amateur.
That's why I'm training like this.
I admire your dedication, at least.
But kid, if you keep dawdling around like that, the war's going to end.
Huh?
Though if you're cooped up on a mountain like this, you probably don't know anything about the world.
I don't care.
Oh?
The only thing that interests me is honing my own skills.
I aim to master the way of the sword.
The country may be at war or at peace, but the path ahead of me will not change.
What's so funny?
I was just thinking that your dedication really is all I can admire.
And I find it interesting how you don't care about the world.
I originally thought this was a pointless trip, but it looks like you might just barely pass...
What?
I also have no interest in the world.
What I'm fighting is, in a way... history, I guess?
If you look at the world and everything in it from the perspective of history, all you see is the surface of it.
What's with you...
Are you a megalomaniac or something?
That might not be entirely wrong...
Well, most people probably see me that way.
That's why I have to fight for results.
Even then, as close as I get, it still isn't enough.
Maybe it really is a problem with the raw materials...
That aspect of it is really just luck.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I guess I didn't tell you.
I'm a swordsmith.
And what does a swordsmith want with me?
Kid, I'm going to take all that passionate effort of yours and make it blossom into flowers.
Of course, whether or not the roots also grow will be entirely up to you...
Yasuri Kazune.
This happened several hundred years ago,
when the country was at war, a time now called the Sengoku period.
Now it is but an ancient tale.
It was the beginning of the story of the man who would later found Kyotouryuu, Yasuri Kazune,
and the swordsmith of legend, Shikizaki Kiki.
meguriatta ga un no tsuki
巡り逢ったが運の尽き
Our encounter becomes thy fortune's end
Mazui
presents
Katana-
gatari
harari koboreochiru
ハラリ 零れ落ちる
Though words doth joined
kotoba tsuranetatote
言葉 連ねたとて
From my lips run over
dare mo watashi ni aru makoto fure mo dekin jaro
誰もわたしに在る真 触れも出来んじゃろ
Can yet any convey the truth I hold?
sakura mau ga gotoku
サクラ 舞うが如く
As cherry blossoms doth dance
konjou to wa osaraba
今生とはおさらば
To this life I bid farewell
saredo oya ni moratta
されど親に貰った
Indeed this body, parent-hatched,
kono mi ga kawaii
この身が可愛い
I cherish duly
inochi yori omoi
命より重い
But graver than life,
bebe matoi warau
ベベ纏い微笑う
Here, smile-clad
kizu wa taenu kenka joutou
傷は絶えぬ喧嘩上等
Put forth battle, such my scars not fade
kakugoshiiya
覚悟しいや
Ready I stand
nuite wa modosu katana to saya tachikiru ha shura
抜いては戻す 刀と鞘 断ち斬るは修羅
To draw is to return, the sword and sheath, to cut what is the battle
sono sakeme ni ochita yume no harawata ha muzan zo
その裂け目に堕ちた夢の腑は無惨ぞ
The heart of the dream abyss-fallen lies bestial
ai mamiete tagiraseru chi wo wakeaeru nara
相まみえて滾らせる血を分け合えるなら
If we share such seething blood as we face,
itoshii sonata todome wo
愛し其方 止めを
Then, my love,
sashitekunnamashi
刺してくんなまし
Deliver the finishing blow
hana no sakari ga oshii kae
花の盛りが惜しいかえ
Dost thou lament the flowers' bloom?
Dokutou
Mekki
Gild,
the Poison
Zettou Kanna.
Zantou Namakura.
Sentou Tsurugi.
Hakutou Hari.
Zokutou Yoroi.
Soutou Kanazuchi.
Akutou Bita.
Bitou Kanzashi.
Outou Nokogiri.
Seitou Hakari.
And with that, we've managed to collect ten of Shikizaki Kiki's Perfected Deviant Blades.
Though it took us ten whole months...
No, it's amazing that we did it so fast.
Really?
It's a feat that Shogun Kyuu and many others failed at.
Consider that in such a short time we've already assembled ten of them.
Of course, I was sure it was possible to begin with because of my superior intellect.
Sometimes I even scare myself with the extent of my skills.
Skills?
Did your strategies ever actually win us the swords?
Cheerio!
Most of them were taken by force...
That's also a part of my strategies!
My role was figuring out how to use you, the sword, the most effectively.
And are you any good at that?
I already said that what we've done is amazing!
Is it?
That's fine then.
As long as you remain my sword, I'm sure everything will go well.
Oh!
Look, a tea stalk is standing.
That's a good omen.
It's like a blessing on the remainder of our journey.
It's just a tea stalk...
You only have to look at good omens whenever things are going well.
Is that how it works?
That's how it works.
The remainder of our journey...
That's right, there isn't much left, is there...
I'll let you play with my hair tonight.
There isn't much to play with.
What?
So that's who you really are, Strategian Togame...
You know, I truly hate you, from the bottom of my heart.
Regardless of if you were important or not, or weren't scheming anything in the shadows, I was planning to smash you anyway.
I intended to go to war with you...
I even felt a strange bond with you in that regard.
Well, I still intend to, but that's precisely why...
I didn't want to settle things with you like this.
What a pity, Strategian.
I truly can't stand your carelessness.
Oushuu
Dewa
Impassable.
I figured you'd appear here if I waited, Maniwa Houou.
And Maniwa Pengin too.
Allow me to introduce myself first.
I am Souda Emonzaemon,
the man who will kill you.
In case you're wondering, I killed Maniwa Oshidori.
As well as Maniwa Umigame.
So you're the one responsible...
Do you understand your situation, Maniwa Houou?
Of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads, you are the only two remaining.
H-Houou-sama...
It would be really pathetic if you truly thought you could scare us with such talk.
Ninja live and die, that is all.
You haven't changed.
Nothing about you has changed at all, Houou.
I haven't changed?
You make it sound as though you knew me from long ago.
Surely you must know by now.
No, I'm sure you already knew when we met in Izu.
I can't let that one just go...
However, what's even more inexcusable is a name like "Souda Emonzaemon".
If you really are who I think you are, then you should announce your name straight up, with pride.
Unfortunately, that is my real name now.
I am different from you.
You certainly have changed.
Get back.
You can't use your ninpou in a place like this.
Okay...
Please be careful, Houou-sama...
This is the man who killed Umigame-sama and Oshidori-sama...
He's no pushover.
I know that.
His strength is probably on par with mine.
Undeniable.
That's quite funny.
Our skills are on par?
Of course they are.
Aioi Kenpo didn't work on Umigame and Oshidori, so pardon me if I skip that step.
I'm not even a swordsman to begin with.
That's true...
Hold this.
No specialized weapons.
Agreed?
Ah... Emonzaemon, was it?
Right, Emonzaemon.
A contest of pure skill and discipline of the body...
I like the sound of that!
He's trading blows equally with Houou-sama...
But if Houou-sama can get within range...
Danzaien!
Houou-sama, use Ninpou: Danzaien!
Oh? So you call that move "Danzaien"?
Maniwa Pengin.
The Ninpou that you call Danzaien was called Namagoroshi by the Aioi Clan.
Ninpou
Namagoroshi
N-Namagoroshi?
And now I call it Shinobazuhou Ikasazukorosazu.
TL note: No sneaking, no sparing, no killing
Shinobazuhou Ikasazukorosazu
No way... he's...
It's quite ironic, Houou.
You are an excellent ninja.
Even were you to be the sole surviving Maniwa Corps head, that would be more than enough to make the Maniwa Corps a threat.
Nonetheless, I do not feel that I can lose to you.
Because you are me.
I died once.
Not physically, but mentally died.
But one person denied me that death—my current master.
And now I put all my soul into following her orders.
So it's true, your master is that princess.
You only know now?
Well Emonzaemon, if you claim that you are me, then I am also you.
As we continue fighting, I may not defeat you, but I will not lose to you either.
Possibly.
They were once friends with each other...
They learned Ninpou from each other...
They dealt and saw death beside each other...
H-Houou-sama!
H-Here!
Please use this!
That was a mistake
Wh-What...
Houou-sama!
H-Houou-sama?
Dewa
Hey...
Is he alive?
It's a sword wound.
This is...
H-Help...
Please help...
It doesn't matter what happens to me...
But please save Houou-sama...
Could this be a trap?
Change of plans.
We're going to find an inn nearby.
Daikokuya
Inn
Houou-sama took the sword and headed for Iga...
Why would he wound one of his allies?
Houou-sama has gone insane...
Dokutou Mekki...
P-Please!
I understand! Sleep for now!
H-Houou-sama...
Please save Houou-sama!
Several days later
Houou-sama...
Assuming what this boy says is true,
we can't afford to stick around much longer.
I still don't trust him though.
He's not telling the whole truth,
and there might still be a trap somewhere in this.
Yeah...
Well, knowing the Maniwa Corps, that wouldn't be surprising.
And is this guy really a Maniwani to begin with?
I can guarantee that.
He is one of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads, Maniwa Pengin of the fish squad.
He's the ninja that was feared the second most amongst the 12 heads, after Maniwa Houou.
This guy, huh?
I heard he wields a Ninpou that may someday surpass even Maniwa Houou.
Really...
It's strange that he's recovering so slowly.
I suppose that's Dokutou Mekki's focus.
His speech has also gotten strange.
He's always talked that way.
Really?
Pengin's Ninpou is one beyond that which even his own body can stand.
Apparently that's the reason he developed such an un-ninja-like personality.
You know a lot about him...
I heard about it from Koumori.
Well, we can't just stay here forever.
Let's go.
I won't disagree that this may be a trap, but our objective from the start has been collecting swords.
If Maniwa Houou has gotten a hold of Dokutou Mekki then we have to go after him anyway.
And this is far simpler than having to come up with tricky negotiations or whatnot.
That's too tight, idiot!
Ah, sorry.
So what do we do with him?
Just leave him here?
Well, given how he looks, I'm sure the innkeeper won't just throw him out onto the street.
So that's your reasoning...
I didn't mean that though.
He belongs to the Maniwa Corps, our enemy...
Shouldn't we just deal with him now?
You mean kill him here?
It's true they're our enemy...
But I don't enjoy killing with no reason.
I'm not one who enjoys bloodshed.
We could use it as a negotiating point.
And even if the Maniwa Corps don't recognize that, we can call upon it as a debt.
And at some point after our sword collection journey is over we can claim that debt.
There are several reasons why he might be useful alive.
Ah...
Alright, let's head out.
Our target is the New Maniwa village.
So they're headed for the New Maniwa village?
They're probably around Tokaido right now then.
Well, go finish off the last of your duties, at least.
It'll be hard, though.
I don't know how strong Kyotouryuu is,
but my ancestor is very, very strong.
He has powers that weren't passed down even to me.
So at least die beautifully for me.
If we stop by Owari, I'll be obligated to visit the castle.
And that would mean having to face that princess.
Sounds troublesome...
Yes, troublesome.
So right now, working alone, or rather, with you, is far easier and more constructive.
So, this New Maniwa village...
I'd never have guessed it'd be in Iga.
That's the place where the Shogunate originally kept its secret service headquarters.
Right under our noses...
Come to think of it, this is my first time in Kansai, oddly enough.
I guess you could say it's surprising, but all we did was stay in the capital at the beginning for a bit, right?
Well...
We started on the island you grew up on, Fushou.
Then Inaba, Izumo, Ganryuu Island, Satsuma, Ezo, Tosa,
Edo, Dewa, Mutsu...
And now Iga.
If you include the in-between traveling, we've pretty much toured the entirety of Japan.
Though I guess we only touched on the Hokuriku region.
When this sword collection journey is over, it might be fun visiting there again together.
And then we can draw a map of the whole country and sell it.
You already know I'm good at drawing maps, right?
There are plenty of maps based on sketchy measurements out there,
but this would be the first ever precisely drawn atlas of the whole country.
I'm sure it'd sell for a lot.
Well wait, we still need to find the 12th sword first.
I already have a pretty good guess of where Entou Jyuu is.
As well as its owner.
If you think about it, Princess Hitei has been pretty proactive about this sword collection.
It wouldn't be strange if she were to keep one for herself nearby.
Given that Emonzaemon has been going around killing the Maniwani,
it's logical to assume that she currently holds Entou.
I see...
But why wouldn't she tell us that?
Things always seem rather peaceful in your head, as well as simple.
If she keeps at least one of the Perfected Deviant Blades in reserve, she'll still have a hand in negotiating with us.
If she plays her hand right, it's possible she might even steal credit for the entire thing.
It's exactly the same plan that the Maniwa Corps had.
Well, knowing her, I'm sure her intentions aren't so simple as just stealing the spotlight.
Perhaps she's planning some strategy to destroy me.
She's already interfered a bunch of times over the course our journey...
Those little trip-ups were nothing but playing around for her.
When that woman makes her real move, it won't be pretty.
Of course, the same goes for me.
Either ways, if our final opponent is Princess Hitei, then it'll be business as usual for me.
As usual?
Right.
That's why I said our sword collection journey is almost over.
Hey, Shichika...
Are you going to stay by my side even after this journey's over?
Unlike Princess Hitei, I've never had a confidant or right hand man for any long period of time.
They'd only have gotten in my way.
That's why I've trusted no one, and lived my life destroying any personal relations I'd made.
The countless times I've tried to beat Princess Hitei also has that kind of purpose, on top of self-defense.
But I don't want to do the same to you.
Originally I only intended to keep you as a partner for the duration of the sword collection journey...
But with the Maniwa Corps and Sabi Hakuhei gone, I need your power.
Our sword collection is almost done, but my own fight isn't over yet.
In fact, the road after we finish collecting them all might be even tougher.
That's why I need your power...
I need the peace I feel when I'm with you!
So, Yasuri Shichika...
I want you to be my trusted partner!
But...
I'm Yasuri Mutsue's son, you know?
Yeah...
The son of the Yasuri Mutsue who killed your father.
So what?
It's not like you killed him.
When Yasuri Mutsue died, any grudge I had against Kyotouryuu died with him.
In fact, when you consider that he died by your hand, it's all the more reason!
Regardless of that, I have no reason to hold any grudge against you!
Am I wrong?
Well, it's not like I have anywhere to return to, anyway.
And Nee-chan's dead too.
If you want to continue keeping me with you, I don't need any other reason.
Also...
I fell for you.
Really?
Alright, let's go then!
Okay!
And so they made quick progress towards Iga.
However, they had no way of knowing that historically, the end of any journey is the end of everything.
H-Houou-sama!
Houou-sama!
Houou-sama?
Houou?
You're mistaken.
I am Shikizaki Kiki!
That strategian...
That witch left me alone...
Not only did she not kill me,
she didn't even bother breaking my legs or anything...
In the past she'd never be this lenient.
That woman is rotten to the core.
Everything, from the way she acts to the things she says, are cold and calculated.
To her, we're nothing but numbers in her formula.
It's not even funny...
Has that Kyotouryuu changed the strategian?
I have to return to the Maniwa village!
Unallowable.
I don't see the strategian or Kyotouryuu anywhere...
It seems I missed them.
Well, whatever.
I'll catch up to them soon enough if I run.
B-Because of you, Houou-sama has—
Because of me?
You're correct, but I don't think you can accuse me of anything.
We are enemies, after all.
Maniwa Pengin...
You are a child, so some may believe it appropriate to grant you lenience and let you go.
But I see things differently.
If I leave a ninja with such an unpredictable temperament alive, you will undoubtedly be troublesome sometime in the future.
I must act for the sake of the Princess.
With Maniwa Houou in that state, the only choice I have now is to destroy the Maniwa Corps entirely.
Well, this is my judgment to make, in the end.
I did not expect you to act as you did, Maniwa Pengin.
And that is why I will allow no hesitation in facing you.
I will use Entou Jyuu from the start.
E-Entou?
I missed?
No, he made me miss...
It's useless.
As long as that Entou shoots projectiles, it's useless against me.
That's my ninpou, Unmei Kuzushi!
Note: Fate ruination
Unmei Kuzushi
I see...
You remain living as you are, even when attacked.
You have great luck... no...
Your luck is strong enough to defy even logic.
I understand now why you were chosen as one of the 12 Maniwa Corps heads.
This is the decisive moment...
If I can come out the winner of this fight, I'll be able to obtain one of Shikizaki Kiki's swords.
Regardless of how strong they are, it's a fact that projectile weapons won't work on me.
The bullets themselves dodge me.
So it's limited to projectiles?
In other words, that ninpou doesn't make you invincible?
That's not my only ninpou!
Oh?
They call me "Pengin the multiplier".
Do you know why?
No idea.
Can you use cloning techniques or something?
Close, but not quite!
I was wondering what it'd be...
This weapon is called Juukyuu.
It seems to move slowly to start...
Wha—
I see.
It's a move that complements your Unmei Kuzushi.
Juukyuu will continue to accelerate.
You won't be able to dodge it forever!
So it would seem.
It's useless.
Maniwa Pengin.
Are you confident that the world will continue to love you hundreds of years into the future, as it does now?
I'm saying that the fate of history is not something that can be so easily broken!
Looks like three hit.
Well, fair enough.
H-How...
Of course, I got the idea from your Juukyuu technique.
I figured that if I ricocheted bullets like your Juukyuu, some might hit you.
Ricochet? In this room?
Unerroneous.
Iron will deflect iron.
If the love fate had for you were to last forever, the bullets would have probably rebounded towards me instead.
I'm afraid that your luck did not last hundreds of years into the future after all.
Wh-What are you saying?
Unnecessary.
There is no need for you to understand.
Do not worry.
I will finish you now.
If you have any last words, I will hear them now.
I-I don't want to die!
I didn't want this fight!
You must surely be the first one in history to die with such pathetic words!
Several days later
Iga
The New Maniwa village...
This is terrible...
Why did he do this?
Your sister isn't the only one who can demolish a village.
I knew the Maniwa Corps were in fairly desperate straits...
But to think even the women and children were slaughtered...
This is beyond insane.
What's wrong?
There he is!
That was close.
For a moment, I thought that sword was Dokutou Mekki.
A Perfected Deviant Blade forged by Shikizaki Kiki would never look so normal.
Togame, this guy must be hiding Dokutou somewhere.
Indeed, it would appear so.
It must just be a coincidence that the black sword he has matches the description Pengin gave us.
There's no way one of Shikizaki Kiki's swords could look so plain.
I figured it'd be some kind of liquid sword. What do you think?
I see... not bad reasoning.
I can hear you, you know.
Having fun running off your mouths?
And at my beloved swords, no less.
It seems that no matter the era, young folks will always be rude.
"Young"?
Hey, you!
Are you really Maniwa Houou?
No, I'm not.
I am Shikizaki Kiki.
Are you screwing with us?!
It's hard to believe what he says, but Houou was never one to joke around.
Seems that way.
His memories tell me likewise.
You must be the "strategian".
You have quite a colorful method of fighting.
I like that type of thing.
It is my humble pleasure to make your acquaintance...
...I suppose should be my line, right?
Shikizaki Kiki-dono.
Right.
Though, the memory of you that this guy has is a bit a different from the one I see now.
You cut your hair?
What a waste.
You look like a kid now.
It's true that I haven't met Houou since my hair was cut...
Is this guy really Shikizaki, Togame?
It looks like the body is still Houou though.
Well basically, after being moved from place to place, I've finally managed to get a convenient body.
Is that Dokutou Mekki's focus?
A preserved record of your memories...
I want to say it should be impossible, but I'm too shocked.
Well, it's something like a dose of deadly poison.
"Houou" signifies an immortal bird.
It is the height of irony that a long-dead swordsmith has been resurrected in such a body.
Note: Life Binding
This guy's ninpou is called "Inochi Musubi".
He steals parts from various people and uses those to lengthen his lifespan.
And not just the physical parts or the techniques either.
He also takes their personalities.
He borrows them temporarily.
Kind of like gilding over his own existence and letting it harden.
So isn't it natural that he would get taken over by someone like me in the end?
He brought it upon himself.
By the way, Shikizaki-dono...
What exactly were you planning to accomplish by calling us here?
Calling?
Stop playing games.
You used Maniwa Pengin as a messenger!
He did?
Ah, yeah, I guess.
Why did you leave Pengin on that road?
That was part of my predictions.
Predictions?
Not predictions, but rather, foresight.
I'm actually a soothsayer.
Wh-What did you just say?
You didn't hear me?
A soothsayer. I'm a soothsayer.
I simply foresaw that you'd pass through that road.
So you're like a prophet?
Right.
There was a time I lived on that.
Actually, the Shikizaki family has been one of soothsayers for generations.
I find it difficult to believe you when you call yourself something as vague as a soothsayer.
Maybe he just got lucky?
That would be far easier for me to accept.
Oh really?
But think about it, strategian.
If what I say is true, then doesn't it explain the Deviant Blades I created?
Or rather, if you don't believe me, it's impossible to explain them.
H-Hey, what's he talking about?
Not just the Perfected Deviant Blades...
He created all thousand Deviant Blades by reverse importing production techniques he learned by looking into the future!
The future?!
Reverse importing??
That's why to us, in this age, it seems like they have special focuses that surpass the laws of physics!
Precisely. You live up to your strategian title.
Well, as surprising as it is, I suppose it's not entirely unexpected.
No wait, that's definitely unexpected!
There's no other way to explain it.
The limits of physics aren't something that can be broken so simply.
Exactly.
At their core, the Deviant Blades are just regular Japanese swords, except they also exploit physics and psychology.
So why did you create swords like those?
Huh?
You told us you came from a household of fortune tellers.
So I did.
Fortune tellers are supposed to at best give hints about the future,
but you had a hand in it by deliberately scattering the Deviant Blades throughout the country.
As it happens, my goal has always been to alter history.
Alter?
Or maybe it'd be easier to understand if I said "falsify"?
That has always been the goal of my family.
For what purpose?
In order to overthrow the Shogunate of the original history.
Though personally, I don't really care...
The Shogunate of the original history?
The Itezora family and the Maniwa Corps were both theoretical possibilities that never actually existed in the original history.
And probably, you too...
Strategian Togame.
T-Togame?
My father gave his life for the sake of restoring the history you altered back to its original state!
Oh?
Someone outside of the Shikizaki family realized it?
Hey!!
Are you trying to say that Kyotouryuu should never have existed?
Oh, Kyotouryuu?
You're different.
You're a sword that I created, after all.
You met Higaki, right?
He must have told you then.
Kyotouryuu is the final Deviant Blade that I created,
the Completed Deviant Blade, Kyotou Yasuri.
The founder, Yasuri Kazune, didn't reach a complete state,
but the foundations he laid weren't for naught.
After all, Yasuri Shichika...
He succeeded in producing the sword that you are now.
You knew the founder?
I didn't just know him, he was my closest friend.
Though, he was kind of an idiot who had no interest in history or anything besides swords.
But thanks to him, the forging of my Deviant Blades is now completed.
Come on, don't glare at me like that, Kyotouryuu.
I can't thank him enough.
Besides, I'm kind of like your father too.
The only father I have is my Dad!
What a heartless guy.
That's fine, though.
No one really needs to care about their origins.
You live only your own life, after all.
That doesn't apply to people who are already dead.
For about an year, I traveled through every nook and cranny of this country,
following your Perfected Deviant Blades that you apparently made with techniques from the future,
and figured I had experienced the majority of what awaited me...
But though I never imagined I'd meet their creator at the end,
when I think about it, it's a very sequential, even ordinary way for things to have transpired.
I've met a holy man, and could probably even meet ghosts.
This plot is turning into a bore,
so I probably won't even mention you when I hand in my report to my superiors.
What a cruel thing to say.
Isn't that also falsifying history in its own way?
This is a stance that a genius swordsman will come up with in about 150 years.
It's a form that surpasses even Sabi Hakuhei's.
The three-pronged attack that comes from this stance is supposed to be undodgable.
What do we do in this situation?
That's obvious.
What we need to do hasn't changed.
Negotiations have already failed.
Yasuri Shichika, my right hand...
Attack and plunder!
Order acknowledged!
Kyotou Yasuri...
Hold nothing back and cut at me with your full strength.
Test yourself on this body!
It's not even your body!
But it is my history.
Show me everything you've got.
I was going to anyway.
However, by that point you'll be torn into pieces!
Let the match...
Begin!
What's wrong, Kyotou Yasuri?
Surely that's not all a Completed blade has to offer!
Don't let me down!
Shichika!
Shichika! Shichika!
What's this? Is that the limit of your strength?
Shichika!
You're a well-sharpened sword.
This isn't your full strength is it, Kyotouryuu?
I see... I understand that future sword style of yours now.
I can't let my guard down.
This is my special move.
Let's see you dodge it!
Shichika!
Sorry, but...
It's still no match for Kyotouryuu!
Shichika Hachiretsu...
Kai!
Ryuuryoku
Kakou
Kyouka
Suigetsu
Rakka
Rouzeki
Hyakka
Ryouran
Kinjou
Tenka
Kachou
Fuugetsu
I-I see...
Not bad at all...
Hey, I don't really get it, but...
Was that really Shikizaki Kiki?
I wonder.
It may just have been Maniwa Houou gone insane.
Then the only remaining Maniwa is that Pengin guy?
Pengin, huh...
It'd be nice if he were still alive.
It's nothing we can change.
The reality is, the Shogunate has branded the Maniwa Corps as traitors.
No matter what their intentions might have actually been,
if Emonzaemon acts on the authority of Internal Affairs, I can't oppose him.
You almost sound as though you'd rather Pengin weren't killed.
Though, I've always said there's no room for sympathy.
It's nothing I'd have said to Shikizaki Kiki, but when I saw the carnage in that village...
It's not like I didn't feel for them.
Not just the Maniwa Corps, either.
In this past year, we've traveled all over Japan.
And we've seen various people in various places.
I've come to realize how narrow-sighted I was.
I really didn't know anything.
That's not like you.
After we descend from here, we'll soon be in Owari...
We managed to make it before sundown.
Yeah...
Let's hurry, then.
What are you doing, idiot?
You're my trusted partner now, right?
Yeah, but...
Trusted partners are supposed to hold their master's hand when they walk!
Really?
Yeah!
I thought you weren't supposed to say that until the very end, in order to keep me alert and on the ready.
You've also changed quite a bit during this journey this past year.
You've come to know of society and the world,
and you've gained knowledge and resolve.
You really have grown.
And while it may not be to the same extent as you, I've also changed during this year-long journey.
Not only that, I've also experienced many things for the first time on this journey.
Stop grinning like that, it's weird!
You're grinning too, you know.
I am not!
The Princess is as sharp as ever.
She predicted when we'd arrive here and made her move first.
Well, that's fine.
It saves us time, since we can cut to the chase.
If she made the first move, we just have to return it with our own.
Shichika, the political war begins now.
I can't really help you out then...
Standing steady by my side is enough.
I see.
Yo, Emonzaemon-dono.
I suppose I should thank you for coming to meet us?
As you can see, we've successfully procured Dokutou Mekki.
Shouldn't you have something to say to me at this point in time?
I guess you're right.
I'm not the Princess from back then, but allow me to congratulate you.
You've managed to take one more step towards fulfilling your ambitions.
Ambitions?
I don't recall ever having any.
Really?
Then maybe I should call it revenge?
Daughter of the former Lord of Oushuu, Hida Takahito...
Princess Yousha.
Note: Yousha = Permit
Forgive me!
T-Togame?
Now then, Strategian.
What will be your dying words?
Right now, at this instant,
the final Deviant Blade that Shikizaki Kiki forged—
Kyoutou Yasuri—is now Perfected.
Nay, Completed.
The story of Katanagatari on this month and this evening ends here.
To be concluded next time.
karada ga kokoro wo shinjite
身体が心を信じて
My body trusts in my heart
okizari ni sareta nara
置き去りにされたなら
If I'm abandoned
kuzureru koto wo shiritsutsu
崩れることを知りつつ
I will continue to feel ruin
nasake wo kakeru
情けを掛ける
I show pity
yomigaeru tagai no yabou
よみがえる互いの野望
Our revived hopes
dochira ka ga horobiru made wa
どちらかが滅びるまでは
Until one of us perishes
nazorae tagai wo idaku
なぞらえ互いを抱く
Will be embraced
samayoeru bourei tachi yo
彷徨える亡霊達よ
Departed spirits adrift
buji nara oshiete yo
無事なら教えてよ
If you are safe, tell me
todokanai koe ga hibiita
届かない声が響いた
My unreaching voice resounded
munashisa wo yadosu aiiro no
虚しさを宿す藍色の
Sleep to the emptiness
uragiri no kotoba ni nemure
裏切りの言葉に眠れ
Clinging to words of indigo betrayal
karada ga kokoro wo shinjite
身体が心を信じて
My body trusts in my heart
tatakai wo kakenuketa
戦いを駆け抜けた
I overtook the fight
kanashii uso de kurushimu you na
悲しい嘘で苦しむような
Like suffering from sad lies
yowaki na kakugo wa yurusanai
弱気な覚悟は許さない
I won't forgive such cowardly determination
misekake no tadashisa ga
見せかけの正しさが
The hidden truth
misekake no yasashisa e to
見せかけの優しさへと
Towards the hidden kindness
kuzureru  koto wo shiritsutsu
崩れることを知りつつ
Continues to feel ruin
nasake wo kake you
情けを掛けよう
Let's show pity
nasake wo
情けを
Pity...