There exists in this world something
no one has ever seen.
"Fluffy bangs soften your face and
allow you to softly capture her heart."
That's a lie.
It's useless...
Man...
Mold
Mold? What the hell!?
I got rid of all the mold not too long ago...
- That thing is very kind, and very sweet.
- I need a rag...
If anyone were to see it once,
they'd probably want to see it again.
That's why the world chose to hide it,
making it very difficult to obtain.
Damn it... I can't get it off...
- Fine. Time to bust out the Takasu Stick!
- But one day, someone will find it.
And that someone will be
the one meant to find it.
Because it was made to work that way.
Pre! Preparation!
pure pureparato
I might not be very strong,
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
pure pureparedo
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
warete baribari
Cracking and crumbling.
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
Love is so bittersweet.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
donna kanji sonna kanji
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
I act tough as we butt heads.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Eco, eco, eco, ecology...
Inko-chan, you still asleep?
Rise and shine.
I gotcha...!
You're such a meanie, Ryu-chan.
I told you last night that
school starts today.
Oh, right.
Opening ceremony day, huh?
Congrats for graduating a grade.
That's all you have to say to your son
at the start of a new school year?
Hey, it's too dark in here.
Open the curtains for me?
They're already open.
Huh?
Oh...
That's one huge apartment building...
Takasu Residence
Gotta wonder what kind of people live in it.
That thing
Since that thing was built,
we lost our precious sunshine,
so now our clothes take forever to dry,
and every day I deal with mold, mold, mold...
There's my favorite glare!
You look more like your daddy every day!
...like your daddy!
Don't compare me to that—
That's so cool!
Now you look even more like him!
Huh? Leaving already, Ryu-chan?
What about my food?
Heat before you eat
-Ryu
It's where it always is.
That was...
That was the last thing
I wanted to hear...
Thanks to the glare you always rave about...
I... I...
Hey! Wait up!
Shit!
Ta-Ta-Ta-Ta-Takasu-kun!
- What're you doing!?
- Um, huh?
- It was an accident!
- What...?
Here, take 'em. Just let us go!
It's all we've got on us!
We swear!
Listen! No loose change, right?
Uh...
We're so sorry!
Freaky...
Those are a killer's eyes!
I...
Ohashi High School
General Affairs - Lost and Found
Again?
You sure pick up a lot of wallets.
Yeah...
I hope we're in the same class again.
Totally.
Found it!
Yay! We are!
He's got a killer's eyes!
Damn it, not again...
Yo.
We're in the same class
again this year, Takasu.
Kitamura!
And that concludes this year's
opening ceremony.
Please head to your classes
and prepare for homeroom.
A new class...
As usual, I'll have to start by clearing
up my image with everyone.
Don't worry.
At least now it won't be everyone.
I already know the real you.
Yeah, thanks.
That's right.
There are some people who get me.
And besides, this class has...
Heya, Kitamura-kun!
We're in the same class this year.
Oh, Kushieda.
You're in class C too?
Oh!
Takasu-kun, right?
Do you remember me?
We've kind of met! I've seen you
hanging around Kitamura before!
K-Kushieda Minori, right?
Well, whaddaya know!
You remembered my full name!
That makes me kinda happy.
Now then...
Let's enjoy our teen years to the max!
Yeah.
R-Right...
And then...
What's up, Takasu?
N-Nothing. J-Just need to go take a leak.
Okay. See you in class.
What...?
Whoa! A battle for supremacy!?
Takasu Ryuji and Aisaka Taiga!
Whoa, the strongest matchup
right on the first day!
The fight to decide the school's
top dog is on!
What the heck?
She's tiny...
Like a doll.
But there's this...
There's this overwhelming
intensity about her...
Like she'll eat me if I let my guard down...
Uh, this is...
Whoa, it's true!
That delinquent Takasu-kun and
the Palm-top Tiger are—
Shut up!
Fierce as a tiger
But small
Palm-top...Tiger?
Oh, I get it.
Palm-top—
Yep.
Suits her to a T.
Okay.
That'll be all for today.
If you haven't turned in a career plan,
drop by the faculty office later.
D-Did you hear that, Takasu-kun?
Y-Yeah.
Are you okay, Taiga?
You were late today, too.
I'm not okay at all. I went to see the doctor.
Said something about "house dust."
What a modern-day disease.
Must be rough.
The Palm-top Tiger...
She's friends with Kushieda Minori?
I'm the one who has it rough.
You okay?
Yeah.
More or less.
But you know...
Aisaka-san and Takasu-kun
really went at it!
The Palm-top Tiger's as strong as ever.
Takasu only looks scary, y'know.
He's not really a delinquent.
Oh, really?
Sounds like your image is
already getting cleared up.
Taiga?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Ta-Takasu-kun, are you uncertain about
what you want to do with your life?
I-It's just, you see, I need you
to turn in a career plan.
Everyone else already has.
Oh, sorry. I forgot.
No, no, I'm sorry!
You don't want to be lectured by an
almost-thirty spinster with no goal in life!
Forgive me for stepping out of line!
Crap, it's getting late...!
The special, limited-time sales are gonna—
Y-You okay there?
Uh...
J-Just getting my bag...
I should probably just leave her be...
Huh!?
- Wh-Wha-What are you d-do-doing?
- What am I...? Look.
I'm just here for my bag.
Th-That's your bag?
Isn't your seat the next one over?
D-Did I mix them...
Up... Up...
Up!
And away!
Why...are you after my bag?
H-Hey.
Cut it out.
Ouch...
The hell're you—
A-Aisaka?
H-Hey!
Idiot!
What a mess...
What a mess!
Daddy's in Heaven.
He was such a hunk!
He kept magazines tucked in his belt
so he'd survive a surprise stabbing!
He was so electrifying!
All because I look like you...
I've gone through nothing but grief!
If I didn't have this face,
people wouldn't be scared of me,
and the Palm-top Tiger
wouldn't have bugged me.
I'd have more confidence...
Cruisin' Tunes - Spring
And then...
My career plan.
What?
To: Mr. Kitamura Yusaku.
Aisaka...
From: Aisaka Taiga
(If you don't want this, throw it away.)
Taiga?
Oh, I get it.
She must've put this in
my bag by accident.
I didn't open it, so I don't have the
slightest idea what might be inside.
I'll just give it back.
C-Crap!
I gotta reseal it!
Is she...
actually a huge klutz?
I'm going to bed.
Huh?
Yasuko...
Nah, she wouldn't be back this early...
- Chug it! Go for it, Mirano-chan!
- Okay, down the hatch it goes!
Takasu Yasuko - Stage name: Mirano
"On the Clock"
Hello?
The window's...
Damn, that hurts!
Wh-What the hell is this?
Huh?
I remember seeing someone
this size before...
Aisaka!
Use a damn tissue!
What...?
Wh—
What the.
Hell.
Are.
You.
Doing!?
Forget about it.
Huh? Forget about what?
Oh, you mean the let—
...ter.
Now that my secret's out,
I can no longer live.
I have to die!
Then quit trying to kill me!
But I don't want to die, so I need to kill you!
Unless you lose all your memories!
That's impossible!
Don't worry.
You won't die from a smack
to the head with this thing.
But I can at least wipe
your memory with it!
Don't "wipe" anything!
Here!
Listen to me!
The letter...!
Shut up.
Shut up! Shut up!
You saw it, right!?
You read it, right!?
L-Like I'm trying to say, there...
Not listening.
Just forget about that love...love...
Love letter!
It was empty!
Empty?
That's right.
There was nothing for me to read.
Hell, you're actually lucky you
didn't give it to Kitamura.
Now he won't know you messed up!
Um, h—
Hey.
Just how hungry are you...?
I'm sick of convenience store food.
Convenience store food?
Why don't your parents...?
I guess all families have issues.
Here.
This wouldn't have happened if you
had just handed over your bag.
How are you going to
make this up to me!?
You still got some on your face.
It's like you were only born to add
the scent of garlic to fried rice oil!
Now look here...
Wh-What's so embarrassing
about a love letter?
Listen.
You've got nothing to be ashamed of.
Hang on.
Behold.
What is this?
Can't you tell?
I guess not, huh?
It's a list of songs for a hypothetical
concert I'd put on for the girl I like.
That's a poem I inadvertently wrote for her.
And MDs to play while
we go for a drive.
Of course, I don't have a license, but...
I have different ones for each season.
Well? Are you weirded out?
Since I don't have the guts to tell her
how I feel, all I can do is fantasize.
Pathetic, sure.
But I don't feel any shame!
You should have more confidence!
You made it out of that fantasizing
stage and decided to take action.
Be more optimistic.
Think happy thoughts.
For Miss Kushieda Minori.
Yes, be like Kushieda Minori!
Wait!
- What!?
- You like Minorin?
For: Kushieda Minori
From: Takasu Ryuji
Yuck, you're awfully full of yourself.
Yuck, she's totally out of your league.
Shut up!
Like you should talk!
What!? I told you to forget about—
Sh-Shaddap...
G-G-...Goosebumps!
Sorry about that, Inko-chan.
Did we wake you up?
How dare you show me such a nasty thing!
What'd you say!?
She's an important part of our family!
Oh!
That's it, Inko-chan!
- I...I...!
- Introduce yourself to our visitor!
- I...I...I...!
- Today's the day you'll finally say your name!
I...
...mpotent.
Uh, actually, Inko-chan isn't
feeling like herself today...
Crap! It's so late!
A-Anyway!
We're in the same boat now!
I won't tell anyone about
what happened!
Trust me!
No.
Why not!?
I even fed you, so go home already!
I mean, please leave!
My borderline-mental mother
is about to come home!
I. Don't. Wanna!
I can't trust you.
And...
I want to know what you
think about love letters.
They're pretty outdated, huh?
Don't get bashful all of a sudden!
I'll give you all the relationship
advice you want!
But it's late now, so can
it wait until tomorrow?
Really? You'll help me?
I will.
I will, I will, I will!
I'll do anything!
Anything?
You'll obey me like a dog?
Follow my every command?
I will. I swear!
So everything's fine now, right?
Right? Right?
How did she get in
through the window?
Later.
Oh, I'll walk you home.
No need.
I live close.
And I have this wooden sword.
Um, that's why it's dangerous.
Hey, about the hole...
Oh.
Well, I can just cover it up with some paper.
To: Mr. Kitamura Yusaku
Here.
Feel free to use it.
If you end up spending money
on it, I'll pay you back.
See ya, Ryuji.
R-Right...
Did she just call me
by my first name?
From: Aisaka Taiga
(If you don't want this, throw it away.)
Hello, you've reached Takasu—
Get the hell over here, you—
Hello?
You hung up!
Where do you want me to go?
Huh?
The balcony?
Why?
What!?
Why!?
Didn't you say you'd obey my
every command, like a dog?
H-Hold on!
I meant that I'd help you out
with the Kitamura issue...
You do realize what will happen
if you don't come.
I can show you, if you'd like.
Uh, wait...
Well...
Give me ten minutes!
My rice dish will be finished by then!
Three?
I mean...
You want some?
Jeez...
Wow...
E-Excuse me.
Huh?
It's unlocked...
What is this stench!?
A-Aisaka-san?
I'm coming in.
This odor's really intense...
Aisaka!
Let me...!
Please, let me...
clean your kitchen!
What?
She went back to bed?
Almost looks fake...
Asleep, Aisaka really does look like a doll.
And the apartment, virtually devoid of
any signs of life, is like her dollhouse.
Even though it's far too big for that.
I'm gonna say...fifteen minutes.
Okay.
What...is this...?
Yo.
It's still a work in progress, but...
It's a lot cleaner, huh?
It was crazy.
Stagnant water in the clogged sink...
The drain, plugged with mold and rotting
garbage, was like a sight from hell...
And the room was covered in dust.
Trespassing.
And imposed cleaning.
You better not have marked
your territory, stupid dog.
Dog!?
Fair enough. It sounded like
an insult to other dogs.
You're nothing but a mongrel.
Mo-n-grel.
Damn ungrateful girl...
And after I...
Not gonna say, "Thanks for the food"?
I humbly thank the rice gods
and farmers for this meal!
Thanks for the food!
Oh, c'mon...
Hey, sounds like your sniffles are gone.
Probably because the place is clean.
Huh? What'd you just say?
Never mind!
banira sorutode
Add vanilla salt.
BURNING LOVE
Burning love.
amai dakenara
If it's too sweet,
soruto kakemashou
we can add some salt.
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I tell you all these things because
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
modokashi sugiru
This is so frustrating.
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
But a love that's purely sweet
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
shiroto iwaretara
If you say white,
kurodatte icchau
I say black.
sunaoni narenai
A little imp
amanojaku
who can't be honest to herself.
sukito iwaretara
If you say love,
daikirai datte
I say hate.
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
soruto kakeru youni
to sweet vanilla...
A sloppy pact.
New misunderstandings.
The power of genes.
Taiga, you're...
one hell of a klutz.
Shut up.
And rot in hell.