What's this? Just some scenery?
Ain't this the same beach we're at?
Looks like it.
Shinpei?
Or Mio?
Or someone else entirely?
Anyway, I'll just talk assuming yer Shinpei.
If yer watching this, I'm not in this world anymore.
Ya just wanted to say that cliche line.
How'd ya know?
Well, I know myself.
Jeez, c'mere. Let's both be in it.
What...
Over here?
A bit to the left.
Ushio and her shadow?
Oh, that's too much.
Perfect.
What are you doing?
Shinpei.
Listen carefully, got it?
Only my shadow and I can unlock this phone.
That means my shadow must be with ya now.
By the way, can ya tell which one is me?
Hey! I'm talking here!
Obviously it's me!
Left? Or right?
No, it's me!
Me!
I'm the real one!
Th-They sure get along well.
Nah, it's definitely me!
It doesn't matter.
We're both me.
Huh?
I'm sure ya know by now,
but she ain't evil like the other shadows, so ya don't gotta worry.
She's on yer side, I promise!
My shadow will explain the details, but I wanted to tell ya directly too.
That's why I'm doing this video.
What should I start with?
Right.
It all began with Shiori.
Following my innate intuition as I go
Trapped in the eddy of what I know will be my fate
I'm sure I won't be coming back from the sea as I was
A cat's mewling and the roar of the tides my memory
Let me protect you, if only once
If only once
I've been torn yet to fight I've sworn, so please wait for me
Until I give my life a decisive bye-bye
Life's so drear if you're not right here
All that's left to me is a summer as I go
There's no end to it
Each time I crush my sadness, all it does is grow
July 17th
It ain't nothing nearly as harmless as a look-alike!
And it felt like someone followed me home from school today.
Flow, My Tears
Ain't that just a stalker?
Be careful.
Should I tell Totsumura?
Totsumura's no help!
I know it's that girl.
Sis, is this the medicine fer Dad's athlete's foot?
Yeah, that's it.
Yer not listening! I should charge ya double!
What is it? What's the problem?
Just forget it!
Thanks fer shopping.
July 18th
Huh?
Mio, look.
Who's there?
Huh?
Wait!
Did I lose her?
A shadow...
Huh?
...as a look-alike!
A shadow?
Yeah, we'll look into yer story about the look-alike.
So ya decided to believe me?
Yes, so don't worry anymore.
Omoto Beach trash collection event is now concluded!
Thanks to y'all, the beach is clean fer its big opening tomorrow.
We'll burn the collected trash at the send-off.
Okay, everyone, see ya at the summer festival on the 24th.
Bistro Kofune
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Yay! I go first!
Hey, Sis.
Do ya think Shin will come back this summer?
What?!
It'd be fine with me if he never came back!
Yeah right.
I know ya like him.
Ya like Shin, don'tcha?
Wha—
What're ya saying?!
Stop it!
Move! I'm gonna take a bath first!
Ya little!
Jeez, Sis...
I wonder what he's doing right now.
Ugh, forget him.
Hi.
Mio!
Ow!
Who the hell are ya?!
Ow... Ya can't listen at all.
Did ya follow us from Omoto Beach?!
I'm Kofune Ushio! I just came home to my own house!
Th-Then... why were ya hiding?
'Cause I saw ya with Mio.
Do...
Do ya know about shadows?
Huh?
Yer the shadow.
Huh? What's going on?!
Wait a second.
If shadows really exist...
Shiori's shadow is somewhere on the island too!
I have a bad feeling.
Huh?
Didn't Shiori say she first saw her shadow on Mt. Takanosu?
Shouldn't we check it out?
I guess.
I'll deal with ya later.
Why're ya following me?
Yer the one following me.
I promised Shiori I'd look into this so that she can stop worrying.
Make any strange moves, and I'll finish ya off fer good!
Got it?
We haven't found any leads.
We're out of time today.
We gotta hike down before it gets dark.
C'mere.
Keep out
Look.
There's a trail up ahead.
This sign totally makes me wanna go in.
I know, right?
Oh, this must be the old clinic Sou's family ran.
Hishigata Clinic
Rumor has it that this old clinic is haunted.
Everyone's afraid of it, so they stay away.
So scary!
Ghosts are the one thing I can't deal with!
Ya too?
Yet ya seem eager to go inside.
Aren'tcha scared?
I'm scared, but I have a feeling...
Reception
Pharmacy
like I've been here before.
Wh-Who is it?! Who's there?!
Th-That's a shadow?
It's got my face!
Watch out!
What was that just—
Let go!
Damn! What is this?!
D-Dammit!
Let go of her!
Let go!
Let go, dammit!
What's happening?
It wasn't my leg that was stabbed!
Oh, I get it now.
It's a shadow's weakness.
I know.
My body clearly felt it.
I'm not human.
Yer not getting away!
My true body is the flat shadow.
This image of the body...
is a device to protect the true body.
What...
did ya just do?
I...
That was amazing! Super cool!
I know, right?
Wow! It healed!
I copied the data of yer right leg.
So it's like data?
I don't know how to put it, but yeah, sorta.
But this copied data will probably disappear.
If the original is deleted, the copy becomes the original.
Deleted?
Does that mean killed?
Will ya disappear unless I die?
I just have that feeling in my head.
Normally, I guess I'm supposed to kill ya.
So that's why people say ya die once ya see yer shadow!
Shiori's in danger.
We gotta do something about it.
July 20th
That means my shadow must be with ya now.
What will Shinpei think when he finds out that I'm a fake?
By the way, can ya tell which one is me?
Hey! I'm talking here!
It doesn't matter.
We're both me.
Ushio...
The two of ya tried to save Shiori.
I remember.
I remember now!
Yer memories...
A-Are they back?!
It ain't just my memories.
My powers came back too.
Powers?
I want ya to see the truth of the end of my life.
I'll recreate it from my memory data.
Let's go to the private beach on July 21st!
Summer Time Rendering
Th-This is...
Hey, Shinpei.
L-Look!
I'm so glad it's sunny!
Right!
It's the perfect weather to study.
Perfect weather fer swimming!
Hey, Shiori!
I heard ya can't swim. How lame!
Big talk from a guy who can't even eat mushrooms!
It's fine since not being able to eat mushrooms ain't lame at all!
Is that...
No doubt.
That's us from the 21st.
Crap. I need to stop them!
Hey, guys!
It's pointless.
This is just an image from the past.
We're just watching a recording.
We can't touch or speak to them.
Right, Ushio?
Damn.
Where were ya at this time?
Come with me.
One, two, three, four, five.
Have I put on some weight?
Don't say that. It's been bothering me.
So this is where ya copied the swimsuit.
Just watch.
I can't get near Shiori like this.
I have an idea.
Can ya turn into this?
Sure.
Okay.
Well?
Perfect!
I turned into the shell necklace and Ushio wore me.
She took off the real necklace and put it in her pool bag.
Hey, Mio.
How can I be a good swimmer like ya?
I wanna learn!
Ya will!
Let's do a swimming lesson today!
Who wants to learn how to swim?!
Me!
Shiori.
That's the spirit!
I'll protect ya, no matter what.
Huh?
What's that? Are ya asking fer my hand in marriage?
What?!
What's wrong?
Akari says she pooped.
Uh-oh.
I didn't! I just need to go!
It's coming out!
Want me to take ya?
Hurry!
It's okay! I'll take her!
Shiori?
What's wrong?
Shiori's gone.
Look! There!
Ushio, in the water!
I sense a shadow!
Tokiko, take Akari!
Come, Sou!
Sure!
Shinpei, did ya see what happened to Shiori?
N-No.
Sorry, this is a memory.
I can't recreate what no one saw.
Stay back!
Don't come!
Leave this to me!
Sis!
Don't be a fool, Ushio! What are ya thinking?!
Hang in there, Shiori!
I see it!
It's Shiori's shadow!
Here I go.
Leave this to me.
Wait.
I chose her.
Ya can't take her.
I can't move.
I'm so close to the surface,
and Shiori's gonna die!
Go! Hurry and take Shiori!
Ushio!
Dummy!
Don't stop!
Just go!
How am I ever gonna return this kinda favor?
Go,
me...
Stop.
I told ya to stop.
Yer defective.
I feel someone coming.
Ya lucked out.
Shiori.
Sis!
Ushio!
I'm sorry, Ushio.
I couldn't save Shiori.
I'll kill the shadows with Shinpei.
I'll save everyone at the summer festival on the 24th.
Is that enough to pay ya back fer this, e-even a little?
Yes, that's enough.
Of course it is.
She pretended to lose consciousness and took Shiori's place.
Yes.
I can't stand that damn monster!
I wanna kill it with my own hands!
Yes.
We killed it already.
Hey!
How can ya be so calm?!
But...
Huh?
I should've been the one to do it.
Shinpei.
I'm sorry.
Who should've done what now?
Found ya.
Hey, Ushio.
Isn't this just an image?
Ya said they can't touch or talk to us.
What's this?
It's not in my memory.
This is bad.
End this, Ushio!
It took me a long time to find ya after that.
I won't let ya get away this time.
A-Are we back?
Shinpei, look at yer arm.
That's where it grabbed me.
Since I remember it all
I'll alter my existence
Take a breath, take a breath
The smell of a tepid tide, a choir of cicadas
It's not something that can be forgotten
Being torn by engulfing regret is best avoided
So we're setting our lives aflame
I can go on living just from the warmth of your palm if it's linked with mine
What will be left remaining of this all too short summer I wonder
It's once in a lifetime, so we want to undergo a change
We want to change
Next time
Into the Darkness