There seems to be more out again today.
The flow of the river is ceaseless,
yet the water is never the same.
The foam that floats on the stagnant pools of water,
now vanishing, now forming,
never reside for long.
Just as is with men and their dwellings on this world.
They are the blink of an eye.
Mii-kun!
What's up?
Staying late again, Yuki-senpai?
Pretty much. Classic literature is hard for me.
I enjoy it a lot, actually. Want some help?
You do? But this stuff is so confusing.
So you're reading An Account of My Hut?
My friend really liked this one.
Isn't this thing here awesome, Mii-kun?
What is?
This thing. It's a really old letter someone wrote, right?
Yeah, about 800 years old, I believe.
It's more like an essay than a letter, though.
But that's 800 years!
The feelings left by someone that long ago are still making their way to us today!
Letters are amazing!
You're really excited over this, aren't you?
All right, then.
Let's keep going.
Student Council
School Living Club
Yuki
Graduation Album
DAMEDESUYO PRESENTS
School Living Club
Taroumaru
We're doing great.
Mii-kun
Arnault
Hatonishiki II
Graduation Album
"Letter"
The wind's so brutal at night.
I know.
It's not an issue as of now, but if we don't
prepare for winter, it might become one.
Winter already?
It doesn't feel like it.
Did Yuki go to bed?
She was up studying until late, so she's sound asleep.
I see.
Why don't we get some sleep too?
Hey, president.
Have you ever thought all this could be a dream?
That we could wake up tomorrow and the school would be back to normal?
I have that dream every night.
Yuki-chan.
Yuuri-san and I have thought of something.
You and Rii-san?
Yes. Something really fun.
How can anything be fun now?
We'll start a new club.
All of us, together.
A club?
That's right.
We'll call it...
the School Living Club.
Yuki-senpai?
Senpai.
It's time to get up.
Morning, Mii-kun.
I had a scary dream.
What happened?
I forgot.
Oh, come on.
Breakfast is ready, by the way.
The other two are waiting for us.
I see, I see.
Oh, but what about Megu-nee?
Um...
Oh, good morning, Megu-nee.
Nice. This should do.
As usual, the School Living Club's
gonna give it their all today, Megu-nee.
This looks delicious!
Let's eat!
So yummy! The gardening club's got the best onions!
It was nice of them to share, wasn't it?
It was!
The udon is so flavorful.
Whoa, uh...
As usual, all attention has gone to her food.
Come on, you're not Taroumaru. At least chew!
Taroumaru
I dare say Taroumaru has better table manners.
Anyway, I think it's amazing all this can be stored without refrigeration nowadays.
The udon's so squishy!
Yet another victory for science.
You're right. We're able to have hot udon like this
thanks to the solar panels and power storage units on the roof.
Not many schools have a setup like ours.
What a great appetizer!
I'm ready for more, Rii-san!
Sorry, Yuki-chan, that's all we have for now.
We have to ration the stuff we
brought back from our field trip.
That sucks...
But that was such a fun field trip, wasn't it?
We even made a new friend!
Th-Thank you.
That was a pretty rough day.
It sure was.
We had to cram the four of us and
Taroumaru in that tiny car for the trip back.
I fell asleep right away,
so I don't remember the ride.
I remember that!
I was driving, Rii-san was in the front with me,
and Taroumaru was having the time of his life in the back.
I can't believe you two slept through all that!
Huh?
It was just us two in the back?
That's weird...
Now that you mention it...
the car only has... four seats.
Yeah,
there was me,
Rii-san,
Kurumi-chan,
Mii-kun,
and Megu-nee...
The four of us?
But then...
Senpai?
What about Megu-nee?
O-Oh, you were asleep, so I guess you must have missed it,
but Megu-nee said her house was nearby,
so she walked home instead of riding with us, that's all.
I remember that.
She... did?
Yeah!
Didn't she?
She must have.
Yuki-chan!
I'm going to ask Megu-nee!
I'm sorry.
Don't sweat it.
It's no one's fault.
Yuki-senpai...
She can't keep going on like that.
Miki-san?
I realize it's her smile that keeps everyone going,
but that's no excuse to...
I think so too.
I'm sure Megu-nee feels the same way.
Megu-nee...
You're here with me, aren't you?
Everything's okay.
Even if I'm hard to find, I'm still here with you.
But I'm so afraid sometimes...
A bunch of my memories seem fuzzy,
and I...
Everyone has memories that seem vague.
That's why talking to others and keeping a journal are important.
They help you keep your memories tangible.
I've always thought so, at least.
Even if the person they're about...
leaves you...
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, Megu-nee.
I'm back!
There you are.
Welcome back.
Mii-kun!
I told you not to get so close...
But you seemed so lonely, Mii-kun!
I was just fine!
But you smell kinda funny today, Mii-kun!
That's not nice!
Oh, wait. Maybe that's Taroumaru.
There, there. Why are you so stinky?
He won't take a bath.
Really?
In that case...
it's time he met his maker.
Oh no you don't!
Come to think of it,
humans and dogs see the world in
completely different ways, don't they?
Do they?
Dogs can't see colors like we do.
They live in a world of sepia.
But it's like a trade-off. They can see much better at night,
and even parts of the ultraviolet spectrum are visible to them.
They can track down odors we wouldn't even notice were there,
but they couldn't tell you the color of our flowers.
Wow.
I didn't know that.
Gimme my hat back!
Oddly enough,
it's as if those two see the world the same way.
It really does.
Right?
Sometimes other people don't see the world the same way either.
Taroumaru, you bully!
Wait up!
Yuki-chan!
You okay?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Senpai, you need to be more careful!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
What... are these?
They look like Megu-nee's belongings.
Oh, what a mess.
I'll help.
Thank you.
You're a member of our club now.
You don't need to thank me.
Okay...
Whoa, look at this!
Hey, hey, look what I found.
Why don't we write a letter?
Writing letters is fine and all,
but how will we send them?
Whoops, you're right.
The post office is outside the school!
You didn't think that far ahead?
There's another option.
Can't we just send them from the school?
When you think of mail,
carrier pigeons come to mind.
And where do you intend to get a carrier pigeon?
We'll catch one, obviously!
And how do we catch one?
Just the tool for the job.
You're gonna chop it up!?
Of course not. I'll take the dull edge, and...
Wham!
Chop!
I don't think this will work.
Slam! Hack! Bam!
She'd never land a hit.
Inflates to
20x the size
Balloons
Inflates to
20x the size
If we're sending letters, we can use these!
Oh, those are from the test of courage, right?
They won't float if you blow them up with air.
Oh, dear.
If only we had some helium.
It's possible there's an old tank from the scuba club still around.
We had a scuba club?
A long time ago, yes.
I'll go check it out.
Hold on.
An air tank is too heavy for you to bring back alone.
I'll go with her.
But...
Rii-san
Mii-kun
I'm a club member, too.
If you don't mind, then.
Sure.
Me, too!
Why don't you get your letter done in the meantime?
Oh! Good idea!
I'll write a real good one!
Do you think there's anyone out there to read our letters?
I'm sure there is.
There's no way everyone on Earth is gone.
Y-Yeah, maybe...
There's always that one in a million chance.
I'm counting on that.
Right!
My name is Yuki Takeya.
What's wrong?
Writing an actual letter is kind of embarrassing.
My handwriting is so messy.
It's okay.
Let's see here.
Whatcha doing?
Oh, paper dolls?
How cute!
If you picked up a balloon on the side of the road, Yuki-chan,
and it had a letter attached,
what would you think?
I'd be surprised!
And super excited!
Would it bother you if the sender's writing was messy?
Of course not,
I'd be happy just to get the letter!
You see?
You're right!
We're back!
And we've brought presents.
We found a helium tank.
I grabbed some traps too.
Haven't given up on the carrier pigeon idea, have you?
How could I?
C'mon, Mii-kun, you need to write a letter too!
Whatever you say...
Hey, Yuki, check this out.
What is it? Tell me, tell me!
This trap's gonna knock a pigeon dead in an instant!
I don't think killing them is the goal...
All right, I'm off for the hunt.
Good luck!
Let's put the tank by the wall.
Staff Room
Safe 2
Yeah, good idea.
Staff Room
Safe 2
Sakura
Mii-kun?
Oh, what is it?
What're you gonna write?
Uh, well...
I'm not really sure.
Kyaah
Hold it!
I don't really know what to write, to be honest.
Anything's fine.
It could be about yourself, your plans for the future, whatever you want to...
Oh, the future...
I'm gonna get an earful from Megu-nee if I don't decide on a college or find work soon.
I think that's the same for every teacher.
I guess so.
We'll have to leave this
school someday, won't we?
Indeed.
Graduation!?
That's it!
My Dream
so many things,
can't write them all.
Let's write about our plans after graduation!
so many things,
can't write them all.
Our dreams for the future?
That's it!
And we can write about how we're happily working towards making them come true!
My Dream
so many things,
can't write them all.
When I graduate...
Can't sleep?
They seem to be gathering around the entrance.
Maybe the rain bothers even them.
I found this earlier today.
Sakura
Isn't "Sakura"...
Megu-nee.
If you don't mind, could I hold on to that, please?
Maybe we'll need it at some point.
Please do.
Thank you.
Someday, all of us will be able to leave this place.
I hope so.
You think the rain will let up soon?
I'm sure it will.
I'm pumped!
It's finally time.
Good luck, Hatoko-chan.
Hold it right there! Who're you calling Hatoko-chan?
Her, of course! She's Hatonishiki Hatoko-chan.
Not even close! His name is Arnault!
No! I wanna name her, though!
I'm the one who caught it.
But Hatoko-chan is cuter!
He's totally an Arnault!
Come on, you two!
She definitely looks like a Hatoko!
Speak up, Arnault!
What if we compromise and
name it Arnault Hatonishiki II?
If we have to...
Official Name
Arnault
Hatonishiki II
Hear that? Your name is now Arnault Hatonishiki II.
What makes him a second generation?
It's your time, Arnault Hatonishiki II. You can be free!
On the count of three, okay?
Ready...
One!
Two!
Three!
To Kei
Kei,
how are you?
To Kei
I've found a new place to live,
and I've made new friends.
I'm doing just fine.
And Taroumaru is doing great too.
It's all thanks to them.
Is staying alive enough for you?
It is. Staying alive is the best.
The dew may fall and the flower remain,
or the flower may wither before the dew disperses.
What was that?
It's a line my friend was fond of.
I see.
I hope it reaches her.
Whatever path I walk,
I pray that someday
I'll meet you again along the way.
We're doing great.
akane iro ni
What was on your mind
kimi wa nani wo kangaete ita no?
as you let yourself be painted red?
mabuta ippai namida wo tamete
I have to remind myself that life is beautiful
gomakashite ita kirei dane to
as my eyes well up with tears.
utagai mo naku konna hibi ga tsuzuiteiku datte
I've never stopped believing that
zutto omotte ita
the days like this would never end
miageta sora wa tooku tooku bokura mitsumete iru
Ever so far away, the sky looks down upon us
tada shizuka ni kawaranai mama
as if nothing at all had changed
nai kono te to te nigiri shimeta
Holding a hand that's no longer there,
mou samishiku wa nai yo
I can happily say, "I'm not sad any more"
owaru sekai mukou gishi e to
Beyond the end of the world
bokura no yoake ga
is our dawn
mieru kara
It's coming
mieru kara
I can see it
waratte
wa
ra
t
te
So smile
Everyone graduate
together!!
Next Time!!
Taroumaru
Yuki
Next Time!!
Where do you think Arnault is now?
If he's a second generation, maybe America?
Whoa, go Arnault!
He's a Hatonishiki, after all.
You know the family!?
Next time on School-Live: Episode 8, "Future."
"Future"