When watching TV,
please keep the room bright...
...and sit well away from the TV.
That's right.
Last time!
Thanks to the Superintendent's
caprious-icious-icious nature,
a Butler Battle Tournament
was suddenly held at Hakuou Academy!
Nonohara, the build-up to your
technique takes a bit too long.
One fierce fight after another and another,
and the butler of the Sanzenin
household, Hayate Ayasaki, also...
...brilliantly cleared the first
round after a life-and-death struggle!
Wh-What incredible fighting spirit!
What kind of super lethal
technique could he have?
Here he comes, Hayate!
That's right! This
is no time to be faltering!
I absolutely have to let
the Miss see me at my best here!
Huh?
The winner is Hayate Ayasaki,
butler of the Sanzenin household!
Huh? Wait... What?!
Uh, um, but I haven't done anything yet...
So you shredded his clothes
with the power of your chi!
That's my Hayate!
End of summary.
Whosoever commands the butlers,
commands the world!
The Great Butler War that will
shake up the world has just begun!
Oh, my, look at the silly
mask you're wearing, Mr. Klaus.
You're the only one who noticed, Maria.
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Dou yattemo katenai akuma ga
A demon that I just can't win against
Megami no kao o shite chakkari (O_O;)
Brazenly pretending to be a goddess (O_O;)
Keikenchi ja tannai kurai dakara
Experience points are almost not enough
Isshou tanren shikou-sakugo ni sessa-takuma
Training for life, working hard at trial and error
Mondai nara muzukashii-hodo ude ga naru shi
Tougher the problem the more it gets me going
Yorokobu kao ga mirerya sore de ii shi
Seeing the joy on your face is enough for me
Takara no chizu o boku wa te ni ireta
I've found a treasure map
Juuou-mujin kimi o tsurete tsuki-susumou!
Totally free, I'll take you and push forward!
Happii na kanchigai
A happy misunderstanding
Chikai wa yuruganai!
My pledge will stand fast!
Kaze no yukue mo kaete-miseru
I'll even change the direction of the wind
Kakkou wa kini-shinai
I won't care how I look
Unmei ja kujikenai!
No destiny will discourage me!
Ano kumo chirasu hayate no gotoku!
Like the sudden gale scattering the clouds!
Black Hayate
Yes, they say a true master can win
without laying a finger on his foe.
Infrared
Hayate, I never imagined
you had gotten to that point.
W-Well...
Um, my opponent destroyed himself
all on his own in that match...
Here you are, Miss.
Ah! Thank you.
Say, Hayate, sitting here like this
sort of reminds you, doesn't it?
Oh? Of what?
Hey, now, don't tell me you've forgotten!
You know, that day.
Oh!
I guess it's been many months since then.
Hayate, you're always doing your best
and I'm grateful to you for that.
Here, you drink this!
Miss...
I mean, after all, we need you
to do your best and grab that victory.
Yes, Miss!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
That's... Himuro?
Sheesh! Shrieking their heads off just
because he's a bit good-looking.
You're way cooler than him!
Oh, please...
Heave-ho!
Little Master, this will be it then.
I see, so Himuro's in this Tournament, too.
All right!
I'll be sure to witness your
lethal technique with my own eyes!
Okay, we're going to get started.
The Saginomiya household Men
in Black Tri-Stars versus...
...Ohkouchi household butler, Himuro Saeki!
Three versus one?! That's playing dirty!
How rude! We, the men in black
of the Saginomiya household...
W-We three are one!
We are as one in body and spirit!
The Girls' Squad!
What an interesting thing to say.
Fight!
Then here we go.
Bonjour?
Uh, um, where is the venue
for the Butler Battle Tournament?
Ça va, ça va.
Oh, dear, oh, dear. Oh, dear, oh, dear.
I have this terrible feeling
that I was unable to be present to
witness yet another crucial moment.
Th-The winner is Himuro Saeki!
M-Miss Isumi is always getting lost...
A-And she has a hard
time getting to school...
S-So we wanted to get the prize
of 100 school credits for her...
Himuro, good work!
I hope I get to see you win soon!
I will be counting on you to pay me
my bonus, Little Master Taiga.
I-I couldn't see anything
of that crucial super lethal technique...
Y-Yes...
I have to make sure to step up my game, too!
But as chance would have it,
contrary to his determination...
Fight!
Kame-hame...
Y-You win...
Ayasaki wins!
What?!
Wh-Why?
That's right. Terrified
by how Hayate won his first fight,
You win.
his opponent small fry butlers
forfeited one after another.
And the competition continued,
quickly determining the top 4 contenders.
First match of the semi-finals!
The Hanabishi family part-time
butler, Hinagiku Katsura!
The Asakaze family
part-time butler, Kashiwagi!
My butler...
...ran away!
R-Rissy...
Wh-Why?!
She probably couldn't
keep paying him anymore.
Th-The winner is my little sister!
We've got our first championship contender!
Hina, do your best out there
for my sake, too.
Risa...
This is just a token of my appreciation.
Wait! This is the bill
from the butler you hired!
Well, I'd been buying
the "Ikki Tousen" DVDs,
because I wanted to see the protagonist,
who doesn't show up very much,
and I went over my credit card limit.
Pay it yourself! Pay it yourself!
Was it really all right
for me to end up in the top 4?
That, too, must have been Heaven's will.
Wait, y-you can even
hear what I'm thinking?!
The Sanzenin family butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
You've been summoned.
R-Right!
The Ohkouchi family butler, Himuro Saeki!
Himuro, why did you enter this Tournament?
Why?
Why? Because I...
...love money!
H-Hayate!
That kid is doing better than I expected.
Indeed.
That's Himuro for you.
I let him set the pace in spite of myself.
B-But...
This finally...
...feels like a battle now!
Huh?
Little Master Taiga?
Mm-hm, I see.
You are being attacked
by a terrifying savage beast?
I-I'm sorry!
I wanted you to do your best,
so I went to buy you a snack, but...
Very well. I shall be there right away.
Hayate, we shall have to
do this at another time.
Wha?! Wait!
Darn it! No helping it then!
The winner is Hayate Ayasaki!
What?!
A-Again?
Ah! That little bastard.
He ran off because he got scared of Hayate!
O-Oh, that's right.
The fact that I've technically
won this match means...
S-So my next opponent is Hinagiku...
This is rough.
Should he actually be happy
with his victory?
We are finally getting
to the championship round.
A Nurarihyon monster! (Nurarihyon!)
What?! (E?!)
May I breathe through my gills?
(Era-kokyuu shitemo ii desuka?)
Interim butler of the Hanabishi
household, Hinagiku Katsura!
Here!
Sanzenin household butler, Hayate Ayasaki!
H-Here!
You have both done well to make it this far.
The way you fought was quite valiant.
But uh, I don't recall
having fought much at all...
Now, enter this championship
round with care!
As the representative of the students,
the winner will receive
the privilege of challenging Sion here.
You have no objections, I trust?
I do not.
I-I suppose not...
To inspire the two of you,
we will now take a moment
to unveil the new school song.
I stayed up all night writing
and composing it myself!
An immortal masterpiece!
A-A new school song?
Hayate, you should take this
opportunity to learn for yourself
just how dreadful the Superintendent is.
I entered this Tournament
in order to defeat her.
Hinagiku...
Hakuou Academy
School Song
The white school reigning
over the land of Suginami
Our mother school
Fire up that engine in your heart
Hakuou! Hakuou!
Six mega shock!
Employment rate of 120
Hakuou Academy!
Calm down!
Calm down and count the prime numbers!
Struck by its overwhelming splendor,
it seems everyone is in a frenzy.
Hakuou! Hakuou!
Mistress Kuzuha!
Zhuge Liang's trap
See?
Th-This is definitely...
She needs to be brought down.
Hakuou! Hakuou!
If we allow her to continue
as she pleases, our academy will be...
Update blogs daily
Hakuou Academy!
Superintendent!
I will win against
that person, without fail!
But of course, I will refuse the prize!
Are you okay with that? Mikky?
I-I do not mind.
Because we are the student council!
We cannot set an example of playing hooky!
But you're always playing hooky.
100 credits?
Offering a prize like that...
It's an awful thing for the students
who take attending class seriously!
This academy is not your toy!
Ladies and gentlemen of the student body,
I will defeat the Superintendent!
And I will bring reform to this academy!
Please give me the strength
to reform Hakuou Academy!
Hayate, you heard what I said.
But a match is a match.
Wh-What should I do? She's serious.
I'm in a real jam now.
Absolute destiny: Apocalypse.
Okay, here we go!
Final match!
Hinagiku Katsura versus Hayate Ayasaki!
Super Battle Time!
Here I come!
P-Please stop, Hinagiku!
There's no reason for us to fight!
Don't tell me you're holding
back because I'm a girl!
Truly, not his home crowd.
Hayate, it's unsportsmanlike
to just keep running away!
Fight me fair and square!
Hey, Hayate, pull yourself together!
What?!
Why are you so by-the-book?
Being a butler isn't just about
using your strength to hurt others.
Hayate, you must know that well.
Miss...
Yes, Miss!
Come, Hayate, fight me!
Hinagiku, I am sorry about this.
I get that you're serious about protecting
the academy from the Superintendent.
But there is something
I absolutely must protect!
Th-The winner is Hayate Ayasaki!
Uh, um, Hinagiku...?
Perv.
But well, I guess a loss is a loss.
I was too worked up about this anyway.
I guess it just means
I still need a lot of training.
Hayate Ayasaki, I hate that I lost,
but I'll entrust you with the future
of Hakuou Academy this time.
What?
That's okay, right? Ladies
and gentlemen of the student body?
No, uh...
Entrusting me with such
an outrageous thing is...
He will be representing us,
the students of Hakuou!
Come accept the challenge, fair and square,
Sion Kuresato, butler to the Superintendent!
Oh! Wait!
Show them exactly what you are capable of.
With pleasure.
You. Shall we get on with it?
Hayate, it'll be fine.
Knowing you, I'm sure you'll win.
Wait, Hinagiku, please don't move
the story along without me!
Hayate!
Well, uh, how to say this?
I've been plenty satisfied with the way
you've fought so far, of course,
but Hayate, to see you
coolly knockout an opponent...
That's what I'd love to see for myself!
It seems there's no turning back now.
I will do it!
Yes, that's the spirit, Hayate!
With the future of the academy at stake!
Fight!
At any rate, I just have to make sure
not to get caught in that weird technique.
It's no use, Ayasaki.
Shoot!
My "poetic world" sends the piano
melody directly into your brain.
You can no longer escape
from within this domain.
Huh? W-What's wrong, Ayasaki?
That's...
Hayate, aim for the feet!
Break your opponent's stance!
Once you shatter the focus,
that technique should also...!
Hinagiku...
Not so fast!
Sh-Shoot! M-My true identity!
Uh, um... Your "true"..?
Could it be that you're...?
D-Don't say it!
Take that! And that! And that! And that!
Allow me to explain.
Top Secret
Sion's Secret
Sion
Girl Sion
The Superintendent's butler, Sion Kuresato,
is actually a female student
at the middle school.
When the Secret Boots come off,
she can no longer maintain
her elegant appearance
and she ends up revealing her
true identity of a young girl.
Hey, those two are completely
different characters!
Take that! And that!
I-I'm an adult! I'm no pipsqueak!
A-A cool adult, suitable
to be in Mistress Kuzuha's company!
Sion, stop this already. You have lost.
Mistress Kuzuha...
Your smaller form is fine in its own way.
Let us withdraw for today
and craft poems of love together.
Yes, Mistress.
Uh, um...
You seem like a toy
that will be quite fun to play with.
What?!
J-Just you remember this!
I'll be sure to get back at you for this!
Silence!
Uh, um...
What to do about this atmosphere...?
Uh...
And thus, the Butler Battle
Tournament came to an end.
Take that!
I said it's over and it's over!
Oh! A jellyfish!
Oh, I wonder if jellyfish are edible?!
So, um... Wh-What ultimately
became of the prize of 100 credits?
Hm? She gave it to us.
The one thing that Superintendent
doesn't do, at least, is lie.
Th-Then...
No, we respectfully declined it.
What?
Sheesh!
I feel bad for always making
you skip school with me...
And after all the trouble I went to...
Oh, could it be
that she did this out of concern
for Hayate's attendance record?
I am grateful for your considerate thought.
But I will fit school in between my duties
and make it work somehow.
Go!
Looks like even the champion
of the Battle Tournament
is a pushover when it comes to games.
N-Next time, I will be sure to win!
Come on! Come at me however you like!
Here I go!
Victory
Sion, what did you think
of that boy named Ayasaki?
What did I think? Um...
That boy is unexpectedly...
...enticing.
What?
I've made up my mind!
Enough of that Battle Tournament!
Come forth, mysterious
Butler Corps of Darkness!
We will make Hayate Ayasaki one of us,
by any means necessary!
What might this mysterious
Butler Corps of Darkness be?
Butler Corps of Darkness VS Hayate
And what of the fate
of Hayate and the others?
Next time, they will fight against a Gundam
model fanatic's extensive knowledge.
Waratte lun-lun-lun
Smile lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu naita hi mo
Lala-lun-lun-lulu even on a day I've cried
Sawagu kaze ni yureru egao kokoro hareteku
A smile wavers in the wind and clears my heart
Kyou mo lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
Today again lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Taiyou no shita de kimi to odoru kimagure na dansu
A whimsical dance with you under the sun
Nanige-naku sashi-dasu te ni mitorete
Riveted by the hand you've casually offered
Tsugi no kotoba maigo ni natchau no
My next words become lost
Otonabite tsutsumi-komu manazashi ni
The mature gaze that envelopes me
Tsuyogari wasurete-yuku
Makes me forget my bravado
Sotto furetete nemurenai yoru no nagai toki mo
Keep that soft touch on long sleepless nights
Yume kara sameta bakari no hoho ni mo
And on my cheek, just awakened from a dream
Lun-lun-lun
Lala-lun-lun-lulu tsun to shita
Lala-lun-lun-lulu that hoity profile
Yokogao hora atto iu ma waratteru desho?
Look, there's a smile there already, see?
Sora to lun-lun-lun mawarun-lun-lulu
With the sky lun-lun-lun turning lun-lun-lulu
Kimi ga fukasu kaze no naka
In a breeze of your making
Odoru hidamari no dansu
A dance in a sunny spot
This is Nagi...
...and Hayate's...
...Butler Report!
Sign: Butler Report
From good morning to good night,
I'm Nagi Sanzenin!
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
The story's starting to take
a boys' manga type of turn.
Are you going to be fighting
groups of monsters every week now?
No, we have a normal story next week.
The anime staff seems to be going
through a lot of trial and error.
I guess original story developments
can be quite difficult.
I agree, Miss.
So, don't miss the staff's struggles!
Bye-good!
Preview
Young Sir, my mother suggested I go
to a match-making meeting yesterday.
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Really? That's great...
Oh, Mother? Please set up
that meeting as soon as you can!
Yes, full speed ahead.
What? Oh, wait, Saki?!
So, tomorrow on Sunday, I will be going
to a match-making meeting.
What?!
Next time on "Hayate the Combat Butler",
"Match-Making Meeting".
Next Hayate the Combat Butler
Match-Making Meeting
Did you know?