Please...
Please marry me!
I guess I have no choice.
If you insist, I'll marry you.
Takasu Ryuuji's Pen
Ryuu-chan, look, look!
Taiga-chan gave birth to so many puppies!
They're your kids.
A dream?
True Stories of Fear
from the Islands of Japan
- I gave birth to puppies! -
Even though it's finally summer break,
I'm having these dreams because of the stupid DVDs we rented.
Even for a dream, that's one awful future.
Oh, Taiga!
I had a bad dream.
You were a dog, and my husband was the dog.
Anyway,
it was a horrible dream.
pure pureparaato
プレ！　プレパラート！
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka nai kedo
強くなんかないけど
I'm not strong
pure pure pareedo
プレ！　プレパレード！
But pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimi wo tsukamaeru
いつか君を捕まえる！
I'll catch you someday!
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa warete baribari
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　ワレテバリバリ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, cracking apart
pure purepa pure purepa pure purepa
プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ　プ・レ・プレパ
P-re-prepare, p-re-prepare, p-re-prepare
yudan shitara sono yubi chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
油断したら　その指　チクチクアタック　覚悟して
If you're not paying attention, be prepared for a poking attack from my fingers
chiisai kedo hasamu no mijinko mitaina anata
小さいけど　挟むの　ミジンコみたいなアナタ
I'm little, but I'll squish you; you're as tiny as a flea to me
hoshii no wa purasuchikku na haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
欲しいのは　プラスチックなハート
(プラス　プラス　ダケドマイナス)
What I want is a plastic heart (plus, plus, but it's a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai soko ni kizuita mono gachi
でもそれじゃつまらない　そこに気付いた者勝ち
But that's boring; when I'd notice it, I'd have won against you
koi wa amaku te nigai mono
恋は甘くて　苦いもの
Love is something that's bittersweet
tanjun meikai fukuzatsu kaiki na shiromono
単純明快　複雑怪奇な代物
Simple and clear yet complex and strange stuff
dou demo ii koto bakkari kini shitari suru no
どうでもいい事ばっかり気にしたりするの
I'm only worrying about things that don't matter
donna kanji sonna kanji
どんな感じ？ソンな感じ
How does it feel? It feels like that
onkou tokujitsu ekisentorikku na anata
温厚篤実　エキセントリックなアナタ
You're gentle and sincere yet eccentric
tsuyogaru soburi wo zenshin matotte tachiuchi
強がる素振りを全身まとって太刀打ち
I pretend to be strong all over and compete against you
sunao na dakeda to shigeki ga tsuyoku te kurakura
素直なだけだと刺激が強くて　クラクラ
Just by being honest, it's so stimulating and I feel dizzy
kizutsui chau no kizutsuke chau no junjou pureparaato
傷ついちゃうの　傷つけちゃうの　純情プレパラート
I get hurt, I hurt you, in a preparation of pure feelings
atama no naka wa itsumo hitori no junjou pure pareedo
頭の中は　いつも一人の　純情プレパレード
In my head, there's always a pre-parade of pure feelings all by myself
You, who are going to the sea
A premonition?
Yes.
It was a warning,
telling me that if I don't work out a counter-plan,
that is what the future holds.
That's what that dream was.
So to change the future,
one side should fully support the
other starting with the trip tomorrow.
I understand that, but...
...why badminton?
Like I said,
we're going to decide!
Decide who's doing what!
Listen, be careful when using the stove.
Stir the rice bran once a day.
Make sure to change Inko-chan's water in the morning.
Read the rest in the note I left behind.
Well, I'll be going, then.
Going? Where?
Didn't I tell you already? On a trip.
See you, Ya-chan.
Looks like the weather's going to be great!
So I'm counting on you for that plan.
Hey, you sure it's okay?
Yeah! It's your win, okay?
Now hurry up and get this thing off me!
If it weren't for that dumb dog getting involved, I would have won!
It was punishment for setting up a
match in something you're good at.
Sheesh. Nothing good ever comes out of anything involving dogs.
Still, will it really go smoothly?
Just leave it to me.
When this trip is over, your relationship with Minorin will be-
What?
Something wrong?
Good morning!
You're right on time!
Fabulous! Simply fabulous!
What's wrong?!
Where's the energy?!
Make some noise!
What's that?
Y-Yeah.
My, the weather seems to be in our favour!
Don't look!
Y-Yeah.
Come to think of it, Amin's not here yet.
There's still some time left.
Okay! I've got an idea!
Huh?
Where are those guys?
There's nobody here.
H-Hey!
You're two minutes late, Ami!
Good morning, Amin!
You're late, Stupid Chihuahua.
W-Where is everyone?
Hey! Don't run away, Stupid Chihuahua!
Ami, we're right here!
Whoa, this is great!
There's a plum in this that makes it super plum!
Just what I'd expect from Takasu.
Want to marry into my family?
No, I don't.
Geez, you're mean.
Huh?
Come to think of it,
it seems Aisaka-san didn't come. Is she late?
Takasu-kun, go get in touch with-
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, the Stupid Chi' is awake?
I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open.
Wha-
Don't fight when we're on a trip.
That aside, what have you been doing
during summer break so far, Kawashima?
Me?
I've been working the whole time.
Oh, you started working again?
What about Minorin?
Club activities, work, club activities, work, club activities, club activities, work,
club activities, work, club activities, work, club...
W-What about you, Taiga?
I was...
Huh? What, Taiga?
I was making this.
J-Just now, I heard "senpai" in a strange voice! Is this...?
Yeah.
Sampled from CD's with more to them than just
what they advertised; a collection of spirit voices.
I knew it!
No! I've been called out!
Do you enjoy horror stuff like that, Aisaka?
Huh? I might like them...
Oh, that's surprising.
It's also rather surprising that Kushieda's scared of eerie things.
I'm scared of it! I'm scared of it!
I'm super scared of it, you know!
Rather than super scared, you could say I'm incredibly scared-
You see, Minorin is really scared of horror movies, spirits,
and occult things in general.
I see.
That's why we're going to scare Minorin to death.
Then you're going to save her when she's at the peak of her fear,
with a, "I will protect Kushieda!"
This is called the "Scare Minorin, Enter the White Knight" plan!
Either way!
Scary things are absolutely forbidden!
It's the sea!
Sheesh, how far do we have to walk?
Can't you see it already?
Huh?
Let's go around the back.
Keep going that way and I think we'll be on the balcony.
This is Amin's vacation home?!
We're going to be staying here?!
That's right, Minori-chan.
Awesome!
I'm so moved!
But we have to clean the place up first.
Nobody's been here since last year.
Since last year?!
Y-Yeah.
This looks like it'll be one hell of a fight.
What?! We've got this pretty sea right in front of us!
Let's leave cleaning up for last!
What?!
Yeah! We can clean later!
M-Me too!
I'm going too. What about you, Takasu-kun?
Why am I cleaning all by myself?
This feels great!
Hey, hey.
Huh? What's up?
Doesn't that...
...kinda look like someone's head?
Wah, it's a floating corpse!
What should I do?!
I've been soaked in corpse water!
Looks like they're having fun.
Sorry, Minorin! That might be seaweed!
Wah, then it's a seaweed corpse!
You really came, didn't you, Yuusaku.
What should I do?! I've been soaked in seaweed corpse water!
Of course I came.
You can't have Takasu...
...come without his good friend coming along as well.
Are you sure about this?
What about the student council?
What are you saying?
Nothing...
Takasu!
Ami said to go out shopping.
Apparently there's a bike in the shed.
Bike?
If that's the case, take Taiga with you.
Take Aisaka?
I-I'm not going.
I'm scared of bikes.
What?!
Be careful, now.
Yeah, got it.
See you!
You finally had a chance to be alone together.
I had an idea, you see.
Before they come back,
we've got to find somewhere suitable to play out that plan.
You're just embarrassed, just admi-
There was a mosquito there! A mosquito!
Sheesh...
Even if you say "somewhere suitable"...
This is...
...a bathroom, huh?
Gotta clean here too-
Wha-
W-Who's there?!
Sorry! I didn't notice!
Takasu-kun?
I-I'll leave now.
Eh-
You're really bold, aren't you?
Coming in while a girl's showering...
I-It's not like I did it on purpose!
It's okay.
We can keep it a secret from everyone else...
What are you say-
Hey, don't you want to do it?
D-Do what?!
Clean the bath!
Oh my! Just what were you expecting?
What's with that face?! It's a masterpiece!
Taiga~!
Huh? Stupid Chi' did?
Making it sound like she was taking a shower?
Playing with a man's pure heart?
And? Did you finish investigating the second floor?
Useless!
That's why you got tricked by the likes of the Stupid Chi'!
Fine. I'll go check!
And while I'm at it, I'm going to tell her off as well!
Hey, Stupid Chi'!
The Stupid Chi' was actually in the bath.
The Stupid Chi' was...
Boom!
And boom!
And here, it was exploding!
Don't say unnecessary things!
We're back!
You sure bought a lot.
Where's Kitamura?
He's putting the bike away.
I-I see.
Ah! I'll carry them!
I-It's fine!
You did the shopping, after all.
Really?
W-What's wrong?
J-Just now, something... o-on my neck...
It's your imagination.
Y-You're right...
That's right...
Something definitely touched me just now!
Something slippery... like seaweed!
I-It really does smell like seaweed! It's seaweed!
Like an animal spirit entwined in seaweed!
A sea otter? When it comes to being entwined in seaweed, it has to be the corpse of a sea otter!
A sea otter with its stomach pocket filled with scallops?!
It's the curse of the sea otter and seaweed!
No way!
I don't want it spicy!
I prefer it spicy!
I can't eat it if it's not sweet!
Hey, Ryuuji!
I know.
I'll make sure your portion is sweet.
You're giving special treatment to Aisaka-san again...
That will make girls hate you, you know.
Minori-chan too.
You called for me?
Almost done?
Wow, you're skilled!
Y-Yeah...
I just have to add the roux.
Come on, you guys have to prepare for dinner-
Oh, already preparing for supper?
Even I can help out with setting the table.
Y-You...
H-Hey, Taiga!
Yuusaku, are you insane?!
Oh, sorry. I heard Takasu's voice...
So the girls were here too.
Are you stupid?!
Taiga, pull yourself together!
Sorry, sorry!
Hey!
You narcissistic being from heaven!
Give me a nude shot!
Quit it! Quit it, you!
What are you saying,
while looking like that and pretending to be modest?!
Come on, stop it!
Just then,
something black and...
...rather lively...
It was probably a seaweed spirit!
Sea...
...weed?
Kushieda?!
Yuusaku, you're the worst!
Sorry...
Enough, just go!
Y-Yeah...
Be careful, everyone.
There's an evil spirit lurking in this house.
Is there anything I can do?
Make the curry...
...really spicy.
Got it!
Whoa, it looks so tasty!
I made it with what I had available, but...
...as per Kushieda's request, I've made it as spicy as possible.
Yeah! Let's dig in!
Let's eat.
Oh, good! It's good!
It's really delicious.
It's not as spicy as I thought it would be.
Really?
You want to try it too, Taiga?
Really, it's-
Minorin?
Spicy!
It's got spicy-
-in my throat! Rather, it's hot! It hurts!
Here it is!
I've received the full impact of this meal!
There it is again!
Are you all right?
Takasu-kun!
You're the best!
It's super spicy! It's super delicious!
It does indeed have a strange, addictive quality...
I'm starting to feel strange...
Oh, there's seconds too.
Seconds!
I thought I was going to die...
All right.
I'm gonna do the dishes.
Ah, me too-
What?
I think it's because I ate spicy food, but...
...I want some stomach medicine.
Your stomach's hurting?
But I didn't bring med-
Aisaka, are you feeling ill?
I brought some stomach medicine with me.
Since it's in my room, want to come with me?
Eh? T-That's...
Then, I'll leave it to you.
W-Wai-
It's a chance for you to be alone together.
Something wrong?
No, nothing.
Well, take care of her!
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
Ami-chan's stomach hurts too.
Eh?
Or something like that.
What now?
Nothing.
You were spacing out, you see.
Watching you never gets boring.
Is that a compliment?
You're just really complicated.
What's up with that?
More importantly, if you'd like, we could go to the beach toge-
Hey, Takasu-kun, could you get that glass for me?
Ah, I'll wash it.
Sorry. What was that?
Nothing.
Was it enough water?
How is it? Is it working?
Pro... bably...
I see. That's good.
Seeing Aisaka in pain hurts me too.
Oh right. If it hurts, would you like to lie down?
You... have amazing cleaning techniques, don't you?
Well, I'm doing it all the time at work, after all.
Takasu-kun's curry was prepared with splendour as well.
No, not at all.
Oh, yeah!
I'll give you something great as thanks for helping out!
Keep it a secret from everyone else.
Takasu-kun, is the green tea flavour good?
Eh? Oh, yeah, it's good.
Not so much with the azuki one.
Aren't the stars amazing?
I-It's beautiful.
It's just the two of us.
Is this what you'd call a chance?
K-Kushieda, do you have boyfriend?
The seaweed spirit from earlier... Do you think it's still around?
Eh?
Takasu-kun, have you...
...ever seen a ghost?
Huh? No, I haven't.
I believe that ghosts exist,
but I've never seen one,
and I don't believe the stories from people who have.
I see...
And then, you see, I think of something else the same way.
I believe that one day, I'll be in love, get married, and be happy.
But there's nobody who has had it spelt out like that, is there?
I think that the existence of people in the world who are meant to love one another is a bit far-fetched.
I mean, I can't see them.
"Ghosts don't really exist, so I'll never see one in my life",
is how I have resigned myself.
And because of that, there is no answer to your question.
What about Takasu-kun?
Are you someone who can see ghosts?
I think... I want to see them.
Because of that, I go to places with spirits and I watch scary DVDs.
You see, I think that...
...people who are sensitive to spirits would be shocked the first time they saw one, right?
I think there are people who have seen them, but then tried to deny their existence,
while on the other hand, there are those who put in an effort to finally be able to see them.
That's why I don't think you have to resign yourself to never seeing one in your life.
Huh? What's that?!
A UFO?
That's a satellite.
A satellite...
What? I thought it was a UFO.
I think it'd be great if you could see a ghost someday, Kushieda.
Because I think that there's a ghost out there that wants you to see it.
So that's why lots of strange things happened today, right?
Huh?
The seaweed spirit is appealing to me!
What's with that, all of a sudden?
Maybe I'll see them one day?
Huh?
Nothing!
What a weirdo.
Hey, Ryuuji. I think my stomach's all better.
Yeah, and...?
I'm so full!
Somehow, even I...
Hey.
What should we do tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'm talking about that plan, obviously.
You're not doing your part properly at all.
What about you?
I'm the support this time around!
Sheesh, I'm so tired.
Eh?
I kept thinking about how happy I'd be after spending an entire day with Kitamura-kun,
but I was so nervous that I could've died an early death.
You got that right.
Though when I'm with you, I'm completely fine...
What's that supposed to mean?
How rude!
It's so dumb.
This room is so big, yet we're sitting this close to each other...
It's like the habits of being in a small apartment have stuck.
Why, you...
Ryuuji...
I was thinking, you know...
That dream was rather...
Huh? What's up?
Nothing.
I'm gonna sleep.
Huh? Yeah...
Good night.
Huh? Did I put my bag here?
What is this?
And it's somewhat slippery...
Ryuuji!
What do you think this is?
It was in my bag, yet when I touched it earlier, it was still warm.
It's as if someone had just been wearing it...
My room's weird too!
On my pillow, there was long hair-
W-What was that?
That was prob-
T-This is a dream, right?
Yeah! It's a dream!
It's a continuation of that dream where we're living in a dog house and giving birth to dogs!
Then, if we close our eyes, we'll wake up sometime, right?
We'll wake up! We'll wake up!
Right?
banira soruto de
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
banira
バニラ
vanilla
amai dake nara
アマいだけなら
If it's just sweet
soruto kakemashou
ソルトかけましょう
Then let's put salt on
dare yori mo motto motto watashi wo
誰よりももっともっと私を
Because I want you to know more about me
shitte hoshii kara sarakedashitai
知って欲しいからさらけだしたい
More than anyone else, I want to bare my self
demo dekinai no keiken nasshin
でも出来ないの　経験ナッシン
But I can't do it, I've got nothing for experience
modokashi sugiru
モドカシすぎる
It's too frustrating
demo amai dake no ai wa chotto
でも、アマいだけの愛はちょっと
But a love that's just sweet
watashi ga motomete iru mono to wa chigau
私が求めているモノとは違う
Is slightly different from what I'm seeking
shiro to iware tara
シロと言われたら
If I'm told it's white
kuro datte icchau
クロだって言っちゃう
I'd say it's black
sunao ni nare nai
素直になれない
I can't be honest
amanojaku
アマノジャク
I say one thing but do another
suki to iware tara
スキと言われたら
If I'm told, "I love you"
daikirai datte
ダイキライだって
I'd say, "I hate you"
ureshii no ni nani itte n darou
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろう?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
amai banira ni
アマいバニラに
Like putting salt
soruto kakeru yo ni
ソルトかけるよに…
Into sweet vanilla...
Next Episode Preview
Fireworks
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Horror movies are scary!
Ghosts are scary! Monsters are scary!
Calm down, Kushieda!
But the scariest might be UFOs...