Come watch, it's time for the appearance
of the three leaves! (yay)
"Three Leaves, Three Colors"
Morning! I'll have three bowls
(Did you eat, eat, eat, eat up your
feminine charm along with your food?)
Wait, wait, wait a minute! I'm bad at P.E....
(I heard something good--
I've found her weakness... Sorry)
What I really want is to have fun
With my f-r-i-e-n-d-s!
Try talking about silly things
Like our love lives and other stuff like that
Hey, why
Don't you
Have any friends?
"My, you are direct!"
You're arrogant
And high-handed
...etc.
"You have no reservations, do you?!"
Are the three leaves running wild?!
No one can stop them!!
Yoko, have some rolled omelet.
What? N-No, I feel bad.
Hayama is so annoying.
Excuse me, are you a friend of Hayama's?
(Ready, set!)
Go, I, my, ambiguous me! (Go!)
My mind's asleep... (zzz...)
I feel refreshed! Oh, really?
With the three of us (fever!)
we have transcendent wisdom?
But when we're actually together, it's just noisy
(One more time!)
Look! Going my way forcefully forward! (Go! Go!)
Forward! Yeah, going my way up! (Jump! Jump!)
Full speed ahead!
Thanks for your hard work
It's the story of my (wow!)
kind of strange and unusual
Best and strongest life in history
Leave her alone or Satan will burst out
I'm sure this is a high school girl's
Normal?
Everyday?
School life
Stand.
Bow.
Thank you very much.
What will you eat?
Maybe lunch set A.
I'm starving!
I am Yoko Nishikawa.
Because my once wealthy father's company
went bankrupt, I now must live as a commoner.
And the other day...
--Futaba, what do you usually eat for breakfast?
--I was able to make...
...two wonderful friends!
Plain rice!
Yoko, have some rolled omelet.
What? N-No, I feel bad.
Please, have some.
But, there will be less for you.
It's fine.
But, then you...
But...
It's fine.
No!
This is way too polite! Relax a little! Re-lax!
R-Relax?
Yup! Like, we should call each other
by nicknames and stuff.
'Cause we're friends!
'Cause we're friends! 'Cause we're friends!
Friends...?
Have we been friends this whole time?
Oh, we haven't been?
Gosh, we're just teasing.
Right?
Hm?
Wh-What...?
A cat!
Perhaps it is a stray.
Hayama?
T-Too cute!
"Nothing Good for You Is Tasty"
What's the matter widdle kitty? Are you lost?
You're so cute!
Hayama looks quite pleased.
She does like cats.
Not just cats. I like dogs, birds, cows,
and horses, too! I love them all!
It's my dream to buy an island
and build Hayama Park!
How grand!
Unexpected from her, huh?
Hmph, is that how you see me?
Do you keep pets at home?
Yeah, a cat named "Bel."
A cat!
My family named her, though.
She's called "Beelzebub" or "Bel" for short.
Beelze--
Beelzebub! A prince of demons.
Also known as "Lord of the Flies."
"Demon"
A-A demon who takes the form of fly!
She was swarming with flies
when we took her in.
So we named her "Bel."
Hey, you have a minute, Hayama?
Oh, yes?
If you don't mind, can you hand
these out before the next class?
--Okay.
--Can you also collect the homework notebooks during break?
--Man, that's a lot of worksheets!
--How could I be thinking that Hayama is a demon?
She is such a good student.
That's okay.
Being class representative seems difficult.
I didn't really want to be class
representative, but they insisted.
Oh, why didn't you refuse if you dislike it?
Well, I don't like having to do random duties,
but it'll look good on my resume.
What?
"Class Rankings"
Shucks, I tried really hard this time, too.
"10th Selina Nishiyama"
You're amazing, Nishiyama!
You're tenth in our grade!
And what about Hayama?
Ah, don't say it! I don't want to hear it.
"4th Teru Hayama"
Yeah, you're right! Grades aren't everything!
This is higher than your rank in middle school!
It's a huge improvement already!
Hayama is so annoying.
She's always getting in my way.
I wanted to be class representative, too.
I know, right? It's too bad.
They randomly chose her just because
she looks like a class representative!
It wasn't random. It was part of her plan.
Huh?! Haya... ma!
An acquaintance of yours?
Hayama had a "talk" with her before.
She called me out for being "full of myself."
It was so scary!
--What's going on?
--Did something happen?
She's crying...
You won't get away with this!
Do people actually say that in real life?
Oh, that was so scary.
Hayama...
Perhaps she is a demon.
"Quadratic Equation"          "May 9th"
So, what if you apply this formula to this problem?
Todoroki, come up and try the first problem.
Okay.
Hey, get those legs moving!
Ugh, they're timing us for this? Why-- Huh?
Hayama! She's beating me!
Or not. I'm about to lap her.
C'mon! Run like you mean it,
or it's another lap for you!
Don't say anything. I can't
talk back to a teacher!
Don't say it!
I'm tired!
--I-I'm gonna die.
--You okay?
How can I be? She was trying to run us to death!
So even the great Hayama
has a weakness, huh?
--Nishiyama.
--What was that for?
Don't mind her, Futaba.
The poor thing. She looks down on people over
such small things. We should be nice to her.
Who are you calling "poor thing"?!
Yeah! And you are not small.
You have a great figure!
What are you talking about?
--W-Well, I do make sure to do
exercises and have balanced meals!
--Beanpole.
--W-Well, I do make sure to do exercises and have balanced meals!
I win!
That's tough. You have to be careful
of what you eat or your weight fluctuates.
You're still young, too.
That's totally wrong! Why are you
always making a fool of me?!
What? You're so mean. That's not true.
Hayama...
--Bye!
--See you tomorrow!
Oh, I still feel nauseated.
You really dislike running, don't you?
Not running specifically,
but I don't have stamina.
I'm running on empty.
Hayama?
You're definitely not running on empty!
"Please take care of us."
Oh my, have they been abandoned?
Wh-What should we do?
T-To think such young kittens have
been abandoned... It's terrible!
What in the world were they thinking?
Hayama actually has a gentle spirit.
"Please take care of us."
"Please take care of us"?
I'll show you who can take care of you!
Whoever abandoned you, show yourself!
That's the voice of a demon!
I found homes for two kittens,
but there's one left...
I-It would be a struggle, but I can house it!
First, I will find a property that allows pets.
That's the first step?!
I wonder if there are any cat-lovers around.
Oh, cats?
Kondo?
Nishiyama used to have a cat.
A cat? I did have one,
but it died three years ago.
Your family had that cat since before you
were born, right? You really loved it, huh?
Hey, stop saying unnecessary things!
Nishiyama!
There is worth in the existence
of someone like you!
So there wasn't any before?!
I'm home.
I actually took it.
Well, there was no other choice.
Nobody else could take it.
I don't like the fact that it
was from Hayama, though.
Ow...
You need a name.
One that will give you a long life.
Yeah! We're not done yet!
What?! Remember how I wanted
to make nicknames for all of us?
Did you?
That's right. A nickname!
We need nicknames to become true friends!
We don't have to...
Hayama, Futaba! Please, give me
a splendid nickname.
Well, er...
Yokoppy!
Princess Haircut.
Not approved!
What? You don't like it?
No, no, they are unacceptable!
Something more lovely, noble,
and intellectual would serve better!
Er...
Former Rich Girl!
Princess Haircut.
As I was saying...!
Please address Miss Yoko as "Miss Yoko."
Oh, it's just you, Yamaji?
You appeared without a sound, so I thought
you were someone suspicious.
Oh, you jest.
If you please, address Miss Yoko as "Miss Yoko."
Wha--
Understood!
Got it!
Miss Yoko!
This was not what I imagined
my nickname to be...
Okay, so Miss Yoko is "Miss Yoko." Next is...
Wait, what's Hayama's first name?
I'm Futaba Odagiri. Miss Yoko is
Yoko Nishikawa. What's your first name?
Isn't this nice? It's so fun to eat outdoors.
Hey, come on! Tell us your first name!
Come on, what's your first name? Hey...
Miss Yoko, what's your next class?
Oh, it's--
Sheesh, why won't you tell us?
What's your first name?
Teru!
Te...
...ru?
Teru?!
Teru. That's my first name.
Teru! Miss Teru! Terumi!
Don't keep saying it!
Nothing wrong with it. It's cute. Right?
Yes, it is quite a lovely name.
Oh, and Terurin... ?
No way!
Teru, I don't have chopsticks in my lunch.
You can just get disposable ones
at the school store.
Oh, that's right! I knew I could ask you!
You're so smart. I didn't think of that.
Excuse me, are you a friend of Hayama's?
Oh, I'm not her friend. I'm her older sister.
What?!
Her sister?!
She is Hayama's...
A demon and an angel!
Oy, oy! It's past April Fools!
I know...
Nice to meet you. I'm Kou, Teru's older sister.
Pleased to meet you.
Are you Yoko?
Yes!
I knew it! Wait here for a little.
Wait?
Here, take one. I made them from scratch.
--Oh no...
--Why, thank you.
No fair!
Go ahead.
Yay!
--Oh...
--I'll try it!
Futaba?!
It's full of nutrients!
Homemade fermented bean candy!
--Fermented bean?!
--Yoko, I heard that you only eat bread crusts.
Teru is all black on the inside, but don't worry
about that and get along with her, okay?
Wh-What?
Don't get the wrong idea.
She can be airheaded, so she'll say and do
interesting things without meaning harm.
Airhead?
Oh, gosh. Lunch will end if you don't hurry.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm going to try out
new ingredients next time!
Yeah, yeah. That's nice.
It's still early, Bel.
It's the weekend. Let me sleep in a little.
B-Big Sis!
Good morning, Teru.
Wh-What is it?
I'm going to make a breakfast drink for you.
A drink?
Special garlic banana milk!
I'm still sleepy...
Aw. Then, I'll give some special
garlic banana milk to Bel instead.
I'm up!
I told her not to put garlic in.
Teru, you'll come grocery shopping
with me today, right?
Huh?
Right?
"Maekawa Fruits & Vegetables"
It's been a while since we've gone out together.
Yeah. So, what do we need to get?
Let's see. Books and--
Books?
I'm going to buy a cookbook.
And a photo album.
Photo album?
Oh, Hayama!
Oh!
It's Futaba!
What are you two up two? Shopping?
Yup, it's been a very long time
since I've gone out with Teru.
You two sure do get along!
I'm an only child, so I'm jealous.
Only when she's not trying to poison me.
Are you shopping, too?
Yup, to get some giblets.
Wow, that sounds good!
What?
I'll buy some giblets, too!
Oh, Big Sis, wait!
"Super Daimaru"              "Meat Fish Vegetables"
Giblets, Chinese yam, okra, and mulukhiyah,
"Spring Sale!"
all mixed together to make a candy!
"Chinese yam, Okra, Mulukhiyah, Cookbook, Photo album"
Blegh...
Why are you obsessed with health foods?
And then making candy out of them?
They're easier to eat in candy form.
Today's flash sale is mayonnaise! 500 grams
for 98 yen! Limit one bottle per person!
--Sale?
--Don't miss your chance!
"Today's Special Sale!"
I-I have succeeded!
"Mayonnaise"
In getting the special-sale mayonnaise
that is limited to one per person!
Miss Yoko!
I see. So, you and your sister
are out grocery shopping?
"Raffle Ticket"
However, are you sure about this?
Can I really take these raffle tickets?
Of course. We got a lot.
Win every time! Fifth place prize is
pocket tissue! Fourth place is a coffee set!
You're too excited.
Third place is new crop rice!
You, too?!
"Central Shopping Arcade"
"Arcade Raffle"
Fifth place prize of pocket tissue...
Fourth place, coffee set!
"Arcade Raffle"
Yeah!
"Koshihikari Rice"
Third place, the great new crop rice!
An unselfish win?
"Koshihikari Rice"
Ack! I can't believe Hayama won when I didn't!
Congratulations!
"Third place, New Crop Rice"
"Second Place, Halogen Heater"
"First Place, One Night Hot Springs Vacation"
Teru, help me!
Wh-What?!
She has pretty good luck with these.
That's not just "pretty good"!
She also got the bathhouse tickets from before.
She did?!
I can't carry all this!
I'm glad Yoko and Futaba
took the heavy things for us.
I'll give the hot springs vacation
to Mom and Dad and--
--Oh no!
--What?
I forgot to go to the bookstore!
Even if you buy a cookbook,
you'll put other ingredients in anyway.
And... a photo album.
A photo album?
There were lots of photos in the closet.
Photos from when we were little.
Big Sis! You'll fall!
Don't worry! I'm a good climber.
A little more...
Almost there!
I'll give the pretty butterfly to Teru.
Ouch! I fell.
Oh, Teru!
You used to get sick and get hurt a lot.
I'm pretty healthy now.
Don't take it for granted. Make sure
you get all your nutrients regularly.
Is she always nagging about nutrients...
Okay!
I'm going to try my best at cooking!
...because she's worried about me?
Thanks.
She says it's a thank you for yesterday.
They're rice balls! With liver,
white roe, and bitter melon!
Mixed?!
But, where's all the stuff you bought yesterday?
Th-This is not a matter
of if it's healthy or not.
But Hayama's sister went out of her way to make
them for us. It's food that she made for... us!
Woah!
--She's eating it!
--Miss Yoko is actually a brave hero!
Please, do not allow Miss Yoko
to consume strange foods!
Miss Yoko, you don't have to!
Yeah, even if this is your
rare chance to eat liver!
Don't encourage her!
Nothing good for you is tasty.
Oh, now that you mention it...
Don't encourage her!
Miss Yoko!
Hello, my name is Shino Sonobe.
I'm the Nishikawa family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative,
the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is
so entertaini-- I mean, wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Even if I'm pitch black inside
Even if I can't live in luxury
Even if there's lots
With three of us, we can eat it all!
Clever and smart
I'm living resolutely
With a full tummy
That's how I spend my days
What makes me smile?
"Food!"
"Money..."
"I can't say here"
We each have our own happiness
Let's enjoy life as much as we want
It's crazy and messy
Look, it's the rock scissors parade
If the three of us gather
For rock, paper, scissors
We'll tie
And it'll never end
The parade's started, and you have to join
The answer to one times three
If you want to know, then come here!
Being rich is not all that wonderful.
But that does not mean my current life is great.
You wouldn't be green after eating
a strange rice ball either.
But, all of us being able to eat the rice balls
that Hayama's sister made for us...
...makes us happy.
Your real thoughts are leaking out.
Miss Yoko!
"Next time: A Taste of Maid"