Needs more of a beat...
Like this!
Maybe I'll up the tempo a bit...
Alright!
The drums set the rhythm,
the melody stimulates your ears
as the lyrics burst out.
That moment you realize deep down
that this is what you've been looking for...
It's as if my heart's about to burst,
ready to leap into the sky!
Already midnight...
Wait, wait, wait!!
What am I even doing?!
I need to study! Study! STUDY!
Overlapping these just feels off...
Right. Maybe if I lower this a bit...
STUDY, DAMMIT!
3: UNORTHODOX PROBLEMS
No way!! Focus!
Sorry...
The pigeon was on the rhythm...
Focus!!
I'm still on the same page as yesterday...
It's like I wasted an entire day!
An acoustic song...
Did Momoka-san have an acoustic guitar as well...?
Please excuse me...
Oh, Nina-chan! Welcome!
Have you eaten yet?
Ah- not yet...
We've got buns! Hot! Steamed! Buns!!
That's just bad manners.
See? You're a real rich kid, Nina.
Sauce? On buns?
It's tasty, trust me.
Ah! You see...
I got these from a friend at school,
who had some spares from her job.
Oh...?
Do you like it?
Yeah! It's delicious.
Nice. I'm glad to hear it.
- So, about that song...
- Oh, is it ready?
- If only it were that easy...
- Really? Then why did you make me come?
I don't exactly live next door, you know?
I wanted to talk about what type of song we want to make.
Like, I'm struggling to see what would best suit us three.
As long as I get to jam on the drums I'm good with anything, really...
And you, Nina-chan?
Yeah! It's delicious!
If I recall, I showed you this app like a week ago, right?
And you already made something like this?
You're incredible!
I mean... Momoka-san told me that with this
I could write songs by feel than by music sheets.
So I gave it a try...
Still, to have gotten this good...
You must've spent like 8 hours a day on it, huh?
Where'e you going?
I'm going home.
I need to study! STUDY!!
Guess I was right.
Momoka-san! Didn't I already tell you that I've got no time for this?!
Especially with my exams coming up!
There you go again.
I know...
If you know, then don't do it.
B-but...
I get it, I get it.
I was the one who showed you the app.
I'll uninstall it, so just focus on singing-
It's fine, you can keep it.
Make up your mind then!
It's all my fault!
I just need to balance both activities, while Momoka-san takes care of the band. Right?!
Who are you talking to...?
To MYSELF!
Bye. See you next practice.
I swear, what's her deal? I can never figure her out.
Ah. I'll head home too then.
Ah wait, I've still got some buns...
You can have them all. See ya!
Nina-chan!
Wanna walk to the station together?
Ah... sure.
Still, you're incredible.
To write a song out of nothing.
I could never do that.
I mean... I just cobbled together some pre-existing sounds...
But the one who needs to come up with the lyrics is you, right?
I guess...
S-sorry, I need to head to the store real quick.
Let's go then.
O-oh no... I...
Thought I'd head home by foot, so...
I see...
Bye then.
Subaru too...
Go yourself! ...uh, can't you?
Got my shift at work after this. Can't you?
It's not that I can't... not do it, but...
Nina! It's okay if it's after school,
but just get it back to her.
Do it for the buns!
Wow, I'm seeing it in person...
Wow, look.
Must be a bumpkin.
Which way?
Ehm...
Eeehm...
Gotta be here.
Or not.
I'm here!
Please excuse me...?
Can I help you?
Y-yes!
Ehm... Is A-awa-san...
Awa-san?
Ah! You mean Subaru-chan!
Ah! Subaru!
Yeah, it's good enough as is.
Wah! Nina-chan!
What's up?
Wasn't it hard getting here?
If you had told me where your school is, I would've come for you!
Sorry for the delay.
Here.
Ah! Thank you!
What, you forgot it?
Yep.
I'm such a klutz!
Ah! Everyone's waiting for you!
- Got it.
- See ya!
Goodnight!
You're free now, right?
Wanna grab a bite? Hm?
I'll treat you.
I... have to study... so...
I see. What about this weekend?
Like say, Sunday?
Really, you don't need to worry. I was just doing a favor...
Right then... I'm leaving.
Do you want me to quit?
Would it be better for you if I quit the band?
I'm not an idiot, you know. I can tell you're avoiding me.
Eh... no, I...
I mean, I don't want to get in your way.
There's other bands I could join.
No! You've got it wrong! That's not what I...
It's just that...
I'm sorry.
You sure?
Yes. I mean, I can always study later...
Though I guess that was just an excuse...
I meant about me, not you.
I started music club when I was in middle school, so...
...it's not like I'm that good at it anyway.
Being in a band means you're someone who
can't cut it on their own,
so it can often end up a mess.
If you have conflicting opinions,
you can't keep them to yourself.
Because if you just care about keeping appearances,
something's bound to go wrong.
So if there's something you're not happy with, I say out with it!
No... it's not that I'm not happy with you...
It's all my fault.
Stop being such a broken record.
Everyone's going to hate me anyway.
No! Focus! That's not it!
I just... distance myself from everyone.
And then that leads people to try and get closer with me...
Hm? And what's wrong with that?
Nothing wrong, but...
It's just that when someone tries to get friendly with me...
"You really thought it'd work out?"
"As if I could have it this easy!"
...I keep having those thoughts.
Ugh, what a pain you are.
That why you quit school too?
That's not it. It's just...
Wait! Where did you hear that...?
Somewhere.
Must be nice, the view from that high horse.
You know,
You know nothing about me.
Just so you know, even if I am going to acting school,
that doesn't mean I'm bound to get a degree.
We're the same in that regard.
Even so! You want to be an actress, right?
That means you've got a dream to chase after!
You've at least got something to pride yourself on!
That's why I said that you don't know me.
Do you know who she is?
I get the feeling I've seen her before...
Detective Grandma on the Case.
Rebrodacasts every afternoon.
She's my actual grandma though.
Oh?
She won't ever shut up about how I've gotta follow in her footsteps.
She said I was going to acting school or she'd kick me out.
Then, you don't want to be an actress...?
Honestly, not really.
And you continue going to acting school...?
Yep. And I hate myself for it.
Why keep doing something
I'm not interested in?
Unfortunately, those around me don't see it that way.
Everyone says it's just natural for me to follow in my family.
Why a band then?
I guess it's my modest way to rebel.
Ever since middle school I didn't want to end up in the acting club, so...
Since I liked bands, I joined the music club.
Gave it a shot and had a blast.
I even ended up forming a band in secret.
Your grandmother doesn't know?
No way I could.
Oh, by the way! Seen Hachiko yet?
Aren't we gonna look like bumpkins?
So what? You're the real deal after all.
If I feel like talking, I'll make you hang out with me.
From now on you're my bestie Nina! You dummy!
Girls Band Cry.
SUNDAY NOON
A street show?
Yeah. Thought it'd be a good place to start.
I've already booked a place for the weekend.
Didn't we agree to finish making a song first?
That's obviously still the plan.
But you know, I wanted to get a feel for a show...
...and for the three of us.
- With a show?
When I saw the pic you took together...
...you come off like a cocktail of tension and unease.
- Rude.
- I agree.
But that's exactly why I called out to you.
That goes for both of you.
- What do you think, Nina?
- It's all too sudden, but...
...I might get what she means.
Even so, can we really throw a show without a bassist?
You don't play anything, right Nina?
Relax, it's just a local event. We'll manage.
Besides, I've got this bad boy.
What's that?
A looper.
You feed it sound just like this...
See?
Ooh...
Ehm... when you say "street show", surely...
You don't mean performing in front of people?!
What else? I mean, didn't we meet at a street sho-
- Where do you think you're going?
- Home.
Get back in here.
Let me go! I wasn't told any of this!
Pipe down! You sang at the station, right?
It's the same thing!
Even if you say that, I'm not going!
There's no way I can pull that off!
Don't worry. If anything happens, I'll cover up for you.
Then shouldn't you be singing, Momoka-san?
Since you're so much better than me?
Sure, wanna do guitar then?
You know I can't play it!!
I told you already. I want you as our vocalist.
Why?
You'll get it when you sing. Trust in me.
I'm going home.
Then you don't mind quitting the band?
Indeed.Thank you for everything.
Wait--
It's okay.
That's cheating, forcing me to leave the band!
What kinda logic is that?
- But I mean, I--
- Stop chickening out!
Whether you kill it or suck at it,
succeed or fail,
you're gonna have regrets eitherway.
That's just who you are.
- That's....
- ...the truth.
So just take all you're feeling
and pour all of it into singing your heart out.
Don't you agree?
Match point! It's Nina's loss.
Subaru-chan, shut up.
Turn that anger into music!
That's what makes you who you are!
Ooh, they've got some sweet gear.
Yeah. Though really, it's just that they're the chepest too.
Let me see, let me see.
Yeah, pretty sweet.
Nina, do you have the song we made before memorized?
I tried to include a bit of the song you made on the app.
I do.
Let's give it a shot then.
Why else do you think we're here?
But I can't so suddenly...!
Like I told you, stop chickening out.
It's practice. Doesn't matter if it turns out good or bad.
You're bound to fail anyway.
Catch.
More slowly.
One, two, three, four.
How was it?
I got goosebumps...
So many goosebumps!!
See?
You fell straight into Momoka-san's trap.
Now that you've had a taste, there's no more going back.
But... why?
You see, human bodies...
...react to the electric waves of music
and can't help but dance.
Singing and dancing is hard-coded into our DNA.
Am I wrong?
Ah, right.
Something wrong?
Nothing, just happy to see you like this again.
Really?
Yeah, I also got goosebumps.
Come on, gimme a song.
Yes!
A regular with a beer.
A regular, without the onions.
A regular...
What, you hungover?
You're the ones who told me to sing my heart out...
That's because no one can sing like that!
Shut up already...
"Th...thenks fur the mealll..."
Well, you'll get your voice back,
by tomorrow, so go easy on it, okay?
Are you a band?
I noticed the guitar.
If you're up for it, come see us.
Thank you very much.
SHIN-KAWASAKI (TENTATIVE)
...so she said.
And?
I was thinking we could tell them about us too?
Fine, I'll go.
Thanks for the meal.
Right, gotta bounce.
Where to?
My job.
Later!
You know, she treated us both today too.
To gyuudon, and the karaoke too.
What is she looking at?
Those are Momoka-san's former bandmates.
Over there.
Now then, our next band is having their very first debut!
A female trio from Kawasaki!
Make some noise for...
..."Shin-Kawasaki" ?
We need a good talk later. And a better name.
I already told you, it's just tentative.
Sorry for being late.
Don't tell me...
...that's your stage outfit?
Is it no good?
Like I told you, you gotta bare your heart naked.
Go get changed.
Ehm. Testing, testing.
Nina, I thought it'd be best if you wore something you wouldn't like.
Don't think about it too hard.
Just throw your emotions out there.
Don't panic. I'm here with you.
Nina, you're a spineless coward.
One who can't believe in herself.
You're like a big ball of self-inflicted complexes.
That a compliment?
Come on Nina! It's our turn!
All that energy and emotion you've accumulated...
That's... what we call rock.
Rock...?
No one knows who you are.
No one cares who you are.
But doesn't that make it more fun?.
Nina... let's Rock'n'Roll!
If nothing changes
no matter how long I wait
Then there's no one who'll reach out to me, no one to care
It's not as if the pain disappears
when you blame someone else
I pray to say goodbye
to these cowering days
While my knees are all the way up to my chest
Even if I don't believe in no God
who'd abandon me like this
- Shut the hell up!
- (Shut the hell up!)
- Leave me alone!
A stranger I don't even know
is singing me a song
telling me with all their voice that I'm not alone
And I'm sure some souls would be saved
with just those words alone
But I don't know.
Or do I?
Is that so?
I forgot.
What a pain.
I wanna break.
I've got no courage left!
Someone hurry up and tell me
a reason to live
After all, there's many that could just replace who I am
You can't just tell me to be myself, it's not that easy
Take it back if it's for granted
In the end, I really am
bursting with dreams
Is there anyone out there...?
This is... incredible...
This is ROCK!!
SUBARU: Leaving the band, sorry!
Next Episode:
"(SHOCKING) GRATITUDE"