When watching TV,
make sure the room is well lit,
and watch from a distance.
Got it?
Kuzuha-sama, please give me another chance!
I, the butler of modern tops, will go.
No, I, the butler of mecha beetles with wheels, will go.
No, I, the butler of mountain bike fighters, will go.
No, to be honest, I'm a little tired of this.
What?
Shion. If I am correct,
our school's culture festival is coming up, right?
Yes. Preparations for stands have begun at many places.
Such as sweet shops.
Then it's time to go steal them.
Please hold on.
Allow me, the second of the Unrelated to Kids Hobby Faction, to defeat Ayasaki Hayate.
Don't make me repeat myself. I'm tired of this.
There's something I'd like to give you.
Hey, those are the cakes sold at a store from that town in the last episode.
Not bad.
Do as you like.
Yes Ma'am.
One who masters being a butler becomes the master of the world.
The Butler War that shakes the planet has started!
It's KOTOKO whether you read it forward or backwards.
Just so you know, she's now starting a band.
It's done.
I barely made it in time.
All right, today, I will  go back
to the mansion and see Milady's face.
Hey, Hayata-kun, where are you going?
The school building's that way.
I love festivals!
Student Council Chairman Red!
Vice-Chairman Blue!
Disciplinary Committee Member Black!
The three of us make up...
The Student Council!
You get to shake hands with us at the event hall!
SFX: Oh~~~
Good morning.
I didn't expect you to really get the archway done overnight.
Yes, it was well worth our efforts of crying to you after not doing anything for days.
If it didn't get done, we would have been yelled at by Hina-chan.
I'm glad this was finished without any trouble.
Well, excuse me now.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
We need you to work more in the classroom, too.
U-Um...
Sorry we made you work like a slave alone.
So as atonement, let us perspire with you.
Here. This is for finishing the archway.
We're really, really relying on you.
Then let's hurry.
We need to prepare for the opening.
He's so understanding.
Okay, off we go.
Oh, Nagi. What are you doing here?
Can't you tell just by looking?
It's a solo culture festival.
I-I think you have the wrong interpretation of "culture".
You're right, Hakuou Academy's
culture festival starts today, doesn't it?
I wonder if Hayate-kun stayed there last night, too.
It seems so.
I bet he couldn't refuse anyone and got a mountain of work.
Seriously, there's a limit to being nice.
Hayate is my butler.
He doesn't have to work for everyone like he does.
I see.
If it's bothering you like that, how about
you go take a look at the culture festival?
It's not bothering me.
I don't like crowded places, either.
I heard Hayate-kun will be running a cosplay cafe.
I'm sure he's becoming a popular figure by now.
C-Cosplay cafe, eh?
Sign: Customer
What? An order?
I'm in despair!
Sensei!
No, I mean Master!
No, no. I've still got a ways to go.
Well fine. If you're so worried about Hayate's well-being...
...then I guess I'll go check on him myself.
Yes, thank you very much.
Call the SPs. We'll leave as soon as I get changed.
Nagi still has many childish sides to her.
Or, maybe not?
Th-This is...
Hakuou Academy's culture festival happens once a year.
It's a huge event and attraction within the S-ward in Tokyo.
After all, it's a prestigious school, so famous politicians and celebrities come one after another.
It goes beyond the league of regular culture festivals and invites excellent guests.
And, due to the high level of research presentations, corporate spies and intelligence from around the world pay attention.
SFX: BO~OM
In any case, it's a very cultured three-day culture festival.
May I have another cup of royal milk tea?
Certainly. Please wait just a moment, Milady.
Yes. How may I help you?
Ah, yeah, you. Bring me more tea here, too.
In a pot.
Yes, right away.
Wait, you three! Why are you playing cards?
Your maneuvers are too fast for us to keep up.
Revolution!
I thought we'd stay out of the professional's way.
Revolution counter!
D-Don't say that and please work!
Besides, this is more like a butler cafe than a cosplay cafe.
We are cosplaying.
Um, did you purposely make it into a butler cafe so you can dump everything onto me?
It's not good to fall into paranoia, Hayata-kun.
Okay, since we've regained our energy, let's get back to business.
Sh-She's right. Good work, Hayata-kun.
You can get some rest.
Then I'll make a run back to the mansion.
Ayasaki-kun!
Are you here? You're here, right?
Hi, Katsura-sensei.
There he is!
If you're here, then come with me!
Right now!
Wait-
Hey, Nagi-chan.
Hey, Hayate. So you know, I didn't come because I wanted to see you or anything like that.
I came since Maria asked me to check on you.
Hayata-kun isn't here.
He just got kidnapped by Yukiji.
What? Hayate's not here?
And I came all the way to see him.
We haven't seen anything from the superintendent so far.
That's good. But maintain the alert.
Yes.
It's a festival we're talking about.
There's no way she'll stay quiet.
Ayasaki-kun, what about this?
You do this and that, then this and that, and this goes like that.
How about this?
Get a stamp at the HQ. ASAP.
Hey Ayasaki-kun. You know, I only have five hundred yen on me right now.
Between octopus puffs and okonomiyaki, which should I buy?
I don't know.
Onee-chan!
What is this about?
Why is Hayate-kun trying to organize this mess?
Isn't it your job as a teacher?
W-Well, I didn't know the answers even if they asked me.
And it's a pain in the butt.
Onee-chan!
I'm sorry!
Haruko, can I leave this to you?
I don't mind.
Thank you.
Come with me for a bit, Hayate-kun.
But I haven't given all the directions.
Um, Harukaze-san, about this...
Make your own judgment.
How about this?
I will not take it out of budget.
Here.
My thanks for taking care of them.
Um, why?
Because I can see it on your face.
It says "I'm starving."
It's great to be kind to everyone,
but you'll collapse if you push yourself too much.
Hinagiku-san.
H-Hayate-kun?
H-Hayate-kun!
What's this, Jor-kun? Don't eat things off the floor too much.
Superintendent!
Hayate is in a crisis.
Meanwhile, Mademoiselle Nagi was...
Seriously, where is Hayate and what is he doing?
SPs. Go and find Hayate.
Welcome.
I'm tired, so I'll be here-
What? Hey, everyone!
Where are you all?
Stupid Hayate.
And I made a resolution to come out of the mansion.
I... I wanted to walk through the festival with you.
You there with the twin tail.
Would you like to stop by for a second?
I don't need a fake reading.
Don't say that.
My accuracy is 100%.
What?
Okay, I guess I'll waste some time here as a break.
It's not a bad idea to reconfirm the strength of the bond between Hayate and me.
Very well. Then first, please look into my eyes.
Like this?
Ah, yes, I can see.
I can see your lonely heart.
Allow me to take advantage of that.
Just listen to what...
Sanzenin Nagi! You are now my puppet!
Ishiyaki Imo~ Oimo.
Ishiyaki Imo~ Oimo. = Roasted sweet potatoes. Potatoes.
Mou. Chotto dakeyo.
Mou. Chotto dakeyo. = Gosh. Just a little, okay?
Hayate-kun, are you all right?
Y-Yes, I somehow managed.
Here's a souvenir from inside.
To be fine even after being dunked in Jor-kun's digestive juices.
Jor-kun?
Jormungandr.
It's his name.
His favorite foods are the five main lands, three great oceans, and anything alive.
And butlers are his choice out of everything.
I'm only joking.
Besides, this is airing in a time slot
where we should be considerate of young audiences.
I really couldn't take that as a joke.
Besides, what is with her strange getup?
Superintendent, what are you planning to do now?
Nothing. I'm off-duty right now.
Ehem. She's off-duty right now.
But, it's a different story if someone else entertains me.
Hey, kid. I heard you returned the 100 credits you received as your prize from the Butler Tournament.
What's your reason?
Well, I don't need them.
And it's not good for Milady's educational purposes.
Milady.
Milady!
Milady!!!
Is "Milady" all you have in your life?
You're much more boring that I'd thought you were.
Who cares? Let's forget about him now.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello?
Hayate-kun. Are you with Nagi right now?
What? You mean Milady's at school right now?
Yes. She should have arrived there quite a bit ago by now.
But she left her cell phone behind,
so I tried to get in touch with the SPs, but...
Erina-chan is the best.
The best. The best.
Erina-chan is the best. The best.
Is something wrong, Hayate-kun?
Yes. It looks like Milady has gone missing.
What are you talking about? She's been there for a while now.
There she is!
M-Milady?
Hayate. There's a place I want you to come with me to.
Obviously something looks wrong.
Y-Yes.
Anyway, I have urgent business, so excuse me.
Wait, I'll go, too.
Um, Kuzuha-sama. Was that...
It's his doing.
He's better than I'd thought.
This is getting interesting.
We'll follow, Shion!
Oh no, my blood sugar level...
K-Kuzuha-sama!
Hayate. There's a place I want you to come with me to.
She's in one of those hypnotic states we see often in manga, right?
Yes.
I don't know who it is, but how dare they do this to Milady.
Hey, she stopped.
Hayate, that's that, but I want to eat this with you.
M-May I have one, please.
Yeah. It tastes really good.
Is this really hypnosis?
Lady Nagi takes the perplexed two,
walks around the entire campus, and...
Not here.
Not here either.
Yes, it's here.
This is where I wanted to bring you.
Th-This is the old building.
Then why didn't you bring us straight here?
Hey! I let you control me just once.
Good job, Sanzenin Nagi.
Well done luring Ayasaki Hayate to me.
You call this luring out?
That outfit! You must be one of-
Indeed!
People call me the Mysterious Butler, Puppeteer Limited to Once!
That's so literal.
What is going on?
Milady, please wake up.
It's me, Hayate.
Hayate. I wanted to go around the festival with you.
Being alone is boring.
Milady.
That's right. I must capture him and undo the hypnosis.
Eh?!
A robot?
Ayasaki Hayate. I will defeat you and regain her trust in us.
Milady!
What is this about?!
What the hell?!
Onee-chan?
Hayate-kun. I'll take care of him.
Take care of Nagi.
Um, where did that shinai come from?
I won't forgive those who disrupt the school's peace!
She's going to fight against a robot with a shinai?
Stop running around so much.
Men!
Th-This girl took out a camera.
Shoot out! Anchor!
Hinagiku-san!
You're mine now.
W-What?
Ow...
Hinagiku-san, don't be so rash.
But I can't forgive him.
Come out of there, now!
I need you to undo Milady's hypnosis.
What are you talking about?
The fight's only just begun.
I will destroy Hakuou Academy!
Oh no, the Spark and the jet engine made the super glue come off!
Um... Ah...
What?
What will I do with Milady?
Nagi!
Seriously, Hayate. It's boring to be alone.
Culture festivals can...
Culture festivals like this...
I hate it!
I knew it.
She's still under hypnosis.
I'm the queen of the true Japanese culture.
I will...
I will teach you guys Japan's true culture.
T-True...
...culture?
This!
Not limited to summer and winter.
Autumn is the season of festivals!
Let there be another festival of Japanese culture!
Very interesting.
Superintendent!
Sanzenin Nagi, right?
I see much more potential in you than that butler boy.
Eh?
Show me this true festival you talk of.
Sure.
Milady!
Um-
Don't follow me.
I don't need dinner tonight.
And make sure that midnight show is recorded.
What is going on?
Is she really under hypnosis?
Next week, the true culture festival will take place.
Of all people, we'll fight against Lady Nagi.
And for your information...
There goes my boiled egg.
They were having their sports day.
Nagi and,
Hayate and,
Nishizawa Ayumu's
Butler Network!
Always the lively one! I'm Sanzenin Nagi.
I'm Ayasaki Hayate.
I'm Nishizawa Ayumu.
So here comes the long awaited Hamster service shot!
I can't wait to see it.
No!
This is a shot taken from a certain ramen shop in the Suginami Ward.
It's a snapshot that reveals the line between finishing and not finishing.
What, you can do this to me...
It's very like you, so I think it's good in its own way.
Hayate-kun~
See you.
Um, this is Hakuou Academy, right?
You agree that it's a strange building, right?
We will now sell Sanzenin Nagi's doujinshi at the special school booth.
Ayasaki Hayate. If your doujinshi beats us in overall sales, then we will-
So this is a doujinshi sales showdown.
My manga can't possibly lose to you!
Next time on Hayate no Gotoku.
Why Did It Die?! School Festival Part 2.
Did you know? At the site of the world's greatest doujinshi event, it's difficult for cell phones to get a signal.