Street No. 04
"The Equation of Curses"
And Yet the Town Moves
This should do it.
I wonder if it's any cleaner now?
You're so enthusiastic. Did you make
an appointment to see someone?
I don't have an appointment, but they may come, right?
Like Mr. Moriaki.
Oh?
I thought you gave up on him
because you had no chance?
On this morning's TV horoscope, they said this week I'd
have a close encounter with the person of my destiny,
according to 6-channel.
According to 6-channel?
7th Scorpio: You want to think about
being nice to others first today.
8th Aries: Be conscious of keeping
a regular lifestyle
9th Libra: Even if you're not benefiting,
it's important to be honest
10th Taurus: A tiring day from dealing
with an older person
11th Capricorn: It's important to listen
carefully to what others say
I flip the channel and look at all of them.
6th Cancer: A possibility that what you've
been doing backfires on you
Lucky color: White
7th Leo: You may be tested for
your everyday behavior.
Lucky color: Brown
8th Aries: A little extra effort will go a long way
Lucky color: Viridian
to prepare for tomorrow.
Lucky color: Navy Blue
9th Taurus: Spend today being calm
Today's Fortune: Taurus
Money
Love
Work
Health
Then, the last one I see is the real fortune.
7th    TAURUS
(APRIL 21 THROUGH MAY 21)
Close encounter with the
person of your destiny!
-Don't forget to have
an active spirit at all times
Lucky item: Mug cup
The other day, the first fortune wasn't all that great,
so I took my chances on the next channel.
Then it just kept getting worse and worse,
and by the end I was the worst out of the 13 signs.
They still had the 13 signs?
I don't quite trust the 13 signs, though.
According to the 12 zodiac signs,
I am a romantic, diligent Taurus,
but in the 13 signs, I become
a hyperactive but insensitive Aries.
The 13 signs is correct!
Really, you seem so happy every day. I envy you.
Do I look that way?
Does this mean the person of destiny
I'm going to meet is Mr. Moriaki after all?
"Person of destiny" can mean many different things...
Like an arch nemesis, or a rival, or a natural enemy.
Why an enemy when it's my love fortune?!
Oh, a close encounter with Mr. Moriaki.
Oh?
SUMMONS
1-A #020
Hotori Arashiyama
Detention for Math.
Stay back after school.
NATSUHIKO MORIAKI
Detention?!
Good for you! Your horoscope came true.
Nanairo no tasogare orite kite
Kaze wa nandaka suzushige
Doyoubi no yoru wa nigiyaka
Kurai kimochi sae
Suguni harete
Minna uki uki
Uki uki
Downtown e kuridasou
An equation...
It signifies an equality in which
an unknown quantity is included,
and only when you give that unknown quantity a specific
number will the equality become realized.
Key Points Regarding Finite Sequences (n-Particle Values)
That specific number is called
the "solution of the equation."
Now, in front of me,
is the second natural enemy of my life.
Come to think of it, my first natural enemy
was my homeroom teacher from second grade...
For example...
When you read a story,
each person has their own impression, right?
The fact that there are as many answers as
there are people is what makes language fun!
Arithmetic
On the other hand, in math there is
only one answer for one question.
That's what makes arithmetic fun!
I see! I like arithmetic.
DIVISION
Oh?
We're still in the middle of division,
but we can't divide any further.
What should we do at a time like this?
That's true, what will happen?!
We can't do anything about the remainder,
so we will write "with a remainder of 5" here.
Sensei!
What is it, Moriaki?
Um...
How should I say this... that's so half-baked...
Is that okay?
That's true, I'm at a loss.
But, there's nothing we can do about it, you know?
What would you do, Moriaki?
I don't know.
B-but you said don't leave anything
remaining on your lunch plate...
So is it okay to leave a remainder in division?
I agree!
I agree with Moriaki.
Thank goodness...
I said it while struggling for an answer,
but that got everyone to agree with me!
That's true, it's not good to stop
when there's still something remaining.
But when persimmon is served during lunch,
you'd leave the seeds, right?
In division, the remainder...
...is the same as those seeds.
Ohhh!
Moriaki, sit down already.
You're so stupid... Are you going to eat
the seeds of a persimmon?
Who's the idiot?!
This greatly affected my life later on.
As a result, I became a math teacher.
My homeroom teacher at the time
was the first natural enemy of my life...
Now, my second natural enemy is in front of me.
Um...
Am I the only one in detention?
Math
Detention
In math, the only one who scored a zero
on both the test and the makeup test
was Hotori Arashiyama... you alone.
I see. That's right.
Oh well! It is just the two of us,
so if I thought of this as a date, then, tee hee...
Math
Detention
My stomach is hurting earlier than expected...
ARASHIYAMA,
HOTORI
Hotori Arashiyama...
Note: With him standing in front of Hotori's name on the blackboard,
the visible letters "A" and "Ho," in Japanese, spell "idiot."
A
HO
I value my morals as a teacher.
And I think I do consider my students to a degree...
Even then...
IDIOT
If you can sense what I'm trying to tell you,
then I would greatly appreciate it.
Somehow, I sense it clearly.
IDIOT
Good. Then, listen as you are.
This happened when I was grading the tests...
Note: In Japanese schools, circles represent correct answers
while check marks indicate incorrect answers
Next is...
Arashiyama...
That always happens.
When it comes to grading yours,
that alone is enough to make my stomach sink.
5.   When the equation x³-3x²+bx-2=0
and has the solution x=1+i
solve the quantity for b
5.   When the equation x³-3x²+bx-2=0
and has the solution x=1+i
solve the quantity for b
It's obvious that you've given up
trying to figure out the problem,
but there's an answer confidently written there...
And of course that answer is wrong.
When I see that my stomach starts burning.
Leaving aside what the answer is or how you got to it...
When I see that the shape of the square root
sign is wrong, my head starts to hurt.
And...
If you don't know the answer, then at least leave it blank!
When I finally see a place where
I can put a circle on your answer sheet...
Oh?
It's the circle I draw to mark a zero.
Your answers are surely eating up my life...
Clearly, you are using your test answers
to carry out a premeditated murder!
IDIOT
That can't be!
You like dramatized and exaggerated
things like this, don't you?
What I can't forgive the most is that you make
decent grades on everything except math.
IDIOT
If it comes to this, I can only think
that you have an ulterior motive.
Well, you know... math has nothing to do
with being a detective...
"A detective"?
Right now, I'm a run-of-the-mill high school girl, but
eventually I'm going to be a high school detective girl.
IDIOT
Eventually? How long do you intend
on staying in high school?
Though in fact...
If we continue like this, you won't be able to
advance, so your wish may come true.
It's not impossible for you to be over 20
and still be a high school detective girl.
Detention is so that you don't end up like that.
Now, solve those problems.
Good...
Sensei.
Well, that was fast.
How did this metal sphere of
1 meter diameter fit into this house?
Door
Metal sphere
Now what is this?
Do you know how they were able
to put that metal sphere into the house?
This... You've written in all the necessary numbers, right?
But of course.
Door
Metal sphere
The sphere's diameter is the same
distance from all angles.
On the other hand, the parallel sides of the
rectangle are equal no matter which direction.
That means a metal sphere cannot pass
through any of the doors.
This is impossible.
Door
Metal sphere
The answer is:
they didn't bring the metal sphere in through a door,
but they built the house around the metal sphere.
Just like this...
It's important to have the imagination
to think backwards in life.
And so in math, if you could just give me
the answer first, I can understand quickly...
Corn is delicious, poko.
Maid
Cafe
SEASIDE
Math
What's going on, Hotori? Are you reading a textbook?
That's rare! I hope lightning doesn't strike...
It struck already. If I continue like this,
I'll be a high school girl forever.
My, I'm jealous.
Moriaki got mad.
If you show him a riddle like this, he would get mad.
He's such a straight-arrow.
To show you how straight-arrow he is...
This is something that I heard
from one of the upperclassmen...
Once, there was a female student
who was in love with Mr. Moriaki.
They say she was a clean and lovely lady
who had a love for literature.
She's the same exact character as me,
anything and everything!
What?!
One day, the female student wrote her feelings
in a love letter and handed it to Mr. Moriaki.
The next day a reply letter came.
Wh-what were the contents?! I want to hear it!
Oh, but I'm scared.
My maiden heart shakes in anxiety!
Shaking, shaking...
Just one line of a math equation...
(MAN + WOMAN) ÷ MORALS = 0
They say the formula bluntly stated that morally,
love cannot exist between a teacher and student.
The female student raised a fuss in spite,
and the principal found out about this.
Oh. Now it sounds more like you.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
But the principal said...
Despite the rise of shameless teachers these days,
Moriaki is the model teacher!
The principal was deeply touched,
and so that letter remains on display
in the principal's office to this day.
Happily ever after.
It's not happy at all!
That's how rigid he is.
And so if you don't study hard,
you are really going to be held back.
So similar... My two natural enemies
have similar characteristics!
Not only does she distract me
with stories totally unrelated to math...
...but I'm beginning to think that
even their faces look similar...
Don't tell me...
A grown-up Hotori Arashiyama traveled back
through time to become my homeroom teacher...
No...
That can't be... I don't believe
in science fiction or the occult...
What has gotten into me...?
Oh!
I did it!
Show it to me.
I'll check your answers.
MORALS * LOVE
What is this?
It's an equation that would overturn
the equation from the story.
I'm going to show him the next time I get detention.
You're going to be held back for sure, you know?
The unknown quantity that makes the equality
become true is called the "solution to the equation."
At times, "there is no solution" is the correct answer.
As a result of
showing him
the equation
MORALS * LOVE
Mr. Moriaki, have some coffee.
Thank you.
Here, Mr. Kameda as well.
Oh, why, thank you. I'll have some.
A long time ago, we used to say
if you pour cream in here,
the initials of the person you like will float up.
Despite your looks, you're such a romantic, Mr. Kameda.
Despite my looks...?
Hmm, I should try to see if "N. M." comes up...
N. M. for Natsuhiko Moriaki!
I see...
Mine looks like pi.
Whoa! He totally ignored my N. M.!
It's not an initial or anything?!
That means that I'm in love with the ratio
of a circle's circumference to its diameter.
Well, I do like it...
What about you, Mr. Kameda?
Mine should be my wife's initials,
or else I'd be in big trouble.
CURSE
Curse?!
What?! The chair suddenly collapsed!
The height adjustment lever is broken...
Oh no...
If I put weight on it, it'll collapse...
The desk next to mine is open...
How about exchanging that chair with this one?
I'll do that.
Such an ominous way to start the day...
Maybe because of the curse initial...
Don't say such a bad thing, Ms. Nishi!
Besides, it's not an initial...
Hey, Mom! Something is wrong!
Hotori is putting something on her face!
I told her to put some moisturizer on
because the air is dry.
Hmm, she's becoming more girly, huh.
I wonder.
I suspect she can't even tell the
difference between lipstick and a glue stick.
What? What's wrong?!
My eyes! My eyes!
My face is burning...
And it's feeling cool!
What did you put on?!
HAIR
RESTORATION
KING
Oh!
HAIR
RESTORATION
KING
The shape of the bottle is similar,
so you must've made a mistake...
HAIR
RESTORATION
KING
Skin Miss
I hate you Dad!
Why do you have hair growth formula
when you still have hair?!
Idiot! It's because of the hair growth formula
I haven't gone bald, you see!
Arrgh, it burns. I can't open my eyes,
so I'm going to be absent from school!
Don't say such a stupid thing!
...and that's why I was so late.
How do you come up with stories upon
stories about why you're late?
I would like to mention, truth is stranger than fiction.
To think you have to put on something
that stings so badly...
Adult men must have it hard.
Is your hair okay?
I'm fine right now, thank you.
If it starts to fall out from stress, it's your fault.
You're transferring responsibility on to me!
You show no sign of remorse...
I am going to start class, so go to your seat.
The continuation to your story will have to wait.
Stay behind after school.
YES,
TEA
Hmm. Well, I can't say it never happened.
I almost brushed my teeth with face wash.
You're so careless!
You're one to talk!
I got scolded.
I was trying to come to your rescue, and what do I get?
Normally if you put something
that nasty in your mouth,
you'd never make the same mistake again.
So you have gotten the two confused.
Summons                                             Summons                                                 Summons
2-B Oda                                    2-A #020    Hotori Arashiyama                   3D-009 Shikao
You'll know when                        Re: Your tardiness                           Please return manual.
you get here.
Amano                                         NATSUHIKO MORIAKI                             Serizawa
Oh! What is this!
Oh man. Being summoned because of tardiness,
are you in middle school or something?
He was serious about me staying after school?
The math teacher Moriaki is a straight-arrow.
To show you how straight-arrow he is...
The story about the love letter, right?
I heard it before from Tattsun.
"Morally, a love relationship between
teacher and student cannot be realized."
I have info on the continuation.
The continuation?
Who would've guessed that the female student,
after a period of 5 or 6 years had passed,
became a teacher at this school.
But it doesn't seem like they are going to become lovers.
It's important to know when to give up, poko.
My! What beautiful weather today, too.
Before it gets dark, let's go home, go home.
I was going to make such a natural escape,
but I couldn't fool him...
You were very unnatural,
so I remembered that I had summoned you.
I have work, so please keep it short.
That's up to you...
I thought of something I should never think as a teacher!
To Arashiyama, who troubles me daily, a little payback...
Whoa!
If I let her sit on that broken chair,
she would be so surprised...
How could this be?!
I didn't know I had such a sense of humor in me!
Faculty Room
What happened, Ms. Nishi?
I'm sorry, I spilled the coffee...
But I finished wiping it up.
I see...
Oh?!
I don't know which one is the chair
that collapses when you sit on it!
Unfortunately...
I'll have to cancel Operation: Make Arashiyama Fall...
Oh!
That means, on which chair am I supposed to sit?!
* Basic lecture styles
MINOR                                                                                         depending on
the weight of the offense
Lecture style when the offense is minor.
* Basic lecture styles
INDISCRETION                                                                           depending on the
weight of the offense
Lecture style when the offense is slightly major.
* Basic lecture styles
SERIOUS                                                                                  depending on the
weight of the offense
Lecture style when the offense is major.
Regardless of the style, I'll have to sit
on one of these chairs!
Say the chair collapses while in front of Arashiyama...
Whoa!
Without a doubt, my dignity will collapse as well.
Which one is the bad chair?
I can't tell just by pressing on it with my hand...
If this was going to happen, I should've
marked it or something this morning...
Cancel today's lecture.
Is an educator going to run away
from the place of education?!
Okay, I will sit down!
Huh... Go ahead.
Damn it! You don't even understand how I feel!
I just noticed, but the letter
"pi" looks like "death"... Ominous...
Death
Snap out of it! Omens and luck do not exist!
What is certain is that the possibility
of this chair collapsing is 33.3333 percent...
What are you doing?
Ah, n-nothing.
Okay, Arashiyama. I'm going to sit down.
So you sit down, too.
Okay... then...
No hard feelings.
Teacher, is something wrong with you?
You were mumbling about 33% and whatnot...
O-oh...
In other words! Out of a month,
you are about 33% late! That's it.
I am not late that many times!
At most, twice a week.
Arashiyama...
Mathematics aside, are you not
even capable of arithmetic?
Wha-?
There's school six times a week,
and let's say I was tardy two days each...
Man!
I thought we were going to talk about tardiness?
Why are we doing something like math class?!
She thought of my class as the
same level as simple arithmetic...
No!
I went through all that trouble
to avoid the collapsing chair,
so what am I doing collapsing myself?
For Arashiyama's sake, I'm going to tell her firmly!
As a teacher, strictly!
Today, after this, maintaining my dignity
as a teacher is 100% impossible!
Oh, heave ho.
Today, after this, maintaining my dignity
as a teacher is 100% impossible!
Not pasta, but spaghetti, poko.
2nd Libra: You may hear something
valuable from a stranger.
3rd Virgo: Today's encounters
are sure to be wonderful
4th Aries: You will come up with
lots of ideas at work
5th Cancer: You may hear something
valuable from a stranger.
6th Taurus: You may hear something
Today, Taurus is having a decline in love fortune.
Sis, are you still watching the horoscopes?
Shut up.
Today, Taurus is having a decline in love fortune.
Be careful of trouble with love.
Hmm, not quite.
Takeru, did you pack your handkerchief?
Today, Taurus is having a decline in study fortune.
I put it in, I put it in.
Don't fall asleep during your test.
This isn't quite it, either...
6th Pisces: Maybe one of those days
you have to work hard.
Lucky color: Yellow
7th Scorpio: If you get your colleagues to help,
you'll succeed!
Lucky color: pink
8th Taurus: Talk to family about deep problems.
Lucky color: Black
9th Aries: Instead of worrying,
think about moving forward.
Lucky color: Light Blue
I'll see you later!
Look out for cars!
Today on the 13 signs,
Aries has the worst of luck in finances.
No, no, this is bad, too!
Don't drop your wallet!
And so, that's why I was late.
I can't figure you out!
Hi, Fu, Hi, Fu, Mi, Yo!
Taikutsuya rock damashi tazusaete
Hitorigurashi no bakuon jinsei
Tennen no chouchin fugu na hoppeta de
Machi wo kaosu ni kyo mo makikomu
Tsundere wa intelligence no akashi nari
Kyou mo kareni wa naze ka kokurezu
Takkyu ni inochi wo sasage ashikoshi wo
Kitaeru tame ni doramu tatako
Konna band mo yarase ja ne
Konna member rock ja ne
Mezashite iruno wa ondo ja ne
Tadori tsuku no wa nehan ja ne
Warera wa Meido "Yeah!"
Meido sugata de
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kokora wa meido "Yeah!"
Jiken genba wa
Sanjo sanjo!
"Ach-ahhhh..."
Muteki no meido "Yeah!"
Benpi wa nanzan
Kancho kancho!
"Ach-ohhhhh!"
Kiyoku tadashiku isagiyoku
Seaside wa zessan! Eigyouchu!!
"Meido arigatou gozaimasu!"
And Yet the Town Moves
Next Episode
Hey, Senpai, don't you think Tattsun is a bit awkward?
Yeah. It's true, she's kind of awkward.
How should I say it but awkward.
If she's subtly leaning toward either,
then she's not awkward, but subtly
nestled in an awkward place.
When it comes down to it, it is a bit awkward...
What?! What is it that I'm so awkward about?!
Hmmmm...
It's something that you can't clearly say?!
It's awkward...
Cafe Seaside
Next episode, Street Number Five,
"The Truly Awkward Toshiko Tatsuno."
Cafe Seaside
STREET NO. 05 "THE TRULY AWKWARD TOSHIKO TATSUNO"
Sometimes we turn around and around, poko.
Cafe Seaside