Draw your swords.
If it shows itself,
we'll only have a moment.
Move!
It's fast!
There's no way to
avoid it inside this forest!
It's catching up!
Captain! Let's switch to ODM!
Captain!
You're not going anywhere!
Reinforcements from the rear!
Captain! Give your orders!
Let's take it out! It's dangerous!
We should take care of it!
--It's about to catch up to us!
--Let's take it out here!
That's why we entered this forest!
Isn't it, Captain?!
Captain! Your orders!
Everyone, cover your ears.
I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"Bite"
"The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 3"
An acoustic shell?!
Tell me, what is your job again?
Is it simply to surrender to
your emotions of the moment?
No, it's not.
This squad's mission
is to do everything possible
to keep this brat unharmed.
Down to our last breath.
It's not to keep an eye on me?!
We're going to keep pushing
ahead on horseback. Got it?
Understood, Sir!
Push ahead?! But for how long?!
Not to mention it's
almost on top of us now!
More...
More reinforcements!
They'll get killed too if
we don't hurry and help them!
Eren! Face forward!
Mr. Gunther?!
Don't fall out of step!
Maintain top speed!
Mr. Eld?!
Why?!
Who can possibly stop it,
if not the Levi Squad?!
Another one's dead!
We could've saved him, too!
One person's still fighting!
There's still time to save him!
Eren! Focus ahead and keep moving!
Are you telling me to
ignore the fighting behind us?!
To just run away and
abandon my comrades?!
Yes! I am! Do as the captain says!
I don't understand
why we're letting them die!
And I don't understand
why he won't explain!
Why?!
Because the captain
doesn't feel the need to explain!
But you don't understand that
'cause you're still wet behind the ears!
Now shut up and follow orders!
No...
I can fight on my own, actually.
Why should I always
have to rely on others?
I can just fight on my own!
What are you doing, Eren?!
You're only permitted to do
that when your life is in danger!
That was our agreement, remember?!
Eren!
You're not in the wrong.
If you wanna do it, do it.
I can tell.
He's a real monster,
and not because of his Titan ability.
No matter how hard he's restrained,
no matter what cage he's put inside,
no one can ever tame him.
I want to slaughter every Titan I can!
Eren.
Our difference in experience
is why we don't see eye-to-eye.
But you don't need to rely on that.
Choose.
Will you trust yourself,
or me, these guys,
and the entire Scout Regiment?
I don't know the answer
to that. I never have.
Whether I trusted myself
or the choices of
my dependable comrades,
there was no telling
how things would turn out.
So, just do the best you can
and choose whichever
you'll regret the least.
Eren!
Trust us.
I've come up with a way to
stop you without completely killing you.
Sir?
Before, I said the only way to
stop you in Titan form is to kill you.
But this method will
only leave you mutilated.
It depends entirely
on individual skill, though.
Basically, it involves cutting the nape--
with you in it --off of the body.
The ends of your limbs
will get severed in the process,
but I assume they'll just
grow back anyway, like a lizard.
It creeps me out.
W-Wait.
I'm not sure how
to make them grow back.
Isn't there some other way?
So you want to do it without taking
any risks or making any sacrifices?
--N-No...
--Then prepare for the worst.
We're in the same boat.
You could kill us.
So just relax.
Yes, Sir... I understand.
S-So, I can start experimenting, right?
It's risky, but we can't
risk not testing him, either.
I'll take charge of the planning, then.
Eren...
If you're unsure about anything,
then just learn as you go.
Anything we learn is
easily worth risking our lives for.
You ready down there, Eren?
I'll fire a smoke signal
when we're ready to begin.
Everything after that is up to you!
Understood!
Mm! Even if he becomes a mindless Titan,
this dry well will hold him!
I think!
There's the signal.
I haven't used my Titan form
since I sealed the hole in the wall...
If I go out of control this time...
...the Levi Squad might end up killing me.
Did he not see the signal or something?
No...
I doubt we can expect this
to work so reliably.
Hey! Eren! The test's off for now!
Did something happen?
Ms. Hange...
I can't turn into a Titan...
Not even the bite wounds
on your hands have gone away?
No, Sir.
If you can't turn into a Titan,
our big plans for sealing
Wall Maria go up in smoke.
Figure it out. That's an order.
Yes, Sir...
Don't lose heart, Eren.
B-But...
This just means you're
more human than we thought.
It's a lot better than ending up
dead because you were too hasty.
It wasn't a waste of time.
Yeah. There's no such
thing as being too careful.
Why are they all so calm?
Is it actually okay
that I can't turn into a Titan?
You okay?
Yes...
--Hey!
--What the...?!
What was that explosion?!
Wh-Why now?!
Calm down.
Captain Levi! I--
I don't know what--!
I said calm down...
...all of you.
What?! What was that sound?!
Eren!
What is the meaning of this?!
S-Sir?!
Why did you do it without
permission?! Answer me!
--Wait, Eld.
--Answer him, Eren! Explain yourself!
No! That can come later!
First, you need to prove you aren't
hostile toward us--no, toward humanity!
--Huh?
--Prove it! Now!
You bear that responsibility!
If you so much as
twitch that arm of yours
your head's comin' right off!
I'll do it, too! I really will! Just try me!
Oruo! I told you to calm down!
Captain! Please get away
from Eren! You're too close!
No, you're the ones
who need to get away.
--Step back.
--Why, Sir?!
A gut feeling.
What's the deal, Eren?!
Say something!
--Seriously, I--
--Don't try anything funny!
Prove to us!
--Eren!
--Seriously, I don't--
--Answer the question!
--Do you think we can't kill you?!
I'm serious here!
--Answer this instant!
--Did you not hear me?!
--Okay! Let's do it!
--You're a threat to humanity--
Will you guys please be quiet?!
Eren!
Can I touch that arm?!
Please?! Can I?! Pretty please?!
--I just wanna touch it!
--M-Ms. Hange!
Wait, don't--!
Oww...
...hot!
Damn, it's hot when there's no skin!
I'm talking crazy hot!
Section Commander!
You live like a maniac!
Say! Is it not hot for you, Eren?!
How is it connected to your right hand?!
I really wanna see!
Oh, right!
If I just pull my hand out...
Come on!
H-Hey, Eren! Don't try anything funny!
Wha...?!
Hold on, Eren! That was too soon!
I still wanted to study it!
Captain...
How are you feeling?
Not... very... good...
Until they actually turned hostile,
I never realized how little they trust me...
Of course they don't.
That's why I picked them.
The common belief is that
the first time you come back alive
makes you a bonafide Scout.
But up against Titans,
there's never enough information.
There are always too
many unknowns and uncertainties.
In which case,
you need to be able to act quickly
and make tough decisions
based on the worst case scenario.
But that doesn't mean
they're cold and heartless.
Pointing their blades at you like that,
they couldn't have felt nothing.
Captain Levi.
Section Commander Hange
wishes to see you.
Were you taking a long crap?
Nope. A pleasant one.
I got stuck explaining
things to the top brass.
But, anyway...
...take a look at this.
A tea spoon?
Yep.
That right Titan hand
you created was holding this.
Between the index finger
and thumb, like so.
Huh?
It's hard to imagine it
was through sheer dumb luck.
And, somehow, it hasn't been
warped by the heat or pressure.
Any thoughts on this?
As I recall, I went to pick it up...
I transformed right after that.
I see...
This might explain why
you couldn't turn into a Titan earlier.
Killing Titans...
Blocking a cannonball...
Lifting a boulder...
In each instance, you had a
clear goal prior to transforming.
It's possible self-inflicted
harm isn't the only trigger;
you might need to have
a goal of some sort as well.
It's true that this latest transformation
is similar to when
I stopped that cannon shot.
But...
Transforming into a
Titan to pick up a spoon...
This is crazy...
In other words,
you didn't break the rules on purpose?
That's right.
Huh?
Huh?!
Wait...! What are you doing?!
Oww...
This really hurts...
Eren. I'm impressed
you can bite so deep like this.
We made an error in judgment.
This is our small way of paying for that.
So it's no big deal.
Huh?
Our job is to keep you in check.
And that isn't in the wrong!
So don't get cocky, kid!
I'm sorry, Eren.
We were so scared...
You must be disappointed
in our stupidity.
But... Even so...
We'll be relying on you,
and we'd like you to rely on us.
So...
Please...
Trust us.
Eren!
Hurry! Decide already!
I'll go with you!
Let go!
I'm sorry!
Target is speeding up!
Keep moving!
We're going to outrun it!
Outrun it? There's no way...!
If we keep riding with our backs to it,
we'll all get squashed flat!
But...
We're on the verge of death...
And we're letting our comrades die...
Yet, everyone's chosen to
keep moving forward.
Captain Levi is staring straight ahead.
And the others trust him fully!
I...
...need to trust them, too.
Just as they...
...trusted me!
Fire!
Hitch your horses a little
further ahead, then switch to ODM.
I have to leave for now.
Eld's in charge of the squad.
Hide Eren a suitable
distance away from that Titan.
Look after my horse!
You don't mean...?!
They're going to take that Titan alive?!
What do you think of that, Eren?!
We caught that Titan!
This is the might of the Scout Regiment!
Don't underrate us, you idiot!
Now do you see?!
Yes!
It looks like she's stopped.
We can't drop our guard yet.
I'm just impressed you
managed to lead her to this spot.
The credit goes to the rear squad
members who gave their lives fighting her.
They bought us time.
It would've been impossible otherwise.
Is that so?
Yes.
Thanks to them...
...we get to see
who's inside this one's nape.
Let's just hope they're not
wetting themself inside there...
If, by chance, I'm not me
then who's to say that you're you?
Can you pick up the pieces of your heart
that fell apart like a broken sand castle?
The voice of someone calling out
changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map
Erwin Smith's top-secret plan
was to capture the Female Titan.
Elite members of the Scout Regiment
attempt to reveal its true identity.
But...
"Erwin Smith"
"The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 4"