Youko-chan, have some rolled omelet.
What? N-No, I feel bad.
Hayama is so annoying.
Excuse me, are you a friend of Hayama-san's?
Stand.
Bow.
Thank you very much.
What will you eat?
Maybe lunch set A.
I'm starving!
I am Nishikawa Youko.
Because my once wealthy father's company
went bankrupt, I now must live as a commoner.
And the other day...
Futaba, what do you usually eat for breakfast?
I was able to make...
...two wonderful friends!
Plain rice!
Youko-chan, have some rolled omelet.
What?
N-No, I feel bad.
Please, have some.
But, there will be less for you.
It's fine.
But, then you...
But...
It's fine.
No!
This is way too polite!
Relax a little! Re-lax!
R-Relax?
Yup!
Like, we should call each other by nicknames and stuff.
'Cause we're friends!
'Cause we're friends! 'Cause we're friends!
Friends...?
Have we been friends this whole time?
Oh, we haven't been?
Gosh, we're just teasing.
Right?
Hm?
Wh-What...?
A cat!
Perhaps it is a stray.
Hayama-san?
T-Too cute!
Nothing Good for You is Tasty
What's the matter widdle kitty?
Are you lost?
You're so cute!
Hayama-san looks quite pleased.
She does like cats.
Not just cats.
I like dogs, birds, cows, and horses, I love them all!
It's my dream to buy an island and build Hayama Park!
How grand!
Unexpected from her, huh?
Hmph, is that how you see me?
Do you keep pets at home?
Yeah, a cat named "Bel-chan."
A cat!
My family named him, though.
He's called "Beelzebub" or "Bel-chan" for short.
Beelze—
Beelzebub! A prince of demons.
Also known as "Lord of the Flies" who takes the form of fly!
Demon
A-A demon!
He was swarming with flies when we took him in.
So we named him "Bel."
Hey, you have a minute, Hayama?
Oh, yes?
If you don't mind, can you hand
these out before the next class?
Okay.
Can you also collect the homework notebooks during break?
Man, that's a lot of worksheets!
How could I?
To think that such a good student as Hayama-san is a demon!
That's okay.
Being class representative seems difficult.
I didn't really want to be class representative, but they insisted.
Oh, why didn't you refuse if you dislike it?
Well, I don't like having to do random
duties, but it'll look good on my resume.
What?
Class Rankings
Shucks, I tried really hard this time, too.
10th                           Nishiyama Serina
You're amazing, Nishiyama!
You're tenth in our grade!
And what about Hayama-san?
Ah, don't say it!
4th                                                     Hayama Teru
I don't want to hear it.
Yeah, you're right!
Grades aren't everything!
This is higher than your rank in middle school!
It's a huge improvement already!
Hayama is so annoying.
She's always getting in my way.
I wanted to be class representative, too.
I know, right?
It's too bad.
They randomly chose her just because
she looks like a class representative!
It wasn't random, it was part of her plan.
Ha?!
...ya.
...ma...
An acquaintance of yours?
Hayama-chan had a "talk" with her before.
She called me out for being "full of myself."
It was so scary!
What's going on?
Did something happen?
She's crying...
You won't get away with this!
Do people actually say that in real life?
Oh, that was so scary.
Hayama-chan...
Perhaps she is a demon.
Quadratic Equation
May 9th
So, what if you apply this formula to this problem?
Todoroki, come up and try the first problem.
Okay.
Hey, get those legs moving!
Ugh, they're timing us for this?
Why—
Huh?
Hayama-chan!
She's beating me!
Or not. I'm about to lap her.
C'mon!
Run like you mean it, or it's another lap for you!
Don't say anything.
I can't talk back to a teacher!
Don't say it!
I'm tired!
I'm gonna die...
You okay?
How can I be?
She was trying to run us to death!
So even the great Hayama-san has a weakness, huh?
Nishiyama-san...
What was that for?
Don't mind her, Futaba.
The poor thing, she looks down on people over such small things.
We should be nice to her.
Who are you calling "poor thing"?!
Yeah!
And you are not small.
You have a great figure!
What are you talking about?
W-Well, I do make sure to do
exercises and have balanced meals!
Beanpole
Beanpole.
I win!
Nishiyama...
That's tough.
You have to be careful of what you
eat or your weight fluctuates.
You're still young, too.
That's totally wrong!
Why are you always making a fool of me?!
What? You're so mean.
That's not true.
Hayama-san...
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Oh, I still feel nauseous.
You really dislike running, don't you?
Not running specifically, but I don't have stamina.
Ahhh, I'm running on empty...
Hayama-san?
You're definitely not running on empty!
Please take care of us.
Oh my, have they been abandoned?
Wh-What should we do?
T-To think such young kittens have been abandoned...
It's terrible!
What in the world were they thinking?
Hayama-san actually has a gentle spirit.
Please take care of us.
"Please take care of us"?
I'll show you who can take care of you!
Whoever abandoned you, show yourself!
That's the voice of a demon!
I found homes for two kittens, but there's one left...
I-It would be a struggle, but I can house it!
First, I will find a property that allows pets.
That's the first step?!
I wonder if there are any cat-lovers around.
Oh, cats?
Kondo-san?
Nishiyama used to have a cat.
A cat?
I did have one, but it died three years ago.
Your family had that cat since before you were born, right?
You really loved it, huh?
Hey, stop saying unnecessary things!
Nishiyama-san!
There is worth in the existence of someone like you!
So there wasn't any before?!
I'm home.
I actually took it.
Well, there was no other choice.
Nobody else could take it.
I don't like the fact that it was from Hayama, though.
Ow...
You need a name.
One that will give you a long life.
Yeah! We're not done yet!
What?!
Remember how I wanted to
make nicknames for all of us?
Did you?
That's right.
A nickname!
We need nicknames to become true friends!
We don't have to...
Hayama-san, Futaba-san!
Please, give me a splendid nickname.
Well, er...
Youkoppy!
Princess Haircut.
Not approved!
What? You don't like it?
No, no, they are unacceptable!
Something more lovely, noble,
and intellectual would serve better!
Er...
Former Rich Girl!
Princess Haircut.
As I was saying...!
Please address Youko-sama as "Youko-sama."
Oh, it's just you, Yamaji?
You appeared without a sound, so I
thought you were someone suspicious.
Oh, you jest.
If you please, address Youko-sama as "Youko-sama."
Wha—
Understood!
Got it!
Youko-sama!
Youko-sama.
This was not what I imagined my nickname to be...
Okay, so Youko-sama is "Youko-sama."
Next is...
Wait, what's Hayama-chan's name?
I'm Odagiri Futaba.
Youko-sama is Nishikawa Youko.
And Hayama-chan is...
Isn't this nice?
It's so fun to eat outdoors.
No, no, no!
Hey, hey, tell us your name!
Come on, what's your name?
Hey...
Youko-sama, what's your next class?
Oh, it's—
Sheesh, why won't you tell us?
What's your name?
Teru-chan!
Teru...
...chan?
Teru-chan?!
Teru.
That's my name.
Teru! Teru-san! Teru-chan!
Don't keep saying it!
Nothing wrong with it, it's cute. Right?
Yes, it is quite a lovely name.
Oh, and Terurin...?
No way!
Teru-chan, I don't have chopsticks in my lunch.
You can just get disposable ones at the school store.
Ah, that's right!
I knew I could ask you!
You're so smart.
I didn't think of that.
Excuse me, are you a friend of Hayama-san's?
Oh, I'm not her friend.
I'm her older sister.
What?!
Her sister?!
She is Hayama-san's...
A demon and an angel!
Oy, oy!
It's past April Fools!
I know...
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kou, Teru-chan's older sister.
Pleased to meet you.
Are you Youko-chan?
Yes!
I knew it!
Wait here for a little.
Wait?
Here, take one.
I made them from scratch.
Oh no...
Why, thank you.
No fair!
Go ahead.
Yay!
Oh...
I'll try it!
Futaba-san?!
It's full of nutrients!
Homemade natto candy!
Natto?!
Youko-chan, I heard that you only eat bread crusts.
Teru-chan is all black on the inside, but don't worry
about that and get along with her, okay?
Wh-What?
Don't get the wrong idea.
She's can be airheaded, so she'll say and
do interesting things without meaning harm.
Airhead?
Oh, gosh.
Lunch will end if you don't hurry.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm going to try out new ingredients next time!
Yeah, yeah. That's nice.
It's still early, Bel.
It's the weekend, so let me sleep in a little.
B-Big Sis!
Good morning, Teru-chan.
Wh-What is it?
I'm going to make breakfast juice for you.
Juice?
Special garlic banana milk!
I'm still sleepy...
Aw.
Then, I'll give some special
garlic banana milk to Bel instead.
I'm up!
I told her not to put garlic in.
Teru-chan, you'll come grocery shopping with me today, right?
Huh?
Right?
Maekawa Fruits Vegetables
It's been a while since we've gone out together.
Yeah.
So, what do we need to get?
Let's see.
Books and—
Books?
I'm going to buy a cookbook.
And a photo album.
Photo album?
Oh, Hayama-chan!
Oh!
It's Futaba-chan!
What are you two up two? Shopping?
Yup, it's been a very long time since I've gone out with Teru-chan.
You two sure do get along!
I'm an only child, so I'm jealous.
Only when she's not trying to poison me.
Are you shopping, too?
Yup, to get some giblets.
Wow, that sounds good!
What?
I'll buy some giblets, too!
Oh, Big Sis, wait!
Daimaru
Super
Meat     Fish        Vegetables
Giblets, Chinese yam, okra, and mulukhiyah,
all mixed together to make a candy!
Spring Sale!
Chinese yam
Okra
Mulukhiyah
Cookbook
Photo album
Why are you obsessed with health foods?
And then making candy out of them?
They're easier to eat in candy form.
Today's
Special Sale!
Today's flash sale is Mayonnaise!
500 grams for 98 yen!
Limit one bottle per person!
Sale?
Today's
Special Sale!
Don't miss your chance!
I-I have succeeded!
Mayonnaise
In getting the special-sale mayonnaise
that is limited to one per person!
Youko-sama...
I see.
So, you and your sister are out grocery shopping?
Raffle Ticket
However, are you sure I can take all these raffle tickets?
Of course.
We got a lot.
Win every time!
Fifth place prize is pocket tissue!
Fourth place is a coffee set!
You're too excited.
Third place is new crop rice!
You, too?!
Central Shopping Arcade
Arcade Rafe
Fifth place prize of pocket tissue...
Fourth place, coffee set!
V!
Koshihikari
Rice
Third place, the great new crop rice!
An unselfish win?
I can't believe Hayama-chan won when I didn't!
Congratulations!
Third place, New Crop Rice
Second Place, Halogen Heater
First Place, One Night Hot Springs Vacation
Teru-chan, help me!
Wh-What?!
She has pretty good luck with these.
That's not just "pretty good"!
She also got the bathhouse tickets from before.
She did?!
I can't carry all this!
I'm glad Youko-chan and Futaba-chan took the heavy things for us.
I'll give the hot springs vacation to Mom and Dad and—
What?
I forgot to go to the bookstore!
Even if you buy a cookbook, you'll
put other ingredients in anyway.
And... a photo album.
A photo album?
There were lots of photos in the closet.
Photos from when we were little.
Big Sis!
That's dangerous!
Don't worry!
I'm a good climber.
A little more...
Almost there!
I'll give the pretty butterfly to Teru-chan.
Ouch! I fell.
Ah, Teru-chan!
You used to get sick and get hurt a lot.
I'm pretty healthy now.
Don't take it for granted.
Make sure you get all your nutrients regularly.
Is she always nagging about nutrients...
Okay!
I'm going to try my best at cooking!
...because she's worried about me?
Thanks.
She says it's a thank you for yesterday.
They're rice balls!
With liver, white roe, and bitter melon!
Mixed?!
But, where's all the stuff you bought yesterday?
Th-This is not a matter of if it's healthy or not.
But Hayama-san's sister went out of her way to make them for us.
It's food that she made for... us!
Woah!
She's eating it!
Youko-sama is actually a brave hero!
Please, do not allow Youko-sama to consume strange foods!
Youko-sama, you don't have to!
Yeah, even if this is your rare chance to eat liver!
Don't encourage her!
Nothing good for you is tasty.
Oh, now that you mention it...
Don't encourage her!
Miss Youko!
Hello, my name is Sonobe Shino.
I'm the Nishikawa Family's former maid.
The black-hearted class representative, the poor girl on a bread-crust diet,
and the walking black hole.
Their "to each their own color" life is so entertaining.
Wonderful, isn't it?
And now, listen to the "Rock Scissors Parade."
Rock, paper, scissors!
Being rich is not all that wonderful.
But that does not mean my current life is great.
You wouldn't be green after
eating a strange rice ball either.
But, all of us being able to eat the rice
balls that Hayama-san's sister made for us...
...makes us happy.
Your real thoughts are leaking out.
Next:                A Taste of Maid
Youko-sama!