Nayu.
Nayu!
It's already seven o'clock.
Don't blame me if you're late.
Hey, Nayu!
I wore stripes yesterday.
I guess I should wear lace today.
Nayu?
I'm coming in, Nayu.
Keigo-san!
Which one do you think would be better?
Should I wear the light green chequered ones for spring?
But if I want to match my bra, I should be wearing these lace ones.
You were having trouble choosing underwear again?
Well...
a great day starts with great underwear.
Right?
In any case, put on some panties and come downstairs.
"A great day starts with great underwear," huh?
Geez, your granddaughter is taking your teachings to heart, Yoko-san.
This Swelling Chest
Awesome, Keigo-san.
You can crack them with one hand.
This is nothing.
Well then...
I'm... in trouble.
By the way, Nayu,
how's school?
I've made some friends. It's fun.
Really? That's great.
There are a lot of misunderstandings, too.
Hey, what kind of underwear are you wearing today?
My top and bottom are lace, and it feels...
N-Nayu-chan, not so loud.
You can't just bring that up out of the blue!
What? Why not?
It's embarrassing.
No way.
Underwear isn't embarrassing.
F-Forget that.
Have you two decided which club you're going to join?
This board is overflowing with fliers.
Have you decided, Haruka?
Let's see...
The Cooking Club would be good.
My family runs a restaurant, and I could give the food I make to my younger brothers.
Haruka-chan, you're an older sister?
Yes. I have three younger brothers.
Are you going to join the Kendo Club, Yako-chan?
Didn't you say you were scouted by an upperclassman?
Wow!
Yako-chan's family runs a kendo dojo.
They have tons of students, and her parents are both instructors.
Oh, and her mother is also a schoolteacher.
Don't talk about my mom.
Hurry up, or we won't have any time left to change.
Maybe she had a fight with her mother.
Maybe...
A club, huh?
I wonder which one I should join?
Nayu-chan, Nayu-chan!
You shouldn't stare that much!
People will spread more weird rumors about you.
I was just admiring everyone's cute underwear.
Haruka-chan, you've got a new bra!
Good. These aren't squeezing your breasts.
Y-Yeah.
She's touching her breasts again.
Does that mean they're...
Lesbians?!
N-no! This is just...
They feel fantastic.
Hey, what about the back?
Let me see the back.
Wow, this will provide great support for your breasts.
Not there...
Hey, what about your underwear, Yako-chan?
A bra?
This is yours, right?
That's just, uh...
My mum put it in there. I don't have any interest in wearing anything like that.
You're not true to yourself.
This is cute...
but it might be too soon for you to be wearing this.
W-wait, Nayu-chan!
But look, it has cups.
For Yako-chan's size, she'd be better off...
I'll meet you there.
Jinguji-san!
Excuse me.
Where are you going with that?
It's nothing!
I just want Yako-chan to wear the right underwear for her body.
Maybe I didn't phrase it the right way.
You said it just fine. Yako-chan's just overreacting.
Oh, I'm next.
Nayu-chan, give me your glasses.
Oh, right. Thank you.
Ouch...
Are you okay?
I'm glad I told you to hold on to my glasses.
It's almost Yako-chan's turn.
They're adding more platforms!
Our level must be way too easy.
She didn't just take second place at the National Youth Kendo Tournament.
She's great at other sports, too.
She's about to jump.
What's wrong?
She's in a league of her own.
Y-Yako-chan!
What?
Y-Your bra!
You're talking about underwear again?
Yako-chan, your bra!
Just leave me alone!
Your bra is shifting!
What is that?
How lame.
Yako-chan, are you wearing that bra?
I-I'm not wearing a bra!
But the cups are shifting up.
I'm not wearing one!
I guess the cups just didn't fit.
You should head over there and fix it.
I won't...
Yako-chan?
Never ever.
I'll never wear a bra again!
Where is Yako-chan?
She's cleaning the bathroom, but she said she was going home when she's finished.
I wonder if she's angry at me.
Hey Nayu-chan...
How did you feel the first time you wore a bra?
A bra?
I was so happy.
Thinking I would finally be able to wear all the bras I wanted made me excited.
I felt like I had become an adult.
That sounds just like you, Nayu-chan.
Oh, and I finally had something to keep my breasts from itching.
They itch quite a bit as they develop.
That's why I think Yako-chan would benefit from wearing a bra, too.
My breasts suddenly started getting bigger when I was in third grade.
When my mother told me to wear a bra, I was so embarrassed I thought I would die.
What? Why were you embarrassed?
But you have such great breasts.
I guess my mother's words shocked me.
I felt like she had told me my breasts were obscene.
After all, people do stare at them.
I don't think Yako-chan's mad at you.
I think she's just embarrassed.
It seems like she got into an argument with her mother.
That's probably another reason.
So for now, it would best to leave her be.
But...
She said she would never wear a bra again.
I-I think she spoke without thinking.
But I don't want her to hate bras more than she already does.
I wonder if there's anything I can do for her.
Something you can do?
They really made one.
They're trying hard to get more members.
T-That's...
This is it!
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
Sorry, I've never made a bra.
Heaven has forsaken me.
There's only one person that can help us now.
N-Nayu-chan?
What? Making a no-cup bra?
I don't mind teaching you...
but what's with the sudden request?
Thank you, Keigo-san.
I'm more than happy to help your friends.
I don't think Yako-chan doesn't have the slightest desire to wear a bra.
That's why, to save her from that feeling,
I will try my best!
Nayu!
Your alarm's going off!
I made my special Napolitain scrambled eggs!
If you don't hurry, I'll eat them all!
Hey.
"Morning Station" is starting.
Shorty.
Idiot.
She's sound asleep.
It's late. Why don't you finish up tomorrow?
Please, Keigo-san. I want to finish by morning...
for Yako-chan's sake!
It was after five by the time she finally went to sleep.
Nayu? You're going to be late.
Nayu?
Hey Nayu!
W-W-W-What kind of clothes are you sleeping in?
Wake up already!
Class 1-A
Where's Yako-chan?
I guess she isn't here yet.
Nayu-chan.
Why are you so gloomy this morning?
Good morning.
I know!
I made this. Do you think you could take a look?
Is this...?
What? You made this?
Wow, it's so cute!
You're a genius, Nayu-chan!
R-Really? I'm so happy!
Nayu-chan, your fingers...
I-It's actually the first time I've seriously tried making a bra...
and thinking I would give it to someone made me nervous.
You're giving this to someone?
I hope Yako-chan likes it.
You're such a good girl.
H-Haruka-chan?
You're a good girl.
You're such a good girl.
I can't believe this!
They're so open about it.
A love scene.
What are you up to so early?
Yako-chan!
G-Good morning.
Good morning.
The weather's nice today, too.
She's here, Nayu-chan.
It's your chance.
Yako-chan, listen...
S-S-Sorry about yesterday.
And, umm, Here!
It's an apology, I guess.
I hope you'll like it.
Did something happen yesterday?
She really isn't true to herself.
The bra...
Do you need that to wash your hands?
What? I, umm...
Let me tell you, I don't need that.
Wait up!
Sorry!
Watch where you're going!
Does your breasts hurt even when they're just brushed?
H-How did you-
Not really.
Listen, Yako-chan, please accept this.
I don't need it.
Just try it on.
Yako-chan.
About the bra, Nayu-chan made it for you.
Your handkerchief's wet.
D-Don't be ridiculous! You can't force someone to...
Nayu-chan, get out of the way.
What are you doing?
Your underwear is soaked.
Haruka, what's the meaning of this?
When you're hungry, you eat.
When it rains, you carry an umbrella.
When you get this wet, you've got to change your underwear.
Winner, Shiraishi!
Haruka-chan...
She really is the older sister of three little boys.
Sorry for getting you wet too, Nayu-chan.
It's fine.
My underwear didn't get that wet.
Neither did mine.
It'll take some time for Yako-chan's to dry.
You still haven't changed?
Are you still going to say you won't wear a bra?
I-It's not like I don't want to wear one.
I think the bra my mum bought,
and the bra Nayu made for me,
are c-cute.
Wai- Then why didn't you just wear them?
B-Because compared to you two I'm completely flat-chested.
Well...
That's why...
Everyone would wonder why a flat-chested girl is wearing a bra!
People would say I'm trying too hard or I'm overdoing it!
And my mother had to go and buy a bra the day before gym class.
I don't want my bra debut to happen while changing for PE.
Does something seem strange to you?
She doesn't have any breasts.
And look at that bra.
You can't expect me to do that!
Could it be...?
Is that why you've got in an argument with your mother?
S-Sorry it had to be over something so stupid.
But... I still think I'm not ready for a bra.
It became very clear to me during gym class yesterday.
Sorry, Nayu.
You went through the trouble of making it for me, but...
Pardon me.
Ow! N-Nayu?
Yes. You're fine.
You should be wearing a bra.
Your bust top is beginning to swell.
They must be very sensitive to the touch.
Y-Yeah.
That's the proof that your breasts are growing.
See? Try wearing the bra I made for you.
Hurry up. Your clothes are still wet.
C-Cut it out! I'll do it myself!
I'm not one of your younger brothers!
Oh, come on.
Let go of me!
I don't need a stubborn little brother like you.
Come on, put it on.
I'll do it myself!
It's so cute!
How's the size?
Yes. It's fine.
For someone like you with developing breasts,
a no-cup bra stays better in place.
Even if you think your breasts are small, you need some kind of bra to protect them.
Right?
T-Thank you.
It's fine. I had lots of fun making it.
That's right. You made it yourself.
Of course, I had my family help me.
I asked the Crafts Club first, but they said they never made any.
Too bad there isn't an Underwear Club.
What is that?
Nayu?
An Underwear Club, huh?
Wait a minute! We missed the lunch!
I forgot!
Let's go, Nayu-chan!
Hurry!
You should worry about yourself!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm in a hurry...
Nayu!
Well... Umm... I'm really sorry!
Nayu-chan, hurry up!
Sorry!
Hayama.... Nayu?
This is all that's left.
Sorry.
I'm on a diet.
This is another form of training.
Preview
Hey, listen.
In England, they say if you confess while wearing red underwear...
love will blossom.
Is that so?
I'll wear red to all my battles.
Don't miss the next episode of Chu-Bra!!
A Windy Day