When watching "Hayate the Combat Butler",
make sure you keep the room bright
and sit well away from the TV.
Wh-Wh-Whoa!
It's smaller than I expected.
What?! Th-This is?!
This is.
This right here.
Then, how big would it have to be
for you to call it "huge"?!
Or wait... um... is this...
Is this really Sakuya's?!
Her warped sense of humor
really shows, doesn't it?
I see...
You did say the yacht is of
a familiar shape and size, but...
This really is incredible.
Hayate, are you...
How is this a yacht?! No matter how
you look at it, it's the Titanic!
Is that what you're thinking?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Miss Sakuya is waiting for you.
Right. Hayate.
Klaus.
Yes, Miss.
Let's go, Maria. Klaus.
W-Won't you please wait
a moment for me, Miss?!
Do you know, ladies and gentlemen?
That a humongous mansion like this
exists somewhere in Tokyo?
The Miss's name is Nagi Sanzenin. And...
Her butler's name is Hayate Ayasaki.
They are both a bit clueless
and both have a bit of the wrong
idea about each other,
but they share the immensely strong,
loving bond between servant and mistress.
A passionate woman's bright red cruiser!
"Let's go cruiser."
The white bullet, is it not?
Zettai nante shinjinai!
I don't believe in absolutes!
Fukanou nante nai!
No such thing as impossible!
Mirai wa hiraku te no naka ni aru
The future is in the open palm of my hands
Honne o misecha make datoka
Stuff like, showing your true feelings means defeat
Dentaku hajiku jinsei datoka
Or a life tapping away at a calculator
Kokoro o itsuwaru kurai nara
Rather than be false to myself like that
Shichiten-battou baka-shoujiki mo kuuzen-zetsugo!
I'll struggle to be uniquely naive and honest!
Komatta kao o mireba ki-ni-naru shi
If I see a troubled look, I'll be concerned
Jinsei isogu riyuu mo betsuni nai shi
And it's not like I've got a reason to hurry through life
Takara no chizu wa kimi ni azukeyou
I'll entrust you with the treasure map
Juuou-mujin yori-michi datte tsukiau yo!
I'll even keep you company on your free-ranging detours
Rakkii-sugiru tenkai
A development that's way too lucky
Kotae wa mayowanai
I won't hesitate to give my answer
Kantan sa! Subete wa kimi no tame ni
It's easy! It's all for you
Fuuhyou wa ki-ni-shinai
I won't worry about the rumors
Rettou-kan ni doujinai!
I won't let a sense of inferiority get to me!
Kakedasu shunkan wa ima koko ni aru
The moment to start running is right here, right now
The Poseidon Advance Generator Gavas
Say, Hayate.
Yes?
Would you ask me, "Why are we
suddenly going on an ocean voyage?"
What?
Ask her. It's to get the story rolling.
Miss, why are we suddenly
going on an ocean voyage?
What?!
You see, the truth is... well...
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to...
That's because...
She totally wants to answer.
"Hey, Britney, would you
please not get too attached?"
"CRUSHED!"
"No... What a cold thing
for my senpai to say to me!"
"But that cold shoulder..."
"It makes my heart race somehow!"
I see!
The reason I haven't won Hayate over...
The important thing
when it comes to romance...
...is giving the cold shoulder!
So she's gone with that angle...
It's true, when it comes to romance,
rather than being the pursuer...
The one being pursued is the winner!
Even that manga author Honou once said it...
That your own manga can
sometimes teach you things!
In that case...
Just you watch, Hayate!
With my cold shoulder,
I'll make you fall head over heels!
Oh, Miss.
Ah, Hayate, morn...
No, no! What are you doing
getting so excited?!
Don't act like that. I have to
face him with an icier attitude.
A-Ah. Morning.
Um, Miss?
Huh?! Wh-What?!
Oh, no, it's just that your shoelace
is a bit undone, so...
Please excuse me. If you
would let me see your foot...
You should be fine now, Miss.
R-Right.
Do not get flustered! This
is where you deliver a decisive blow!
Right.
Good work. You may go now.
Huh?
I swear, that Hayate. He's a formidable one.
Miss, please don't leave me behind!
I need a place that's more unfamiliar
to Hayate somehow...
Hayate's so cute.
And find a situation where
Hayate will need to rely on me...
Nagi, a phone call for you from Sakuya.
I hardly have time for this right now,
but what does she want?
She is inviting you on
an ocean voyage on her yacht.
That's it!
This is where the flashback ends.
I can't tell Hayate this...
Let's hurry! Saku's waiting!
Um, what about answering that question?
Oh, well.
At any rate, Sakuya's...
Sakuya's "yacht",
as she calls it, put out to sea.
Oh, I really hate these
rich folks. Just hate them.
This is incredible.
All these people seeing us off...
Maybe they're hired extras.
Precisely.
What's that about, Saku?
Why that's 'cause the more
rowdy scene suits me.
This is absurd.
I'll wave to them, too.
Don't.
Hey!
The passengers are extras, too.
The mood's everythin' with these things.
You have a band, too?
Yup.
The people dancin' are extras, too.
How many non-extras are there?
Miss, I've been looking for you.
Saku, do you have a female dancer
capable of dancing forcefully?
I do, but what're ya plottin'?
This ship is incredibly huge.
I almost got lost...
Would you dance with me?
You want to... dance... right?
That's right. I won't let you
turn down a lady's request.
Miss!
What should I do?!
I guess ocean voyages
are demanding, aren't they, Miss?
Why?!
Saku... so on and so forth...
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Activate Trap C-5!
Miss!
What're ya up to?
Make this ship rock!
I don't really get it, but leave it to me!
Miss, where are...
Oh, Miss!
Right!
Left!
And back to the right!
But why the heck do I hafta do this?
"Hayate the... Combat
Butler"... is a good anime!
Miss!
I won't help him! I won't help him!
I won't help him, no matter what!
Miss, this is my first time aboard a yacht,
but I guess it rocks
a lot more than I expected.
As I had anticipated,
he's totally keyed up being
aboard a yacht for the first time.
But this is according to plan!
And now...
Ah! That felt good!
What else might there be, Miss?
This is it!
Miss...
Don't ask me about every little thing!
How about it?!
Did that do it? Did that get
through? Did that get to you?
Did it hit you hard right in the chest?!
P-Please pardon me.
Y-You idiot!
D-Don't look like some abandoned puppy!
A-At any rate, I'm going to
have some tea over there!
I-If you want to look around
the ship, do it on your own!
Oh, Miss!
What is the matter, Hayate?
Um, did I do something
to offend the Miss again?
Who knows? I wouldn't know about that...
Yesterday, it seems
she was drawing her manga,
groaning and agonizing over it as usual...
Perhaps something happened
that was not to her satisfaction.
Something that was not to her satisfaction?
Speaking of which, all Hayate had
for breakfast was fermented soybeans.
But you know, Saku,
this is a pretty well-crafted ship.
Ya think so?
Well, that's nice.
You can give me the cold shoulder
all you want! I'm not falling for you!
What're ya talkin' about?!
I'm not talking about anything.
Sheesh, yer not makin' any sense.
By the way, I heard
that you invited Isumi, too, but...
No doubt she's gotten herself lost.
This ship's huge, after all.
Where am I?
Oh, dear, oh, dear.
Just as she had surmised.
But is this ship all right?
Meanin'?
I mean, with this design
that seems like it's destined to sink...
What're ya, a moron?!
Ya listen to me! The "Ti"
of the "Titanic" stands for...
The "Ti" stands for...?
The "Ti (tai)" in fishin' for shrimp
with red snapper (tai)!
That's the other way around.
This ship is so sinking.
This ship cost more than the Titanic movie!
No way it's gonna sink, unless
it gets taken over by terrorists or...
Was that a gunshot?
Yup, yup.
To all you crew members!
We, the terrorist group,
the Chirp-chirp Corps,
have now taken over this ship!
Therefore, you will quietly do as we say!
So they say. What are you going to do?
There sure are some reckless
adventurous bastards out there.
Uh, you terrorists there.
What is it, you little girl?!
We have no interest in pipsqueaks like you!
So he says. What're ya gonna do?
Don't lay a hand on the crew
or the passengers.
The fewer hostages the better, right?
H-Hey, Nagi, yer not thinkin' of...
What's this, little girl?
Are you volunteering to be a hostage?
Yeah, I think it's her responsibility.
After all, she's the owner of this ship.
Wait, I'm gonna be the hostage?!
Behold this brilliantly sharp wit,
not even letting that small jab go by!
What're ya doin', calmly recommendin' me?!
For funny men like you, who haven't
learned a thing from robot anime...
Why you...
But goodness, this ship truly is huge.
It's so huge, I almost
don't know where I came from.
But I wonder why the Miss
is in such a foul mood.
And I was lost.
And so, Die Hard at sea continued.
We'll hafta play it by ear!
(Deta toko soubu ya!)
Please stop that.
(Yamete.)
I swear. Terrorists these days...
They think they can win
as long as they have guns.
They leave much to be desired.
Their kung fu was not enough.
Wh-What a tough bunch.
And yet, they have
a gentlemanly way about them.
Who in the world are you?
You fools!
You snuck onto this ship
without even knowing who we are?
Now, you listen carefully!
We protect our mistresses.
We are first-rate butlers!
We will do everything in our power
to eliminate anyone
who attempts to harm our mistresses.
Remember that well.
Butlers
Ya can act cool all ya want,
but it won't erase yer blunder
in lettin' this bunch get on board.
Eep!
So, what were these guys after?
Who knows?
Isumi's here, too,
so I'm sure there're a ton of reasons
they could've been after us for...
We attacked your ship because
it looked full of rich people.
To repay my debts!
I don't want my wife and children
to suffer any more hardship!
So you have a wife and children?
Sorry about that.
You're poor?
Y-Yes, I am.
You got some problem with that?!
Nope.
C'mon now, confessing that easily?
Even on Conan, ya don't see that often.
Explaining your own
motives in their entirety...
What are you, a criminal
from a Tuesday Suspense drama?
H-How dare you mock me?!
Since it's come to this, I'll end it all!
Wha?! This is...!
A bomb?!
To put it bluntly...
It's all over!
My debts will disappear
along with this ship!
And a one, two...
You're not scared?
Actually, I'm scared.
Yeah, right?
What'll we do?!
I wonder if the design was bad, after all.
This is no time for that!
Where are Hayate and Isumi?!
Miss Isumi!
Ow, that hurt...
Ow...
Wh-What was that?
Don't tell me... Did we
hit a glacier, after all?
Considering the design of this ship,
I feel like it'd sink easily
if anything happened to it.
You think so, too, huh?
Huh? What?
What?!
What the heck is this?!
Blood?!
There's like a whole lot of it!
No, no, calm down.
This is an anime.
By the next scene,
it'll be like nothing happened...
That's the scenario! The storyboards
should show that, too!
Look, even in the original manga!
Looks like you were wrong.
But that was close...
Bleeding like this, if I'd been thrown
into the cold water...
Generally speaking, the amount of time
a person can withstand cold water
is said to be one hour in 4-5 degree water
and 20-30 minutes is the limit at 0 degrees.
I might die in that.
You poor thing.
That's...
Bobbing along...
Bob, bob, bobbing along, bobbing along...
Oh...
Um...
What?! Isumi?!
Wh-What are you doing here?
That is because...
I shouldn't need to ask.
You got lost, right?
So, are you all right?
I am not all right.
No, right?
Please wait one moment!
I will be right there to save...
Getting in cold water
when my body temperature is down
from loss of blood means...
Mortal danger!
Isumi and Hayate are nowhere to be found?!
Yes, they are the only two we cannot find
and all the butlers are
in a huge panic, if you will!
On top of which, it seems
this ship will sink like that
in less than an hour!
Like that?
Like that.
This is bad.
Even DiCaprio was swallowed
up by the sea in the end...
Don't say such ominous things!
That's not it! I'm sayin' we need
to worry more 'bout the butler-in-debt.
More worried about Hayate?
It may not seem it, but the goddess
of good fortune dotes on Isumi,
so I'm sure she'll be fine, but...
But ya know how he is.
He's possessed by the god of death.
I just hope he doesn't
do anythin' reckless...
Miss!
I'm going to go look for Hayate!
H-Hey!
Um, are you all right, my dear Hayate?
I am all right.
I work out more than DiCaprio, so...
On top of which, this water
was painfully cold at first,
but it's sort of gradually warmed up...
That probably means that your
condition is getting dicey...
DeKaprio
Well, my body's pretty tough,
so it'll work out somehow.
But you are also bleeding a lot
and lured in by that blood...
...you seem to have attracted
some rather large fish...
Surely not...
Hayate!
Take that! Take that!
Take that! Take that! Take that!
What am I seeing here?
A-Are you all right...
No, I can sort of tell
that you're not, but...
H-How are you feeling, Hayate?!
W-Well, let me think.
I'm probably... in a pinch.
A pinch?! Are you in a big pinch, Hayate?!
Wh-What should I do?
I guess this fish is the kind
of fish that eats people.
I want to save my dear Hayate,
but with him in its mouth...
If only I can use this branch somehow to...
Take that! Take that! Take that!
Th-This is an incredibly
desperate situation somehow...
On top of which, I feel like there
were two sharks out there...
If the other one attacks,
then it'll really be...
...over.
What?!
W-Wait for me, Hayate!
I-I'm coming... right away...
...to save you!
You mustn't, Miss! There's one more shark...
You leave me no choice!
My...!
My Miss!
Don't you touch her!
H-Hayate...
M-Miss...
Hayate!
Oh, this is bad.
I used up every last ounce
of my strength doing that,
so I can't even lift a finger now.
Am I... going to die?
I am sorry, Miss.
I wasn't of much use to you...
I am truly sorry.
I am... sorry...
If you're going to apologize for it,
why don't you wake up already.
What?
What?!
I swear. So you've finally come to.
Hayate!
I'm so glad!
Haya...
Where are we?
On board a rescue vessel.
I swear, you were a pain to carry on board.
You saved me?
Not really.
I only saved you because
the Miss asked me to.
Haya...
I swear! To think a Sanzenin butler
would be defeated so easily...
Haya... Haya...
Haya...
P-Pardon me.
But thank you very much for saving me.
Hey, Hayate! Why are you blushing?!
What's with that background?!
I have no need of thanks from you.
They say that the cold shoulder sets
men's hearts aflutter for some reason...
And thus, the Miss...
Y-You can't, okay?!
Anything but that, okay?!
Huh? What are you talking about, Miss?
...found herself with more to worry about.
Next time, they will fight against
the anime production schedule.
Freshly caught, freshly made
shark fin soup in one big gulp!
HOT!
Aisaretai fureraretetai
I want to be loved, to feel that touch
Motomeru bakari no kimochi wa
The sense of continually seeking
Hibi o kumoraseteta
Used to darken my days
Kimi ni deau sono hi made wa
Until the day I met you
Namae yonde sora ni hibiku-youni
Call my name so it echoes to the skies
Mayoi-michi mo kitto futari nara
Even lost, with the two of us, surely...
Tsunaida te to te hanasanai
I won't let go of your hand
Mamoritainda
I want to protect you
Saa ikou bokura wa
Come on, let's go, we'll...
Ima o mitsumete aruki-hajimeru
...look at the present and start walking
Nagi and...
...Hayate and...
The Katsura Sisters'
Lettering by Shizuka Ito
...the Katsura sisters'...
Butler Report
...Butler Report!
I'm Nagi Sanzenin,
little sister to 100 million people.
I am Hayate Ayasaki.
I am Hinagiku Katsura.
I'm Yukiji Katsura, pervy terrorist,
a message sent from a supernova,
and a national pretty girl.
But with four of us side-by-side,
this place sure gets crowded.
Well, but if we leave
Miss Katsura unchecked,
terrible things may happen like
they did the last two times, so...
Your remarks towards me
are as scathing as ever, Hayate.
Sis, you're a teacher, so you
should act more like one...
Oh, it's time.
Bye-bye!
Preview
What do you think? The completed version of "Magical Destroy"!
The next episode of
"Hayate the Combat Butler" is...
Um, it doesn't seem
that different from before...
What?!
After I took it upon myself
to make revisions targeting the masses,
are you saying it's still
beyond your comprehension?!
Then I'll explain it to you in the most
eminently understandable way!
Next time, "The Mystery of the
120 Employment Rate (Temp.)".
Wait, what in the world is this place?!
It is where the creators of this anime...
The Mystery of the
120 Employment Rate (Temp.)
Tekset to "Hayate the Combat
Butler" anime next time!