SORA NO WOTO
Fansubbed by Nekomimi
The radiance of this sky will carry to your heart
The melody you dreamed of is like serenity
For your hands the dream is still far away, but
remember the voice so gentle
when someone sang the chord of happiness
The sound of the skies echoes high over all sadness
Everything reflected in your eyes is the real world
Not even the shedding of of tears can stop you here
We're playing tomorrow in the light that rains without end
Prepare to advance.
Forward!
Advancing.
Enemy locked-on.
Ready the main cannon!
Distance, 800.
Load HE round!
R-Roger!
Loading complete!
Steady!
Fire!
Kaboom!
Direct hit!
Good, signal the trailing forces!
One enemy unit destroyed, follow our lead.
Roger!
One enemy unit destroyed, huh?
Well done.
It's not over yet.
Filicia, it's Claus.
Oh, my...
Let's break for tea, then.
Good job, all of you.
MOUNTAIN CLIMBING
THE END OF THE WORLD
Shuko's recovered completely, hasn't she?
Her wound's healed, but she's used to this place now.
This place is lovely after all.
Hey you!
She's so energetic in this heat...
Yeah, really.
It's from headquarters, sign it please.
Okay.
And the private letters.
Kana-chan.
Yes! Here! I'm here!
This is for you.
Thank you very much!
There.
It's from Mommy!
Noel-chan, you have a letter from Professor-san as usual.
Professor-san?
Yeah.
First name Pro, last name Fessorsan.
A common name in Sept.
Ah, so it's Mr. Fessorsan-san.
It's amazing to have a friend from so far away.
Sorry...
It's a joke.
Ah! Jeez, Noel-chan! You got me there.
Bring Claus a souvenir.
Roger!
Rio.
It's the usual.
Throw it away.
Jeez.
So, what's the order from headquarters?
Excuse me...
What is it, Kureha?
Major Claus-dono, for you!
This year's product, eh?
Yes sir!
U-Um, th-thanks for the hard w-work!
Don't worry. It's my job.
Major.
Please look at this.
Roger that. I'll cover while you're away.
Away?
Have a safe trip, Private.
Ah, yes sir.
Everyone, we're having a field trip tomorrow.
Yay!
A field trip!
Isn't it great, Noel-chan? I can't wait!
Filicia, what do you mean "field trip"?
I wonder what should I bring!
I said "field trip", but just walking is boring, so let's make a game out of it.
It's a field trip, after all!
Game?
At the southern end of Seize-or in other words-at the border of No Man's Land,
there are observation devices from the past era. You know that.
Checks are scheduled for three of these devices.
I want all of you to inspect them during your trip.
Isn't that-
It's obviously a mission!
It's a field trip, I tell you.
Even if they broke, we couldn't do anything anyway.
Noctur-type observation devices are a perfect black box.
Disassembly is impossible.
Like I said, field trip.
So this is what he meant by, "have a safe trip".
You won't be walking normally.
And that's why you'll be...
carrying those!
You're such a weakling.
Listen, for these you need to put the weight forward...
That's amazing!
I can't move...
Clutz.
Look who's talking!
You're all such good girls trying to meet our expectations.
Listen up! When dealing with a heavy backpack, first you need to lean back.
And then...
After putting all the weight on your back...
That looks horrible...
Just do it... already!
Yes ma'am!
Alright then, Filicia and I will be waiting for you at the goal marked on the map.
If you can't move another inch, blow your trumpet.
I'll come looking for you.
Understood?
Also, there are wild animals on this mountain.
Should you encounter one, use your judgment. Firing your gun is permitted.
Got it?
Well then, have fun!
Right face!
Right! Face!
Forward, march!
March!
Now then...
I'll leave the rest to you, then.
Roger that.
It's heavy...
It's heavy!
It's heavy! Freaking heavy!
Stop that, Kureha-chan.
Just saying that makes it feel heavier.
Noel, how much further?
Come on, Noel!
Hey wait, Kanata!
Found it!
Yahoo!
Incredible!
It's operational. No irregularities.
What, that was easy to find.
Let's keep pushing ahead.
Yeah!
What's wrong?
No, it's just that...
when I think about how this has been sitting here, watching over the town all by itself...
Alright, what's next, Noel?
Let's see...
If we're here...
That mountain.
That mountain?
Someone do something about this backpack!
It's heavy.
I knew it, Captain and Rio-senpai hate me after all.
I'm sure they do. That's why they did this.
It's heavy.
Hey, say something, Kanata!
It's not like you to stay quiet.
Come on!
You talk too much!
What the hell?!
I can hear it.
What?
I can hear it!
Ah, wait! Kanata!
What happened to her?
Malfunction?
Okay then...
Whoa, this is wonderful!
It's so cool and beautiful.
We're taking a break!
I don't care what you say, we're taking a break!
So that's it!
I'm first!
That's not fair!
This is so good!
Now you've done it!
Take this!
There!
Since we're wet...
Noel, you-!
Take this! Here!
It's a fish!
Look, look! Kureha-chan!
This is great! This is so fun!
Yeah!
Wait, no!
You're lacking awareness.
Well, it's a field trip after all. We gotta have fun!
Didn't you forget those stupid, heavy backpacks?
This is supposed to be training.
But, Filicia-san said...
You should've realized by now.
That woman is the darkness! She's the queen of darkness!
But she's blond and her skin is so white, she's lovely.
That's not what I meant...
You don't get it, Kureha.
What do you mean?
That's Filicia's good point.
Right?
No, it's not! I swear, you two are seeing something else entirely!
Jeez! Someone do something about this airhead duo!
Now, let's have lunch.
We're soaking wet.
In this weather, we'll dry in no time.
What's this?!
The food is missing.
It might have been a wild boar.
They often appear in my hometown and damage the farmlands.
But food is plentiful in summer, so they usually don't come out into the open.
There's a larger problem.
What?
The compass is gone.
What?!
Do you think it's okay to leave our backpacks behind?
We should focus on completing the objective, now that it's come to this.
Are we heading the right way?
The first device is here. The river is here.
We are on a mountain with the second device at its summit.
So, for now we just need to climb.
Okay, no matter what...
Of course we'd be hungry.
Is there anything we could eat?
Over there!
Bayberries!
Are they edible?
Yeah, they're sweet and a bit sour, but delicious.
That was like a musical chord.
But we couldn't possibly climb that. It's too dangerous.
You think so?
We must stay on course.
They say Major Claus survived for three days without food or water,
crossing the harsh desert in a tank to destroy the enemy fortress.
This is easy in comparison!
Really?
You've never heard the story?
He's so awesome, they call him "the desert wolf".
Really? That Claus-san?
That's why we should do our best.
Bayberries...
Stop whining.
Found the second one!
A wild boar?!
Where is that last one?
It's getting pretty dark, huh?
It's because we need to check our bearings often.
You sure this is the right way?
Probably.
What do you mean "probably"?!
Without the compass, I can't be 100% sure.
So, what?
Are you saying we came this far for nothing?
I didn't say that.
On top of that, you should've held onto that compass at all times if it was that important.
Hey.
Don't start fighting here all of a sudden.
It happened because we stopped at the river.
Yeah!
You seriously lack awareness.
"field trip", my butt!
You're always spacing out and absent minded.
That's why we got ourselves in this situation.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
There it is!
Yahoo!
Hey wait, Kanata!
Oh jeez. Looks like they'll manage.
Goal!
We did it! We did it, Kureha-chan!
Okay. I got it, so get off me!
I can't breathe.
Look.
No Man's Land.
This is the end of the world inhabited by men.
Good work.
I'm sorry, Captain.
We failed to accomplish the mission.
What mission?
What? But...
Didn't I say it was a field trip?
But that's....
I just wanted all of you to see these.
These are signatures of your seniors.
All the girls from the fortress have been here at least once.
And they have all seen this scenery at the end of the world.
This is history, isn't it?
I suppose.
Can you walk for a bit more?
There's one more thing your seniors left behind.
You're late!
Rio-senpai?
What happened to you?
Here!
Bayberries!
I'm alive again.
So, did you win?
Don't ask.
But...
...I guess it's all worth the trouble.
Resonate the feelings of love and friendship
Let's perform the important things
I cried when I was happy
I laughed when I was hurt
But, they're all proof that I'm alive
Let's walk slowly
Everybody singing
Tell me what you truly want
You're just my friend
Even if love and friendship change over time
I know, You know little happy
I want them to echo forever
Can you hear my precious note?
Speaking endless words touched by love
This is our harmony
I can hear our harmony
KANATA'S DAY OFF - HAIRDRESSING
Next episode: Kanata's Day Off - Hairdressing
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.
This story is a work of fiction.
It has absolutely no relation to any
real persons, organizations, or events.