[note hato sabure, lit translated to pigeon shortbread, is a really yummy cookie in the shape of a pigeon :D]
Well then,
what should we do?
Let's have some fun then...
What's going on, Yuuji?
There seems to be some kind of event.
Event?
Fumizuki Academy is hosting a treasure hunting and orienteering competition?!
Yoshii Akihisa has discovered some treasure.
It's a rare occasion to be able to eat this much.
I will enjoy this meal!
As expected of Fumizuki's bread crumbs...
This tastes just like bread!
If only I had some jam...
Then I would have nothing to complain about!
He's not in a state to be complaining.
Crumbs get digested really fast...
Phi the Fox,
Kisaragi Grand Park's mascot.
It's also very popular among kids.
Isn't this the Kisara—
I've already explained it in narration.
Maybe the kid who dropped it will come back and get it,
so I guess I'll put it back to its original spot.
Not here... Not here...
Morning, Hazuki-chan.
What are you doing?
Good morning, stupid onii-chan.
I'm trying to find something I dropped.
Something you dropped?
My Phi-chan strap fell off.
It's a limited edition that they don't sell anymore.
Oh really?
That thing is right—
Crap... What should we do?!
Phi-chan!
What's wrong, Yoshii-kun?
F-Fukuhara-sensei!
What perfect timing!
Please give me permission to summon.
What's the reason?
It's an emergency. Just hurry!
I guess I'll do it.
Just know that this is an exception.
Awesome! Summoned Being, summon!
All right! Go get that strap!
Save Phi-chan!
Are you okay, onii-chan?
Stupid onii-chan!
Ow... The feedback effect...
Seriously, what kind of stupid thing were you doing?
Good morning, Principal.
That scared the hell out of me.
Don't use the Summoned Being to cause trouble!
I wasn't trying to cause trouble;
I was only trying to pick that...
In other words, you shouldn't become obsessed with toys.
You didn't have to put it that way!
Summoning permission canceled.
You can't use Summoned Beings for violence.
Violence?!
I was just doing that for Hazuki-chan—
Summoned Beings are not toys for idiots.
If you don't acknowledge my advice, then why not prove to me that you're not an idiot?
If you do, perhaps you can obtain what you truly want.
I'm sorry, Hazuki-chan.
No, it's fine.
Hazuki-chan...
Was this what the Principal was talking about?
The prizes are written here.
A one-year-free-meals ticket?
Ticket for new games?
It does seem pretty luxurious.
There are also secret prizes.
Phi, Noin, and Ain's limited edition strap set?
This... This... This... This... This...
What about it, Akihisa?
You're interested in that stuff?
Who cares?
How can I get this?
This is our campus map.
We're going to search for treasures using this?
I'm pretty good at finding treasures in RPGs.
And then there are the test questions!
The test answers are the coordinates of the check points.
The target located there is the exchange ticket for the prizes.
Doesn't that mean... There's no prize if we don't pass the test?!
And it's a first-come-first-serve basis.
If we come in contact with another team, we can use a Summoned Being Battle to settle it.
This is disadvantageous in every situation.
Oh right! If we have Himeji-san...
Everyone, get back to your seat.
I will now announce the teams of the orienteering competition.
My team is... Yuuji and Hideyoshi?
Himeji-san, Minami, and Ninja Pervert are on the same team?
All the problem children are together.
I can't fathom what you guys might do.
Why is it like this?! Isn't this unfair?
Hideyoshi is cute, so he's okay.
But Yuuji is utterly useless!
I return those same words back to you.
It's over when school ends.
This is still part of class. Go do it seriously!
Sign: Serious
So, it's three questions in a set?
The first answer is the X value,
the second answer is the Y value,
and the third answer is the Z value.
In other words, the floor the ticket is located at.
Oh, it's all multiple choice.
If that's the case, then it'll be easy.
Are you good at multiple choice?
You don't know what I'm good at?
All right then. I'll show you.
I'm an idiot for even having hope for a moment.
This is for mathematics! The Striker Sigma V!
For modern Japanese, I'll use the Problem Breaker!
For history, I'll use the Shining Answer!
The accuracy percentage is super high!
Is your life controlled by a dice?
Don't underestimate me!
Observe!
Do I have to?
Spin! Striker Sigma V!
Let's do this!
Okay!
I got it!
X value is 652.
Y value is 237.
The Z value is 5.
The target is right there!
So it's just floating blatantly in the air...
You go get it then.
That's weird.
Was there a mistake in the question?
More like the answers were wrong!
We found it!
Awesome! The ticket for exchanging prizes.
We got it all right on the first try.
It seems like we hit the X and Y value correctly.
See! Striker Sigma V is amazing, right?
I think you're more amazing to believe that the thing works.
A one-year dessert ticket.
Let's split it among the three of us.
I don't want it.
Are you on a diet?
Instead, can I have this if we find it?
Is this the Kisaragi Grand Park's premium entrance ticket?
Oh, I get it. You're going to go with your boyfriend!
No, with my husband.
I suddenly got the chills...
You certainly don't have it easy...
I can't do anything aside from math!
You're pretty amazing, Tsuchiya.
These are just Health and Physical Education. I skipped the rest.
Okay. I finished.
Awesome! Let's go find them.
T-This location is...
Sign: Girls' Changing Room
Legally going into the girls' changing room...
Okay, let's find some prizes.
It's the girls' changing room,
yet there are no girls changing!
Of course, Sherlock.
We need to tidy things up.
This is what happens to places where guys can't see.
This place is worthless unless people are changing.
What's wrong, Tsuchiya? You okay?
I'm fine. This is nothing...
Tsuchiya-kun!
It's only to this level... I can't lose.
Tsuchiya!
Amen...
Okay. Show me.
The tenacity of those idiots.
Crush it, Problem Breaker!
The map says it's right around here.
In our classroom?
What's this?
Definitely not a prize.
How weird...
Would it be better if we sharpened it?
Sharpen it until there's nothing left.
Um... Did you guys find that?
Is this yours?
Yes... In that basket...
Um... Yoshii-kun...
What's up, Himeji-san?
Do you like sweets, Yoshii-kun?
I do. I love them.
That's great. I woke up early today to make some chiffon cake!
You even know how to make cakes!
Wait a second!
Not bad... Problem Breaker.
Isn't this a treasure?
You were such a great guy.
I won't ever forget you.
Don't talk as if I'm about to die!
If you guys don't mind, let's eat it together!
Eh . . .
Okay, please enjoy.
If there are four people, one person won't be able to have any.
Three slices of chiffon cake... and four people.
That means only one person will be able to live.
The is the first annual Competition of the Strongest!
The rock-paper-scissor competition of death!
If I lose, I die!
Mizuki and Tsuchiya sure are slow.
I wonder what they're doing?
Impossible! I can't solve these questions alone!
No, onee-sama!
Miharu?
Right here!
I solved the question.
What the hell are you doing?!
Look, onee-sama.
I worked so hard to answer these questions.
I matched the answers with the map,
and I found out that the prize is in onee-sama's bra!
All right then... Hand over your body to Miharu like a good girl...
How is that possible?
Let me go!
No way. That's what the map said.
The Ministry of Education said so. There's no way it's wrong.
You're mistaken!
Then let's make the mistake together! Together!
No!
Seriously, I don't have the time to waste on this.
I was hoping to be able to take more classes.
The location on this map indicates...
This is Yoshii-kun's shoe box!
If I were seen by someone at this time...
wouldn't I be mistaken for putting a love letter in Yoshii-kun's shoe box?
No, no. I'm just here to get the exchange ticket.
Wait a sec.
Won't it seem like I'm trying to steal someone else's love letter to Yoshii-kun?
No, no. I'm just here to get the treasure inside.
No matter what, I have a proper reason.
But to some people, perhaps Yoshii-kun's shoe box is a treasure chest!
If that's the case, no reason will matter!
I...
What should I do?
Do whatever you want.
Illuminate, Shining Answer!
We got one! As expected of Hideyoshi.
I think I had nothing to do with it.
Okay then, what's the prize...
Failed?
So it's not here then...
Damn it. They tricked us!
How can chance fool anyone?
So the angle of elevation of this will have to be...
I don't think that can increase its accuracy.
Now then,
how's that?
What? You answered them?
You sure, Yuuji?
I don't want to go to some weird place because the answers are wrong.
You don't have any right to say that!
Yuuji's answers indicate...
that it's here.
It really is here!
How did you solve it, Yuuji?
I chose the set that even I could solve.
I'm amazed that you could solve this.
Your test scores were the lowest of the class though...
Did you cheat?!
Is this really so hard to believe?
Anyway, what's the prize?
Couples Only - Kisaragi Grand Park Premium Entrance Ticket.
If you're lovers, you can also participate in the special event: the "Wedding Experience."
This seems interesting.
Yuuji, why not go with Kirishima-san...
Don't say such horrifying words!
That won't be an experience, but the real thing!
Don't make me imagine such scary things!
You guys go!
Really?
Hideyoshi, are you free this Sunday?
It says for couples only!
What? Does that mean you hate me?
I'm a boy...
I was rejected... How unfortunate am I?
This is the only way I have left to wipe away this misfortune.
Hideyoshi, I like you!
What the hell are you saying all of a sudden?
There's an important meaning within those words.
Hideyoshi, you might not have known this,
but in Japan, there's a myth that if you confess your love beneath the legendary tree, you'll be able to obtain happiness!
That's not a myth.
If we're talking about a legendary tree in this school,
it has to be the legendary beauty, Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
TL Note: This is a play on words with Hideyoshi's last name. It can also mean "ki no shita" (木の下), which means "beneath the tree."
Meaning that I'll be blessed if I confess my love under Kinoshita.
Sign: Wh-What?!
What, Yoshii?
If it's true, then we can all confess to Kinoshita without fear!
This is so wrong that I don't even know where to start.
I like you, Kinoshita Hideyoshi.
Are you guys serious?!
In the end, we didn't get any good prizes.
It's such a sad event for stupid people.
Looks like there aren't many prizes left.
What the heck are the secret prizes?
Phi's strap is still out there.
You want to continue, Akihisa?
All of the next questions are very hard,
unless you mean you're going to randomly try and find it.
Randomly...
That's it. If you take all the answers on the sheet...
What are you trying to do?
I'm going to fill all the coordinates.
All of them?
There might be a prize on the intersection of the X and Y coordinates.
What about the levels?
Of course, we'll just have to check them all!
That's a hell lot of places.
If we're going to look all over the place, it'll take...
Randomly searching is fundamental in games.
You're pushing it.
I see... That's interesting.
We can't answer the questions anyway.
Idiots have idiotic ways of doing things.
Let's show them what we're made of!
Yuuji...
I'll go to the fourth floor.
Akihisa, go to the third.
Hideyoshi, take the second floor.
Okay.
Got it.
The Janitor's closet
Nothing.
Currently Occupied.
What about lockers?
Nothing.
A dog?
Over here!
Trash can!
Nothing.
None.
No—
The girls' bathrooms!
Nothing.
There's someone here.
The fish tanks!
Nothing.
Ow!
One more time!
Nothing.
Let me off...
Another time!
Someone's in here.
This is great. Nobody's here.
Wait!
Damn it. We got nothing.
There's nowhere else...
No, there's still this place.
But there's no place to hide anything here.
No way...
The strap still hasn't been found, so it must be somewhere!
I found it!
Just like I planned.
Hideyoshi, even if I can't solve the problems, I can still...
Oh? I came here by solving the questions myself.
You are...
Sister!
Why are you here?
According to the rules, we can take the ticket by using Summoned Being Battle.
D-Don't tell me...
Permission granted.
Summon!
This isn't looking good, Akihisa.
Our battle strengths are too far apart.
I didn't think we would encounter them.
What should we do?
We won't go easy on you.
You realized your fate yet?
The it's time to say bye-bye now.
What?
Time's up.
That means...
That's right.
Yup.
Hurray!
Amazing. This is the Phi's strap, and it's a set of three.
Isn't that great?
I wonder if Hazuki-chan will be happy?
What're those?
Could these be the secret items?
What're they used for? There's also an instruction manual.
Iron Bracelet. The activation code is "Awaken."
Even if you say that...
What would happen?
Let's try it.
Awaken!
This is...
It can't be...
Summon!
Amazing!
We can summon without a teacher's permission.
Although the area is rather limited, this is pretty cool.
Why are only my clothes torn?
Akihisa, is yours all right?
Yeah it is.
So that means only idiots can use it, huh?
What do you mean? Aren't you also an idiot?
Then that means you're a super idiot.
What?!
The ultimate idiot then?
What did you say?
Then a supreme idiot.
Supreme? What do you mean by supreme?!
I see. It still needs to be tweaked.
However, idiots are like scissors; you have to know how to use them.
Everything has its uses.
The sixth question. Name the styles used in individual medleys in swimming.
Anime song medleys, Nostalgic melody medley, and Pigeon shortbread!
I also like pigeon shortbread.
Next week:  Me, Pool, A Paradise of Swimsuits, and...
This will be on the test.