It's just as I thought.
What is?
Hirono-kun is a person who will treat me well.
What's with that?
Now I... I only want to be around people who treasure me.
If that's not what it is,
then it's better off to be alone.
Miyako...
I don't want to disappear from someone's heart anymore.
If that happens, it's better not to meet in the first place.
Can I stay here?
Yeah.
Whatever happens, will you only look at me?
I no longer want to lose things precious to me.
What is this?
Kei...
So it's like this?
Onii-chan's...
Kei!
Don't go.
Miyako.
Please, don't go.
But...
Me or her, who are you going to choose?
You won't go, right, Hirono-kun?
Look at me only and no one else other than me.
Miyako...
Please...
Wait for a bit, I'll be right back.
In the end, you're going.
Kei-chan.
Leave me alone!
Don't you want to film it?
You want to film it, right?
Film it!
It's good if you film it.
There won't be another chance when something like this happens.
Film it!
Kei-chan...
Kei...
It's me.
Sorry, but I'm searching right now...
For Kei-chan?
Can you meet up with me for a bit?
What is it all of a sudden?!
What are you thinking, Hirono?!
Thinking?
You, going out with Miyamura...
What does that have to do with it?
Then what's with Kei-chan?
What are you talking about?
Me and Kei are nothing like th-
What the hell!
You're half-assed.
Your studying is half-assed.
Your working is half-assed.
Don't mess with people by being like that!
Stop saying senseless things!
You think you can beat me with your left hand?
The right is for work.
Even your fighting is half-assed.
What?
You're running away from everything like that.
I have never run away!
Without any thought, you get close and drag it out.
It's just the same as running away!
Your old man... Didn't you run away instead of trying to persuade him?
How can you even understand about my family?
Which side is Kei-chan?
Family, or a woman to you?
Neither, Kei is Kei!
That's why I said don't be half-assed!
It's because you're not sure is the reason that Kei-chan is crying!
Because of your indecisive attitude and running away,
that girl is suffering.
If this keeps up, that girl...
will only keep crying, and follow you like a stray.
Only you, Hirono, can rescue that girl's feelings.
I'm back.
Miyako?
Miyako...
Hirono-kun?
Miyako.
I was thinking...
About what?
Let's stop seeing each other.
What are you saying, Miyako?!
For me now...
it hurts to think about Hirono-kun.
I know that I'm saying whatever I want.
And sometimes it's not always the right thing.
But...
Hirono-kun's heart isn't mine and mine alone.
Miyako...
Someday, when Hirono-kun's heart fills with other things, then I...
will disappear again, right?
So...
Let's break up before that happens.
Wait, Miyako!
Miyako!
Miyako?
Hiro-senpai.
Hayama.
What are you doing here?
It's nothing.
How was the sandwich that Kei-senpai made?
She called suddenly last night and asked how to make it.
I'm so jealous!
Oww oww oww~
Just what is it?
Since she suddenly started cooking...
I asked why because I thought it was strange.
Then, without hesitation,
"For Onii-chan,"
was what she said!
Plus, she was blushing.
So I had no choice. For Kei-senpai's happiness,
I taught her how to make it with tears in my eyes.
Really?
Well, there was something that I received in return.
What's that?
A postcard for the monthly MIMI.
This month's issue's reader prizes are very luxurious.
What are you doing?!
Hayama.
Are you a Shindou Nagi fan?
Yes, since the name is similar to Kei-senpai.
That's it?
The interesting work is another author?
Because Shindou Nagi is boring nowadays.
It's as if his enthusiasm has disappeared.
Before it was more upbeat.
It's been too plain recently.
Shindou Nagi's uniqueness disappeared.
Still, Hirono-senpai doesn't really know, right?
Y-Yeah.
All half-assed.
I already know, or something like that.
Just knowing something, and understanding something are different.
I know that too.
Because everything is important,
you don't want to lose everything, right?
Yeah, something like that.
But still, someday you need to give up one side...
in order not to lose the most important thing.
I said that everything is important.
But if you don't decide,
you will lose everything.
Even if you say that,
I can't treat something like it never happened and throw it away!
You're not throwing it away.
You're being asked to throw it away.
That's why it hurts.
I don't like getting hurt anymore.
But as long as you are alive,
you can't run away from pain.
I know that.
I know those things, but...
To untie the bonds of a relationship once made...
the same amount of pain will come with it.
Can all of you withstand it?
Even if we can't withstand it...
we can't run away from it.
Right?
The truth is, the answer was already decided from the beginning.
Even if I had the answer...
I didn't have the courage to understand the meaning of it.
For some reason, I...
feel like I found the color that I was looking for.
Kei, are you there?
Why are you here?
You forgot your crutch.
Go away.
Since your leg is broken, you shouldn't overdo it.
That's not your concern.
Kei... thanks for the sandwiches.
I ran into Hayama and heard...
Also, I heard that my manga was boring.
Kei, I'm thinking of leaving school and devoting my time to working on manga.
Up until now, it was wrong just to work with partial effort.
After all, I'm not good enough to do anything if I don't do it with my full effort.
Does this have anything to do with Miyamura-senpai?
No, it was something I thought about myself.
Have you already made your decision?
Yes, I have.
Is that so? That's just how you are, Onii-chan.
In everything, you decided for yourself what to do and would go at it alone.
Kei...
In order to follow your dreams, no matter how difficult it was, you stood by it.
It was only after you saw it.
Eh?
Before you started calling me Onii-chan, in order to make you happy, I started drawing manga.
Onii-chan...
It was fun back then, wasn't it?
Do you remember... when we got into a fight right after you read my manga?
Yeah.
What was that about again?
Things really took a sudden turn. That was a shock, wasn't it?
Me, you and Chihiro argued back and forth over what was good or bad.
Onii-chan, in the end, you looked at it from the perspective of a rejected girl.
Well, I didn't listen to you as to the problems with that, huh?
It's because I didn't think you did enough for a good ending.
Now that I think about it, we never finished it.
Although, even without thinking about it, we were really serious about the ending.
That ending was like reality.
I guess you're right.
It wasn't a standard happy ending. To cut it short like that makes it more realistic.
Someday, the end just visits suddenly.
Like myself who was a fool looking at a dream, everything just crumbled down suddenly.
Kei...
Don't say it!
Don't let it end...
Kei...
I've always, always thought that things would stay the same.
Onii-chan is here. I am here.
We support each other even when I'm being unreasonable.
But I did my best to support you, and when I was down, you supported me.
Though we sometimes fought, we always made up.
And then, we'd go from being like brother and sister to being lovers.
Then we'd get married...
And have kids.
I've always...
I've always gone on believing this.
Kei...
Onii-chan, what about you? Please tell me the truth.
I also thought about it along the same lines.
Somehow or another I did.
Really...
In that case, I just realized it a bit too late then.
It would have been better if I had confessed my feelings sooner.
I'm sorry, Kei...
Onii-chan! I love you!
I love you! I've always loved you, Onii-chan!
Ever since I was little, I've always...
I've always yearned for you.
You were my pride.
I've always... always wanted to say, "I love you!"
I want to go back...
To when I was always with Onii-chan.
The time when I called you Onii-chan.
We can go back there.
Let's go back, Kei!
We might not be related, but you are my little sister.
You are very important to me.
That's why...!
I guess...
you were in pain as well, Onii-chan.
I see...
Kei...
I'll be fine.
It might take a while, but I'll be fine.
I guess this is the end for here too.
Are you running away again?
In any case, it's just like it was before.
If it's something you don't want to face, you can just close your eyes.
If it's something you don't want to hear, you can just cover your ears.
That's what I've always done, and that's how I live.
You won't obtain anything that way.
It's all right. From the beginning, I didn't have much hope anyway.
But, he is doing his best.
I can't be strong in Hirono-kun's eyes.
That's too bad. I wanted to see it.
Eh?
My dream of seeing someone like me possibly finding happiness...
A dream?
Miyako?
Yes.
Where are you now?
I can't tell you.
Can we meet up and talk?
No way. It will make my resolve weak.
Resolve?
You see, I'm going to leave this town.
I'm going to go somewhere where no one will find me.
Miyako...
This call will be the last.
This is my last goodbye to Hirono-kun who has always been kind to me.
Miyako...
You see, I think up until now I've been testing you.
Testing me?
Ever since we met that Christmas night.
At that time, I wanted to see what your reaction would be.
I wondered if Hirono-kun would take care of me or not.
That's not something worth just to test.
If it wasn't the case, then I wouldn't want to be involved with anyone else.
Well, how did I do?
Eh?
Did I fail based on my test results?
No, you passed with flying colors.
Hirono-kun is someone that is too good for me.
Don't say it that way.
I have a good eye for judging people.
In that case, why do you want to leave town?
I didn't want to be erased from Hirono-kun's heart.
I'll disappear first while you still love me.
Miyako...
You see, at home there was no sound.
Sound?
My parents were very distant, you know.
My mom and dad couldn't get along.
They never talked.
It seemed that there wasn't ever the sound of talking or even footsteps heard inside.
They only thought about the things they disliked about each other, paying no attention to their daughter.
And my name...
Name?
They wouldn't even say my name at all.
No matter how good my grades were or if I was first in sports, they wouldn't say anything to me.
I even worked hard to learn Mom and Dad's favorite fish recipe.
Anything to get any affection from them.
However...
Miyako...
It's weird, isn't it?
There was no reason to pretend, but I also lived while hiding my breath.
In the end, six years ago they divorced.
To be honest, I was relieved.
I suddenly felt liberated.
I left home and thought I'd go wherever I wanted.
I thought that I would one day, somewhere, find the place where I belonged.
Though I was by myself, I felt relieved.
I didn't need to prevent myself from being tired or hated.
I chose to go some place whenever I wanted, wherever I wanted.
I was a person that could go anywhere.
But... But you know...
Being able to go anywhere means that there is no place to belong.
Not having a place to go or go back to, it was... like being alone in the world.
Shut up!
Eh?
Don't talk like that by yourself!
Hirono-kun...?
Why didn't you say so in the first place?
You've been lonely, right?
You've been in pain, right?
Then you should've said that to me.
There's no way I could say that!
If I did, then Hirono-kun would pity me.
What I want isn't pity, but rather for someone to treasure me.
Then, I will be the place where you can be!
Therefore, all that stuff about you being alone will be of the past. Isn't that good enough?!
Even if there is a place for me, I'm scared of it disappearing!
That won't happen!
How can you say it like that?!
Believe in me.
I want to believe... I want to...!
What are you so worried about?
I'm horrible, that's why. Someday you'll just push me away.
That won't happen!
I knew about the feelings that you and Kei-chan had for each other.
I thought that I couldn't win against Kei-chan.
But I wanted to be with you so much; I desperately clung to you, Hirono-kun.
And therefore, I also knew about the pain you felt inside.
I'm horrible. I could only think about myself!
I will think about my own situation.
That should be enough for you! That is who you are!
I will answer for my own situation.
After that, it is up to you!
Is it really all right to believe in you?
Of course!
I don't want to disappear anymore.
I'm right here. I no longer want to be ignored!
I'll always be watching you. There's no way that you'll disappear!
I want to stay! I want you to eat my cooking while it's warm.
I want to be involved with you.
For me, being dumped by someone...
When you get good grades, I'll say that it's great.
If you do wrong, I'll tell you.
And of course I'll eat your cooking.
No matter how pathetic it is, I want to be by your side.
You can do things the way you want.
I'll accept everything.
Hirono-kun, I...
Miyako, listen to me!
I... About you...
I...
I love you!
Hirono-kun!
I didn't know places like this...
I looked around all the phone booths in Otowa.
Hirono-kun!
Miyako!
You have a responsibility now.
Responsibility?
You caught me, so don't ever let go.
Didn't you not like being bound with someone this way?
A person's feelings can change.
I'm starting to return to the memories that have not yet faded.
Next ef - a tale of memories:
Ever forever.
Do you have memories you don't want to forget?